I'll see you at hell.
Folks!
It's will see with hell!
Patrick Rawls and Jotaro, so here to talk about the movies, Pat, how are you today?
I'm doing well, Joe.
It's been too long and we're going to talk about Mad Max beyond Thunderdome in a tribute
to the great late Queen of Rock and Roll, Miss Tina Turner.
I've been, uh, her song from this movie was, we don't need another hero.
That was one of the -
What do you mean another hero?
There you go, you're one.
Yeah.
I've been working diligently on a weird -out -style parody.
Called, I could eat another hero.
I love it, yeah.
Ham and cheese is what I need, bro.
So so lucky and for a judo.
Oh, yeah.
You should sing that at your store or put it on a pair of like tights, get up on the bar.
I should hire weird out to do it for the store.
What do you think they cost me about $750 ,000?
Yeah, and it's certainly timely.
Uh, you know how weird out likes to parody songs from 40 years ago.
Well, that song is great.
I always love we don't need another hero.
The song that kicks off the movie is like, it seems like it's 18 minutes long.
And it's like, um, oh, Max, walking through that desert.
It's like, I mean, it's ridiculous.
It's a terrible song.
I, I, my, we'll get to this, but I, I'll say it now because it's relevant, but
my favorite thing about Mad Max being on ThunderDome is to watch that opening
and imagine the most die -hard Mad Max fan sitting in the theater and the movie opens like that
and just going, oh, no, what is that?
What's about to happen here?
It is such a curveball from the way the other two movies open.
It's like, what is going on?
I like to imagine that song playing to Max pumping iron shirtless.
Like he's getting ready for the movie to that song,
using it to wind himself up.
A lot of conflicting viewpoints on whether or not we needed a hero in the music of the 80s.
Because we got, we don't need another hero.
Then I think two years later, in Short Circuit 2,
the song was holding out for a hero, implying they do need a hero.
I'm holding up a hero to the end of the night.
Wait, that's Short Circuit 2.
Well, 90 % sure.
Let me look at that.
Where does Let's hear it for the boys come in?
Let's hear it for the boy.
My dad loves that song for a hero.
Often erroneously referred to as I need a hero.
It was in the film Footloose.
That's right.
That's what I was going to do.
What's the song for Short Circuit 2?
All right, I got to look this up.
Sorry, Jeff.
Robot, city or something like that?
No, it's I need a hero.
Short Circuit 2.
They used it again.
It just wasn't written for Short Circuit 2.
Okay.
It's got to be used ironically in short.
It's supposed to be funny.
Like the robot saves the day and it's playing that.
If you don't consider if you don't consider Johnny five a hero,
which I certainly do.
My father loved the songs.
Let's hear it for the boy and like a virgin.
I couldn't tell you why.
He bought the 12 inches of both.
Wow.
Yeah, it's weird.
Like a virgin.
That's a real weird choice for a dad.
Loved it.
I mean, maybe he just thought the daughter was hot.
I don't know.
But were you old enough to press him on it or say like,
hey, dad, you know what the song's about or?
No, I was young enough that I was like,
oh, that song on the radio.
My dad likes.
I don't like it, but he likes it.
Now that I'm older, I like it.
Actually, no, I don't.
I don't like that song.
I think that song kind of sucks.
It's corny.
Do you like like a surgeon by weirdo?
Dad, I felt like was the true.
Well, actually, that's the joke in the movie is that he wrote that first.
That's that's such a funny joke in that movie.
I finally made it through med school.
Somehow I made it through.
I'm just an intern.
I still make a mistake go to.
I know every word I loved.
Weirdo.
Yep, I had his video collection.
I watched it every morning.
Do you remember how hard we left?
Getting why I still watch that?
Yeah, what was the?
State of shock, the guy doing state of shock at his dance.
Yeah, I think we talked about it on here,
but yeah, it's a record company executive,
just like singing the entirety of the Jackson song,
state of shock.
Do do do you got to check it out?
It's really influenced my comedy.
I must say I send voice notes to friends all the time doing the same thing.
He's just fat enough.
He's just sweaty enough.
Like it's perfect casting.
Yeah.
All right, well, let's do with your life, Pat.
Well, Joseph, I am 12 days sober.
Good for you.
Alcohol and Mary Joanna.
And I do a month, a year of sobriety, generally, a little reset.
And I'm thinking maybe I had just not done it in a while,
but the first two, three days of this,
I fell into such a vicious depression
that I realized why I have not been able to do it in a while.
You know, like an extended period of time.
I can take days off and stuff,
but I was just like, well, I really must have needed this break
because I felt awful.
My brain crashed.
Like I was having awful thoughts.
I didn't want to leave the house.
Then and everybody
hates to admit this, but I'm almost two weeks in
and I feel like I'm walking on sunshine
to pull out another 80s song.
Feel amazing.
All of my spiraling thoughts are gone.
The very dark clouds that have been following me
for years have lifted.
And although I'm knocking on wood,
I am intending to just see how long it goes.
I got the app to track my daily sobriety.
I might be doing it.
I don't know about permanent,
but trying to get a good long time in
because I feel like I really needed this.
And I also feel like
it was the weed more than the alcohol.
I felt like I've been doing all this work in therapy,
but I was wondering why it wasn't really working for me.
And then I realized it was like under class.
Like because all the work I had done came rushing
to the forefront and made me feel amazing.
But I hadn't been feeling it because I was numbing myself.
This is going to turn into a sobriety podcast.
But I do feel amazing.
And I hope to continue with it.
And also, it's like you get into that thing where you're like,
you wake up, you feel like shit.
And it's like, oh, I got to have an edible or whatever,
because that's what makes me feel good.
But it was actually exacerbating my anxiety, paranoia, anger, depression.
Yeah.
I open up.
Real life opener.
I, well, you know, my stance on weed.
It's the daily intake is insane to me.
It's not insane to me to do it.
It's insane to me that people do it and think it doesn't have some kind of effect.
But yeah.
Well, they told you it didn't for years.
They're wrong.
Yeah.
They're lying.
And then without alcohol or something.
I, every, I'm at a point in my life, every single drug has been phased out of my life,
except for alcohol.
Yeah.
And even with alcohol now, I just did a week out
at a beach house and with friends.
And I, I couldn't, like on the fourth day,
my buddy was like, come on, let's go to the bar.
And I was like, I don't want to like, yeah, I can't, like, I'm waking up with anxiety.
I can't do this anymore.
Like, I'm not saying I can't drink anymore.
I'm just saying like, I can't do this like day after day.
Yeah.
Like party like, and you feel way better when you do back away.
I know that for a fact, you look better, you feel better, you sleep better.
You know, my problem has always been the same.
I'm like, I want to take a break and then I start thinking about like
the big fourth of July picnic I go to.
And I'm like, what am I going to not play beer pong this year?
That's so fun.
Like, there's always the stupid thing that like,
and then I'm like, but why can't I just do that?
And then not do it again.
If you two days later, I was talking to our buddy,
the criminals about this.
It's like each time you beat one of those situations,
you feel like mad Max.
You feel like you're indestructible.
And then you build up a few of those.
And you're like, oh, this is the easiest thing in the world to do.
I you know, you're going to feel good.
I went to the Hollywood Bowl the other night.
So I flew to Chris and Janet Jackson.
Big show sold out, everybody's dancing.
And I was like, I'm going to be sitting there miserable.
And I had more fun than I've had in ages.
You know, like, just as you numb the shit inside of you,
you also numb fun in a way.
It's really weird.
But yeah, it's been great.
It's been great.
And I'll get to stars born in the movie corner,
but I rewatched that movie and it had more of an impact than I would like to admit.
He does pee his pants at the Grammys.
Maybe I saw that in my future and didn't like it.
Yeah, I did.
I did this thing skank fest every year that my friends pretty much.
And it's always very fun.
I did skank fest Vegas last year, sober.
I thought I was almost canceled.
I was like, this is impossible.
I can't go to the sober.
And I did.
And I had the time of my life.
And I was, yeah, why am I afraid of sobriety?
And then all those encounters, all those encounters,
you remember them.
You remember how funny they are.
They become memories to you.
And then the next day, you're not like, oh, shit, I talked to 200 people.
Browned out.
I hope I didn't say something stupid.
All that's gone.
You just wake up like, man, I feel great.
Maybe I'll grab a little breakfast.
Yeah, wake it up.
It's really good.
I mean, Vegas, yeah, they're talking down the strip, stepping on heroin needles.
So I'm certainly due for a break.
I might do it this summer.
I don't know.
I'm thinking about road tripping for my birthday.
I've got basically, I go on the road this coming weekend
with the impractical jokers.
I'm opening for them for three shows.
And then I'm home.
And then I don't do the road again.
My only responsibility all summer will be recording my two podcasts.
And I'm like, I can, the world's my oyster.
I can do whatever I want.
And top of my list is I need to work on myself.
Because I keep, I keep sliding into this dark.
I get into this place where I'm literally, I'm like,
Tim Robinson in that sketch where he's in the suit going.
Yeah, I don't think I want to be around anymore.
I get there as well.
You know, and you start, I wouldn't, that's your norm.
You start to feel like that's, that's just what it is, but that's not it.
Yeah.
And I want to stress, I wouldn't do, I wouldn't harm myself.
And I don't think, and if anybody's, you know, that's a very serious thing.
I'm not making light of that.
But, you know, just this concept of, you do start to think of,
well, what if I evaporated?
Would anybody do this?
You know, like more along those lines.
And, yeah, so anyway,
I had lunch with a buddy of mine yesterday.
He was like, he was really going through it and talking.
He's got kids and he was like, you know, I, I wind up, my wife goes about
early and then I wind up spending the last four hours
the night, like doubting myself as the husband and father
and just going into this bad place and, and I got a shake it somehow.
And I told him, my, I'm not, I'm not never going to be the type of guy who's like,
you know, if you tried sobriety.
But I was like, are you like drinking?
Because that, I found out that that was really fucking me up anxiety was.
And, and we, and he goes, yeah, because I started a bad habit during the pandemic
that I've yet to break.
So we're talking about three years.
So of this, he's like, I always do a bottle of wine kind of in front of the wife
and then I got my downstairs wine.
So then I'll have the second bottle of wine.
So I'm like, between the hours of eight and midnight,
you're doing two bottles of wine every night.
And he's like, yeah, to hear you say it, it sounds, sounds pretty bad.
So I'm like, give it a shot, man, you know,
it's, we're getting to that age where it's like the old,
as as Bradley Cooper says, and a star is born,
maybe it's time to let the old ways die.
You know, you know, John?
Yes.
We often need the cinematic representation of John Cougar Melon, can't.
He's better than John.
He'd change our lives.
I just think, yeah, every that movie, every version of it, I think of
John, I guess it's Chris.
I'm really thinking of Chris Christopherson.
Yeah.
And John Cougar is the derivative of Chris Christopherson.
There's the Judy Garland James Mason version, which is great,
but it's three hours long.
The Barbara Streisand Chris Christopherson version, which is ridiculous,
but fun.
And then I honestly think this new one is kind of a masterpiece.
I hate to admit.
Yeah, Eddie Vetter.
I think it was Eddie Vetter said to Bradley Cooper.
Bradley Cooper directed it, right?
Yeah.
I think it was Eddie Vetter.
Yeah, Eddie Vetter was like, what are you doing, man?
You're just going to remake a classic.
That's crazy, man.
And then he did it.
Like Eddie Vetter, for some reason, don't like Eddie Vetter.
I like everything he's done in terms of ticket master and all that.
I just am out of Pearl Jam guy.
I don't think he was being a prick.
I think he was being like, you're nuts.
Like, but like God bless.
Yeah.
And I might be defending Bradley Cooper.
Making that story up.
I don't even know if it's true.
I think it is.
Who knows?
I got wet blood over here.
All right.
I feel hungover for the first time because last night at 3 .30 in the morning,
and I'm still a little shaky.
3 .30 in the morning, my house alarm went off,
which is like the loudest, most horrifying thing
that can happen.
It's happened a few times when I've been awake.
Like somebody will open a door when the alarm's on and it goes off.
It's terrifying.
But to come out of a deep sleep with it.
Man, I was running around the house.
I had a bat in my hand.
So I come upstairs.
All it was was a power failure.
Drunk driver crashed into a telephone pole.
The power went out for like an hour.
And that activated my alarm for some reason.
Or I'm up and I check the alarm.
And it's supposed to tell you what the issue is.
And it said motion detected in the living room.
So that led to a half hour of me just freaking the fuck out.
And then I couldn't go back to sleep.
But not good.
Not good.
It was, it was nothing.
It was fine.
What's new in your world, Joe?
I feel like you've been traveling or something.
We haven't been talking as much.
No, I just, I went away for a week.
I tried to relax.
I had a nice time, but I couldn't relax.
Yeah.
I was worried very much.
The, my partner and myself were out of town.
And with the bar, that's the, the bought my bar partner.
And that's very nerve.
Your partner.
My partner, yeah.
That's very nerve -wracking.
He's still gone until Sunday.
I leave again.
But it's like,
it's a weird thing with the bar.
Like, there's,
whether I'm here or not, it doesn't matter.
Like, it's kind of going to go as it goes.
You know what I mean?
And like, even like going over and like,
just, I'm like, I should probably go check on it today.
It's like, I'm like, check on what?
Like, like we're surfing food, we're surfing drinks.
I know the place is like in a normal state.
You know, I've gone, I've been away from it enough times
and I know the staff knows what to do.
So it's just this weird thing where,
and I'm not saying I don't check on it.
I'm just saying like, but it's just this weird thing
where it's there.
It's an organism of a certain type.
And it's kind of like, I guess having a kid
who's away at college or something.
You're like, right.
You know, you can't, it's past an age
where you sit there and feed it
and loom over it constantly.
It's its own thing and it's functioning
and you just got to hope for the best.
And if there's a big problem, people will let you know.
You know, your staff will let you know.
But that doesn't mean it doesn't stress me out.
And like, it just does.
And I think that's very normal for a business owner
and especially in New York City.
So that made it hard for me to fully relax into the vacation.
But then also too, it was a very like,
let's hang by the pool kind of thing.
It was not a let's go into town.
And yeah, your activities kind of,
that's what a vacation is supposed to be.
I feel like we always add more activities
to a vacation instead of relaxing.
Yeah, this was there was a pool at the house.
Let's hang at the pool.
And and that's fine.
But then also too, that inspires like,
well, let's let's play beer pong or let's play a drinking
game or or whatever.
And and that was not I had fun.
Don't get me wrong.
And I got nice and I never got drunk.
I would just get like in phases of of buzz
than then that would wear off.
And because I was I was sort of having my own
personal anxiety about that where I was like,
if I go away and I tear it up every day,
I am going to fucking come,
I am going to come back home with such a dread.
And I can't do that.
You know, like I just can't do it.
I'm too, I'm too, I'm not too old.
I'm just at a place in my life where I can't do it
at least for right now.
So so that's that's what's been going on man.
And then not to mention too,
not to get too heavy here, but you know,
the the burglary of my apartment,
it's still bringing up a lot in me and
I'm having a hard time getting past it.
And I'm trying to figure out what the next phase of life
looks like.
Like do I know one thing's for certain.
I need to get out of the lower east side of New York.
I'm not I'm aged out of this at this point.
Like I can't do it.
So I got to figure out what that means.
Moving into another neighborhood in New York or whatever it means.
Whatever it means that you're entering your sex in the city phase.
That's what I think.
Honestly, that's just I think you're I think you're getting a brown stone.
You're having, you know,
hunky guys take you home at night.
Walsh, I'm not kidding.
I keep saying the way I keep describing it is.
I think I want to keep living in the in the New York movie.
I'm just done with this movie.
I've been in.
I want to be in New York now.
Yes, exactly.
I've been in the Scorsese movie.
I'm done.
I got to get in the F run.
Yeah, you know,
where's where's the Woody Allen Boat?
I want to do that.
Going to art viewings and having discussion.
You know, whatever it is or sex in the city is another good one.
Well, that requires a lot of money.
You know, that's those people all have one thing in common.
A lot of money.
I don't know.
Lord knows my three years in New York.
I never even could afford living in the city.
I always lived in one of the outer places.
I think at length about moving to a part of Brooklyn.
Where, but, but, you know, there's also the thing too of like,
you just can't, wow, goddammit.
You can't win in this damn city.
You go out there and then, and then I'm like, okay,
well, that'd be great, but then I'm out there.
And you feel like you're alone, you know,
but then if you go, you go, my best time there was in a story.
That, that to me is like, it feels like you're living in a community.
It's a lot of old Greek people, but also a lot of young people coming in.
And it's, I really like the story in terms of living quality.
But that was 15 years ago.
I think there are parts.
I think there are parts of Williamsburg
that still aren't, that, that we can get just enough away from the nonsense.
Right.
Oh, god.
But see, then my head just goes right back to booze.
I'm just like, oh, Williamsburg, that's a fun bar strip out there.
Like, goddammit.
Anyway, I don't know.
I, it's just time for time to get going.
Time to backbone, time to move on.
I'll figure it out.
But look at him. He's that time to get going on that he died.
So yeah, that's, yeah, he's not a bad idea.
You ever thought about burning the bar down and collecting the insurance money?
Not on the podcast, Pat.
All right.
Fine.
I don't think of that.
But sometimes I do dream that like maybe lightning hits it.
Sure, sure.
It's, it's a, I will tell you it's a wonderful thing.
My friend Dylan Postal, who is the, who also known as horn swag, swaggle of the WWE,
who played leprechaun in leprechaun origins.
Okay.
He's become a friend of mine.
He went to my bar yesterday with his kid and he didn't, we didn't, I didn't see him,
unfortunately, because I was tied up.
But you know, he sent me this really nice text and he was like, dude,
you got a hell of a place there.
It was awesome.
Like, and you get a, and that's, that you go, this is awesome having this.
Like, that's really sweet when people, when you can tell a person genuinely liked it and
they're not just saying like, hey, I want to say something nice because you know,
you're a friend and you open to thing.
You know, so, so, you know, and it's, it's all going in the right direction.
So, I knew, I knew you must have been busy this week, Joe, when I sent you news about
a leprechaun's sequel in the works and there was no response at all.
I didn't quite know what to respond to because I don't, they give you such little information.
I'm excited about it.
I've always felt like that's a franchise that deserves better and never quite got it.
The idea of an evil leprechaun is really scary and fun.
They, I agree, sort of brush up against it in the first one.
And then there's all the sequels and two reboots at this point.
And now a third reboot is coming.
It's not going to be a sequel.
It'll be a full reboot, they said.
But they, you know, they're not saying, how many other franchise have you seen?
They own all of them.
But how many have you seen?
All of them.
Wow.
I've only seen leprechaun one with you on the show and I figure if that's the best one,
that this is a terrible franchise and nothing's worth watching.
You're in trouble after that first one.
I liked Returns, which was the one they made that was like the direct sequel to the first one
that brought back Francis from Peewee's Big Adventure.
And Origins was a good attempt.
But I liked what they were trying to do.
They just got so far away from it having anything to do with leprechaun
that it was, and I didn't like that it was like this faceless monster.
So I think this new one, I have a feeling they're going to be, you know,
look, they're going to end up saying what they always say, which is,
we're going to make it scary again.
And then they comes out.
It's like a slap that comes out.
It's never won.
Yeah, so how's leprechaun in the hood?
That seems like it might be a questionable,
you know, like, is it racist?
How is it?
It's not great.
Yeah, it's, you know, it's called leprechaun in the hood.
I know.
That's the one I would watch if I had to watch one.
Is there a space one?
Or did I imagine that?
There's in space and then there's leprechaun.
Back to the hood.
Okay, okay.
All right.
It's not a great franchise.
When I met Ricky Jervais, I met Ricky Jervais on the OP and Anthony show,
and we laughed quite a bit and had a really good time.
And after the show, I said, I have to ask you one question.
Because I didn't ask him anything about his work or anything the whole time.
I didn't want to be a fanboy, but I have to ask you a question about life
short, the work David showed you that.
And he goes, yeah, I go, why did you never make fun of leprechaun once?
I was like, it's insane.
That franchise is nuts.
Like, you trashed so much shit that he did.
And he was like, ah, mate, I don't know.
And he was like, I bet we shot it and it just didn't make it in.
But like, I go, well, if you're not familiar with that franchise,
you need to sit out and watch it, man.
Like, he's like, okay, cheers.
And that was that.
But I was so confused that they never brought it up.
Yeah, you know, I wish that show would have,
I would have liked a second season of life is too short.
I really like Warwick Davis playing the like Ricky Jervais style asshole.
Like, it's funny.
It's funny. He's good.
Was that on HBO?
And it was the last thing Merchant and Jervais did together.
Okay, okay.
Yeah, maybe they pulled the plug on a second season.
It's like, they seem like they had some friction.
So maybe they were like, we can't do this anymore.
I just watched an interview with them on the Alan Car Show.
Yeah.
And it's, it's right around that time.
It's right around the time of that show.
Because Jervais is, is, is thin.
It's like, thin Jervais.
And they come out.
And you can, they don't say anything,
but you can just see that they don't care to be around each other anymore.
They're both killing.
They're both separately saying things.
Most of the times that are shots at one another,
that like, that like applause break laughs.
They're killing.
And neither guy laughs at what the other guy is killing with.
Right.
At all.
And, and Steven Merchant at one point makes a joke about,
they're like, what do you, what do you, Alan Car is like,
what do you think of Ricky's weight, you know, transformation?
And he's like, Steven Merchant's like,
why don't you care for it?
I think he's funnier when he's fat.
And I hitched my wagon to this particular fat horse.
And it's, it's, I mean, people are howling.
Yeah.
Jervais is just like, you know, like looking off at like a boom mic operator or something like.
Yeah, you know, he hates him because usually what makes him laugh,
the hardest is a great joke at his expense.
Like when Jim and he could let Kitsom with, you know, like that's usually what makes him
cackle.
So, you know, he was like, not having it at that point.
Yeah.
It's interesting British comedians, I don't know if it's just that they
hair less or something, but I, you know, American comedians hate each other a lot of the time too.
But British comedians hate each other and talk shit about each other in the press constantly.
Like they all hate Steve Cougan.
They all hate Ricky Jervais.
They all hate James Corden.
And they all hate each other.
But like an interviewer would be like, what do you,
what did you think of the office to Steve Cougan?
Like did you feel like he kind of ripped you off with Alan Partridge?
He's like, oh, I think it's a fat cunt.
You know, like that, that'll, that'll be their answer to things.
Like they don't, they don't give a shit.
I do think the office is more than different enough for Alan Partridge.
But it's completely different.
It's not, it's just you.
England, I love you.
The country has had such little good television that the second
a thing came out that was also funny.
They were like, you stole that from out in bloody portrait.
You're like, it's nothing.
It's literally nothing like it.
Yeah, I mean, then you could say Alan Partridge ripped off faulty tower
was because they both have awkward moments.
The truth is you guys just have brilliant comedy once every 10 years.
And it seems like they rip each other off because they're speaking in British accent.
Yeah, when I was in Ireland and I was talking to a bunch of Brit comedians,
they were like, every one of them was like the American office is better than the English off.
And I was like, what the fuck are you talking about?
Like they were like, it's more seasons.
It's funnier.
I'm like, wow, it's the grass is always greener, man.
Like we, we, I think what it is is we all got at least I did.
I got the office as like a dude.
I saw this thing.
Yeah, I never heard of it.
Like, you know, you know, you got, I got the DVDs on, on a British Amazon,
because it wasn't available on American Amazon.
I had to like order it internationally.
It arrived in this package and I put it in.
It felt like, you know, finding a lost treasure or something.
And the office for us has been on TV 24 hours a day for most of our life.
It's the same thing over there.
The British office was a massive phenomenon there.
So they all got sick of it.
And then I think British people think Americans are cool,
even though they're very wrong.
Just how we think all British people are cool,
because of the accident and they're not either.
So it is grass is always greener.
Yeah.
I'm happy to announce.
And this will lead us to the movie corner.
Yeah, very excited.
We're about two weeks out from Dial of Destiny premiere.
Oh, yeah.
I am going to watch an Oppenheimer.
Yes.
I'm going to watch all of the Indiana Jones movies,
the final week leading up to that.
Sam, seeing that you know, special that we should, we should do, yeah,
we should do the Indiana Jones franchise.
That should be the first day.
Because I got to, I got them all on board.
Okay, I can't wait.
I only got them on Blu -ray,
but because I was, because by the time the four case came out,
I'm like, in a year, there's going to be the five pack.
And I'm just going to get that.
I'm holding out for it.
But anyway,
I'm happy to announce that the score on Rotten Tomatoes is going up.
Now, it's not going up tremendously, but it is going up.
And movie web, our favorite movie website, gave it a glowing,
pretty glowing review that said like,
this is a, this is a great send -off for an iconic character.
Even in its weakest moments,
those are, those are things you can get past.
It's great.
Yeah.
I hope that that's the case.
I'm feeling good about it again.
And, you know,
and speaking to the criticism of effects,
this is why I don't take all that too seriously,
like the de -aging thing.
Oh, the stuff with the de -aging looks bad.
His de -aging looks ridiculous.
My first movie corner entry is
a re -watch of the frighteners.
Peter Jackson
directed, Michael J. Fox starred.
The frighteners is an awesome movie.
It's awesome.
And the effects are painfully dated at this point.
The CGI effects.
And I remember
when the frighteners came out,
it looked pretty goddamn good.
The effects looked pretty good.
Uh, you know,
you were aware that it was CGI.
There was no part of you that thought,
oh, the ghost is literally,
you know, or the ghost is, you know what I mean.
Like, there was no part of you that thought,
oh, that's a practical effect when the ghost image
three -dimensionally comes out of the table or whatever.
Um, you knew it was CGI just like we know this is de -aging.
Uh, did the effects age well?
No, again, no.
But who gives a shit?
You get past it.
You know, when I watch Jason and the Argonauts,
I don't go,
you know, stop with the cremation, Hollywood.
It looks like, you know,
we came up with a new technology that was better.
And now the old technology looks dated.
And that technology in and of itself got better and better and better and better
up through and including the first two Star Wars movies.
And then they start using it and start using a different thing.
And that's what the de -aging thing will do.
And in fact, what they do now is they go into movies after they're released
and improve the effects which Lucas did with the Star Wars prequels.
Um, so I am not phased at all by the criticism of the de -aging effects
I wasn't phased about it at all with the Irishman.
And I got to tell you, the Irishman effects
already looked dated to me.
And I still think it's an awesome movie.
And at the time, I did not think it looked weird.
I thought I was like, oh, wow, this is pretty cool.
That's the nature of the beast.
Uh, and if you haven't seen the frighteners,
which is really the, the, the, the, the, the, what I'm supposed to speak about here
is the film itself.
It's a really fun movie.
It was supposed to be a tale from the crypt entry.
Uh, so mech has produced it.
It wasn't, which is a bummer.
It is such a tale from the crypt store.
It's crazy how much it feels like tells in the crypt.
And, uh, you know, it's, it's a great flick.
It's a really, really great flick.
Pat has gotten up now twice in the same review of the frighteners.
Walked away from his mic twice now.
He's walked away.
And I got to tell you it annoys me.
That annoyed, that second get up annoyed me.
I'm talking about it.
You just got up a second time and it really irritated me.
The second, well, I don't know if they're hearing it,
but you're, it's, it's your Wi -Fi.
It catches.
So I tried to turn off all the Wi -Fi in my home
to improve the audio in case it's on my end.
I was actually trying to help.
It sounds fine on my end.
I haven't gotten any catches.
Okay.
Well, then, maybe it's me, I don't know.
It happens every time we record.
So it must not be an issue.
I think somebody would have said something, right?
With our hits the asshole fans, yeah.
These little bitches.
Anyway, the frighteners definitely worth checking out.
Yes, you're kidding, of course.
The frighteners definitely worth checking out.
It's a, it's very, very fun movie.
And maybe the last big J -Fox release, right?
I believe it was because he said
that he was on location in New Zealand.
I believe shooting that.
And that's when he was watching American television.
And he was going, I'm away from my family.
I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm having a good time shooting this.
But I'm away.
And I'm alone.
And American television has gotten really great.
Like, why don't I do American television again?
Like, and that's when he made a phone call to do Spin City.
Okay.
But then he retired from Spin City was when he retired at the end of that run.
That's a great sitcom.
I want to get more into Spin City.
Never seen an episode.
I was in high school and I just never watched it.
I've watched a little here and there.
But, you know, you got Richard kind.
You got Michael J. Fox.
You got Alan Ruck.
Alan Ruck.
You got the guy that lost.
Is that the guy who plays the mayor?
Yeah.
Yeah, it's, it's, you know, anyway, what do you got?
I, well, let me just kick things off with the stars.
Born.
I don't know what possessed me.
I saw it in theaters and I rated it on letterbox a three and a half.
So I probably reviewed it on this show and said, yeah, it's pretty good.
You know, but I watched it.
I planned on watching it again this week.
I'm annoyed to say that Bradley Cooper is an excellent director.
Everyone raves about the first 45 minutes in particular just because it's put together.
So beautifully, but I really think the whole movie is excellent.
But it's the age -old story of the
pretty big rock star
complete alcoholic pillhead who in a ball are
stumbles upon this woman with an amazing voice played by Lady Gaga
and brings her out on tour to like, he's like, I think you got talent, you know.
And he has her up and she sings a few songs and before long she outshines him.
She becomes a major pop star and he can't handle it.
It's a, it's a mean piece of work like I forgot in the back half.
When he's drinking, he'll call her ugly.
He'll call her like just, I mean,
he's mean. They don't, they don't sugarcoat it at all.
He's a complete asshole destroying his life.
But she loves him and stands by him.
When the movie started just like the first time, I was like, Bradley Cooper is doing an impression
of Sam Elliott. Why is he doing this?
And then Sam Elliott shows up as his brother and goes, you stole my voice.
And that's a big sticking point between them.
He's like, the reason you're successful is because you stole my singing voice.
Sam Elliott in this movie, I think it's the best he's ever been.
And I know you know that I love the Sam Elliott.
You know, outside of maybe Lebowski because it's so iconic.
He is so good in this movie.
I don't know how he did not win the Oscar.
And something that always makes me cry is a man struggling not to cry.
And he's got the best ever struggling not to cry seen.
I've ever seen in this movie.
And it wrecked me.
I spent most of this movie crying probably because I lifted the emotional block that I had
had for some time. But it's an excellent movie about sobriety, about fame, you know, all sorts of
very interesting themes. Bradley Cooper's great, Lady Gaga's great. I love how, like she has an
interesting face with a lot of character which on the big screen does not necessarily translate as
hot. And she doesn't wear makeup for the entire movie.
She looks like a lady who works in a bar. I admire that.
It feels real. The music scenes are great.
I actually like the music quite a bit.
Not enough to listen to it outside of the movie, but I think the music's great.
Including shallow, the big hit.
And you got supporting performances from Dave Chappelle, who is great.
Andrew Dice Clay, who is amazing as Lady Gaga's protective father, who
one guy once told he sings better than Sinatra, and he's held onto that his entire life as like
he should have been as big a star as Sinatra.
And then like I said, Sam Elliott just absolutely destroys.
Above the movie. I hate to say it, but a few more
viewings this could become a favorite of mine. And I urge you to watch it. That's all I'm
going to say. It's not corny like you think. It's actually the opposite. It's not schmaltier at all.
Your audio is a bit wonky. I think it's your fault though. I don't think it's mine. But who knows.
I think we're okay though. All right, to keep moving here, but just, you know, just so you know
that that's what's happening. We'll see whenever you you're never you talk. It's like it'll catch
Sherry once in a while. Yeah, it's not catching on my end. It's just it's just your thing starts to
I don't know. It's weird. Anyway, folks, let us know in the comments or messages if there's
some major audio issues that you're hearing, you know, as far as I can tell, it's just here and there.
But yeah, you know, we're doing all we can. You know, we're on two sides of a
ailing crumbling nation. So, you know, you do what you can. Anyway, yeah.
It reminds me of one of my favorite comedy lines ever from Fred and Willard and
Waiting for Guffman. He goes, we consider ourselves by coastal. If you consider the Mississippi river,
one of the coasts. Kevin is wife. That's a good no bit. I miss Fred Willard every day.
Every day. That's every day. I wake up and I look at my picture of Fred Willard. I hate that he was
tainted at the end by just jacking off an important theater. Same with Pewy. I was jacking off it.
Could there be a less serious crime than jacking off a loan in a porn theater? Leave the
fucking guy alone. Fred Willard's probably like, I don't know how to work the internet. I got to head
up to the Tiki bar and rub one out. I get it. Excuse me. You ever stumbled upon your dad's browsing
history, by the way, because dad's not gonna clear it. No, you never have one. My dad is my dad's a
deacon and staunchly against pornography as far as I know. But he's pro like a virgin.
Well, he was one of the most graphic songs ever been. Well, I don't think my dad was really getting
into the lyrics. It's the name. It's you. Well, like a virgin. What? You agree with Tarantino,
that like a virgin is a song about having sex with a guy with a huge dick.
The disgust at the beginning of reservoir dogs. It's like, oh, I feel like I'm a virgin again
because you're dick so huge. I don't know that it's about a big dick necessarily, but I think his
concept is very accurate. It's about, as he says, a fuck machine. Oh, well, he says because it hurts
her. I don't know. I know I think that that's a very interesting. No, but yeah, what would I do
think it the aspect of that I do think is accurate is I do think it's about a girl that's fucked a
lot and his feeling love through sex for the first time. That's what I think it's about. So anyway,
what was I? Oh, my next two films, the first of which, is the Road Warrior. I went back and
watched some other Mad Max films to prepare for this episode. Yeah. The Road Warrior in my opinion
is without it. Well, okay, from a technical standpoint, I would say is without a doubt the best
Mad Max film. I don't know that it's my favorite, but it is the best. It is the one that's the
most groundbreaking for its time. It is the one that defines the character much more so than the initial
movie does. It's what they model aesthetically every other Mad Max movie after. You know, this is
me. Road Warrior is to Mad Max. What Evil Dead 2 is to Evil Dead. Same basic thing, but every aspect of
it is much better and cooler. Yeah. And it starts with a four minute recap of the first one. So
you never have to watch the first one if you don't want previously on the Road Warrior. Yeah. So
the Road Warrior is a it's got the coolest opening of any Mad Max movie, which is the recap of the
original film with then a crescendoing sound of a like a turbo engine and it like snap zooming in
on Max now in a in the midst of a chase. It's just such an awesome opening. It throws you right in
and immediately establishes what a bad ass he is. And then from there, it's it sets the the
prototypical, you know, precedent for whatever Mad Max movie is. He's this guy who's lost a lot.
He's out in the wasteland and he's met with a challenge of helping some other people that he
doesn't trust initially out of interest in benefiting himself and then ultimately finding his humanity
again through this gesture. It ends as all Mad Max movies do with a very climactic car chase.
The car chase for the most part, you know, again, in this concept of revisiting what once was quite
a spectacular thing on screen. Seems a bit dated and not quite as awe inspiring as it probably once was,
but it's still for its time very well done. There's some really cool deaths in it. There's my favorite
death is when the two guys strap to the hood. They drive them into the back of the truck and there
you see their heads like smash on the truck. And then the there's a great twist ending and I don't
need to ruin it for you. And some really interesting characters in it. The road warrior is the one I
find myself most furiously wanting to revisit more than any others. What? You mean,
fury road? No, the road warrior. The one I've been talking about for the entire time. But you said
that the one I want to revisit, you just watched it. I said the road warrior is the one I find myself
over time wanting to visit more than any of the others. Yeah, and I understand. Yeah, yeah, so
but fury road is, well, you know what? I'll just do fury road now then you can do too. How about that?
Okay, we don't have to play these games. We don't have to do this dance.
Big games. Did you see Tenacious D's Wicked Games video?
The XM or the series XM? No, they did a video of them and they're underwear rolling around in the sand
and it's very fun. Okay, singing Wicked Game. That's funny. I watch this and then I went
right into Thunderdome, which we'll get to. And then after Thunderdome, I went to Fury Road.
The only one I haven't revisited yet is the original. But Fury Road, I was very excited,
because I hadn't seen this since the theater. And I have the Blu -ray collection that contains every
version of the, you know, it's got the documentaries from all the movies. It's got the Black and
Chrome version of Fury Road. It's got the 4K. It's got the original. It's a pretty definitive Blu -ray set.
And I was very excited to re -watch Fury Road. I started by watching the 4K and then about a third
of the way through I switched over to the Black and Chrome, because I just kind of wanted to see what
that was all about. I'm not reviewing the Black and Chrome version, but just as a side note,
I think it's fucking pointless. I think it's really hard to tell what the fuck is going on
when you're looking at it. I had no interest. What good is a sand movie in Black and White?
Yeah, it's like that doesn't make any sense. I thought that there was maybe going to be things that
they like made like a specific color to pop out. Like they kind of like a sincerity or something
and they didn't do that. I was very confused. But anyway, I liked that in Sense City and I also liked
I re -watched Logan in Black and White. They called it Logan Noir or whatever. And that was pretty cool.
That makes sense. Usually it's an experience. Then the mist is cool in Black and White too, actually.
The mist makes usually it's an experiment that doesn't pay off. Yeah.
As for a movie, I saw Fury Road in the theater. I was blown away. I haven't seen it's sand.
I haven't seen it since revisiting it. I got to say it doesn't really hold up.
Like it's in a theater with booming sound and on a towering screen, it's pretty amazing to watch.
But at home, I'm like, okay, they're in the cars again. I was going to jump. That guy's going to jump.
And then you start wondering what does the script of Fury Road look like?
Because he's just like, and then they jump from the one car to the next car.
And then you got it. It'll be easier when you say it, but you get it.
It's got some really cool elements. It's got some really cool moments. But as a fourth Mad Max movie,
here's the thing. After a 30 year wait, however long it was between the 25 year, I don't know,
revisiting Mad Max was a fun thing. But when you watch them back to back,
this just feels like, oh, you just took the concept of the other Mad Max movies and blew it into
like this insane budget with special effects and whatever. And it's just so crazy and big.
And then also it kind of loses some of the charm because you're like, and a lot of it is real.
I mean, like the guy one guy died, I think, making it or whatever. But like the stunts are real, but like,
I don't know, it just wasn't, it just felt like a lot of money on the screen.
And the, I like Furiosa as a character quite a bit. I thought the storyline about the wives was
really cool. The message, though, of men controlling women and how that's unjust, it's a lot
hamier than I remembered it being. Like there's a part where they're in the car. Max is in the car
with the five wives, which by the way, there's a Rodney Dangerfield movie called My Five Wives.
It's not connected at all to this, which I thought was misleading. Rodney got a story by on
Mad Max Fury Road, because they did use a lot of the relationships. And Jackay is in Fury Road.
She gets killed early on. People don't remember this, but Jackay is in Fury Road.
There's a scene where they're like, you know, there's like quick pause. She would have,
she would have been amazing in the Tina Turner part, Jackay. She would have been. She would have been.
It's very, very exciting. Tina has never seen her dramatic work. Yeah.
But there's like a scene in this where they're in a dire situation and Max is like
to one of the wives or concubines, whatever. And he's like, you know, he, he, like, gives her
not an order, but he's like, I need you to do this or whatever. And then one of them goes just
because he's a man, don't, doesn't mean you have to listen to him. I'm like, all right guys.
Joe's in his apartment going, yes, you do. Yes, you do. Got to listen.
So it's a wild flick. It's not a bad movie. It just didn't hold my interest the way it did in the
theater. You know, it's fine. I'm curious to see what Furiosa looks like.
I'm, you know, I think what's her name from the witch? What the fuck's her? Jesus Christ.
The girl from the Taylor joy. Yeah. I think she'll be great in that role as the younger version of
that character. Then it's Tom Hardy still in it? No, it's like a prequel when that girl's a teenager.
So Max would be a teenager. You know, look, I, and I tell her joy was in row. I was in
not Fury Road, isn't it? I think, I think in a flashback or something. Oh, okay, okay. But
you know, my, my, thank you. Just watched it. My biggest, I, I, I, I, I'm fully admitting there were
moments where I kind of zoned out a little bit because it wasn't holding my attention. I watched it.
I didn't not watch it, but I was like, you know, how it goes. I think, I still think this.
George Miller has said that Mad Max to him, which he said this when the last one came out. So
you're like, are you just saying that now because it's not Mel Gibson anymore? But he said like,
I always saw this as a new, a variations of a story and variations of the character.
It was never meant to be like consecutive, you know, like continuing, a continuing story,
which is pretty obvious in Thunderdome for reasons I'll bring up in a moment. But it's also obvious
in Fury, there's an element that's pretty, in Fury Road, the actor that plays the villain in the
first Mad Max plays the villain in Fury Road. He, he does that. He also might have just been saying
that so Tom Hardy could play Mad Max in a way we care. But I have said that from the minute Fury
Road came out, the urgency of the movie and the social commentary of the movie of older men controlling
younger women would have resonated a thousand times greater with Mel Gibson as Mad Max. The urgency
of an older Mad Max in that situation is so cool. And then the idea that the savior of, or not
the savior, but the guy that actually does find this humanity through helping, helping these
imprisoned women is also an older male and not a young, great looking guy, you know, like, but a
guy that is grizzled and like maybe does have an archaic way of thinking or whatever. And you know,
what can you do? That's not what the movie is and whatever. But I don't rule out that George
Miller makes another Mad Max movie at some point with Mel Gibson. I'm not, I wouldn't be surprised. But
I was especially with the patch of gray in Thunderdome. I think he's supposed to be an older version.
And I just think Mel can only stick to the direct to DVD stuff at this point. Although he did
daddy's home, I just think we're in a climate now where he's not going to come back in terms of
being a leading man anymore. I just don't see it. But who knows? I would interview him with him yesterday
where he was talking, he was talking about Hollywood. And it was fascinating. He popped up on TikTok or
something. But he was like the number one rule in Hollywood. You can't get mad. He was like, I've had
people shove a knife into my back so far that my heart comes out the front. And the next time I see
him at a premiere, it's all smiles. And that's Hollywood. And it'll break you and destroy your
soul. And you got to decide if you're ready for that. But people will do the worst things you've
ever seen. And he's like, you just got to say he didn't mean it because you know, at some point,
you're going to stab somebody in the back. And you're going to be glad that they didn't call you out.
It was, it was very dark and nihilistic. And it was done like around the time of lethal weapon. But
he's right. I mean, he was just talking about how disgusting a place it is. Well,
the last thing I'll say about him being in another Mad Max. Don't forget, even when you're
Harrison Ford, you don't get to do it alone. They're like, we're going to add a younger person in here.
You know, we got, we got Dan Acroid top billing back at the movies again. I mean, we never thought
we'd see that. You know, so it's like, they'll make them, I think in what? The new ghost
posters they're making. Like, okay. Like he's leading the charge with Ernie Hudson. So my point is is
yeah, it would be Mad Max. And also these other characters who are younger.
You know, but like, but I don't think it's impossible, especially with, with seeing Indy come back,
seeing, I mean, Christ almighty, we just, we saw a movie where Mark Hamill had a starring role as Luke
Skywalker. I mean, when you think you never see that again, yeah, Mark, Mark Hamill never told his
girlfriend publicly that he hopes she gets raped by a pack of black men. You know, that's the
difference. I know that he got canceled, but I also think that, I mean, look, he's back on award
shows. I don't know, you know, he seems to have been let back in. But anyway,
I would, you know, Elvis Costello, my favorite, I'm driving up to venture to see tonight. And I'm
his, his blackout needs to be drunk 100 % of the time days. He referred to Ray Charles
as a blind n -word in front of some people in the incident got reported in like the 70s. Right.
And they later, Costello sought him out, apologized profusely. He's worked with, you know,
hundreds of important black artists and covered their music and talked about them. And you know,
it's not, he's not canceled. This was in the 70s and everybody kind of moved past it. But
when they interviewed Ray Charles about it, they were like, what did you think when you heard that
Elvis Costello said this? And Ray Charles was like, that's drunk talk. He's like, who amongst us?
I'm not, I'm not, I don't think anything about drunk talk. And I was like, that's very big of you,
Ray Charles. And I, but he's kind of right, you know, you would hope. They always say the truth comes
out when you're drunk, but sometimes you're just stupid. You know, I, I've, I, I certain, although,
you know, I've been drunk a million times, those words don't come out of my mouth, but, you know,
people do stupid shit when their brains fried. So, uh, also without, without justifying anything,
no, you, you, you get drunk, your product of your times. Yeah, you know, certain outlandish things
were probably a little, a slightly less outlandish and, you know, in a certain decade or whatever.
And it's still an asshole thing to do, but not quite as heavy as if you did it right now.
Right. So, you know, who knows? But, um, I never knew that story, but I won't, I'm going to have to,
I guess I got to take a trip to the incinerator with my Elvis Costello records after we finish.
Well, he, he very admirably put it in his biography as like one of the lowest moments of his
life and everything, like, and, and I think no one would have had any idea that it happened if he
didn't drug it back up, but I, he was probably like, if I don't drug it up, somebody else will,
uh, he also, he said in a bar, he said it in a bar to the members of Crossbees Stills and Nash,
because he hated them. It was trying to get a rise out of them, but it's not, he, it was interviewed
and said it, not that it's ever right. I'm just saying, you know, he, he owned it. You gotta,
you gotta forgive people at some point, you know, unless it's a repeated pattern.
Well, yeah, there was a time where you could also admit to a mistake and say, I made a mistake.
I'm sorry. And people would have a thing called humanity. Yeah. And say, we'll consider that.
Anyway, let's not sidetrack. Go ahead. Uh, I am going to do on the solo corn spider man into the
spider verse and the new spider verse because Joe, you still haven't seen that, that one, right?
Couldn't give two shits. I felt the same. And I really hated spider verse the first viewing.
And then I watched it again and I totally get it. It's just too much movie and it's kind of overwhelming,
but I do think it's pretty brilliant. And I loved it. And I'll talk about it more because people have
been requesting that title for a very long time. I do think that's, that franchise is the good one.
And the other ones I might be done with after I see the flash. Although now they trick you into seeing
them multiple times because this new spider man, you watch it for two and a half hours. And then
it's to be continued. And the audience was the audience was not pleased with that because they didn't
hint that that was going to be happening. So the cartoon is two and a half hours, about 220. Yeah.
The first ones, you know, a tight 110 or something, but yeah, all movies are too long. Gun to my head.
No way. Uh, you'd like into the spider verse. I can almost guarantee it, but you don't have to watch.
All right. Maybe then maybe I will.
Um, I saw, I'll do a couple of quick ones. I watched The Chamber. I realized that I was like, you know,
I saw all those Russian movies in theaters. The firm is the best. And then you got, you know,
Pelican brief, the client time to kill. These are all pretty solid courtroom dramas, good movies.
At least I remember them being good. But I had never seen The Chamber starring Chris O'Donnell
and Gene Hackman. I knew that it was supposed to be very bad, but in the Wikipedia,
and even the Wikipedia about it, it came out in 96. Okay.
Ron Howard was set to direct Brad Pitt in this movie. And then they both left and they asked
Ron Howard why? And he goes, just a hunch. Just a hunch. And boy, that was a smart move because
this is a movie speaking of racism, where our hero that we're rooting for
is an active fully paid up on his dues member of the Klux Klan played by Gene Hackman who says the
N word a thousand times. He's the hero. It's like the Green Mile. If we were hoping that at a
Klansman, didn't make it to the chair, that's all it is. So Chris O'Donnell, who in my opinion is
the worst actor of his generation, and I'm including pornography. He's worse than Keanu Reeves,
unquestionably. He is a guy where I was always kind of confused. He's not even particularly great looking.
He just looks like the guy at your high school that did everything the right way that was annoying.
Yeah. If you're a woman, he's the guy your mom hopes you bring home, you know? And I guess that's
his appeal. He sucks in this movie in particular. There's a scene early on where he opens his
closet, and there's a bomb in it that the clan is putting his closet or it's a makeshift bomb,
like a warning, but he opens the closet and he goes tick, tick, tick, tick, tick, tick, tick, and it hits
and a balloon pops in his face. And he cannot convincingly portray fear in that scene.
It cuts to him, and I'm like, if that's the best shot they got of him being scared of a bomb in
his closet. This is the worst actor that's ever lived. Anyway, the point of the movie, and I'm not
kidding, is KKK members are people, too. It is Chris O'Donnell who returns home. He's a high -powered
lawyer who returns home to defend his grandfather, who is Gene Hackman. And Gene Hackman will say this
horrific race is shit in front of him. And Chris O'Donnell doesn't even really correct him.
He's just kind of like sitting there, taking it. It's so weird. And you know, the movie, they
eventually, Chris O'Donnell goes to this like clan rally thing where they're doing a Django thing.
They got this muscular black guy boxing all these white clansmen, and I'm like, what is this? It's
it's a ludicrous film. Grisham hates it. He's like, yeah, they bought the rights before I was done
with the book. I don't think it's a good movie at all. I hate it. Everybody involved hates it.
William Goldman came in to do a pass who's the best screenwriter of all time pretty much. He tried
to get his name off it. Like, it's a real train wreck. And it's just because the premise of the movie
is completely flawed. Let's root for a clansman. The only way it would have worked is it was a guy
who is it let's let me ask is it let's root for or is it like a challenging thing of like,
hey man, an innocent man needs to be represented. And that's the kind of the point here is that
this is challenging. No, they actually, they used to get you on the side of Gene Hackman. This
picture of him as a kid at a clan rally. And it's like, see, he was he was taught to hate. That's
what that's what they're doing. And it's like, yeah, but he's 70 now. I got to see this picture.
It really, I mean, it is. And then I read it like Ebert's review of it. And he's like, you know,
he's like, there's an hour and 15 minutes of this because nearly the end, it's not like Gene Hackman
has a change of heart, but he becomes like slightly nicer, I guess, is his journey. And Ebert's like
that hour 15 is like, his racism is played for laughs. And he goes, I guarantee, in most theaters
across this country, he's getting those laughs. And I think this movie is really messed up.
The warden or the guard in the movie is played by baseball and football player Bo Jackson.
Yeah, I'm seeing that here. And and he, they interview Bo Jackson on the stand. And he's like,
he's like speaking affectionately about Gene Hackman. It's the wildest movie. It really is.
Did not care for it. But then to praise William Goldman. And I'll be quick here. I just got the 4K
of marathon man, which William Goldman wrote based on his novel directed by the great John Schlesinger
who did midnight cowboy and has made many a genre film that he elevated and made made way better
than it should have been. I've never read marathon man. I intend to because the story is so great.
But the 4K of this, I think what it does to 70s movies is actually my favorite thing because I
felt sitting in Times Square watching marathon man opening night. They keep the grain of the film.
It looks great. Dusty Hoffman, amazing in it. Lawrence Olivier,
one of his greatest performances as this ex Nazi who tortures in the most famous scene,
dental torture on Dustin Hoffman to try to get information out of him. I remember watching this
movie with my father who has to be completely knocked unconscious to have his teeth cleaned. And he
doesn't often talks about the premiere of it. And he's like the entire theater cleared out halfway
through. And I was devastated because I thought we had a flop. But it was just everybody had been made
aware that there was a scene of dental torture and they waited in the lobby because it is intense. But
this movie it's structured in a great and unusual way Roy Scheider is in it. And he kills even who
Roy Scheider is is a great reveal. It's just packed with awesome twists. The plot of the movie is
I almost don't want to tell you because it'll spoil it but basically Dustin Hoffman is a marathon
runner who gets tangled up in a bunch of real crazy shit. There's an ex Nazi played by Lawrence
Olivier who wants to come to New York City to take all these diamonds out of a safety deposit box.
And he needs to know if it's safe or if somebody's going to try to kill him because much like an
app pupil. He's like one of the last living Nazis. And man, it's good. That's just all I can tell you.
It's a classic. It's considered one of the great movies of the 70s. But unlike the godfather or
apocalypse now, I think a lot of people don't know this movie. So don't read up on it. Just sit back
and enjoy. I fucking love marathon man. Check it out. All right. Let's get to the picture at hand.
And Mad Max almost a teen a turner beyond thunder. Mad Max be on Thunderdome. A movie
whose title is quite misleading because Thunderdome not only doesn't
I guess it does play a pivotal part in the movie. But it's in it for five minutes. They make you
kind of think that Thunderdome is like going to be this ultimate whatever in the movie. But it's not
this is a mad manager one man leave. Very famous line from the film. Mad Max be on Thunderdome is
certainly before Fury Road the most spectacle laden Mad Max film to date. It's interesting. This
movie to me I like to be on Thunderdome a lot. It might be my favorite Mad Max movie because it's the
most fun one to watch like the most there's it has the most versatility a bunch of different stuff
happens in it that they don't do in the other movies. I like that there's this weird town he goes to.
I like that he has to fight in this thing called Thunderdome. I like that there's an array of interesting
characters. I like that he's got a very interesting adversary and teen a turner. I like that visually
it goes to this place halfway through the film where there's like a garden of Eden occupied by
these young kids that are going to you know the metaphor being that they're going to rebirth society.
I like that you get to see at the end of the movie one of the burnt out cities.
I like that there that the chase car chase the obligatory fucking car chase is much a much smaller set
piece in this film than it is in the other ones. I really like beyond Thunderdome. I think
my theory is this script was drafted after a studio exec saw return of the Jedi though and said you
need to make that for Mad Max like it's considered the return of the Jedi of the franchise. The kids
replace the Ewoks it's too cute to see you know a barter town is job is palace right right
that's the only Mad Max that's not rated are yeah yeah um it's return of the Jedi but but because
of that with Mad Max it it it works the the reason in my opinion return to the Jedi is the weakest of
the Star Wars movies is because Star Wars and Empire Strikes Back go to such crazy amazing heights
visual heights and then such amazing emotional depths that what they do in return the Jedi seems kind
of lackluster uh whereas in this it's the quite the opposite I think this kind of takes Mad Max and
turns things up in notch they also they also make the character much more Han Soloish in this you know
he's got a little more of an attitude he's got a few quips you know there's a little bit of a
comedic side to him um I watched this two weeks ago I barely remember Mel Gibson speaking in the movie
to be honest with you they he doesn't he I mean like all Mad Max movies he doesn't speak a lot but like
you know there's the gag where they're like give us your weapons it's the law and like you know it takes
out 87 guns or whatever that's like it was like a Leslie Wilson gag um they do know I think it's
heart of the movie um I like that you know the the the basic plot is first of all it's confusing because
it opens with the a shot of the it opens with the actor who plays the guy in road warrior who flies
the propeller thing it opens with him flying a plane and he looks exactly the same but it's not the same
character it's a completely different character I don't really know why George Miller makes a
choice like that if I was watching this in the theater I would be like oh that guy's back and then
you're like wait it's not that guy and they never explain that it's not that guy but it's just not
that guy it's an old school thing uh in sitcoms they do this too older showrunners are always like oh
you'll have a great guest part come up and like oh we'll just get that girl we had play this other
part in season two and you're like people will remember but uh I guess now in the age of streaming
it's way more obvious but yeah if you watch the whole run of like phrasier you'll see people play the
same are people play different parts and stuff like that here's what I would say to that though at least
in phrasier the character is introduced as oh so the gardener is coming they tell you it's not the same
yeah right right this it oh he's flying the plane and his whole thing and the other one was
that he flew a thing and it's not the same guy anyway yeah um so that's that's how it starts they
they rob Mel Gibson of his he's got I think it's camels in a cart you know there's a camel drawn
card or whatever carriage they take that from him excuse me um he trails the thieves to a place called
barter town in barter town he Tina Turner runs barter town she says I you know I can make a deal
with you to get your stuff back you have to do something for me I need you to kill master blaster
who's the guy that controls the methane in the underground section of our city here the methane is
produced by pigs uh master blaster initially seems like an asshole uh Mel Gibson agrees to a deal to
kill master blaster inside of thunder dome in a fight want two men enter one man leaves as fat says
but then during the fight he realizes master blaster is a little person on the back of a huge man
and he has to fight blaster who's the big man uh during the fight though Mel Gibson realizes that
blaster has he's wearing a helmet it gets knocked off and he realizes that blaster is down syndrome
and he's like I'm not gonna kill this guy he's he's an innocent person being manipulated
and in that and then master comes in and expresses his humanity for blaster
Tina Turner ends up killing blaster in a very coldhearted move and right then you realize oh she's
the actual villain of barter town mel Gibson is then uh ostracized uh banished to the desert
to die as his punishment for not fulfilling the deal and out in that desert he finds a group of
children who think he is a savior that is meant to lead them to salvation he doesn't want to
do it but lo and behold he gets roped into helping them when some of the children venture
off without him and he realizes I can't let these kids go at it alone that's the basic plot of the movie
big surprise in the end the kids find salvation mad max helps them and somebody in a voice over says
they've never seen them ever again which is how every fucking mad max movie is yeah uh he really
is like a guy he's like a fuck boy with saving people like he he's like your money's on the night
stand he heads out of town you know yeah the lone ranger fuck boy yeah for me it's been a it's been a
little while but I think over the pandemic I watched the mad max movies I gotta say the original
mad max to me as I said earlier it's like the first evil dead I just don't have much reason to watch
it when you've got a much better more apt up version in part two um fury road and theaters one of
the best experiences of my life when it finally takes a breath about halfway in in the middle of that
car chase the place erupted like in in a pause just for the movie I've rarely seen something like that
yes yes um loved it uh for me this does feel like the return of the Jedi in that I don't like it as much
I just don't I think the original sets the template the second perfects it and the third makes it
too goofy um but what it has is enough great set pieces to make it a good very entertaining movie
you got the car chase you got the um the two men enter one man leave you got it just keeps the
hits coming throughout I just find the story kind of uninteresting I like I was not involved in it
anyway I think George Miller actually struggles with characters even in his straight movies that
aren't like this it's just not his thing he's more a technical director but he's a great technical
director um Tina Turner should have acted more I like her a lot as the villain in this he's great
she's great she plays it she plays it picture perfect she's not overly sinister she's she's
hammy in in the right moments she's not like broad yeah yeah yeah like good hammy like the way
you need to be to be this kind of villain like you know right she's she's my favorite
of the Mad Max villains uh out of all four movies uh followed by and even though I said I didn't
like Fury Road that much on the second viewing image image in Joe is is it awesome pretty awesome
bag guy but I really like Tina Turner in this movie um and I it's fun every time I watch see I this
was the first man Max movie I saw I saw this as a kid because it was kid appropriate um so it
always have a soft spot in my heart for that as it one of those movies I saw when I was 10 or whatever
I but every time I watch it I'm like Max it's because there's a moment at the end
where he he manages to get these kids home free and then he's left behind as usual because he sacrifices
himself and Tina Turner walks up to him and you're like they're gonna kill Max and she's just like
we make quite a pad don't we which by the way Tina Turner has an accent through this entire movie
where I'm like I googled her I'm like was she born in England or something like I like it's
so it's such a weird accent she has in this but it's it works anyway she says we're
quite a bad don't we a raggedy man yes and she laughs and leaves and I'm like why would you not go
with her and you have sex with Tina Turner for the rest of your life and run barter town agreed
I don't understand like like it seems like she's into you dude and uh yeah he's like nah that's
not for me you know I gotta fuck yeah live out here with my pet monkey and whistle or whatever
the fact that I would have had if Tina Turner died two weeks ago which I think she did I would have
had sex with Tina Turner three weeks ago I want to be real clear just a stunning woman and uh
if Tina Turner died two weeks ago I would have sex with her one week ago
if you haven't seen uh her documentary Tina it is on HBO Max excuse me Max
uh and it is excellent it is a great documentary it of course goes through the the terrible
like Turner years but you just see how unbelievably happy she is in her current marriage
and it it'll make you feel great about where the place she was in when she passed away because
you knew that she was absolutely loved and happy and peaceful and it's a great documentary and it'll
introduce you to a lot of great music I feel like people know proud Mary and they know the 80s hits
but there's a lot of really great stuff including though it's obviously problematic I have
several I can Tina albums because they did make great music together not at home but on stage they did
and also check out what's love got to do with it with incredible performances by Angela Bassett
Lawrence Fishburn which is a great dramatization of her life one of the few movies by the way
the possibly the only movie where you hate Lawrence Fishburn I can't think of another movie where
he plays somebody wholly unlikeable unless I'm blanking here but I can't think of one
yeah it'd be tough to think of one for sure I'm sure we could find it he had to have played a villain
at some point but yeah I agree got moving roughly we saw that once I don't know if I could revisit it
it's it's it's traumatizing that movie yeah it is miss Pat always talks about how it changed
her life and she she got out of her marriage and was like what am I doing and blah blah blah out of her
relationship you know well um we are going to be back of course as always we're not going to
probably get too dial of destiny because it comes out June 30th that'll be a July title yeah but
Joe and I are circling doing the flash we're talking about maybe doing the boogie man we're talking about
a few things but we'll be back um Joe do you have plugs I'm just on you know Instagram the Patrick
Walls where we have CU and help odd on Instagram where we show sort of a greatest hits and little clips
that Emily picks out of funny moments past and present new album is out studio recordings of my
penthouse columns it's called the penthouse papers selected readings did this one with a special
thing records a very cool comedy label I've admired for a long time and finally got to do something
with them it's out on all digital platforms please check it out people seem to be enjoying it
and then I have a huge salsa windfall announcement coming very soon uh for those interested and in
the meantime I will be in Toronto at the JFL Comedy Festival this coming fall tickets are available
now uh passes and pre -sale and all that stuff is available now go to the JFL website and uh get yours
please but Toronto is happening I'm doing a bunch of the performances of I never promised you a
rose garden up there I'm looking I'm looking forward to it immensely uh I have not been back to Toronto
for some time let's try to see if I can find the exact link as I talk about this uh I have not been
back to Toronto for some time uh it's one of my favorite cities in the world and uh it's just it's just
actually really an honor to be going back uh if you go to toronto .haha .com that's the website
toronto .haha .com you can get uh the dates the information the times of the performances
all that good stuff and you can get your pass and ticket there as well so that's it uh for me
we will see you next time and we will see you in hell