I'll see you in hell.
it's we'll see you and how back from the dead to talk about a resurrection movie called
what else would you call a resurrection zombie movie but the crow that's the title you think
it would have right wouldn't you it just assume bro yeah a strange picture a picture about to be
remade a picture I was unaware had three four sequels including one with Kristen Dunst including one with
who else was in the franchise for did you see any of these sequels any furlong is in part four
and for long as a husky crow oh he's the crow yeah he's a somewhat bloated crow in part four
uh the leads in the other two were not shown on set looking more like a penguin the the the male
leads in the other two or not names I was familiar with at all I did know how he furlong and terror
read oh that's right terror reads in the and Dennis Hopper yes as and his his Dennis Hopper's characters
got like the king of hell or some ridiculous wow I didn't realize it got that bad for Hopper near
the end well this is what I don't get everybody this new crow looks terrible but everybody all the fans
and the and the stars of the original are like how dare you remake the the crow it's like well
first of all guys they're not remaking anything you didn't make this story up it's a comic book
that right something else is based on so it's it's a reboot it's not a remake second of all
your legacy has been tarnished for years with three god awful sequels that nobody wanted to watch
and a series that was an adaptation of the original movie there was a TV series
there was a TV show okay I have no idea I never saw it but it existed so it was only as the crow flies
it was a British murder mystery where the crow wakes up in uh Yorkshire England and he's got to
solve a case angel of landsberries in it they partner up together well you're not like my usual
partners but I suppose we could give it a try well you're a bird of a different right this the crow
and and landsbury teaming up to solve crimes in Yorkshire I just have ideas like that just falling
out of my brain a CGI landsbury and let's be real a CGI crow well that's what we're not doing real
actors anymore this movie's gonna come out in a few years oh I thought you made a literal bird
oh you mean voiced by like Hugh Grant or something yes it's not bad Joe Joe just got himself an
EP credit she rides he rides on her shoulder you know they call her they have a little back and
floor and then when uh when uh people like show up she's like no I swear to god it helps me with
the crimes but the crow won't talk around anyone else so everyone thinks landsbury isn't saying
I swear to you I would pitch if she was still alive I'd go into a studio right now and I would
pitch be Arthur sure as the crow like guys we're gonna do the crow but it's gonna be the woman is 70
yeah and she dies she comes back it's it's it's I like that shot completely straight very serious but
she's doing her be Arthur lines through the entire movie and she's a reaction shots to stupid things
people say but in the full crow makeup yeah be Arthur full crow makeup I like that coming home at
the end of the night sprinkling some bird seed on a piece of cheesecake before I'd watch it I'd watch it
well it's kind of like the um it'd be kind of like in the everything you wanted to know about sex
were gene wilder the thing with uh that you know they talked about that in that documentary
Woody Allen said to gene wilder I want to do a remake of and it was some great love story I can't
remember he's gonna use it except it's you in a sheep right or a lamb or whatever and like
there are no jokes in fact there's two there are two jokes in that thing that that always bothered me
because they're the only joke jokes the first is he comes home and his wife goes is it me or do you
always smell from lamb chops which is a dumb joke because you you wouldn't smell like lamb chops from
being around a sheep like you wouldn't smell like cooked lamb oh we'll see I I don't think it's a great
joke but I took it as all the friction from fucking a sheep cause the lamb to heat up oh okay
so really she's smelling sheep pussy what she says lamb chops all right that's fair all right I'll let
that go the second joke is when he's like rock bottom and he lives on the street at the end and he's
drinking woolite yeah that always but I'm like I get the I get the gag but it's like it doesn't
have any sense but anyway those the that joke is the only joke joke like the entire thing is played
incredibly straight like when he's in divorce court like ashamed it's so funny dude if you
took the sheep out of it and just put a woman in there it would you would you just think it was a
drama mellow drama right anyway that'd be my inspiration from my b arthor i'd show them that
and say this is how you see I mean I I really love it do we do some sort of crow like ritual to
bring b arthor back from the dead to appear in our crow and maybe make a documentary about that
document that process sell it to max in real life now that'd be great seeing scenes of us around a
table with the candles lit and a gypsy and a crystal ball and you're hearing you're hearing quips
yeah from the other side right yeah maybe you and I start saying really stupid shit because we know
like in poltergeist that it'll draw her into our side because her desire to make fun of our quips will
be so strong yes I think that's a good idea we'll call it so the making of documentary is called
bringing back b it's on max september 13th and then b arthor as the crow will be an i max thing
sort of kicking off the summer movie season in may i'm calling my shot all right i like it speaking
of summer movie season yeah bev hills cop drop that's basically the only summer movie i'm excited
about it's next week i just learned that the Egyptian theater formerly an amazing los angeles
repertory theater is now showing netflix movies so you can see a netflix movie a week early
i've had no desire to do that i'm not going to see the j low a i movie but this weekend i think i'm
going to go see acts of left in theaters a week before it hits netflix i don't know if that's possible
elsewhere but they do it here so i'm pumped it looks good yeah it's been fun seeing
um uh judge ryan holed back on like the interview circuit uh you know it's nice seeing him again
if i'm seeing jud ryan holed and uh paul riser in i max you know seeing those giant faces on the screen
the uh and i'm i'm very excited for uh john ashton
amazed he's a lot they asked uh riser i saw him on some red carpet thing and they were like so why
want you uh invited back for three and he goes i don't know i never got a call i wasn't too bothered
by it when i saw the reaction it is not a lot of people's favorite Beverly Hills cop movie now i'm
back in this one they're good again i ask you what's the what's the connecting tissue it was very
very funny very funny he's still got it i might have talked about on here but for me i like hearing
about bad behavior but when you hear that someone is nice yeah it's just it's so such a beautiful thing
because it's rare but i met on the paul riser show which was his curb for NBC it lasted i think for
episode it was not a success it was him and Andy daily but i went in and met with him and for one
hour it was like it was clearly just like i want to see if you're funny and can hang and i could but he
was so sharp and so funny and everything he said was just a great joke right i i loved him i
didn't actually didn't expect them to be that funny now we also we also got sorry did i cut you
no please no no we also got Kevin Bacon in this thing which i'm looking forward to while it uh
who is he the villain well he's a he's a police captain i'm i'm gonna assume that that
bacon is the captain that's like we don't need your hotshot bullshit around here yeah and like
maybe not a villain but not supportive you know i bet he's nice at first and and is revealed to be evil
as my guest but dude now would you have gotten that Woody Allen joke if if it was a pig fucking and his
wife said when she comes home why do i always smell bacon would you have gotten at them
um no i i still think i i wouldn't have thought oh it's friction heat i i just was like
well maybe because part of it too is is that it's in the movie it's a sheep and then she makes a
lamb joke and i know they're saying you're getting that specific i don't know it's just
it's on tiktok the other day on the set of nine to five uh a blooper from nine to five and it
was dolly pardon and jane fonda and dolly goes uh what's green and smells like bacon or what's
green smells like bacon and jane fond of like i don't know she goes kermits finger kind of a similar
joke jane fonda like did a spit take with her coffee it was great that's great and then yeah
and she goes i gotta go to church y 'all yeah you ever seen that golden girls behind the scenes blooper
where uh room a clan of hand is telling a dirty joke to betty white yeah it's great what a delight
it is it's wonderful it's wonderful yeah i love an older person telling a dirty joke
i saw on uh oh again on tiktok i'm aware that there's a problem but when i removed vices as i
ever moved my uh you know my drinking and so forth the tiktok flares up i need something to calm my
tangled nerves but uh they were talking to i know it was it was a clip where i guess and i watched
all the golden girl i don't remember the episode but room a clan of hand is saying like i am 42
years old i am this that but she's pretending and she always lies about her age it's a character trait
and this thing had like 200 ,000 comments because the poster was like i have to kill myself i'm the same
age as a golden girl and everybody's like oh my god like can you it's crazy how much older people
looked back then it's like guys did you do you think about looking up the episode and seeing if
maybe something's going on here people are dumb there's no media obviously well along those lines
yes we've got new we've got new jimmy glic which has been great he's been doing these
tater one is that hater one is uh on all time top 20 i'm not sure where i'm placing it
and hater is not funny in it at all it's all martin short but the hater is enjoying the ride
it look look there's there's few people i enjoy watching crack up more than him he adds his own
thing but he what the only person i've seen fight back at jimmy and succeed is ice cube
yes like when even when sign fells doing it like you can tell he's like hurt by what jimmy is saying
and i'm like no that's not what you're supposed to be doing i don't think he's hurt i just think he
can't be the butt of it yeah he just has to be he has to be the guy that shows you he knows what's
going on that's why i've very much the mar thing i was like jimmy should not be on mar
because mar's whole thing is he cannot take a joke and a shot now look when i watched the clip
the clip i saw mar was laughing but um you don't want somebody with like thin skin who's taking this
giant muppet making jokes that they're expense seriously it's like really well uncomfortable the
mar uh like mar uh uh uh uh surrendered to it yeah more than i thought he would but he still has
moments where he's like okay okay you know what i mean and also too mar doing it on his show
the intro is dear lord i think mar i've said before on the show i think mar has some great points about
some things there are other things i disagree with him on i won't deny though that his personality is
just oh god and i do his podcast like i would sit there but i know it would be uncomfortable you know
because he'd be like he's just he just does not seem like an interactive guy he seems like i'm
going to talk at you guy yeah and he is the smuggest i mean i i burr burr was on that club
random the other day and tore him apart and that just doesn't happen to it but burrs the same way
i'll say it out loud on a behind -to -pay wall uh i wouldn't say this publicly but i trust the fans
burrs the same way he's another guy where it's like he has to tell you he has to show you he always
that's why every single bill burr clip is like bill burr school so and so on like
because he's yeah he can't just sit back and be the butt of anything he has to be like no i'm in
control i think it's all say so mar's that way he does again uh he does surrender to glic more than
i thought he would but but here's the problem the bigger problem with that glic interview the live
ones are never good like glic on the red carpet is never good the live stuff is never good it's like when
they can shoot overshoot and then edit it into what it needs to be it's the most magical thing ever
yeah it's uh any sort of long form improv i mean my guess is those interviews take about a half hour
i don't know that for sure maybe longer but you're not gonna have a hundred percent success rate
so yeah i mean i i the live ones like when i saw his live show on Broadway
there's sort of the thrill of like having i think it was Conan up there with him and stuff but yeah
it's like nobody can improv with a hundred percent success so seeing it cleaned up a little bit
is always better the shan haze one was funny not as funny as as hater but i hope we get five this
week or four well here's what i was getting at yeah the hater one overall was funnier as a just an
interview the the haze one is great too but what a sigh of relief i breathed watching glic interview
shan haze and everybody laughing at every joke yeah inappropriate gay jokes fat jokes
trump jokes every kind of joke got a laugh nobody's taking it too seriously i loved when he when he
described will it when he goes will and gray it's he goes and they never did the deed because he was
he was different yeah and shan haze goes yeah and he goes well that's why trump's gonna get raised
yeah i was like what a joy that people are just laughing i'm not i even went into the youtube comments
nobody's being like this is offensive on this um you know what i mean yeah i i i sense a bit of a
thaw in people's insanity about what you can't can't say we've talked a lot about how scary and and
bad that movement has been with its pluses of course but i do personally sense they're being a bit
of a thaw i noticed new you know i noticed jokes and things that wouldn't have been there a year ago
yeah i agree it's proving holy your mind i don't think we'll ever i don't think we ever will or should we
tilt back to like the late 90s early 2000s when i see some of those sex comedies from those early
2000s lately i'm like wow like culture has never changed that much that drastically in that short
of time i don't think there's some pros to it but um i think we can get to a place where yeah what's
up to fill your mic down a little bit because it's gonna keep it's gonna cut out if you don't the audio
go ahead sorry yes um i think it's a place for waving a pad for a minute straight he's literally
looking off at the horizon as he i was tiffing it's not a late squirrel there was a squirrel doing some
funny shit that's stealing my limes literally like a like a jud uh pet cemetery jud soliloquy staring
across i saw any who uh anyone know what the fuck i was talking about yeah you were just saying
you see some of those late 96 comedies and they're just yeah i mean like when when the hero is like
sexually a so you know revenge of the nerd as an example our hero essentially sexually assaults a
woman pretends to be somebody else under false pretenses um we're not going back to that but i do
think we can start to live in a world where if your humor is more extreme you access that on your
hulu or your netflix if not you go watch bridger tin or whatever the fuck you want to watch that should be
the dream of streaming watch what you want if something's her if she pedals trans thoughts offends you
you simply don't watch this special but we were in this weird thing where everyone thought you had
to scream at entertainment that wasn't made for you well also too people lost and still are
hopefully it slides back but people lost focus between what was truly bad what am i trying to say
there's a difference between not liking a joke made it another person's expense and celebrating
criminal behavior uh in a way that that sort of champion it champions it so in other words what i'm
trying to say is is like Dave Chappelle you might not like his trans jokes that's fine but he's making
jokes at the expense of a trans person just like he makes jokes at the expense of white people
or black people or whatever now you whether or not you define punching down this that's a whole other
discussion but the point is is at the end of the day it's a guy making jokes at a person's expense that's
all that is when you that's a far cry to me from saying guys we can't have our protagonist and hero of
the film uh hide a camera in the woman's bedroom and and rent uh broadcast her nude on the internet
those are two very different things and it's like with any of this stuff there are there are degrees
you know i'll i'll quote Bill Maher uh he said once i don't like that Republicans uh are against gay
or at least some Republicans are against gay rights he goes but i know it's not as bad as
gays being thrown off roofs in other countries he's like one is clearly worse than the other so
i think we just kind of lost sight of degrees uh and you know and it just got into this thing of this
craze of like everything is this and clump it all together and we lost sight of degrees and we lost
sight of intent as well it's just like what you know not not having the media literacy or curiosity
to say what did this person mean by that and look i i loved american pie when it came out i don't know
how i'd feel about it now i bet i'd laugh a lot it's a it's a great comedy with a lot of great jokes
and a lot of funny people in it but is that damaging to a generation of like i saw when i was 18 i was
in high school the dumb jocks that went to see it and see oh my god this hawk girl maybe i should do
something similar maybe that's how i should view women as like something i should trick into getting
naked i get how that can be damaging i sort of think about it more as i get older i think you think
about it more if you're a parent as well of what your kids are saying but um that's a big problem too
i mean that's yeah you know look i just read up on the tin drum last night actually never seen it i
own it criterion i never saw it's streaming on hbo max which is by the way based they're now they're
going back to hbo like they're they're they're rebranding again anyway uh but but quick pause isn't the
tin drum like really dark so you know like molestation subject matter did they put a warning up
because there's a warning up on good fellows now so so here's the deal the tin drum it's it's been
very controversial uh because it's about a boy who who declares he will not grow up so a child
plays the character an 11 year old plays the character throughout the movie but the character is actually
aging theoretically in the story oh okay so it's you know so like it's like still the 11 year old actor
but at this point in the movie he's 16 and at this point in the movie he's 22 or whatever
so there's a scene where when he's 16 he's having sex with a 16 year old girl however
in in real life the actor is only 11 years old and the woman's 23 now he's not actually having sex
with her but it's simulated now do i think that's an appropriate thing to shoot and put a child in
no absolutely not um do i think that if legally they were allowed to do it at the time and they
made a piece of art and that art should continue to exist yes i do i do think that for better or for
worse that's how i feel um what scares me is losing what we're losing the concept too you know you
saw just with this with this mad max actor who had to come out and say i'm playing a character i
don't condone kidnapping small children um because it was like a social media thing people were
writing to him and saying how could you condone playing a character that he's like i'm it's a
character i want to be clear i don't think kidnapping is okay it's a character um my point is this
take a we're we're we're take American pie take the thing they do in American pie
uh where they videotape shadow Elizabeth in the context by the way there are much more morally
repellent movies in American pie in this exact genre in this time period but it's a good example
because it was so popular so in that context i if it was my movie i'd be like guys we can't do this
this is crazy right yeah uh now back then people thought differently and and that's how that's
what evolving is you realize that shit that was what was way off yeah so but i would say guys you
get it but if you want to make you know a daring Todd Haynes style whatever flick and you go the
protagonist is going to do this thing where he videotape a girl and it's a common it's not being
celebrated it's a commentary on the male gaze and male toxicity or whatever
where we that's what scares me is losing our ability to say it can exist for that reason it can
exist to be abrasive and to put in your face how hard some of these things are yeah um that's not
what American pie is doing but you but there are movies that do do it there are movies that have
that that feature great brutality and the whole point is is this is a character study on this type
of thing that our society suffers from i worry that we're going to lose that i mean we have
maybe it'll come back i don't know or i feel like you could still do it overseas
that's where this whole discussion starts to get very very very very foggy
because if anybody can come out and say you know um elmer fud harrowing a shotgun in a looney
tunes cartoon is the same exact thing as uh making a movie that depicts the events of column
buying because both celebrate gun violence we're you're in a real tough place at that point
that's not i don't i don't like that um that said how often am i watching these a lot of times i don't
even want to see these abrasive whatever movies you know i bought salo just because for for the sake of
film preservation i don't think i will ever watch it you know uh it's not a fun one
no no no like that's that's one i sort of had to block out of my memory i saw it but like
there's stuff in it i'm like i don't ever need to think about that again yeah i don't know if i
need to like i like i'll never watch a serbian film because i've heard of that i was just about to
say that one i mean that's the legendary one a i don't think you can find it but yeah i have no
desire at all right i recently actually when i say recently i mean last night i was like i
know this is supposed to have really disturbing shit in it and i'll never watch it but what is in it
and if you go to like the parents guide on imdb of a serbian film i was like holy shit i would
imagine this being a horror podcast we we have some listeners who have seen the thing but um i got
me i guess spoiler alert i believe the movie ends with you know this guy well you know the old boy
twist or maybe you don't but it's it's this guy who's who they're you know these gangsters or whatever
are trying to punish and they convince him he's i guess that he's having sex with a beautiful woman
or something and then the final scene of the film is they reveal that he's soldimizing his five
year old son and i was like oh so this is beyond worse than what i thought it was like irreversible
which i have seen what was that was that serbian film irreversible is is beyond disturbing it's
nc seventeen i'll never watch that one again but i certainly respected the hell out of the film making
there's a ten -minute rape scene in it that is hellacious it's yeah i remember that
it beyond difficult to watch but boy it's not it's not that the the serbian film thing sort of feels
like the filmmakers should have been locked up you know well yeah actually when actually read what
was in it i was like so what was the purpose of this because in irreversible it's a revenge movie
and again that's that's kind of my point is like do any of us want to see a ten -minute scene where
that happens no but if the if there's a concept where the filmmakers trying to say look i'm trying
to show you a level of brutality so so you can understand the level of brutality it draws out of
another human being yeah and that's what that movie is for sure and it's supposed to be challenging
it's supposed to make you want to discuss it blah blah blah do i like it or not is a different story
but but whatever serbian film yes that's the american pie of you're like guys i don't know about
this i tell you when uh when era because the audience matters too and intent of watching the scene matters
too you know like when i um on irreversible in particular when i saw that pop up on porn hub
the ten -minute rape scene i was like you know what now i have different thoughts about this
well why that what why that Serbian film scene when that's when that i guarantee start showing up on
the dark web or whatever that scene then you start to really question it you know you can't
you can't you know you can't say only this group of people can watch my movie um people are going
to be watching it for nefarious purposes unfortunately that's part of it but that goes back to parenting
and shame on porn hub porn hub should be policing its site better yeah if that kind of stuff is
showing up on there and well but but porn hub is a site that has tons of i mean i assume all these
porn sites unless they've banned it and i don't think any have they have rape simulations on there
um so it just sort of fits right in with the rest of what's on there it just is
gross to me i don't think i don't think i will never agree with the statement that the that the
five percent or whatever percent of sick that's like saying beevus and butthead should have been
banned because the kids set a fire yeah no i where where are the parents and obviously the parents are
not you know responsible for a grown man uh watching porn but there's just always going to be that
there's always going to be that so there should be control there should be some kind of moderation i'm
not to i'm not disagreeing with that but porn hub also is under fought porn hubs under fire for a lot
of stuff porn hub has has been accused of a lot of things i won't get into it because i don't know
what if it is true what if it isn't what is an allegation what is not um but i think like
porn porn stuff i don't i don't even want to i don't even want to i don't even want to say it out loud
because it's you don't want to be smirch no because i'm very careful to it's it's there's
legality and you know i don't want to start saying things that may or may not be true but my point is
is porn hub has been under fire for for they've been accused of a few things you know this bullshit
of you know once it's out there it's your problem is is nonsense it's nonsense all right
if if if these streaming services want to put warnings in front of movies because they're they
think it needs to have a trigger warning that's fine that's they're fucking that's their opinion that's
that's their prerogative if they want to say we're not going to show good fellows anymore
because we don't want it on our site that's fine i don't get man i've never been mad at instagram
you know i know a lot of people that get or not even know but i see a lot of people get mad at
instagram oh this site sucks i showed a nipple and they well that's their rules i don't know you know
that's instagram sure i don't yeah instagram is a right to have rules oh twitter sucked because you couldn't
okay well that was twitter's world i don't know like okay now you can say whatever the fuck you
want on there whatever but now that's the rule okay great i just you know i just think there's
always going to be a group of unsupervised children of teenagers that were not raised
properly of adult psychopaths whatever that are going to misuse anything they can in the worst
humanly way possible and the rest of the civilized community shouldn't have to suffer for that i
don't think but people got to take care of the shit i agree i mean yeah you can't you can't really
put restrictions on art you can certainly put restrictions on where that art is shown and who can
access it you know yeah when i was a kid i only had basic tv i had the standard five channels you
know i was never going to see anything but that's why i would see a trailer for a horror movie and
be scared for a week i didn't know about all the other stuff going on in the arts until i started
going to my buddy's house and slipping the occasional r -rated movie off of his collection or whatever
like that's and that's on my parents that's good parenting it may have fucked me up later in life
made me sheltered given me hang ups about certain things but their goal was to keep me from seeing
fucked up shit until i turned 18 and by and large they did a pretty good job of it well that's the
other side of it the other side of it is we want our children to understand the world we want our
children to act without judgment we want our children to have open minds and it's like at the same
time we don't want to and them to know about violence we don't want them to know about sex more
importantly and i'm like i don't i don't understand there's a weird there is a weird weird
thing with this where it's like the moral majority of the 1980s all over again
but that same moral majority this time is also pushing a more much more lacks agenda and discussion
when it comes to certain parts of sexuality and sex certain areas of violence and what have you
you know we don't want our kids to know violence but we'll talk about them every day about genocide
right it's like okay that's fine if you think that that's important but that is violence so
so understand that you're still you're still exposing them to violence yeah you have to you know like
you know David Cross had that great thing about like they they complained about violence on tv
and how bad of an influence it is and then they show the dead bodies being carried out of Columbine
the footage of the the dead bodies being pulled out of the window repeatedly like on a loop on CNN
when that happened and he was like that's violence on TV like how is that not you know
so it's very odd i don't really understand but whatever none of it matters
uh i'll just keep watching reruns of phrasier and perfect strangers i guess
um let's hit that movie corn shall we i think i know we're gonna get that deep
hey you never know what you're gonna find when you pop into we'll see you and help
some of the times we're talking about our dicks for 45 minutes sometimes it's a it's a passionate political
discussion i got a great one to start the movie corn sure given this discussion i watched south park
into the panda verse okay what a masterpiece uh it was like a special episode of
south park an extended episode i was called yeah i saw that one i haven't seen the new ozampic one
into the panda verse um it starts it begins with kartman having a nightmare that he's been replaced by a
black woman in his life yeah i saw that one and the Kathleen Kennedy is hiding under his bed
because she's trying to replace him um it starts as an all out attack on the overwokeness
of disney stuff and the over diversification you know that disney is like kind of wearing on its
sleeve right now uh and then of course like south park usually does very well they start to hit
that discussion from all sides and you start to see why both sides of that argument are being
are over the top and wrong and um and most importantly feeding one another as the story unfolds
they realize they're in a multiverse they talk about how tired the multiverse concept to his
kartman does switch places with an alternate universe kartman who is a black woman so now he's the only
white person in her world and she's the only black person in their world um the uh uh this is
the the the companion story is a bee story about how all the white men uh in in the in the town
are have have depended on technology too much and don't know how to do anything anymore so now all
of the immigrants who did all the handy work uh become billionaires because they're the only ones
that have any skills it's really funny man it's a really really really sharp really funny
commentary it ends with kartman finding Kathleen Kennedy and them realizing i've only acted this way
because of you and you've only acted this way because of me because he hates what Disney's been doing
and she hates the trolls and they they and it is strangely storybook type ending they they find
a very common ground which is nice um it's really really funny um i i loved it um
and again those hour -long ones are good they get you know instead of getting one week
gun to their head to write the episode they get however much time they need so you definitely feel
more of uh strong structure to these episodes that i think they're really good they're
right south park episodes and they don't really feel the lamp either no it was awesome it was like a
little mini movie um and it's really it was just really really funny i really liked it and i thought
it was the best commentary on because it was how i felt about all this stuff i'm like yeah i'm not
and they talk about it when they're like when when they're like they go to the principal and he's like
he's like you have a problem with kartman now being a black woman that sounds like you have a problem
and he's like no i don't have a problem with a black woman don't you think it's weird that the guy
that's always been kartman is not kartman anymore like that's all i'm saying it's just weird
yeah yeah uh it just kind of hit that note of like no we're for diversity we're into it just
make it just just make it make sense let that's all like like so i don't know i i i still get nervous
talking about this because i don't want to sound like some out of touch guy but i thought they
i thought they walked the line very very well and i thought that they uh i thought they hit the
argument from all sides people taking it way too seriously people being racist and overreacting
and then people also gushing and patting themselves on the back to say look look look at what we are
doing it kind it also made me realize and then i'll shut up diversity in film uh and in television uh
progressiveness in film and television is nothing new people it's nothing new people have been pushing
for it for many years artists have pursued it for many many years um and people have achieved it
for many many years what sucks about it now is this is the first time we have groups of producers these people
at these different studios saying to all of us we do it better and we do it right and we did it we
ours is more worthwhile and that's what's making everybody kind of go you know what fuck you
fuck you yeah you know i agree your best wasn't good enough look at we did oh could it be that you also
have access to the most money that any human beings have ever had access to and you can just do
whatever the fuck you want including pulling fully produced projects
because your tax write -offs are so big at this point losing 50 or a hundred million dollars means
less to you than than i mean it's so insane so that's that's the problem i think it's the attitude
it's the condescension if they if they got rid of that i don't think anybody have a problem with this
stuff i really don't yeah or most people would there still be the group of assholes out there
anyway i do think there's there again like i was saying earlier there's a
slight thawing of the extremeness of the last three years or whatever and i hope it continues
don't think it needs to thought of the point where we're as bad as we were i don't want that
i'm saying there has to be some somewhere between the two
um and i think we'll find it i'm trying to be more optimistic about it um i saw kinds of kindness
the new film from your ghost lantimos um i saw dog tooth which was kind of his big breakthrough movie
i think it's a brilliant movie about how parents can fuck up their children it's very funny dark
comedy i highly recommend dog tooth and i think a lot of people haven't seen it and i was like who is
this dude i love this dude after that he made a couple movies i did not care for aton bergen alps
and i was like all right i'm losing interest came back with the lobster which was great
killing of a sacred deer which is excellent the favorite which i liked a lot and poor things which i
also liked a lot he's a filmmaker i'm a big fan of for the most part he makes interesting and weird
movies kinds of kindness is when you let when you let a guy go too far um a lot of filmmakers especially
ones that kind of push the envelope open make weird or difficult movies as they go along in their career
they think they're making better art by becoming more obtuse becoming more difficult to follow by making
longer and more unwieldy movies that don't really make sense even filmmakers i love greatly
Paul Thomas Anderson i much prefer his early work to his later work um i just think these guys
disappear up their own ass and sometimes having final cut on a project makes it worse sometimes
you need to listen to other people's opinions on things we talk a lot of times about how shitty notes
have kind of ruined entertainment but a good intelligent person giving you notes can be very very helpful
for the final project i think this your ghost movie this new one shows a guy who is just not
not was not rained in properly on this one uh it is three hours long
uh it is three stories which i was not aware of it so it's an anthology film they're not advertising
that they're not advertising that it's three hours of course either and this guy coming off poor things
which was a hit um you know he was kind of given cart up launch here it's a very low budget movie
and therefore it can be more experimental but it has huge stars in it too um it's Emma Stone who
weirdly as i believe now going by Emily Stone um what yeah no yeah what i saw at some press conference
somebody's like uh Emily can i ask you and she's like yes thank you that's my name thank you
somebody finally called me by my name because she announced it three months ago she wants to be
Emily now shut up thank you finally thank you oh because because you've had such a rough run of it
Emma we've all been so cruel to you you fucking moron oh yeah i hate her now no it was annoying
well i always really loved Emma Stone until her acceptance speech at the Oscars and then i completely
turned against her the some of these people lose their connection to humanity instantly when they
become famous and when i say some i mean easily 50 % right i mean like that receiving an Oscar
is like crying like that if the Nazis gave you a car
yeah yeah and you needed a car but you're like i can't believe you have recognized yeah
these are the worst people on earth and i worked for them and i will work for them again
but can we just call it what it is no they never will um it's all right so Emily Stone uh
Jesse Plemons Willem DeFoe Margaret Kwolly Heng Chow Hunter Shaffer from Euphoria and Joe
Alwyn from Banging Taylor Swift um it's three stories that group of people i just mentioned plays different
characters in each um the stories are meandering aimless they don't make much sense they don't have much
of a point they are very surreal um the first one is kind of the best i guess but it's about an hour
long it's called the death of r -m -f Robert Fletcher second one is called r -m -f is flying the third one
is called r -m -f eats a sandwich there were it was nearly sold out there were two people in the audience
howling laughing that demonstrative you're going to see a Woody Allen movie in New York performative
laughter that was very annoying to me the whole experience was just deeply annoying um the filmmakers
insist that it's supposed to be a hilarious comedy it's not that's why those people were performatively
laughing so that they could say i get it why is nobody else laughing and i look part of it is just
seeing one of these movies in LA can be a deeply annoying and frustrating experience i get it but
man what what a jerk off this this movie is kind of everything that people complain about in the cinema
um wrapped into one thing at the same time there's great stuff in it your ghost knows how to make
a great scene there's there's crazy cool scenes in it there's good music in it there's you know
moments that spring to life but overall your ghosts you keep the head out of your ass buddy don't go
further down this direction where you make more and more obtuse things and critics just because you
don't understand a movie doesn't mean you have to call it a masterpiece so that you don't seem dumb
thank you you're welcome uh well i'll stay on the theme of that i was on of diversity
i watched uh pet cemetery bloodlines now here's a movie
i i i give it a huge nod i thought they did diversity perfectly well
in pet cemetery bloodlines it's a town in Maine you like how a syamie's cat was played by a true
syamie's cat they didn't bring in i did okay sorry it took place in Maine in 1969 which would
have been a predominantly white community just historically uh but would they do they put a full
american indian family into the story wow that makes perfect sense especially since the huge part
of the plant line has to do with american indians i was like and they didn't give some white guy
an indian wife right where some white couple an indian kid where it doesn't make any sense
they actually took away from their precious white quota and build several roles with an american
indian family wow isn't that fucking great uh i thought that that was awesome i uh
the movie itself sadly uh starts pretty good i thought it's certainly way better than the uh
it was well at least at the beginning it's better than the remake of pet cemetery
and it's better than pet cemetery too at the beginning uh and all the way through the halfway mark
i was like all right i'm kind of into this uh this is interesting
decently directed decently enough written well acted uh david the company was was good in it uh
pam grier was good in it um i thought it was a decent movie and then it's it's the story of
timmy baterman who's the kid that that jud talks about when he comes back from the war something's
not right and they realize he was dead and they buried him in the pet cemetery right um
that they they they play with that for a while they establish a bunch of rules
once it rises from the pet cemetery it will need to gradually kill more and more and more
um um okay great i'm with you i'm listening but then they do a thing and this is somewhere
towards the middle or end of act two it's only an eighty five minute movie um where timmy kills
um a woman and instead of just letting her be dead and eating her guts that they've established
that's what these people do when they come back because they eat your guts
he buries her in the pet cemetery and then she rises
i don't understand why they sort of insinuate that she had he had a crush on her at one point when
he was normal maybe that's why but anyway she rises from the grave she instantly starts killing
now this is already a movie where they have established the person will be sort of normal for a period
of time she rises and the the the morning of is already trying to kill people that makes no sense
then timmy kidnaps the the jud is the main was one of the main characters is jud crandle whatever
uh he has got a girlfriend timmy kidnaps her
you know what why does he kidnap her that's not what they do you just said they have to kill he
would just kill her that didn't make any fucking sense at the end they reveal he's created some like
hideout firms it's not if it made any fucking sense it gets so away from itself it is absurd by the end
of the movie it's stupid it's so far from pet cemetery by the end of the movie as dumbly and stupidly
as pet cemetery to starring Edward for a long the king of bad sequels i prefer that cemetery to
that's ridiculous pet i prefer to bloodlines joe oh oh oh i thought you meant and to the remake of
pets i thought you meant to pet cemetery no no Edward for a long he's only in bad sequels terminator to
pet cemetery to yeah the crow part for um i don't know man it's just not a good movie it's not a good
movie um but i did think that they they did is it bad to me to say they did diversity well i don't
mean that in a shitty way i just i was like no that's not bad at all no i mean like they weren't being
like look at us look what there was like no this is like this is great he had diverse cats and it all
you know i don't know yeah i mean i i think it's hard to argue that any diversity is a negative thing but
i think that that there are much more positive ways of handling it so at least that's a good one
out of positive thing about the movie that's a good one i hated that movie and i saw it in a cemetery
which i thought would be more fun but no um i went to the local
iMacs theater for a one -night only screening of the mid -summer directors cut
easily one of the most controversial titles and arguments that we've had on this show
was mid -summer mid -summer and a reausters work in general has always been a bit of a thorn in
the side of this show we we differ strongly i love him joe does not
and the directors cut i do own it you can buy it from the a24 side at a very expensive price it's
not really available elsewhere um kind of cool packaging whatever i got that and they're they're
lighthouse special edition and they're stopped making sense special edition and they're cool they're
cool little packages but i had not seen the mid -summer directors cut i was excited to
the original movie of memory serves was a little shy of two and a half hours
and i think part of it was creating that kind of dread that kind of kubrickian outdoor dread horror
feeling and and it worked gangbusters as i said i think that movie is really really great
the directors cut like like all directors cuts like James Cameron's in particular
there's stuff that is so crucial and integral to the movie that they left out that you're like how
did you do this how did you mess up this bad then there's stuff that they add that you're like why would
you put that in there that's so stupid and all it is is tastes are different directors are different
my guess is mid -summer had to be two and a half contractually and he always wanted more stuff in it
but overall i'd say it's a one -time watcher also like most directors cuts i love the directors cut of
like aliens for example i'll always watch that version if possible uh the abyss is the same way
but by and large you just want the original back this one showed me some things i'm glad i saw
it adds some depth to certain elements of the movie but for the most part it's making
Florence pubes boyfriend look like more of an asshole much more of an asshole and they really
capture a toxic relationship well as he did well in the original cut of this movie but there's just a
lot more of him being a dick therefore when she agrees to have him killed and sacrificed at the end
you're like yeah fuck you dude you know and that's great but i do prefer the original version of
seeing this guy be a bit of a shitty boyfriend be a bit of a narcissist a bit of a you know self -absorbed
you know not a good partner etc but has some good things as well you know like he forgets her birthday
but he forgets it because they're in a place with no night and day and when he explains why he
forgot it you're like i get it that makes sense it has the the the moon hasn't come out while they've
been here um that's in the original in the new one you actually really see him breaking her down
emotionally and being awful to me that's pushing it too far i like the ambiguity of the original cut
is there more violence more scares than it not that i could recall maybe a couple of moments here and
there um but yeah it for me it's a one and done if you want to sort of fill in some of the gaps
that the original movie leaves you with it's great if you'd rather not have those gaps filled in
and rather have enjoyed and embraced the mystery of the movie which is kind of how i feel
then don't see the director's cut but i still love the movie Joe um i'll never see it
no i know you won't see it but i hear you yeah yeah i think the ambiguity uh carries a story like
that a little bit further because i was you know i didn't like the film but i was conflicted at the end
yeah because you it it goes it goes it carries more water for you to say should she be sacrificing
Jesus Christ you know what i mean like you know so um um movie just i mean he is a guy who has a mastery
of how to make the viewer feel dread and feel awful and i can't say i always want that experience
but i feel it more than enough dread in my day to day life but i do think he's a master of it and this
movie you know even the director's cut shows he can kind of sustain that tone for three full hours
um i dig it i'm a big fan of this movie as you know i will uh i won't do a third movie but i i'll do
a quick news psycho that relates sort of to what you're talking about because these two directors are
often clumped together but the uh roger which is named roger at the light terror daggers the robert
eggers lighthouse uh his trailer for Nosferatu finally arrived yeah i haven't seen it yet man it looks
awesome good looks awesome he doesn't reveal the vampire very wisely but man it is fucking creepy it is
i was like this looks awesome Nicholas howt plays the jonathan harker role and uh william defo willum defo
plays the you know the sort of uh van Helsing role um i think they have different names though in
this but uh but jesus it looks it looks scary i was like this looks intense and scary and so does
the new uh Hugh Grant horror movie uh that trailer i did see yeah it looks kind of cool what's it
called again now i do something here are the name of it you know these two like sort of you know
bible thumping christian you know women of course hot as shit yeah what door to door christians are
well they're actually mormons or mormons yeah uh and mormons are hot generally knock on his
knock on Hugh Grant's door he invites them in and you because he is the one person that wants to
talk to them about the lord save you jesus christ and then he traps them and it's one of these
sinister things it's almost like a ten clover field lane where like is he a bad guy or are they
gonna come out of this appreciating the test he's put them through or whatever like it looks really
interesting but both of those uh i'm very very excited about same i mean my uh i'm most excited about
long legs um partly because i know nothing about it but i really like that director osgood perkins he's
made nothing but good super low budget horror movies he's anthony perkins son um and this movie is
just supposed to be terrifying and nickless cage is supposed to be amazing in it what i find crazy
is that it's a low budget movie and they're to they haven't shown a trailer with nick cage in it yet
so i don't know what he looks like or what he's doing in it but it must be crazy it's supposed to be kind
of a solace of the lambs type movie um and i will close with the insider michael man's classic uh
1999 film 99 is is i read a whole book about it considered to be one of the great years in american film
and it really is if you look at the titles released in 99 holy shit the year i graduated high school
i was seeing so many great fucking movies um insiders a five star movie it's it's not heat it's not as
perfect as heat but it's it's close and it's a different style of movie yeah michael man made some great
shit there for a while i i hated for arey i don't know what he's doing lately but the insider is so
funny too baby he too is coming he too i'll watch it um i've heard that uh austin butler is playing the
Val Kilmer role okay fine that's great casting yeah it works and then he's got driver is
didn't hear oh right i'll buy it or out the insider is uh is michael man
at his best it's russ crow coming off gladiator playing jeffrey whygand who's like this middle -aged
uh heavy set sad guy who decides to be a whistleblower um to the nicotine corporations that he has
been employed at for many many years russell crow is thirty was thirty three when he made the insider
talk about a performance like holy shit you never doubt for a second that this is a 55 -year -old
brutally depressed man he's incredible in it uh it makes you sad when you compare it to the monthly
exorcist movies that russell crow is making now but that's what hollywood does um this is one of the last
excellent pichino performances it's one of the you know i'm not i'm not a guy who thinks he has to be
super subdued and not crazy to be good um but he is sometimes more effective in a more controlled role
like this when he's not screaming at everybody pichino is killer crow is killer the story is excellent
it's the modern day all the presidents men which i also watched this week but they go real deep into
every angle of this story it's a character actor's dream or character actors fans dream yet
Christopher plumber is mike walless he's incredible fill up baker hall as pichinos like kind of
slimy advisor you got the great steven tobalowski Bruce McGill steals the movie in his few scenes
michael gambons incredible rip torn has like three lines in the movie if that tells you anything
it's just one of those like jfk or or peat whatever where it's just an epic where every performance is
perfect every moment hits and you just kind of want to live in the movie forever and i think insiders
a bit slept on because people view it as homework but it's just such a fun uh well written well
acted well directed movie and let's move on to the crow starring the great the deceased tragically
brand and Lee um i hadn't seen the crow in a while i actually thought that brand Lee was kind of a
look i love nirvana but kind of a Kurt Cobain story of where we're pretending that this guy was maybe
a little better than he was i've loved nirvana for 30 years but when somebody dies young you get lionized
you kind of can't help it but when you watch this movie brand and Lee was definitely a star
yes great so great you won i wondered on this viewing if he might have influenced heath ledger's joker
there's a lot of similarities there he um he plays it very well it's not an easy task
no it's an eccentric role he's got to swing wildly between emotions you know he's he's devastated
in one moment he's riding in pain the next moment he's scary and intimidating in the next moment he's
he somber in the next moment it's a lot a lot to do and he pulls it off uh and you know he
there there there are there are areas where he needs to be a bit hammy and and a little over the top
and then there are other places where you need to believe that this guy has lost the love of his
life and he's absolutely devastated so he he does very very well in it everybody in this movie is great
it with their Ernie Hudson as the good the one good cop in the bad town is perfectly cast
he's love Hudson it love Hudson don't like wincott i don't care for the villain i love it
god i believe he is the most evil prick that's ever lived in this uh john polito
say i want it over the fence love polito love a polito creepy uh pawn shop owner all the thugs
are you know politos a gay man yeah was he's dead i must say i love that too um oh why all of the thugs
are very scary very creepy led by uh what's his face from dream scape the guy that always plays an
absolute fucking creep yeah yeah what's that guy's name uh i'm not sure the uh sure i'm looking at
the cast list but i'm not sure hold on i'm gonna just go to dream scape it was David Patrick killing
this is name he always plays a shit yeah uh he and he's great at it he's great he's in commando he's
dreams oh he's in the war he's the main bad guy in the war years that's what i when i see that guy's
face i'm always like trying to place him and i always come back to the warriors that's where i know him
yeah um he's also in uh in crickland spikeley's crickland which i saw with your dear friend James
Pinkstone theatrically um he plays the the neighbor who's like the white neighbor who's like always
causing him shit he's an annoying presence in a movie yeah everybody in this and the kid this was
kind of the only thing she was ever in but she's great everybody in this nails their part it's
beautifully directed by the director of dark city uh Alex proyes beautifully directed um yep
i mean proyes he did dark city after this which i remember ebert calls i think he called it his favorite
movie the year and wound up doing a commentary on dark city on the on the blue ray but um a great
sort of visionary visual director who i don't think ever really got out from under
the fact that his first film not him but his first film led to the death of Brandon Lee
you know i i don't know if if there were trials and stuff about that like there were with rust and
bald when i don't recall but um but he he did he's done several movies since it's just his last couple
were were bombs yeah he's kept he kind of kept working but he seems to be sort out of the game at this
point um it's beautifully shot it's amazingly paced he shoots it like a comic book he tells so much
of this story through visuals without dialogue they waste no time the film opens with the scene of
the crime where Brandon Lee and his girlfriend have been murdered by this gang of thugs
uh and immediately it goes to one here later and Brandon Lee rising from the grave i mean they get
right into it man and it's great and then some through some flashbacks after he rises from the grave
you see a little more of the details of what happened to them um and then it's and then it's on
he puts on the makeup he puts on the outfit and he goes after these guys
and it's creepy he's he's he's creepy in it he's freaky like the when he comes into the like
room and and and like toys with them before he kills them he's legitimately like freaky i'm like
yeah i'd be scared right now um it's written by by James O 'Barr wrote the original material graphic novel
to cope with the death of his fiancee who was killed by a drunk driver so story really comes
from a dark place a place of pain and you kind of but you definitely feel that i mean that's what drives
the movie um it's not a super complex story it's not unlike a john wick or any other revenge thing
it's aside from the the you know coming back to life element it's basically a guy getting revenge on
the people who killed him and his girlfriend you know there that was what was sort of frustrating
to me is that the story is so simple but the visuals are so strong on brand and Lee is so strong
supporting cast as you said is strong and the soundtrack is excellent you know it's it's just
banger after banger soundtrack every whenever when i knew we had this soundtrack in their car on cd
back in the day um i don't love the crow yeah you don't love it overall i don't love the crow even though
i just acknowledged all that positive stuff about it um it doesn't make me like pump my fists
it doesn't make me like cheer and not that a movie needs to it just kind of feels like
i wish it had been fleshed out a bit more or something there's a generic quality to it that bothers me
i don't know what it is i just don't find it particularly involving um i did just read that the
first meeting james obar had with a major studio uh was quickly dismissed after the studio's vision
for the film was to make it a musical starring michael jackson he's christ almighty
tell you i mean that that's why this business is so scary you know you go in with your
your real personal tragic dark story and so many people would go a musical with michael jackson
okay if it'll get it made you know it's like sometimes you're just like all right let's go with it
this guy very wisely stuck to his guns um i actually i don't i actually don't like how
in different i am to the movie because i've seen it six times and i feel the same every time
it might just be my own reluctance to to get into a super hero movie i don't know what it is but
i i like and respect and admire almost every single thing about the crow and yet
i'm never going to rank it above a bee for me a bee is it solid score it's a solid score sure
it's not a hog down situation uh it's just uh it's a movie i wish i liked more i have the 4k coming
today actually i look forward oh the 4k looks real good i look forward to owning it it's a perfect
Halloween movie uh i i like the movie quite a bit i think it really captures i remember when this
came out i remember the soundtrack coming out i remember thinking it was one of the best helmet
songs ever i'm a big helmet fan uh i remember the phenomenon of it it's fun i started laughing
a couple times while i was watching it because i was like my god this was like a hot topic goth's kid
goth kids like what dream when this thing i would be guys who would come to school dressed as the
crow i mean when this came out i was like 13 and i didn't even see it probably till five years later
but i like uh before obsessed i like the movie quite a bit um i think it gets a little
a little bit lazy at the end not lazy it's just at the end it's sort of deteriorate i don't
use negative words it just kind of devolves a bit into you know like a sort of big shootout
sequence at the end that you feel was the studio saying we need a bigger set piece here at the end i
would have much preferred you know like a wrath of man ending where the main bad guy goes back to his
house and turns the light on and Brandon Lee is in sitting in there already and like and kills him
uh but clearly the studio wanted something a bit bigger so um but i do like the movie quite quite quite a bit
and um i do uh i think hey man it's it's tragic that Brandon Lee was lost during this it's tragic
he's not around anymore but i will also say i'm happy for him that if this was if he got to leave one
mark that this mark was it because this is a really really solid film uh yeah he's he's so charismatic
and uh you know doing it all with with makeup on and everything else like you it makes you kind of
wonder what would have become of them by the way might have been nothing we never know but um
he's a much better performer than i remembered him being when i watched this movie this time
yeah uh my hog is up for the crow my hog highs fly my hog flies high
for the crow my hog does not fly high but my hog is certainly plumped for the crow
and the 4k really does look great we will be back next month i'm not sure release dates on some of
these things but i would imagine we will see long legs i would imagine we will see that Hugh Grant
picture i would imagine we will see um what's the other big one well Beverly Hills cop will probably
yes we'll definitely do that of next month not forado i don't know the release date the Hugh Grant i
don't know the release date but these are some of the thing you know Beverly Hills cop absolutely
and uh those when they come out and uh long legs and all that stuff so uh
redic is the uh Hugh Grant picture we also got smile too common we got ale the new alien coming we
got a lot what is the Hugh Grant picture called
uh heretic heretic or heretic what heretic okay heretic um folks jota rosic comedy on instagram
if you're not following uh i think it's that on x or whatever the hell i think it's jota
was a comedian on tiktok um i do not have any live dates probably until september um where i'm
going to be adding a couple warm -up shows for the special taping which is already sold out thank you
all for that um i'm going into the writer's room next week for tires season two so i will be
off the road and writing for my buddy Shane gillis's tv show i'm excited about that i haven't been
in the writer's room in a long time uh so uh that'll be fun uh other than that i'll see you here on
the podcast and if you're in new york city come on out to joey roses we're open seven days a week
joey roses dot com we won by the way the deniro hero competition we won audience vote best
italian sandwich in new york city at the tribeck of film festival which was very cool nice
so does deniro present you with that award no he did not find the time to come to the hogey competition
yeah he's doing a uh panel with scorsese and he's like excuse me i got to get over to that hogey
judging competition um i am on instagram at the patch walsh we are on instagram at cw
pod the miss pad show is back season four is streaming and doing extremely well i as always
recommend watching it on bt plus and not linear because every episode is ten minutes longer and full
of rate dirty are rated material uh we'll be back we love you we'll see you next time and we'll see you
in hell