Hello.
Helen's.
You're welcome to the high -outs.
Welcome, everyone.
How are you?
Sit the fuck down.
I'm kidding.
Sit down at your leisure.
Hello, I was just telling Joe I'm extremely nervous for some reason.
This is why I stopped doing stand -up comedy.
My hands will be shaking probably throughout the night, but it's fun.
Well, this is for you.
You kill it with a drink like Bradley Cooper and a star is bull.
It worked out good for him.
I don't know if you guys have seen it, but everything turned out great for him in the end.
I haven't seen it.
But it's based on Bradley Cooper's actual life, correct?
I believe it is.
It's a biopic.
I haven't seen it.
How was it?
I'll get to it in the movie corner.
Very good.
Welcome to.
We'll see you in hell.
Your favorite podcast covering horror sci -fi fantasy films.
Thanks for being here, everybody.
We're really touched that all of you came and some of you flew, which we don't understand.
I'm telling you right now you're going to regret it.
You're going to regret it.
I've never flown for anything.
Not even barely family.
No, absolutely not.
But it's very touching and nice.
You're the only reason I'm on Facebook opening myself up to my bank account being cleaned out.
My family being targeted and assassinated.
Really, I want to get off.
I like it for reading your guys' comments and I read all of them.
And then I like it for bragging about my career to my enemies as well.
Right.
I have no use.
I'm still not on it.
Right.
I can't stand to look at people even digitally anymore.
So I'm off of all social media.
Sure.
What's going on, Pat?
How was your day today?
My day was good.
As I said, there was a lot of nerve diarrhea.
A lot of pacing.
I don't understand.
I like performing.
But this is why I walked away from the spotlight when I was at the top.
You know, less like a Destiny's Child.
They were like this, this can't sustain itself.
I was the same way.
Pat backstage, much like in bookie nights, stared into the mirror for a good 10 minutes.
Calling himself a star.
With his dick out.
I figure we're there.
We've become very close.
This is so much nicer than our usual setup.
Usually I am looking down Joe's billowing Gymshoes.
Or watching his dog defecate on the carpet.
This is a really nice setup.
Beautiful.
I love the toe of my ribs.
Thank you for hosting our first ever watching.
Thank you.
Before I go much further, Joe,
I'd like to get on with the show.
And at the same time, on with the
Joe, my mom, I'm in fear for my wife.
I don't know her.
I'm up the line.
The woman is going into my running.
And I'm so far from my home.
Joe, my mom, I can hear you are crying.
You're so scared and all alone.
I don't know anymore.
How did we...
The super hot, the beer is cold.
We're going to Broadway.
I don't know what the lyrics are.
So let's hit the danies.
What do we do?
How did we miss that after we actually saw sticks?
How did you not do that as the arm with the Joe?
I don't know.
I don't know. That's wild.
Pat, that's good to see you.
I watched episode four of Cool Kids today.
Did you like it?
We did.
Yeah, we just got picked up for a full season.
Pretty exciting.
I enjoyed it very much.
Thank you.
It's a fun show.
That Leslie Jordan kills me.
He's a killer.
If you're in LA, he's at a live show and no members sometimes.
It's supposed to be the filthiest thing you've ever seen.
So I'm excited to see that.
And I like the show.
You know, by today's standards.
It's pretty edgy.
You're getting away with some...
It's a joke.
But you're not wet.
The recurring joke in that episode is that Leslie Jordan's
is several people.
My son doesn't know I'm gang.
And then people laugh hysterically in his face.
That's an edgy joke.
Sure.
I won't pat you on the back.
Pat, thanks.
You're welcome.
How was your day, Joe?
I just told you.
I watched Cool Kids.
That was the sum total of your day.
That's the saddest thing I've ever heard.
When I got tons of time on my hands here.
What did I do?
I watched Cool Kids.
We got it.
And I watched...
You know my favorite joke was in there this episode.
It was Leslie Jordan.
No, I watched Cool Kids.
And then I went to a place called the Toasted Bun and had breakfast
at the counter by myself like a drifter.
And I wrote at the counter.
And then I came home and I watched Halloween H2O in my bed.
And then I made an oven pizza from home run -in.
It's home run -in.
It's apparently where they're knocking the pizzas out of the park.
Say no more.
I don't know.
It's a frozen pizza.
I ordered online.
I got it delivered.
I'm getting my groceries delivered.
I'm preparing for the point where I don't even get out of bed anymore.
So I don't have groceries delivered.
Home run -in made a pizza.
And then watched two episodes of cheers while I ate the pizza.
Okay. Very nice day.
How was the pizza?
Disgusting.
No offense to home run -in.
I mean I haven't had a frozen pizza forever.
I know Ilio's is very popular.
Disgusting.
Ilio's is dog shit.
It affects me that people like that fucking pizza.
And I'll tell you something else.
Mama Celeste stinks.
And each of your two leading brand pizzas.
This is why the fucking country is in the toilet right now.
Nobody knows quality anymore.
That's my big truth.
Yeah.
You never heard of Mama Celeste?
Not to my knowledge.
Says Abendanza on the box.
What's Abendanza?
Delicious.
Her lying fucking mouth.
Oh, Abendanza's Italian.
Or maybe it means eat.
No, that's monjet.
I don't know. It means good or something.
You make a strong point there, Joe.
So that's all I get.
Okay.
What else did I do?
Oh, I went to Vaughn's supermarket.
And I bought liquor.
Because you know, you're all invited obviously.
We're drinking with everybody after the second show today.
And the venue was kind enough to say,
you guys can just do it here.
And I said, great.
But you don't have liquor.
And they said, no, we don't sell liquor.
We sell beer and wine.
And I said, well, can I break liquor for free?
And just, can Pat and I just break free liquor and give it to people for free?
And they said, yeah, totally.
So, Pat and I don't want a shitload of liquor.
Give it to people.
I brought a lot more than Joe.
I brought maybe three times as much as Joe.
I know he's trying to kind of loop us in as one big unit.
But I brought a lot more than Joe.
You did.
I went to Vaughn's because it is the cheapest.
Sure.
Why didn't you just order it from your pizza delivery?
Because, you know, I ordered once from the one grocery store.
Now I'm afraid they know where I live.
And I've got to switch it up.
I've got to find a new service.
Sure.
I'm telling you, but pretty soon you will be the only person I ever speak to.
Via this podcast.
A lot of you.
All right.
As long as it's just that hour each week.
Yeah, I don't want more than that.
I'm pissed I got to do this right now.
Is it extra hour this week that I have to spend with you?
Do it.
Folks, what I'd like to do up top here is I know we all enjoy Joe's theme song.
Joe wrote it.
He performed it.
And we like it.
It's getting a little stale.
Am I right?
No.
Thank you.
No, I love it too, people.
But help me out with the fucking bit.
It's getting a little old.
Am I right?
That song took me minutes to write it.
Yeah, I have to do this now.
So this will clear up most of my nerves.
But I felt what our theme song was lacking.
Sorry.
It was emotion.
I thought it didn't quite paint the story of how you and I were once, you know, bitter -riding, screaming at each other on here.
Now dear friends, it didn't quite paint the full emotional picture.
I'm sorry I didn't have that foresight before we ever recorded it.
I never said it.
And I wrote the song.
But I've written a new song.
I've written a new thing song for the show.
Three people want to hear it.
Yeah.
I told you how nervous I am.
And the reception there made me doubly so.
But I'm going to do it.
Is this my call?
Yeah.
Okay.
I believe so.
I guess I'll do it there.
Thank you.
Um.
Oh.
Pat.
So those of you at home, Pat went backstage and got an acoustic guitar.
Now I've heard the song.
Hello.
Oh yeah.
And it is much in the vein of Pat's favorite band, The Gin Blossoms.
Which played non -stop as the house music tonight.
Just so everybody can see how fucking wrong you are.
I didn't know Joe was going to play all Gin Blossoms before the show.
He requested his kind of a joke.
I would have said I only really approve of the first album in a half.
We were here in some deep ghosts.
Rolled over on him immediately.
I heard a live Gin Blossoms track in the next.
And I apologize to you for that.
Okay.
So here we go.
What's the name of the song?
We'll see you in half.
I'll probably mess this up.
You see how bad my hands are shaking?
It's not great, folks.
Do you need the lyrics?
She left them over here.
I don't have a lyrics over here.
I know you're in my head.
Got it.
All right.
I think we're good.
See you in hell.
Like Larry and Balkie.
Like Keenan and Cal.
We'll see you in hell.
See you in hell.
Like Elf and the Dead on Elf.
Like Jerms and Purell.
See you in hell.
That's who the corner is.
And Joe's scary stuff.
I think I got to figure it out this week.
Joe says I'm not good enough.
Hello?
You're not.
See you, hell, see you in hell
That was awesome!
With the new theme song
That was very good.
I would have written a song too, but I didn't know we were showing off tonight.
We always were showing off.
Why don't you, uh, you want to take us for a stroll?
A stroll over to Pat's movie corner?
Yeah, I was just describing the song, sure.
It's a wonderful song.
Thank you.
Let's kick it off with the stars, born.
Okay.
I saw it.
Has anyone seen it?
Okay.
I mean, it's long.
Pressing is hell.
Um, Bradley Cooper is good.
The entire time he's doing a Sam Elliott impression.
Commonly so.
Really no different than yours or mine.
Um, he'll probably win Best Actor for doing it.
You know, we're giving it away for free, week after week.
But, what does he, you know, what does he say?
Yeah, he's like that.
Oh, yeah.
Let me touch your nose.
There's like a 10 minute scene where he's like, you know, flicking her nose, like a clitoris.
I can't think what's going on.
If you've seen it, I'm not scared.
There's a lot of nose sexuality in the film.
He's like, I got a big nose, and he's like, I love your fucking nose.
Let me suck on that nose.
And you're like, should I be watching this?
Maybe we cut this.
I can't think of one lady Gaga, John.
What is one called in a bad romance?
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
You got me in a bad romance there.
And there's a, ah, ah, blah, blah, blah.
I think that's the same song.
Yeah.
The same song?
Oh, yeah.
Now, I'm not a Rome man.
Yeah.
Okay.
Let's see one more right now.
There's a, you are beautiful.
Oh, no matter what you say.
No, that's Christina Aguilar.
Hit me, baby, one more time.
There's a Vogue.
Yeah.
That's your body.
Vogue to the music.
Bye, Sickle.
Yeah.
No, give me, I do need to hear one, what is one more lady?
Oh, yeah.
Pop, pop, pop, pop, pop.
It's my fucking bad.
Yeah.
I sing that at the poker table in Vegas.
I sit down and I'm like, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop.
It really freaks them out.
They don't know how to respond.
Oh, I'm like, I fold.
And I move to another table.
I yell.
Do you guys know the tales from the crypt episode, Cutting Cards?
Just clap if you know it.
Okay.
Because that's what I was, a few people know it.
That's what I was.
I yell lines from that episode at dealers and casinos.
They don't know what the fuck I'm talking about.
Like they'll be put in the cards out and I'll go, come on,
deal them good this time.
Guys, don't please don't yell at me.
No, it's an episode of Tales from the Crypt.
It's my favorite episode.
They're like, sir, leave.
Yeah.
I get that.
Was it a good movie?
I think, yes.
It was a good movie.
It was well made.
It's the same story they've told 50 times before.
Guy discovers a girl.
She outshines him.
He's jealous.
He drinks himself into a stupor.
That's what it's about.
Yeah.
I thought it was about.
He was like, you're not that pretty, but you got spun.
It's that too.
That's what they make it look like in the commercial.
No, that's about that as well.
And then Chipel comes in and goes, I'm worried about you.
My end.
Yeah.
I'm falling in love with these non -pretty girls.
Well, Chipel's got one scene.
I do remember from last week's episode, Joe asked if Dave Chipel played.
Lady Gaga's dad.
And was not making a joke.
But so Sam Elliott at some point shows up
in the picture as Bradley Cooper's brother.
I think, although it was very confusing.
He's his brother, even though he's 900 years older than Bradley.
And then so they keep arguing and it's like, listen.
I told you when you started in this business.
And then they keep talking.
And then finally Sam Elliott goes, you stole my voice.
So I was like, all right, they acknowledged it at least.
But clearly he was like a vocal coach on the movie, Sam Elliott.
I can't tell if that's what you just said was true or not.
It's all true.
He says you stole my voice.
I swear to God, it's a line from the movie.
Why?
Because you stole my voice.
They're yelling at each other's face.
And Bradley Cooper is doing a Sam Elliott.
That's what I came to fucking.
That's like in the, we're not the next show.
Today's movie, by the way, is Tales of Halloween.
Tales of Halloween.
We're reviewing it.
T -O -H?
Yeah.
We're reviewing the new Halloween on the next show.
But I want to reference the new Halloween right now what you just said.
That's like in the new Halloween when Jamie Lee Curtis is the doctor.
Oh, so you're the new loomist.
Right.
Oh, for fuck's sake.
By the way, the cast and actor that doesn't have the exact same voice as Donald Pleasant.
I hear it.
Anyway.
All right.
So you're going to love stars, born is that Lady Gaga's dad is played by a mystery actor.
Yeah.
Hey, you're a fucking star.
Talk about a star being born over here.
Honey, bend over.
Show me your star.
It's his daughter.
Dice wouldn't care.
Dice wouldn't.
Not the dice sign.
He's got a funny running bit where like every time they pan by and he's going,
you know Frank, he said not to have told me I was the best singer he ever heard.
He doesn't like 10 times in the movie.
He's probably going to be nominated.
Andrew Dice Clay.
Dice?
He's a great actor.
He's great in Blue Jasmine.
He is good in Blue Jasmine.
And that reminds me.
Why did you tell Woody Allen to do what he did?
I didn't think he'd go through with it.
I was just spitballing.
So was he.
Folks.
That's a terrible joke.
Conjuring images of Woody Allen spitballing with his young Asian daughter.
You don't need it.
You don't want it.
But it's there now.
Thank you for jumping in on that because I felt like I took it too far.
They're married folks.
It's fine.
They have a great relationship.
Soon ye and woods.
I see him at the dog park.
They seem very happy.
Dice.
I have a question.
Is it uncouth?
To fuck your stepdaughter.
It doesn't sound too good to me, baby.
Couth don't cook.
Who gives you fuck?
Guy.
Let's get off this.
Immediately.
I'm going to do one that I suggested we review on the pod.
You never saw it.
I don't think we're ever going to do this.
Joe, by the way, is watching a YouTube video.
It's checked out.
It's funny.
I love this angry video game.
Anyway.
This is one I suggested we do on the pod.
But you hadn't seen it.
And I'm not going to subject you to seeing it.
So I'm going to review it now.
The nun.
Okay.
The latest and stuff.
I probably wouldn't have seen the nun.
Yeah.
The latest installment in the why the fuck is it not stopped yet?
Conjuring universe.
When I era an early supporter.
Conjuring one.
Solid.
Conjuring two.
I thought slightly better.
Because it was an R -rated version of conjuring one.
Right.
After that, everything sucked.
Everything.
Well, what else did they do in the conjuring number?
Two anabels.
Okay.
The nun.
That's three.
Okay.
That's true.
All right.
More bad than good.
Yeah.
Right.
Both anabels were terrible.
I thought the nun is a fucking travesty.
It is an insult to horror fans in so many ways.
The biggest way.
Other than it not being scary.
And relying on stupid jolts and things.
You know, he's goddamn movies.
All it is is jump scares anymore.
There's no atmosphere anymore.
Every scare relies on, well, that wasn't scary.
But put the sound effect of a piano and a door slamming behind it.
That'll be scary enough.
That's like every fucking scare.
And that's all the nun is.
But what I was most offended by was I have never seen a movie
steal from another movie so shamelessly.
Which film.
So tails from the crypt demon night, which were fans of.
Yeah.
The nun lifted.
Okay.
Ready for this?
Yes.
You remember demon night, right?
I do.
Okay.
Ready for this?
So the nun is a demon.
First of all.
Right.
She needs not hold.
Hold on.
There's lots of movies about this.
Let me take you down the road.
All right.
Take me down the road.
Nun's a demon.
First of all.
Sure.
Who's got a face off with her?
Female lead character.
Okay.
Those are two similarities to demon night.
Not enough to say, hey, this was copied already.
Obviously.
You're not even getting in the courtroom with that case.
Yeah.
Let's keep going.
All right.
How do you stop this demon?
Well, you got to seal off the portal from which she came.
Getting a little closer to demon night.
How do you seal off the portal?
We just happened to have the blood of Christ.
Now we're in demon night.
What do you have the blood of Christ in?
An amulet that you wear around your neck.
This is fucking demon night now.
This is demon night.
And how does she kill the nun at the end of the movie?
With a demon night.
By secretly drinking the blood and spitting it in the demon's face.
Exactly the end of demon night.
Are the levels...
We didn't give them that big a swing.
We thought we'd stay in a party.
It's a complete fucking ripoff.
And it's a bad movie and it sucks.
But how was Moopy Goldberg as the nun?
She was great.
The musical numbers were fantastic.
I heard they were dining on it.
But yeah, it's a bad movie.
It's terrible.
I couldn't even...
I couldn't even good conscious say,
watch this just even because it'll be so bad you'll like it.
It's just the right time.
And it's good conscience.
What I say, good conscious.
That's like when you're not unconscious.
How about I slap your fucking face.
Alright, go ahead.
I mean, honestly, fine.
Couldn't we all just use a slap in the face once in a while?
We could.
Joe texted me the other day.
What did you text me?
I rattled me.
I hate...
I wrote to Pat.
An interaction with somebody on Instagram that really pissed me off.
Because every time I post something that somebody doesn't like,
the only people I get attacked by are my so -called friends on Instagram.
And this happened this way.
Weird danger, Jared Lido.
Yeah, you know.
Jerry O 'Connell.
You know what I mean?
The cast of Sliders, really.
I was going on my so -called life thing.
So my friend comes after me.
I got so mad.
And I'm like, it's always a friend.
And I text Pat.
I go, I hate everyone we know.
And he wrote back.
Sure, sure.
The only time we spoke all day.
You get me.
Yeah.
I get it.
We're drinking a little ditty about Jack and Diane.
That's funny.
The next picture I saw was called Quincy.
It was a documentary about Quincy Jones.
Oh.
Best known probably as being the father of Rashida Jones.
And nothing else.
So...
No, I think she directed it.
It was good.
You know, is anyone seeing that one?
You know, Quincy Jones is obviously a very fascinating man.
But it's just kind of intercutting his amazing accomplishments,
which they're just checking off on a list.
He produced We Are the World.
He produced Thriller.
And there's like three seconds of each major event.
And then a ten -minute segment of him going like,
man, I wish I could drink some vodka.
And they're like, you can't, Quincy.
You'll die.
And he's like, but vodka.
And he's like, no, no, no.
That's the whole movie.
Is he an alcoholic?
He's an alcoholic.
And he's not doing well health -wise.
And then he just keeps asking for alcohol, really.
And it's like I said, 98.
Let him drink.
I couldn't have could not agree more.
But he said all kinds of major health problems and stuff.
And then there's like a long thing in him doing Tai Chi with some girl.
And you know, I just don't care about anything.
And if you have a man with literally one of the most fascinating careers in all of music,
why are you devoting an hour of the documentary to him doing calisthenics and asking for vodka?
I can't get that at home.
Folks.
That's how...
Did you ever see the Elaine Strich documentary?
I did.
Yeah, it's the same thing.
It's called like one old bitch or something?
Yeah.
An old bitch in Tai Chi.
And it's the same thing.
She's like 102.
Right.
Do it her 78th Broadway show.
She's like, I can't drink.
I'm a mess.
And it's like clearly you're doing fine.
You're still on Broadway at 102.
Yeah.
Just fucking get bombed.
Have Gibson shit at this point.
Yeah.
And she dies.
But not cause of drinking.
No.
Sober she dies.
You know, I have heard that Hollywood treasure Betty White has two strong martinis every night.
And she's like 102 years old.
What's that stuff, folks?
It pickles your insides.
It keeps them strong.
I agree.
Keeps them strong.
I watched an old, well no, this is new.
I watched a TV series, a new anthology series called likely stories by Neil Gaiman on the
shutter network.
It's only four episodes, I believe.
Maybe six.
Fantastic.
It's a wonderful anthology.
You can only get it on shutter.
It's a shutter exclusive.
It's based on Neil Gaiman short stories.
He sort of cameos weirdly into each episode.
And they venture more into odd territory than straight up horror.
But there are some real like freaky elements in it.
And it's just a real, Neil Gaiman is the man.
So it's like you can't go wrong.
You're getting four or six episodes based on stories he wrote.
And it's just a fantastic anthology that I never even would have fucking known was there.
You know, on shutter.
Yeah.
It gets no, it got tells you the hood to all over the place with, you know, advertisements and stuff.
Neil Gaiman, nothing.
Where are you seeing tales from the hood to advertisements?
Buses, billboards?
I moved down to the hood recently.
That's that was a long time ago.
And I've been interning at a funeral home.
Oh, okay.
There's a lot of talk about the show.
Sure, sure.
But no, it's a really, really great anthology show.
And I feel like nobody's going to see it because it's kind of buried in the TV section of the shutter app.
No.
It's people will watch it.
But what a great title.
Like these stories.
No, you should.
You'll like it.
All right.
And they're, dude, they're like 22 minutes each.
Any stars?
No.
The baby's that.
Did you hear that?
Not the opera.
Downgraded to the Oma ribs, rafters.
It's like yelling out heckles.
The guy used to be in the opera house.
Hecklin' over and over.
Oh, my ribs.
I love all my ribs.
But, you know, the Phantom of the Opera wouldn't have a bigger venue.
You understand that.
I hope that he finds you as his inspiration after the show and he travels around stalking you.
By the way, do they serve ribs here and if not, why?
Yes.
No?
No. No ribs.
Seems to make sense.
It's laughter.
Oh, my ribs.
I know.
But, oh, my ribs.
Oh, these ribs.
Why not?
It's two on the nose.
All right.
No, no stars.
Some renowned actors from England, but it's all shot over there and done over there.
And it's very well done.
And I really highly recommend it to everybody.
All right.
Great.
Yeah.
What else you got?
I saw the Kindergarten teacher with Mags Gyllenhaal, sister of Jake.
It's good.
It was on Netflix.
I don't want to see in that picture.
Sorry, Maggie.
Better scoop up another Batman.
People ain't watching.
You're in these shit.
It was very good.
I'll never watch it again.
It was miserable.
It's on Netflix, which has now become like, they release more independent movies than the cinema.
It's absurd.
But that's kind of cool.
I mean, I've seen all kinds of great little movies that I wouldn't have left my house to go see.
I would have waited.
And it was cool.
The Kindergarten teacher is about Mags Gyllenhaal.
There's something off about her from the jump.
She's like obsessed with this little kid who's really good at poetry.
Anytime there's a movie about someone who's really good at poetry, the poem sucks.
So you don't ever believe the movie.
So they're like, wait, do you hear this poem and they keep building it up and then you hear it.
And it's like, the sun shines on my house.
My house is sunny.
And then everybody in the audience is like,
He says, I'm a dais again.
I'm a dais didn't write poetry.
No, I know.
But they reference I'm a dais a lot of them.
Wow, you sound like a fucking moron when you say it wrong.
You sound like an idiot when you say it wrong.
If you look aside, the poem's being shitty.
She's like obsessed with him and she's like, this kid's going to be a great artist.
But he doesn't have the best home life.
So she takes it upon herself to like start becoming really obsessed with nurturing him as a poet.
And you realize it's because she failed as a poet herself.
And then she starts using the kid's poems to fuck her poetry teacher even though she's married with kids.
And then at a certain point it gets way darker than that.
And she is like stealing the kid.
And then you're like, does she want to fuck the kid?
Does she want to kill the kid?
It gets very weird.
And I recommend it, although you won't like it.
It's not fun at all.
She's a really good actress.
She's a very underrated actress.
I don't think she's underrated at all.
She's overrated. I'm sick of her.
She's very celebrated.
She's a wonderful actor.
Brave actor.
I don't know why you have to say actress and define gender with it.
I don't see gender.
I think she's great.
I want to see it because I like when she plays anybody that's a little off.
She's super off.
You know?
Super off.
Yeah. I didn't like her in the Batman movies because she played too clean cut.
Yeah, I didn't care.
She had the bed really.
Why did home step out?
She didn't want to do it.
Oh, okay.
Because Tom Cruise had implanted chips in her head.
I didn't even understand.
I didn't get a lot about Scientology, but the tortilla chips in the brain.
I've always just been baffled about it.
Gives a new...
Yeah, forget it.
He's gone.
No, I realized halfway through it.
It didn't make sense.
And I'm backing out of it.
Pat, I'm going to bring us to a mutual close here with a final third thing from both of us.
Oh, okay.
That we can discuss.
Bringing us both to a mutual close sounded like we were going to have a thirtil jerk.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm going to let us close on the same third thing.
Oh, okay.
She's doing a third one.
Right.
I've done three.
You've done three?
Son of a bitch.
I was never good at math.
Go sing.
Well, no, fuck, I'm not going to...
Yeah, fuck it, I'll do it.
The scariest thing I've seen...
Oh, all week.
And that was...
Premiere of the Conor.
You're asking me to talk about an industry I work in, which is tricky, but I saw it and I'll go with you to a certain point.
We got a goddamn friend in the show.
In and on, yes.
Sarah in the scene.
Sarah G.
As I stated once on this podcast, when I got the boot from your sitcom, thanks for looking out.
But when I got the boot from Pat Show, Sarah G.
was the first one to text me and say, this sucks, fuck this.
You're great.
I love you.
Yeah.
She's wonderful.
She's not in witness protection.
I call her Sarah G.
We're on that kind of level.
Let's pick up that name, Joe.
But she's wonderful.
She's the best.
She's great on the show.
Yeah.
I loved her on the original Roseanne Incarnation, or reincarnation rather, but this show is...
I don't know if any of you haven't seen it.
Let me try to explain it.
You know when sitcoms would do...
Not a very special episode, not that.
They would do like the dark episode.
Like the family ties where all the lights are out, and they keep shining spotlights and corners.
And you're like, what the fuck, man?
And you're having nightmares about family ties all of a sudden?
Was there one with Alex P. Keaton on a stool in the dark, talking about drunk drives?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Picture of that except the whole show is those episodes.
The whole show is going to be...
I mean, Jesus Christ, this episode ends with Dan tossing and turning in bed because he can't get used to sleeping without Roseanne there.
Right.
Now, a woman that they've thrown into the streets and pissed me.
That's the weird part about the show.
That's a really weird part about the show.
Everybody's like, I love Turn.
It's like, I didn't.
You're just fired.
Yeah, with good cause, but why are you still doing this?
Everybody in the show is crying about Roseanne.
But they're crying about the fictional Roseanne.
Who's based on the real Roseanne?
Who they...
Oh, Chester!
Yeah.
I don't know, man.
It feels like Happy Days after Ron Howard left.
It's just not right.
My issue with it was that it was a drama.
It was devoid of even attempts at jokes.
And it was so much comedy is now.
They're relapsed.
The balance is so shifted that you're surprised to hear a joke in comedy nowadays.
And I didn't really get it.
They got Mary Steinberg and showing up.
I didn't sell her the pills that killed her.
She was a pill addict screaming in Goodman's face.
And I'm like, what's going on?
I just...
I can't.
I need Roseanne back on.
And I think they made a mistake by...
I understand why they fired her.
Get all that stuff.
Why did you write that tweet for her?
Let's get it out now.
I...
You don't have to answer that.
No, but I...
Look, I get why they fired her.
But leave it open ended.
Why do they have to finalize every...
Leave it like she's often an asylum for a while.
Because maybe you smooth things over eventually with Roseanne.
And she comes back to the show.
And it's the fucking show again.
This would be like if you did the Cosby show without Cosby.
And it's...
Well, I know.
Not a great example.
But that was the best one I could think of.
Let's...
Let's dig a little deeper, for example.
But me and look, it's like the Kevin Spacey hour without Kevin Spacey.
You don't get the great songs, the great jokes.
Would you...
Would you watch a Kaiser So Say movie without Kevin Spacey?
No, I wouldn't.
That's my point.
You mean like Young Sozi or something?
Old Sozi.
Somebody good I do it.
Sozi makes it out of the end.
Yeah.
All right.
My point is it's the titular character, if you will.
Yeah.
And fine.
If you don't want her to be on the show, fine.
But then you can't do the show.
It doesn't make any goddamn sense anymore.
Yeah.
You know what I mean?
You don't have to say it by the bell without Mario Lopez.
Or Zach.
Or Zach. That's a good point.
I love Laurie Metcalfe.
I don't need to see her wide eyed having a nervous breakdown about plates in the kitchen
for 15 fucking minutes of the episode.
I'm sorry.
It's just not entertaining to me.
It's depressing.
I hear you.
I don't think it'll be around too long.
I think it just felt kind of weird.
But hopefully they shake it off and move on to comedy.
I'll keep watching.
Also, is John Goodman dying?
Every line.
He's like...
Hey, sport heavy.
Well, he moves a bunch away.
Yeah, you lose weight and you sound worse.
When he used to narrate diners,
drive -ins and dives.
That's what it's called?
That was Guy Fieri.
No, no, no.
But he narrated one of those shows.
And he would be drooling describing the food.
You could hear it.
And he would be like...
You pile so delicious.
And it would just make you sit.
Like, you could hear the salivating going...
Do you putter drill?
It was just like...
It was a wet sound.
And again, I'm not lashing out at ribs.
I want to say to the orders of home my ribs.
I just use it as an example.
It's disgusting.
I watched on the Today Show this way.
I watched it later.
I wasn't watching today's show.
But they interviewed for 30 minutes
Goodman Bridges and Buscemi about
the 20 -year anniversary of Lebowski.
Oh, that's cool.
It was awesome.
I recommend looking it up to 30 -minute interview
with some idiot who keeps pointing at each of them
when he asks them a question.
It was like...
Did you like the Cohen Brothers?
It's like...
They're not on trial here.
Sitting in a booth at a restaurant.
I hate the interviewer, but everybody else is good.
The sad thing about it, though,
is they're like...
What's your favorite line?
And every time, every question,
all three of them are like...
And they can't remember anything.
So good...
They're like...
Did you ever work with the Cohen Brothers before?
Goodman's like...
Yeah, before Lebowski, I had done...
Ooh...
What's that movie called?
And they're like...
Raising Arizona...
Raising Arizona, yes.
It's like...
That's dark.
He's in all of their...
He's in all their movies, Bart and Fank and all...
Yeah.
I'll go brother or out there, etc.
Uh...
All right.
Well, I mean, it's...
We'll see where the Conners go.
I wish them well.
I'm not wishing...
I don't wish them well.
I wish you know...
Gensere G.
Dear friend.
I wish them well.
Gensere G.
Dear friend.
I wish them well.
Really dinner at HBO's camping for some reason.
Oh God, me when I talk...
Well, we've already shit on that show.
We've already shit on that show.
It's tough, man.
You get into this business.
You've got friends that just do these...
Pieces of shit,
And you can't talk about it publicly.
Except we do!
Which is why...
I'm not well liked.
Yeah.
Uh...
Pat.
Can we do some stuff?
It was Joe...
Joe dated Tervolta for a while.
When Battlefield...
The Earth came out...
I remember that being...
Particularly rough.
It was a tough move.
That hair wasn't for the movie, so he'd bring Tervolta to a party, and he'd have the
battlefield earth dredds, and it was like, oh boy, you know, we tell Joe that this relationship
isn't going to work out.
Yeah.
That was a tough time for me.
Let alone him being married.
Because I met her through Kelly Preston, who I was having in a fairy.
Yeah, sure.
Joe, why don't you take us over to whatever the hell you're, uh, column, it's called, column
segment?
No respect for me.
Let's do a little Joe's scary stuff.
I'm going to, uh, we're doing something different tonight.
I'm not, we're not going to discuss any scary stuff.
We're just going to give scary stuff away to audience members.
We each have five things to give away.
We never discussed how we were going to decide who gets them, uh, yeah, I mean, like,
I mean, let's just announce what we have, and then whoever gets the most excited gets
it.
Sure.
Within reason.
I mean, that's fine, right?
No.
No good.
I mean, I wouldn't jump up to get a prize.
I had no interest in.
So you're on your honor system.
I had no reason.
We owned all of these.
These are from our private collection, uh, these, we didn't buy these today.
Uh, this is a graphic novel called neo -nomicon written by Alan Moore.
Yeah.
I read it once.
It's of some of the HP love craft, whatever, because everybody thinks that squid monster is scary.
And uh, I read it once, and it's pretty good, uh, until the good he's giving it away.
So the main character sucks the squid monster's tick toward the end.
Really?
Yeah.
That happens.
And I thought, you know, Alan, you've been living in that cabin with those two witch wives
years for too long, uh, the, uh, but it is a good book.
Any takers on neo -nomicon?
Wow.
Again.
And this was mine.
I did own it.
Part of my private collection in the deal, I don't think.
All right.
There you go.
Excellent.
What's your name, sir?
What's your name?
Nick?
Thank you.
Enjoy it.
I am offering you two copies of poltergeist, because I have it on Blu -ray and don't need the DVDs.
Two copies.
You can take one.
You can take them both.
And it's just one is, is shittier DVDs than the other.
This is actually is covered in dust.
And, you know, how the sticker won't come off sometimes of DVDs.
It's got that sticker residue, so it might make it more valuable, I don't know.
But this is the better addition.
This and can be calls it marvelously spooky if that sweetens the deal.
Oh, sure.
There you go.
Thank you, sir.
Emily, everybody.
Well, we'll give her her due later.
Let's keep the focus here.
But thank you.
I've got a stack of prints.
These are cool.
Yeah, these are great.
These literally the only reason I'm giving these away is because I moved into a new apartment and I didn't have room to hang these up.
But I would have.
And I thought, you know, why keep them in a closet until I have.
You'll never get a bigger place than this.
Your ambition ends here.
I don't think you understand when I keep telling you how to cutting myself off from the world.
Okay.
But I didn't have room for these.
And I thought they were really cool and some higher fans should get them.
Here is a print of Edgar Allan Poe's murders in the Rue Morgue.
Very nice.
You can hang this up or sleep next to it, whatever you want to do with it.
Use it as a placement.
I don't give a shit.
It's once it's yours.
It's yours.
Just take it.
Who wants it?
There we go.
This is a dark segment.
People have flown from across the country and they're like, still no.
What do you got?
Well, I think I'm about to change this up a little bit with something truly scary.
A last man standing blank.
No.
They're my lead in at the closet.
I want city roads.
I thought you were kidding when you said you found that.
No.
I have friends that work on it.
Do they like Mr. Allen who I heard as a massive asshole?
He's supposed to be terrible.
Yeah, I bet it does.
They're not swapping any jokes out.
I'll tell you that one.
Look, I love the Fox Network.
This is a great political move on your part.
Shitting on your lead in show.
That's true.
I watched it and I'm like, why do we get notes from people?
If they're putting this on, I'll drop it.
I would.
All right.
Here's another print.
It's no home improvement, folks.
This is of the old, dark house of horror classic.
Any takers?
Yeah.
All right.
There.
These are going quick.
Enjoy it, sir.
I'm offering
a four disc collector's edition of the most boring movie ever made,
Blade Runner.
I know a lot of you love it.
Reveal yourself.
All right.
Good.
Oh my god.
Now, will you watch all four shitty versions of that terrible movie?
The two unicorn version, the two unicorn version, the note.
I think more than four on that thing.
It's like Ridley Scots.
They have Tony Scott come in and direct one.
Adam Scott directs the version.
Does his added of it, which I've heard is actually better than the others.
Scott Beo does a cut.
He directed a top of the unicorn which they have footage of on the documentary.
Not the horror.
This?
This is a movie I'm unfamiliar with, but it was just such a cool poster that I bought it.
This is a film called The Phantom Empire.
And it's just...
I'm going to say The Phantom Broadcast.
Well, it says both.
Oh, okay.
Phantom number four of The Phantom Broadcast.
So, I guess this was some sort of weird, serial science fiction thing from back in the day.
But it's just so fucking cool, the electricity going through the writing.
And, you know, these guys, whatever they're doing.
You know, cheer at typical.
I don't know.
We did bring alcohol, everybody.
I don't know what it is.
Does anybody want this?
Yeah.
Woman yelled woo.
This is the last one.
And the best one.
I have a movie frequently discussed on the show as perhaps the scariest non -horror scene certainly in all of cinema.
Well, Holland Drive.
On digital video disc.
Digital versatile disc.
Is it digital versatile or digital video disc?
Then you don't get it.
I get it.
Is it, is anyone not first?
First of all, thank you.
Don't do that.
All right.
We're good.
We have, I have one more because I brought five free show.
Okay, great.
By the way, it's in an amoeba bag.
Anyone go to amoeba on your trip?
Pretty cool, right?
How many people traveled in for this?
That don't live in California.
Wow.
Thank you very much.
How many people don't, how many people living in California but aren't in LA?
Okay.
Wow.
Al Hombre.
Serietos.
Valley Village.
Anaheim.
All right, I'm done.
This is the best one that I have.
And it's from the most famous of all the harmonies.
It's a classic.
It was remade by John Carpenter.
Not a good remake.
But this is the original.
Children of the damned.
Very cool poster.
Yeah.
Where are the eyes that paralyze?
Okay.
Deserve.
Hang it right next to your bed.
So every time you wake up that staring at you.
So Pat.
Yeah.
Our movie today.
Did you all do your homework and watch Tales of Halloween?
Okay.
Raise your hand if you liked it.
Oh my god.
So right.
Like why is it this acclaimed movie?
It's not.
It is.
Where is it acclaimed?
There was a lot of buzz about it at the Oscars last year.
But I know people love that and trick our treat.
And I've seen them both.
I think they're fine.
Trick or treat is bet much better.
Okay.
Not great.
But trick or treat solid.
You just don't kind of just don't give a fuck about anybody in it.
This got really good reviews.
Tales of Halloween.
And Brian Cox once again playing.
Does that guy play anything except a creep that potentially touches kids on his block?
Jesus Christ.
There's no potential kid touching.
He's an asshole.
He's always a prick.
Yeah.
What is that accent he's got?
Brett's British, right?
No.
That's why I asked.
What is it?
Welsh?
I think it's Welsh, yeah.
Yeah.
Anyway.
We'll see in.
He's an adaptation.
He plays Robert McKee, the script guy.
If you want to write a script.
That sounds.
That sounds like Jack Palin's.
You are my number one guy.
And I.
It's from Batman.
The original.
All right.
So Tales.
Not the original.
I guess that would be Adam West.
No, that's not the original.
The original is the 1940s.
1940s serials.
Yeah.
I own them.
All right.
Do they ever make a show?
Chose to keep those for some reason.
Do they make it into a movie?
No.
No, they were serious.
So the original would probably be the first Batman feature link movie was the Adam West film.
Which came after the TV show.
Which came after the 1940s serials.
That's all right.
That's the first film.
If you watch any documentary about the history of Batman and Cinema.
They'll start with the serials because the serials played in theaters.
Now by serials you mean like, oh, don't.
Don't.
Don't very.
Stop it.
Countshop your line.
That's what we thought.
And those are only serials.
He fought Count Chocula.
He fought the Lucky Charms Lavercon.
In my favorite, he fought Captain Crunch.
This is what it takes to write for television, everybody.
There you go.
That's how you write it.
Well, I get the big blankets.
Enjoy that, sir.
I don't like just straight alcohol.
I don't do that anymore.
You're doing it now.
All right.
She's about to get messy.
I'm feeling great.
That first...
It burned.
That first whiskey diet just hit me.
I'm smooth sailing.
This movie, see you guys know, the Towns Halloween.
It's a anthology film.
Every story centers around Halloween.
We're going to go through each story here tonight.
Yeah, I wrote the list down because there...
None of them are memorable.
No.
I mean, I'm sorry.
Like, I was like, okay, sweet tooth.
And I was thinking about it.
And I was like, okay.
Look, some of them are cooler than others.
I don't think you can get much going in 10 minutes.
That's my issue with it.
There was some I'd like to see a little longer version of, I guess.
That's my first beat for the movie.
The 10 stories.
Yeah.
The beginning of this thing, they keep...
In the credits, they announce all the stories that you're going to see.
And they keep going.
It's like some night of too many stars.
Credit opening.
How are they doing all this?
The credits went on forever.
Yeah.
That's true.
And it's also subjected to this thing that is done now in anthology,
which I don't understand where or why this started,
but every movie is directed and written by a different person or every segment.
Right.
Which leads to a complete lack of continuity through the whole thing.
You've got one that's zany, you've got one that's terribly dark,
you've got one that's sort of scary, you've got one that's goofy.
It doesn't add for some glue.
And then also they have...
I have to stop you.
It doesn't add for some glue.
It doesn't make for glue to glue everything together I meant.
It doesn't make for good connective tissue.
All right, that works.
All right.
And they did the thing that is being done.
And they might have done it first, but they're doing that they did the thing
and that's being done now in every anthology film.
I feel like that I see, which is there is a radio personality.
Adrian Barbos.
Yeah.
And in the Christmas one, it's a chatner.
In Southland, it's a different radio person out, whatever.
But I feel like that's kind of becoming hard for the course.
Yeah.
I mean, for me, even though they were all done by a different director,
they all looked the same and they all looked to me, like,
software porn without the pornography.
They were late in the same way.
They were varied, like, everything just looked boring and drab to me.
And like, it was shot on an iPhone or something.
But we can go through them one by one.
Sweet tooth is the one where this kid eats all the Halloween candy.
And this is the best one.
It was usually I liked it.
Yeah.
But you're in trouble.
If somebody told you at the top of the movie, this is the best one you're going to see.
I mean, it's not great.
No.
My biggest gripe is sweet tooth is about a demon who is a child
that died because he ate the candy out of his own stomach
because he couldn't get enough candy.
Right.
Kind of a weird thing.
Some of my cat eats.
Yeah.
Just no bottom, no end.
Just like, you'll eat this massive bowl and then be like,
yeah.
There's no satisfying.
That's how my dog is.
Yeah.
It's animals.
That's what animals are.
And then they'll be like, blah.
Yeah.
It's right back like rattling that bowl.
Like you're sitting in a pile of cat pew.
Maybe think about what you've done before demanding fourths.
You realize it's not a person, right?
Yes.
It's a cat.
I do.
It's got a brain the size of a peanut.
I know.
But it's an idiot fucking cat.
I don't know what you expect out of this thing.
And the stomach drags on the steps when it's going on stairs.
Push the bowl away.
Yeah.
So sweet tooth about a kid who turns into a demon because he dies
from eating the candy out of his own stomach when he's nine or ten.
Yet, when the demon of the kid comes back, it's a 78 year old man,
which I don't understand.
Sure.
And that pisses me off.
That's just a lack of attention to detail.
I don't know if it's the lack of attention to kids.
That's a choice they made.
It'd be scarier if it was a ten year old demon kid.
I don't think they said, though.
Hey, do you think this 74 -year guy looks like this kid and the director went,
yeah, yeah, yeah.
I think that's him.
That's exactly what they did.
That would be a lack of attention to detail.
All right.
Oh, that looks scary.
Yeah.
Yeah, but he looks 78.
Make it look like a demon kid.
Sure.
Well, then they had a 78 year old demon, a different one,
and the next one, the night Billy raised hell.
The Barry Bostwick of Spin City fame as Satan.
That was the guy from Spin City.
That's correct.
The guy that played Cameron in Ferris Bueller?
No, that's Alan Ruck.
Okay.
Barry Bostwick was the mayor.
That was the mayor from Spin City.
Yeah.
He didn't look like him.
No, he doesn't.
And Barry Bostwick auditioned for the coolest audition three times for the cool kids.
And I hope I don't even need to say, oh, he doesn't listen to this podcast.
But it looked as though he looked at 10 a .m. audition and he came in just like,
look like he had held a jug of scotch up.
I'm just gonna be like, what are you doing?
What are you doing tonight?
What are you doing on this thing?
This isn't the gossip co -op hot pit.
It's simply a goddamn Hollywood fucking minute pod.
He probably wasn't drunk.
So Barry Bostwick played Cameron in Ferris Bueller?
I honestly don't pull kidding.
I'm joking.
Folks, I look into his eyes and I'm not sure he was joking.
Remember the early days of the podcast we talked about you working on two broke girls?
Did I pretend like I didn't understand it?
It wasn't an extension of the Thor movies?
Yes.
That was a funny bet.
Yeah, I liked it.
It was a good fit.
All right.
I watched, I blocked out so much of that show.
And I, some night in...
Of what?
Spin City?
A two broke girl.
Okay.
And I was, I mean, it was a terrible time of my life.
And the other night I was going to bed.
And the end of one was on.
And here was the last joke.
This episode had my name on it, but this was not my joke.
I assure you.
It's Kat and Beth and they're sitting there.
And then the whole episode was about the Kronut craze.
And they were trying to make something that was both sweet and salty,
because they made cupcakes and shit.
Thanks, Jim.
And she goes, it's just like us.
It's sweet and salty.
She goes, I'm the sweet.
And then Kat goes, and I've been assaulted.
And then the credits roll.
On a multi -cam sitcom.
It's a crazy show of all time.
Now you've boasted to me that you were most proud of that joke.
Well, that's the problem.
When the guy who ran it, he'd rewrite your script and add jokes.
And you'd be like, this is the most racist thing I've ever seen in my life.
And you have to go around to the cast and be like, I'm sorry.
But people don't know that.
I think you write every word in your name's on a script.
Sure.
Now you've burned a bridge with him, too.
That bridge is long gone.
Long gone.
The night break.
Is the next one.
Yes.
I was going to say the night billy -raised hell was pretty good.
It was fun.
It was kind of like problem child sort of, which you know I love.
Trick.
Trick was.
What the fuck was trick about?
Trick was, that was the one where those kids are like punishing them,
because those potheds were also torturing kids in the pool house.
That's not weak and wicked.
Maybe it is.
What is trick?
Anyone know?
Third story.
I think that was it.
Oh was it.
That one made no goddamn sense.
It's like, so these people are potheds.
I tell you, I've known a lot of potheds.
I dabble at it myself, folks.
You can't be a pothed and also kill kids in the shed.
It's one or the other.
Who had that joke about?
Remember David Crosby from Crosby Stills and Nash?
Yeah, I remember.
Now, some kind of got a joke about him in the 80s.
He was like, you know what, David?
You can't be fat and a co -cat.
That's true.
The only thing I ever liked that Rob Thomas of Matchbox 20 said was he was like,
I was the only guy who got fatter on cocaine.
Yeah.
Remember there was those years of Matchbox 20 where you were like,
oh, we're like Matchbox 220.
Folks.
Very good.
I want to push you around.
Well, I will.
Try and push.
Because he's so fat.
That's what I was going to say.
I wanted to help out, but you took the whole joke for yourself.
We all love Matchbox 20.
But we can lick it.
Which one was that?
Weekend.
And those two blend together from me.
All right.
Anyone know what weekend wicked?
It wasn't a standout, clearly.
There was grim, grinning ghost where it was a whole thing about a girl being like,
am I going to see a ghost?
She doesn't for nine minutes.
And then at the 930 mark, there's a ghost.
Cool.
And that was the one with the lady from Insidious.
Yes.
Lynn Shea.
Yeah.
How the fuck did they get her into this thing?
Well, I know her as a lady from Kingpin.
How did they get her?
Did she feel no offers?
I mean, Insidious.
She's not an entrepreneur.
Insidious.
I love Lynch.
Sensitive, proud.
Insidious is a big franchise.
I wouldn't think she needed to do some short film.
All right.
Fair enough.
I mean, I don't know.
Maybe it was her kid that made it or some shit.
Well, Lynch is the sister of the former head of New Line Cinema.
Yes.
You're right.
She plays the teacher in the original nightmare on Elm Street.
Yes.
But any kids remember.
The next one is Ding Dong.
Hold on.
I was going to say real quick.
The grinning ghost?
Yeah.
Terrible.
Terrible story.
Piece of shit.
Still better than Insidious 3 and 4.
Sure.
I would say.
Honestly, I'm being honest.
I agree.
You go ahead.
Ding Dong.
I thought was the most interesting because I love Lucky McKee.
And I know I've recommended it on the podcast, but he made an amazing movie called
May.
It's Anna Ferris in a supporting role, but it's a horror with touches of comedy like a lot
of breeders on the soundtrack.
Well, I love.
I recommend that.
It's a really cool horror comedy issue.
But Ding Dong, I want the witch that wants the baby.
That's correct.
That one sucked.
I like that was good.
No, Joe.
I don't think any of these were good.
I liked that it took a swing and it felt different than the other.
It had a different visual style.
Sure.
I thought they had.
Her husband, Hansel or whatever.
That was an embarrassing performance.
That was just an embarrassing fucking performance.
This fucking thing made no sense.
No.
It made no sense.
Yeah.
It looked like the Swiss myths.
It's dressed up as like the hot chocolate.
Oh my god.
And then she was the witch.
I thought she was good.
She's in a movie that he made called the woods.
The woods?
I think the one called the woods.
I thought she was great.
And as a newly single man watching this for the podcast, I immediately.
I immediately looked her up to see if I could have some sort of Chris Guest,
Jamie Lee Curtis, meet through the agents kind of like,
has her career and life gotten bad enough?
Much like Rebecca DeMorne, who you thought you stood a chance for.
She's married anyway.
Yes.
The lady from the witch.
That's what I think that's what was keeping you guys apart.
You know, I think she probably gets just a scared lonely and this big,
crazy town as I did.
That's true.
This means war was the worst of the law.
I mean, I told Joe I liked it better the first time when it was called deck the halls.
Folks.
I mean, it's people competing over their Halloween displays in their front yard.
There's really no horror to it, and it wasn't funny.
This is what I mean about tonally.
This is what fucking happens when you let eight different guys and gals
direct and write these fucking things.
There's no goddamn connective tissue.
You said you didn't see gender.
See what?
You said you didn't see gender earlier.
But now you're dividing people into guys and gals.
But when I said gals, I meant guys.
When I said guys, I meant gals.
Because that's how I'm progressive I am.
He's good.
You're good.
All right.
This means war.
Now, here's what's kind of interesting and it didn't work out.
I tried to get Dana Gould down here tonight as our first ever live guest.
Along with Jennifer Runyon from Ghostbusters, Jennifer was very kind.
And she was doing a signing and some convention down to the airport.
She's like, I can't make it.
And she was very bummed that she couldn't be here.
But she was really great.
Never heard back from Dana.
But I'm glad we didn't because I was like, how are we going to have Dana on?
And then shit on.
Yeah.
Well, if it was Sarah, I guarantee you would have been like, it was a great day.
Well, clearly the standout of the bunge.
Did you just slip into a little Dana Carvey, George H.
It was great, Dana.
I think I heard the Dana.
Real good.
Loved it.
Now, remember when Wayne's World 2 has some, I just remember when you watched it the other day.
Well, I love both of them, of course.
But Kim Basin goes, she goes, take me, Garth.
And he goes, take you where?
I'm a little on gas and you need to jack it.
That was fun.
Pretty funny.
I love the Wayne's World movies.
My favorite.
Yeah, they're great.
My favorite Dana Carvey thing though is the Regis filming.
Sure.
Impression.
It's the greatest thing.
Yeah.
When she goes, he goes, Kathy just had a baby.
What did you name it?
She goes Cody.
He goes, Cody, a great name.
If you're a pony.
Did I tell this room my Regis?
Did I tell the Regis story ever on the podcast?
I like that I can ask now so I'm not repeating myself.
I worked at Blockbuster.
Again, not bragging.
I got out.
When I got out there was a bird, like a big pigeon type bird,
eating human vomit.
And I was like, Jesus Christ.
And I decided that day I need to get out of Missouri.
And I went in and opened the store.
I was a manager.
Again, I'm not trying to break.
And I turned on the TV.
You opened the store at 9 a .m. to open at 10.
And they had Regis and Kathy Lee at the time on.
I'm watching it.
I'm kind of like putting tapes on the shelf
and hearing it in the background.
And then Matthew McConaughey came out.
And Regis goes, he decided he was just one of them.
Oh, I think he meant it.
I tuned out for a second.
I thought he meant he came into Blockbuster.
No, no, no, no, no.
I was like holy shit.
He had to risk it.
So McConaughey comes out.
And then Regis is sitting and looking at him like this.
And McConaughey is kind of weirded out.
And then he goes, take a look at hey, hey, McConaughey.
Would you take a look at hey, hey, McConaughey.
This man is beautiful.
Take a look at hey, hey, McConaughey.
He does it 50 times.
And you see McConaughey getting very agitated.
And he's a cool guy.
But he was like, I want to talk about the movie.
So then Regis keeps shooting at him.
And it got very tense.
And then I was like sitting on the floor watching this.
And it built to a point where they clearly didn't like each other.
And McConaughey is talking about the movie called
The Wedding Planner with Jennifer Lopez.
Remember when we thought he was done?
That's when we were like this.
McConaughey guys finished.
Yeah, but Regis is like, tell us about The Wedding Planner.
What's it about?
And he goes, well, you know, when the movie starts,
I'm about to marry this woman that's just completely wrong for me.
And Regis interrupts him and goes,
not if The Wedding Planner's got something to say about it.
Just shitting on the movie.
And I loved Regis from that on.
Anyway, we need to get through this.
For the 31st is the most embarrassing with the alien.
What the fuck was that?
Oh my god.
Just bad special effects, bad comedy.
Too many things going on.
It had Jason kind of from Friday the 13th,
fighting an alien who says,
twig or tweed.
It was, it was, it was dark.
I almost didn't get through the movie at that point.
Yeah.
That point was like this when the second finger gets into your asshole.
And I was like, you know,
I said I wanted to try this,
but it's, it's going too far.
Yeah.
Sure.
At least trim the nails.
Yeah.
Tuffs.
Speaking of ransom of rusty wrecks.
I don't know.
Ransom of rusty wrecks, they steal like a freak kid.
Is that appropriate?
Freak kid?
Yeah.
He's like a monster kid.
He was a monster.
That one is actually not that bad.
And I am a big fan of Sam Whitworth.
John Landis played the dad, which was kind of cool.
Terrible performance.
And the man killed a Vietnamese family in 1983.
But it was good to see him working again.
I've told this, I read a book about it.
I'm very well versed.
He did kill a family.
I've told his relentless pursuit of success.
And Spielberg backed him up if this book's to be believed.
But you just keep seeing Warhorse, don't you?
I told the Thriller story on the podcast before, right?
When I was watching the making of Thriller with my mom?
Or did I not?
No.
Okay, great.
I was watching the making of Thriller with my mom.
I'm like six.
Yeah.
I love Michael Jackson obsessed with this thing.
Sure.
Watch the making of.
And there's a part where they're interviewing John Landis
who directed Thriller.
And he goes, I got a call to do it.
But my family and I were up in Canada for some reason.
I can't remember why.
My mom goes, because you murdered somebody in son of a bitch.
I know.
Yeah.
But, um, ransom a restaurant, little fun movie,
fact trivia, whatever you want to call it.
Sam Whitworth who was also in the mist plays the...
Love the mist.
The Army kid in the mist.
He does all the voices.
That was the story of the founder of Sierra Mist, correct?
Yes.
Sort of like that.
And Michael Keaton played in my belief.
Yeah.
What a bastard.
And he was like, I want Mountain Dew, but I want it to be
Fizzier.
That was the trail around me.
And America agreed.
He does a lot of the voices for the Star Wars animated stuff.
He did the voice of Darth Maul and Solo, actually.
There's a lot of Star.
And so, Sam Whitworth is okay in my book.
All right.
The last one was from the guy who did the descent.
Neil Marshall.
I was offended by this one.
This one was so eating people.
He was fucking stupid.
I was like, what is happening right now?
I think I liked it more because I love the descent.
I know that guy is a good director.
But...
And I thought the pumpkin running around eating people
there was something kind of funny and stupid about it.
It felt like critters or ghoulies or something.
But, yeah, none of these were good.
For sure.
So, two hogs down.
Two hogs.
Way down.
Three.
Damn.
Guys, we've got about 10 minutes left here before we have to stop
to do the next show.
How many are coming to the next show?
Oh, boy.
Great.
It's way more than I thought it was going to be.
You're going to have to really think of some other shit.
We would have to think of other shit.
Yeah.
I know other shit preparing for.
I'm also good off the cuff.
Joe, everything Joe said the night he wrote earlier.
Every single word he said was written earlier and memorized.
That's not true.
It is true.
Right?
When you said that just now, I saw it backstage.
That's not true.
And you wrote two times next to it.
I wrote it three days ago.
Wasn't it?
No.
We wanted to do a Q &A.
Yes, please.
If anybody wants to do a live Q &A,
if you don't want to, don't worry about it.
I'm going to call on the first.
Let's get a hand in the air.
Again, if you don't want to, don't worry.
We're not so arrogant that we're like,
here in the white shirt.
Yes.
Go regarding your activities today.
Why would you get a frozen pizza delivered?
Well, I got an excellent question.
Honestly, great way to kick it off.
Well, I'm ashamed that I missed that question.
I can explain.
Do you live here in LA?
I do.
So you're aware that nothing good exists here,
including pizza that's hot.
I had a first brother the other day.
That was great.
You're a fucking trash pig.
Shut the fuck up.
Fresh brothers, fucking disgusting.
They had it at work.
I had a piece.
It was pretty good.
I got groceries delivered.
And one of the things I was like,
oh, I'll try this $10 frozen pizza.
That's pretty much the top of the heap.
When it comes to frozen pizza prices.
And I was wrong.
But I got other shit delivered, too.
I got some chicken broth and orange juice.
Joe and I had a romantic Italian dinner last night.
And Joe was telling the waitress about how he prepares meals
with chicken broth.
They went on for like 20 minutes.
She liked it.
I don't know.
Next cue.
Yes, sir.
You guys ever do the hallway more nights of the interval?
Yes.
I haven't.
I have.
I've done the haunted hair riding River Park,
which is sort of the age of six to eight kind of.
But it's fun.
I took my mom.
I took my mom to Halloween hard nights when she was visiting.
My mom has some mobility issues.
We got to do a lot of moving.
She's got to get a wheelchair.
She can't walk for long periods of time.
So we went with her and my dad and my friend Scott.
And we wheeled her through the haunted houses.
Did they take it easier on a lady?
No.
Not at all.
Just slashing in her face.
Screaming the entire time.
But she loved it.
But my mom has always been super scared of the exorcist.
Because she's Catholic.
And she's always like, you know, if you watch that kind of stuff,
it opens your mind up to the bean poset.
Like, you know, all that stuff.
And the first one we went to was the exorcist house.
And like, she fucking loved it.
It was cool.
It was fun.
Have you been doing it?
It's great, right?
There's a trick or trick and make it happen.
Maybe it's based on like that.
That's pretty cool.
Well, do people not, like, do you have to know anything
about the movie to enjoy the thing?
I know with people that they're not CNN and they thought it was cool.
All right.
We were laughing.
My friend, Pinkstone, who I mentioned frequently on the podcast,
we were laughing because he was, he's a big Rick and Morty fan.
He was talking about they did it at Nightmare on Illustrate Rev episode.
We're Freddy's chasing them and he keeps saying bitch.
And they, in the Rick and Morty, like this guy really says bitch a lot.
You know?
And Jim called me and he's like, I never realized it.
He says it so much.
And I was like, yeah, you're right.
And then I called him because the year I went to Halloween,
or whatever the fuck.
They had a Freddy versus Jason Mays.
And the first thing you hear when you walk it is welcome to my Nightmare bitch.
He's like, dude, he does it in the maze.
Yeah.
To me.
Beyond the child murdering, beyond the tormenting people in their nightmares,
I always hated the misogyny.
I thought that was his worst quality.
Yes.
Get ready for him to be on the Goldbergs.
Anyway.
I am ready.
Anybody else?
Do I?
No.
It's funny when you go on a man's radio show that he's had for eight years
and call him a content front of his entire audience.
You're not invited back.
We haven't spoken.
But here's the best part.
So don't quit shaking your leg.
Sorry.
During the argument we had, if anybody heard it, we started arguing about Atlanta
and he was being really condescending and he goes, I got it all the time!
Like that.
Which became a drop on the Jim and Sam show and on the bonfire with Jay and Dan Soder.
I was doing it four times.
Yeah.
Right after I left there, I went to China and Japan and do shows
and I went to Atlanta to record my new record, which I'm giving exclusively to Sirius XM.
And they were like, what's it called?
And I was like, it's called I go to Atlanta all the time.
And I thought Sirius was going to be like, come on, dude.
Like, please, don't, just don't.
And they were like, that's fucking hilarious.
Right.
So don't be out soon.
Yeah.
Anyone else?
Yes sir.
Do you guys have a pattern of how we navigate through when we don't need to go at the same section first?
Then you go to the next section or at the same time?
We always dovetail immediately.
And it's never even discussed.
We just go to different sections.
I think the drive there is enough time together for us and then a little spacing out.
Joe usually goes to rap first, I go to rock and then we make a trade.
Sometimes we'll hit the DVD upstairs together.
That's sort of the dessert.
Joe always goes there.
I mean, to me, they're, in a world where Amazon exists and I know Amazon has a lot of problems,
their prices are way too high.
They're buying back prices are also way too low.
I've given them new albums.
They're like 60 cents.
Vince, Vince Avril says it's all who you get.
And I agree with you.
It is.
Because one time I went in there with so much shit and I got like $28 or something.
Right.
And I was like, come on.
Another time I went in with three things.
A lady's like, well, 63 bucks or whatever.
What the fuck is going on in this place?
Right.
Well, you had a hotel room key in your bag that you slept to.
I remember.
Yeah.
And I winked.
Here's the good part about me, though.
Even though you're right about the prices and the buy back rates,
you'll find shit in there that's like out of print.
That is so fucking cheap.
Oh, yeah.
I mean, I found vinyl in there.
The prices are second to none.
I love that place.
Where do you start, sir?
I'm 45.
Nice.
Okay.
I just want to hear you talk again.
You have a commanding voice.
I like it, sir.
Congrats.
I love.
My voice sucks.
I love upstairs into me, but that is far in a way.
I can't bring myself to purchase any DVD or Blu -ray in there.
It's so over, right.
Market value.
Yeah.
Like, you know, season one of suits and it's like $38.
Look, I wouldn't take suits free.
But where you get off of this $38.
And VHS copying all of us?
We had time for one more question if anybody has one.
Great.
Yes, sir.
Is that Mississippi grind?
Yes, I've seen Mississippi grind.
You mean because I like to gamble?
Yeah, I thought there was a pretty good movie.
It is a...
It is very similar to California's split with Elliott Gould,
which is a Robert Altman movie, I believe.
In many ways, too similar.
And that's a better movie, but I thought Mississippi grind was great.
That is Mendelssohn, right?
Mm -hmm.
And Rand Reynolds.
I always like Reynolds.
California's split is also quite similar to a film called Banana Split
about a gambling chimp.
Should we go out on a high?
Yeah.
I thought...
Not medium rare.
It's funny to picture a chimp playing cards.
I don't know if nobody is arguing.
Obviously.
Ladies and gentlemen.
This was awesome.
Thank you so much for coming.
Before we finish, please, Emily Farns, come up here and introduce yourself.
She does it all.
She put this whole thing together.
She runs the group.
She runs the merch.
She does everything.
We're not a path without Emily.
We are very lazy.
Thank you, Emily.
Guys, thank you for being here.
We can't express our gratitude enough.
We really, really, really mean that from the bottom of our hearts.
And we'll see some of you at the next show.
And hopefully, we'll see all of you at the after party.
Like, please, if you're not safe at the next show, come back and drink with us.
Don't be a fuckup.
You know what I mean?
Like, come on.
Just do it.
Yeah, it'll be here.
And also, this is, we completely missed it.
But it was our hundredth episode, like two weeks ago.
Oh, yeah.
A celebration of that.
That's another thing Emily pointed out to us.
That we didn't know.
That we missed it.
Cheers, everybody.
We'll see you next time.
We'll see you in half.