Folks, it's We'll See You in Hell, Pat Walsh and Joe DeRosa back to talk about
a movie and that movie is Pat.
Do you want to tell the good people?
Yes.
Even though for the second time around, the name bothers me.
Uh, we're talking about the equalizer three and the missed opportunity to
not call these things the sequel.
Uh, it upsets me.
I'm going to be real with you.
It upsets me a lot.
And have you said yet the three equalizer because that Joe, take it away.
Yeah, the three, if they had called this equalizer, I mean, part two, if they
had called it the sequel, they would absolutely need to call this the three
equalizer and they didn't do it.
And I think I might have chose not to do it.
I think I might've said on this show, I am, I am jaw on the ground shocked
that the second E in equalizer is not the number three.
That's insane.
You are leaving money on the table.
You're leaving money on the table.
That's all I'm going to say.
I am very excited to talk about the equalizer three.
We'll get to it.
Um, but why don't we, why don't we new one they're doing with that, with the
let, with the number instead of a letter and, and question was seven with the
weird, uh, number seven as the V was that the originator?
I, not only do I think the first time I saw it, not only do I
think it was the originator, it was a balls to the wall originator.
That the number seven doesn't even come close to a V.
And that is what I'm saying to you.
You have to turn it on its side to even make it work.
Yeah, they didn't, uh, I'm impressed.
They, I, whoever did that in marketing when they pitched that, that's a,
that's one of those classics, you know, the, the, the president of the company
goes, it's you crazy son of a bitch.
It's so crazy.
It might just work.
The slow clap at the end of the boardroom table starts up.
Everybody stands up.
Right.
Uh, the rest of you were fired.
Fires the entire board.
Get the fuck out.
Uh, expendables has a four in place of the A which is kind of works, I guess.
That's close enough.
I'll accept that.
The old school four is, is basically an A without the left leg.
Like I'll take it.
It, uh, that movie bombed hard this weekend.
I, you know, what I found weird is that half the posters have the whole list of
people and at first it was like a who's who now I only recognize half the names.
But then there are some posters where it says Statham Stallone expendables for.
And I'm like, we're giving Statham top billing.
Oh, he's from the very beginning of, um, publicity.
They, they made it kind of clear that Statham has kind of taken the reins now.
And he's like the new, new guy.
Okay.
All right.
Yeah.
He's the new, and, and the first trailer makes that very evident that he is like
got to lead the mission and whatever, but I agree it's the, the whole charm of it
was that a younger guy wasn't the main guy, but now I guess Statham's getting
old enough that they're like, you take this dude, take this into your sixties.
And you know, and then the guys from the original expendables can come over to
our coffee breath, uh, old folks, home, caper comedy that we want to do.
I would love that.
And I got to tell you, I love nothing.
Well, nothing more is a slight exaggeration, but I truly do enjoy
Stallone in a tried and true comedy.
Like when it's, when it's actually good.
Yeah.
I mean, that's, that's crazily rare, but yeah, I actually don't hate Oscar.
Even though it's widely despised, it's not bad.
It's John Landis.
It got, I think it got some unfair hate.
10 years later, Oscar would have been like the fifth Adam Sandler movie.
You know what I mean?
It would have just been, and everybody would have been like, yeah, it's funny.
Um, Oscar that was really in that period where it was like, it was
really cool to hate on Stallone.
Uh, you know, so who knows, uh, it's a great cast.
I mean, it's every, every great Italian actor.
It's an early Tomei, you know, it's got everything you want.
It's not, it's not a great movie, but, uh, it's better than
stopping for my mom will shoot.
That, uh, SNL sketch where he's dying, but no, Norm McDonald is in like the
fatal almost fatal car crash and he's dying and Stallone just happens to
be there to help him and all Norm McDonald is doing is referencing his
bad movies.
Have you ever seen that?
You know, it rings a bell and I must've, but I don't know.
He's like, Norm McDonald's like, Oh God, I can't believe this.
I can't believe this.
And so on.
It's like, what, what, that you could die.
And he's like, no, that I'm being rescued by the star of Oscar.
Yeah.
No, I saw that.
And then the funniest one is he goes to move them and he goes, stop, stop,
stop it.
I want you to take me to the news psycho.
Cause you got some big news here.
Yeah.
I mean, it's not, uh, not hilarious, but the strike ended last night at around.
You know, 8 PM or something.
Um, it's the weirdest thing.
And I'm so disgusted with this business overall, as is everyone, but it's
like the strike went 150 days.
Basically.
We're talking about four ish five ish months.
Then on Friday, they meet after not having met for months, weeks at least.
And they go, we've got to get this done by Yom Kippur.
Yom Kippur is midnight Sunday to midnight Monday.
It's 24 hours.
It's a ridiculous deadline.
So they worked on this all day Saturday and they came in and worked on it
Sunday and then all the writers start going, I think they're actually
going to finish this.
These are, these are billionaires working on Sunday.
I think they actually have the plan to get this done.
So they did it.
And you know, we're still waiting to see the deal points.
The writers guild is like, it's an excellent deal.
Uh, they know it's gotta be, or people will be pissed.
They're going to send out the results shortly this week and we'll all vote.
Could take another three months to finalize the contract, but the strike is
done essentially unless there's an issue.
Um, so it's great news.
It's just kind of like, why did they suddenly decide we've got to work all
weekend and get this done and where was that urgency over the last four to five
months?
These are the big questions that will never get answered, but, um, can't
complain, can't look a gift horse in the mouth.
If we got a good deal, I'm happy.
I'll probably go into Atlanta shortly.
Getting some money in my pocket shortly.
They didn't reveal the deals, the details of the deal.
They didn't.
The, uh, the letter from the guild last night was like, we're dotting the
eyes and crossing the T's or in Wayne's world to the lowercase J's.
Um, and that's it.
It's it's, um, there's no chance that when it comes out, we would all be
like, no, this doesn't work.
We're not accepting it.
I smell her.
Things could go awry.
Things could absolutely go awry.
Here's why I smell a rat.
Yeah.
We're going to, we're going to say we have to get this deal in by Yom Kippur to,
as, as, as you already said, as a sign of urgent, a gesture of urgency.
Yeah.
Also, given the large percentage of Jewish people in the entertainment
business, it's saying we're trying to, you know, you can relate to this.
We want to get this done by a, by a very special day for all of us.
I get that.
Yes.
But here's where I smell the rat.
Don't release.
Now we can't release the details because it's Yom Kippur.
Give everybody 24 hours to be excited that we signed a deal, cool off.
And then on Tuesday we dropped the bomb of here's what we compromised on.
Yeah, you could be right.
You could certainly be right.
Who knows?
I think what, what the guild's lawyers are doing now is making sure that it's
airtight and that there aren't loopholes because the last time we did this, there
were, there were, and there will be this time too.
That's what these people do is try to phrase things in such a way that you
don't notice that you're getting buttfucked, but we shall see it's a, I'm,
I'm tentatively celebrating and what I will not be is like, I'm seeing some
friends later on tonight.
I will not be the one guy who stands in the corner with his arms folded while
everybody's celebrating and it's like, go ahead, have your fun, but I don't think
it's, you know, nobody likes that guy.
You gotta be a, you gotta be the guy.
No, you gotta be brother Baines in Malcolm X when all the, uh, when they're
in prison and all the black inmates are celebrating by playing baseball that
Jackie Robinson was led into the league and then brother Baines, the one guy
going, they let one of us through when we're supposed to make up for 200 years
of a project, you gotta be that guy with the writer's guild now.
Yeah, I can do that.
Have you ever seen the quick little interview clip where spike league gets
asked about green book the night of the Oscar win?
No, can imagine it's, it is so funny.
It is like, well, the Sarah, he can do it.
Well, obviously my impression is not going to be near as funny, but, um, he's
getting interviewed by these really prestigious like British, uh, interviewers
and they're like, uh, you know, spike, we, we, uh, we gotta ask, you know, we've,
we've heard you kind of speak derogatorily about our best picture winner tonight.
Did you not enjoy, uh, the film green book?
And he goes, did I enjoy green book?
And he sits there like, he's thinking for a minute, but he's got this grin on
his face and then he goes, let me put it in terms you boys would understand.
It was not my cup of tea.
And then he does like four sprints in circles, curly from the three students
style starts running around like, it's hilarious.
It's hilarious.
The night it won the, uh, the best picture.
Anyway, uh, I've got a new psycho here.
Well, congrats.
I'm in the guild as well, but you're a career writer.
So I hope it all works out.
I really do.
Um, well, you're more of an actor than I, uh, the next up is the sag after it.
Like, like, and, and the writer's guild is claiming that we are not going to
return to work until sag's deal is done because we're going to support you.
And, you know, I guess that's nice, but you better get it done fucking quick.
It's so tough with the sag thing.
I had a debate with a friend of mine the other day who does not act a lot and I
don't act that much just here and there, but he was complaining about his royalty
checks and I won't name the project or who he is because I don't want to give,
you know, I don't want to burn the guy, but I go, I go, you had one line in a seat.
What do you think you deserve for this?
Do you think you deserve to retire on this?
And he was like, yeah, God damn it.
I was like, you're crazy.
You're crazy.
That, and again, you want to talk about something I would not be saying in a
group of people only over a podcast that anyone can listen to, but it's, it's nuts.
The actors who, and most actors have one line in something or once a year or
something like that, and they're making $800 for that project and you get a
couple of residuals or whatever else, but you know, it's a tough business,
but it's the age old thing.
I was talking about this on the old, uh, solo corn.
You can't expect this industry to coddle you.
You got into this industry knowing it would be next to impossible
or else you're an idiot.
And unfortunately you have to work other jobs sometimes that like I get saying,
Hey, I'm working for four jobs a year and I can't make health insurance.
That sucks, but that amounts to four days of work.
So if you're not supplementing that income with something else, that's on you.
Yeah, it's one of the, I supplement my income with this.
I supplement it with the Amazon sales that I do every single morning.
You know, like it's a side hustle world and it's going to be for decades to come.
So you can't be complaining about not, uh, having mansion because you had a
line on the Buffy, the vampire spin -off, you know, come on.
Yeah.
It's one of the reasons I didn't go into acting or ever pursue acting full -time.
It's one of the reasons I admire full -time actors.
I'm like, man, it's a, you know, our buddy, uh, David Kremholtz, great example.
I admire what it takes to get to that point.
There are so many variables and you're at the mercy of so many other people.
I liked standup cause standup was like, Hey, I'm going to call the shots.
If the audience sucks, I'll tell them they suck.
If I kill, I get all the glory.
They pay me right after I'm done.
I leave.
Like it was pretty easy to, to see the point a to point B of that with acting.
It's like, Nope, you're going to go into a room.
You're going to audition for people.
Those people may or may not like you.
Somebody might just not like your face.
Uh, and then you're going to go through 10 rounds of that.
And then there's going to be all kinds of other stuff and stunt
casting and whatever else it's very hard, very, very hard.
So, well, yeah, I mean, when I was deciding between it, when I got out of
college, I was either going to go to Chicago and do second city, or I was
going to go to New York and try to get into writing and I was just kind of
like, Pat, you're not hot, you know, even 20 years ago, it's not like I was some
hottie and that, that requires a lot of it, or at least like a very interesting
face or something and a whole lot of luck and just the amount of hilarious and
brilliant actors I've known who have never done anything, you can be, you
look a movie, I guarantee that's probably happening out there somewhere.
Stand up on the other hand, if you are getting up there with a mic and you're
genuinely hilarious, let's say you're the funniest comic in America, you will
be found out, you will be discovered at some point, especially in a Tik Tok world.
Um, acting just isn't like that.
It's a crap shoot.
At the very least, another established comic will pick you up and take you on
the road and be like, you know, Hey, I know you started 20 years before me,
but you need to be seen, you know, like there's, there's, there's, yeah,
there's no such thing as a club where actors can do monologues and then
everybody goes, Oh, he's good, you know?
So it's tough, very tough.
Um, all right.
I got a new psycho here.
I don't know why I look at movieweb .com.
I do it and it, here's the title.
The Simpsons, Apu and 21 other problematic characters on the long -running TV show.
So off the bat, I'm like, okay.
I'm familiar with the Apu controversy.
I get it.
Five years old at this point, but all right.
Yeah.
I go, so maybe there's a bunch of other characters like that, that, that I didn't,
I'm not aware of because I don't really watch the show.
Yeah.
I'm aware of almost every character on this list because here's the list, Pat.
Okay.
First listed Apu, we're all aware.
Mo problematic character.
Why?
Cause he's a bartender?
Uh, cause he manipulates Barney's relapse.
Holy shit.
Hold on.
So they're picking one thing they did.
There's 5 million episodes of the show and they're focusing on one thing he did in one.
Yeah.
Also Mo is borderline homicidal, threatening to murder Bart every time he prank calls.
So, you know, Homer's getting it for being a abuser.
It's a cartoon.
It's fucking cartoon.
Wayland Smithers.
Closet perpetuates every bad stereotype about a personal assistance, and
notably people having trouble embracing their sexuality.
Okay.
I'll give you that one.
Mr.
Burns, but the villain of the show, Smithers doesn't perpetuate every stereotype.
He's a hilarious character.
If he wanted to come out, he would.
Um, that's what makes him compelling.
And also the Simpsons invented a lot of these stereotypes, you know?
Well, okay.
Fair enough.
Mr.
Burns, the villain of the show.
Problematic.
He's racist, homophobic, misogynistic.
Cause he's, he's the villain.
The villain.
Homer's parody, a parody of old wealth.
Homer is the character.
Homer Simpson.
Alcoholic child abuser that I get.
I don't get that one.
I mean, at this point, just say the Simpsons is problematic.
Yeah.
Like, yeah, I mean, he's your, he's your standard sitcom dad.
I mean, they're going to say the king of Queens is problematic.
You know, that's, that's ridiculous.
Side marches on this list.
Sideshow Bob for being murderous.
He's a villain.
Tries to kill children.
Yeah.
He's a villain.
Uh, principal skinner, principal skinner, all he wants is order.
All he wants is order.
Oh my God.
What is happening?
Cause what's his issue?
Cause he has contempt for his students.
Guys, we've lost.
I don't even, I can't even tell.
Okay.
I can't even, this goes on and on and on.
Ralph Wiggum's on here.
Chief Wiggum.
I can't even tell fat Tony.
Oh, the mob boss character is problematic.
I can't tell anymore which shit like this, if this is written to be like
a sort of humor piece of like, ha ha, these characters are problematic
when you think about it for multiple reasons.
Number one, nobody knows how to convey sense of humor anymore.
Number two, uh, everybody is offended by everything all the time.
And number three, people aren't good enough writers to establish
what the premise of the piece is.
You're reading a 21 paragraph piece that seems to have no comedic take on it.
So I don't think you can look at it any other way than an actual genuine list
by somebody offended by these characters.
First, first line in the piece is the characters have aged like milk.
Uh, let's start it in 1988, I believe.
I can't anymore with this shit.
Um, anyway.
Yeah.
The show's been on 30 years.
I mean that things have changed and didn't they replace a pood?
Haven't they been making concessions to this?
I don't know.
I never watched the show.
No, I think Hank is area still does it.
I think I thought he stepped down.
I mean, I haven't watched it in 15 years myself and I, and I considered
it one of my very favorite shows.
It just hit a point where I was like, yeah, I don't need to watch something
I love slowly die, you know?
Yeah.
Um, and it was never, you know, even when I check in now and I'll watch
five minutes of a new episode, it's never a disaster.
It's just more like a standard Fox comedy show and not like the genius
at once was, so I don't watch it.
That's it.
Uh, they said, um, it's I've read things also a movie web funny enough,
but that it's a, it's been a return to form and it's been, it's, it's
getting back to being good again, but I never watched it, so I don't know.
Anyway, let's go down to that corner if you want, if you want.
Yeah.
Um, I would love to start with something that really captured
my imagination yesterday, all day.
I have not been paying for the streamers because, and I actually sat down and
was going to get one the other day to watch something and I, my hand
wouldn't let me click the button.
I was like, no, fuck this.
I'm waiting.
But I had been watching six feet under and I was about halfway through and
I was starting to forget what was happening.
So I was like, I'm going to take a free trial of six feet under of HBO
max and watch it this week, finish it.
So I get the HBO max trial and they are highly touting a brand new show.
I think it started yesterday imported from the UK six seasons and it is
called naked attraction UK.
If you have HBO max, I need you to watch at least one episode of the show.
Um, here is the gist.
I watched two seasons of this thing yesterday, shamefully.
The gist is this.
There are six pods, each a different color, green, blue, whatever.
It's a British shows.
There's a British fit 40, 50 year old lady who's the host.
She welcomes the contestant.
Let's say the contestant is Joe.
Then they also, you know, they, they do, uh, it's mostly straight, but sometimes
they have gay rounds as well, but Joe looks at the six pods and he's going to
be, it's a standard dating show.
He's going to be picking the one he likes the best.
The first thing they do, meaning the show has been on about 30 seconds
at this point is they raise a platform.
And reveal to you the lower half of the six women that are in these pods.
They're completely naked.
So the pod goes up to wait to the waste revealing six bare vaginas.
Then Joe or the contestant would walk around with the host.
I eyeball to the glass, inspecting each vagina and saying what they like and
don't like about each and the contestants can fully hear them.
So they'll be like, Hey, you know, this, this vagina looks a little bit like, uh,
the burgers falling out of the bun.
If you know what I mean, uh, I like it when they pack, you know, the
vagina back more up into the body.
They're having these conversations.
This one looks a little floppy and loose to me.
They'll move on to the next one.
Just, they're discussing pubes.
Oh God, or her pubes go all the way around the back.
It looks like they connect with her, but I definitely don't want that.
Then they turn around.
They do the same thing with the women's asses.
Then they raise it all the way up to the neck.
So you're looking at a headless naked body with the tits out and they go around
and go, yeah, I just, for me, it's a big turnoff when like the right areola is
way bigger than the left and like, sorry, a woman with hairy nipples.
I can't do that.
You know, and they say it and they keep eliminating these women who then walk
over to the contestant who was fully clothed and as they get eliminated, the
two people hug.
Okay.
So there's men too.
There are men, they do it as you can imagine, you're looking at six dicks
and they go through and that was a little big for me.
They're all British.
They're almost all uncircumcised.
Many of them are, I would say disturbingly small and you're volunteering
to stand there and be criticized and it's not anonymous.
Eventually your face is revealed.
Some of these contestants are like 20, you know, so you've got to imagine
like their parents and their friends and everybody being like, dude, like
you go on there and they, and they make fun of your dick for five minutes.
Then you got to like face your peers.
How do you get a job?
I'm, I'm so fascinated by this show, but at the end, the main
contestant goes in the back, comes out completely naked because it's only fair.
And then the couple that they, you know, the couple that winds up together,
hugs and mashes their genitals up against each other.
And then they move on to the next round.
And in this day and age, I think this is the craziest show on
television to, to have on sounds.
What, what is it called again?
Naked attraction UK.
And then they show you clips of their date.
Like, well, you know, like a newlywed game or whatever that love connection
show was they go, you go on the date with them, but it is so wild in the first
season.
There is a guy standing there with a visible erection, trying to pretend
he's not once the girl comes out and she's naked in front of him.
You see him kind of get hard and they just don't mention it.
He's it's crazy.
It's absolutely crazy.
You got to at least see one episode.
It's like, it's like a Japanese game show or something where you just
can't believe what you're saying.
Check it out.
It's not good.
And it's not even really arousing.
It's just kind of like fascinating.
You'll, you'll get addicted to it.
Fair enough.
Uh, I, uh, I watched, uh, uh, well, I bought from Severin films when I was
in, uh, uh, Austin shout outs to, uh, Waterloo records, one of my favorite
place to go places to go buy physical movie media.
Uh, one of the things I grabbed while I was there was a beautiful Severin copy
release of Dracula versus Frankenstein.
Uh, just an insane movie, uh, low budget stuff, but a lot of fun directed
by Al Adamson, who is the director, uh, that I reviewed the documentary about
him, which I believe was called blood and flesh.
He's the guy that was found murdered by his contractor and put
into the cement of his house.
Uh, just insane.
Um, anyway, Al Adamson, they, I don't know, they got into some argument
and, uh, something happened, but anyway, Al Adamson is, uh, was a, one of the
great, uh, B movie directors, shoestring budget guys, uh, and Dracula versus
Frankenstein is a lot of fun.
It stars Lon Chaney Jr.
And I'm guessing one of his final roles.
He's quite bloated from alcohol at that point.
Um, who else is in it?
Uh, David, who, who, who's David, uh, married to David Cross again?
What's her name?
Um, Amber Tamblyn, Amber Tamblyn, her father's in it.
Uh, Russ Tamblyn, Russ Tamblyn, yes, he's in it.
Uh, it's a fun movie.
It's nuts.
It's low budget and it's nuts, but it's a lot of fun.
Uh, and it made me want to purchase, which I had on my watch list on Amazon
for quite some time, it made me want to purchase the Al Adamson box set.
Uh, this movie is in there along with a bunch of other movies that I'm curious
to see, and I was like, you know, that thing was like 150 bucks or something.
I should just buy it.
I go on.
Of course it is now out of print and it is going for $550 on
Amazon and 799 on eBay.
So I guess that's out.
If anybody out there that listens to this show has a copy of it that they
might want to part with, uh, I'd be interested in maybe purchasing it from
you, not for that money, but maybe for something a little closer to what you
paid, uh, but I enjoyed it.
Uh, he's one of those, it's one of the Dracula versus Frankenstein is one of
those B movies where not necessarily that it's so bad, it's good.
It's just kind of a lot of fun, kind of like the Herschel Gordon Lewis stuff.
It's just kind of wild and nuts and it's a hell of a ride.
And some of the practical gore effects in it are actually quite nice.
So, uh, I would recommend it for a fun watch.
All right.
Um, I forgot to mention that since these people all have British accents, you
get moments where a guy will be like, oh crikey, that's a nice vagina.
Uh, that Ariel is a little bit of all right in it.
That's all right.
It reminds me of when the Martin short sketch from Jiminy Glick where the
doctor is like drunk doctors or something was the sitcom.
It's like this spoof of an English sitcom.
And then one of the reviews is it's English.
So it must be smart.
Yeah, that is true.
They get a pass.
Yeah.
Um, I saw, well, Joe on your discussion last week, I saw a swamp thing
finally for the first time, Wes Craven's swamp thing.
I got the 4k, certainly not like a breath taking transfer of this thing.
I got to say, uh, and the movie will be right back on the, on the sale rack for me.
I found it very uninvolving, uh, almost dull in spots.
I thought the swamp thing character design was shit, like just had no
character to the face or the body or anything.
It just, I mean, it's, it's a, it's a guy in a suit, but it's like,
did it need to look this bad?
Like it looks worse than the 1950s creature from the black lagoon.
Um, always like Adrienne Barbeau.
This unrated version, like Joseph, that just has a couple of scenes where she's
bathing in the river with her top off.
You know, that's the difference.
But, um, yeah, it's about the only West Craven I haven't seen, I think.
And I always thought I was saving this kind of like cult classic, but
it it's, it's not a great movie.
Maybe if I had seen it in the eighties and I was a kid or something, I might've
got a kick out of it, but, um, it doesn't put its tongue far enough in its cheek
to be funny and it's not suspenseful or scary enough to be horror or a thriller.
It's just kind of a weird anomaly.
I guess I would say, uh, didn't hate it.
I just wasn't, wasn't impressed.
I saw it as a kid.
I liked it.
Disturb me greatly as a child, especially when the man turns
into the little pig creature.
Sure.
So that's when it gets fun.
That's when it gets fun is in the back half.
There's enough of that stuff in there.
You know, as I said last time, the.
Sequel return to Swan thing is a lot more fun.
The, the, the costume looks awesome.
It looks straight out of the comics.
It's got jokes.
It's kind of wild.
It, you know, the sequel is a lot bigger and different, uh, than, than that
original, but I like the original.
The original strikes me.
And I think I said this as I guess, sort of made a fun made for TV horror.
I am kind of surprised it was in theaters, but, um, uh,
and, and then Barbeau of course is wonderful.
So, uh, my last, not last, sorry.
I got, what do I got here?
I got another pair up movie, Sam and Kate.
Uh, this is a movie starring.
There's four people in this film.
Uh, Jake Hoffman, son of Dustin Hoffman, Schuller Fisk, daughter of Sissy
Spacek, Sissy Spacek and Dustin Hoffman.
These are your four leads of the film.
Uh, baby is the movie, the very independent film.
Uh, it's about a father, a single father, a widower, excuse me, uh, whose
son lives with him single that's played by Dustin and Jake and a single mother,
not because she's a widow, but because her husband left her and her daughter
Schuller Fisk and the four of them meet.
It's a lot of will, they won't they between the parents and the kids.
And it goes from there.
It is a incredibly charming film and it goes through a lot of different moods.
It starts as a straight up, just sort of indie kind of comedy.
Uh, and then it starts to get quite dramatic and, and, and romantic.
And then it really gets into like some deeper, darker emotions.
When you start to learn about the loss that these people have gone through
and why they are the way they are.
None of them are bad people, but they're all sort of just stunted
in growth in their own ways.
Uh, I really, really, really liked the movie quite a bit.
Uh, Dustin and Sissy are wonderfully charming in it.
Uh, and so are Jake and Schuller.
Uh, I've seen Schuller in a couple things, cause I remember her from
Orange County and some other stuff.
I'd never seen Jake Hoffman in anything.
I think he's great.
I don't know why he's not in more stuff.
Maybe he isn't.
I just haven't seen it.
Um, Henry Thomas is also in this as a pod head.
He's pretty funny in it.
Uh, Darren Legallo, who I love from it's always sunny and, um, he, you know, he
plays, um, uh, more God damn it.
Maureen, what's the Ponderosa.
He plays Bill Ponderosa on it's always sunny.
And then he plays, of course, the guy that the head writer in the
comeback, the asshole, uh, dad on young Sheldon.
Yes.
Which what a relief to see him play a sweet, fun, all shucks kind of dad on
young Sheldon, because I've only seen him play complete fucking assholes in
everything about a guy who's probably made 25 K and his entire acting career,
who then steps into a role that pays, you know, 4 million a year
for the rest of his life.
He's a great, he's a great actor.
I'm happy for him.
Uh, anyway, uh, you know, I don't have much more to say.
Sam and Kate, uh, is it's a, it's a newer film.
Uh, it's from 2000, I think 20 or 21.
It's pretty new.
Um, no, 2022, this is brand new.
Uh, I don't know how wide the release was, but it reminds me of a sort of,
uh, a bit of a heavier, but like a, there was a time where independent films.
You know, would sort of do that.
You've got mail kind of thing.
And they would just kind of capture some characters living in a neighborhood
together and their interactions.
And there was always a love story or whatever.
And this kind of, that this felt like that to me, it felt like a throwback.
It's also a movie that takes place.
And I don't know if they ever say exactly where it takes place.
It was shot in Georgia.
It feels very much throughout the movie, like rural Pennsylvania
or Connecticut or something like that.
I'm a sucker for stuff like that.
Schuller's character owns a bookstore and she rides her bike there every day.
It's very charming.
It's very sweet.
It's very small town life.
And something I found really interesting as a non -spiritual person, uh, the
two parent characters both go to church and there's no like commentary about that.
They just, it's Christmas time and they go to mass and it's just, I don't know.
I'm not a religious guy, so I don't look for religion in things, but like, it was
kind of a relief to see, or refreshing, I should say, to see a character who's
religious in their own way, where it's not the center of the story or there's
not some commentary on it, just like, yeah, there are people out there that
go to fucking church, different religions and stuff.
So I like salmon cake quite a bit.
I would recommend it.
Dustin Hoffman is not playing a Jewish man.
No, he plays a Catholic father who, uh, is, yeah, that's all I'll say anyway.
All right.
Uh, well, I got one more.
I saw dumb money, uh, in a sneak preview.
Uh, it is the movie of the GameStop incident that as far as I can recall,
happened a year ago, a year and a half ago.
Um, and I think there's a few movies being made about it, uh, because it's,
you know, it's a classic underdog story just with the stock market.
So it's not like you wind up pumping your fist for anyone making huge
gains in the stock market, but you know, the story it's, uh, it's young
kids or, you know, people in their early thirties who were like, Paul
Dano plays the main guy, Keith Gill.
He sees, uh, a weakness in the stock market and that people
are undervaluing GameStop.
He buys in and very quickly he's making millions and millions of dollars.
And some very wealthy people are losing a lot of money.
One of whom played by Seth Rogan.
Um, it is the kind of cast where it's really stacked, but every,
it's definitely an ensemble.
Everybody's in it kind of, um, in a supporting way, except for Dano,
I would say, but it's Paul Dano, Pete Davidson, America Ferreira,
Nick Offerman, Sebastian Stan, Vincent D 'Onofrio, always good to see him.
It's a, it's a deep bench.
You know, you're going to recognize pretty much everybody in it.
Um, it does feel like maybe it was rushed a little bit to capitalize
on how new the story is, but it's funny.
They take a comedic route, um, in a very similar way.
It's a lighter movie, but they, they, they go about, uh, a serious tech
issue, um, with a comedic style.
So it's a lot like Blackberry, I guess, in that regard with a, with a hotter cast.
And it's funny, there's good laughs in it.
Um, it's interesting.
And then the message is one we can all get behind.
It's like, if you're going to have this stock market and say that anyone
can make their way in America, um, you can't shut down people when
they start making money.
And that's what happened.
Robinhood, the big tax, uh, online website just started closing people's
accounts and not letting them make any more money.
So it's a movie about how the system is rigged.
I think with a little more finesse, it could have been an all time classic
along the lines of social network.
But as it is, it's kind of a, uh, you know, a fratty version of something
like that, the social network, it's not as deep, it's not as good, but it's
funny and I think anyone would enjoy it.
It reminded me of air where it's like, all right, that was kind of fun.
You learned a couple of things and you move on.
Uh, my, excuse me.
My last one is it's just a retread of something I've talked about.
I've watched before, but I've changed my opinion.
I started watching just shoot me again.
And I keep, I kept saying like, I must be missing something.
Why do I not think this is funny?
And I do think it's funny now.
I think I was getting stuck in the first season and the first season just
doesn't really have its footing quite yet, but as it goes, it, uh, it, uh, I
found the second season to be quite enjoyable.
I particularly enjoyed an episode called my dinner with Woody, where
the main character writes an article about a fantasy dinner with her hero,
Woody Allen, and then a guy comes, calls her and says, you're great.
This is Woody Allen.
And then it turns out to be a mental patient who thinks he's what
and it's really funny.
And then of course they do the gag at the end where the actual
Woody Allen calls and it really is him.
And he's like, he's like, I thought your piece was great.
And she's like, I told you to go get help.
I don't have time for this.
You know, uh, anyway, um, spade of course is great.
Uh, Siegel, you know, everybody on the show.
Uh, I love, um, uh, uh, for God's sakes, of course I'm blanking, no, I'm
blanking on, on, on the women's names.
And I look like a real asshole now.
Uh, I love Laura, but what's her name?
Wendy Malik.
Jesus Christ.
I really do think is the sort of sort of steals the show.
Um, it's a fun show.
Reminds me a lot of news radio.
It's not quite as funny, but it does remind me of news radio.
It's that kind of thing.
I will say this though, sitcoms, you watch a sitcom.
It makes it look like when it says some of some sitcoms, it'll be like created
by you're like, what, what did you create?
You said we're going to do a show in a magazine office.
Yeah, that's about it.
Create the characters.
Right.
Yeah, that's true.
Yeah.
So, um, and I'm sure too, that the concepts are, are, are overwrought with
details that never make it in, you know, it's like, it'll be this pilot is
impossible to write, especially if you're involved with network notes.
Um, I like just shoot me quite a bit.
I'm going to, I'm going to, I plan on trying to finish the series.
It's, it's definitely become my new go, go to sleep to it series.
Very comforting.
And Jesus Christ, talk about a show.
I mean, this thing's got like a 80 % or something on rotten tomatoes.
You, you couldn't even come close to doing this thing now.
Yeah.
Like there's a, there's a scene where spade goes up to a model.
It's the cold open.
This is the cold open.
And he's like, Hey, how's it going?
So here's the deal.
I think you're hot.
I think you're real hot.
I think your body's even hotter.
Uh, I'd like to take you out.
I'd like to have sex with you.
After that, I'm going to brag about it and I'm going to brag some more.
After two or three minutes of hard sex, I will sleep for about eight hours.
What do you say?
And she's like, get away from me before I staple your head to the wall or whatever.
And then he walks back to his coworker and he goes, let's be in.
The cold open.
Um, I think you could do that today.
Sort of, maybe you could definitely do the first part.
You could do it on sunny.
You, you could, no way multi, no way.
Call me cat is letting you do that fucking cold open.
Sure.
That's true.
That's, um, anyway.
All right.
Our movie of today, the three equalizer, the three equalizer, uh, is the.
I would say unnecessary, but certainly welcome, uh, continuation
of the equalizer saga.
It is here.
What I liked about it best is the way it opens with, with Denzel, um, shot
in the line of duty.
Well, can I stop you?
Walsh?
I don't mean to interrupt.
Please don't interrupt, but, but don't, don't leave out what leads
to him getting the opening of this thing.
Yeah.
The Italian man.
And what do you assume is his son coming home to this estate, the sprawling
like vineyard and walking through the house and just seeing a massacre, just
men, dead bodies of men murdered in the most heinous ways you could think possible.
And then he gets to the back room where the barrels of wine are and Denzel
Washington is sitting there with a gun to his head and you realize the
good guy did all of this.
Yes.
It's a hell of a fucking opening, man.
It's a great opening.
It's a very dark, uh, opening.
He gets shot, which makes him obviously, I wondered, cause you know, Denzel's
getting up there and he's a little slower, maybe a little out of shape, whatever.
And I wondered if that's why they had him kind of taken down a peg, but it works.
It really works.
Um, because they, they, they open this in about as dark a fashion as possible
because after that massacre, then Denzel considers suicide.
It's very brief, but he's basically, you know, putting a gun to his head
and, and deciding against it.
Yeah.
Cause he gets shot.
He gets shot by the kid.
He kills the dad and then he walks outside and he sees the kid and he lets the kid,
he tells the kid like, get out of here.
The kid's like nine and the kid shoots Denzel in the back.
Which is what temporarily cripples him.
Um, and they, they set this up so beautifully.
He's sitting in that room and the two henchmen have their guns to his head.
And he's talking to himself and he's just going, they should have just let me in.
They should have just let me in.
Cause he's like, I didn't want to do this.
God damn it.
They made me do this to them.
I didn't want to do it.
And here we are.
And then that's also, by the way, in that scene, and these are my
favorite parts about this movie.
It's not the actions awesome, but the best parts are Denzel in his, like,
in his moments of being poised and how he's going to take down the enemies.
Cause he's just so slick.
And in that scene, it's so awesome when he, cause nobody can understand them.
Cause they all speak Italian, but the guy he's going to kill can understand him.
And he says, the man to my left with his finger on the trigger, put his
foot one foot too close to me.
He doesn't realize he did it yet.
You have nine seconds to decide if you want to live or die.
And then like kills everybody.
And it's fucking awesome.
But then he comes out, gets shot by the guy's son and yes, puts the gun to his
head, like, what have I become?
Like, what am I doing?
I should, the lesson here is I should have killed that kid.
Cause the kid almost just killed me.
Um, yeah.
And then he's nursed back to health by the most lovely Italian man that we
all wish we had in our lives, frankly.
Um, yeah, real Geppetto type, uh, brings them back to health.
And then it becomes a, you know, an Italian style equalizer movie.
Essentially it sets up a pretty basic plot and it's Denzel taken down people.
Now Dakota Fanning, who was his sort of child, uh, sidekick that he was
rescuing in the first one is a Jodie Foster esque, uh, FBI agent and keeping
her in the franchise, I didn't need that at all.
No, no, no, she's not in the first one.
She's man on fire.
She's not in the equalizer.
Whoa.
She's not an either equalizer.
No.
And the first one it's, it's, it's, um, I mixed them up Chloe Grace.
Moretz is the prostitute that he helps.
No, no, Dakota Fanny.
This was just a nod.
I thought this was cool stunt casting.
I was like, oh, that's cool.
They got Dakota now, like helping Denzel cause he helped her and man on fire.
That's pretty cool.
I totally mixed that up.
I thought she was all grown up and helping Denzel.
No, no, no, no.
Um, okay.
I didn't know she was a big enough star that like they would cast her in adult roles.
I didn't know she was still working like that.
I think it was literally Denzel being like, it'd be really cool if we got
Dakota fanning to play this part.
Like I've helped her.
Now she can help me, you know, like, um, uh, the rest of the cast, by the way,
outside of Dakota is it's all Italian actors.
It's nobody I'm familiar with.
Uh, is that, is that you've got nine second gimmick?
I assume that's from the series, the equalizer, the original.
I don't remember.
I never watched the show as a kid.
I was not familiar with it, but I don't run.
I don't.
So I don't know if he did the watch thing and if he was OCD like he is in these
movies, if they didn't, it's a really cool thing they added.
It's a great, it's what makes the character to me, it's the icing on the cake.
Uh, and if it was in there, then it's cool that they still did it.
But, um, he, uh, here's okay.
So you just said it becomes an Italian style movie.
So, so this movie takes place in a small town in Sicily.
Denzel as he is nursed back to health by this Geppetto man begins to fall
in love with the town, he falls in love with the people and realizes
what wonderful people they are.
He's found this salvation that he's sort of been looking for, for three movies.
This is the final one they said.
So, um, yeah, but it's the, it's the John Wick thing where I would not be
surprised if he came back, if Denzel had a couple of bombs, but what you're
describing is what I liked about it the best, the beginning and the end.
I liked that he, uh, like found peace and happiness in this Italian village.
That like, that's a nice, other than that, I think it's, it's pretty by the,
by the numbers, but I liked it.
It was very likable.
And it's, it's well, the fact that here's what I liked about it taking
place in that village, aside from the emotional thing, I liked that this,
you know, the equal, these movies are Westerns, basically the hero.
He's always in a new place.
He's always a little mysterious.
He's always got to save the people around him.
This one is the most literal of the Westerns.
He's literally in a small village or small town and he's got to save the town.
He's got to liberate the town from who?
From their version of El Guapo, the mafia that comes through and shakes them down
and is violent and tortures them and all that stuff.
It also looks to me and it's funny because I'm, I got my eye on this
Frank Nero mafia movie box set and I've never seen any of the movies, but when
I watched the trailers for them, I was like, Oh, this is like what the equalizer
three was kind of based on, right?
Like the mob is terrorizing this small town in Italy and one man's
got to stop it and all that.
So I liked this because I felt like this really was the culmination of what these
movies have been about, uh, where he is the gunslinger coming in from out of
town, who's forced to pick up the gun again.
And the bad guys in this out of the three movies are by far the most sinister.
I mean, they are f*****g vicious.
They are so unlikable and it makes when he kills them awesome.
They're pretty unlikable in the other movies too, but they are really
f*****g unlikable in this.
This is also the only one where it's one, uh, point A to point B story.
This is the most simple of the three.
The other ones, there are little side things he has to do as the equalizer
in addition to the main mission, you know, pick up groceries and yeah.
There's like a, yeah, like some frat guy assaults a woman.
He has to go murder that guy and then he has to come back and deal with the,
whatever else, you know, his main thing.
There's a Karen at the grocery store.
He's got to break her neck before he goes home.
Right.
This is the only one where it's like, no, it's all connected to the same thing.
Um, it's tight.
It's very tight.
Sure.
It's about it.
But when it went to the end where he's killing all the bad guys in the mansion,
I was like, wait, is this the end already?
All right, cool.
Um, the best scene and he's gotten at least one of these in every equalizer.
And this was my, probably my favorite that I've seen of the three.
It wasn't my favorite overall movie, but this scene, signature scene that he does
that thing in the restaurant, man, when he's like terrorizing the cop and his
wife and Denzel sitting there watching them.
And the guy's like, you got a problem?
And he goes over and he does the pressure point thing to him.
Right.
He's like, you feel that?
You feel that?
That's a three.
You don't want me to go to four.
I go to four.
You're going to shit on yourself.
You don't want that.
I don't want that.
Like those parts are, those are the best parts.
It's him.
It's like classic Denzel being classic Denzel, badass.
I go to five, you're going to shit on yourself.
Then I stick my hand on the back of your pants.
I take a big pile of your show.
Don't shit up.
And then I shove it down your throat.
You want to go to 10.
I wait for you to digest your own shit and shit out your shit.
And I make everybody that you ever dated, watch a video of it.
Yeah.
And then he goes down and that's no shit into Canada.
Winks a bell dings on the wig slide whistle and we're out.
I, um, yeah, I mean, in a, it's crazy that I think it came out this year.
The John Wick four, John Wick four is like one of these movies, whatever,
like they used to say in the eighties on steroids, you know, it's like every
action scene goes on for about 15 minutes too long.
Um, but it's so cool and so relentless that you just kind of had a good time.
We talked about John Wick on the show.
This is sort of the flip side of that.
It's the meat and potatoes version of the story, you know, not a lot of fat on
the bone, um, and the action scenes are quick, brutal, very effective story hits
its points quickly, brutally, effectively, and it's out.
Um, I like both, you know, I like the excess of the John Wick franchise.
And I like that the equalizer is just like this, you know, it's a tight,
almost like a Burt Reynolds in the, in the eighties kind of vibe.
But you've got our best actor playing this like cheesy Liam Neeson action role.
It's great.
I would watch, you know, four more of these movies for sure.
It is wild.
Well, number one, I have two things to say.
Number one, of course, the, the, the, the, they've upgraded all of these now to
4k and there's already a three movie set, 4k set on Amazon.
I've already bought the first two goddamn things on Blu ray and now
fucking Christ, it's mad.
Anyway, the four, do they call it the 4k lizer?
Nope.
See again.
Yeah.
Um, anyway, the, so, so what I was going to say about that was, and I brought
this up to you the other day, why the hell is there, how is there not a 4k
dial of destiny announced yet?
I don't understand.
This doesn't make any sense.
Well, what I was saying to Joe last night was Paramount might be on the verge of
collapse because of Indiana Jones, because of Dungeons and Dragons, because of all
their big movies are failing.
Their streaming service is failing.
Um, Viacom, as I mentioned on this show, does not even pay us residuals anymore,
even though they know that they are owed, which means they're in trouble.
So also we're in a time where, uh, Disney and other studios are like, we're almost
never going to do new 4k releases anymore or new DVD releases.
Now 4k does pretty well.
I think, is it enough to save the, um, home video industry?
I don't know.
The fact that they haven't announced Indiana Jones is very weird.
It's very weird, but I know that they are very disappointed in how that movie did
because it lost a lot.
I don't have the answer, Joe.
I know it lost a lot, but it's also Disney movie.
It's not a Paramount movie.
And that's true.
That's true.
And I just don't understand a world where the final India, they've
really, I'm going to buy the goddamn thing on digital UHD because, because
that's the only way I can get it.
Like it's crazy.
And then they're going to announce it and then I'm going to fucking
have to buy it again.
Oh, anyway.
Um, I would wait.
They will announce it.
They'll announce it by the end of this year, more than likely.
They'll have a new set with all five movies in it.
You know, it'll be this.
I actually, um, sold my Indiana Jones 4k after I watched it.
Cause I was like, you know, even though I'll probably never watch
Dial of Destiny again, I like having all the movies.
I like, I'm a completist.
Yeah, me too.
Just wait, save a little money.
What I was going to say about Denzel before we wrap up here was I was
thinking about this when we were, when I was watching the equalizer.
How amazing is it?
You just want to talk about things working out his best role, in my
opinion, in Malcolm X, uh, one of my top 10 favorite movies of all time.
How amazing is it that that came together the way it did?
How amazing is it that at the time Spike Lee is trying to
make a Malcolm X movie, Denzel Washington is there.
He's interested.
He is, he's got the chops to pull it off.
He also just by chance looks and sounds almost identical to the real
Malcolm X in an age where prosthetics and all that stuff would have not
worked and it would have made it look weird in an age where he was the
perfect age to play it, de -aging was not an option.
It's just so crazy to me that that came together in the way it did.
It's, it's, it's uncanny.
It's uncanny.
The only other actor of that time that I could think of who would have made
sense is like Morgan Freeman, but Morgan Freeman, so he is not Malcolm X.
He's so, he's not a Martin Luther King either, but he's closer to that sort of
a vibe, sort of a warm, Malcolm X was always a very hard edged, uh, person,
which is what makes him such a fascinating character, but yeah, I don't
know who else he would have got.
I'd be, I'd be curious to see who he even looked at, but since he had been
working with him, I'm sure he was like, Oh, we got to do the Malcolm X story.
As soon as he started, as soon as he met the guy problem.
Tons of people, tons of people, uh, in throughout movie history have played
Malcolm X and a lot of them have been really great, but the Denzel one, I
mean, it's just so uncanny Denzel was like in a place where it's like,
probably just walked onto set.
Where are the glasses?
Thank you.
We're ready to go.
Here we go.
It's so uncanny, uh, that that, that, that I have, I have by any means
necessary, the book, which is like Spike Lee's journal of making Malcolm X.
He wrote every day journal and it's, I have never read it.
I would love to read it and kind of hear about how it all came together.
It's supposed to be one of the great filmmaking books there is.
I've had it forever.
Folks, that's our show.
We will be back with, uh, insidious, the red door and is the
exorcist next month or no?
Yeah, the exorcist comes out.
It'll be late in the month.
It comes out like October, mid October, I think.
Let me check.
And we're also going to do a couple of special EPS, but, uh, you know, we got
you, you know, we got your EPS coming and everybody, and of course, check us out.
October 28th, Orleans grocery in New York.
You see fantastic bands, salsa, windfall.
You see me and Joe do a lot.
We'll see you in hell.
You see a lot of things much more happening.
Oh, October 6th.
It comes out believer.
So that'll probably be an October app.
Yeah.
Lots happening.
Oh, it's, what is it?
Exorcist the believer?
Yeah.
Wow.
What a weird title.
Um, also we should do the creator, which is getting reviews as like one of the
great sci -fi movies ever made.
I haven't even heard of it.
I'll look it up after, um, uh, we got, uh, I got tour dates folks.
If you're around November, well, the 28th at Orleans is Pat already plugged.
And then November 9th, I'm doing a show where I do at KGB bar in New York
or doing readings from my audio book, the penthouse papers, uh, November 11th,
the TLA in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania for a big homecoming show.
That's going to be very nice.
Uh, Pittsburgh on November 17th, Buffalo, New York, November 18th,
November 30th, Denver, December 1st, Phoenix, December 3rd, Salt Lake city.
All tickets and show information available at joderosa .com.
And, uh, and if you're in New York, come on out to Joey roses, seven days a week.
You can get all our info at Joey roses, NYC .com.
Thanks folks.
We'll see you next time.
And we'll see you in hell.