Folks, it's We'll See You in Hell, and we're back with part
two of the Q &A session, ready to rock, ready to do this. Let's
do it. Godfather two of of sequels to Q &A podcast is not
going to be the European gigolo. Yes, there you go. I'm
going to order Jersey Mike's. God, I want that badly right
now. You know, I feel like a bit of a, you know, fraud getting
that. Because, you know, I'm in like, fucking, you know, I'm in
Jersey, I should be it's like, you know, why aren't you
getting, you know, Tootie's hoagie house or whatever, you
know? Yeah. And I'm like, goddamn it, because I'd rather
just go with the thing I know I'm gonna like. Sure. You know?
Sure.
I don't know. Is that okay? I don't object. All right. Thank
you. Appreciate it. I hope it comes after we do this, because
it's gonna make me break my diet here. I see you eating. Yeah,
I'm not gonna eat on the show. I'm just gonna do a pre order to
get it here. For as well as the lettuce hanging off your mic.
Yeah, I just wanted to arrive as we're wrapping up. They do a
sandwich over at Jersey. My disgusting term. Yeah, it really
makes me sick.
Wet. Why is it called that?
Don't know.
Anyway, can't you get your own sandwiches for Oh, you're not
home. I got you.
Yeah, you want to rub it in?
How big do you think the giant is?
24 inches.
$18. It's got to be pretty big, right?
I bet it's a foot and a half 18.
All right, I'm just gonna go with the regular.
Okay.
Probably could have handled this off air.
Yeah. All right. I'm just telling you what I'm doing.
Okay, here we go. Ready?
Mm hmm. Yes.
Jeff Lebowski.
What?
Yeah, that's an interesting name. Is it there?
The Lebowski.
He asks,
if you were a dictator and could change Hollywood, what would you
change? Preferably an answer other than everything?
Yeah, I mean, that is the answer. But
I will. Here's I mean, number one is removal of
executives, you know, at you. I don't think there's anything
wrong with having one trusted executive or another pair of eyes
on it to give you notes. But we have entered this world and it's
changed so much, even in the last decade, where each step is
noted to death. And it's noted out of fear of what the person
above them will think, even though they don't know, they're
just guessing. And it adds a tremendous amount of work, you
have to go through the production company, then the
studio, then the network. Sometimes there's multiple
studios involved. There's always some actor who chimes in
on the writing process. Sometimes it's more than one
actor. That, I think more than anything else is what is is
really hurting the business. And I would say, start making
comedies again, because people need them.
I think the worst aspect of Hollywood is the media. And I
would police the media. That's how I feel. I think they're
are responsible and corporately continue to contribute to the
destruction of our culture and our love for one another, and
they're devils, and they should be stopped. There you go. Sarah
Gofflot, who are your favorite female directors? And what are
some female directed films that you would recommend? Oh, here's
a question where we could just step right in it, huh?
No, I mean, we're saying positive things. I mean, no, I'm
just kidding, though.
Yeah, I mean, for me, the female director who got the biggest
bum rap is, at least in my lifetime is probably Penelope
Spheeris, who did those amazing documentaries history, or the
decline, the decline of Western civilization about years, and
then directed one of the greatest, most influential
comedies of our generation, Wayne's World, and then was not
cast back for Wayne's World to despite Wayne's World, making
about $100 million on a $5 million budget. She also
directed Tommy Boy, correct?
No, she didn't. She directed Black Sheep, which is
Oh, that's that's what I meant. I'm sorry, Black Sheep. Yeah,
the stories David Spade has about her from Black Sheep are
pretty bad. Really? So I wonder if she, you know, I don't know.
Maybe she was maybe she I don't know. I don't know. But I agree.
She does great work. I mean,
yeah, she I mean, and then she was doing like little rascals
and stuff. And then essentially, they threw, they kicked her out.
But I mean, for me, she's a she's a great female comedy
director. There's also Tamara Dave, or is it Tamara Davis
married to a beastie boy? I'm going to look her up. See,
this is the thing she did. Billy Madison. Another great comedy
and then moved on to like, tank girl Tamara Davis. Yeah, she
doesn't direct much anymore. It's like, you know, like,
they'll let a bad male director do 10 movies, even huge budget
movies, they still do. And she just kind of got tossed out. She
did half baked Billy Madison, and then kind of off there.
I think I think she if I may counter you, I think she's a
terrible director.
For some reason, I was just thinking of comedy people, but
half baked is one of the most poorly directed films I've ever
seen. It's up there with and I think she also dirty work. I
think she also directed CB four.
Okay, yeah, that sounds right.
She's a point and shoot director, put the camera on the
tripod, just, you know, anyway,
so are a lot of those old comedies, you know, they, they're
not visually spectacular. And that's part of their charm. Mary
Lambert got a got a bad shake. I'm focusing on people who got
kicked out before their time, because she could obviously
direct a movie really well. And, you know, I think that sucks.
But my favorite female directors. Who are you gonna say
Penny Marshall did some great work? Excellent. Excellent.
Who do you got Joseph?
I can't remember anybody else's name other than who we already
said, Mom, me. Well, that's why I said this is not a problem. I
can't, you know, if somebody said, you know,
any, I don't know, it's tough. It's Hollywood's problem. I like
that's what I'm saying stuff. It's easy to say white male
directors, because it's a zillion guys. And you know, you
could wing that answer. You know what I mean? Like, you know, you
know, I like Patty.
Oh, Christ.
Patty Jenkins, Patty Jenkins, I thought Wonder Woman 84 was
terrible. But I think she's capable. And I think she's very
good. And I think that she could do much cooler stuff than
another fucking Wonder Woman movie. But that's, you know,
that's up to her. She's kind of like a Zack Snyder in the sense
that like, she's capable of doing cool stuff. I just hope she
doesn't get into the rut that he got into where he's making,
she's making these things that are inexplicable passion
projects. You know what I mean? Yes, yes. Who directed Near
Dark the same later that did Hurt Locker?
Catherine Bigelow. Catherine Bigelow also did the very
underrated Strange Days, which you can't stream rent by
anywhere for some reason. Nicole Holliff Center is an amazing
she co wrote Last Duel, but she also has done a lot of great
work, including Enough Said, which is my favorite romantic
comedy of the last 20 years with Gandolfini and Julie Louis
Dreyfus. She wrote and directed that Amy Peckroling did Fast
Times clueless, you know, I have a good one. I have a good one. I
think and I think she's unsung. And I think she, you know, as a
director, I think Bryce Dallas Howard has an amazingly bright
future. I'm watching what she's doing with a lot of the Star
Wars television stuff as director and she's fantastic.
Okay, I'd be directing some big budget action movies like an
adventure movie. She's got she's got that what it takes. And
she's great. And I don't think anybody even knows that she's
directing these things.
I didn't. Yeah. Karen Kusama did a lot of the new season of the
first season of Yellow Jackets, which is a show I really loved
on Showtime. She also did the invitation. And I think she's
got a lot of future in the horror genre if she chooses to
stay in it.
You know, there's there's the other obvious shortly nor
Efron, obviously, you know, sure.
Sophia Coppola, I haven't liked her recent stuff. But I think
Lost in Translation and Virgin Suicides are a couple of
masterpieces. There's there's many.
Oh, it's also too. We're just gonna name every female
director.
Well, better than going I don't know any I mean, we for it that
we blank on them, because so much of the director
conversation is about men. And that's the patriarchy folks.
Well, that's what I was gonna say. It's not it's not a matter
of having a greater interest in white male directors, which
leads to you being able to at least for me, you know, and I'm
assuming for you, that which leads to you being able to name
more of them. It's just because there's a million of them. You
know what I mean? Like, yes. But I was gonna say, Regina King,
I'm very excited to see which which she has in store.
I loved Lynn Ramsey. She did.
Um,
we need to wait. Well, we need to talk about Kevin is one of my
favorite movies of the last 20 years. She did that. She also
did Morbren collar. A very strong director I loved. I
didn't like Greta Gerwig's Little Women, but I thought
Lady Bird was absolutely fantastic. And it was I just
Claire Dennis. Yeah, yeah, the French director, Bo Travail, I
think is her masterpiece.
All right. Jeff Purgante asked, Who was your favorite musician
turned actor? I gotta go with Bowie. He was always just, man,
he's awesome. Just awesome. Like he's great. And then Tom
Waits to Tom Waits is my other one.
Waits is good. I love I loved Elvis and movies. I always liked
and continue to like Elvis movies, to be honest. I'll tell
you who I hope stops acting, singing and being around is
Machine Gun Kelly. I don't ever want to see this man again. And
I think he's going to be around a very long time.
Oh, I hate him. All right, Meg Dorsey asked, Pat, how is your
cat? It's still hitting on you after Heather goes to bed and
Joe, how is con con as well? He lives with my parents. He is
healthy. They love him very much. He has a dog friend there
because they have another dog named Riley. And I see him when
I visit them. And when I stay over, he sleeps with me in the
bed I sleep in in the guest room. And he's awesome. No, it
is by that, by the way, your what they they all says if I
ever got a cat. No, I didn't. I decided not to.
Yeah, I miss my cat tremendously Maz. And she gets very hurt
and standoffish when either of us leave for any period of time.
And then it takes a while for her to warm back up to you. So
when I was FaceTiming with Heather the other night, she,
you know, puts the FaceTime up for me to talk to the cat, which
would normally be like the cat meowing and being excited to see
me and so forth. And she turned her head and full body away from
me, because I have been gone for a while. That's that's cats. You
know, they're very emotional.
Meg Maz is great. She's great.
Meg tried to sneak in a second question here.
Let's hear it.
What are your
this is a half hour discussion, this one, what are your top five
page streaming services for the real horror stuff? I've got
shuttered Netflix and Hulu, not trying to drop $1 ,000 a month.
What's this? I don't know.
You got the streaming services.
That's that's all I really have. I add Amazon and a few others.
But shutter shutters, the definitely the primo horror one
for sure.
Yeah, I guess prime has the best second best horror selection. I
would say Netflix has the worst. Yeah.
Ours has a decent heart.
Who has a terrible selection of horror.
Jesse H. White Joe, what's your og rap track, you know, front to
back that you recite like a fucking mantra sometimes.
And then Pat karaoke in ill defined Eastern Macedonia, you
desperately need to get it wet.
Three ladies, four gents, zero Alf dolls. What are you singing?
Oh, I don't get the Macedonia bit. But if you mean what do I
sing? My go to is let's get it on.
Always worked for me and I perform it very well for a white
man.
My favorite rap song of all time is hit it run by run DMC. That's
my I mean, I've got a lot of favorites, but that is my number
one all time.
Oh, g jam.
And I'll rock that shit. Michael McBurnett asks, review woman in
the house across the street from the girl with Oh, maybe we will.
I don't know.
With crits Kristen Bell, I feel like it's a 10 part thing. I'm
not gonna do it do 10 parts of Kristen.
I'm not doing one part Kristen Bell, I can't stand her.
I wouldn't say I can't stand her. She's not for me. Not my
thing.
She's the female Dax Shepard. It's perfect that they're
married.
Eric Shepard has always been very kind to me.
I don't give a shit.
And I liked his chips, his directorial chips. I kind of
thought it was fun.
All right. Well, when somebody asks, who are your favorite
underrated male directors?
Say Dax Shepard. Yeah. Aaron Schwartz. What are two examples
of movies that surprised you the most one in both direction?
One that you knew was going to be great, but ended up being dog
shit. And one that you had to force yourself to watch but
ended up loving.
Well, I can say recently scream five was the was the ladder. I
was like, I gotta go see this. I have no interest in seeing it.
We're going to review it for the pod. We can't not review
scream five. And I you heard the review. I loved every second of
it. And I just was like, Wow, I was really wrong. I thought I
wasn't going to be into this. And I loved it. And I thought it
was brilliant. One that I wanted to love that ended up being dog
shit. There's so many. Yeah, for sure. Of course, again, I'm
blanking but I can't I mean, the one that made me the angriest
in the moment was inherent vice. But when I watched it again,
with my expectations adjusted, I enjoyed a lot of it. But when I
saw inherent vice the theater, I thought he had an unbroken
streak that was broken hard by that movie.
I would say a few things would top my disappointment in the
last Jedi that really hurt, especially after I love The
Force Awakens as much as I did. Richard Howenstein, do you guys
ever listen to the early episodes? Looking back, are your
memories fond of that time? I never listened to any episode of
this show. I never will. And the memories are fine. The old days
of going to the or fond excuse me going to the Cheesecake
Factory tying one on with Patty Walsh walking stood into the
movie theater. Afterwards, drinking more. Yeah, very fond
movies that time or fond memories of that time. Excuse
Yeah, I would like to add Bad Santa to to my previous
Oh, yeah, question. I hated it. But um, I do listen to them
not not often. But I listen and I laugh. And I, I don't know if
it's just loving myself or what. But I feel like we're funnier
than most fucking podcasts out there. There's just consistent
belly laughs. But then you listen to them. And I'm like,
ooh, boy, was I depressed at this period of time, you know,
and that's not always fun. But yeah, of course, fond memories,
you know, and and you also get a tour through the many LA
apartments of Jodorowsky, which is in the double digits, I
believe by the end.
The we're into the Facebook questions now. So now we're
going to be saying handles instead of like, proper names.
That's why. But just explain that. So Terry Zulli asks,
what's your favorite animated movie? I'm going to go with
Ralph Basque, Baski, whatever you say, the Lord of the Rings,
animated that he did. I love that. I think that movie is
awesome. Oh, wait, is that Ralph Baski? That's not him. That's
the guy that whoever the hell it is.
I think it is back. Yeah, the Lord of the Rings animated is
just so cool. And then second would be secretive name.
Yeah, secretive name is awesome. My my favorite animated movie
would probably be
that I've never even as a kid, never been a huge animation guy.
But I would say Toy Story three is the masterpiece and and to
have the third in a series be the best one is pretty
impressive. I really love Toy Story three.
All Matthew everything asks, why did you tell blank to do what
they did?
Hey, who can keep track anymore? They're all doing so
yeah.
Blair Mitchell 666666 asks Roseanne where you should go with
Blair Mitch project. I'm gonna I'm gonna punch up some of these
usernames. Okay.
Roseanne Barr or Rosie O'Donnell. I'm a, you know, look, I'm a
ride or die for Roseanne Barr. You know, I'm sad that it ended
the way it did. And I hope the redemption phase of her career
comes into play, you know, but you know, I think Roseanne Barr
really reshaped comedy in a way that she does not get enough
credit for that was sight unseen, like you did not see
that on television until unless you saw it in an absurd way,
like with married with children. But yeah, you know, I go I go
far and away. Roseanne, although I did used to watch Rosie
O'Donnell show after school when I was a little or not little
13, whatever. But um, yeah, Roseanne is is as good as it
gets. Those early seasons are incredible. Her stand up was
incredible. Just being a proud, loud fat lady was just not
something that was done. And she broke down all kinds of doors,
all kinds of barriers. She was deeply abused by Hollywood by
the men in her life by her family. And I feel I just, I
have bad feelings for her. I don't think of her as being some
monster. You know, she made mistakes. Don't get me wrong.
But it sucks that her entire legacy is tarnished. And, and,
yeah, but she she she's amazing. She was amazing.
Zombie Shark 1980 for the boys. What's the worst movie from your
favorite directors? I got to tell you, I'm glad you asked
this. I've tried to watch it over and over. Gangs of New
York is a terrible film. It only saw it once. It's not for
me. It looks ridiculous. It looks fake. It's he has his
Irish accent. Yes, an abortion.
Even even Daniel Day -Lewis who's who's solid in the movie, like
even he's kind of dropping his accent here and there. Yeah. The
movie just I just think it's cartoonish. Like I find it
absurd. And then I would also go with Carpenter's escape from
LA was who confusingly bad to me. I mean, I would dare say
maybe worse than Ghosts of Mars, which is saying a lot.
I mean, Ghosts of Mars is worse, for sure to me. And I watch
Gangs of New York again over silence any day of the week or
But yeah, those are mine for in terms of Scorsese. You know,
Tarantino is never really whiffed for me. I don't think
he's ever had something I would consider bad. Yeah, who is my
favorite director? I don't I don't know. It changes. It comes
and goes. You know, I really love the early works of both
Albert Brooks and James L. Brooks and James L. Brooks fell
flat in his face with that Owen Wilson one, which I don't even
remember the title of is cost like $120 million is a romantic
comedy, terrible film. And then Albert Brooks, you know, I got
to go with looking for comedy in the Muslims.
I don't hate that movie. It has enough Brooks laughs in it that
I'm not mad at it. But it is his worst movie. Yeah. Chris, Chris
Salas. Have you seen the horror movie poster on pop chart? 100
scratch off horror movie classics on one poster great for anyone
starting their horror movie journey. I haven't seen that.
That sounds very cool.
It's a yes, it's a poster. I'll check it out. I guess you
can scratch off and it tells you what to watch. That's pretty
cool. Laylon reads, which scary movie would you love to see as
limited TV series starring who and directed by? Well, I've
always wanted to see more Hellraiser and more Hellraiser
done the right way because so few of them have been. And I
think the Hellraiser series is coming out finally. So I'm
excited for that. That's that's my pick. I would have loved to
have seen a good run at creep show or a reboot of Tales from
the Dark Side, but we're not going to get it. So
yeah, it is coming out. I would I would love a good poltergeist
show, you know that there's another example of a remake that
just depressed the fucking hell out of me. But yeah, you know,
slowing slowing poltergeist down and kind of like having that
first episode end with like the first the chairs on the on the
table or something would be great. And look, if we can go
pie in the sky, why not have Stevie Spielberg do it? Sure.
Toby is dead. So sure.
I am Penske material. Joe, do you have any advice for
aspiring restaurant owners? Well, I don't own a restaurant. I
need to be clear about that. I own a bar that also serves food
and that it's an important distinction. I can't imagine
what goes into a full service restaurant. But that said, I
don't have any aspiring advice other than if you see your
opportunity and you have the means to do it, you should jump
and do it. It will be terrifying. You will have
sleepless nights. You will be worried. But it's an opportunity
that is not frequently available to most of us. Certainly not to
me. It was a risk for me as it is for most people. But I would
say the regret I would have felt had I backed out of this at any
point would be would be overwhelming. That's that's what
I would say you see the window go jump.
Yeah, I'll ask you at some point, Joe, I'm very interested
in how it works and just how you make your money and etc. Not
maybe for another night if you want to talk about on the show.
No, no, we sit down over a few whiskeys. Okay, I'll tell you
all about it. Mr. suit records. That's my buddy Mikey. That's
his record store in Lancaster, PA. Check it out. Would Pat and
Joe like to have a TV show where they hunt for ghosts, a la ghost
ventures, or would they rather produce a ghost hunt show,
starring the leads of perfect strangers? The latter 1000 %?
Yeah, I mean, I'd love to come in and guest star but if we can
have Mark Lynn and Bronson, then obviously we're doing that.
Mant white or man T white thoughts of a john thoughts on
the john Hughes film. She's having a baby doesn't seem to
get much love but I think it's great. I never saw it so I
couldn't speak to it. It's a really good film that I liked
when I was a kid and rewatched a couple years back and still
really liked it. It's it's very much a piece of with planes
trains. It's it's it's way more a drama but it's definitely that
year I think if they both come out in the same fucking year
that's why you can you can actually hear a clip from she's
having a baby. When Steve Martin's wife is back home
watching television, he that's how simultaneous they were. But
Kevin Bacon is awesome in it. Elizabeth McGovern is one of
the great underrated actresses and I love her in that movie.
She's great. And they do some kind of surreal stuff in it that
some work some doesn't. But I think it's a really interesting
step for john Hughes and I wish he had gone more in that
direction than the baby's day out Beethoven direction,
although then we wouldn't have gotten the great home alone.
Mr. Kenny Thomas asks what underrated movie would you most
like to see get a super special blu ray edition from criterion
scream factory etc. I actually answered this sort of already
when we did the deep cover review. I think juice deserves a
criterion release. I feel very strongly about that. So that's
my pick and it's and juice is not a movie I hear a lot of
people talking about.
For sure. I am pumped that Miller's Crossing is coming to
criterion and I hope against hope that that means we are
finally going to get a great in depth criterion for raising
Arizona, which is one of my favorite films of all time. That
would be my answer. The show
pictures of Jay, if you had to narrow all of your streaming
down to one app, which one would you choose based on value and
I'm going with the big the biggest and most evil of them
all Amazon Prime. I like Amazon Prime. And Amazon Prime allows
you access to IMDb TV. It's connected to shutter. Amazon
Prime all day long. They have the best deals as far as like
add ons for movie services. That's how I have stars. Amazon
Prime, baby.
Yeah, I would I found myself rarely opening Amazon Prime
because they never have anything new that I care about
or want to watch. I feel like they really struggle with making
new quality programming. But they do have an extensive back
library that I appreciate. Lately, you know, I got to give
the edge to HBO Max. And I hate to say that because they were
such a dud out the out the gate. But their television shows and
it's it's mostly you know, HBO stuff. And, and their movies,
they have a good they have a good selection of like Turner
Classic movies in there a great hub. Lately, I've been enjoying
them probably the most. That's where I go.
From J eight asks now that the Skywalker Walker saga is over
and Ghostbusters afterlife has been released. Can you think of
the next scenario where you will be beside yourself excited to
see a movie? Well, I think there's plenty more great Star
Wars coming. And if you're watching Boba Fett, my god, I
mean, the stuff they did in the last episode alone gives me such
high hopes for Star Wars in the future. And I think there's more
Ghostbusters coming too, which is exciting. But but obviously
that the answer for me will be Indiana Jones, you know, it's we
got a fifth one coming. It's a character I've loved since
childhood. And I'll be extraordinarily excited to see
the movie.
Yeah, I'll be I'll be able to sort of whip myself into
excitement for Indiana Jones. And I hope it's better than the
last one. I would say what I'm most looking forward to right
now. I mean,
it ain't much, you know, I think
what score says he's doing now with the cap DiCaprio. I read
that book killers of the flower moon, flower moon or something.
Yeah, I'll be down for that. You know, he's he's the one who
definitely still gets me pumped, no matter what it is. Whereas
like Joel Cohen doing Macbeth, I couldn't get excited about it.
And then I watched it. And I wasn't excited about it. So like
the one him and Tarantino are really the two that are always
going to get me very excited.
Nick Amber asks, What's the weirdest thing you've ever seen
on public transportation?
I mean, the weirdest probably a guy jerking off or digging in
his own ass. But you know, I gotta say the most audacious
thing I've seen are when people ask you for money, and they're
wearing brand new, pricey clothing. That's always I'm just
like, wow, this is wild.
I've seen jerking off more times than I can count on the subway.
But of course, mine, and I'm sure I told it on here before
would be when I had my headphones in, I looked across
and the lady was pointing and clearly trying to get my
attention panicked. And I turned and realized that the homeless
woman next to me had had very watery diarrhea.
She was asleep and it was sloshing up against my pant
leg like the tides with each rock of the subway would splash
me with diarrhea juice. I'm Oh, no. And well, that was the
worst for me personally. But I also real late night on the
subway going out to Astoria. This guy gets on the subway
look methed out. And he licks every available surface. He's
licked the poles, he licked the seats, and then he got off at
the next stop. And it was gross for two reasons a for him because
what the only thing gross would be looking an actual toilet seat
and then gross for everyone who comes on that subway and grabs
that pole. It stayed with me forever. And it's why I have
never touched a subway pole again, I just rock and balance
myself.
I had a friend that when he got drunk would be purposefully
pissed himself on the subway because he couldn't wait. Wow.
And then he got off at the next stop after he did it. And he
did it in short. So it went all over the floor. And I was like,
and then everybody around me was going, Did you see that the
country? Do you know that guy? He just pissed himself. And I
was trying to good friend of mine. Well, yeah, I was trying
to pretend like I didn't know him. And I was embarrassed. And
then. And then one of the guys goes, you're Joe DeRosa, right?
And I was like, Jesus Christ. Anyway, Max on wrath, do you
love Do you think the country is this question? Do you think the
country will ever heal from the Trump error? Or do you think a
succession is our next step? It won't heal this country. It was
terrible before him, it will be terrible after it will never get
better. It will only deteriorate. He was he was not a
cause of the problem. He was a symptom of the disease. That's
my
I think he pushed us further into the toilet than anyone
before. So, you know, I think he holds a lot of the blame. But I
mean, yeah, it's, I think basically, the last four years,
whatever has has made a lot of people realize how shitty things
have always been. But I think he's he's very much to blame for
where we're at now, which I don't see us getting out of in
my lifetime, certainly.
Ah, cad, man, cat, cat, caveman 19 asked what movie makes you
cry? Just as much as the first time you saw a strange question
from a guy named caveman.
Malcolm X, the end of it gets me every time. Just just it, it
really breaks me up every time I see it.
Without I, what always gets me is a last minute of the movie.
When they hit you with something at the very end, sometimes that
really catches me off guard and makes me cry for me. The big one
is about Schmidt. The ending of about Schmidt makes me weep when
I see it. The ending of planes trains makes me weep every time
I see it. And I've seen it a bunch.
grumpy old men in the hospital.
Math is to see jack lemon. And the lady asked her you family or
friend and he doesn't know how to answer it. Yes. Brutal.
Brutal. And then of course, it's a wonderful life. I have never
watched it's a wonderful life and not had to excuse myself out
of embarrassment.
Skeletor Reynolds, who are each of your favorite working
directors and or writers in horror these days? And bonus
question for Joe, if you were to dedicate a sandwich to the pod,
what would be on it?
Who are your favorites, Pat?
Favorite directors in horror? I mean, I feel like very few
directors stay in horror. I mean, everybody's doing their
little things so that they can do Ant -Man 12. But like I said, I
think Karen Kusama is one to watch. I really I wouldn't call
force majeure horror, but almost I think if that guy ever decides
to do a horror, it will be amazing. The Ruben Asland,
because I think force majeure is it feels like horror. It's like
a lot of Kubrick, like Eyes Wide Shut feels like horror, even
though it's not. I think that guys should do a horror movie.
And my favorite, which will infuriate Joe, my favorite
working horror director is Ari Aster.
Oh, for God's sakes.
My up and comer. I mean, he's stuck. He's sticking with the
genre. And I love what he does.
Let's see. He's got a new one coming out. We'll see.
It might not be horror. It's Joaquin Phoenix and the clips are
the images I've seen don't appear to be but who knows?
I ask I honestly can't answer this question. I don't know
somebody that is working, consistently directing and
writing horror. I will say I have a great appreciation for
Mick Garris, and that he is still going strong and still out there
promoting and cultivating and making things happen. And he's
still such an enthusiast. That makes me happy that there's guys
like him still out there. And so I'll say Mick Garris. And what
would be on the sandwich? Oh, boy, maybe a little sweet,
little spicy. Some hot peppers, some sweet peppers, and some
goth cheese to give it that creamy finish. Okay, you come to
us for love finish. And then hog, of course, some kind of
salami or something. Yeah, represent the hog. Insta CDR,
you have, you've had a fair amount of food discussion on the
podcast. If Pat were a guest on taste buds. What food might you
battle over? Well, we would just ask Pat, what's his favorite
food that he'd want to defend? And we would try to find a
worthy adversary? What would that be, Pat?
Well, I'd probably want to go with like a grocery store
sheet cake. I mean, that's, that to me is something that a lot of
people find disgusting. And to me is the pinnacle. I would rather
have a grocery store sheet cake than any of the world's finest
pastries, I guarantee it. Okay, so that might be it.
So we might do like sheet cake versus, you know, Klondike bar
or something like that, like two desserts you get at the
supermarket. DJ Lan Haar, I think is how you say that? Or I'm
sorry. Oh, I'm so dumb. It's Dylan. It's dy Dylan Haar.
Sorry. Would you say what would you say is your least favorite
Stephen King adaptation?
Um, you know, I mean, fucking where to begin? hearts in
Atlantis. Ooh, Dolores clayborne. I hate those ones
where I love Dolores clayborne. Watch it again. It's really
good. I don't like the ones that have nothing supernatural
happening in them. I just don't give a shit. Like I'm just I
don't care. I you know, I just don't care. You know, that's
that's me. For me. The one that popped immediately to mind is
Dreamcatcher. But it's so bad shit that I might if I watch it
again, get a kick out of it. It was just really, really awful
at the time, especially the fact that it was written and
directed by Lawrence Kasdan, the great Lawrence Kasdan. I will
never forget that demon coming out of that man's butthole in
Dreamcatcher. Never forget it.
Lailin reads as if you could watch three movies for the first
time again, scary or not, which one would you choose? Star Wars
trilogy hands down.
I hate to go to this answer, but I'll my eyes were completely
opened by Goodfell. There's there are three movies that when
I watched them, I wanted to become a filmmaker or do
something in movies. Goodfellas, Raising Arizona blew me away.
And then to later learn that Raising Arizona was kind of
borrowing some evil dead tricks. But at the time, I was
like, I've never seen anything like this in my life. And
probably Boogie Nights. The that was one where I walked out and I
was like, I'd like a ticket to the next show, please. I want to
watch this again. Those would be the three that I can think of
off the top of my head.
Yeah. I was just nothing was more magical than the Star Wars
trilogy. And I can't imagine if I got to see that again for the
first time. Sure. Nick 22. James asks, Joe, how did your first
open mic go? Horrifically. Absolutely horrifically. I used
to physically shake or the physical, that's the only way to
shake, but I would visibly shake, I should say you could
see my hand shaking. I was so scared. I would drink six
whiskies on ice, and I would just feel normal. And you'd go
up and you'd bomb for five minutes. And then you know,
there'd be one thing that was good enough that made you want
to come back for the next week. But I mean, it was a it was a
bumpy road there in the beginning. Yeah. Miss Manny's
maybe I'm behind and I missed any commentary. But I did just
rewatch Trainspotting one and two any thoughts on
Trainspotting two. I was excited for it. I watched half of it.
And I was bored out of my fucking mind. I did not enjoy
t2. I hated that it was called t2. It also was like a joke on
Terminator two. I don't get why they did that. But I hated the
second one. I really did.
And I really good. Yeah, I really love Trainspotting and
Trainspotting two I watched. I remember being kind of neutral
on it. But I don't remember one second of that movie. I you
know, I like checking in with everybody again. And I don't
Yeah, again, I don't remember being terrible. I just didn't
like it.
I mean, it's just to me, it was like everything that made the
first one mesmerizing, which was like these young lost kids from
Scotland, that were products of the, you know, of the of their
environment, but also the legacy of Scotland and the torment and
all these things. You know, just being so crazed and drug addled
and all this stuff with nothing to lose. I felt that all of that
was lost in the second one, where suddenly now it was like,
you know, the one guy's like, respectable. And then you know,
the other guy is a lot of money from making porn or whatever it
is he does. And I just thought it was a pointless return. I
feel like if they did Seinfeld now and Seinfeld lived in a
house, sure, because it wouldn't make sense, you know, if you're
still living that apartment. And you'd be like, I'm out. That's
cocktail, Pat. One quick, I'm sorry, one quick thought on that
too, is like, people will say, Oh, you don't like the new one,
the old one still exists. Go watch it. Or you don't like the
sequel. You don't like the remake, whatever. And that's
true. But when you do a sequel like that, like T2, there's way
worse examples than Trainspotting 2. Bad Santa 2 is a great
example. Yeah, I know the original Bad Santa still exists.
And it's a masterpiece. But I can't shake Bad Santa 2. Now I
know that that's where those characters go instead of
leaving them in my mind to do whatever I want them to do.
That's what pisses me off about a really bad sequel. Sure. All
right. Home cocktail. Pat, why did you tell Whoopi Goldberg
that the Holocaust wasn't about race? Man, I still I haven't
even I see the headlines and I have yet to click on it. It's
like the fact that Whoopi Goldberg is being dragged for
anything. A woman who has just seemingly been on the right
side of everything for ages, except maybe Ted Danson wearing
blackface when they were married. But I don't know, I
have a great deal of respect for Whoopi Goldberg. I feel like
what did she say the Holocaust isn't about race but and people
are mad because she said it wasn't about race because it was
too it was whites doing something to whites. And I
understand what she was trying to say because I there was a
time in my life where I didn't understand that Jewish was
considered a race. I thought it was just considered a religion.
So I got her mistake. I also got why people were taken aback by
it or offended by it. But you know, we've lost this this
whole thing is gone of intention and discussion and it's like,
and you're gonna you're gonna think she was trying to hurt
Jewish people. Like I don't think that was what she was
trying to do. But you know, I feel like I could get canceled
just for saying that about her. You know, like, who knows? I
mean, she's got a Jewish last name. She might even be she
might be Jewish. I think I remembered hearing that at some
point or half Jewish or something. But um, no, it's nuts.
She's on a show where the job is to discuss the issues of the
day, and should be to have sometimes painful, often
uncomfortable conversations. That's what that's what one of
those shows should be for for women talking about the issues
of the day is what the show is. So to ban her or suspend her or
for that. It's like, come on, guys, like it led to really
interesting discussions. That's what the show is. I don't know,
it drives me crazy. I think if you don't understand what she
meant, you're you're trying not to understand what she meant,
you're going out of your way to make her the villain. And I
guarantee if you asked just about anybody on earth, they
don't care that she said that just about anybody. But we all
have to pretend we care.
And again, I get I get it. I even get it if you're saying
like, my God, I was so offended by that as a Jewish person, or
maybe as a survivor, or whatever it is, I get it. But
like, yes, I can understand that somebody is saying, No, no, no,
I was saying not race, because I thought that it was a religion.
It was two white people doing I don't know. Anyway, great
plastic, someone horror and horror adjacent films you think
are underrated, or at least deserve more attention. Well,
mine are always the creep show films. I you know, I say it all
the time creep shows in my top 10 movies of all time. I love
creep show two and I love Tales from the Dark Side, which is the
unofficial third installment. And as that series goes, I know
less and less people that have seen the subsequent installments.
So I think it's just an amazing, amazing approach to a
franchise. I think it was you know, they did it before they
were able to do Tales from the Crypt because they couldn't get
the rights. And it was just a great fun nod to horror. And it's
what every horror, it's what all horror should be. That's what
horror should be, in my opinion, fun and monsters and whatever.
It's perfect. So that's my take.
Yeah, I mean, it's for me, it's always hard to come up with an
underrated one. Because it's like, if you love the movie,
then you don't think of it as being underrated. You know what
I mean? But I think enough people know It Follows by now,
but It Follows was one that really caught me. And that guy
immediately moved away from horror. I loved his next movie
too, under the Silver Lake, filmed and in part on Joe's old
street, which I don't know if you ever watched that one, Joe,
but I used to tell you like, Andrew Garfield walking down
your street. I really loved It Follows. I think that's a good
one. And then like trying to think of one from the 80s,
maybe I, I can't off the top of my head, I wish I could. I well
stir of echoes is one I always recommend to people that I don't
think got the play it deserved. I love stir of echoes.
Mick with knock, Mike with knock, I don't know. Wendy, we
get to see your physical media collections, which sounds like a
euphemism to me.
For mine, go to my Instagram, I posted, I haven't, I never do
Instagram anymore. But it's one of the last posts I had was a
picture of my blu ray collection. Vinyl, I could, I
could put up a picture, but it's not interesting to look at a
vinyl collection, really.
I'm actually going to start doing a video game based
podcast, video podcast, whatever, where I review games
and stuff that I really love. And so that'll be a start. And
maybe it'll bleed into movies and other things too. Tory Ray
slipping in double question here. Just the real audacious
now. What were your top three favorite films of 2021? You're
gonna have to wait for the next episode. And we'll get into
that wait. Are there any plans for the Etsy shop to be
relaunched? Would you ever guys put out any more merch? I'm
pretty sure I would live in a we'll see you in hell t shirt
or hoodie. Emily offered an answer to this because she she
is, you know, you know, she was handling a lot of that, or all
of it really. Sure. And I paused the merch at the beginning
of the pandemic, because to me, it felt a bit weird promoting
merch when people were losing their jobs, homes, lives, etc.
Absolutely. And well, that was two years ago. I never imagined
we would still be in this shit show, which she means the
podcast, not the pandemic. I'm kidding. If there's enough
interest, I can start it up again. Exclamation point
enthusiasm, I definitely have stock of some stuff, but we
could always make it a live show exclusive to be determined with
the boys later. I think that pretty much answers the question
as best as I could. Do you have anything to add to that, Pat? I
don't. If if people want it, let Emily know, you know that and if
she has extra, then then great, I think. Yeah, I know. My wife
still wears her We'll See You In Hell shirt. I always like it.
I'm always way more attracted to her when she's wearing it
because it's got my face on it. And Joe's, let's be real. But
yeah, I'd be down, of course.
Beeliz Feezer asks, What are your comfort movies you can
watch ad nauseam and never get tired of? My number one is Fatso.
I've sang the praises of this movie many times on this show. I
love the movie The Odd Couple is another one for me. Those are
two films that I can just put on and just be so at peace, so at
ease while I'm watching it and just love every minute of it.
Yeah, I mean, I'd go with a couple of John Hughes from when
I was a kid because that, you know, I know every word and it
doesn't matter. I still think it's funny Home Alone and Uncle
Buck. My dad was texting me the other night. I actually had my
dad and two other friends were texting me that they were
watching a John Candy marathon on IFC. And I looked it up. And
even though I of course knew this, it hits me every single
time that he died when he was 43. Yeah, it's younger than than
Joseph DeRosa. A couple years older than me. Absolute tragedy,
but but John Candy is a guy who I just love to look at even his
bad movies just make me feel good. And I miss him. So it's
like checking in with a friend you lost, you know, it's sad,
but it's also wonderful to see him.
All three look different than if you met 43 year old John Candy
now your assumption immediately be that he's older than you.
Yes. And a lot of it's when you first see somebody I think but
Robbie Goodwin, you know, you know that guy, don't you, Joe?
Sounds familiar. I think he's a comic but he I follow him on
Twitter and he posted the other day a picture of George
Costanza from the first season. And it says, this is what a
29 year old man used to look like. Really made me laugh
because yeah, the thing he's you know, he's bald and pudgy and
everyone on camera has to be beautiful and it sucks. But
well also to bald and pudgy back then wasn't like he wasn't
hipster II like you couldn't write. He's not wearing like an
ironic t shirt and whatever like dressed like he's dressed like
an older man to they always talk about Brimley. You know how
Brimley looked like he was 80 when he was 40. Like I think
Brimley and cocoon was only 52. Yeah, it's wild. Yeah.
B. Hamlin, what is your favorite George A. Romero movie?
Oh, unquestionably Dawn of the Dead, I would say.
Same. You know, Romero, like we were saying earlier about
Scorsese, he did nothing better than zombies. And yeah, that is
the quintessential zombie film. My second place would be the
dark half.
Our calf leaves me cold for some reason, but Night of the Living
Dead, oddly, well, doesn't set me on fire. You know, I know it
never did. I don't know why. But I think Dawn of the Dead is is
way superior in the way Evil Dead two is way superior to Evil
Dead one. They're both classics. You can't deny either one. Right.
But the best version of it is the sequel. And actually the
remake of Dawn of the Dead is about on a par with with
Romero's. That's how good I think the remake is.
The remake is great. Gummy Venus asks if Pat is comfortable
talking about it. I'd love to hear what went down behind the
scenes of living biblically. He definitely teased a tell going
up on Patreon a couple of times, but I don't think we ever got
the real scoop.
You know, there's there's not some real real scoop to be had.
They were all really sweet people. The cast I loved, of
course, the you know, it just it boiled down to then thank you
for not asking about cool kids. I can't talk about that without,
you know, just falling apart. No, it broke my heart that show. I
think it got way better as it went. And the best episodes of
the show never even aired or they aired on Saturday night in
the old empty nest time slot or whatever. But basically, it was
supposed to be a show about an atheist trying to support her
husband going down a full on biblical path. And they
ultimately did not want the atheist to ever speak about God
because she didn't test well. And I don't even think that's
the actress. I think that your your average CBS viewer is a
devout religious person. CBS was the wrong choice for a show
about religion. And I wound up going in a direction of making
it as funny and goofy as I could. But I think it would have
been a better move to make it a juicy show about religion, which
was just never going to happen on CBS. So I don't I don't blame
anybody for that one. And especially with my next
experience, I look back sort of fondly on on living biblically
at this point.
Day bow bow asked if Pat could have a featured sandwich or
Joey roses, what would be on it? I sort of already answered that
No.
Well, he said if Pat could have a features. Oh, I see. If you
want to pick your ingredients.
Oh, I mean, all I would need for sure is banana peppers. To me,
that is the ultimate ingredient banana peppers make us take a
sea sandwich.
We'll find him you'll get hot cherry peppers, babe, and they'll
take you to the next level.
All right. All right.
Syrup Mountain. Have you guys ever watched Ari Aster's movie
border yet? No, and I refuse to I think that is nothing better
than framing and shock value. That's my opinion.
I obviously completely disagree. But I didn't even I never even
heard of border I watched his incredibly disturbing short film
and then I watched what I thought were his only movies.
I'm going to look up border.
It's probably one of his she's got a bunch of short films.
Okay, Dr. Dan cake. Is there a song or album you tear up to
when you listen maybe because of nostalgia maybe because of
premise?
Lately, lately, for me, it's it's the I never liked emo or
screamo or any of that shit. But lately, it's that that kind of
kids for a while in the 90s. There's a few songs they have
that, I guess just take me back to being a teenager and can kind
of mess me up the wrens. Again, that album is sticking with me
a lot lately metal lands. And the river. Bruce Springsteen's
album has several songs stolen car always makes me cry. You
know, there's there's several that get to me. A pair of brown
eyes by the Pogues is a song that always just destroys me.
You know, I got some
the only time I can remember crying to a song is the when
Eminem Eminem put out the Marshall Mathers LP to and it
was there was a song on it where he was apologizing to his mom
for all the stuff he had said in the past records and saying
like, I know you just did your best with what you were dealt.
And it was right after I had moved to LA and I was driving to
furniture for my apartment. And I was missing my parents and that
came on for the first time and I was weeping almost uncontrollably
in my car. Yeah. That's the only time I can think of actually
crying. There's plenty of music that gets me amped but crying I
couldn't say. Yeah, music makes me cry more than movies
generally.
On the opposite. Yeah. Tuttle Sunday trousers. Even with the
of the unbearable weight of massive talent. Nick Cage seems
to avoid the hyper reality acting pitfalls of modern day
Goldblum Downey Jr. And to some extent, Murray, I don't agree
with that at all. But what is it that allows a cage or cruise for
that matter, to keep an almost day Lewis level of commitment
that continuously suspends disbelief? I don't agree with
that either. I'm not challenging. I'm just saying I
don't agree. Are they more talented? Or is it just their
popularity never reached a fever pitch? Well, Cruz and day Lewis
have reached a fever pitch, undoubtedly, of exposure during
the irony obsessed, early, odd era. Can you Jesus fucking
correct? What is this a symposium? You still deliver art
when you become a bumper sticker of yourself. Love you guys.
With that last sentence, I get what you're saying. It was a
little confused throughout. But I get what you're saying at the
end. Has cage become too much a parody of himself is basically
how I'm taking the question. And I thought he was saying he's
hasn't whereas a Goldblum Downey Jr. and Murray have. Okay. I
mean, Goldblum is is definitely a parody of himself, especially
seeing how raw and different he was in deep cover, which we just
did on the show, you realize what a parody of himself he's
become. I don't think that about Murray. And I don't think that
about Daniel Day Lewis. Nicholas Cage, for many years was very
frustrating to me when everybody was just like, look at this
idiot and laughing at him. I've done many tweets about Nicholas
Cage through the years where I'm like, how dare you laugh at
this amazing he's brought more excitement to movies than almost
anyone else.
But he also does with the thing I disagreed with in the
He does do the ironic thing. He he knows when to steer into the
cage, as they call cage and all that. He knows when to do that
stuff. Just like Goldblum does just like you know, they all do
it. You know, I've been watching the world according to Jeff
Goldblum. And it's like, he's great. He's charming. He's
charismatic. He's fun to watch. But he knows when to lean into
the like weird Jeff Goldblum shit. He does for sure. I mean,
he's my, my really good friend, Kevin Atten co wrote this new
massive weight of talent movie with Nicholas Cage. And I'm I
can't wait to see it. But he's fully stepping into like, I'll
appear as a parody of myself in a movie. And that's fine. I just
I want Nicholas Cage to have enough money at this point. I
hope that he's doing well, because I've always loved him.
But I was rewatching a little of pig this morning, which is a
movie, everybody tells me I was wrong on because I just thought
it was fine. And I still think it's just fine. I think Nicholas
Cage in that movie is not doing like subtle work. I think he's
kind of doing a hammy version of a depressed guy in that movie,
really. I'll never I'll never get back the feelings I had for
him, even up through like a super underrated comedy,
Honeymoon in Vegas, which I've talked about many times, I think
his performance is next level. Because he does what so few
romantic comedy leads do, which is be super funny. Generally,
they're just there to be hot. And he was like balding, wearing
silk shirts screaming at people. And he was also romantic and
very funny. So I just love the edge he brought to mainstream
stuff back in the day. Now even something like color and color
out of space. I think he got way too hammy by the end. I did not
understand what he was doing with the Trump impression. He
frustrates me sometimes lately, for sure.
Jota Rosa fans. That's the best name on this whole thing today.
What are your thoughts on the upcoming Scream 6?
Unneeded. They did a perfect ending with five. It's great.
They're not going to top it. The idea that this killer comes back
again is it's ridiculous. It already was teetering on
ridiculous, if not crossing over into it in some of the sequels.
They nailed this this fifth one, they nailed it. That's it. Let
it go. And it will they who the fuck knows, but no, we'll have
eight more of these screen movies. They never ask, should
we? It's all about money. The should we question never comes
up. Look, I'll see all the screams they throw out. I enjoy
the horror franchise more than most. But yeah, I don't think we
need more either. And if we're going to have Courtney Cox and
Neve Campbell come back again, it's like, what are you doing,
guys? What are you doing? Yeah, no, it's it's it should be over.
Yeah. All right. Too fat to skate asks, is Manwich an
acceptable name for my meatloaf cover band? Or should I consider
something else? Baby, if you don't call it Manwich, you're
making a mistake. Why not sloppy Joe? I think Manwich is that's
a great man, which is bad. I haven't heard Manwich in ages
that that was one meal a week for my our one dinner a week at
my house was man, which my mom could only make seven things. So
you know, I'm going to order food today. And as I said, I
resorted to Jersey Mike. I find this local sandwich place and I
see they got sloppy Joe's on the menu. And I get all excited and
I go, I'm going to get something from this place. And then I go
to the sloppy Joe's and it's like chicken tenders with gravy
and cheese. And I'm like, you can't call it a sloppy Joe's
menu just because the sandwiches are kind of sloppy. Yeah.
Really sloppy Joe sloppy Joe.
All right, Nikki Minaj 93. You think that's her? I think it's
the real it might be. I want to ask her about her brother's
balls. Have you guys covered upgrade? If not, would you
consider it? We did consider it. And it kind of got away from us.
I never saw it. And it just got to a point where it was like, it
wasn't notable enough.
Yeah, we've had a few of those where we're like, we're gonna do
this. And then it winds up just not catching on. I did see
upgrade and really enjoyed it. And I thought he bettered
himself with invisible man, which of course, I liked a lot
more than Joe. But that's that's a guy. That's a guy who's who's
sticking with horror for the most part and doing great work.
Upgrade was more of an action movie. But I love what he does
on a small budget. I think he's he's really talented. And I
like that guy a lot.
Upgrades a long shot for me. You're talking Blumhouse and the
invisible man director.
No, you'd like upgrade. It's really fun.
Um, Chris.
Swale.
I hope I said that correctly. What is your favorite scene from
Pee Wee's Big Adventure?
Oh, boy.
Hands down for me the the the exhibit. Hey, that's
it's it's so funny to me. And him going through that.
That's something you'd like to share with the rest of us
Larry.
Yeah, the way when he hits the horn and he's shaking with like
madness.
Yeah. But
his big adventure is a true masterpiece. And I think some
day it will be regarded as we regard Chaplin and Buster Keaton
and that shit because it's better than those movies.
That's one that deserves a criteria.
That would be amazing. I would they should do more Burton
criterion. So be, you know, cut, make sure you cut them off at a
certain year. But yeah.
Cox talking about Johnny Depp and Edward Scissorhands.
Who talked about Brian Cox?
No, what is a Brian Cox is a treat to read those interviews.
He's just going on about how Johnny Depp isn't that good. He's
like, you know, he's like, the guy comes out with fucking
scissors on his hand. Oh, brilliant. What the fuck did he
have to do?
Yeah, the makeup did a lot of work in Edward Scissorhands. My
my favorite scene in peewees is probably the one Joe
referenced. But, you know, Tom Sharpling, who I read about last
time he
Thomas sent me his book recently. His new book, go by
Tom's new book.
It's maddening to me that like he talks to you and not have I
told you to Tom and I are pals. Now we text here and there and
very much sent me an autographed copy of his book he wrote in it.
Continue to be funny or your or we'll make fun of you next.
Okay, of Tom Sharpling ties into the podcast.
His book is fantastic. It never ends. But Tom Sharpling talks
about how the scene that makes him cry is peewee running back
into that pet store over and over and over again. And then
finally getting the snakes, which is his biggest fear. And
I you know, that that's kind of the beauty of him is like that
that's the scene that wouldn't make your average person cry.
But it's you also sort of get it. Like it's just a completely
selfless act.
Let's go ahead. Sorry.
No, no, no. My my my favorite scene as a kid was always
tequila, of course, followed by knocking all the bikes over. But
the the tour of the Alamo with Jan Hooks. I mean, it's just it's
banger after banger that movie.
Sal and I talked about the movie recently. And he pointed out.
And it's something I always noticed, but it never registered.
You know what I mean? Because as soon as he said it, I was like,
Oh, yeah. The biker scene when he's riding away, and goes
through the side, which is just classic Looney Tunes shit. But
someone would laugh. Yeah, so I pointed out he goes he goes, he
does the most perfect, like little wobble, like wobble.
Yeah, yeah. crashes, which just a genius stunt man who knew like
now wobble, the wobble is the key. It's like, it's a little
bonus laugh before the massive laugh of driving through that
thing. Yes, I agree.
Yeah, that's a you rewind that and you know, the third time
you're like, look at the wobble, you know. All right, last
question. All right, well, Glasgow asks, Do you think one
day util will work on a feature film or pilot together or maybe
write a script or produce? Nothing would make the hellions
happier than a Pat and Joe collab PS this podcast is my
favorite by far. And thank you for getting us through the dark
times of the pandemic. Well, thank you, Will, very much.
Thank all of you for the support of that show us. All of you are
wonderful. We appreciate your interest. We appreciate your
questions. You know, we joke and we break balls, but we love you
guys. And then as far as Yeah, I mean, of course, I'm 100 % open
to it. It's not a matter of whether or not Pat and I would
want to do something together. It's a matter of the businesses.
Yeah, we've just we've discussed a few things and kind of knocked
it around. I, I would love it. And yet, Joe and myself, maybe a
little bit more Joe, have a history of not winding up not
friends with people that they work with, you know, I get can
happen, I wouldn't say I do that often, but it happens, you start
to resent people when you work with them in a way you don't as
friends. And since Joe and I had a couple of sort of rocky
periods in our friendship, brief rocky periods in our friendship,
like day maybe, but I wouldn't I wouldn't chance that Joe's
friendship is too important to me. But I think we could do it
if we set ground rules and really stuck to them.
I agree. And I think if we did it the way we do this, which is,
you know, a fun, enjoyable way to work together. Yes, it would
be fine. You know, they make the, you know, half the problem
is they make the experience of working in film and television
quite frequently, so awful. Right. And then the shit starts
to roll downhill. So then when you're, you know, then when
you're at the receiving end of it, you know, people start to
get angry and mad at one another. It's, it's, it's hard.
It's a hard, it's a hard business.
And you know, you miss a you miss a deadline or something,
and then you start hating your friend. It sucks.
So yeah.
But that's our show, folks. That is part of listening. Thank
you for this incredible outpouring of questions that
gave us two episodes and made sure that at this really busy
time, we didn't have to go out and see movies. But I think next
time, well, next time, we know we're going to do the top five
film, top five TV show of 2021.
Well, combo. I wasn't saying five of each. I was saying like
we do your top five movie slash TV shows of 2021.
Oh, I think we should do five of each.
I don't have five of each.
All right, I'm gonna do five of it.
I need to do I need to do like movies and TV combined. I
couldn't. There wasn't enough.
At least do your your 10. Otherwise, we're not gonna have
enough to talk about.
Or do your five worst, you know, I'm going to do my five TV,
five movies, I already wrote them out. I spent time on it.
Okay, and that that's a wasted seven minutes.
We'll discuss it. We'll discuss all right, we're gonna do that.
And then the other one, not set in stone, but I am definitely
going to the theater to see the new jackass. I need it. I crave
it. I'm actually waiting to go until I am in the perfect mood
for it like that. I can't waste a new jackass. So excited for
that. So we'll probably that'll be our other one.
Alright, folks, we'll see you next time.
And we'll see you in hell.