I'll see you in hell.
And when the sound of your screams becomes a thing of my dreams, you know I'll say.
You know I will.
I'll see you in hell.
Folks, we'll see you in hell is back, back, back, back to take a bite out of Abigail,
the new vampire ballerina, reservoir dogs hybrid, directed... who made it?
The guys that made Ready or Not.
That's right.
Which I never saw. You saw that. You said it was good, right?
Yeah, it is good. It was sort of similar. It goes for a huge tonal shift in the home stretch.
I don't know.
You know, Abigail, what did you think about marketing this as a vampire movie?
Since that's not revealed for 45 minutes.
Well, I thought they... look, there's no reality that exists where they wouldn't have done that, right?
But I think it does do it a disservice because when it finally happens, and we'll get more into it, obviously,
but when it finally happens, I was like... I was already thinking this is sort of like from Dust Till Dawn, I mean, Reservoir Dogs.
And then when the twist happened, I was like, oh, this is like from Dust Till Dawn.
But I knew it was coming.
And I remember when Dust Till Dawn came out at first, they didn't reveal initially in the marketing.
Eventually they did, I think.
I was just going to ask that because I remember trailers that had vampires in it for sure,
and I can't imagine they would have just marketed it as a gritty crime drama with Looney and Tarantino as brothers.
Maybe what it was was back then you had a fighting chance of seeing a movie with that wide a release
without seeing a commercial for it yet or a trailer because I knew people that saw it that didn't know about the twist.
Right.
And I was like blown away.
Like, what was that like, man? You must have been like, what the fuck?
Yeah. I mean, I showed it to my ex unfamiliar with the twist.
It was a lot of fun, but I had to wait 25 years to clear the public memory.
And I had locked her in a room for 25 years.
It was like pet cemetery.
Draining her of nutrients.
All for the goal of just, I just wanted to show her movie.
Yeah. It's like that Ethan Hawke movie, The Black Phone and The Final Twist.
He's like, and now we watch 1996s from Dusk Till Dawn.
You've grown up enough.
Honestly, it'd be about equally as horrifying as whatever he wanted to do to the boy in that movie, which was, I think, nothing.
Yeah, I don't think he just killed the kids.
He didn't. There was no sexual component.
I don't think. Right.
It seemed like he just wanted a friend.
Did he? He was killing kids. All right. Well, then fine.
Yeah, because the dead kids would appear.
That's what they would talk to him.
That's right. That's like, here's how you get out.
It was like, I think they're doing a sequel.
You know how all your friends are always talking about how they want a sequel to The Black Phone.
What could the sequel possibly be?
Phone's ringing again, Joe.
That's what it could be.
That phone's ringing again.
I was out the other night.
I'm not telling.
Well, this was kind of a very cool thing that happened, but it's not the main reason I bring up the story.
But I opened for the Impractical Jokers at Radio City Music Hall, which was a wild experience.
Yeah. And really wonderful.
And it was great. And I had a great time.
And they were amazing. And the audience was amazing.
And the fans and it was a really beautiful thing.
And the best part was seeing Joe Gatto was there backstage as a surprise.
And they did a photo at the end of the show with the audience.
And they were like talking about how like the Radio City is like our Super Bowl.
This is the peak of the tour and all this stuff.
And they took like the picture a couple of times.
And then Murr kept going like something's something's missing.
Something's not right.
And then Joe Gatto ran out and the fucking place I almost started crying.
They went so crazy. It was awesome.
Anyway, that's not the point of the story.
But the shadow gets on the microphone and he goes and Joe DeRosa is also here and runs out to complete silence.
I had already been on stage.
Thank you very much.
I got my juice out there.
We went out. Me and Q and some people went out after the show.
Yeah.
Some of which are in the horror movie family who two very nice gentlemen.
I met Joe, sorry, James DeMonaco, who created the Purge franchise.
Oh, OK.
And I met Michael Levy, who produces the Terrifier films.
They were both awesome.
They were really cool guys, really fun, funny guys.
They both want to come on the show.
We should have them on as guests.
That'd be great.
Yeah, sure.
They're what, producers, writers?
Well, James wrote and directed the first two or three Purge movies.
OK, OK.
And Michael produces the Terrifier movies.
I'm going to hold on.
Let me see here.
It was interesting, though, because I asked James about the Purge.
And I said, I was like, did you have any idea that you had like this massive franchise on your hands?
Yeah.
And he said, no, he said, I just, you know, I wrote this movie and I thought it was, you know, you know, I believed in it.
And it was, you know, he said, but Jason Blum was the one with the.
Oh, and I just went, oh, that's cool, man.
I love him.
You got to be, you know, this is what that's one of those moments where you're like, is this podcast going to bite me in the ass?
Because I've been so critical of the Blum now.
But I'll pull the cord on this podcast in five seconds if I feel the heat coming around the corner.
You'll never find one of these episodes again.
But this is not the point of the story either.
The point of the story is, is minutes before I started talking to James and Michael about the movie, James did direct and he wrote and created it and then also directed the first couple.
Anyway, we minutes before that, I was talking to another friend of Brian's who's in wrestling and a very, very nice guy.
And Brian just walked over and like, like, like, like a menacing puppeteer or something, just pulling the strings just goes, hey, hey, buddy, why don't you tell Joe what you thought about that new Halloween trilogy?
And the guy turned and he's like, I fucking dude, I loved it.
You know, the last one kind of stunk.
But I was like, what?
Yeah, yeah, they're out there.
Contained myself.
So he was saying that Halloween ends was terrible.
But Halloween kills he thought was good.
And we debated and debated and debated.
And his wife or girlfriend, who was very sweet, went, you know what?
Now that you're saying it, I do think it kind of sucks.
And it's like, yeah.
Yeah.
Blumhouse sucks.
I was going on and on about Blumhouse.
Yeah.
Not realizing moments later, I'd be speaking to a man.
I didn't know the purge was with Blumhouse.
I like the purge franchise has done some good things.
Yeah.
They've done some good things.
Kind of like the first purge.
You know what it was called?
The one with the drums.
Rimshot.
Oh, no.
Whiplash.
You're thinking of Rimjob, which was your performing debut.
Right.
Also starring.
Very Andy Warhol like just like a 15 minute steady cam shot of Joe getting his asshole
tongued.
Whoa.
Bye.
Yeah.
And that's the connection.
That's how we got away with it.
But what's it called?
I like the purge.
And I like I like that.
I saw the first four or something.
I liked every one.
Yeah.
They did get out.
Right.
Yeah.
OK.
There you go.
Anyway, this this guy I was talking to about the Halloween was his girlfriend or wife
said she said she really enjoyed the black phone.
And I said, oh, that was Blumhouse.
I like the black phone.
And then I said, I have a podcast.
Yeah.
And my partner, my co -host, I hesitate when I say partner, because then they think we're
married.
Right.
But I said my co -host didn't like it.
However, I told the story.
Yeah.
To Michael and James about you and it killed.
You went over big in this story.
Which what I do.
Well, so Michael, we were taught I think he produced the mean one, which was the Grinch
horror movie that they did.
Didn't even know that happened.
There was a Grinch horror movie and it's kind of like those where the rights came back or
something.
That's what I was asking him.
I was like, how can you like like how do you get away with it?
Because then James was talking to me about Meet the Blacks.
Right.
And and like how that was like a purge spoof and the fine line between spoof and whatever.
Yeah.
And I was like, yeah, sometimes it's a spoof.
But sometimes you have to get the rights like where do how was that all defined?
And they were like, it's very, very murky.
It's very murky.
And I said, well, that that answers a question for me.
I said that I have this podcast and I was telling about the show and I said, I'm always
going we're always going on about why do they reboot these things that nobody gives a shit
about?
And I was like, oh, it's because they it's just a means to not get sued.
They like the idea they could.
They don't even do it that similarly.
But to avoid any chance of getting sued, they just call it a reboot.
And I brought up head of the class.
Yeah.
And they I think even they were like, they rebooted head of the class.
I was like, yeah.
Yeah.
And I told the story of when you texted me, I think we're on lockdown still when that
was on.
When you texted me and and you were like, head of the class episode three, they just
grabbed back Robin Givens like she's Luke fucking Skywalker.
I'm supposed to give a shit.
And they were they were laughing heartily at that.
They thought that was very, very funny.
Yes.
My friends wrote for that show.
I never actually watched it, but it's done now.
All right.
I was looking at your sporn.
Never hear this.
They won't hear this.
They they also speak critically of the program.
They know they know, as my old boss used to say, they knew what it was.
I was looking this morning at a review of Palm Royale, the Kristen Wiig show on Apple.
There's all these mystery shows on Apple that I guess somebody must watch.
But yeah, I feel like bad reviews are coming back.
I read a scathing review of the new Mulaney show on Netflix, which kind of deserved it.
I read a scathing review of Pool Man, Chris Pine's Big Lebowski homage, which is supposed to be one of the worst movies ever made.
That thing is getting like I can't wait to see that.
I know the level of reviews that's getting.
I know.
It's supposed to be one of the all time bads.
And then Palm Royale, this high profile Kristen Wiig, Carol Burnett show.
Here's the headline on the Onion AB Club Palm Royale season one finale.
An ending so bad it defies all belief.
Wow, like you haven't seen bad reviews.
It seemed like we started getting into this whole like, let's be sensitive of everybody's feelings.
But like this morning I was like, did they just pull a, you know, pull a restriction or something?
Because every review I read was like, you piece of shit.
Well, Walsh, speaking of bad reviews.
Love it. You got to read.
You got to read.
Reads, reads. That's what we should call this segment. Reads, reads.
Did Reed hit unfrosted?
No.
I don't even know why he saw this.
I don't even know it existed.
I didn't even, I don't, it can't be in theaters, but it must be if he's reviewing it.
Who let John Travolta agree to the trash wallow that is cash out.
Trash wallow.
That's the headline.
Cash out is directed by a cast member from Vanderpump Rules under a pseudonym.
So I believe that this movie is bad for sure.
This is how he starts and this, the trash wallow caught my eye.
Yeah.
But this is, and by the way, this is one of his only bad reviews because I noticed he's reviewing a lot of theater now.
And I think Reed was like, I'm moving over to theater and all his theater reviews are glowing.
I think he was just like, I can't do it anymore.
I can't watch another movie.
So.
On the rare occasion that someone talks John Travolta into taking up his old position before the camera.
Rex, what are you talking about this guy?
He's in five pictures a year.
Is there anything?
He does anything.
See, here's where Rex has shown his age a bit.
He doesn't have an internet connection, so he doesn't see all these streaming titles probably.
He's saying it's either a favor for a pal who needs a job or an exercise in which Fred Durst maybe,
or an exercise in poor judgment that raises some financing for a bomb that otherwise would never be made.
I don't know what he's talking about, but it caught my eye.
OK, that's the little paragraph under the headline.
That's the little leader.
Yeah.
Here's the true first sentence of the review.
John Travolta doesn't act much anymore.
Rex, you're wrong.
Bring up his IMDB page before writing your review.
It's nuts.
It's, you know, it goes on the rare occasion, whatever.
We don't see a lot of Bobby Cannaval in movies these days.
In this time waster, the star plays Mason Goddard.
There it is.
I love that too.
Guys, they've run out of names.
Yeah.
There's been too many movies.
Just start recycling names.
I'm sure they have.
In the 80s, it was all Jack.
Yeah.
Just Judd Clampett.
This guy's name is Judd Clampett.
Nobody's going to care anymore.
Rumpelstiltskin mahogany at your service.
By the way, just to digress, speaking of names, I'm going to do a bit about this on stage.
My hand to God.
I saw a poster in the street running for office in New York City.
Harvey Epstein.
Nope.
You got to do a switch, Harvey.
Yeah.
So the first punchline, of course, will be, baby, you got to change one of those names.
And it'll go from there, folks.
A thug with a penchant for masterminding major heists like bank robberies and an idiot brother
with a talent for screwing up, for suspense, Mason spends his life planning and negotiating chief
larcenies and figuring out ingenious ways to make them work.
For laughs, he's got a part -time girlfriend named Amelia played by Kristin Davis.
Who's Kristin Davis?
Sex in the City.
Is that Sex in the City?
Yeah.
I don't know what she's doing in this either, but.
Holy Christ, lady.
Yeah.
Who works for the FBI without his knowing it.
Jesus Christ.
And then parentheses he writes, pretty stupid for a criminal on the most wanted list.
Amelia works hard to catch him with a pleasant side effect of champagne, caviar, and sex.
Okay.
First we see Mason trying to steal a valuable once -in -a -lif -
Wait a minute.
Does that mean there's a Kristin Davis, John Travolta sex scene in this movie?
I would bet you no.
I would bet you that you see the kissing and the pulling into the bedroom, cut to them
lying there post -coitus.
I'm betting you see Travolta start to lean in for the kiss and we dim those lights.
Just like cut to the next morning, birds chirping on a telephone wire.
He starts kissing her and then immediately starts gagging.
I thought you were your brother.
Don't do that ever again.
Yeah.
Next, his idiot brother, Sean, played by Lucas Haas.
It's not a bad cast.
Not a bad cast.
Haas was coming back for a while.
I guess he fell off.
I'm trying to hop to the shitting.
Then he's just going through a plot.
The moronic one -dimensional screenplay.
Okay.
Here we go.
Ready for this.
This might be the most vicious thing he's ever said.
This is my first time reading this since.
The moronic one -dimensional screenplay by Depo Ocini and Doug Richardson, parentheses.
Two credits to forget immediately.
Come on, Rex.
This awkward clumsy and the jerky direction is by someone with the pseudonym Ives.
That's who you're talking about.
Yeah.
Randall Emmett.
I don't blame him for wanting to keep his real identity a secret.
It would be a shame if this got out.
It's nice to see Kristin Davis in a larger role than just a supporting sidekick on Sex and the City.
Ashford Travolta.
He shuffles through the whole thing scruffy and bald without bothering to reveal anything about the character he plays.
Yeah.
There you go.
I mean, there's a little more, but it's nothing that funny.
It's crazy to me.
People watch these.
It's got to just be dads, you know, watching all these Bruce Willis Travolta joints.
I mean, have you looked, you know, recently, you know, we were talking about the Bruce Willis ones recently and whatever.
Yeah.
Have you looked recently at like box office on these things, dude?
It'll be like $89 ,000.
Well, I didn't even know there were theatrical releases.
I mean, I thought they just went straight to on demand.
Most of them do.
Yeah.
But like with something like this that hits the theater and you're like, what the fuck is that?
Like, hold on.
I'm going to look it up.
There's got to be some sort of like, if you release it, you get a tax break or something like that.
They're doing something shady, especially knowing that Randall Emmett guy.
Well, I think now producers go around to these actors and they're like, the script doesn't even factor in.
It's like what I can do is get you $3 million.
You'll be in and out in two weeks.
We'll do this.
The movie will get this release.
You'll make this on the back end.
Like, I think those movies are just part of a factory.
You know, they're not like made with love.
Well, I'll tell you this in Googling it.
Yeah.
I found out that there is a rapper from Atlanta named Cash Out.
Which I am willing to bet you affected the title of this movie.
You know, they do that.
They did that with.
Remember when they did that with.
Oh, you mean like when they would do Lord of the Things or something to try to trick you into getting the movie?
Meaning like, no, meaning like when they made the.
Remember when they made the Nurch Ratchet show and it was called Ratchet and it was like when Ratchet was a popular word.
It's like they do shit like that.
Yeah.
No, actually.
OK.
Limited theaters released by Saban.
Saban.
How you ever say that?
Films.
Saban.
The makers of the dildo machine that you ride.
I mean, Saban's.
Oh, God.
I mean, that's never a good sign.
Right.
When they're.
Jesus.
God.
I'm seeing.
I'm looking at Saban's other works.
Hollywood star dogs.
Piping hot.
No, these are their brands.
This is like, oh, God.
Walsh.
This gets darker and darker.
Saban Films is owned by Saban Capital.
Saban Capital is a multi whatever conglomerate.
Global corporation that owns clothing brands.
They did.
They were Cirque du Soleil.
They they produce an American Spanish singing series.
This is really depressing to me, man, that this is like where we're at.
Like, this is who's making movies now.
Yep.
It's going to keep heading that direction is my guess.
Oh, God.
That's really sad.
I have a page here, but I can't find it now.
Anyway, let's get to that movie corn.
Okay, I think we need to start with unfrosted because Joe hit me with a pretty surprising review of it.
Well, do you want it?
Let me ask you, do you want to just do an episode about unfrosted?
No, I don't got that much to say about it.
Did you?
I watched it.
It it is not one of the worst movies ever, as I've heard people say.
It's it's pleasant and, you know, passes the time and is moderately entertaining mainly.
And I hate to say it because I hate the way the comedy has gone into, you know, since the Rogan days into just pack on celebrity cameos.
You know, this movie at every role, essentially, we're talking about 100 roles probably are filled by a comedian or someone similar who you know.
There's a big surprise cameo of John Ham coming in and playing Don Draper, which was a very bizarre kind of crossing of worlds where he's playing the Mad Men character.
Wait, he was actually supposed to be Don Draper.
I didn't even catch that.
Yeah, because he's there with Roger Sterling, who's the the white haired guy.
Yeah, OK.
But yeah, it's Jerry Seinfeld.
He wrote it with some old Seinfeld cronies who wrote B movie with him.
He directed it.
You can watch a very chilling interview online where they ask Hugh Grant about the movie and he goes, well, the thing about Mr.
Seinfeld is he has no interest at all in where the cameras are, how the actors are, anything, really the script.
He's not much of a director at all.
He only cares about the words him and one of his writers sit in the corner and and giggle to themselves about the words.
And that's the only thing he cares about.
I mean, he's shitting on him.
And apparently they did not.
They did not get along.
You can find that clip.
But Seinfeld does kind of, you know, I'm sure he just surrounded himself with top people.
He's got a great cinematographer and a bunch of good people on his side.
But there is a lack of story, a lack of engine to the thing that kind of bugged me.
It's a time where the serial wars are going on.
Who's going to emerge as number one?
And during this time, Post and Kellogg's are both coming up with a pop tart, something similar to what we now know as the pop tart.
And they do it like the right stuff, like the battle for something great, even though we're just talking about who gets a pop tart, you know, to the market first.
To me, this would have been a hilarious five minute SNL sketch.
There are little sketches within the movie that are that are funny.
Good ideas, well executed.
But as a whole, to me, it was just kind of this endless.
It's not over long.
You know, it's about 90 minutes, but it just kept hitting that same punch line again and again for me, which is like, can you believe how seriously we're taking the serial wars?
And I wasn't laughing.
The funniest bit to me was the serial awards show where set earthy entertainer is hosting that had a lot of really funny bits and gags in it.
But that to me and then the funeral sketch, the funeral sketch where all the serial mascots come out and are like doing a military funeral with cereal for some reason.
These things, I think, would have been great sketches as a whole.
The movie is just like.
It just kind of sits there for me.
There's no there's no suspense.
There's nothing you're really following.
You know that pop tarts made it to, you know, we know which one won.
So you're really left with a comedy that isn't hilarious, in my opinion, although everybody it was good.
It's good to see all these funny people together.
You know, it's like, OK, I had an OK time, but it's not a good movie, in my opinion.
This is excuse me.
I'll give my review of this.
This is the only one I'll do for the corner today because I intended my read to be my corner.
But I turned it on.
I was not in a great mood.
I needed something sort of light and brainless to watch.
Yes, I am a Seinfeld fan.
Sure.
I did not have a lot of faith that the movie was going to be good, but I just put it on and I found myself laughing way more than I thought I would.
I think that it could have been better structured.
Yeah, I definitely thought it should have been.
I mean, they they they they altered reality in the true story so much anyway.
I was like, guys, make Kellogg's the underdog.
Yeah, like make it that post is the because Amy Schumer plays Marjorie Post, who's the like evil in this movie.
The portrayal of her is that she's like a sort of sinister like mob boss in the serial world.
And it's like you're you're but but then you're making post number two, make post number one and Kellogg's is number two.
So then when they when Post steals the pop tart idea from Kellogg's, it's egregious.
Yeah.
And you guys are fighting to get your idea back and also beat post to the market who's stolen it and do it better.
And then it's the underdog story.
They didn't do any of that.
It was Kellogg's on top just trying to stay on top and staying on top by being as dirty as anybody.
Like, you know, they say at one point that the cereal awards, the bowl and spoons, whatever they were called, they were bought and sold.
And which was all kind of funny, but it was I thought everybody did a good performance.
Jerry Seinfeld was was was charming and fun and good in it.
Like, you know, I thought he carried the movie well.
I thought Amy was little kids were really funny.
They were a girl.
I wrote her name down, which I probably shouldn't say, but I was like, if I ever need to cast a little girl in something, I was like, that girl is it.
She's hilarious.
The kids were funny.
I thought Amy was great.
I loved Gaff again.
My favorite was done again as well.
The Walter Cronkite shit with done again was so funny when he was like when he's when he's that one where he trailed off about his wife complaining about his drinking.
Uh huh.
And then he starts pounding the desk, but he's not breaking the Walter Cronkite cadence.
And he's going, I pay the damn bills.
I'll drink as much as I goddamn want.
That was really, really funny.
Yeah, I thought Melissa McCarty.
I read a review.
Very funny.
I read a review that criticized that aspect in particular.
They they just casually make a mockery of one of our greatest newsman Walter Cronkite's career.
I almost wrote the person who wrote the article and was like, you should not be allowed to review a comedy movie.
That's that's not fair.
I thought Melissa McCarthy was very funny.
I liked all the little I didn't see it as a one no thing.
I this was one of the times where I actually enjoyed the gags.
You know, look in a comedy like this, that's self referential.
That's absurd.
That's a little slapsticky or whatever.
And then also a period piece there.
You're going to get a lot of jokes that hinge on what we didn't know then, but know now.
So many.
Yeah.
Well, I mean, I thought for the most part they were funny.
Like, I thought it was really funny when it was just a throwaway when Melissa McCarthy's reading Mad Magazine and she goes, they don't pull any punches.
I was really funny to me.
I really liked the guy is Carvel.
Like when they were like talking about how gross the Carvel guy was, I thought.
Did you like the ravioli with eyes and a mouth?
I hated that.
And it didn't.
I didn't understand why it was in there.
It was weird.
It didn't make any sense.
Like, I was like, what?
Jerry was like every every comedy needs to have one crazy thing.
You just go for and you'd tell everybody to fuck off and do it.
And I'm like, all right.
Yeah, but that that's not it.
That wasn't it.
A talking ravioli.
And it was like a sea monkey that came to life or something.
Yeah.
Like for those of you that didn't see it, it's he assembles a team of people like the creator of the sea monkeys.
The guy that the head of Schwinn Bicycles, Chef Boyardee, Tom Carvel, Jack LaLanne, Jack LaLanne to create help.
They're like the think tank for the pop tarts and the guy that creates sea monkeys.
One of the sea monkeys comes to life and it resembles a ravioli, which makes, I guess, Chef Boyardee fall in love with it.
And they raise the it ends up that they raise it together.
By the way, that guy that Thomas Lennon plays in the movie is a real guy.
And I looked him up and he was till till his death was a huge, even though he was Jewish supporter of Aryan groups.
And one of his final interviews, they asked him a question about race or something in America.
And he goes, you know what side I stand for?
We don't need to discuss this.
So like so when they kept making the jokes in the movie about like, where were you in 1942?
And he's like, that's not for you to know.
Like they were making Nazi jokes, obviously, but they were potentially very accurate.
But I there were a lot of there were a couple cameos in this.
I really loathed.
I won't point them out, but for the most part, I, you know, I look, I'm not sitting here saying it's a great movie.
I'm not saying, oh, my God, you know, you got to go see it.
I'm not saying I'd even necessarily watch it again.
I'm just saying it was it had more laughs in it than I ever would have expected.
And and I enjoyed it.
The cameos weren't too egregious.
I really thought it was going to be annoying.
Yeah, but they weren't so bad.
No. Well, here's why.
The cameos in a Rogan thing in your average episode, Jimmy Fallon, whatever, you know, are here's a famous person.
And they come out and wave, you know, that's basically it.
You know them.
They say fuck wants everybody cheers and they leave this movie to its credit.
Wrote a script and cast the roles with really funny, famous people.
They everyone in the movie down to John Hamm is Don Draper is playing a role.
It's not like Amy Schumer walks in and it's like your girl Schumer's here.
Everybody's playing a role and doing it well.
I think Gaffigan is a pretty strong character actor.
The movie got generally bad reviews and I heard some guy in a podcast speculating and I bet he's right that Seinfeld's whole thing.
He did this big article where he's like the movies are dead.
Like you can't get anything made anymore.
TV's dead. The movies are dead.
It was like I think that's just Jerry freaking out.
This is probably the last thing he'll put out into the world and it's getting bad reviews.
So he's taking the whole industry down with him, just being like you can't make anything good anymore.
And he might be right.
I mean, Jerry's not used to failure.
It's also at a time where everybody's celebrating Larry David.
He might not even give a shit at this point.
But I don't know as a as a thing that Jerry did, you know, to me, he's he's stand up in his show.
Still, these movies are just footnotes to me.
They're not really a part of his career to me.
I'll tell you this and I can't believe I'm saying it.
Pat, I laughed more in this movie than I did for the entire final season of Curb, cumulatively.
I'm shocked to say that.
I would say I laughed. I laughed the same amount in both two, which is zero laughs, zero out loud laughs.
So all right.
What else you got for us?
Big boy.
Call me big boy.
I mean it in a sexual way.
Relax.
I was talking about you.
Then say that my dick is big.
Call me big dick boy, please.
What do you got for us?
Long cock, long, skinny, long, way too skinny cock.
It's very long and rail thin, rail thin.
Like you won't know it's in till it hits the back of you.
If that makes sense, you know, you'll be like, are you even that kind of thing?
Because it's sharp, too.
There's a point.
Mean Girls.
I sat down and I was going to watch the new musical version of Mean Girls because I saw that it was written by Tina Fey.
You want to talk about a comedy writer who I absolutely respect, right?
I made it two minutes, you know, which isn't to say it was terrible.
But sometimes you start a movie and you're like, I'm not watching people sing and dance right now.
I'm out.
So yeah.
Instead, I was just agreeing with it.
I was like, it looks terrible.
It does.
And the fact that they didn't even tell audiences that it was a musical should tell you something.
So I looked up Mean Girls just dropped on 4K and once in a while, usually a comedy like this, especially a 90s comedy, you're not going to get a bunch of upgrade from a 4K.
But I was like, I haven't seen it in a while.
I ordered it.
I watched a 4K Mean Girls and I'd only seen it once in theaters.
I know it's considered a classic.
This movie is very, very funny.
Have you seen Mean Girls, Joe?
Oh, yeah.
It's great.
It's so funny.
Yeah.
And, you know, Tina Fey is really, really good as a lot of sketch writers are not at giving you five laughs a scene and not really taking away from the scene itself.
The story works.
You care about Lohan.
You care about the world.
You're rooting for her.
That all works.
But in addition, you're talking about a relentlessly funny movie.
Amy Poehler as the mom who's trying to be hip, who's like bringing the kids Cosmopolitans and like bringing them condoms.
The five year old daughter watching Girls Gone Wild and lifting her shirt up and stuff like Tina Fey goes real dark with shit, especially for a PG -13 movie.
The amount of racially based humor in this for a movie that came out in 2004 was pretty shocking.
Yes.
There are two Asian exchange students who are slutty girls who are both sleeping with the 50 year old gym coach.
And when they go at each other's throats and fight over him, they refer to each other as the N word.
These two young Asian girls.
I mean, there's there's jaw on the jaws on the floor stuff in this from a movie that in my mind I had I had just chalked off as being a pretty funny teen girl movie.
You know, like she's all that or something.
The truth is not that racial humor makes something great.
I'm just saying it's a very edgy, shocking at times PG -13 movie, you know, and it's super funny.
Great soundtrack, perfectly cast.
Everyone in it went on to become a star for the most part.
Yeah, it's great.
It really is great.
I'm going to watch it again in the coming weeks.
It's like a new fave.
And almost unrecognizable.
Who's the girl that plays like the goth friend?
Lizzie Kaplan, one of the hottest people alive.
Yeah, she's great in this.
They're all great.
Lindsay, you watch that movie and you're like, God damn it.
Lindsay Lohan is a fucking star man.
Like I root and she's going she's doing the Freaky Friday sequel with Jamie Lee Curtis.
I Freaky Friday with those two is excellent.
And they're both great in it.
I can't wait for a sequel.
Well, we can cool our jets a little bit, but excellent.
Excellent is too much.
But it was it was entertaining for sure.
And they were both great in it.
Cut to Pat outside of a theater with a sleeping bag.
Sir, you don't know nobody that tickets will be available.
Don't worry.
No, I I I truly do.
I root for Lindsay Lohan.
Like I know she's doing just fine, but it's like I want her to have her come back.
And I think she's great.
I really do.
She's so good in this.
She looks 10 years younger than the other girls.
And she probably was, to be honest.
So that's part of it.
She looks like very like you want to take care of her.
It's before she kind of got that pardoned edge.
But she's excellent.
Amanda Seyfried is excellent as the dumb one.
Rachel McAdams is awesome as the meanest one.
She's on.
She's unbelievably good as a bully.
Yeah, she is.
And and Kaplan, like you said, it's just super, super funny.
I love this movie, Joe.
I don't I don't I don't have any more unless you do.
I'm ready to talk turkey here on Abigail.
Um, no, sure.
Let's well, yeah, let me do one more.
You know, I rewatched Silver Linings playbook.
Mm hmm.
You seen that one, Joe?
I watched it with my mom and dad when it came out.
We liked it very much.
I really enjoyed it.
I never felt a need to ever rewatch it for whatever reason.
Same.
I had only seen it in theaters.
I loved it.
I remembered really loving it.
And it's nuts.
It's like a crazy screwball comedy.
David O.
Russell does these movies where he has everybody yelling at each other.
They're like always sunny episodes.
And he directs everybody to like improv and be going crazy in every scene.
And I forgot that aspect about it.
Like it's really intense.
Just every scene is like six people screaming at each other.
Mm hmm.
Bradley Cooper is awesome as a guy who's released from a kind of psych ward
along with Chris Tucker, who has a very odd sort of small supporting role.
Yeah, I forgot he was in it.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's interesting.
His parents are De Niro, who is awesome as his dad back in Philly,
who's obsessed with football.
And his mom is the great Jackie Weaver.
I completely forgotten this that De Niro has extreme OCD that he is trying to
keep in check.
And I thought that was the heart and soul of the movie is that De Niro loves
Bradley Cooper so much and also gets him because he's got his own affliction.
I had completely forgotten that, but I loved it.
Yeah, go ahead.
The movie is kind of like rec.
It's kind of like a funny requiem for a dream where instead of drug addiction,
everybody's got their their mental thing that they're dealing with.
They all have a different thing.
Yes.
Yeah.
And that's what Jennifer.
Jennifer Lawrence, who he meets, who I learned was 21 when they did this movie
and Bradley Cooper was 37, which you would not have that today probably.
But Jennifer Lawrence is man, she's good.
I weirdly forget about her.
Like whenever I watch everything that she comes out with, I always think that it's
good and she's good, including her comedy, No Hard Feelings, which I liked a lot.
But like she's really great in this.
You buy her as a sex addict, as a fuck up.
I forgot that too, that she fucked like 20 people at her job and that's why she
got fired.
She's got weird sex addiction stuff.
It's not a perfect movie.
The way they handle the mental illness is all played, you know, pretty big, pretty
broad.
I forgot too, that it all ends in a dance competition, which was really when the
movie starts to kind of go off the rails a little bit, but really entertaining.
I think David O Russell has completely lost this touch.
He's made several movies in a row where I'm just like, wow, this guy, I think
directors, once they get richer and more isolated, just lose the ability to
connect with humanity.
And Russell has definitely done that.
If you watched Amsterdam or others, other, other shit he's done, but I love
this movie.
I think it's, it's, you know, strong B plus a minus the acting is what sells it.
Let's talk about Abigail Joe.
I was just looking up David.
He's 65 and he was like 50.
He's, we're all old, man.
I don't know.
He's, I guess he has been around that long.
Jesus Christ.
All right.
He's a guy who's dodged some shit too.
Do you remember that story?
Of course there's the video of him calling Lily Tomlin a cunt, but do you remember
the story of him holding his, that was, that's on video.
You can watch him screaming at her and calling her a cunt.
It's nuts.
And I love that Lily Tomlin is so old school that she's like, go fuck yourself.
Like, like she's just, it's just two old people yelling.
Made me absolutely love her.
Made me absolutely love her that she, that she didn't take it and everything
else.
But he also has the story that you can look up where he has a trans daughter
or trans niece, I'm sorry.
And he's like spotting her at the gym, holding her feet while she's doing
sit -ups.
And then he reaches in and starts squeezing her tits and gets thrown out
of the gym.
And like, this was national news.
And this guy has given a hundred million dollar budgets every time out.
Was the niece, did she think it was funny?
Like, I mean, I know that's not appropriate,
but I mean, no, you can Google it.
I mean, the story is, is I think worse than I'm remembering it, but yeah.
I'll Google it.
Yeah.
Okay.
Abigail Joseph, tell us what it's all about.
Well, fairly simple plot.
A little girl who's about eight or nine years old, 10 at the most is kidnapped
at the beginning of the film.
She's clearly part of a very affluent family.
They take her to another palatial estate across town that looks sort of haunted.
By the way, maybe the same set as the, the Stranger Things Dude Santa movie
that you and me saw in Florida.
Oh yeah.
That's a, you're right.
I was like, is this the same fucking house?
That's a good call.
That's a very good call.
The fuck was that called?
Christmas?
Silent Night?
I don't know.
There's one with Joel Kinnaman that John Woo did, but that's different.
Another Santa killer movie.
Hang on.
What's, what's the guy's name from Stranger Things, Joe?
David Harbour.
Harbour.
Santa.
Violent Night.
That's right.
Okay. Good title.
Anyway, when they get to this other house, they're met by,
what's his name?
Christ Almighty.
Giancarlo Esposito.
Yeah, yeah.
By the way, by the way, within one year, Joe, of you and I seeing Violent Night,
the Joel Kinnaman Santa movie is called Silent Night.
It's like we're living in a goddamn joke.
They look like the exact same movie too.
Uh, uh, Esposito tells them their only job is to watch the kid all night and make
sure nobody, you know, wait for the,
wait for the person to show up to give them a bunch of money that they will
split eight ways.
Classic reservoir dog set up, eight criminals all brought together.
They don't know one another.
They're all with six, whatever it is.
They're all in this, in one location.
They even do.
Tell me one thing about myself.
If you know a lot of that dialogue.
Yeah. And also too,
they even do the thing where he's like no names and he gives them like fake
names. I'm like, all right, it's reservoir.
They start to think something's afoot.
They think that there's a plant amongst the crooks, again, reservoir dogs.
Right.
Uh, and then they find out there is no plant amongst the crooks that this
daughter is the daughter of,
of a Kaiser Sosa type, like a fabled gangster.
So evil that blah, blah, blah.
People don't even know if he actually exists.
Um, they tell stories of this guy that he has this hit man that literally cuts
everybody into pieces, blah, blah, blah, blah.
Eventually the girl turns into reveals herself to be a vampire and you realize
she is the hit man and she's not this guy's.
Well, she is this guy's daughter, but they're, they're clearly a family of
vampires and, and, and they're also gangsters.
And this girl is also not 10.
She's like 300 or whatever.
So it goes from there.
It's, it's just cat and mouse game of survival.
They're in the house.
The girl is loose.
Blah, blah, blah.
Now the big question you're going to ask is why wouldn't an all powerful vampire
who has run of the house, make a waste of everybody, you know, quite quickly.
And that's the question I was asking.
And the device they use to explain why she's drawing it out and not just
slaughtering them is that she likes to play with her food.
She likes to, to, to, to get people scared, dah, dah, dah, dah.
But they never really justify that.
So for instance, in it, um, you know, the Pennywise says like he needs the kids
to be scared because if they're not scared, they taste better when they're scared.
And if they're not scared, he doesn't get the full like power when he eats them.
So this needed something like that.
I thought, cause I'm like, it's not an, she, the, the vampire girl leaves
herself vulnerable way too many times.
They do a pretty good job of justifying it each time.
There's a part where they get her in a cage and you're like, I don't
understand they have her in a cage.
She's like negotiating her way out, like, and then eventually she just hits the
door of the cage and blows it open.
And you realize she could get out whenever she wants.
She's fucking with them.
There are moments like that where it's kind of cool and I buy it.
And then there are other moments where I don't.
Ultimately it reaches the, you know, fever pitch of there's only a
couple of characters left.
One is the main woman and the other is the guy from the offer who played
Robert Evans.
I forget the actor's name, Dan Stevens.
And you know, Giancarlo comes back.
He turns out to, I don't know if I should get into the whole ending.
It's just going to get confusing.
I can get into it if we need to.
But let's put it this way.
By the third act of this movie, I was, I, I had gone from going into this.
Wow.
This is really interesting.
Cool.
It's like a Tarantino thing to why is this so fucking complicated guys?
It's just, and I find myself saying that a lot on this podcast lately.
It's the same thing I said about late night with the devil, which by the way,
is the only time I have ever responded to comments on our Patreon page was
two, two fans that they criticized our take on welcome to late night with the
devil. I thought we needed to respond.
But anyway, it's, it's, it's the same thing.
It's such a simple point a to point B premise.
Just, just make it scary and fun.
Like they do it's dust till dawn.
They do it in dust till dawn.
The vampires are out there.
We're in here.
How are we going to do this?
And, and they do.
And, and that's it.
And that's all this had to be.
But when I saw the trailer, I was like, thank God, because really my favorite
tone and it's so rarely done well is comedy horror.
And the trailer looked like people reacting, not with jokes, but like with
funny reactions to scary things.
And I was like, this is going to be a really fun horror movie in the style of
ready or not, which these guys recently made, you know?
And it's, it's kind of not what intrigued me about it just now is that this was
created to be a part of the universal classic monsters update that universal
was doing along the lines of the invisible man with Elizabeth Moss, which I
liked a lot more than Joe or Renfield, which we both fucking hated.
But this is part of that, which they don't even announce to the public.
Oh, because her dad is Dracula.
Yeah.
So this was supposed to be part of that sort of rebirth of the universal projects.
It was originally titled Dracula's daughter.
The same name as the 1936 film it's based on did not know that either.
Universal said that they had considered a singular continuity on the mummy from
2017, which I don't even remember coming out.
Yeah.
The Tom Cruise one, I think each release will continue to be rooted in the horror
genre with no restrictions on budget rating or genre.
They are not part of a shared interconnected universe.
Each film instead will stand on its own.
This new direction is filmmaker driven, inviting innovative filmmakers with
original bold ideas for these characters to come in and pitch us.
So that's cool.
Yeah, it's cool.
But like, let us know if you're doing a new universal universe, let the fans
know who might be interested.
I don't get it.
There might have been some desire to change this from Dracula's daughter to
hide the fact that she's a vampire.
But then all marketing shows that she's a vampire.
So who knows?
Yeah, I like the premise.
I thought the little girl was very good.
Girl was good.
I love Katherine Newton from Lisa Frankenstein.
I think she's talented.
I like Dan Stevens.
I liked him in this.
He was funny.
Angus Cloud, who passed away, RIP from Euphoria.
It's got a good cast and Esposito.
I just, I didn't smile.
The humor wasn't hitting and the scares really weren't hitting.
I didn't find this scary at all.
And that was the bummer for me.
It's like a, it's a perfectly average movie in that it doesn't do anything badly,
but it certainly doesn't do anything great.
It's just sort of there to me.
I thought, I thought the humor was there.
It was a little, look, it's a very cliched movie, like, you know,
the slick crooks and, you know, like you said, the whole,
the whole scene where she's like, you know, tell me something about me.
Oh, big boy, you were in the military, you know,
I could tell by that semper fi stance, you know, you're like, all right.
You know, like that, there's cliche shit like that in it.
But I did, I did laugh a couple of times.
I thought, you know, when, when, when the big like Russian guy,
whatever the fuck he was, when that Stevens would be like,
you fucking moron, she's, you know, whatever.
Yeah.
He would, I thought Matt Stevens was pretty good.
I thought the main girl was very good.
I thought Matt.
Melissa Fomero.
But Melissa.
I'm sorry, Melissa Barrera.
God, I mixed these two.
Barrera was great.
I thought Matt Stevens was good.
He played it a little too cartoony.
Yeah.
I thought, what's his name?
The kid that died stole the show.
And I was like, that's a really sad that he's dead.
Cause that's a kid.
Like when he died in the movie, I was sad.
Cause I was like, this kid is the best kid in here, man.
Yeah.
And I didn't realize he died in real life.
That was sad.
But.
He's good that cat.
He was, you know, he's a drug addict, but he's great on euphoria too.
But, you know, I thought, look, vampires, you're going to have to do,
you're going to have to do like a Bram Stoker's Dracula Coppola refacing of
vampires at this point to make vampires scary again.
Like you got to do something new.
They're not scary anymore.
They're not.
I had a great zombie idea movie and I started outlining it and I bored myself.
I know it's a great idea.
And I was just like, I can't, I don't want to watch another zombie movie.
I just threw it in the trash.
And no matter how like glowing the eyes are and how jagged the teeth are and
whatever, it's like vampires are just not scary anymore.
They've got to get back to atmosphere and they don't do anything in this
movie with atmosphere.
This is the part that just stumps me with these, with these attempts at
rebooting something, whatever.
It's like, guys, you have the most precious and valuable treasure trove on
planet earth.
It trumps even Freddy Krueger.
How do you not understand the product more?
How do you not understand the focus on atmosphere?
The need for a certain type of direction.
This was well directed and it was well acted and it was well shot.
Hey, it's better than Renfield.
I'll tell you that way better.
Yeah.
Renfield was this was, this was a solid enough movie.
I just thought they over complicated it.
And then by the end, so look, this is the first of all, they did, they did the
thing in this that I hate and I've complained about it before when it comes
to zombie movies and vampire movies, I can't stand bending the rules for
convenience.
There were people that got bit in this movie that took hours to turn and then
other people that would turn immediately, always coincidentally as the plot
needed them to turn is when they turned.
It's lazy writing.
It's stupid.
Forget it.
Whatever.
So they do that at the end, Matt explain it to us.
Like have there's an antidote in there and they all get to take a sip, but
somebody gets a double sip.
So they have, you know, you can do whatever you want something making shit
up like at the end a little bit when Esposito comes back and he's the vampire
and he reveals that he lets Matt or he sorry, Matt, what's his face?
Let's him bite him.
Yeah.
Dan Stevens, Dan Stevens.
Sorry.
So he can then bite.
He's because his plot is he's going to kill Abigail.
Yeah, he's going to get her powers.
And of course he turns immediately and then he harms Abigail.
He doesn't kill her and then immediately turns on the main girl.
And I'm like, why is he turning on her?
Like they don't have any like this doesn't make any sense.
Yeah.
They've already they've already shown that the vampires can control themselves.
Like this.
Why would he?
It's not enough that he's just suddenly power hungry.
He actually and also his backstory was kind of interesting.
He was a guy trying to do the right thing as a cop.
And then he went undercover and he was too deep and he couldn't get out and all
that.
And it's like that guy doesn't sound like an inherent bad guy to me.
Sounds like a good guy that went down the wrong road.
Give a redemption of that guy would have been great at the end.
They don't do it.
He turns then on the main character.
Then Abigail, because she's not dead, comes back and hurts him.
Then he bites her again.
And Abigail says out loud, you you won't kill me unless you drain me.
And then he doesn't drain her.
And then he leaves her there to what?
Jump up and help out the other girl again late.
It's stupid.
So Dracula comes in at the very end.
You meet the father and the little girl.
There's this plot line where she's mad that her dad doesn't care about her and
doesn't have an interest in her as his daughter, which fine.
But then like at the end when she's helping the main character and she's she's
basically almost fighting her own father to stay away from the main character
shows up so she can save her life.
She goes, she was there for me when you weren't.
And I'm like, guys, what are this for Christ sakes?
Daddy issues with Dracula.
Yeah, it was it was crazy.
It's just too much.
It's too many layers.
It's like I guys you had me.
I was having fun.
I was enjoying this.
It got away from itself because you're doing too many gotcha moment.
You know, David Mamet said this thing, something along the lines of if you can
surprise your audience in the third act, you've got a good movie.
If you can surprise them in the last 10 minutes, you've got a classic or something
like that.
And I feel like that quote, you know, cycloned throughout Hollywood and every
screenwriter and whatever has it like on a, you know, embroidered banner above
their desk.
Yeah.
And you see these movies where it's just like twist, twist, twist, even Mamet fell
victim to it.
Some of his later movies, you're like, dude, enough with the twists.
Like Jesus Christ, the obsession with twists to me, of course, a great twist is a
great thing.
There's been many, many, many movies with amazing twists that I'll remember forever.
But when you're forcing it in, not only does it sort of make the ending of the
A lot of times the twist undoes everything you've been watching and you're like,
what?
You didn't need to do that.
It's a drag and it's worked its way into the television business too.
You write a multi -cam pilot.
Where's the twist?
The twist.
Like it's strange.
I don't get it because then if you're always expecting a twist, a twist is never
surprising.
Yeah.
I would say this is a solid C movie.
I'd revisit it.
I'd watch it with, I'd watch this one with like my parents.
Like, yeah, let's, you know, you guys will get a kick out of this.
And even after a second watch, I could see myself maybe liking it more and, you know,
maybe even owning it.
But for now I was like, it wasn't bad.
It just had too much shit going on.
But then again, it is that kind of wild popcorn summer horror movie.
So maybe that's kind of the point is like, you know, so I'm not mad at it.
My hog's not down.
It's not necessarily up.
It's just kind of out.
Same.
Yeah.
I'm, I'm out.
I'm out.
Maybe slightly raised, you know, maybe I'm, maybe I'm taking a pee outside and the
wind hits it, but I'm not hard.
Yeah.
You know?
I'm at, I'm at Pat's family reunion.
His mom comes out with a tray of lemonade.
She said she bends slightly over to set it down on the table.
I get it.
I get the underwear crease.
I go, Oh, this is Walsh.
All right.
We didn't need to bring her into this.
I am at the Patrick Walsh on Instagram.
That's about it.
At this point, Miss Pat show season four kicks off in a couple of weeks on BET plus
May 23rd, I want to say, and we will be back with a discussion of the film called
Civil War.
Newport, Rhode Island, May 25th, the Jane Pickens theater is the final show of I
never promised you a Rose garden for the spring.
And one of the final shows of the tour period.
There will be a couple of shows in the fall to be announced soon, very early fall
because I will be shooting this finally.
And I will be announcing that I'm shooting this quite soon.
So keep your ears peeled.
Please.
You can also catch me at Skankfest in Vegas in September, late September.
I'll be on the bird crusher fully loaded tour for select dates in June.
And I got some other not the dates I'm on, but she might be on other dates.
Yeah.
Anyway, and then I got some other stuff coming up.
Select things coming up that I'll be announcing over the summer.
That won't be.
I promise you a rose garden, but other stuff anyway, folks, also my new YouTube
and Patreon of solo content will be launching soon.
I will keep you posted on all that very soon.
And that's that.
Come to Joey roses in New York City.
Joey roses .com and joderosa .com for tickets to the shows.
We'll see you next time, folks, and we'll see you in hell.