Huff, Puff, and spin the house down at Golden Nugget Online Casino.
Right now, new players can deposit just 5 bucks and get 500 total spins on Huff and
Mortpuff, the slot that's blowing players away.
Download the Golden Nugget Online Casino app and use promo code Nugget1.
That's code Nugget1 to enjoy 50 spins a day for your first 10 days.
All on our players favorite game of the summer.
Now's the time to score daily bonuses and spin for all the bacon on the game everyone's
hoffat about.
At Golden Nugget Online Casino, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamberler.
Please play responsibly.
21 and over, physically present in Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania, and West Virginia
only, void in Ontario.
New customers only.
Non -withdrawable casino spins issued as 50 spins per day for 10 days valid for featured game
only and expire each day after 24 hours.
C -Terms at GoldenNuggetCasino .com slash promos ends at 11 .59pm Eastern on August 31st, 2025.
The football season is full of guarantees. And here's another. No other sportsbook has
been offered this good. With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now
until October. If your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash. If you bet on
football with fanatics, you're either winning or winning money back in fan cash. Guaranteed.
Switch to Fanatic Sportsbook, winning hits different here.
Monthly 21 -plus, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamberler, offer not available in all
states, terms apply, see Fanatic Sportsbook app.
Happy New Year, everybody, a belated, happy New Year from us, your friends that will
see you in hell.
The podcast that is now part of the Fengoria Podcast Network, it has been since the beginning.
For more information about this network, including other programs, how to follow, our show,
other shows, we'll find episodes of any of these shows, including we'll see you in hell.
Well, of course, please visit Vingoria .com, and here we are, Patty, 2016, January, about
to watch the movie Nurse.
I was whistling old Lang Zine.
I could tell, and thank you, for bringing a little flavor, you're welcome, to the podcast.
What's new with us, we're on different sides of the couch, I can tell you that.
It feels wrong, but it also feels so right.
It's where I moved. We're in my new apartment. I had a birthday. I'm 35 years old. You're only 35. Yeah, you bastard
When my father was 35, I would have been
12 right God, that's disturbing
You're only 35. If I had a 12 -year -old it would be dead
Long dead
Why do you say that like I wouldn't think about it very much?
I wouldn't think about the child's death very much.
It would have died so long ago.
Why do you say that, though?
I mean, maybe it would have whipped some responsibility into me,
but I just, I'm in no place.
I'm starting to maybe kind of think about possibly
getting in the place, but I'm not in the place.
At this point in my life, I don't know if this will
stay the constant forever, but I'd rather kill myself
than have a child.
Well, wrap it up, Joseph.
I just I have no desire to have a child. This dog, old Connie boy right here. That's all I need. Yeah, he's right next to me. Seems to me to be pretty much the same responsibility. Not at all.
You got to run home, walking, you feed him a couple times a day, you walk him a couple
times a day.
You know, he goes and sleeps in a crate at night time.
He lays around the house, there's no crying, there's no teach me about things.
It's nothing.
You'll never develop.
It's great.
You don't have to teach your kid about that.
But the problem with a child is it develops.
That's always been my issue with it, it's like it's not, it starts sassing you back.
Who wants any of that?
But maybe you get an awesome kid. There are awesome. Maybe I was an awesome kid. What if you don't my parents that I never cried
I just sat and judged people. I'd like the baby years. I think that'd be fun
And you have cute time with the baby and then after that. That's what a dog is like. It's like a baby Instagram likes
Yeah, you know, that's all we're out there looking for you
You're a your energies down today. I will I will say
Does it sound like you're ready to conquer the new year?
I am. I feel like I've already been conquering it and I'm weary from that.
Really?
Because everyone kind of looks at me walking on the street and they're like,
this guy's been conquering 2016.
And I come here and I, you know, I've already spent my A and B game.
You're getting my C, frankly.
You're getting my C. I'm not going to lie to you right now.
I already did. I did Jimmy Parto's podcast today.
Never enough on it. Yes, and it was I loved Jimmy part of two and I love doing that podcast
But it is a solid two hours. Yeah, we're more of talking and and and with no real theme unless changed since I last
Yeah, you just kind of futs it around so yeah, so the idea of talking to you now for two hours is not exciting
But I did meet I did meet a very nice lady on the road
Who told me that she's a huge fan of the podcast. Oh, right?
And she said I love listening to you guys talk
Because I feel like I'm watching a movie with my friends, and they're just talking the whole time
And I said I said god bless you. I'm glad you feel that way because about the 60 -minute mark
I don't even know what I'm saying anymore. I'd say I always have a nice time. I have a nice time too. We visit we talk
Shoot the breeze we're gonna watch some nudity you pour some sort of a soda cocktail every time something with soda
Would you actually not every time because you never have soda, but this is a Jack with a splash of DC Diet Coke Diet
You brought your own Diet Coke. It was in the fridge. Oh, okay. I've just bought some nice
natural cane sugar soda at the new coffee shop that opened near my apartment. Is it the new green coke?
No, which I haven't even seen advertised at work. We have green coke green coke is like it's like another version of diet and it's gross
But it's also 90 calories, which is like, it's like not diet because they keep trying to make this like hybrid like
It's not totally as pertain. It's like some of that and then right sugar
And it only just tastes like Diet Coke. Is it worldwide or are we in a test market for it?
I don't know, but I got it. I was very excited to try it because I thought maybe finally it's like a compromise and it just tastes like Diet Coke
Yeah, you can't ask pertain is like garlic. Yeah, once it's in there. You're not there's no way you're not tasting it
You know at least once a year I'll go up to a bartender and I'll go
Know what I'm gonna have a
Little ditty about Jack and diet
And no one has ever laughed on
I would to this day no one's ever laughed at where you to tell me a bartender did laugh at it
I would go and demand he'd be fired
I think it's pretty strong. That was a bartender and all I listened to all night was like, hey bro, yeah a couple more shots
Is the Yeager and somebody comes up to me like a
Classy distinguished gentleman like myself. Hey, man. I got a little ditty about Jack and Diane
I'd laugh and I go, hey, you're all right, but it's on the house. I wouldn't even know what the fuck you were talking about
John Cougar Melican. No, I know I get the reference. I'm saying like John Cougar. Where are we not talking about Jack and Diet Coke right now?
I'd be like what the hell is diet like I wouldn't I wouldn't even know what you were saying
Diet coke they get it. That's that's what's infuriating is that they usually do get it. They just don't laugh out
Well, look
Maybe I maybe I'm just meant to be a bartender because I'm not finding the humor in it either all right
Well, then go bartend. I'll finish up this pot
I want to have a drink tonight, but I had so many last night
and
And I'm just not going to drink tonight.
It helps me speak freely, it helps, it helps all of us speak freely.
My problem is as I get wanting me and then I just, you know, I want to keep going.
I'm going to finish this and then want to go paint the town and it'll only be midnight.
Let's think about it.
You don't have to work tomorrow?
Worked at 11.
So you'll stay up til 2 a .m. tonight.
I always do.
I'm not against it.
It's Wednesday.
You ain't got shit to do tomorrow.
There's a bar over there called L something I can't remember the name. Uh -huh. I want to check it out apparently. It's a real beer swill and
like
Like tough guy room
Hey, I can be tough when I need to be I'd go over there for a beer. I can't be tough folks
That was a lot alright ladies and gentlemen
We're watching the movie nurse today. Why? Because Pat seen it and I haven't another new twist for the new year
We've never done one where I didn't see it and Pat did but I watched it pretty recently and
And it's reasonably entertaining and it's chock full of nudity. It's got Paz de la Huerta, who seems
criminally insane. I don't know who that is. She was on boardwalk empire where she was naked
every episode. Okay. I like that. Uh, and that's what this is. It's kind of like she's a sexy nurse and she
kills people. Okay. Very good. We're back on the Netflix because the new setup involves my new Mac mini computer.
thank you again to Keith Robinson for betting me that Star Wars would not make
more money than the Avengers and pretty staying me $500 when he lost that
I can't believe you paid that but that's the kind of that's the amount that you
can be like you know man sorry he's a betting man he likes to gamble so I took
that money to the store I bought me a Mac Mini and our new setup is watching
these on the Mac Mini instead of the Apple TV so if you want to pause now and go
your Netflix and look up Nurse and watch along with us. Please do so. If not, you don't have to.
And here comes the count off, Patty.
Why don't you do the honors? Okay.
I'm going to go one, two, three, play, here we go, one, two, three, play.
Now when Nurse, there we are.
Nurse was actually released theatrically 3D.
It was released in 3D.
Yeah.
It's coming in a little loud for me.
It's a little loud for me, too.
Can you, do you want to talk for a minute while I adjust it?
Yeah, I'll talk for a minute.
You got to cover this.
Okay.
Yeah, so yeah, Nurse was released 3D and there's been a few of these horror movies
that are released like almost under the radar.
Like my, what's the one?
My Bloody Valentine?
My Bloody Valentine 3D?
It's still very loud, Jim.
That's better, yes.
They opened with a title screen about how the medical profession is full of malpractice
and people killing each other and things like that.
We're opening on a butt shot.
I like how they felt like they needed to justify the purpose of this movie.
Yeah.
Well, it's probably to pad it out.
It's an hour 23.
It is an hour 23 and folks, we're not going to lie to you.
That's part of why we chose this too.
It's about 10 .30 on a school night for us.
Yeah, we're like let's do the shining and then realize it's two and a half hours long. We'll do something better next time
I mean, we're not I'm not saying this is bad. I've never seen it, but
Now why is she in this
Hours outfit already
She's on the hunt. I think it's what she does is she targets like cheaters married guys
Assholes and it's own Benjamin and then she kills them. It's sort of like a dexter almost
Which is probably how it's my buddy Owen
Say he's too attractive to be a comedian. He's a very good -looking man
And he's the tallest man I've ever met in my life. Oh wow. I'm gonna get to see my buddy Owen get killed. Yeah, exciting. Yeah
Now have you ever seen one of your friends killed in a movie or television only in real life?
And I yeah speaking of Dexter oddly enough I
dated this girl for a while when I first moved to LA and her friend was an aspiring actress and
And then she started getting rolls. She played Don Draper's mom in a flashback in madman, but her big break
She was like I'm gonna be on the season premiere of Dexter
I'm in a scene with John Liffgaugh, which is probably the best season of Dexter season four. Okay, and I'm like
Oh, that's so great. I watched that show so I'll be watching anyway. It's so cool that I get to see it
And she's actually don't think that's my friend Owen by the way, I think I made a mistake
I'm sorry to cut your story off. It doesn't look like him now that I see it
It just popped into my head. Sorry, go ahead also her ass is out in the club
She's got a she's got a terrifying look to her. Yeah already. She looks like a lunatic
Who's she honestly looks like a girl I would have dated at some point in my life now finish your story
I'm sorry, okay
So anyway, I tune into the season for me of Dexter. I've spent like hours with this girl
She's my girlfriend's best friend and I turn on Dexter in the opening scene. She gets full -frontally naked
Bush included. I'm like holy shit. Then John Lithgaum murders her spoiler alert
brings her into a bathtub and like
Tenderly caresses her completely nude body as he like her she bleeds out into the bathtub and I'm like
Wouldn't you tell somebody?
buddy. Hey, not only am I going to be on Dexter, I'm going to be
full -frontally nude and murdered. She probably designed an NDA. Maybe. I
thought she was going to be like a barista who sells Dexter a cup of
coffee. Well, I mean, I'll tell you what's weird is this guy's about to
get his dick that off. You know, how many times did she think that was
going to happen when she was watching Harry and the Henderson's? Yeah,
probably never. You know, that's a weird situation to be in with John
on Lithgow. Yeah, exactly. You know, she just cut his dick with a scalpel. And can
I tell you, he did not react big enough. Now, is this, is this girl a good actor? Or
is this, she's, she's convincingly crazy, kind of like a Sharon Stone, you completely
buy that she's insane. But she's not a strong actress now. I don't know if I'm buying
this character she's putting out there already the nurse it's it's I don't know it's it's
real monotone the delivery I don't I don't know she wasn't great on board Empire I only saw
the first season of that show and I'd like to finish it at some point who did she play
on that show she played bishemi's like mall like you know she was kind of like on call to bang him
and she was always naked.
Well, there's the reason the movie was in 3D.
Oh, God, terrible CGI.
So she shoved him off a roof and one of those...
One of those fence metal -iron, cast -iron fence posts went through him.
Yeah.
I'll, uh, the Omen, I believe, is the movie that happens in.
And, uh, and it was an unnecessarily weird shot
that clearly was made just for 3D.
yeah this is kind of weird it does like a you can tell they're going for a camp
thing but it's never really funny or scary which is the danger of the horror
comedy I know I always want more niecey Nash in my heart movies and she's in
this yeah she is I don't know if I have a frame of reference to say I like her do
not like her I just don't think hard when I think niecey Nash or should do but
She's effective. She's great on getting on which is an HBO drama. I do like her on that show. And I thought she was funny on a Reno 9 -1 -1. Yes, yes.
I, I missed, I'm a massive comedy buff and have been since I was five years old, but I completely missed mad TV. I had never seen an episode of it.
We tell you something you didn't miss shit really yeah, it wasn't that funny now the other night
They did their reunion show and it was done all really on the cheap
But I was like I wonder if I might have enjoyed this. I did find there to be a shockingly racist Asian character
That I guess was one of the biggest characters on the show done by the woman from getting on Alex Borstein
Who voices the mom on family guy yes
And a lot of this Bobby Lee and a lot of this I was like this is would probably not fly to that it wasn't and there was only 10 years ago. It wasn't that funny of a show. I love Bobby. I have friends that were. I mean Bobby Lee's Larry's key and peel were all.
I'm not friends with them but they were both on the show.
But yeah, there there have been some great people on the show, but I never found the show to be that great overall.
Okay, I can best describe it like this.
Mad magazine is funnier than mad TV.
Oh, I forgot that it was there were one on the sand.
Yeah, so, you know, and I'm not hating on mad magazine, but you're not reading it and, you know, doubled over.
No, unless maybe you're like Homer Simpson or something, you know, right?
the, uh, look at Judd Nelson making an appearance.
Judd Nelson, you sort of figure he retired from acting, but the truth is he's
probably just not getting work, which is a little sad.
But I mean, that's pretty cool that he was in a movie that was in theaters again,
because I think he was kind of, yeah, is that Kathleen Turner?
You know, I, I watched, you know, dumb and dumb or two.
And, uh, I saw some California Cation, which is a show that got pretty bad by the end.
but Kathleen Turner, her entire role in both of those projects and in most of the things she does now,
is everyone tells her how fucking ugly she is and how much she looks like a man.
There's 800 jokes in dumb and dumb or two about how ugly she is.
And look, she was unbelievably sexy in her prime but people age.
You know, Jesus Christ, like she's a decent looking woman for her age.
I it really bothers me and you know dumb and dumb was kind of a nasty movie in some ways, but it was also very sweet
Dumb and number two like on the 20th minute of Kathleen Turner looks like a bulldog jokes
I'm like I want to write this woman a letter and say that I find her to be attractive. Well, why don't you?
I mean I should have who's stopping you and again she like she gets sent the script for Asian has to send her a script where it's like you're playing
really disgusting looking woman. It breaks my heart.
That hurts me to hear that. I don't like to hear that.
That was woman who people wanted to fuck for 30 years.
That scene in War the Roses, where she like seduces Danny DeVito.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
The part where she walks on her hands and everything.
Yeah, she was something else, man.
War the Roses is spectacular.
I love it.
I remember my priest doing a
Homelier a monologue or whatever about war the roses and how evil it was because it was about divorce
Yeah, I was like nine years old and they're like isn't it funny a couple divorcing just shameful on and off
Hey, you know, I respect the guy for for sticking to it hardcore
Priest yeah, if you're gonna do it do it right, right? Yeah, you know good friend for not being a half -ass
I don't agree with him, but I just admire how fucking nasty that movie was and it was a huge hit
I loved it and they both died at the end. They'd they'd do they'd do it's incredible
I remember the first time I saw it. I couldn't believe that they both died at the end. Yeah, I
Could not believe it. I was a death to smoochy fan. Love death to smoochy. Yeah, I mean Davido's just one of the sickest fox in the world
Yeah, he's you know even his kids movie Matilda's fucked up. Is it? It's really dark
This is Katrina Bowdoin of 30 Rock fan.
This is the girl from 30 Rock?
Yeah.
Who'd she play on there?
I didn't watch TV.
We're seeing this guy.
This guy's button, you see, not no nudity of Bowdoin.
Well, that's stupid.
I think the kid is from high school musical.
That's upsetting.
Yeah.
You know, he's got a Donald Glover vibe.
This kid.
The, uh, just watch Donald Glover play, uh,
the smartest man in the world and the Martian.
That's literally what he plays.
Yeah, he plays like this lazy, stoner guy who strolls in and is like,
oh, I think I can solve your problems, NASA.
Is that movie good?
It's pretty solid.
It's not a comedy.
It's just one best comedy.
I don't understand.
Yeah, what is that?
I mean, the Golden Globes is the most worthless television program on Earth.
They just buy the awards.
words, the best comedy television went to Mozart and the jungle, which no one has seen.
And I think it's a drama as well.
But basically it's like everyone behind the Martian is like, all right, we know we have
a good movie here that people really enjoyed, but it's not going to win best picture drama.
So let's just enter it as a comedy.
And the Golden Globes people are like, yeah, that's fine.
It was Obama's favorite movie of the year.
You know, it celebrates science and it celebrates intelligence.
And I like that about it a lot. It's very nerdy like the last line of the movie is like
Well science sure is special isn't it? It's like that nerdy. You keep some you should watch the school spoiler alert if you haven't seen it. I
That tells you nothing. I'm never gonna see that a narrator says he's a wonderful fan. I'm asking you to tell me the end of the movie
Oh, no, I don't want to do that for the podcast. I just said spoiler alert. Well now
Do you think Matt Damon dies alone on Mars? Do you think he comes home? All right. Well, you're right
I'm right. Yeah, yeah, it's like a big triumph. Yeah, but it's a good movie. I liked it. Look
It's a good team of people. It's just not the kind of movie I care about it looks like castaway with a lot of gardening in it
Well, I fucking love castaway. I'm Martian. It's nowhere near as good as that, but I did like it. I
Enjoyed castaway. I've heard the Revenant compared to castaway. I don't see any comparison. I have a castaway really
Kind of broke me up as if I can get a little pretentious as like a metaphor for loneliness
and that's what I thought was pretty fantastic.
I didn't, I, I haven't seen Castaway in many years.
Yeah, but I do love the part where after he gets rescued,
they have that party form and then he's alone in the room
and he just picks up that king crab leg.
Yeah, and like, just throws it like you gotta be kidding me.
Yeah, like in bridesmaids, I love that.
Crystal Wig when she's sobbing, watching a movie,
it's Castaway and she's not watching
like when Harry met Sally or something you know like Castaways to me a perfect metaphor for like
just being completely alone and and then how hard it is to readjust to people when you're not
alone anymore. Can I just take us back to the movie for a second? Yeah. Did you see? Look at this,
she's showering in her underwear because she clearly has some no nudity clause. But then why
Chester folks. This is an all hard R horror movie. That's not even what I was going to put at the shot of the shower head with the water coming out of it
Just so you can have the 3d water. Yeah, so stupid. This movie's making me angry. Um, I am finding the main character sexier and sexier as we go.
That's what she does. That's kind of her thing. But she's got like, uh, you know, I write for a show that does a lot of current event jokes.
And I look at a couple different websites each day to see what the new like Celeb Gossip is so I can be up on it and
There was a period of like three years where she was always like
Tit falling out of her dress
Blackout drunk fainting at a bar like legs spread like every night like a Wednesday night. There she is
All right, you know, look at that. Look at that. Yes
We sell like a couple of pigs
We're just disgusting. Yeah, I know
but she is she is I'm seeing the appeal yeah I get it too now do you see her boobs in this oh yeah
yeah constantly I just came from seeing daddy's home they were going to say I just came I came a
little bit all right you saw daddy's home god only knows why I'm a huge fan of both uh
feral and wallberg well then there's your answer you know but the movie looks terrible and like
there's so many comedies that are just completely panned. A great example would be the remake of the
cation, which is not a classic by any means, but I laugh throughout, and that's all I need.
And critics made it seem like it was, uh, you know, a fucking disaster, and it wasn't.
So now sometimes they're right. You and I get hard. Get hard wasn't good, but I'm like, Kevin
Hart, well, Farrell, why would I not say this? I didn't see get hard. You saw that with that.
Not with me. We saw get hard together. We did. I've never seen that movie.
We'll Ferrell and Kevin Hart pretty moving. Yeah, I know what it is. I've never seen it. We didn't. No, I didn't see that either
Because I was like this movie looks terrible. I think we talked about it on this podcast. We might have talked about they're in jail
You saw it at the Glendale Galleria. Yeah, I didn't see it with you. I've never seen the film. All right. I don't know who I fucking saw with
Yeah, it's disturbing. I didn't think it looked funny. And I'm a fan of both of those guys. Well now dad
I didn't see it daddy's home did not look funny either
Right
You know on the last podcast we talked about get hard and you said yeah that fucking sucked. We saw it
Pat I didn't see it with you. I might have said it sucked because I thought it looked like it sucked, but I never saw the movie
It looked like a terrible movie, so I didn't see it
I'm baffled by this. What do you think I'm playing a prank on you? No, I guess not
But I just the lamest prank ever. I can remember who I saw like every movie of my life with and I couldn't really can't apparently I can't
You're brains going to shit. I don't think my brain's going to ship. What's that from cuz your brain's gone to shit
What is that from what movies that from I don't know that's gonna kill me no no because you're
Turning your brain into muck
Yeah, you better check some because your brain's gone to shit. I can't remember anyway. Go ahead. How was daddy's home?
so
I don't give a shit about Walbert really, but I love Ferrell. I like Walbert in a comedy and
I figure Ferrell is gonna make me laugh ten times minimum whether the movie's good or bad and I was wrong folks
It's really bad and a woman I work with who I think is very funny said it was good
But then I remembered she's got kids and she never leaves the house and sometimes you go to see a movie once a year that movie is going to seem pretty good
It's really
Aggressively bad all of the music is from 2001
What's the music like give me like the year 2001?
It's right now give me like the hives
Like hey to say I told you so and what is the significance dirt off your shoulder Jay Z
It's literally all the music is from two thousand. Tell me how many times do white guys walk in slow motion to the JZ song
Well, that's the scene they do it. But white guys walking slow motion 10 times in the movie they walk in slow motion to
Dirt off your shoulder once because how many fucking movies are it's in every trailer?
How many guys walk into a place in slow motion to hip -hop music?
It's it's every fucking movie. It's honestly even though I know it's not
I'm gonna just say it's racist because I'm so sick of it all right, I'll back you on that like stop it
What the the entire joke is that a white guy is walking to rap music?
Stop it goes got an unbelievable body. I'm not talking like Howard Stern right now, but I mean it really is
She really is a tremendous. She's just naked the entire specimen. Yeah, it's all natural. Yeah, that's
I'm confused. I don't really feel comfortable watching this movie with you anymore.
I chose it so we could perhaps take our friendship to the next level.
She's got this amazingly boss pimped out apartment and then she's got a carry coffee machine.
Carricks, you know, they're not cheap. Guess they are. They're pretty cheap.
I used to live in an apartment building that had a
carig in the lobby.
Uh -huh.
And I go down there and have eight, ten cups a day.
And then one day I was like, you know what?
If you're heating a small plastic thing
that can't be good for your cancer was.
Well, that's why I switched coffee pots.
I used to have the carig big time.
I switched because of that.
But then my parents are still in the carig and they found
They found cake cops that are the safe plastic or whatever.
Okay.
There's like a safe plastic you can use, so I guess that's what you do.
They make some that aren't.
They make a majority of them aren't.
I would assume.
That's pretty disturbing.
I would assume they're not.
So they recognize the cancer risk because they make an alternative.
There's nothing, there's been...
Look, I switched just to be safe.
There's been really no proof yet about the hot Jesus.
She's going full frontal.
old frontal phones. That's full vagina shot. Yeah. Um, not no bush. That was like,
full. You just saw her vagina. Yeah. Um, it's also like this Bowden who's going to be doing
this the entire time, like wearing a bra and underwear. You're in a scene with a woman with her
vagina out. Did anyone like say to her like, also, why do they keep showing? Here's the thing,
I respect if Bowden doesn't get naked in a movie. Why do they keep showing her in her bra? Stop showing
I don't need to see your putting your shirt. They're trying to wind you up a little bit
I guess they just showed this girl's clam
The hell am I gonna get out of her victory a secret or shit? I
Did enjoy it. Maybe they're they're going for the guy who likes something a little more classy like myself that guy would walk
Out of this movie by now that would have been offended
So I mean daddy's home the premise everything about it's like you're like, okay, this is a
No -brainer this is gonna be a pretty solid comedy and they just miss a
again, and again, and again. And none of the jokes hit. Nothing
about it is funny. They do this bit where Will Ferrell talks
about how the Ford Fiesta or something is like a great car.
It's got some fun bells and whistles for him, but also it's
safe for the kids. And you're like, okay, I get that this is a
joke, but you know, they got a lot of money from the Ford
people, right? Then they do it again at the end for longer. So
the legitimate features of the Ford whatever car it is and it's a new Ford model and it's the
first and last scene of the film essentially talk at length about how great this actual car is.
You're kidding me. And Nate give its full name. I was kind of appalled by the whole thing.
And it's not done satirically either. It's not like a Wayne's world where they're doing the
all about enough sponsor or whatever which is fucking genius still because that
was unless I'm wrong that was like the first time I had ever seen anyone call
that shut out. No it was I was blown away by that when I was a kid. Yeah that
killed me the new print part where it goes black and white. Yeah little yellow and
it's the choice of the new generation. Yeah that killed me. My favorite sequence in
The whole thing though is when, when Garth is sitting back with his feet up in his hands,
when I said, in full, Nike air, gear, gear, and he's like, it just makes me sick, man,
you know, these people, it's like they're corporate slaves.
Yeah.
Yeah, like real like above it.
Um, and this daddy's home, it did everything that just bothers me about a movie where there's
like scenes where like, it's Thomas Hayden Church playing a scumbag, which should be
funny. He did it great inside with and it's him and Farrell and they're sitting in this office
and for like a six minute scene neither of them says anything funny and I'm like why not just
show me a recording of Will Farrell talking to Thomas Hayden Church for six minutes because it'll
be funnier than this. Where the hell was Thomas Hayden Church been? You know what I bet happened is
he got nominated for an Oscar for sideways and he got all that acclaim and then everybody was
didn't really know what to do with him, but he also wasn't going to take some shitty project.
I actually also heard that he's like not like he's just kind of like, I'll work if I feel like
working like he's not like, he's got wings money. They kind of had to talk him into sideways.
Well, that role was written for Clooney who I've not been able to do it.
Yeah, and Alexander Payne apparently called him and said, I want you to be in my movie and he was
like, nah, I did not know that. He said, you get to have sex with my wife in it because he was
married to that girl. Sandra, yeah. Yeah. He is great in that movie. I would have loved to see
what Clooney do with it as well, but it wouldn't have been the same. No. Clooney, Clooney,
Clooney's too likable. I don't know if I've ever seen him play like a dark, not that dark, not.
It's really, it's just like such a small kind of special movie and Clooney would have upset that balance,
I think. Yeah. And it also would have taken away from GMATI and that was kind of his breakout.
Yeah, right. I felt like, you know, yeah, this daddy's home. Now they have Paul Sheer come out as this announcer at a big basketball game. Paul Sheer is on screen for five minutes. And I'm not saying that nothing he said was funny. I'm saying they didn't write him even anything in the proximity of a joke.
They just didn't like you you couldn't I'm sure Paul she was on set and it's like guys you don't want to give me one joke
I'm funny. I'm a funny actor. You don't want to give me something funny to say it's an infuriating movie
I find it's always a bit problematic when Pharaoh were is without Adam. What's his face? Yeah, okay
And then I saw McCabe produced it and I was like well, that's kind of a shock or two you know like I liked I like the basketball one
semi pro, but it would have been 20 times better if McCay did it. I agree. I'll take blades of
glory over semi pro even. I like blades of glory. But like Andy Daly and semi pro is a great example
of like a bit part where they gave him some funny shit to do. Like Andy Daly is really funny in that
movie. And it is very funny. But by the way, how happy are you that that trope has finally ended?
The zany announcers? Oh yeah. That are saying like well, you're never going to do it better than
Yooker in Major League. I would say the crown Yooker and Major League is really great, but
just a bit outside. I would give the crown to Fred Willard in Best and Show.
Okay. Well, sure. Can you really call that a sports movie? I don't know.
But it's the character. It's the announcer saying like inappropriate stuff though.
Yeah. Now on our last podcast, we talked about John Michael Higgins and how he steals Best
and show, give me a pepperoni, I'll hold it, I'll hold it, I'll hold it, I'll hold it, I'll hold it, I'll hold it, I'll hold it, I'll hold it, I'll hold it, I'll hold it, I'll hold it, I'll hold it, I'll hold it, I'll hold it, I'll hold it, I'll hold it, I'll hold it, I'll hold it, I'll hold it, I'll hold it, I'll hold it, I'll hold it, I'll hold it, I'll hold it, I'll hold it, I'll hold it, I'll hold it, I'll hold it, I'll hold it, I'll hold it, I'll hold it, I'll hold it, I'll hold it, I'll hold it, I'll hold it, I'll hold it, I'll hold it, I'll hold it, I'll hold it, I'll hold it, I'll hold it, I'll hold it, I'll hold it
like 20 jokes for this guy and then you see him in the thing and it's like yeah we're
going to need to bring him back at the end of the episode like he just elevates everything.
It was him and Coolidge and then we also had the woman who played the descendent of
Blaine Fabin and waiting for government. The really intense, weird black hair woman.
Yes, yes, yes, yes. These three like I'm hoping they do some improv even though our show doesn't
really allow it but just reading what we wrote they were fucking incredible.
like they're just fucking pros like they make everything funny he worked with
Coolidge on the guest movie so it was it was like a little reunion thing for
them it was a reunion and you know you didn't get the feeling they didn't like
each other but like they came in and didn't seem to know each other and then you
remember that those casts are so huge Coolidge and him probably never met that's
weird like they're in no scenes together in those movies he hits on her in oh yeah
consideration. That is true. I've got about that. Which is the only character I've ever seen him do
that that could conceivably take the trophy from the best -in -show character. Yeah yeah. It's it's
tremendous. All right. So here she is in a bra and panties again. Why? I don't know. I mean she's
she's not a name so you can get anybody in there. I never understand in a hard art movie like this
Where the nudity is a lot of the appeal while you're casting somebody with a known nudity clause. It makes no sense I
And again, I know I sound like a scumbag. I don't really care folks. I've paid
Zero attention to the story
There's not much story. I mean she's she's kind of a it's a single -white female type deal with her and Bowden and then on the side she
You know just a bunch of dudes and kill some she's obsessed with Bowden and she wants to be with Bowden
Yeah, and she also, you know, she tries to kind of blackmail her by saying that, you know, she got her on ecstasy and got pictures of her with dudes out at a bar.
She just likes to fuck with people's lives. She's a villain. It's all there is to.
What does she try to blackmail her for sex?
I don't even remember. I don't even remember.
Okay. Now, now, if you had to marry one of these two characters, which one would you marry?
It's a fascinating question, it's like that same question works from Mahal and Draught, you know, but you didn't know that the dark -haired one was crazy.
You can't, that can't come into account.
I think I could sense that she was crazy.
That's what I feel like too.
It took me 10 years, but my crazy radar is so strong right now because I've dated a lot of really nuts, girls. Actually, that's not true.
I've dated a couple.
I always say if a guy says every girl he's ever dated is crazy, the guy is crazy, but
if a guy says one girl he dated is really crazy, that girl's crazy.
Well, give him a few.
I mean, you should get more than one.
I've had a couple.
You know, I'm sure girls have thousands of guys that they think are crazy and I'm sure
they are as well.
Now, how many times did you, I'm not done with daddy's home yet.
How many times did you laugh out loud in the theater?
I usually a movie like that at the beginning you'll laugh because you're still kind of like this could maybe get funny or whatever. I didn't even have that. I didn't laugh out loud one time. Nothing.
At the end of the movie I liked the ending of the movie and it's a dance scene and they go up against your dear friend Bill Burr.
Bill, Bill's in that movie.
He's randomly in the final scene of this movie,
and he has a dance -off with Mark Wahlberg and Wolf Feral.
That's kind of funny.
Bill dances in the movie.
He dances.
He's like an asshole who wants to fight the dads.
Really?
Yeah.
All right.
It's a nice little part.
In fact, I think he told me when he was doing it.
I don't remember.
It's the kind of movie where you just feel like I bet everyone
had a way better time on set than I did watching this movie.
OK.
And they didn't show any outtakes, so maybe they didn't have fun because these are the movies that always have outtakes.
The outtakes from, there's a clip online, a YouTube clip of Will Farrell, the best of Will Farrell like bloopers.
Yeah.
And it's just one after the other from all these different things.
And as an acting exercise, I've watched it and tried not to laugh.
Yeah, cuz I was like, what if you're in this situation you'd have to get through it and it is impossible the funniest outtakes in the history of
Film and television are will Farrell on Eastbound and down. That's still that's it starts with that
That is the funniest thing I've ever seen and he has dynamic bride like
It's in the scene as air dynamic brides head is violently trembling. It's brutal. It's so funny the thing when he somehow is
Get down to my plumb let the kid walks in and he says let the boy watch when I was having sex this wife
I said let the boy watch
They are
Those outtakes are the funniest things ever
If you get a chance will Ferrell he's bounding down bloopers outtakes let the boy watch let the boy
Yeah, he talks about I was ball he keeps doing the thing about his nuts and he goes take him to Thomas mock
Yeah, or get ready for the market put one in my sack lunch
For my for my dessert. I feel the juice dripping down my chain. Yeah, it's it's it's it's it's funnier than anything he did on
He's bounded down like the outtakes are incredible. I had one I had two moments like that on this shooting things
And I'll tell you the stories Pat first was the first was on when I did Louie
It this line didn't make the episode, but he said Joe
I want to end the scene with you holding up a parking ticket and
saying
Do you guys pay for parking because the fat content the front desk says you don't validate?
I couldn't get through the fucking line. I was laughing so hard.
I got through it once by like the skin of my fucking teeth.
And he had the camera right on me. It was so low close up like it was brutal.
And the second one was one of the times I was doing Amy Schumer.
I was in a sketch with Kurt Metzger and Zach Braff.
Uh -huh I remember that sketch. Yeah, and the end of the sketch is Amy saying like
She wants his act her husband in the sketch is played by Zach
She wants him to come upstairs and shit on her. Uh -huh, and he
He would end the sketch. She would grab this chicken wing and you go I better eat up
I got shit to do and he would start chopping the chicken wing and
Dude, I was fucking we were we couldn't fucking it was so fucking funny
It was so funny like there's something about
When a guy does something that's so real, right, he was doing it exactly the way like an excited 15 -year -old kid would do it
Yeah, yeah, it was so real. I couldn't stop laughing. It was one of the great moments of my life
You said I can't even I can't look at you and I was like, oh, that's pretty cool the guy from scrubs
Yeah, I can't get through it. I can pretty much always stop laughing
Oh, it's a rare gift
Yeah, I got it all I used to laugh at church with my sister all the time really pissed my dad off. So now I'm I'm really good at clipping it when I need to.
You what? Did you stop clipping my laughs when I need to. Oh, it's not like you're going to keep talking and you cut it off. That's all I had to say on that.
now she just killed this guy with a needle in his neck she said it made her come
yeah that that's fine but then she pushes the car down an alleyway with the
dead guy in it and it just so happens a truck t -bones it and then it makes it
look like it was a car accident right what how did she know that that was
gonna happen I don't know and what was she gonna do if the truck didn't hit it
She didn't know she couldn't see that there was a truck coming I
Can't believe this movie was in theaters
3D
Did you see my bloody valentine?
No, but it's the second time you brought it up
No, I might be I might be even getting the title wrong, but it was a 3D kind of low -budget thing like this
I remember I
Remember but did are you gonna tell a story about it or you just bring? No, I eventually saw it
I mean, I have a 3D TV and player and all that and I love like I got Mad Max and watched
on 3D and it was fucking incredible.
I love watching a 3D movie at home.
I love going to the theater and seeing them.
But these low rent ones just scream like like, that's like you're saying they'll show a shower
in 3D and then 10 minutes later, there's a pencil that gets thrown at the screen.
There hasn't been one 3D type shot since that shower.
No, it's just like a, they tried to jump on the bandwagon.
to be in 3d now they and they don't make the money that they'll make either they think that just
any idiot will go see a 3d movie but they won't now the second time I saw Star Wars the new one
it was in 3d how it now how is that difference it was an incredible experience okay better in 3d
I wouldn't say better necessarily it was just slightly different my favorite viewing I've
seen it three times now my favorite of the three was the 35 millimeter screening at the Vista
Okay vintage cinemas that was really cool because it was the grainiest of all of them. Yeah and it just I
felt like I was back like a kid again like watching Star Wars in the theater. Now we haven't
discussed the new and I know you loved it. I liked it very much. Are you gonna see this seven times
in the theater as well? I think I'm gonna see it one more time. I think four is gonna do it for me.
Okay and then and then I'll still be excited for it to come out on Blu -ray. Okay I can't
for the next one. They're John Boyega said that the next movie is very dark. And the next
one is like a clone side shot. What? It's like a side movie. No, no, no, no. He's saying episode
eight, the sequel, the four awakens. But aren't they making some sort of interim clone movies?
They're making one -offs. They're not clone movies. The first one off is Rogue One. And it's about
the the rebel assault to steal the plans of the death star okay so it's a
prequel to star wars the original with any of the same characters um they
there's rumors going around that young Han Solo might make an appearance in it
to kind of set up his solo movie okay but I'm gonna show how many of these things
are made or I think is in it until we have like 30 Star Wars movies coming they're
gonna do one a year they said it's gonna be like Marvel they're gonna do one a
Where do you slip in Force Awakens now to your ranking top three or two?
You're saying possibly Empire followed by Force Awakens. Empire's number one. I'd go Empire Force Awakens Wow Star Wars
Revenge of the Sith
Return of the Jedi. Okay, Attack of the Clones Phantom Menace
That's my order. All right. What's your order?
Well, I've rewatched all of them now except I need to rewatch Sith, but I'm going to go, I think I'm going to go empire, yet I starwarked your mind.
Force Awakens, you know, I got to see these all again. It's hard to compare something you saw once on a Saturday afternoon to something you've seen 18 times since you were a little kid.
I mean Jedi, I think it's unreasonable to compare those two. It's Jedi is just it's the it's too
I love the opening the whole opening and I love all the stuff with Luke versus Vader, but I mean just the Ewoks
I love the Ewoks the Ewoks like like making keystone cops out of the Empire. Yeah, and and also too. It's like
Guys in the last movie you kick the shit out of the Rebels when you need it to
Mm -hmm. Why don't you have the walkers down on indoor taking care of business you got one thing down
You know what I mean like where where's your back? Where's your artillery here? Sure doesn't make any sense to me
I wasn't
Completely enamored with the two new heroes and force away. I thought the
I mean forgive me here the the black guy. I don't remember his fin fin was just
needlessly screaming the entire movie like scared of everything to a point where
I was like shut up man and I thought that the girl I loved her was yeah very
likable but also I don't know they didn't have the same thing where I was like
I'm excited these are my guys here like I did with the other ones I felt like
that I'm excited to see her like and Chewbacca kicks a mass in the next one I'm
excited to see her become more powerful. Yeah. I did love Kylo Ren and I
love that he was like weird and like potentially homosexual and everything
that he was bringing to the table. I was like, I like this. This is different
and weird. I like Podamro too. Yeah. Everything felt a little too familiar to me
except Kylo Ren. That was, I was like, this is a weird like psychosexual kind of vibe
that I'm into. And I like that he had like a woman's hair cut. And I like the, I like
his voice. I was into it. Now, did you only see it once? I only saw it once. I think on second
and third views you would appreciate the new characters a lot more. I think so too. I definitely
think so too. You know, it's a lot to take in on that first screening. Sure. I liked it a lot.
I had a great time. Yeah, it was quite fun. What was your favorite part?
You know what? If I could, if I may be so bold, if I had to pick a reason why I wouldn't say
it was like one of my favorites of the series is because I didn't have a scene where I was like
fuck yes, I didn't. I don't even understand. I thought it all kind of was like kept it at an even B -plus
Kiel and it never really it never went anywhere near like the fucking Phantom Menace where you're like what what am I watching?
What is this trash I'm watching but it also never went into the like a zone where I'm like holy shit
This is amazing to me. I never had a scene where I was like this is new and exciting and crazy. I think you're nuts
I did like when she was able to use the powers of the force. That was very cool
You didn't light up when she goes garb the garbage will do and they run towards the ship and it's the Millennium Falcon
And that whole sequence of her like learning how to fly it and I think people clapping is what made me realize it was the Millennium Falcon
Yeah, that that scene brought tears to literally tears to my eyes. Yeah, it got me so excited
Han and Chewy with when the when the
Rhyl arcs, whatever the fuck they were called get loose. Yeah, I'm not I'm not the the diehard store where I was guy
Evidently so you said you didn't know it was the Millennium Falcon when everybody clapped
I was like, okay, this must be the Millennium phone. This must be the
All right, let's sir. We don't need to talk about this anymore. It is what it is to a child evidently
DC Nash I'm just picking up now is the comic relief in this film yeah we've been
talking through all of we've been talking through the whole film but through
all of her scenes as well right and I just realized she's this is supposed to be
some comedic thing they've got a character running around the hospital putting
smiley face stickers on everybody yep not quite sure why it's ironic you know I'm
sure there's a reason, but who is this girl playing the smiley face girl? I don't know,
she is. We're having a Judd Nelson. Is he dead? No, he's around. He does die. Spoiler alert.
I watched the Danish girl. Eddie Redman dressing up like a woman. Yeah, how was it? Didn't care for it.
It's not getting great reviews. I'm surprised. I thought that guy was going to grab a
and ask her two years in a row,
but the reviews have been kind of mild about it.
I mean, he even shows his dick.
He tucks it back, Buffalo Bill style.
Does he dance in the mirror like Buffalo Bill?
No, he makes, straight up, he makes way too many faces.
Like he's already like in a full dress
and like Sunday ladies hat,
but then he's like really overdoing the faces
and acting.
And I thought at times, and I could not be more accepting and tolerant of the whole movement.
Well, here comes a statement. That was a hell of a disclaimer you're putting.
I really could, but I was just like this guy is he's not trying to treat this with any kind of respect.
He's desperately begging to get an Oscar because he got a taste of it right out of the gate.
And now he's like he's just you're already playing a woman. You're already dressed as a woman. You don't need to
Insanely gesture and move your face around
All right, well, I don't think you needed that disclaimer. That's not intolerable
Joe you know the times in which we live I do I do I just didn't care for it
And I'm sitting you know, I turn to my girlfriend to be like this is ridiculous and she's got tears streaming down her face
So it works on some obviously the
I went to see Creed with my dad love cream. It was sold out. You didn't see it yet. I haven't seen it.
Joe, that's fucking nuts. It was sold out because that's fucking nuts, Joe.
The Philadelphia area that movie is even more popular than everywhere else.
Creed is really great. Well, it was sold out. So my dad and I ended up seeing hateful
eight instead, which I couldn't believe wasn't sold out. Right. And we loved every minute of it.
It was a little awkward sitting next to my dad during the scene where there's a forced
male on male blowjob.
But now let me ask you this and I think it's fair now it's been out a while and that
is only the act one break.
Do you think that actually happened or that he was trying to force Brewster in his hand?
I think that's one of the, all right, we're going to go real heavy spoiler right now because
I've been waiting to talk to you about why.
But now wait, are we only spoiling up to that hour and a half mark?
I'm gonna hear him speak freely about this movie all right, well folks. I
Don't know what you want to do here. It's it's movies and theaters
I don't necessarily love that we're about to spoil the movie. We're not spoiling because we're giving the warning
So you can tune out if you don't want to hear it anymore. Okay, so my I then they don't know when to come back
You want to talk about this any longer
All right, well when you click back in this when you click back into the show
Well, just make sure we're not still talking about it.
I'm trying to get to this goddamn nurse movie.
If you're a film fan, you should have seen the new content to the movie by now, frankly.
One of the things I loved so much about the movie was the brilliant setup of Samuel Jackson's
character with that letter from Lincoln, yeah, where you didn't know if what he was saying
was true or not.
I thought that was brilliant.
Another place where they exploited that was he talks about how the lady that owned the
Habadashary hated Mexicans.
Yes.
And when you see the scene in the flashback
where she meets the Mexican guy, she's,
she's a joy to him.
Yeah.
So they just, they were little nuances in his stories
and whatever like that, where you were like,
is he lying, is he telling the truth?
Is he not?
I love that.
I thought it was awesome.
Another Easter egg thing that I thought was so cool
was when Tim Roth, when they showed the flashback
And you see that he is speaking with a put on accent through the first act of the movie right the accent
He goes into in the second act that which is his real accent. Yeah is the same accent. He uses in reservoir dogs. Yeah
That's true as the undercover cop that's true. Like that's so fucking cool, man
I really I there were little moments like that that I really really liked
hate the late there are multiple little moments that I was like that was great
and yet on the whole it's my least favorite Tarantino movie although I
give it a B -plus gladly I had a good time I just thought you know I would
love to see any of his other movies extended to a three -hour length and
shot in 70 millimeter and this seemed to not be the one to do either of those
things in to me. I loved it. It was one of his most impressive movies to me as far as the shots
they were pulling off. Yeah. I mean, the outdoor stuff was fucking incredible. I was like, this is
one of some of those beautiful things I've ever seen. Well, there's a scene where there's a naked man
going through three feet of snow and it's really happening. Yeah. You know, like, how are they doing
this right now? So there were there were if I'm if I want to be in a Tarantino movie, I'll walk naked
through the snow. So there was it was an amazing. I got nothing to hide. It was an amazing feat
that they shot in that kind of weather and whatever. It was to me. I liked it better than his last
three movies. Oh, okay. Here's why we're talking Django and Glorious Bastards. I liked it better
than Django and Glorious Bastards. Kill Bill or death proofs. So it was last four. Wow. The only
The only one I could understand would be death proof.
Here's why I'll tell you why.
It's the, those are all great movies.
Yeah, not knocking those movies.
This movie to me was the most Tarantino thing
he had done since Jackie Brown.
It was pride and true Tarantino.
Would you know Marlonne or the?
It was dialogue driven.
It was, these are your characters.
It wasn't jumping like into all these different storylines
and sequences that were happening
in all these different places. I know Pulp Fiction kind of does that. Yeah. But I just mean like,
you know, Django Unchained, Ingolier's Bastards, Kill Bill, these are like epic movies. Right.
Epic sprawling movies that tackle very specific genre of pieces and cinema. You know,
Kill Bill is the samurai movie. Right. You got the World War Two movie. You've got the Western.
And this of course was a western too, but it was reservoir dogs to me
It was like it was like here eight guys. They're strapped in this room and we're gonna figure out who we can trust and who we can't and I was it just I loved it
Man, I fucking loved it. I again, that's one I would very I will definitely see again before it leaves theaters, but
To me, I couldn't help but feel a little let down by the whole thing and I hated everyone in it
I know. I know. I thought Samuel Jackson was awesome. But at the end of the day, I was like, I liked the reservoir dogs. I don't like these people.
Oh, I know. See, I felt very similar about the reservoir dogs to these guys. I felt like they were, there were guys you kind of started to like and then they would say something horrific or do something horrific. Yeah. And you'd be like, I don't like this guy anymore. Yeah.
And by the end of it, there was kind of like one or two guys that you liked and it was it was Roth and
Kitell and that and then this one it was the sheriff that redeems himself. Sure and Sam Jackson
Sure, and and the whole the whole revelation at the end of it like it's kind of becomes this movie about racial progress
And I don't know. I just thought it was great
We should go see it at the arc light because the arc light is showing the two -hour and change cut
I'd be curious to see what the tighter version is like
Yeah, I only saw that road show version as well. That's all I saw. Yeah, I did dig it
Very much at Tarantino has has done so much greatness that it's really not fair to compare a
Movie of his to his other movies because there's some of my favorite movies
but
To me, it's his least successful movie. Maybe repeat viewing. We'll change that
Well, here's the thing too that I also appreciated because there were certain people were complaining
about the road show aspect of it and the length and all this stuff.
Oh, I love to have an intermission.
I like that he tried to create an experience for my dad.
My dad was like blown back by that too because it took him back to be in a kid again.
He was like, yeah, we got home.
He said to my mom, he's like, when's the last time you saw a movie with an intermission?
Yeah, like my dad was was tied into that movie man
I haven't my dad really falls asleep a lot during movie. Yeah, so the fact that he was in there and stuck with it
I probably helped me yeah
The my enjoyment my own enjoyment of it. Well, I think I said the last time on this podcast the last the only movie I ever saw the intermission was dance of the wolves
Which was 1990 I don't think they've done it since I've never seen dances. I thought that was pretty cool dance wolves
at least when I was a kid, I loved, I'm sure it still holds on.
Shocked that as a kid you'd have an interest in that movie.
My dad brought me, I don't know.
Yeah, it was ten, it's a western, it's fun.
But you didn't answer my question,
we talked for ten minutes and still didn't answer my question.
Do you think Samuel Jackson forced that guy to suck his dick or not?
No, I thought I did.
What I was saying was the beauty of it was you don't know.
Right.
That was but what a youth I think probably not I think not. Yeah, I think he probably just killed the guy's son
I did laugh really hard at them because it was just so shocking. It was intense
It was up there with well again classic Tarantino was like the gim scene in Pulp fiction. Yeah, whoa
He totally just showed it the music is exceptional the any Omar cones the any Omar Coney scores Grant is exceptional
it just won he just won the Golden Globe and then Tarantino got in trouble for
saying ghetto. What did he say? He said any more cone is my favorite composer of
all time. He's like I'm not just limiting it to film composers that ghetto. I'm
talking about Beethoven and then Jimmy Foxx gets up after it. Jimmy Foxx who did
Django One Change arguably Jimmy Foxx's best movie with Tarantino. He gets up to the
Mike after him and he goes ghetto like disgusted with him that's a term that
means that means neighborhood and now no I'm I'm well aware I just thought
like that people really want to mark Tarantino as a racist and I just do not
buy it because he's given some of the most interesting parts for African
Americans of the past 20 years for sure you look at Jackie Brown somebody who
creates that movie around that character. Simply cannot be a racist. And granted his usage of the
end word is a little insane at times. There was until the end until where I realized where
hateful it was going, I was like, okay, this seems excessive and and and weird. Yeah. Yeah.
And then at the end, the way it all came together, I was like, okay, I get it. I see what he was doing.
He was, to me, what he was trying to do, at least, was he was showing how much of a jump
it was for that sheriff to side with Samuel Jackson.
Yeah.
For sure.
He was also showing how awesome Samuel Jackson's character was and how mistreated he was.
Yeah.
And the justice being finally served in the end.
Yeah, yeah.
You know, Bruce Dern was, that was another thing I loved in the setup was when they showed
the flashback Channing Tatum says to Bruce Dern, you say hello, you tell him your name
And you don't say shit else right and Brewster and can't fucking help it. Yeah, so racist. Yeah, you can't fucking help it
And he he sets off the chain of dominoes that gets everybody killed
Yeah, I will I even just this conversation. I want to see it again
So that part was great. Clearly. It was not a failure. No, it was great. I also love to the
The what's it called? What's it gonna say? I can't remember. It's funny my dad had no my dad
Like I knew Tarantino's name, but doesn't know who he is right and he called me and he's like and he was like
Hey, I just want to let you know that any Omar Akone guy won the Golden Globe for best soundtrack to a movie
I was like oh, that's cool. Yeah, I go. I didn't see the show and he goes well that Tarantino fella accepted for him. He's
He's a strange guy. I was like, yeah, he's got a weird, right? He looks like Frankenstein at this point
what he got like weird fake hair and everything looks like he has bolts coming
out of his neck his far head seems to be growing yeah exactly it's very
odd but I love I'm glad he's making movies I'll tell you that much yeah I there
was one other thing I was gonna mention I can't remember oh what did you think of
the that's what it was about the Golden Globes what did you think of the
Jervice, uh, Mel Gibson XD.
It actually made me feel bad for Mel Gibson.
I was like, you know what, man?
Like the guy is going to show his face now after like 10 years.
And you're just going to bring up the same fucking thing.
Yeah, I agree.
And here's the thing.
What it what it reminds me of and so my favorite songwriter of all time is Elvis
Costello. I love Elvis Costello and I understand he's a divisive person. I don't really care. But
well -documented is in a bar with like Crosby Stills and Nash who he despised in the 70s.
Right. Costello used to be like a two -bottle of vodka day alcohol. And he's so drunk he can't stand
in this bar and he's trying to get a rise out of Stephen Stills across just
doesn't match we considers like a hippie loser and they start screaming at
each other and he's like tell me somebody you like or whatever and he tells
him that he he likes Ray Charles and Elvis Costello refers to Ray Charles as an
end work right to get a rise out of Stephen Stills and try to give him to punch him
in the face right now it's got still his base pretty much his entire life on a
celebration of African -American music and working with African -American artists and
but this is out there and it's been out there and he addresses it in both of his
biographies and discusses it like gives an entire chapter to it when you know
he'd rather let it go right but he feels clearly a lot of guilt and bad about it
and someone asked Ray Charles about it because they shared a bill together
I was gonna tell on Ray Charles and Ray Charles they said now you know I was
gonna tell us about you in 1979 or whatever and Ray Charles goes oh drunk talk
is drunk talking it should be left at that all right now look there's a lot to
say about this kind of insane but like I I at my absolute drunkest have not said
the end word I don't get that I don't understand right but like when I look at
Mel Gibson, I'm like, look, I heard those tapes, him screaming at that woman.
You got to blow me in the jacuzzi, me and Pete Holmes used to work at outsource.
And all day we would listen to these smellgibs and tapes and how hilariously insane they
were.
Like, I'm proud to say at my darkest, drunkest moment, you're not going to find me saying
anything that would get me ex exiled from the entertainment industry, right?
Which happened with that, but like, I mean, God damn it.
Like we're just never going to let this guy back in well, no, we're going to keep bringing up this the most painful
And then this is why I brought it up. Yeah
Well, number one, I've always been in the belief obviously I don't agree with anything the guy said
Of course always I've always been of the belief like when I've heard
Those tapes of him. I was like this sounds beyond drunk to me
This sounds like a guy that's off his medication and is having some sort of a breakdown thousand percent
Yeah. So obviously you try to give a guy a little more leeway because there are things
interfering. I don't think Mel Gibson is a racist. Having seen him be like best pals
with Danny Glover all those years. You know, right. And I guess his remarks were focused
on the Jews. Correct. Well, that's the that's the second incident. I'm referring to his
And bomb in the original voicemails or whatever. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Oh, yeah. My point is is like I think the guy had a problem
Now wait, did he say I hope you get raped by a pack of was that him? Yes. Oh boy
So and then we're focused on sugar tits. That's weird too. Well, I mean, I think there's even some things that
People don't feel comfortable joking about sure, but here's my point. Here's my point
I think the guy was in a bad fucking place clearly and fucked up and I think he's sorry for it
And I think that he's trying to redeem himself and he's apologized and I think that that
appearance was a huge step in the right direction for him
Because two things the first thing is he got that colonoscopy line in on your face. It got a huge fucking laugh
Yeah, it got a huge laugh
Regi race comes back out which was kind of a baby move. I agree. He got you needed the last word. Yeah
usually gets the last word walks off and then Mel Gibson says in response to the
sugar tits question you'll have to ask the guy that said it because it wasn't
me hmm so he's just like dude he said that on stage yeah he goes you have to ask
the guy that said it wasn't me and it's he's like dude I was I was fucked up man I'm
sorry yeah I think I think he I think he got a lot of ground for himself and
that appearance I really do and look he he agreed to do it he clearly knew like
I'm gonna be brought out by this guy. He's gonna make jokes yeah, and he was like ready to handle himself and he did
I just think like Jody Foster who was like an out -and -proud lesbian and all these people coming forward and being like
Guys, this isn't Mel Gibson or whatever else
You know, it's enough for me to like at least be like all right
I don't need to throw a tin can at this guy when he walks on stage. No, it's not ideal
But like you know the shittiest things people have said and done
he's one of the few people that has had his publicly dissected now for a fucking decade.
Yeah, I think he had a bad run and he was in a bad place and some unfortunate things were said
and hopefully horrific things. He comes back, you know. But that appearance I was rooting for him,
I was like I want to see the guy but you know what else I think helped seeing an awesome Mad Max
movie and everybody kind of being like oh yeah remember we love Mel Gibson yeah like it you know
I think you know my mother the only and looking back on it now it's a little strange the only time
I ever knew my mom to be like to watch a movie more than once even was lethal weapon and she would
watch it like 20 times all those lethal weapon movies and she loved them and later on it occurred
to me. She had the hots for Mel Gibson. Yeah. He had a lot of butt scenes in the 80s and she'd watch
all his movies again and again and no one else's. I remember my mom and her friend talking about
how much they love the bear -ass scene that Mel Gibson did in Leifah Weapon. He was kind of a huge
deal in his day and I think Braveheart and Apocalypse are fantastically directed movies as well.
So like I should the crisis of fantastically directed film. Yeah, I thought his smart move would be to step be to stay behind the camera and direct. But then again, anyone who wants to act with him now has to
Fess up to like people saying, well now you're aligning yourself with an anti -Semite.
I think and I've always been of the belief too that this is always my this is my Woody Allen defense. I think when somebody has these types of
When somebody is this person truly in their heart, yeah, or at their core, I think they're, it's never one or two weird slip up things.
It's like there are several incidences or incidents usually.
That's my, that's my opinion.
I don't know if I'm right or not, but and I think if he, if I think if Mel Gibson wasn't a guy that had a bad run in with drugs or alcohol, whatever, and made some mistakes.
And truly was that guy there would have been a hell of a lot more accounts of it
Yeah, I mean I think there is also as much as I
Hear that and respect that opinion is also a part of me that thinks that might be what we want to believe
Because we like these people
Whereas if Jamie Kennedy was caught doing it, you'd be like fuck that guy
We don't know no one knows all I can do is say I like muggips as movies. I like him as an actor and director
I like Woody Allen's movies, obviously
And just hope that they're not the monsters that we've come to believe they might be it's a scary thought
But I think there's a lot of people who are way worse who are never exposed. I guess my point. That's unfortunate
I guess my point is is you know you look at the Cosby situation. Oh Jesus Christ. It's it's it's it's an endless stream of people saying yeah
No, that he does do that. Yeah, I mean when when Travolta got accused of grabbing that masseuse's dick or whatever
a lot of the juices came from it was a shitloads. Yeah, you know, I mean it was like it's so I don't know we'll see how much longer
does this goddamn movie have by the way? It's about over. I mean, I thought it was about over about four times now.
We're way off. I don't even remember. Well, it's not even midnight and we started at about 10 .30.
We only started at 10 .30. Maybe a little prior. I'm gonna do a little.
I think it's a fascinating topic and it's a topic that in a bar with a big group of
people I wouldn't necessarily discuss.
That's what I wouldn't.
You know, that's why it's kind of fascinating that we're talking about it now, but like
I feel comfortable talking to you about this.
I wouldn't talk about this.
Yeah, except we're talking to a lot of people about it.
Yeah, but I mean, we're all so safely just having this conversation.
You know the two of us there can be no confrontation right now sure we're just talking sure
But yeah in a bar. I mean look, but here's the thing. I wouldn't have the conversation to bar not cuz I'm afraid to voice my opinion
It's because it's not worth
The person that's gonna start yelling at you sure where I hear to have fun
I don't feel like hearing this right now. Yeah
Here's what I will say in the defense like Justin Bieber
you know by all accounts it's kind of a scumbag. If I heard Justin Bieber raped a woman I would be like
oh god fuck him like immediately. If I heard that John Candy raped a woman I would want to do
anything in my power to not believe that. Sure and I think that's wrong and yet it's also just kind
of a true thing. Like, I look at Mel Gibson and I'm like, he can't be this. I look at Woody Allen,
I'm like, I hope he's not this because I like their work. But ultimately, that's not fair
to potential victims of crimes, you know. Of course not. Yeah, you're, however, Mel Gibson
yelling some fucked up shit at somebody is a lot different than Bill Cosby raping everyone
who ever lived. And, you know, no matter what terrible things Muggibson said, you know, we're
not getting 800 women who come forward and say, yeah, you're right, me. Yeah, I would agree with
that. I would agree with that. Cosby facing jail time. Facing jail time, except he just got let off in
California, apparently. Yeah, but he's being tried that big trial that he's, what's happening in my
hometown. Oh, is that right? That is happening at the courthouse in my hometown. You see him with
that sweater hobbling up like he's all old and decrepit or whatever. That is a guy who like
you almost want to see people at the court steps like throwing rocks at him. It's just fucking
disgusting. It's devastating. When all the stuff came out about Led Zeppelin stealing their songs,
Yeah, it was heartbreaking and the example I would always use is I would say my god
I can't even wrap my head around it would be like if I heard like that Richard prior stole all his material
Right and this is essentially now the way way way worse version of that right like it's it's it's so devastating to me that a guy
I looked up to that much is this guy like I can't sure believe it and was just held as an example by my parents
I'm like we have to watch the show every week and like brutal and the fact that he's devoted so much of his life
telling black men
To get their shit together and pull their pants up and stop listening to hip hop. Yeah, it's you just it makes it
It makes you just want to
Just beat the shit out of this guy. Yeah, I know because frankly
If a hundred people say something
It is it is truth and you see this shit like I really respect
Obviously outcast one of my favorite musical acts of all time and big boy
I follow him on the all the social media. I love what he says all the time and then he randomly posted something like
Hey, let's not jump to conclusions on Bill Cosby and it posted some crack pot websites
You know disproving some woman's
Testimony or whatever and I was like fuck you big boy
a hundred women aren't lying and it it shouldn't need a hundred women to make
something true and it doesn't. I believe the recent
K .O. Hartman shit a thousand percent and that's now only two women. I would
believe one woman if they told me I'm just saying a hundred there can't still be
people who say that's not true. That can't happen. Yeah, I agree. I agree but I I
Now, what you said earlier, how we want to believe certain people, it can't be true.
It speaks to how devastating it is.
Yeah.
And I'm not saying, so you should be defending him in any way.
No.
I know that Bill, in my heart, I know Bill Cosby is guilty.
Yeah.
I don't know for a fact, but I know in my heart, I believe in my heart, I should say.
But you know, I, it's devastating.
This is how devastating it is.
If you wrote a screenplay
About this not about Bill Cosby just a screenplay where this was the story. Yeah, and the big twist at the end was
He's been raping all these women. You'd be like this is poorly written. This isn't believable. Yeah, it's it's the most insane
reveal I've ever experienced
Ever in my life
Like I can't I there will never be I know I'll never see anything like this ever again. I would think I mean my god
You never you'd just never know if people the coolest thing to me is like thinking back on all those
Tina Fey on
SNL and on 30 rock multiple times called him out for being a rapist before anything came out never
He was like, I'll just pretend that didn't happen or like it wouldn't get a laugh
I guess I didn't hear that but it's been kind of legend for a while. I had heard rumblings about it for a while
Well, there was stuff on his you know, there was stuff on his I remember hearing stuff and there were stuff on the Wikipedia page
but then both things said like they were these accusations and they were
settled out of court and whatever so it was it was just enough that it made
you feel okay saying like okay maybe he didn't do it then yeah you know and
then some guy just got sped by the way just to stick with the movie and some
capacity scissors through the neck again needless 3d shot and it was CGI scissors
scissors I don't necessarily think could go through a neck I don't know that
sure that was absurd. And this woman would have to have the strength of bigfoot. Do you know
how hard it would be to shove scissors through the back of somebody's neck and make them pop out
the front? I don't but I could guess. It would take a lot. And then she just stabbed him to
know what guys are. This is one of those horror movies too because it's in 3D where they're doing like
like all the Gore effects or CGI and it's just terrible.
Yeah, you know, fucking daddy's home had a lot
of comedy terrible CGI effects,
which to me is more infuriating than horror.
Like Will Ferrell gets on Marky Mark's motorcycle
and then he winds up crashing into the,
it's in the trailer.
He crashes into the house and the motorcycle flies
out the window and it's the worst special effects I've seen maybe in my entire
life and in a comedy it's like what is CGI though to me special effects and
comedy do not mix unless you're doing like a ghost busters what is CGI like
Will Farrow himself or just the motorcycle like when it the motorcycle crashes he's
in a wall and you see the motorcycle come crashing back out the upper floor
window and it looks like basically like they had a sticker of a motorcycle that
they moved over the lens. It looks so fake. This movie's just really ripping stuff
off from a lot of different movies. They ripped off that that omen thing at the
beginning. They just did a Freddie versus Jason thing where she cut the nozzle off
one of those like oxygen tanks. Yeah. And it's shot. Yeah. This is a pretty shameless
Phil. It's a pretty shameless film. I'm sure there's also a bit of killer
nurse and something else too. Probably yes. She hasn't orgasm every time she
hurts somebody. Yeah it turns her on I believe. Because she saw her dad murdered in
front of her. Right. Which this also takes a great deal from Dexter. Because
she's punishing people Dexter also saw his dad murdered her mom murder whatever
the hell it was. It really is just a, all right, well, not a good film. Who directed
this thing? That I don't know. I'm going to look it up. What if that was the twist that
I directed it and I was waiting to hear you? Give me an honest critique. Did I ever tell
you about the time I was talking to a guy about cabin fever? No. I like cabin food.
I said we were talking about cabin, we were working on a acting gig together and we
And he brought up cabin fever and I said are you going to be out in LA and he said well probably come out
Because they're doing it like a cabin fever remake
And I said he said so I will come out for the premiere of that and I said oh, that's cool and I go
Yeah, I'm not a big cabin fever fan. I started going off. I'm riding like the movie and yeah, like about it
And I go you must really love it. I mean you're coming out to see this remake premiere and he goes yeah, well, I wrote it
Oh, do you lie we're off didn't write cabin fever this guy wrote it with Eli Roth
Okay
And then I went and bought cabin fever and said I'll give it a second chance. All right very funny though. I enjoy it Kim
I like when she shaves her skin off. Yeah, I like that part. Was it Shannon Elizabeth and that man? I don't remember. I really don't remember
All right, hold on here. I'm looking up nurse
The phone's at 20 percent. I hate when it gets down to 20 percent.
Is that the killer nurse? Oh, she's playing fake like she needs help.
I believe so. And now she's going to sucker these guys.
I believe so. Now does she make it through this? Hold on a second.
No, they definitely, from when I recall, leave it open for a sequel.
that they may be making for all in.
Any movie with violence and gratuitous, really good nudity,
is going to have a shelf life.
It's got a 4 .6 on I &DB.
It's got a 55 % of Rotten Tomatoes much higher than I would have given it.
Yeah.
And we're trying to figure out who directed this thing.
Oh wait, the nurse is a 1997 movie as well.
Traumatized nurse plots revenge against a catonic business man
Who she blames for the death of her family this movie is just lift and shit
Jesus God that's not that different nurse 3d. That's what this is yeah
Your pain is her pleasure, right? That's a line almost verbatim out of hell razor. Yeah
What is this part now? She's getting arrested now
She thought she made it out
Another cut Doug Aaron oskey that I said a Doug Aaron
Not related to Darren Aaron. I don't know. It's Doug
Arnie Ocaskey. That's how you say
He directed this criminal minds and sleepy hollow and arrow. He's done TV all TV
You a Tim Burton sleepy hollow fan. Yes, very much so I love fucking love that movie
Uh, he, uh, got to start on the horror feature, Dr. Mordred.
Okay.
First A .D. worked on from Dustle Dawn.
The faculty.
Spy kids.
That's first A .D.
First director, to our effort was Highlander Endgame,
which I believe is the fourth Highlander.
I own Highlander.
I've never seen any of the Highlanders.
never saw one of them. Never saw one of them. No. Never had much of an
interest in it for some reason. I don't know why it seems like something to be
right my alley. I mean Connery. I'm on board. Connery's in the first two, right?
Yeah. Oh yeah, because I remember the sequel, the the commercials for the sequel,
him going greetings Highlander. Hello Highlander. Who did Connery play like the
master or something? I assume he was the Highlander, I don't know. No, Lambert's the
Highlander. Isn't he like an older Highlander who trains him to be a highlander?
There can only be one. Okay. There can only be one Highlander. So she got the, she got the kid,
the nerdy neighbor kid to help her dispose of this body at the end and now it's going to be like,
he's her minion because he wants to bang her. I believe so.
Something along those lines. Getting back to your base.
guys. I saw the office very early. I had heard a recommended, I think Christopher
Guest talked about it and something I saw when I was like in high school. And I was like,
this man is a genius. This is the funniest thing I've ever seen in my life. I watched it
constantly. I showed it to everyone I knew. Right. And I was like, this, this guy is like
the coolest. Then at some point, I guess it's talking about the atheism and talking about
like, oh, I don't want to be the bad boy or whatever. He became someone that everyone
cool and comedy shits on and hates. Right. Which I get. I don't like somebody who,
like, like, like, Russell brand who's like, I'm a bad boy and has to say it a thousand times
because then you're not really a bad. However, when he's hosting the Golden Glove, which is for
a mass audience, who is that for at this point? Like, middle America. Middle America doesn't
No, or care about Ricky Gervais though. He's never been in anything they've seen except like night at the museum
He's apparently that famous. I guess that's why I don't get I don't really like the the self -aware
I'm a bad boy crap. I think that's stupid, but I don't either and I haven't seen Derek. I like Derek a lot
I'm a fan of his work, you know, uh
If you make the office you get a pass folks and extras is great, too. I prefer to the office
Um, but I see so much hate towards him and I'm like, well, who do you guys like them?
Yeah, I mean, I didn't love them at the Golden Globes either and I don't like his whole stick
But like holding gloves are not a show meant for entertainers and artists to watch
No, for middle America, and that's in middle America. We'll get a kick out of that stuff. And that's it, you know
No, my wrong thing. No, he just needs to make something else great again
I don't understand that everyone with their arms folded like oh this piece of shit again the guy was awesome
He was your hero not long ago right and then if he dies, you'll all suck his dick like you did with Robin Williams when you turned on him
Yeah, you know
I there's no dick. I'd rather suck less than record your best. I'm just saying the guy did the office in extras
Do y 'all have to spit so much bile at this man?
Who's I think all you're seeing is some Twitter bio. Yeah Twitter
But I don't know, Joe. I don't know anymore.
I mean, even when we're grown men for Christ's sakes, it says, you know, come on.
You ready to close the South Paddy?
Let's close it up. They're recommending that we watch Nymphomaniac.
That's, they say, hey, you guys are disgusting perverts.
I actually loved both Nymphomaniac.
I do not feel comfortable watching that with you.
No, we're not going to watch. You want to watch a three hour movie right now?
At midnight on a Wednesday.
You've been listening to We'll see you in Hello presentation of the Fangoria podcast
network produced by Thomas DeFail, an executive produced by Ken Hanley of Fangoria Entertainment
for press opportunities, advertising inquiries, and information about We'll see you in
how contact can you can email them can at Fangoria .com.
We are on Twitter at the Patrick Walsh and Joderos Accomedy.
We love hearing your guys feedback.
Tweet us.
There's been a lot of it over the holidays, which was much appreciated and very cool to
hear.
Yes.
We're still doing our best.
And should we announce what the next one will be?
Should we just do the shining?
That's a tall order, that shining man, that's two and a half hours, man.
We promised people we'd tell them what the next one would be all right and we have a month. We're going to give you guys a real
treat. No, we don't have a month. We got to do another one. We have two weeks folks. We don't have two weeks. Here's what our next one's going to be. And I guarantee you can watch this because you've
already seen it. Our next one will be the shining a two hour and 22 minute version of we'll see you in hell. Imagine the things that we'll say in regret on that one because I'm
already thinking what did I say about Bill Cosby that could be misconstrued but
please folks know that we are on the side of good.
That is a massive tall order.
We're gonna do it next up is the Shining.
If you've never seen it watch the Shining.
The Shining next on we'll see you in hell.
In the meantime follow us on Twitter and leave some good reviews on this.
Please do yes.
I tone tunes page to fucking combat the troll cunts that leave one star reviews.
that. Take care everybody. Good night folks.