I'll see you in hell.
We will see you in hell.
I'll see to it.
That will be my dying motive to see you all there, Bernie.
Oh, that's not the start we wanted.
It's hard to keep coming up with these starts.
Yeah, clearly.
I could do it.
I could do them for a while.
You could do them for a little while.
I got no ego with this.
You could take it over.
You took it over for a while.
Then you gave it back.
That's true.
And now we're back.
We're back and we're talking this week about the Nicholas Cage movie.
Everybody in America is talking about Arcadian, the shutter original.
Shutter very craftily realizes that everyone's into long legs right now and
chose this week to drop their Nicholas Cage horror picture.
We'll get to it.
My criticism of both movies is needs more cage.
Both movies really kind of sideline your boy Nick Cage.
I'm sitting there.
I actually just finished watching this movie and I realized Cage hadn't spoken in about a half an hour.
It's not a dialogue heavy movie, which is a plus films a visual medium.
And it doesn't take place in a video arcade, which I don't think.
What does Arcadian mean?
I know it.
I know Arcadian rhythm.
That's a line from an REM song.
So I guess it's, is that like our crickets involved?
No, Arcadian means one who lives a simple life.
There's an Arcadian.
Huh.
And the movie is.
Or a native of Arcadia.
And I don't know where Arcadia is.
That's like a fun place.
I think that's where the Mario Brothers hail from.
Well, that's what I was going to say was Arcadian is a great type.
Like if you did a Freddy got, sorry, five nights at Freddy's.
Yeah.
Style thing.
Like in a video horror and a video arcade.
And then it's about the guide, the caretaker, the overnight janitor of the arcade.
And he's a simple man that keeps himself.
So then it means Arcadian.
And then he got the word arcade in there.
And then it's an arcade horror survival.
Yeah.
That'd be good.
It makes no sense really for this movie, the title.
Well, it's a post -apocalyptic.
So I guess that's what they meant was like you live this.
You know, desolate life.
I guess.
All right.
I was thinking of circadian rhythms.
That's.
Locust.
That's like an adult's natural internal clock.
Boy, REM must be obsessed with rhythms of sleep.
I mean, that's the name of the band.
REM.
Never enjoyed them.
Never enjoyed one goddamn song by that band.
Well, it's not true.
There's a couple, but like it's absolutely loved them for my formative years.
I don't throw them on much anymore, but I absolutely love them.
And the name of my everyone in the entertainment business has a corporation
that you do most of your tax dealings from.
And mine is called Rockville in honor of the REM song Don't Go Back to Rockville,
which was a song I listened to when I wanted to quit and return home to Missouri
upon moving to New York.
Okay.
Love that song.
Love that band.
I was never a big REM fan because it was always the guy
in high school or college that wore the circular, like John Lennon style glasses.
Sure.
And more tweed jackets, a two young of an age.
Yeah.
You'd be like, I mean, the, you know, I wish track seven wasn't just power chords,
but it's a brilliance.
You're like, Oh, God.
Oh, God.
That was, that was maybe the class.
You're about four or five years ahead of me.
That was probably the class ahead of mine.
My class, there was a few different subsets, but the big one coming up was Britpop.
Yeah.
And that was a very small subset, but those guys were the most insufferable.
And I actually love Britpop.
Like I would have loved to talk with them about the music if they weren't so fucking obnoxious
and dressed so obnoxiously.
This one guy had been saving up to go to England because he loved Oasis.
He would call them Nolan Liam, first name basis.
And then he went to London, and then for the remainder of high school several years,
all he did was talk about how he had been to London.
Oh, that reminds me of when I went to London.
Yeah.
Okay.
I'm just taking a piss, man.
Yeah.
I know you're at a McDonald's of the flail fish.
You know, when I was in London, they ate a lot of, all right.
I was in a record store recently with my buddy Steve burn, my national in the last episode.
And Steve is, he's not like super into vinyl, but he's, he's into it.
He likes buying records and stuff.
And his favorite band of all time is Oasis, which is fine.
Fine.
But we went into a record store in the town I live in that I wanted to show him.
And he went up to the guy.
Now, it might have been a gift for me.
Maybe that's why he was asking because he did buy a record and then he gave it to me.
And he said, I got this for you, actually, did the old switcher room.
It was very sweet.
Yeah.
But he said, you got any Oasis.
And the guy was like, oh, you know what?
Actually, we're, we're out of it.
It sells kind of quick or whatever.
And I just remember thinking, Steve, you don't have all the Oasis, your favorite band.
You don't have all the vinyls by now.
There's no deep cut unreleased Oasis record.
That's like he's getting there.
I'm like, I've never seen this one.
Yeah.
Yeah, they were huge.
But it was just a brief kind of window.
I saw their big documentary.
I mean, they were way bigger in the UK than here, but they were huge here too.
Their documentary is really great.
They actually just brought it out again in IMAX.
It's awesome.
It's one of the funniest things I've ever seen in my life.
It is because the music is great.
You know, it's heavy or heavy or beetles, rockier beetles, whatever you want to say.
It's not breaking new ground per se.
But those guys were destined to be rock stars.
The whole story is just perfect.
The quiet, you know, pure talent.
I just want to sit in my room and strum my acoustic guitar.
And then this mouthy alcohol castle.
And their brothers.
And they hate each other.
But they love each other.
It's a beautiful thing.
And they're not reuniting.
It's more annoying to me than the Smiths.
Because, you know, the Smiths would probably cancel that two dates in.
Morrissey would be impossible.
He still cancels all his fucking shows.
He's canceled three in LA in the last like five years.
And people still go see him.
Oasis.
Guys, suck it up.
You can tell whenever they speak about each other.
There's like this little smirk they have.
They love each other still.
We need you.
High flying birds.
It's fucking awful.
Vince Averyl's always trying to sell me on their side projects.
I'm like, dude.
BDI's music sucks.
BDI's not bad.
That's the singers.
Which one's the singer?
Liam or no?
Liam.
Right?
Liam's the singer.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I don't want to hear the guitar players band.
But Liam's band.
And it's not bad.
And they do like the tie -dye lava lamp backdrops.
You know, like we're still from the 60s, mate.
It's just stupid.
I still remember him.
His name was Grant.
Only guy I ever met named Grant in high school.
And he just.
He's always working blood.
Oh, we being choir class.
You really botched that solo, mate.
That sounded bloody awful.
Oh, God.
I'd kill him.
I'm a 16 year old kid from Missouri.
Speaking of the Smiths.
Yeah.
I was hanging out with Shane one time.
Gila Shane.
And he sang a thing at me.
Very randomly in an English accent.
And I was like, what the fuck is that?
And he was like, Smiths.
You don't like the Smiths?
He goes, I would have pegged you for a huge Smiths fan.
And I was like, you would be right to think that I would be really into them.
But I'm not.
I don't dislike them.
I'm just not.
I don't know.
I just never got.
Well, his miserable outlook on humanity.
You should speak to you.
But I've never bad a night.
Anyone saying they're not a Smiths fan.
I mean, it's not for everybody to listen to that goat bleat.
You know, but I love it.
I always have.
The music is is incredible.
And his singing and lyrics are great and funny, depending on your mood.
But yeah, it's not like pleasant to listen to all the time.
He can be annoying as fuck.
Well, the part, the thing Shane wasn't familiar with was I go, I go.
I don't listen to them, but I love them.
And I was like, Marcy's nuts.
And he was like, what do you mean?
And I was like, oh, you never did like a deep dive on Marcy interviews.
He's like, no, I was like, do do yourself a favor.
Yeah.
He's a madman.
Pull up to that YouTube tonight with a VAD of popcorn.
And just go down the rabbit hole because they're wild.
He quietly canceled like three shows here.
He was doing shows like for albums.
So like, Marcy's performing the entirety of you are the quarry is 2000.
And by the way, I like that album a lot.
But you can do that when it's the blue album.
Yeah.
Like, so he's trying to book like arenas and shit going off one of his albums.
It's like, Marcy, baby.
And he's got the fan base, but it's a weird fan base.
I don't know if you ever read that Chuck Closterman article,
but he's got an obsessive Hispanic fan base.
And they all think he's straight, despite him saying that he's gay constantly.
Yeah.
No, no, no.
Marcy's straight.
Girlfriend in a coma.
How about that song?
That's maybe my favorite Smith song, Girlfriend in a coma.
His newest album, which has not been released, the record label wouldn't put it out.
Yeah, because it was too controversial.
It's called Bonfire of Teenagers.
I listened to a few of the songs on YouTube.
And they're great songs.
And he said he's like, this is my best album and they won't put it out.
And it's very good.
What's the theoretical issue?
He's usually going after like Margaret Thatcher.
Who gives a shit?
He's referring to some incident.
And forgive me that I can't remember the details because it's horrible
where a bunch of teenagers died in a fire.
It was a political something clash.
So he's saying like, you made a bonfire of teenagers.
And they're like, you can't, it's basically like it was like a Columbine kind of thing.
I got you.
And he said, they're like, this is too much, man.
You can't, you know, you can't do this.
What you can't.
Well, you can't, I don't give a fuck about M &M anymore.
But like I just heard a clip from his new album and it's like.
Alan Baldwin shot that bitch on the set of rust.
What?
Were she's your target?
Like he's like making fun of that woman.
And it's like clear.
So clearly that's his thing.
He has to shock you at age 50, you know, whatever.
He's got to try harder.
But like you can release anything.
He that new album is very good.
The, the, I guess it would count as a scary stuff because it's.
It's intense lyric, lyrical content would, would suffice.
But it's a, the premise of the album is that he, he resurrects the Slim Shady character
and he's going to kill him off.
Because he's like, you know, my whole career, I used you to say crazy shit.
And then he's doing like this duel.
It's very interesting.
He's doing like this dual personality thing through the record
where he's like, Slim Shady's like, I made you.
How fucking dare you try to get rid of me.
And he M &M's like, but I don't think that way.
And I'm trying to be a better man.
And it's a very interesting commentary.
But the song he does like full on Slim Shady.
He is saying crazy shit.
Like, but, but like a lot of the targets very fair.
Goes after Diddy real bad.
Pretty, you know, what's her face?
He talks a lot about how.
Oh, damn it.
What's the lady?
Who's the black lady?
The political pundit.
That always says crazy.
And his own.
Hannah Soats.
He talks a lot about her.
Like, she forgot she was black.
And stuff like that.
Like, it's sort of the stuff is.
It's stuff that a lot of people would agree with.
But it's still wild.
Like, it's still wild.
He says Diddy beat that woman up in the hotel
because she wouldn't put the dildo back in his ass.
And he got mad.
Like, it's crazy.
Yeah.
Diddy's sitting at home like, how does he know that?
Diddy thing, man.
It really just goes to show you.
The reason I think it's so easy to slip into hopelessness
and despair is just if you think about things.
And I've been trying to not think about things.
Just occupy every minute of my day.
Never allow my brain to wander.
And it's doing okay for me.
But we've seen that video.
We know some confirmed some rumor,
but we know about dozens of physical sexual mental assaults
done by Diddy over the last 30 years.
And he's out on his jet ski every day.
Yeah.
Well, and if and look,
I think Trump's going to be president.
But he just got indicted on a million things
and he's probably going to be our president.
And if you're a victim or if you have been assaulted
or whatever, you kind of just be sitting there
going, what a disgusting world this is.
I'll tell you what's real weird about it.
Even if you haven't, by the way.
But especially if you have,
it's just like nuts.
So if he was still in the position
of just flat out denying things.
Yeah.
And the video hadn't come out.
I would think his publicist is being like, dude,
you got to go out and just live life.
Because if you don't,
it's going to look like you're guilty or something.
But now the video's out.
And he has apologized and said,
like, I'm ashamed of myself.
So to do that and then not disappear for a moment.
Yeah.
But still kind of live like that's real weird.
That's real weird.
Agreed.
But well, we're going to get into that more probably
in the movie corner because I watched that documentary.
Yeah.
Well, speaking speaking of that about going away
and how long you should go away.
And if you should have to go away.
And what an apology means.
And what can we forgive?
And what can we not?
There's a new documentary called Sorry Not Sorry
about Louis CK Joe and I both watched it last night.
It's a tight 90.
I'm sure it'll be on one of the streamers in a couple of weeks.
But I was just curious about it.
And the review I had read of it was like,
it gave it a C minus,
which generally if something,
if a,
if the goal of a documentary is pure,
like shining a light on Harvey Weinstein,
whatever it may be,
they always give it a good grade.
Even if the documentary is just shit.
And this one was like,
now this sucks.
We know all this information.
We've actually seen all of these clips.
Anyone with even a passing interest in comedy or CK
or any of that would have seen or heard everything that's
in this documentary.
There's no bombshell revelation.
And that was their issue with it.
It's like you've had years now.
Like you didn't dig up anything new.
And that's a valid criticism.
What I will say is at the beginning of this thing,
I was very annoyed by it.
Annoyed by all these comics coming forward.
Being like, you know,
some of them are like,
we knew when we said nothing.
And then some are like,
you knew when you said nothing.
And everybody's judging and passing the buck and saying,
well, what could we have done
and could we have stopped it and blow a blow.
And then as the documentary went on,
I realized that that's what I liked about it.
I thought it was asking pretty interesting questions.
And it didn't really have a definitive fuck this guy.
He should go away.
People said that.
That didn't seem to be the point of the doc, though, to me.
Point of the doc seemed to be just what I was saying.
What can we forgive if a man apologizes
and he goes away for nine months?
Do we really need him to go away for another three years?
When can he come back?
What do we allow?
Those questions I thought were interesting
and made the documentary worthwhile.
And as a student of or fan of comedy,
a guy who works in comedy,
I love watching anything that disgusts it.
You know, whether I agree with it or not.
So I liked it.
I wound up liking it more than I expected to.
I don't know what you thought about it.
I didn't like it.
I felt the kind of the opposite of you.
I felt like they were presenting it like
it was going to be this balanced dissection on what you're saying.
Yeah.
And I felt like, aside from Noam Dorman,
who owns the comedy seller,
who I thought made some very valid points of like,
look, we can all have different opinions on this.
But when you start, because his club got attacked
for being the first club that put Louis back on stage.
Yes.
And when he started saying like, look,
we can have different opinions on this.
That's fine.
But when a man apologizes and there's no crime at hand,
when you start saying proprietors are not allowed to employ the man
in specific ways and fans that want to see him
are not allowed to see him.
And you start damning those people.
And when he started to get into,
so what does that mean?
He becomes a ward of the state.
Yeah.
I thought he had a great point there.
You know, I thought that was very, very fair.
But I felt like he was the only voice outside of the one clip
of Matt Damon they showed.
And then some fans at the very end that I felt they tried to make
look shitty.
Yeah.
I mean, that one fan and, you know,
if I said something like this,
I don't think I'd sign my name to the release form,
but I got it.
He was like, we all,
you just seem like some dude off the street who was a fan of
Louis CK, but he's like, we all are willing to look past
something in our day -to -day life.
We all have a fucked up blind spot.
Louis CK is mine.
I think he's really funny.
I'm here at the show.
And, you know, the documentary can't praise that attitude,
but I thought it was a little more balanced than I expected.
I have problems with what Louis CK did,
whether it's technically illegal,
which I think it is in most of these cases or not.
But I also, more and more,
I'm trying to lead with forgiveness and not shut people out,
especially if they're apologetic and so forth.
So I don't know.
I didn't think it really had an axe to grind,
despite there being several, you know,
of the women who come forward and tell their stories.
But it's another issue.
The stories aren't horrific.
And that's, well,
that depends on your definition of horrific.
But like what Matt Damon is saying in it,
it would be horrific to have that happen to you, okay?
But they're not as horrific as a rape.
What Matt Damon says in here,
what even Jen Kirkman says in here is like,
there's got to be differences
in what we consider assault.
So Matt Damon, they don't show the whole interview,
but his interview basically said like,
there has to be a difference between slapping a woman on the ass
or saying nice ass and rape.
And some of the celebs who agreed with that at the time,
sharing stone and stuff like that,
were highly criticized.
Matt Damon's still when he has a new movie coming out,
if you look in the comments, they're like,
well, here's another piece of shit I won't be seeing
because this guy thinks, you know,
all assault is the same, whatever else.
I just wish, and Joe and I have been beating this
for since the start of this podcast.
I just wish there was a bit more nuance in life.
Well, that was my problem with the whole thing was,
this is what I'm trying to say.
They didn't interview regardless,
and I know we won't get all into it.
I'm friends with Louis.
I think he did a thing, he denied doing the thing,
he then apologized and admitted to the thing,
he went away, he should be allowed to work again.
That's my take or agree with me or not.
What bothered me in this was,
they weren't interviewing anybody that was saying,
well, I think he did take enough time off,
or I did think the apology was good.
It was only people saying it wasn't the right kind of apology,
or he didn't say this in the apology,
and he didn't go away long enough,
or when he did stand up about it,
he didn't address it in this way.
It's like, guys, it's a minefield,
and I did think that Kirkman had a really,
it was a little confusing, the amount of,
she wanted to talk about it, then she didn't want to talk about it,
then she wanted to be linked to it,
and then she didn't want to be linked to it.
That's fine, it's your prerogative,
it's different for everybody.
But I did think she walked the line pretty well,
and that's it, it was an odd thing to bring out at this point,
and I was scratching my head a little bit about it
and walked away from it thinking,
this is made by, I mean it's the New York Times,
it was behind it, so I felt like it was just made by people
who were saying, don't forget about this,
which fine, sure, let's not forget about it,
but also we're still not happy with what's going on,
and I, you know, that's fine too,
to each their own opinion, but I don't know,
there's no answer, there's no real answer, it's foggy,
and that's why I would have rather had, you know,
I guess what I'm describing that I liked about this,
I wish it was much more of that than it is.
I think especially if you're doing it this far after the incidents themselves,
there should be some new information in the doc,
I do agree with that negative review I met, I read.
It's a lot like when they came out with like this Taylor Swift scooter brawn documentary on Max,
and I'm like, well I'm not gonna watch four hours about Taylor Swift's legal battles,
but they rushed these things out just because they can get eyes on them.
This wasn't a rush job, you know,
these incidents happened five years ago,
and it definitely doesn't feel like it's a new look at things,
it just kind of feels like digging up old shit.
However, you know, we cancel people,
and we don't cancel people,
and there's degrees of cancellation,
and certain things are hypocritical,
and certain things aren't.
But Luis A .K. is not allowed to make money off Netflix,
or Hulu, or Amazon,
none of these places has stepped up and said,
you know what?
We'll take the PR hit,
and let Luis A .K. do a stand -up special for Hulu, let's say.
Nobody is letting him do that.
He still has to make all his money himself,
and he still has many fans to go see his show.
That is a punishment.
I agree.
But Hulu does have...
His old special.
Hars and Pete.
I think it's a little Hars and Pete, yeah.
So there's a little bit of it.
But the, you know, look,
it's kind of like...
No, yeah.
And it's...
But here's the thing, too.
I would have...
They have a clip of Janine Garofalo.
And I'll veer into a bigger idea here,
but they have a clip of Janine saying,
like, coming to his defense,
and not saying he didn't do it,
or it was okay that he did it,
but saying he should be allowed to work again.
I would have just liked to have seen
a little more from people in that position,
especially females,
and I would have found their thoughts interesting.
Again, whether you agree or disagree,
that's besides the point,
it would have bounced it out.
For me, it's kind of a lot like
when you get into the abortion discussion.
Now, I'm pro -choice, very pro -choice.
There are many women in my family
that are not pro -choice.
Right.
But whatever I see a thing about abortion,
it's either a right -wing,
fueled Candice Owen style.
You're all going to burn in hell.
You baby killers thing.
Or it's women's rights,
we need abortion to be legal,
and it's that side of it.
I'd like to see a thing that shows both.
I'd like to see a thing where you're seeing women
saying I'm for abortion,
and then women who are saying,
I'm against it,
and hearing the arguments from both.
This is the class of people
we're supposed to be listening to on that topic, for instance.
Yeah.
And I just never see, as you said,
a nuanced approach to any of these things.
You watch a gun documentary.
It's either...
This is why we need gun laws
or they're taking our guns away.
It's one or the other.
It's like, show me some people from both
and just let me hear the argument.
You know where that kind of started?
And when I saw these movies,
when they came out,
I was very passionate,
and I loved them,
and I got into them.
They were really the things
that kind of started getting me into politics,
because I didn't care about it till my 20s,
late 20s.
But it was Michael Moore's documentaries.
Now I don't think I would watch one of these things
with a gun to my head.
No.
But he put himself in these things,
and it's not only one -sided,
it's heavily, aggressively one -sided.
You're only seeing what he wants you to see,
and then he's narrating it and appearing in it.
So you're really just watching a guy
tell you what he thinks.
That was never what a documentary was before.
Yeah.
Well, also too.
He was the guy that got caught,
fudging statistics and all this stuff.
Yeah.
And then when he got called out on it,
the defense was,
well, who cares?
It's for a good cause.
And that's where that all started,
where you're like,
this is very dangerous.
The road we're going down here.
Yeah.
And there's documentaries
that are like anti -Michael Moore documentaries,
and then like when they'll go
and try to interview him and confront him,
the way he tries to confront Dick Clark,
for instance, in Bolivian Columbine,
and Dick Clark shuts the door
because he's bombarded with these cameras.
And he's like, what is going on?
Right.
And slams the door.
And Michael Moore is like,
yeah, nobody wants to be accountable.
And whatever.
There's footage.
I've seen him in documentaries
where I think the one was called
Michael Moore hates America or something.
The guy goes to a Michael Moore event,
and he goes up at the Q &A,
and he addresses like,
what do you have to say for this?
And Michael Moore has him thrown out.
And I'm like,
yeah, you're doing the thing that you're complaining about.
And you should have nothing to hide, Michael Moore.
You shouldn't care.
If they really wanted to spin it back on him, though,
they should have gone to his home,
and just like open the door
while Michael Moore is sitting there in sweatpants
and a piss -stained t -shirt
and asked him his opinion on things.
Like, don't go to him at an event
where he's had time to make himself look pretty.
That's not what you did to Dick Clark.
Yeah.
Dick Clark.
Mike, before you throw me out,
could I at least have some of that chili,
it looks good.
I didn't make enough for two.
We got a giant pot on the stove, hot pot.
Sorry, Mike.
All right.
Well, that was, you know,
look, obviously it's a,
it's a watchable documentary.
You know, you can have lots of conversations about it at least.
I saw a picture called
Chuck and Buck.
Oh, yeah.
I see that one, Joe.
I think I did in college.
I remember that movie.
That's kind of what set off.
What's his face?
Mike White.
Yeah, White Lotus.
Yeah.
Okay.
It came out in 2000.
I would have been working at Blockbuster.
That title,
was the Brazilian director.
Work hit by the writer.
Remnted it had no idea who these people were,
Mike White is a very odd looking guy.
He's written many great movies,
including Orange County.
And particularly the school of rock.
He used to be like.
Just a great writer of.
Funtie character based non -raunchy comedy.
He was just the guy, you know.
And then over time.
His work got darker and stranger and weirder and deeper and now he's doing the white lotus one of the most acclaimed shows on television and an excellent show.
I'm a big fan. He's also an actor. He wrote this and acted in it. Chuck and Buck is about a guy with the maturity level of a child, basically.
His mother dies and he goes to Los Angeles and looks up and starts stalking Chris Whites. Chris Whites is the guy who is now a director. He did.
I'm thinking of Paul Whites. Sorry. Paul Whites is Chris Whites's brother.
He's in this movie too, which is why I'm confused, but the Whites brothers did American pie. So they're also actors, writers, directors.
And you don't see these people very often in things, which is why the movie feels even more real and disturbing, but basically he's stalking this guy, his friend from childhood who is now married.
It's not clear why and over time the movie reveals that these two fooled around sexually when they were kids, which was heavily egg -drawn by Mike Whites character.
And he's still obsessed. He's the only sex he's ever had. So he thinks this guy still loves him and not that it was a couple of kids fooling around.
Very dark, very funny at times. The Mike Whites character decides to put on a play about the two of them, which is how the guys fiance finds out that this weird shit went on when they were little.
Just a really good ultra ultra low budget indie. It's funny. It's uncomfortable. And the reason I saw it out is I watched this great 15 minute black and white discussion, where it was actors being asked their favorite performances of the 2000s.
And everybody had interesting answers. There's always the boring thing where, you know, somebody's like, I like Daniel Day Lewis and Lincoln. You're like, shut the fuck up. You don't want those answers personally.
Right. And they go to Jeff Bridges, always a reliable, funny old coot. And he goes, I'm best in the 2000s. He goes, you know what I'm going to say? I like that weird looking guy and chuck and buck. You see that movie? That was a wild one.
That was my favorite performance. Was that kid in chuck and buck? And I was like, what now that's a great answer. And he's right. It's a one of a kind, very bizarre original performance and a great early 2000s indie. Check it out if you haven't seen it.
Disney, very controversial. Everybody's yelling about the accolade. Why is it controversial? Everybody's mad. They're ruining Star Wars. They're ruining the Lord. This is not the other thing. And some of that is sort of true. Yeah, or that they're changing things sort of.
Look, my beef is this. I could give two shits if you make an entire Star Wars trilogy that stars nothing but, you know, women and.
And, and trans men and. I don't care. I'm not mad about any of that. Just make the God damn thing good. The show is bad. They spent I think $130 million on this show is more. The budget for the show was more than one of the prequel movies costs. Yeah.
It was double the budget of the Obi -Wan show, which was terrible and should not have been. It looks good. It's decently directed. The action sequences are pretty cool. But it's just bad. It's just poorly acted. It's not well written. It's confusing as hell.
The characters are not deep. You feel like you're watching like a bad episode of Star Trek Deep Space 9. Not even one of the good ones. It's just a bad show. And what they did in the finale, because the big controversy about this was.
There were force beings that were created without that were created from the force. Which is Anakin's story. Yeah. And people were mad that a hundred years before Anakin's birth, they're saying these women on a planet created two young women from the force. And they're trying to say that women did it first. And Anakin, because he's a man is not the chosen one. It was these and that's not what they're saying. It's not.
But people are getting really hung up on that. But what they are saying is is that they're rewriting the history of what happened in the universe. And all of that is supposed to be contributed to this character named Darth Plegas, who was Senator Palpatine's master.
So through the whole series, everybody's going, where the fuck is Darth Plegas? Darth Plegas was the one that did this. And they're going, we're not doing anything traditionally. We're not put any classic characters in this. We're doing our own thing, blah, blah, blah. They're sticking to their guns and then hits the finale. And what are they doing the finale?
They drop in a scene of who Darth Plegas lurking around in the background of a scene. He has no lines. He's just peeks out from around the corner. It's so obvious they added this to be like, we are getting destroyed by the fans. Like, we have to do something.
And then they tack on this other scene, the finale itself just stunk. It didn't there was a couple cool moments, but it was it's done. Then they tack on a scene at the very end, where this green Jedi lady, who in real life is Leslie headlands wife on the show. I can't remember her character's name, but it's not a very interesting character.
Again, it felt very Star Trek. And they had a repeating joke that she gets diarrhea when she's space travels, it messes with her bowels.
Forget how they phrased it, but it's just not, it just doesn't make sense. So anyway, one doesn't seem necessary to talk about.
Yeah, perhaps in the accolade. Yeah. So in the final scene of the entire series or the season, she walks into a room in the Jedi temple and she says to somebody off screen, we need to talk and the camera pans down and you see the back of Yoda's head.
Again, clearly they jammed this in at the last second, because they're like, everybody is like, where the fuck is Yoda? What is going on? None of this makes sense.
I thought it was odd to that he had the bandaid on the back of his neck like Marcellus Wallace. It's linking it to the Pulp fiction universe is very strange.
Pat, if you look at the screenshot, it's shot exactly like the Bruce Willis. I'm not kidding. It's shot exactly the same perspective as Wallace with with Willis.
It's just a bad show. It's just not good. And it's it's an upsets me because again, here we are. I said this to my friend Scott after Trump got shot.
You know, I was like, these times we live in are just terrible. It's so it's just the turmoil. It's just unbearable anymore.
And he said, well, this is terrible. He said, but is it any worse than the 60s? I mean, Kennedy got assassinated in the 60s. And I said, look, here's the difference to me.
The 60s had their tensions, obviously, they were turbulent. There was race issues. There was Kennedy. There was a lot of stuff going on in the 60s.
But here's the difference now. We have all that kind of stuff happening.
And on top of it, you can't even talk about Star Wars or Marvel anymore without within two minutes it devolving into some kind of discussion about civil rights and stuff.
It's like, it's exhausted. So what Disney has started doing is they make a bad product. And before the product even comes out, they start calling the fans racist.
They start predicting the backlash and whatever. And it's become painfully obvious, which was once just a hair brain theory by YouTubers is now fact and we're witnessing it happen.
They know they have a bad product. So they try to get ahead of the bad reaction by saying, you guys are going to just review bomb it because you're racist.
And it's like, no, you're making a shitty fucking thing. It sucks. It sucks. Just make a good fucking thing.
So they've got the even George Lucas recently said in an interview, he goes, yeah, I was the only one that knew what Star Wars was.
So nobody else knows how to do it. I was like, you've got the guy that created it now saying this.
Yeah. So it just sucks. It's bad. The act of wonder if he watches this shit and is just like shaking his head and disgust or if he gets into any of it.
I feel like he is, I feel like he's the McDonald brothers. Yeah. Driving past Ray Crox latest monstrosity on a highway just going like son of a bitch.
Yeah. What did we do? Yeah. So I think he's like, whatever. I did it. And that's it. And he's not coming back. But it's just just make a good goddamn product.
It's and this is not just Star Wars. It's not just Disney. It's everything. There are libraries of content that's already out there that people love that people like that's even if they don't know about it.
It's good. It's well done. Whole from that. I don't understand this thing of like, nope, we have to not pay a single dime to any previous creator ever.
We have to do everything in house. And you're spending more money that way. Right. And then it doesn't work. It doesn't work. Peter, when I saw I told you I was at that thing with Peter Billingsley. Yeah.
He worked on the first Iron Man movie. Right. A little bit or a little bit or a lot. I don't not sure to the extent of what but he worked on it.
But he said the most insightful thing was so fucking smart. We're talking all this. And he said he goes, look, man, if you're going to do that kind of thing, comic book, you, whatever thing, he goes, you make it for the fans. If you don't make it for the fans, the fans immediately will hate it.
And chances are the other people you're making it for aren't going to like it either because they're not that into it. But if you make it for the fans and the fans love it, that catches wind to the people that don't know what it is. And now they want to see it. And he's right. And that's just not what they're doing with almost anything anymore.
I don't get it. It's weird.
Nothing makes sense. That's about what it is. Nothing makes the goddamn sense. And speaking of to stay on theme, I rewatched movie 43. You familiar with this movie, Joe?
Oh, boy, it's yeah, yeah, in theory, this should have been fantastic. Sure. It was assembled by this big producer who knows a lot of big talented actors and Peter Farley, the Farley brothers fame.
And when this came out, I was like, oh, sweet. It's like 20 short films, all starring big names, recognizable names, all hard are rated, outrageous comedy. So you're thinking, okay, great. It's like the Kentucky fried movie or Amazon women on the moon or one of these things.
You're expecting it to be hit and miss. It's a sketch movie. But they're made so infrequently that I was pumped. I remember renting this movie 10 years ago. I remember getting the Netflix disc in the mail, ladies and gentlemen, because I am 100 years old.
And I put it in and I was like everyone else who watches this thing blown away by how terrible and disgusting and just bad it is.
Socks. And I saw it pop up on Amazon. And I was like, I'm going to give this another try, but I want to know how this thing even came to be. I urge you to check out the Wikipedia or the IMDB trivia. There's all kinds of fascinating information about how this came to be. But basically this producer who put it together along with Peter Farley is just apparently like a great guy and people love him. And he had this idea and the fairly brothers are supposed to be great really nice guys too.
And they reach out to these actors and we're like, Hey, you're like Hugh Jackman's in this. Halle Berry's in this. Oh, yeah.
You to never do comedy. How'd you like to be in a five minute short will pay you X. You get the chance to do big broad comedy without having to commit to it and derail your career. What do you think?
And some people were excited and others kept dodging him. And then for five years, he would chase them down and be like, remember when you told me you're going to do this, we're going to do this.
They waited people out. People said, I've got a movie to do. It takes two years. I'm going to be overseas. They're like, great, we'll shoot it when you get back.
And I admire that. I admire that kind of Roger Corman and Wood. We're going to get this done no matter what. But everybody thought along the way that this was going to be a huge hit with all these stars. How could it not be.
They just chose all the wrong sketches to do. They're all so bad and so not funny. And some of them are disgusting. But what's weird is that when I watch this, the premise of it was Dennis Quaid.
I believe had a meeting with a big production executive at a movie studio. And he was pitching him all the worst ideas. Like he was a crazy guy. And they're like, we got to get this guy out of here. He was crazy. But he just kept going and going.
And every time you would pitch a new movie. Okay, you don't like that one. How about this. And then it would go into the next sketch. Stupid, but a good framing device.
When I'm watching it now 10 years later on Amazon, it's three kids on the internet looking for the most disturbing and fucked up internet video. And that's the framing device that leads to all these sketches.
So I go, well, what's going on with this? I remember Dennis Quaid. I remember an entirely different movie. And I looked into it and sure enough, this movie was such a disaster and tested so badly that they put together a bunch of different versions of it.
It shot an entirely different framing device because they're like, maybe this one will work and people liked that one less because that's the problem always is the framing device.
Exactly. So now I've seen every possible version of this. When you look it up online, there are sketches that have still never seen the light of day, including one Bob Odin Kirk did. I'm sure he's very relieved that they cut this thing.
But yeah, it's gross. You got Chris Pratt and Anna Ferris. She's begging to shit on him during sex. And he's like, I don't know and they go back and forth, back and forth. Finally, he decides he's going to do it and he eats a huge meal because he's going to really let her have it.
And they wind up something happens and they have to run outside. He gets hit by a car and he explodes and a thousand pounds of shit go flying all over the windshield of this car and all over the street.
And that's essentially the level of comedy you're dealing with throughout the Halle Berry Hugh Jackman one. She's like, I'm going on a date with this guy. I bet he's going to be ugly because he sounded perfect on the phone.
And they go ugly show him a picture of Hugh Jackman. Oh, wow. They go out on the date. Hugh Jackman shows up and he has a large set of human male balls attached to his chin.
Right. And Halle Berry is trying not to look at it. And then he like bends over to like get the salt and his balls drop into his soup.
Oh, for God's sake. And you're like, how did these people sit here on set and do this?
It doesn't make any sense. There should be an aniferous box set. Yeah.
As soon as you say movie 43, that's the first person that pops in my head. She's been in more bad fucking comedies.
She had well, I also watched her in funny ones called smiley face, which I recommend. But she can be great. I'm not saying she's not great.
I'm saying she's been I mean, she's when you're the the lead of the scary movie late phase sequels. Yeah, three four five.
Like it's your your rough shape.
These shorts were directed by Elizabeth Banks. Yep.
Years ahead of cocaine bear James Gunn who went on to much bigger things Brett Ratner who went on to much bigger things and then got cancelled.
The great Rusty Kundeef who did you know, tells from the hood and a lot of CB4, that kind of stuff.
There's good people involved.
Don't give me wrong and the cast it is kind of fun where every time a new short starts, you're like, oh, here's some big stars.
You got Sean William Scott and Johnny Knoxville who have kidnapped a leprechaun played by Gerard Butler.
That's one of the sketches.
You got Leo Schreiber and Naomi Watts as a married couple who homeschool their kid but make it that was actually kind of funny.
They make it like real like they're always beating him up and calling him slurs and Naomi Watts makes out with him at one point to teach him about sex.
It's a it's an extreme or rated comedy it's shocking almost none of it works.
I'm sure everyone involved Jeremy Ellen White is the you know, the guy from the bear is the kid who's making out with his mom in that short.
I would imagine all these people wish this movie never happened and could be scrubbed from their resume.
Emma Stone, Emily Stone excuse me, Kiran Culkin, Steven Merchandt.
You got great people at it. It just doesn't work.
There's nothing more dangerous than people trying to be funny, which is always a challenge of writing comedy.
Once you start trying to be funny, you got a problem.
This is a movie that starts with trying to be funny and then it incorporates dozens of people who are not funny.
Trying to be funny and trying to be shocking is also never, never a good thing.
And the fairies know that, which is kind of weird that they were involved in this, but I'm realizing as I say it, I'm mixing up a couple of them.
Kate Winslet was the one who went on the date with Hugh Jackman and his balls chin.
Pete Winslet, Halle Berry is the one who went out with Stephen Merchandt, which is already an unbelievable premise.
But yeah, this is one of the weirder movies ever made.
When you look up worst comedies ever, it's always very high on the list and it's only 10 years old.
So like I recommend watching it. It's insane and it's certainly not boring.
So there you go.
My last entry is not a movie.
It's an audio book, but it is pertaining to entertainment and it does apply to comedy.
I listen to this when I was driving to Pittsburgh, but I listen to Phil Rosenthal's, you're lucky, you're funny.
It's his book about his, his half memoir and half how the excerpts of his life that he does recap influenced his early career and everybody loves Raymond.
And what it would have it went into the show and how it helped shape the show and all that.
It's a very fun listen. He's an extraordinarily positive charming guy.
That also does talk about how he used to get depressed and stuff. It's not annoying.
And it's just a great listen. And the thing I appreciated most about it is he talks about his horrible experiences writing on TV shows, pre -Raymond.
And he names some names and he names some shows.
He tells a great story about he was doing, oh God, baby talk, which was the TV, the sitcom version of Look Who's Talking.
With Clooney, yeah.
Yeah, and Clooney was in it and he said Clooney, they were like giving him terrible, you know, the showrunner was giving him like terrible jokes or something.
And Clooney screamed, I believe in front of an audience.
You're not the one up here with your dick hanging in the wind and threw his script across the stage.
Yeah. And he said the writers all got called upstairs by the showrunner and he goes, he goes, he's got an interesting way of putting things.
He goes, well, let him do pilots for the rest of his career. Maybe his character is on a plane to Africa next week and we never see him again.
And Phil Rosenthal goes the next week that character flew to Africa and we never saw him again.
Yeah.
But the stories are great.
He's talking about nothing is ever funny at 2 a .m. when they keep you there till 2 in the morning.
Yeah, he talks a lot about like it never has to be that way.
If you have your shit together and you know what you're doing, your writers can leave at 5 or 6 o 'clock.
So they can go live their lives and bring in funny things for the show.
Yeah, because that's what you need to do is live life so you have ideas.
Right.
It's a great listen.
I recommend it.
And I've always been fascinated with him because obviously they did 200 plus episodes of Raymond.
I've only seen the first season of the show. I think it's excellent. I just don't have the time.
But it's an exceptionally well -written family sitcom like one of it's a pinnacle of the form basically.
But the guy never really did anything else.
Well, he he talks about that.
He said he tried to sell shows after Raymond and he was denied.
And he was told by CBS nobody wants to hear from people in their 40s anymore.
Oh, my God.
And he said he goes, I'm doing every somebody feed Phil whatever the hell it's called.
He goes, I do that now.
And he goes, everybody thinks that's just what I want it to do.
And I just got to do whatever I want.
He goes, it took me nine years to get this show on TV.
He goes, it's it was hard.
He was like, that's so fucking insane.
It's crazy.
And I'm seeing pilots he's had here.
You know, like the winklers, which I assume was Henry Winkler and so forth.
But yeah, Henry Winkler, Judith Light.
It's like CBS in particular should should still be making whatever this man wants to make.
Yeah, they forget so quickly that the only reason they're still standing is that you had a show like everybody loves Raymond go 210 episodes and win all the fucking Emmys
and go into massive syndication that you still make money off of that still keeps the lights on.
And you're going to tell this guy nobody cares about people over 40.
You should make whatever the fuck this man wants to make.
And I'm not saying do it till the end of time.
If he has three bombs following Raymond.
Okay.
You struck lightning once.
It's not going to happen again.
But he should be another he should be another Chuck Laurie for sure.
You know, but he he was told he was like they all wanted their friends.
Everybody wanted to clone friends.
And he and he talks about the shows they put on.
And he's like, and none of them worked.
They all bought.
He goes, you can't it's people.
I mean, those shows are about the people you cast Frank.
You don't get the friends cast.
It's a it's a one and a billion shot.
Everyone on that cast like this.
Aniston was in another pilot that they let her out of this show didn't go so.
It's it's a one and a billion.
Like, what are you doing?
What are you doing?
These show I'm thinking about that when I was in like high school college, etc.
Every show was six hot people.
But they had no writing.
They had no jokes.
They had no chemistry.
And they're just like, well, we'll just keep doing until we get another friends.
They don't know that it's a fluke.
Well, the one thing that friends had and Raymond had that these other shows don't is they were based on people's life experiences.
Yeah.
He talks about the meeting with Romano.
When he gets the development deal and he's like, what are you thinking?
And he said, Ray, Ray Romano was like, I don't know.
And he started.
He goes, just tell me about your life.
Yeah.
And he's like, I got a brother who's a cop.
He still lives at home.
Yeah.
Parents are overbearing.
And he was like, this is the show.
And he said Ray Romano was kind of like, I don't know, man.
Like, what are you talking about?
You know?
Because there's no hook.
And he said he was the best episode of Seinfeld was the contest for a reason.
All four characters are involved in the A story.
And that's what you're there to see.
You're there to see them all together tackling something.
And he talks about how a lot of everybody loves Raymond was only an A story.
Because that's what you wanted to see.
It's a really inside their like plays.
I mean, I can only remember a handful of times they even leave the living room.
You know, they might go up to their bedroom or something.
But that's about it.
It's writing.
It's all the writing in a sitcom.
It's the personal experience of the guy writing it.
And it's the cast.
You can't, you can't make these things happen.
Let's get to Arcadian.
Starring Nick Cage.
And is the, is the kid in Stranger Things?
No, he's it.
It's Bill.
Yeah, I was watching it.
First like 30 minutes.
I was like, how the fuck I know this kid?
Yeah, he finally looked it up.
He's a good actor.
So it was the other kid.
And kids.
Yeah.
And Cage is good in this.
It's on, you know, it's not a, it's, it's a, he's a present role.
But it's not a big role.
But he's good.
There's no, there's no.
All right.
So here's the premise.
The premise is at the top of the movie.
Cage is running through.
It's very handheld camera shaky.
He's running from a dilapidated structure of some kind.
And he's hiding and ducking around corners.
And every time he kind of ducks around a corner,
you see in the background, there's like explosions happening and things.
And it's clearly like something terrible is happening.
Is this the end of the world?
Whatever.
He finally gets to his shelter.
Which you see he's living in like a cave.
Yeah.
And he has two babies there.
And then it cuts to a card.
It's us 15 years later.
He is there with his two sons who are now grown.
And the premise of the movie is which they never explain.
The end of the world has happened in some capacity.
And they have to sort of batten down the hatches every night.
Because something comes out of the darkness that's not out in the daytime.
It's basically I am legend.
I mean, the movie really is just I am legend.
They just kind of took the premise.
I mean, it rips off a lot of things.
But I'd say what it feels the most they ripped off is quite a place to me.
There's some of that.
I agree.
But yeah, it's.
Yeah, it's it's your standard.
It's the apocalypse.
And we're all fighting for a survival.
And there are aliens here.
What's set it apart for me is the alien designs which on an extremely low budget.
I thought were much cooler than those in a quiet place.
And also cooler than most alien designs I've seen over the last ten or so years.
So you thought they were aliens because I thought there's a part where they.
So there's a farm.
Like a mile from the homestead that Nicholas Cage has called the Rose Farm.
Where one of his sons keeps sort of running off to it throughout the first part of the movie.
And the Rose Farm is sort of like rush on the daughter.
Yeah, the it's like the nice version of where they live.
They have more supplies.
They're happy to see the kid.
He's a nice kid.
He likes the daughter.
And he plays a game with the daughter called.
It's called like to find the apocalypse or something.
And you have to say what happened in ten seconds and they both give their renditions of what they think happened.
Because nobody knows what happened.
But they say these bugs infected people and the people turned into zombies.
Another version they say they turned into werewolves.
I didn't take it as aliens.
It took them more as like these are mutated people, which again very I am legend.
These are people that were normal.
And now they've mutated into these animal things.
The design was.
I agree.
It was kind of cool.
It was.
This was my biggest problem with the movie.
Eventually they get into, of course, these things are able to access their homes.
Because they've been boarding up the normal entryways for so long.
These things evolve and learn how to burrow underground.
They start coming into the houses through the floor.
Yeah.
And that's when you start to see them.
I found the designs interesting, but I was very confused.
Every time they fought these things, like the things do a chatter thing with their teeth.
Yeah, I like that.
Which was cool.
But then they also drip stuff as they walk.
Like they walk and like blood and shit drips out of them.
Yeah.
But then also the jaw opens up and a thing comes out of the jaw that looks like a plant.
It gets to a point where I was like, what the fuck?
I don't know what the fuck I'm looking at right now.
This is confusing the shit out of me.
Like I don't, but maybe that was the point.
I don't know.
Well, to me, it goes back to fucking Gremlins.
Give us clear, concise rules early on about the entity we're dealing with.
Gremlins does a better job of that than almost any movie in the history of time.
And I feel like it's just because that movie was kind of made for kids.
It's PG.
I felt they were like, well, let's really explain it to them.
But you have to do that.
It immediately puts you in the mindset of the person fighting the alien.
You're like, okay, now I know what will and won't work against it.
It just adds suspense.
So I hear what you're saying.
I thought they were cool looking, but you definitely don't know moment to moment what they are or what they,
what makes them tick or how to stop them.
They're resistant to light, which at this point, you can't make your alien or creature resistant to light guys.
That's also Gremlins, by the way, but it's also every other movie.
Yeah.
The the basic, you know, hook is Nicholas Cage gets injured, rescuing his son falls into a cab,
cavern or something when he's trying to get home.
Nicholas Cage has to go out in the night time to find him.
Because of this, they encounter these monsters.
Nicholas Cage gets injured.
He's going to die if he doesn't get medicine.
They don't have medicine.
The farm has medicine.
So they have to go to the farm to try to get the medicine.
The farm people won't give it to them.
They try to steal it.
The farm people try to kill them.
Then the farm gets attacked by the monsters.
And it ends up with the girl, the two sons and a half dead Nicholas Cage in the cage homestead for the big finale fight.
It's a tight 90 minutes.
The thing flies.
The movie flies.
It did.
It was well paced.
And that's it.
Is Cage going to live?
Is he going to die?
Who's going to live?
Who's going to die?
There's not much to this.
I was a little.
It's another one of these RJ LE, whatever the hell it's called, movies that this company.
I don't know who the fuck they are.
They have an unlimited budget.
They make movie after movie with notable people.
Uh, yet to me, they're no different.
Or really any better than the companies that would release like.
Um, Lord of the.
Lord of the bracelets, you know, like, remember when we were in high school and they would release these, these rip off movies of the big hit to.
Side stores.
A silent.
Yeah.
And they're really, in most cases, trying to make the cover art and the title so close that idiots rented by mistake.
Um, this is maybe a little better than that, I guess, but it definitely feels like this is their low budget take on a quiet place.
Everything about it feels very similar.
Um, in a quiet place, you know, we eventually, uh, with the help of Joe kind of blew up a lot of its plot holes in that movie.
I liked it a lot better on a, you know, first midnight viewing than I did a second.
But.
Yeah, there's just not enough to it.
I like a tight 90 minute movie, but.
There's no surprises of any kind.
It just feels like every other one of these except, as I said, I did like the creatures.
They showed a little more, uh, innovation than I've seen lately.
And I always like cage, but.
To me, why are you casting Nick Cage in the Bruce Willis role?
Why are you casting him in the, in the role of the guy who barely speaks, who's off camera, a lot of the film.
And when I say the Bruce Willis role, I mean Bruce Willis post diagnosis.
These movies, a lot of them for the same company where he would show up, not know where he was because he had dementia and acting these movies for a million or two million dollars.
And cage sadly has become one of these guys.
I guess not sadly because it keeps him in money, which is good.
Yeah, sometimes he is sometimes.
Yeah, not to the extent.
Yeah, but yeah, I hear you.
It's just like that's not cage.
To me, you don't waste Nicholas Cage in a near mute dad role.
It's just silly.
Um, because he is, he's electric, you know.
As we're seeing now with fucking long legs and with everything else he's made for the most part, he brings some other quality to a movie, a crazy, a scary, dangerous quality to a movie.
And to just plug him into this role where he's like, I got your son.
It's just a drag to me, you know, especially because he's 60 and he's saying he's going to retire soon.
But that said, he's good.
The kids are good.
Um, I thought it was directed really well and a lot of these shots of just them driving around looked really cool.
It felt to me almost like a director who's like, I'm ready to show you what I can do.
I'm a little sick of having to keep doing these low budget rinky dink movies because this was a pretty well done movie.
Benjamin Brewers, the director's name written by Michael, Michael nylon, I'm a pronouncing Michael, Michael.
Um, but yeah, you're right.
It's R L J E films.
My guess is they're in chats worth L A.
My guess is they have ties to the porn industry.
And oh, yeah, the company originally distributed X rated titles in addition to mainstream titles.
Um, they also used to work in the CD.
The ROM market.
Yeah.
That makes sense.
So look, I mean, my guess these movies and shutter is the new home for them.
Um, man, I just wish there'd be a great one.
You know, there's just so rarely a great one.
My guess is what attracted Nicholas Cage to it was that he's not doing his crazy thing.
I think he was like, I want to do something where I'm not doing that.
Look, it's an effective enough movie.
I cared enough.
I didn't love it.
I don't know how to watch it again, but I didn't hate it.
Cage, they did a very effective thing in the beginning where Cage, when he gets back to that cave I was talking about.
He picks up the two babies and he's holding them and he's going, you're safe.
You're safe.
And it's a touching moment.
And in the end of the movie, which did get me excited when a half dead bed ridden cage gets up.
Good moment.
Yeah, and he's like, he's basically like, out of my way.
And he's like going to sacrifice himself for the kids.
And then again, they're like, what are we supposed to do?
And he's like, I like that.
You know, that's an easy cheer for me.
Yeah.
And when he, when in the final moment, when he's, when you realize he's going to sacrifice himself for the kids,
they do a, they do a cutaway to that scene where he's holding the babies.
It's very sweet.
It makes you care.
Yeah.
You're sad to see him die, but then the kids live, the girl lives.
And they write off into the sunset in the hopes of finding the rest of humanity.
I would have much preferred, and I'm assuming it just wasn't an option.
I would have much preferred a rendition of I am legend starring Nicholas Cage.
That's all I kept thinking about was like, this would be so awesome.
If this was just I am legend with Nicholas Cage.
Yeah.
I would watch that in two seconds, because they still haven't made a true to the book.
I am legend.
And I felt like they kind of skirted up against it more.
This felt very much like last man on earth, the Vincent Price one.
And I'm making a sequel to I am legend, though, which where by the way,
they're making a sequel using the unused ending where Will Smith lives.
That's nuts.
It's that shit.
It's fucking bad shit.
Yeah.
So now if you see the sequel, you have to go by the DVD and watch the bonus feature ending.
I'm sure they'll re -release it with the new ending, whatever, but it's crazy.
And now it's even crazier.
He's like, wait, now you're making a sequel that's even further away with now making the original
even further away from what the fucking, they say the original, the unused ending of the Will Smith one is closer to the book.
It's only closer to the book because he lives.
Right.
Like it's not that close to the goddamn book.
So I don't know.
What's the, what's the Heston movie that's essentially I am legend?
The Omega Man.
I kind of dug the Omega Man actually.
I love I am legend.
I love the Omega Man.
And I love the last man on earth.
I loved all three.
And the asylum, the company we were talking about made a movie called I am Omega, which was there.
You are legend coming soon from RLD film.
And I am legend two, by the way, of course, of course, has what's his name?
It's in it.
Creed.
Jordan.
Michael be Jordan.
So it's of course, it's like now we're going to get a younger guy who's going to be like the younger Smith and Smith will be like the dad kind of guy to him.
Yeah.
Well, he's just going to go back and do all his old shit because he knows he's too big of a risk at this point that that latest bad boys.
I don't remember if I ever even talked about it on here, but the movie was made to rehab his reputation.
It's out of nowhere.
The Martin Lawrence character is insane.
Right.
That's strictly so that will Smith looks normal and can keep telling him you're insane.
And then there's women throwing themselves that will Smith throughout.
And it's just very like, hey, everybody, I'm straight and I'm normal.
That's why I'm making this movie.
Does any slap Martin Lawrence at one point?
Isn't there a slap joke in it?
He slaps and they make a little slap joke.
Yeah, it's just it's almost more important than the story in the latest bad boys is you start to realize that there.
It's a PR piece for Will Smith.
He's the bad ass in every scene and you're like, that's not what bad boys was about bad boys was fun because these guys aren't bad asses, you know.
Yeah, I heard to I don't know.
I mean, I'm sure some of it's true, but.
I heard there's footage of like Will Smith having to.
Like off screen footage, having to like help Martin Lawrence like walk a little bit and stuff and that Martin was in rough shape and like they had to kind of shoot around that.
Yeah, maybe.
I don't know.
Arcadian, you know, hog is.
I don't know it's creeping out. It's not up. It's not down. It's just kind of.
Yeah, my hog is.
It's down, but it's like after a 90 second piss.
Where I've just been pissing so long it's about as full as it can be without starting to plump, but it's not plump.
We'll be back in August with long legs.
Probably Maxine because that's hitting the streamers in August.
Yeah, and the fall guy, which is short soon to come to peacock.
Yeah, we'll do it all.
Until next time folks, we'll we'll see you next time.
And we'll see you and how.