Howdy folks, welcome to We'll See You in Hell. It's a podcast where we discuss movies.
Patty Walsh and myself do just that. Today, I have the COVID booster fallout.
What do you call this? The effects of the COVID booster.
Yeah. The, you know, the fog, the brain fog, the sluggishness, and you're bringing
that to, uh, to a form of audible entertainment, bringing that energy.
Got myself, uh, very tired. 7 .30 AM. I think this is the earliest we've ever done the
podcast. Absolutely. 10 .30 for you. I think the previous earliest we've ever done is,
uh, about 2 PM. Yeah. But, uh, I'm leaving today for a 10, 11, 12 week assignment. I
have no idea when I'll be back. If I'm allowed to come back or if I have to stay the whole
time, uh, I will know nobody there. And, uh, I got an email this morning that there's a
big COVID outbreak on, on the set I'm heading to. So, um, I'm very pumped about this new
career opportunity for me. And, uh, that's where we're at. I, uh, I feel for you. I will
try to visit you where you are. Thank you. The show will continue. We'll still record
Oh, yeah. Um, I'm sure there's going to be all kinds of new. I don't, you know, you, you die
hard. You'll, you'll remember the days of, uh, cool kids and, uh, some of the angst that brought
to the show from Pat's side of the table. I'm curious to see if this new program will do
anything similar. I hope not because that would mean it's tough. Hopefully it's a fun time.
It actually can't. I'm not in charge. So like that, that right there removes for me,
75 % of the, uh, spiral, the stress, the misery, the pain that Joe, is this your first booster
and what, what possessed you to get it now? Well, there is only one booster, right? I mean,
yeah, I guess I think you only get two. If you're like severely immunocompromised or something.
I'm sure somebody's out there bragging about how they got more than one booster.
I know people that got two of the vaccines. It's insane. Yeah, that is insane. Like you don't know
what the that's going to do to you. Two doses. Like, well, to do two doses of two. Yeah. Two
different, I don't know. Um, by the way, I just put my hands under my armpits, Mary Catherine
Gallagher style. Yes. And, uh, I just realized that the sweatshirt, which I wear out all the time
has a softball sized hole in the armpit. Well, giant hole. As a Seinfeld once said,
do you know the message that sweatpants give to the world? It's a sweatshirt.
I feel similar about the sweatshirt though, that unless it's like, unless it's like a sort of hip
copy, like, you know, like stylized, whatever, I feel like it's the same thing as those pants.
It's just, you know, everybody, I don't give a shit rolled out of bed, which God bless. I'm not,
I've gone outside of my pajama pants several times this winter so far. Oh, in this, in this
new COVID world, I'll go out flip flops, you know, free bowling and a pair of gym shorts with a
outline of my dog out and about, and then a half unbuttoned dress shirt.
And I was at the grocery store, like, here I am. I got a mask on, you know, say something to me.
I saw a guy and you know, I'm not mocking the unhoused folks. They're going through a,
they're always going through a rough time, but this is obviously a real rough time. But this
homeless unhoused individual comes into a grocery store I'm at the other night,
holding pants up, very tight briefs, but the briefs were fully out. Like you could see not
only the briefs, but the leg skin beneath the brief, like the upper thigh, that's how far the
pants were now. He was trying to hold them up. And then he picked up a basket to start shopping
around the store. I don't know how much money he had, but I mean, like something out of a looney
tunes. He grabs the basket, let's go with the pants. They fall to the floor. Slide whistle noise.
So he puts the basket back there and that it just keeps going on and on. There's people kind of
crowding around to watch sadly. And then I learned that this guy had been in and out of the store all
night, but he goes over to the liquor department, lets the pants fall. And then while he's looking
through the beers, just absentmindedly starts, he's got hand fully down dick part of the pain
of the underpants. And he's just rubbing that dick hand down the pants, pulling the underwear down so
you can see the top half of the dick and the pubes. And it's just scratching himself like a
dad eating Thanksgiving leftovers on that Friday after in the morning in a pair of briefs.
And this was the store manager, folks.
That's how, that's how bad things have gotten. No, it was wild. And I feel like every time I
leave my house now, I'm not seeing any of the screaming, the, you know, I'm sure people are
frustrated and pissed off, but what I'm seeing now is vacant -eyed zombies strolling through public,
wearing worse outfits, less clothes, zombie times. We're in the walking dead.
I wonder if, if, I wonder if it's a harder time for homeless or if it's, or if they're,
or if they actually see this as a leveling thing, you know, like,
Oh, okay. Interesting. You know, I am curious what the perspective would be.
Not really questioning. You just ask a guy. It's probably insulting to ask, but you know,
know that the guy masturbating in the liquor aisle has a viewpoint on it, but
maybe I should have asked him. He could. I like to now with these new terms, one of you,
one of you just used on house is go back and read dub, uh, classic movie scenes with the new
terms to see if they still play. So I did pulp fiction last night and, uh, had John Travolta
saying, and that would add an address of residents. That's what you're going to be a
fucking unhoused, unhoused individual. Didn't hit quite as hard, but it worked. Yeah. Yeah. Uh,
how about, uh, big Lebowski, uh, the unhoused lost, sir. What I don't want to house Mr. Lebowski.
I don't remember. I don't remember that. When does he say that? Is that when he's
meets the big Lebowski for the first time? Yeah. Yeah. Are you, are you a bum, sir?
Oh, that's right. Yeah. Yeah. That's right. Yeah. The bums lost Lebowski.
Is this, is this how you dress? Uh, on a, what is it? This is how you dress on a, on a, on a,
on a weekday. Oh, is it? Oh yeah. Yeah. That's right. On a weekday weekday. Exactly. What my
Oh, is that you're telling me it's a, it's a Monday. Okay. He goes the brilliance of Jeff
Bridges and probably it's in the script too, with the Cullen brothers. He goes to answer it before
he asked the question. He goes, is this how you dress on a weekday? And he goes, is this a week?
He gives the faintest yes, like, and then realizes he might actually be in the wrong.
Yeah. I love the casual way that he's a smart ass. It's a, it's, it's just one of the great
characters. We'll get to the Cohen's latest in a bit. I watched Macbeth or the, excuse me,
the Cohen, one of the most sad title cards I've ever seen. No Ethan involved anymore.
Is everybody splitting up Wachowski's? Yeah. Cohen's the sister, sister girls.
They parted ways. Uh, you know, what's, what's going on here? Why are the Cohen's not working
together anymore? The lesbian twin sister porn stars that I follow are now, uh, I don't even
remember the last time I saw them go down on each other. You girls used to stand for something.
You used to lay down for something. Now are the Cohen's split or this is just,
he's just doing a solo thing for another split. Uh, Ethan is like, yeah, I don't want to do
movies anymore. And I don't know if he just wants to chill at home or if he wants to focus
on plays or books or what, but he's, he's out. And then, I mean, I watched this Macbeth, which is
the worst movie they've ever made. So it's kind of like, well, I hope you guys get back together.
I have the screener. It looks, the trailer, it looks awesome. Uh, I just haven't watched it yet.
Um, because you know, Shakespeare is sort of a heavy undertaking, but, uh, I'm sad to hear
I mean, it looks like, you know, uh, one of these cool, like a 24 black and white lighthouse,
horror type deals, which is what it is essentially. But at the end of the day,
you're just watching people do Shakespeare. Never been a fan, never been a fan. And quite
frankly, never believed any actor I ever knew that like prized and cherished Hamlet and said,
you know, the day I get to do Hamlet, I was, I was like, Oh, fuck you. You're just supposed to
say that it's all actors because they, in school, they're taught like, this is the finest text and,
and you can't be a real actor unless you've done Hamlet or whatever. But, uh, the truth is it's all,
it's, it's what actors love. It's, it's being able to talk for several pages without anyone
interrupting you. And everyone performs Shakespeare in the same way.
That's the only way to tell if somebody is a good actor. Yeah. Let me tell you,
if you're an old British guy with a beard, you're going to be great at it.
If you're Francis McDormand, you're going to suck at it. You're not,
you're not a good Shakespearean actress because you're too modern.
Which, uh, by the way, I got so many thoughts running through my head.
Do you think anything with the Cohen breakup has to do with Francis McDormand? Do you think
his brother was like, look, buddy, we can't put her in the movies anymore, man. She's a drag.
And he was like, that's my wife. If I was Ethan Cohen, I would say
we have, we have access to every actor who has ever, like anyone in the world,
we can get in our movies. Everyone's first answer. I want to work with the Cohen brothers
and they put her in everything. And she's like, she's, she's crazy miscast in this McBeth movie.
She's wrong. She, she, she's more miscast than Denzel, you know, and, and Denzel,
you know, I guess Othello is the black, uh, Shakespeare character. I don't,
I didn't mind McBeth in it at all. I mean, uh, uh, Denzel in this role at all.
And I thought he was awesome in it, but it's just kind of like.
You mean he's miscast because it's because of the time period and it makes, it doesn't make sense.
Well, yeah. And he's, he's cousins to a lot of white people.
I got you. It doesn't bother me. I mean, everybody's talking. I just mean,
technically he's miscast. And then when you have McDormand, who looks like
a modern, she looks exactly like my therapist, to be honest with you, but, um, yeah,
she's just wrong for it. I bet. I thought you were going to say, did McDormand, uh,
like after a tense Thanksgiving, be like, we're not making movies with your brother anymore.
That direction too. I mean, I, I, it's funny. The thing that sealed the deal for me with
McDormand was, and I was, I, you know, I still think she's a great actor, but just that made
me be like, Oh God was when I watched that behind the scenes about dark man thing where she kept
Sam Raimi was saying how she referred to her character in that movie as a bimbo. And I'm like,
and she goes, it's the only bimbo I've ever played. It's like, what about, uh, uh, uh,
after reading, like what, like, and that character wasn't a bimbo. And then the, but the
burn after reading character was way more of a bit. I just was like, this lady just seems like,
you know, like she seems like the kind of person if you said to her, like,
you know, Ms. McDormand, like she would go, um, it's Mrs. Thank you very much. No big deal.
It's just, I prefer, you know, and you're like, Oh Christ. And then if you said Mrs. She'd tell
me it's miss and so on. So whatever. Yeah. But, uh, yeah, she was also, I watched in one night,
uh, the French dispatch with her and Shamale fucking, and then I started Macbeth and I was
like, I'm not doing to McDormand's tonight. I'm not doing it. I don't know what it is because I
used to love her, but she's, she's too heightened. Like she, she, she plays normal roles as if it's
a Cohen character and that doesn't work for me. Well, she's also, I also had an issue and this is
stuff we've said before. I get a real issue when somebody like her starts lecturing everybody else
on the need for diversity on in Hollywood. And you know, she up until that point had never been in a
diverse movie cast ever. And it's like, I, I realized when she was talking to Denzel,
it's the first time I've ever seen her talk to a black person ever in a film.
Honestly, yeah, no, I don't doubt it was, uh, was Denzel, uh, he, I love Denzel, but was he able to
drop his contemporariness for something like this? Cause I, I thought that, um, um, I forget what
movie it was, but we were, my friend and I would, would talk about how good the, the, the, how good
the acting was, but, but Jack Lemmon was in it. And we were like, Jack Lemmon was miscast for
Shakespeare. Like it doesn't work. Oh, even though Jack Lemmon's awesome, you know, like,
yeah. But I thought that when I saw Denzel, I was like, is he able to be, or, um,
it'll not to be, uh, eating popcorn. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Shaking a box of junior
men's kind of thing where you keep shaking it while you're eating it. So, uh, I don't know
whether it's, it's better to this, the slings of the arrows or you, you tell me.
Yeah. Yeah. Is Denzel able to break out of the,
cause he's a pretty contemporary guy. He is. Denzel is a perfect example of like an actor. All those
actors around 60, 60 plus came up having to learn all the Shakespeare. I don't think your boy, uh,
Jacobi Lordi is doing that. I don't think your boy Ansel Elgort is doing that, but
he seems like a guy who would know Shakespeare backwards and forwards, but not talk about it
and not be annoying about it. But when the Cohen brothers called him up and said, you want to play
Macbeth, I have a feeling he knew a lot of those key speeches because he's such a train, classically
trained actor and he's played, uh, Shakespeare shit on Broadway too, but he's great in it.
I mean, he makes the monologue super compelling. I read a really funny, he's like the Collins don't
talk too much, but, um, he said day one on set, he goes up to Joel Cohen and he goes,
so let's talk about the black and white of it all. Let's talk about the black and white of it all.
And he said, Joel Cohen stared at him for a minute and then he goes, well, Denzel, um, you're black
there's no shooting in black and white. And he was like, Oh, thank God.
Okay. He was like, I thought you wanted to talk about race. Jesus Christ. But, um, it's,
if Denzel found it funny, I'm sure it was a very funny story, but, um,
Denzel doesn't seem like a big laugher. He's great. I mean, I'll, I'll remove one of my, uh,
my movie corners. I mean, Macbeth is a, it's like, it's like going to see a great presentation of
at the end of the day, you still don't love it. It just kind of like, I mean, he shot the shit out
of it. The person who steals it is the lady who plays the three witches. She plays all three.
She's some sort of contortionist and she's like, her limbs are all like bone basically.
Yeah, that sounds cool. But she plays the witches and she's cool. It's short, which I wasn't
expecting. It's like a tight a hundred minutes or so. But, uh, yeah, if you don't like Shakespeare,
you're not going to dig it. Speaking of, and then I'll do a movie corner, but I had this quick,
scary stuff. Yeah. The Shakespeare, uh, I, I bought, I urge horror fans to do this.
Go get yourself the box set of tales from the crypt. If you have not gotten it yet, um,
it is woefully out of print at this point. And if you're trying to get the original cardboard
sleeve seasons, which are the original ones I had, they're very overpriced at this point.
Um, but there's, I believe an imported version of it, um, that you can find on eBay. Usually
that's plastic sleeves for the seasons. And it's in a housing box that's black with green
or yellow writing. Uh, and even that now is starting to go up in price. Uh, I would grab
box set that I got for 50 during the pandemic is now a hundred. Yeah. I was going to say it's
going to be passed a hundred soon. I managed to find one for like 60, I think. Yeah. Um,
but there's like, it's so out of print at this point that there are, and be careful about this.
There are several scammers on eBay. It's one of those things that like fake eBay,
people sell for fake on eBay. So whatever you do, if you buy it, do not buy it from somebody
where you can see, they took a picture of it, like in their store or in their house
or whatever. Do not buy anything that has pristine stock photos of the box set. That's fake.
And I actually got burned with that. Um, but anyway, I got, I finally got my hands on this
and I had to rebuy the set because my original discs, some of them just wouldn't play anymore
in modern players. So I got this set and they all play fine. There's one issue with it. It's
entirely mislabeled, which is really annoying. So like the season two discs are actually like
season three and the season three discs are actually like season five. So once you figure
that out and put the discs in their respective cases, you're in fine shape, but that's kind of
a pain in the ass. But anyway, so that's the scary stuff. Uh, I urge you to go get it. It's a great
show. It's such a fun show to watch, but I only watched, I think the first three seasons, like
a lot to go. Um, one of my favorite episodes is the Shakespeare episode with John love. It's
called that one. Yes. I don't know. It's called final curtain or whatever the fuck. Yeah. Goofy
tales from the crypt name it has, but that's a great one where he's going to go do. He's the
actor that can't wait to do Hamlet. Right. And John Aston is playing the insane director.
Yeah. I know that one. I love John Aston. He's awesome. Father of Sean Aston, right?
Father of Sean. Like the two look nothing alike to me for some reason. Well, that'll bring me to
my first movie corner. A John Aston project actually, or something he's in. Okay. It's not
a project, but he's in it. Uh, I, uh, John Aston vehicle. Yeah. I am DB, which is a great streaming
service that you can access for free if you have Amazon prime. And I think you can access it for
free anyway, but, uh, there's a lot of good stuff on there. It has commercials, but it's all free.
And who cares? You sit through a few commercials. I sometimes like it on to be, it gives you it.
What it helps me do is set my phone down when the movie's on and pick it up when the commercials are
on. And it, it's especially good. Like I was watching a little of that Jackson's mini series
and you want that with the commercials, you know, it takes you back. I agree. It makes you feel like
you're part of a society again. A little, yes. It's not enough, but it reminds me of what it was
like when society existed. But I watched, uh, they, they finally, and I, I'm assuming it's
because of this paramount reboot sequel series they're doing, but they finally, the entire
series of night court has been released on streaming. Yeah. It's like an 11 season show
or a nine season show or something. The cost of each season has never dropped on DVD. It's
never been offered in a full box set. It's, it's never streaming. They find it's finally out.
I would have bought it long ago, but I mean, it was like, it was pricey buying all the seasons
separately. So I didn't do it anyway. Um, it's been streaming, I've been watching it and what a joy,
what a joy. I mean, I can't think of the last time I saw a sitcom
that had characters this distinct and carved out that went this hard for the jokes.
Yeah. You know what I mean? It's like curious to see it again. I loved it when I was a kid
and I would put it along with like a news radio where it was like weirder, darker, edgier than
most network fare, but they also got the job done of just being a well -read and likeable funny sitcom
to news. Radio's a good example. Good parallel. Um, I was never a big bang theory guy, but like
a big bag theory, if it was like a little, if it was edgier and a little sharper and that's not
shitting on big bang theory. I never saw the show, but, uh, you know, but definitely along the lines
of news radio. And I mean, it's just so look, you could never ever do the show. Now I can't even
believe they're streaming it, to be honest, because it is wholly inappropriate by today's
standards. Well, the reboot is, is NBC. I think it's old fashioned NBC and then I guess it'll be
on Peacock too. Yeah, I think so. And the reboot centers around Harry Stone played by Harry
Anderson. His daughter is now the judge taking over his mantle, I guess at the, at the night court.
It's very sad. They're all dead except for John Larroquette, Richard Mull and Marsha Warfield.
John Larroquette, I believe will be a regular on the new series. I don't know how. I mean,
it is wild. Some of the shit they have him doing in the original show. Like it's like, it's beyond
like they'll just retcon it and apologize for him and say that he's a better man. Now it's like the
second anybody goes back and watches these old episodes, they're going to be like, Jesus Christ,
man. Like, like him being handsy and gropey is like a running gag in writing. Like it's crazy.
They have the women enjoying it or slapping him or both.
Some of them enjoy it. Some of them are just think he's a pig. Yeah. I mean,
he won Emmys for that part. Yeah. As the show goes, it centers more on him as it goes along.
Yeah. I mean, I remember the whole cast. You know, I used to love
Marsha Warfield. I used to love Richard Mall. I used to love all of them, the whole bunch.
However, Mac was great. I don't remember any of the plots of the show at all. I don't remember
any. I don't remember how they were structured. I don't remember what the sets look like outside
the courtroom. So I need to revisit. I'll give you a thing they did and one I saw recently,
it starts out a much more serious show. It's still a sitcom, but most shows. Yeah. The early
seasons that you can tell that practice of a network show, having to show a lesson every
episode is full effect. And you can see the minute that goes out the window. But
there was an episode where Dan gets a bomb handcuffed to him by a kid he used to pick
on when he was in high school. Okay. And the subplot of that episode is Bull is dating
Elaine Boozler. Okay. Plays a blind woman. All right. And she's mad at Bull because Bull treats
her like she's handicapped. Right. And he's too protective of her. And she's like, I have needs.
I want to be naked on your table. So anyway, the end of the episode, Dan finally gets the
briefcase off his wrist. It's in the courtroom. Bull doesn't realize it's in there, stumbles in
there with his girlfriend. They make up. They're like, let's have a smooch. They kiss. The bomb
goes off. Cut to everybody running in to see if he's okay. And it's like Looney Tunes, as you said
earlier, it's like the whole court room's demolished. They have soot on their face. Yeah.
And they they unlock lips and Bull's like, wow, mama.
You know what it was?
Does he do the thing where his eyes go ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding,
down, down. Blinks off the ash and the soot.
Like doesn't even realize a bomb went off. Like it's, it's, it's absurd. Like, and then that's
followed by an episode where like Marsha Warfield has to lecture a young Don Cheadle because he's
turned to a life of crime. Like if they'll, but they'll back those right up against one another.
Yeah. I kind of miss that, to be honest with you. I mean, it's, it gives you whiplash, but it makes
the show more fun to watch. I mean, people forget that by the fourth season of news radio, they were
doing whole episodes on the Titanic. I don't know if you remember that, but like they had Steven
Rood as the captain of the ship. And I mean, insane stuff they did in space. Yeah. Yeah. Wild. So
anyway, if, if, if you're not, if you're not going to be too set off by NPC humor, yeah, I suggest
checking out night court again. It's the cast. The core cast is, is, is really wonderful. John Aston
is on it. He plays a crazy person who's Harry's like stepdad. I remember him on it. He's a recurring.
Yeah. You know, but it's a wild, it's a wild show. I'm going to do one and then sprint to the bathroom
while you take over Joe for a number one, but it's becoming urgent. I rewatched and the first time
for the Mrs. Little picture called taxi driver. If you want to talk about non -PC Marty Scorsese's
taxi driver, part of, you know, when you look back at this kind of an unofficial trilogy of
just like broken, lonely men, De Niro Scorsese teaming up, you got taxi driver raging bull,
king of comedy. King of comedy is of course the lightest and funniest, although it's an extremely
dark movie, very underrated movie that people just now are learning to love. And then raging bull is,
is a miserable slog, but a wonderful, beautiful movie taxi driver might be the best of the bunch.
It's like, I mean, it's so good. Licorice pizza really did steal this, the subplot about the,
it even looks like the same office where Albert Brooks and Cybill Shepherd work.
They do the same kind of thing in licorice pizza. There's a guy trying to kill a political candidate,
but yeah, it's an amazing movie. My favorite scene in the movie. And I remember reading Ebert's
when I was a kid and it was one of the first times it made me look at a movie in a different
way, aside from just sitting down and being entertained is Ebert talked at length about
the scene where after De Niro takes Cybill Shepherd to the porno movie on their first date,
he's calling her and like, I don't understand, like, why are you breaking up with me? I don't
get it. And the camera pans off down a hallway. So they pan away from De Niro and down this long,
empty hallway. And then when I was a kid, I was like, what the fuck was that? And then Ebert talked
about how like it's the viewer and Scorsese can't even bear to watch De Niro do this. It's so hard
to watch. And this is how lonely and pathetic he is. And Scorsese does so much amazing shit in this.
It feels very current. It feels like the way it was shot and edited is all kind of like inventing
new stuff. The gore is really intense. They pass a theater, a marquee for Texas Chainsaw Massacre,
which I'm sure Scorsese intended. I was just reading a bunch about Scorsese's love for John
Carpenter and the thing in particular, which I would look up. It's making the rounds on Twitter.
But you sort of feel the Texas Chainsaw influence on Taxi Driver. Like the home stretch is really
gory. It's an amazing movie. To me, it felt like it could have been made today.
Jodie Foster, that whole subplot is super unsettling. Keitel is awesome in it and creepy.
It's a great portrait of loneliness. One of the best. I told Joe, you never want to be watching
Taxi Driver and keep saying, yes, yes, I agree. Yes. But that's what I was doing. Reminded me of
early days in New York where I would just do push -ups and not eat and get weird and go on
horrible dates. I never tried to assassinate anybody. I also never rescued a child prostitute
from her pimp. But had I stayed in New York, it might have gone that way. Obviously, if you've
never seen Taxi Driver, check it out. My wife hated. Absolutely. I'm not a fan. No. Damn. I
find it too. It's too dreary for me. I don't know what to cling to in the movie.
I just don't enjoy it. It's not eventful enough for me to want to spend that amount of time with
that character. Falling down is dreary, but at least he's doing crazy shit through the whole
movie. You're like, this is wild. Taxi Driver, I literally feel like I'm just hanging out with
that guy for two hours. I'm like, dude. Sure. When he's hanging out with his friends,
Peter Boyle, and then when he takes Scorsese to go camp out outside his mistress's house,
that is it. The fact that Scorsese played that part is insane that the director's like, I'll
play the racist misogynist character. But I don't know. The movie, it just makes you feel scummy
and gross. To me, it reminds me so much of living in New York in the early 2000s. That was when it
cleaned up. But for me, I just really relate to it. It is crazy that it's such a beloved classic,
though, because of what you're saying. I mean, Heather was really repelled by the movie. She
really didn't like it. And it's not an easy - It's like that movie, Narc. The whole thing
is so goddamn depressing. I'm just like, oh, Jesus. I don't know. Anyway, depressing. Great
film. It's still a gasp when they whip up and he's in that mohawk, even though it's like the
poster for the movie. When Scorsese does that low shot and then the camera goes to give you the
shock of his mohawk, it's a gasp every time. Great movie. Speaking of on PC, MacGruber has
dropped the TV series. I'm not finished it yet. I'm about halfway through. What a wonderful show.
What a wonderful treat. You're going to sprint to that bathroom? Yeah. What a wonderful show.
What a wonderful treat. Especially in this day and age of tame, tame comedy, clean comedy,
comedy, a lot of the time that doesn't have any punchline to it.
And look, MacGruber is far from highbrow comedy, but it's well -crafted comedy.
So maybe that is highbrow. I don't know. I don't know what highbrow means anymore, but
it's just a funny fucking show. It's crass when it wants to be crass. It's not when it doesn't
need to be. He's awesome. Will Forte is just so funny, man. He's just such a good actor.
Kristen Wiig is so funny. She's so great. Everybody kind of knows this, obviously,
but there are actually two actors that I feel we don't see in as much. I mean, they're in stuff,
obviously, but you don't see them as much as you see some other. It's not like, if you remember
the time when every other movie that came out during the year that was a comedy was Ben Stiller,
or whatever. They're not like that. They're not out there. I feel at least that they're not
over -saturated. They're not overexposed. They are placed into often, or they choose often the right
projects, and they seem to do the stuff that counts to them. And this one obviously does.
They're very, very committed to it. And it's just a hilarious show. I've been hard -pressed
to think. I was talking about Night Court, which I'm enjoying. I'm not cackling when
I'm watching it. There are laugh -out -loud moments, but this, I'm laughing like you're cackling
watching it. And that's rare, I think, these days with a comedy, especially since so many comedies
now are like dramedies, and almost depressing reflections of real life. And it's just fun to
see something like this again, where it's an outrageous character. It's an outrageous reality
that character is living in, and he's surrounded by outrageous circumstances and other outrageous
characters. It's also awesome to see Billy Zane in the villain role in this, and in a comedic
role, because Billy Zane, I always thought was really funny ever since I saw Demon Night.
And he rarely does comedies, but he's funny, and he's great. Ryan Felipe also. Great to see
Ryan Felipe back. He's very funny in the group. Yeah, very funny in this. So it's a great show.
Crass is all hell, but watch it. It's a joy.
I love that my two favorite moments are when MacGruber is running away from the gas station
and yells back at that woman. Yeah, fuck you. Fuck you. I rewind that over and over and over.
Tears in my face laughing. It had been a long time since I laughed like that.
And then the other is Wig's first song when he goes to see her in that nightclub,
and she's singing that song for like five minutes. I was like, this is naked gun level gold here.
That song is insane. I don't understand how she remembered that. I'm looking and I'm like,
she's got to be reading this. She has to be. This is so crazy.
Wig is genuinely funny. She is a weird, super funny lady, and I hope she does not turn her back
on comedy. Well, that's what I was saying while you were gone. I think the good thing about Forte
and Wig are they're obviously people that work, but they're not overexposed. They seem to pick
the projects they want to do. It's not like when Ben Stiller was in every movie every year,
every month or whatever. The fact that Wig is as big as she is and is still doing a show like this
says a lot, you know? Forte, it's a little more his baby, right? But still, it's just, you know.
They both have a true appreciation for very strange, not necessarily commercial comedy,
and they keep making them, which you can't say the same for like Feral or a lot of these people.
Barb and Star is a really weird movie. Not even an entirely successfully weird movie,
but it's got huge funny laughs in it. I like what they do.
I'm ready to move to the movie if you are. I don't know if you are, if you have anything
else you want to talk about. I mean, sure. I'll pop my third in here is The Humans.
Another A24. They're putting out about 25 movies a month now,
but The Humans has a very intriguing cast. Richard Jenkins, who I always love,
Steven Yeun, Beanie Feldstein, Jonah Hill's sister, June Squibb, star of Living Biblically,
along with Joe DeRosa, and Amy Schumer, comedian. All of the performances are great.
They really are. It's a strong cast. This was a play first, and you definitely feel that,
it's about a family getting together for Thanksgiving. Dark secrets are revealed,
of course, but it's also shot and edited like a horror movie, particularly an A24 horror movie.
At first, it's like, oh, I get it. They're making it seem like Thanksgiving with the
family is horror. That is sort of the gimmick of the movie, but I don't know. There's something a
deeper, a little more interesting with it going on. It's one of those where everybody who saw it
would have a different take on what happens at the end of the movie. Is this real? Is this not?
Is this just a simple family gathering, and the music makes it seem like I'm watching something
more intense than it is? But it's well done. It feels kind of like a one act play. It feels
a little stagey, but the performances make it click. They make it sing. The movie is stolen
by Jane Howdy Shell, who I recognize, but I don't really know where from.
But it's worth checking out. It's on Showtime. It's the only place I've seen it. It's called
The Humans. Solid, solid. Beautiful. And are we talking? What are we talking, Joe? Well,
I think it makes sense to talk scream since we're talking about throwbacks and
non PC and all that sort of thing. I think this connects and that we're talking about A24
scream, a movie that takes scream five, the newest scream,
recall, reboot, sequel, whatever the hell you're talking about, whatever you want to call it.
They call it a recall on it. That's a term I'd never even heard before.
I mean, either very meta franchise, obviously. And this one is the most meta of all the screams.
We'll get into that. But a movie also that takes a direct shot over the bow at A24 right out of the
gate when the initial call comes in in the cold open of what's your favorite scary movie? The
teenager goes, Babadook. It's a meditation on loss or whatever. And the killer is like, basically
those movies suck. Yeah. Yeah. And then rattles off three others with it follows. Yeah. Hereditary.
So it's clearly a shot, in my opinion, right at age at the A24 style of horror. And they're
letting you know right off the bat. No, we're doing an old school horror movie here. Yeah.
Well, and it works because it's the it's the thing of course, and I'm not spoiling anything
here. It's the kind of thing where the killer, of course, knows and is obsessed with the scream
franchise that and that's made clear right off the bat. But in the universe, those movies are
called stab. Yeah, right. Yeah. And that we've seen clips of those and the other scream movies
and et cetera. So when these characters look like IMDB stab, you're seeing the cast of the movie
stab, which was a recreation of the movie scream. It's all very clever. Don't get me wrong.
But the care that character, whoever's doing the killing would, of course, hate A24 movies,
because it's somebody who's obsessed with slasher movies. That's a very clever turn, I think, as
well. Yes, this movie, I saw it the other day. And I texted Pat afterwards and said, it's almost
like they're doing a meta commentary on what a meta commentary is. I mean, this is your your
several layers deep at this point. Yeah, it's kind of like when curb did the Seinfeld reunion,
it's like when then you're seeing Seinfeld scenes inside the Seinfeld reunion inside
the curb episode. It's like, it's that kind of thing. Usually watching scream at one point,
saying like, turn around, he's right behind you. So it's they're watching the scene where Jamie
Kennedy is saying turn around, he's right behind you. The girl who's watching scream is saying
turn around right behind you. And there's somebody right behind her that is causing the live audience
to say turn around. Yeah, yeah. A lot of clever moments like that. It's a wild Russian doll kind
of thing. Kind of a back to the future to vibe where it's like they're almost watching the events
of the first movie while you're in this movie. Now, as you know, I've criticized this approach
on the show many times. We both have. In this case, I thought it worked tremendously.
I went into scream because it's scream. This is the thing that's supposed to be doing this.
Yeah, so it is the scream franchise's claim to fame. So it's hard to get too annoyed
when it goes completely meta from the opening seconds. But I was in I was in from the beginning
when that first attack happens with ghost face on the young girl.
Jenna Ortega, who is awesome. I've never seen her in anything. She's fantastic.
She's so good. She really stole the show. She when he when he goes after at her,
when he finally gets her and he's stabbing her, it's disturbing. No, I'm not saying I was in
because I enjoyed seeing a disturbing stab scene. But up until that moment, I was sitting there
going, they're going to hold back on this so much. There is no way it's going to be anywhere near
as brutal as the first one. And then that scene happened. I was like, holy shit, they're going
for this. And they continued to go for through the entire movie. And I got to say, this is a movie,
an installment in a franchise I do not have a great love for. I'm not a huge scream fan.
I loved this movie. I thought it was awesome. It kept me guessing the entire time.
Even in the very last moments before the reveal of the killer, I still wasn't sure who it was.
There was a massive, bloody, gory kill about every seven minutes to keep you to keep you hooked.
Clock kept twisting and turning. I for some reason lit up when David Arquette came on screen.
I was very happy to see him. I don't know why I've never been a huge David Arquette fan, but I was
very happy to see him. They give him a full hero's return in a way. They don't really do
for the other. They don't really do for Cox or Campbell. Everybody gets great moments to shine,
but they really treat our cat like he's like, uh, you know, the hero of the franchise,
which he kind of is. He's the heart and soul of scream. And then they're doing a commentary
on our cat and Cox because now they're divorced and they were a real couple in real life.
I'm sure our cat loved when he got the script and saw that his character was still hung up
and in love with his ex -wife, but, uh, it, it adds a level of kind of sweetness to the thing.
Cause you feel like Arquette probably does miss his ex -wife and realize he fucked up,
even though I know nothing about the details of that marriage.
No, they broke up because she was having an emotional affair. It was Cox that broke,
which means a dick and pussy affair. Right. Right. But, uh, but, and then even like little,
every time I stopped and said, that's dumb. Five minutes later, I'd be like, oh no,
that wasn't dumb. They're fucking with me. So like the characters, for instance, the, the,
the high school kids, which by the way, classic horror movie where a high school
chick is banging like a 24 year old dude. I was like, I was like, they're throwing it back,
babe, to the old days. But anyway, um, that kid's awesome in it too. The kid from nightmare,
nightmare and Elm street remake. Uh, he's not in a ton of stuff, but I love him. He plays a real
fucking creep in this. Oh, Kyle Gellner. Yeah. Yeah. I like that guy a lot. Um, but anyway,
owner he, uh, but they, they, every time, like one of the younger characters would be like
Jordan fucking peel rule. I was like, oh God, this is so obnoxious to die. And I was like,
no, they're doing that because that's the way those nineties movies people talked.
Yes. It was this unnecessary, annoying use of the word fuck to put emphasis on things.
Yes. It was done by the team, uh, written and directed by the team who did
ready or not, which I thought was a very solid, uh, you never saw ready or not. Did you Joe?
I think you'd like it. Oh, we did it. We did it on the, oh wait, no, I'm sorry.
We did your next. We never did ready or not. Right. Ready or not. I thought it was fun.
Um, but never quite won me over. And I guess that's how I feel about this scream. I wish
I could meet you at your level of enthusiasm. It was also co -written by James Vanderbilt, who
wrote Zodiac, which is one of the great movies ever. Um, and he also wrote murder mystery
starring Jen Aniston and Adam Sandler. It's a crazy career the man's had, but, um, I like
the original scream. I think is a classic scream. Two is a fun SQL scream. Three sucks
scream for, I was like, you waited too long and I guess I enjoyed it, but I don't remember a
single thing about scream for, except there's a showdown and a barn at the end of it. It
just seemed like they did it because it was cheap. Uh, this new scream, I would say.
I'd probably rank it third after scream one and scream two. It's good, but everything you're
saying is correct. The story, uh, you know, they keep the twists coming relentlessly,
almost to a comical degree. And I think that's intended. I didn't know who the killers were
going to be. That's kind of fun. The script is tight. It is written well, but I can't really
ward a full blood engorged hog up. If I'm watching a horror comedy where I am never scared
and I never laugh. And to me that nothing actually funny happened in it. It was a lot of kind of
whippy references and stuff. And I get that that's what scream is, but scream had laughs too.
And scream was scary to the Drew Barrymore scene and et cetera. Scream was actually genuinely
scary in parts. This I found myself just kind of, it was a fun exercise to me, but didn't
necessarily work as a movie. I did clearly admired what they did. I would see another film in the
franchise, but I didn't love it. I just didn't love it. I did find myself tense and nervous
at times. There was that one sequence where they did it so well, where the kids going through the
kitchen, getting the sushi plates set up and they do like five of the like door open. He's been
right behind it. He closes it. You're waiting for the scare. Yeah. So I was, I did get tense
in certain areas. I absolutely cackled a few times in the theater allowed watching watching it.
And then also too, I love that when I love that they successfully did a sequel to the first one
without this missing the other sequels while also recognizing that the other sequels didn't
live up to the first one. Right. Which is not what a lot of these movies do. They just go,
we're going to erase all that and just, it'll be a sequel to the first one, you know, which
was what they did with Halloween. I love that they did that. I thought they executed that perfectly.
I loved that the, I mean, you know, we're talking about, they're, they're just doing the whole high
school kids date and whatever, you know, the goddamn the spoilers, by the way, guys, there's
huge, I'm about to say a few huge spoilers here. So turn it off if you need to see this movie.
The killers at the end ended up being a couple. That kid was like 25. That girl was a high school
kid. Yeah, great. She's on better things, which is a very good show on FX. She plays the oldest
daughter, but I always liked her too. The cast is all great. That's not me saying, that's not me
saying I approve of such a relationship. I just, it just brought me back to old horror where
everything wasn't so precious. Like it just, it just, I don't know. Like I just, I appreciated
that aspect of it or, or even when you do shit like that, that these movies open up more too,
you know, like you, you truly don't know who's doing it. If, if you're in a world like the real
world where a 30 year old guy can date a 17 year old girl, that, that immediately opens up things
because it's outside of the way you're thinking about these people. So it makes it like the
Spider -Man reveal, the great Spider -Man reveal where Zendaya goes home, whichever one that was,
and her dad is Michael Keaton. It's like, oh shit, this, it's just a simple colorblind casting thing
that makes that whole twist work a million percent better because you're expecting Zendaya to have
a black dad. It's just, it's just the nature of the human brain. They do cool shit like that. I
agree with you. It, the script is good. I think, I think also too, it creeps out the characters
more. It makes them more vicious. It makes them more open, open -minded villains in the sense of
that they're willing to do anything depraved and they have no boundaries. It adds a layer of evil
to them. Yeah. I loved that Courtney Cox and Neve Campbell came back with full intent to kill.
There was none, there was no soft shoeing. They were like, no, we have to kill this person.
Yeah. But Cox and Arquette are kind of also in the way that the older Ghostbusters were in it.
They like keep kind of walking in as a team. And I was going to say, I was going to say they added,
they use these characters better than the old Ghostbusters because they weren't, they were
really folded properly into the plot, which I liked. It was kind of like the way the Force Awakens did
their thing. And I was like, in a lot of these newer movie reboot things, it's like the character
comes in for a, for a, you know, how you doing cameo real quick and then leaves. And this wasn't
like that. And they also got into that commentary about the legacy characters versus the original
characters and all that. But we're burying the lead. My favorite thing they did in this thing
was they had a commentary about how the stat in the movie that they talk about how the stab
franchise didn't have a legacy killer. It didn't have a Freddie or a Jason or whatever.
Right. And then the plot of this, the big, one of the first big reveals is that the main character,
whose sister is the first person get attacked, is the daughter of Skeet Ulrich's character from
the first movie, who then is guiding her through the movie. And by the end of the movie,
you're rooting for Skeet Ulrich, the worst person, first movie that he's helping his daughter figure
out how to kill the person trying to kill them. And I was like, this is fucking insane. This is
off the reservation right now. I loved it. Did they use like a Patrick Stewart de -aging on Ulrich
for those ghost scenes? They did. Okay. Cause I was like, this guy should not look this good
after a failed career in Hollywood. He should be nearly dead. He nods in the last scene to her to
show her where the knife is. And then her, her big line is never fuck with the daughter. Rule number
four, never fuck with the daughter of a serial killer brutally murders. Yeah. The girl in the
same style that the first that drew Barrymore's killers happens with like the repeated stabbing
the chest. And then like, and in the last frame of the movie, she like looks into a window and
sees the reflection of her ghost dad. And he nods to her like, like, good, good job.
It's like the end of star wars when they're watching and nodding or whatever.
And they reference force awakens. I mean, they, I feel like actually, as we're talking about it,
I'm finding more to appreciate just in the, in the, in the theater sitting there, I was getting
a little bored. I don't know what it was. A lot of it lately with me is my mood. You know, I fully
admit that, but it's a really well written movie that just never quite, quite took off for me,
but a really good scream sequel and, you know, a sequel that really understands the franchise,
a way better sequel than any of the new Halloween's for sure. Did you, what was my other,
Oh, so like, have you, you haven't even seen any of the scream sequels, have you?
I saw one I saw, I never saw four. I think I, I remember seeing two, cause I remember
Jamie Kennedy comes in in two, doesn't he? Or is he in the first one? I think kind of
blend together for, or he dies in two, right? Yeah. I think I saw two. I never saw three.
By the time I got to three, I was like, well, what are we doing here?
And then he sucked. I mean, they brought Marlee Shelton in this, who looks a lot like Heather
Graham, which is weird because they reference Heather Graham's character as well. But Marlee
Shelton, who plays the police chief lady, like, I don't know that we needed to bring her back. I
mean, if you're a diehard scream fan, you're going to find a lot to love here. They go through and
update you on characters who you truly didn't care about, like from scream three, like they,
they don't do the thing where we're going to forget that movie didn't happen. It's like,
yeah, they, you know, somebody sat down with 800 note cards and mapped out the scream franchise.
And that sort of attention to detail is always appreciated for sure.
And then the other, the other brilliant, the other brilliant piece of writing is the main
character's boyfriend is watching a YouTube review of stab five. Yeah. And it's YouTubers
going, it's just lazy writing. It's lazy writing. They're hammering the point of lazy writing
and how that franchise has gone off the rails. That is almost immediately followed by a sequence
where David Arquette, that guy and the main girl go to save her sister at the hospital,
they know the killer's there. David Arquette shoots the killer twice in the chest and then just
leaves him sitting there. And you're going, why would you do that? Rip the mask off? Like,
why would you do? And he walks all the way to the elevator and they're about to leave. And he goes,
got to go back. You don't shoot him in the head. They always come back. And I'm watching this and
I'm going, it doesn't make sense. This is so lazy. And then I'm like, oh my God, they just did the
thing where they talked about the lazy writing. And now this is how David Arquette's going to die
from lazy writing. And sure enough, that's what happens. And it just, it really fucking blew me
away, man. I really liked this movie. I would buy, I'm now going to purchase this one and scream one
because I feel like they work. It's a nice bookend set to have. I don't think I need the other ones,
but anyway, my hog's way up for scream five. Yeah. My hog is, is straight ahead, but quivering up,
you know, you get those little twitches sometimes when you're, you're kind of horny where it's like
jolts, kegels almost. I really got a deduct for something really bothered me. And I love, as I
said, Jenna Ortega, but when she kills Ghostface at the end and says, I still prefer the Babadook
as the smoke is still emerging from her gun. I was just like, what do you do? If you're going
to make that quip, make it in the scene after when they're putting the code on you in the backseat
of the ambulance, you know, like to me, a 16 year old girl shooting and killing someone and then
making a quip in the same breath, even in the scream world is just ludicrous. But, but that's
what all those movies did. That's what I think she should have said it before she shot. I still
prefer the Babadook. I mean, they all had goofy stuff, but it was always like the theme was like,
fuck you, when they would kill somebody. It wasn't a quip about their movie tastes, but maybe
that's a wink to all of us as well. And it's definitely a fun homage to like the 90s horror.
And in the scenes where all the teenagers are sitting like in the quad talking about stuff,
they were annoying, but it also kind of has that added layer of being annoying in that very specific
way of 90s horror where the teens all talked and like Gilmore girls speak and everything.
So I'd love to see how much of this was intentional and how much of it is just
a good recreation of 90s horror, but those guys are so clever and ready or not was so clever
that I'm willing to give them the benefit of the doubt. It might be one I revisit.
It's worth a watch. Check it out.
All right, folks, that's our show. We'll be back right straight away in the next episode with
deep cover. We'll see you next time. And we'll see you in hell.