I will see you at Hell and that's where we will see you.
because that's where we're all headed.
Welcome back to the Hard Hitting Podcast.
It tells it like it is.
Shoots from the hip, pulls no punches.
What's up?
Hi, Joe, and I'm Pat Walsh.
What does shoot from the hip mean?
You would naturally, I assume it came from gunslinger times.
Yeah.
Where you keep your gun on your hip.
Shooting from your hip does not make you a more, you know, what's the word in gunslinger times it did.
It means I believe I'd have to look it up.
But I believe what it means is like, hey, man, I shoot from the hip.
I do a fair draw.
I'm not like sneaking around with my not doing your backs to me.
And I'm shooting you in the back.
Yeah, yeah.
It's like, hey, I'm showing you where I'm showing my guns are my guns are out.
Yeah.
You ever see the SETV sketch called yellow belly?
It's John Candy as a cowboy in western times named yellow belly.
And his like claim to fame.
You just shoots people in the back.
He shoots women children.
And then like when anyone steps to him at all, he like cowers and like.
That's very funny.
We're doing today on the show folks weird.
Which what comes after the colon a weird al yankovic story or something.
No, weird, weird the al yankovic story.
Okay.
We'll get to it.
It's available on Roku.
I said, well, Joe, I don't know how I'm going to find this.
And he's like go to Roku .com and watch it for free.
I don't know what business model they have over there at Roku, but it's not wise.
My friend Chip was telling me because we were talking about that about this movie.
And he said that he read a big article about like this isn't this is going to be a new.
There's spec speculation that this will be a new trend where it will work like cable.
It's just it won't.
It won't be cable.
Well, this is cable.
I mean, I'm not cable.
I'm sorry to work like network television.
It's just going to be ads pay for the content, you know.
And you can watch a feature film or whatever.
I guess that's what to be does, but they do it with acquisition material.
But this could be the start of something new.
I guess so.
I mean, I always ask my friends who worked on broke curls with me.
Hey, it's great that we get residuals from this airing on standard TV.
But when are we going to get an streaming service?
You get shit residuals, but you still get them.
Yeah.
And it was like, we're not airing anywhere.
My thinking was that obviously times have changed.
And the show is often horrifically racist.
So that's probably why it's not air anywhere.
But last night I get on.
Roku to watch this.
They got on the homepage right next to weird out all six seasons of two broke girls.
So it's like, where are those residuals?
It's like, so I'm glad you sent me to Roku for two reasons, one to watch the movie.
And two, because I'm going to write the writer's guild and hopefully get some money out of it.
That's how it works.
Like, it's hard to fathom, but this is how it works.
I have so many friends who'll be like, yeah, I just found out my show's randomly streaming on, let's say to be.
And then you contact the writer's guild.
And after a few months, they're like, oh, here's a check for for a bunch of money.
It's like you have to.
Like, you know, threaten them pretty much.
Any any show like let's say cheers or any show the last a long time broke girls too.
The showrunners always have to sue for profits.
It's like a requirement.
You you factor that in because these places hide so much money that they just still like it's like the Lord of the Rings guy like new line was like we didn't make any money off Lord of the ring.
Sorry.
So Peter Jackson had to sue them, but it's like, why do we have to sue?
Why can't people just be honest, they can't sucks.
It's a real drag man.
I read I read the other well, I read on Twitter the other day.
That apparently or allegedly the Beatles manager when their first single came out because the other day was the anniversary of that happening.
Yeah, they the manager bought 10 ,000 copies of the single to assure that it would go to number one as part of the strategy.
And I was just like, nothing is fucking pure like nothing.
You know what I mean?
Like nothing.
It's all rigged.
It's all been rigged the whole time.
I hope he kept him 10 ,000 of the Beatles first single.
He could probably make more money than he made off the fucking Beatles at this point.
Yeah, well, he's dead.
Right.
Well, good.
I assume.
Yeah, when there's when there's blood in the water, man, people really come out.
Yeah, it's come up to damn shame.
I'm sitting here.
You people can't see me, but I look like Tom Hanks and Philadelphia right now.
Joe, I was about to say the exact same thing.
You look at your about to sing lip sync to that opera song at the end of Philadelphia.
I have a beanie on.
I have eight o 'clock shadow.
Yeah.
I hit a phase of depression this week, which I've hit before where the I like to call the I don't care that I got stuff on my shirt phase.
Yeah, sure.
Eating, it's spilling.
I'm like, I don't care.
I'll just get another one of these I guess at some point.
I was at the grocery store the other day realized I had what, you know, and maybe it was maybe it wasn't.
But my God did it look like a big come stain on the crotch of my sweatpants that I was walking around the grocery store in.
What was it great tell if it wasn't come.
You know, it was one of those classic.
Is it come or is it toothpaste that guys face whenever you get white crusty stuff on any of your clothes?
I'm going to be real with you 90 % chance it was come.
I've been coming a lot.
And I ain't been brushing my teeth a lot.
I'll tell you that much, folks.
Yeah, you look fine, Joe.
You look good.
I know you haven't been drinking.
I've been what's that called intermittent fasting.
Yeah, I do that too.
I've been drinking very little, you know, here and there, but very little.
Very little for me, you know, at least let's put that one.
Six, seven mixed drinks a night.
I talked to my, so I have my doctor then I have my friend Steve who's also a doctor and I get advice from Steve on top of whatever my regular doctor tells me.
Just a second opinion it.
And I was talking to Steve.
He's got a great pod called weird medicine.
By the way, check out Dr. Steve's weird medicine, but I was talking to him.
And I said, you know, not really supposed to be drinking much.
I can drink sometimes, but I don't know.
I said, that bad if I drink sometimes.
And he was like, well, it depends on how much you drink.
And I would go, you know, I want to have a night.
I want to have a night tonight.
I'm bored.
And he's like, okay, so what's the night?
I go nothing.
Six drinks.
And he goes, well, let's try four.
Yeah.
I don't understand.
It takes, it takes talking to a doctor to learn that your numbers are elevated.
You know, I'm always like, and you also, I usually clean it up for the doctor too.
I'll be like, yeah, you know, four drinks or something that they're always like, no, no, no, way too much, way too much.
I, I, I'll tell you this, I've hit a hellish patch with it because the times I have drank.
Again, handful in the last month and a half, whatever it's been.
It, it, I don't sleep right.
Yeah, I, dude, I tried to have a whiskey last night.
And I was like, it tasted horrible.
When you go away from it, you realize what, what it, it's poison.
I mean, you know that.
But it, it takes going away from it to get that feeling on your lips, your tongue, your throat, your stomach.
It's like, oh, wait, this is just like drinking gas or something.
Yeah.
And I ended up drinking some wine, which at first tasted good.
And then after a while, you're like, I feel like I'm eating like too many gummy bears or something.
Um, yeah, just tasted bad.
And then, and then I don't sleep too.
I, I noticed this just from, from kissing chicks more lately, who are drinking.
But like, your breath are their breath, let's say, after wine is not good.
No, wine breath is terrible.
It gives you the purple teeth and tongue.
Yeah.
I mean, all these women drink wine generally.
And it's like, um, there's a certain, it's just like there's a certain taste and smell to beer that isn't great.
The wine thing is not good.
So then, you know, it's when you kiss, it's not like it, oh, I'm, I'm gagging.
I can still get the job done.
But it's like, I wonder how often I have been talking to somebody and they're like, oh God, this guy's a fucking wineo, you know.
Yeah, red, red wine is a, is a problem with, yeah, with if you're going to be intimate.
It just is, that's, uh, it's in my movie.
In my movie corner today, uh, is Wolf of Wall Street rewatched.
But she, she asks for the straw at one point.
I remember when I was in the theater that got like a laugh.
Yeah.
It's like, it is kind of funny because it's kind of like, you know, I think I got a laugh in the theater because it was like, oh God, like, that's not like, like, that's not classy.
She's in a nice restaurant.
But it's, it's funny because it's like, no, this is a woman that knows how to maintain looking amazing at all times.
And she was like, no, you drink it through a straw.
So it doesn't make her a teeth purple.
You know, I think that was the last time not that there aren't stunningly beautiful women all across the globe.
But I think that was the last time I can remember in the theater.
In an audible theater wide gasp and like guys going like fuck like, you know, like when she first came on just like a Jesus Christ.
Yeah.
That used to happen all the time because they used to be all about the male gaze.
So like, you know, you'd go see.
I remember going to see summer catch with a date which is like an unwatchable movie with Freddie Prince Jr.
Is like a minor league ball player.
It's like shitty bull Durham.
But there's this scene where Jessica Biel gets out of a pool.
And it's just like is a slow motion of her walking for like a minute.
And I would just remember the crowd just be like, I was biting my fists like B. Arthur.
You know, people planning themselves.
You're doing like a night court style gag.
Yeah.
But maybe just because it was the last time it was acceptable or the last time they like actually featured a woman in that way.
But I just remember her when she first enters it was like, holy cow.
She's probably is one of the most beautiful people that has ever lived.
And yet doesn't excite me for some reason.
Like I read I'm not blind.
I recognize the woman is gorgeous.
But yeah, some reason I don't get.
I don't get.
I did when I saw that movie.
But yeah, I don't know what happened.
Something switched.
That happens to me sometimes with an impeccably gorgeous women.
I'm just like.
It's like you want to read or something.
You know, it's like I had a friend who was obsessed with jewel.
And I was like, I couldn't get past the teeth.
And he's like, that's what makes her attainable.
This guy by the way, 350 pound.
I agreed with Joel.
I thought Joel was smoking hot in the teeth.
We're part of it.
Yeah.
But Joel seems like she'd be really annoying.
And always trying to read your poetry about the unhoused.
Whereas Margot Robbie seems super fun and cool.
Hey, Joel.
How about we get into the unbloused already?
She's good.
I think I always think Margot Robbie is.
She's better than her material.
She's great in Wolf of Wall Street.
It's very funny, though, because you watch her in Wolf of Wall Street.
And you're like, oh, she's doing Harley Quinn.
Like, that's her Harley Quinn or her Harley Quinn is where her Wolf of Wall Street.
To say, yeah, voice.
Right.
She's great, though.
She's an excellent.
I will get to the movie.
But she did her best on that Amsterdam dog shit.
Jesus Christ.
You know, I keep trying.
I haven't had time.
But I, there's been one or two moments where I've had a little window.
And I'm like, should I go to the movies?
I want to.
I really want to see this.
The fuck's it called the Hounds of the Baskervilles.
Whatever.
This new Colin Farrell.
Oh, the banshee's of insurance.
I want to see it.
But I'm also like.
I know that doesn't feel like a thing you sit in the theater for.
That feels like you watch it at home.
Well, that, that mentality.
Uh, it's not unusual.
And it's what's destroying the movie business.
It's, it's whatever one has.
I mean, I, I myself am dying to see it.
I love one in bruge is one of my favorites.
It's the same cast, same director.
It's in Ireland, which I, yeah, my people are from.
And I'm in, I'm in the same boat.
I'm like, I'm going to get 10 copies of the screener here in a month.
Let me, let me rephrase.
It doesn't, I don't.
My, with my regal Essex.
It doesn't feel like a movie you sit in the regal Essex.
It's a state of the art theater to watch.
I feel like I need to go to the upper west side.
And, you know, get a cap of chain.
Yeah.
Going to the theater that plays the latest Parker Posey film.
Right.
What do you have on it online behind you?
That's, it's funny that you just said that there's a theater on the upper west side.
I saw all, not all, but like when match.
I saw a lot of Woody Allen movies there when they came out.
And I saw a Parker Posey movie there.
The one with her and Amy Schumer.
Where Parker Posey plays.
The woman who can't find love.
And she dates a rock star at the beginning.
And then ends up moving to Europe.
And I forget what happens.
It's like a romantic comedy.
And I never heard of it.
Parker Posey is the lead.
And Amy Schumer is supporting.
This was when Amy was first.
I'm breaking out.
But I, well, I have to know what this is now.
I went in just because of the, I saw the poster.
It was playing at the, I did was one of the only times in my life.
I did that where I was like, I'm just going to go in.
I'm going to go into whatever's playing.
I'm going to see it.
Price check.
It's called.
Yeah, that's right.
Because she works at a supermarket or something in the beginning.
Okay.
Anyway.
There you go.
There's your.
Yeah.
My, my father sees everything Irish.
And he was very excited about bans.
She's of insurance in a sheeran, whatever.
And he said.
I said, what did you think?
And he was like, I'll tell you when I can piece together what the hell the movie was about.
And you know, for all his faults, he's a very intelligent man.
And never has a problem understanding movies or books or anything.
So I, I haven't heard from a single other person that it's hard to understand though.
So I don't know what he's getting at.
Like he's acting like it's inception or something.
So I'm curious to see what it is.
They show a lot in the trailer.
And I'm like, as I watch the trailer, I'm like, this is not what the movie is.
Like this is not.
This is not a trailer with the hook that he cuts this guy off.
And that's it.
There's going to be a lot more.
It's not.
Yeah.
That trailer is not anything that wants to get you into the theater.
You're like, I don't care why he's not talking to his friend.
It's not interesting.
So there's got to be something.
But I don't know what.
Yeah.
I also want to see decision to leave.
The new Chan Wook Park vehicle because he's made some incredible movies.
Old boy and the handmaiden and all sorts of great flicks.
And I really want to see par the Kate Blanchett movie.
I was almost in the seat the other day.
And I looked it up and it was two hours and 50 minutes.
And I was like, I can't do it.
Can't do it.
Did you walk down?
Did you see sort of a new psycho?
Did you see the clip of John Stewart in conversation with Mo Amir about his netflix?
I think it was a great show.
I guess it was probably after the premiere.
They didn't know.
I didn't, but, but Mo.
A buddy of mine was brought in to kind of help get that show ready to start.
You know, just they were like, we have like two weeks.
You want to just like get the scripting red shape and get it going.
So he went in and he was all excited.
And he's like, I think it's really funny and Rami's producing it and blah, blah, blah.
So I texted him the other day and we're texting back and forth.
I go, Hey, man.
I wanted to watch your show.
Whatever happened to that Mo show.
It's been on Netflix for three months.
It has like you, you search it and you can't find it on it.
No, I'm not kidding.
I go, I go, no, I'm looking through new comedies.
And I'm like, I'm looking through like new comedies with foreign leads.
And you just could not find it.
Well, I guess they did.
Mo posted this on his thing the other day is Instagram.
And he, he, it's him talking to John, John Stewart.
John Stewart goes, you're going to get a season two.
And Mo goes, they're still deciding we're waiting to hear.
And John Stewart goes, there's still Netflix still deciding.
They got a lot of great stuff in the pipeline.
Huge laugh, right?
Yeah.
And John Stewart goes, I mean, don't get me wrong.
I'm real excited to see the sequel to Jeffrey Dahmer.
Yeah.
And I'm real happy that Lindsey Lohan has fallen in love again.
And then he goes, Hey Netflix, I have an idea.
Instead of hiring Ryan Reynolds and Chris Evans.
Maybe just hire one of them and then give Mo five extra seasons.
Yeah.
Places going crazy.
I was like, God, man, that was like, he really just cut straight through it.
It was, it was awesome.
It was really funny.
By the way, five seasons of, of Mo's show would not equal the salary of Chris Evans or Ryan Reynolds.
Netflix pays them $40 million.
Yeah.
It honestly would.
But that sounds awesome.
And I will watch it.
I always wonder why guys in his position, like John Stewart has a billion dollars.
He has his own show on Apple, even though he's a decade past his prime, maybe two.
And he can make movies if he wants whatever he wants to do.
Why not use that position to talk more shit like this because we all can't.
You know, like you're in a position where you can make us all feel like we're not crazy when Netflix releases a hundred unwatchable shows in a row.
You know, I admire that.
Yeah.
Now speaking of Mo Mir, uh, mode travels a lot with Chappelle.
He tours a lot with Chappelle.
Uh, Chappelle.
In movie news.
This is his.
He and Neil Brennan's movie.
His bank is banked is getting a sequel with a theatrical release.
With me.
We're talking about this all week.
The only returning cast members being Rachel true in a lead role.
And then at the way end of the list, it says and Harlan Ellison, which means he's popping in and out in one scene for a cameo or something.
I'm like, what is this?
I'm friends with Moses storm.
He's in it.
But I'm like, why is this been recast with all new people?
This is this.
I love.
I'm a huge fan of Dave.
Uh, and, and I'm a huge fan of Neil.
Like it's, I like those guys a lot.
And I like half baked.
It makes me laugh.
It is not a good movie.
It's a bad movie.
It did not do well.
It did not age that well.
Well, you know, it became a comedy central staple.
It became a real like everybody's watching it.
The difference is we used to be this fun crazy thing back.
Honestly, Cheech and Chong threw knocked up and beyond.
Weed was like a weird, uh, subculture thing.
Now you go to the doctor and your doctor is stoned.
It's like, um, it's not a novelty anymore.
Half baked to me has one funny scene, two funny scenes.
One with John Stewart.
You ever look at a dollar bill on weed.
Uh, and two, a, an absolutely brilliant comedic set piece that I am,
I've always been jealous of the date with no money with a countdown clock
of how much money you have in the date.
A brilliant comedic concept executed pretty well.
The rest of the movie.
It's a Jim Brewer vehicle.
The, uh, Brewer, again, I like Brewer.
I love how they, they couldn't get Brewer for a cameo.
I like Brewer.
I'm a fan of the guy.
He's unbearable of that movie.
He's unbearable to me.
Yeah, character.
It's, I've said it before.
He's doing a Jim Carrier performance without the jobs.
I've said it before and we, you disagree with me.
It's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's why it's the same reason I can't,
I can't stand it.
There are three characters that come to mind.
It's Brewer and Half -Bake, uh, Sandler and Little Nikki and Eugene Levy and Mighty Wind.
I can't take the way the character talks.
And I'm just like, please get the scene over with to get me to the next part.
I completely understand and agree with your first two examples.
Uh, Eugene Levy makes me cry on a Mighty Wind.
I think he's incredible.
I can't do it.
Um, the, by the way, Rachel Trues character hates weed in the first one.
So now he's in the second one.
I promise you, I'm guessing.
Yeah.
Let's call it right now.
She hates drugs, but has to open a dispensary.
Yep.
Hi, I got you.
Mo.
God almighty.
Anyway, like if they announced that was going to crackle.
I'd be like, yeah, that makes sense.
The actual release.
I don't get.
Um, I know Moses.
This is pretty well too.
I feel like 12 times a year, you and I realize we know someone.
Both very well and have never discussed it.
Hat and I are two sides of a same coin in this business.
Well, Moses.
I don't even think well, he was a standup at the time, but uh, the girl,
my girlfriend before I got married, she was like his best friend.
So we used to hang out a lot, but not in comedy settings.
He's still a standup.
He just, you know, he had that HBO special.
Oh, no, I know he is still.
I was wondering if he was.
He definitely wasn't a big standup at that time.
He was just kind of starting out.
Last but not least, uh, in the news cycle.
There's a movie called paint coming out.
Just saw a little, uh, clip of it.
Yeah.
Starting on Wilson.
I heard the private.
It's a Bob.
It's a, it's a Bob.
Uh, Rob Ross.
Ross parody.
And it looks very much to be like in the vein of like anchor man
in those styles of comedies.
And you hear it.
I rolled my eyes when I heard the premise.
I was like, uh, another Bob Ross thing.
Aren't we past this?
And then you see the picture.
And the picture will make you laugh for seven minutes straight.
Like Owen Wilson and the wig.
Making the classic Owen Wilson face with a pipe in his mouth.
As he's painting his.
It's a really funny looking picture.
And I got it.
I loved that the plot.
Also is a younger like hotter painter hits the scene.
You know, I was like, all right.
This, this might be funny.
Bad.
This might be really funny.
I hope so.
His, his career is one of the more baffling careers.
Like, you know, Pharaoh keeps it going.
He does one for him.
One for us.
That kind of deal.
But, um, Owen Wilson for.
I don't.
I know he is made at least one movie a year for the last ten years.
And I have not seen a single one of them.
I have no interest.
I feel like he takes anything that comes across his desk.
Um, and he also is completely out of the public eye.
He doesn't.
I've never seen him be interviewed.
I don't know what he's doing.
I don't know what has happened to his life.
But hopefully this brings him back.
I, I would hope so.
Uh, yeah.
Pharaoh is.
I.
Yeah.
I mean, my God, man.
That new fucking thing.
Ugh.
Well, what's he doing now?
That thing that's like a rip.
Well, I don't know if it's a rip off.
But the thing that looks like Scrooge that he's got out now.
With Ryan Reynolds playing like a high end executive.
Did you know it's a full musical.
Fuck off.
Full musical.
It's out.
I mean, talk about a movie.
No one is discussing.
It's out.
Yeah.
It's on Apple TV and it's in theaters.
Shout out to Jay Leno.
I hope he recovers too.
They said he's going to recover.
But he's full.
He got burned really bad.
His face.
I didn't know denim was that flammable.
Hey, pope.
Oh.
All right.
When he when he first caught fire.
For at least five minutes, Kevin UBANKS was just off to the side going, boom.
And then finally, he was like, I'm serious.
UBANKS, did I discuss on this pod.
I did, right?
That Kevin UBANKS was a key.
One of the talking heads in that horror documentary.
That was.
Yeah, we neither of us understood he's never scored a horror film. I mean, it's just maybe it's just a shot. So so is Joe Latrugio though.
But then I learned that Joe Latruglio has a horror movie coming out that he directed and wrote.
That's a big thing that comedians are doing now. Yeah, I've been trying to do it for three years. Yeah, the face repeatedly.
Um, anyway, folks, well, let's get to this to the movie corn. Yeah. Um, I'm going to start with you mentioned his name. I hate to do this, but I got to talk about Neil Brennan.
Um, uh, his new special is appalling. Let's go blocks, blocks. Um, it was directed by Derek LaGuardia or whatever the guy's name is who did the.
Yeah, the special where he, yeah, the magic, you know, because guess people's trauma or whatever that show was. Um, so Neil Brennan comes out and there's like a bunch of blocks on the stage and he goes, you know, it's crazy.
I asked this friend of mine to create sort of an art installation for the background of my standup special and she gave me this weird like blocks set.
And it's like, why are you doing this fake story? That that's your set. Just, just turn around and start interacting with it. If that's your bit, do it. Don't come up with my friend. I didn't, you didn't give her any guidelines for your Netflix special. No, you told her it's going to be called blocks. Make me a thing with blocks. Don't fucking lie to me.
And I know comics lie and make up their premises all the time. But Jesus Christ, it annoyed me right from the jump. And what really annoyed me is that the special looks absolutely terrible.
It looks like it was shot like on the surface of Mars or something. It looks awful. Um, the lighting is bad. The set is terrible.
And then, you know, Brennan gives you, you know, 45 minutes of solid standup, but the whole time I'm like, something is a mess here. And then I realized what it was every five minutes he'd say something a little serious.
Then at the end, he sits down in a chair, puts his head in his hands. And he's like, I just hope that someday, you know, all of these flaws in me.
Read to other people like a personality. God, I hope that's so much.
It's like, it's, it's corneer than that. I'm making that up. It's actually senior than that. What you've done, Hannah Gatsby, are you satisfied?
That's what he's doing. He's like, oh, okay. Hannah Gatsby did this. And people started talking about her like she's Maya, fucking Angelo, not like she's Amy Schumer.
People start saying, oh, this is a profit. I want to be that profit. That is the level of narcissism, frankly, on display.
And what's weird is that I related and had some of his same personality quirks and issues, as do a lot of people in comedy, but like the way I urge you to watch the last five minutes of this special.
And see if you don't just puke. I mean, I have never lost my respect for somebody so quickly.
This, this claptor thing that we've been doing now of like fuck it being funny. I just want to like change people's lives.
He says something so generic at the end of this. And yet so corny and embarrassing that I can't believe in a world as ball busting as the comedy world.
One of his friends didn't go, buddy. This is fucking awful.
It's listen, all respect to Neil. I think meals are really great comic. I don't like the ending of the special. I'm just being honest. I don't like that kind of thing.
I didn't like when I liked Drew Michael. I didn't like when he did it at the end of his special. Yeah, I have nothing against Hannah Gatsby. I don't like that she did it at the end of her whatever.
It's your I had a reason to compel him reason to do it. Gerard's stunk too.
It is. I don't like when people do it. It feels manipulative to me. It is manipulative. It just feels like you're trying to pull something out of me.
And here's the thing. Okay, that's fair. You're allowed to do that. Like I'm not saying fuck you or fuck Neil or fuck anybody for doing it. You're allowed to do it.
It's just I don't like when it's being you know what I'll take back what I said about two of the people initially with Hannah Gatsby.
It seemed like she did have a compelling reason or you know of a worthwhile thing to do there and to try with that.
And I'll give it to you to Gerard to.
But in other cases, I just find that it's just I don't know. But then anybody could go well then why isn't Drew's vowed or why isn't Neil's vowed and I have no excuse.
I get annoyed with stand -up comedy. I think it's stupid. I mean, look, the first get person that I remember to ever do this was Carlos Mincella, believe it or not, on his half hour.
His half hour, his comedy central presents he ends with sometimes life doesn't have any meaning. Sometimes it's chaos. Sometimes it's this keeps going. Sometimes, sometimes. Sometimes you get on a plane and then they point that plane towards twin towers.
And your life is over in an instant. This is literally how it ends and he goes sometimes a comedy show doesn't have an ending that's funny and then he walks off stage.
Oh, it's just it's just never good.
You know, like and that's the thing wasn't good when the person he stole that bet from did it either.
Just go. I don't know. I guess everybody. Look, I'm trying to start a residency with this new hour I have and we're billing it more as a one man show. So I guess I have no room to talk.
Well, like when I don't know I just certainly not, but I'm certainly not trying to get the crowd to feel anything. I don't like when you're trying to make me feel. You know what I mean?
Yeah, I don't know. I was in London. There was this Eddie sold out Eddie Pepitone run being billed as a one man show, but there's a guy who like, okay, call it whatever you want, but at the end of the day he's giving you relentless laughs.
The this like I'm going to do it's like it is infected all of comedy it is infected these comedy series comedy movies sitcom stand -up comedy the priority is never laughter anymore.
And that's why nothing is funny. Do you know what it is to me? It's not even though my thing is it's not even the laughter aspect of it. It's it's all compare it to pop punk.
If you listen to like the early early like, you know, for instance, green day records, the ones before before they got, yeah, a slappy, you know, they're poppy, they're infectious, and what you hear as a guy like really like blasting out vocals over this power pop punk about a girl that he loved that broke his heart or whatever it is.
And it feels really genuine. And then you hit fast forward to like the fourth blank 182 record and the hot topic scene and all that stuff. And it's the same formula, but the substance isn't there and you go, you're trying to make me feel all goose pimpley about this girl you're singing about in this sappy melody.
And it's not genuine to me. It's just I'm not buying it. That's the difference to me. These things could end on a serious note.
But it better. Well, I'll give this to Hannah. She fucking cried at the end of the hers. Like I was like, okay, she seems serious. You know what I mean? Like like.
Yeah, but when it's when it's a thing where it's like, no, you're in your head. You thought about this and thought this would be a cool ending because it'll leave the audience feeling a certain. I don't like that. I don't care for that.
By the way, you know, and I'm talking about Chappelle before he became a single issue comic, which is trans people, but well, no, he's now in trouble for other things, but let's not go right and he sent it to me.
He would often and still often end to ship with a serious sort of state of affairs where he sits down and smokes a cigarette.
Yes.
Now, for whatever reason doesn't bug me at all when he does it doesn't bug me at all. I don't know why, but I think it's because he's been relentlessly hilarious for the previous hour.
You know, Neil's thing is kind of generic relationship stand -up comedy that tries to suddenly pretend it's important at the end like his whole special isn't even about the issue that he sits down and buries his head in his hands about. It's very, it's very manipulative is the word didn't care for Joe. What do you got next?
What do I have? Well, here, I'm probably going to get shit for this, but I I've been watching rules of attraction of engagement, the sitcom. I'm almost finished with it.
I got to say this is a sitcom that starts, you know, kind of boring and kind of cookie cutter and whatever. And as it goes, it becomes increasingly more and more inappropriate. And in my opinion, very funny.
It's a very, very funny show and it's never seen one minute of it. It's an, you know, it's, it's like Patrick Warburton doing like an elevated version of putty.
You got spayed in exactly the way you want spayed playing like the biggest fucking creep on planet earth. Yes.
And the rest of the cast is very funny and great, you know, you know, it's just it the show just makes me laugh, but I'm there 100 % for spayed.
It is the sort of one vehicle I feel like we got where we got to really see David spayed at his best comedically. I feel like there was never really a great movie version of that like Tommy Boy is considered a classic by a lot of people.
But spayed I feel like doesn't really get to shine as much and that is as Chris Farley does spayed his way more of the straight man.
I got to say though, he says fun, you know, he says great a straight man is Martin and plan straights. I think his, his quips are equally and the movie doesn't work without him.
He's great. He's great. But when he, I guess when he gets to play a scum back, he gets to do all of the spayed stuff for sure. So there's like a lot of point parts in the series.
As it goes on where he will do something fucking heinous and then tell his assistant like you owe me an apology and the system will be like I have nothing to apologize to you for sir and spayed to be like, I can't think that you do.
You know, like it does all that kind of quirky spayed should it. It's really funny. It's really inappropriate. But this is the thing that struck me about the show.
Are there gay jokes? Yes. Are there racial jokes? Yes. Are there rape jokes? Quite frankly. Yes.
Are there, is there an argument that you don't need to make those jokes to be funny? Sure. Is there an argument that if you make those jokes all the time, it's cheap and easy and it's pointless and it's been done and blah blah blah. Absolutely.
I will say this though. I think the show.
I think I'm not saying just those three topics. I just mean a lot of comedy topics in general. I think that the fact that we've made certain types of jokes, not just an appropriate, but even the mention or pitching of them in a comedy room, a writing staff, a fireable offense.
Yeah. You see the effect that it just has overall on comedy. Seinfeld never had one rape joke. Seinfeld didn't really have a ton of racial humor. It, you know, it did not have cheap gay jokes.
But no, when it did a racial bit, it was at the expense of how white the show was and how they had no black friends and etc. Right. But what you do know is that if you watch like interviews with Larry, not Larry David.
Charles Larry Charles.
That there were incredibly edgy quote offensive unquote episodes that that were got to rehearsal level but never got aired or taped because they were deemed too offensive.
That's my only point. When you start to say you can't joke about certain things and beyond that, if you even bring up the joke, you could be fired or canceled or whatever.
It just puts an air into the room where there's constraints on the jokes and whatever and you end up with a lackluster product. Say what you will about a show like rules of engagement. It is not I love Lucy. It is not Seinfeld.
It is not a class. It is not a classic. It's a funny sitcom. And at times it's corny, but the point is it's a funny sitcom. You put that show that went off the air less than 10 years ago up against any almost any modern day multi cam.
Yeah.
It's it's no contest. It's a show that gets big laughs. Boom boom. And it moves and it gets funny. You know, you know, I'm not I don't say this to be to be I'm not I'm not taking a shot here, but you know two broke girls gets plenty of that criticism as you've said on the show.
You know, deserved. Yeah. But you offer criticized it in the room and say, don't put this on the air. It would still happen.
But you put that show up against the modern multi cam and you go, well, guys, at least it's getting big laughs, you know, big bang theory was another one. People trashed big bang theory.
It got huge organic laughs that was not piped in right and laughter that was real like we don't realize how much people.
I mean, obviously everyone needs that and no one is doing it like the last time I laughed really hard couldn't even couldn't even think about when that was.
Which is disturbing. I don't know. Yeah, we talked about this all the time, but need, you know, we need laughs, folks, and we're not going to get it the with the style of comedy we're doing now.
I punched up a movie yesterday. I punched up two comedies this week.
One kind of a big broad happy Madison type thing.
That was already very funny and punching it up with a room full of comedy writers was a blast and we were laughing and having fun and cheering.
And then the next day I punched up a romantic comedy that was laughless.
She was like, I know, obviously, we need more comedy in it and the whole rooms kind of like, this was a comedy like there's nothing in it that indicates that right.
It's, it's bleak in which one will probably see the light of day the one with no laughs. That's the other issue.
I saw a picture called Chacha real smooth easily one of the most obnoxious titles of the year, but I was excited to watch it is only available on Apple TV.
They had for whatever reason they buy like two movies a year and this was one of them and I think they spent $15 million to acquire it.
It looks like it costs maybe a mill. This guy Cooper Rafe wrote and directed a movie a couple years back during the pandemic called shit house.
And I talked about it on the pod. I said, this is a really, really special movie. It was made for like 10k.
I said this guy's got a real voice. He's funny as an actor. He's funny as a writer. He's good as a director. I love this guy. I can't wait to see what he does with a budget.
Well, this is what he does with a budget. I mean, I would imagine this was noted to death by Apple probably. It is super generic. He plays a guy. He's very young.
So for me to like a super young guy who's like doing his own thing and being successful. He's got to be pretty good. My my instinct is to always hate those people just out of jealousy.
But this is a movie about a 22 year old guy played by Cooper Rafe again. He works as a party starter for bar mitzvahs.
And while working one of them, he strikes up a relationship with a young woman. That sounds like an Adam Sandler movie, really.
Okay. But it is just a generic not very little laughter. It's like the guy who made this movie for 10k.
May I was like this guy's the next Kevin Smith or somebody like a very different style of comedy, but I was just like this guy really gets human beings and how they talk to each other and he's funny and specific and I love him.
He then for his second movie, he designed a movie about how everybody loves his character. Like he's a guy who when he walks into a room, everyone lights up.
Every woman that he meets falls in love with him whenever he's not on screen, everybody else is talking about how great he is.
You know, it's the classic I got a little success and now I've lost what makes me special immediately.
The woman is played by who's what's her face from 50 shades of gray Dakota Johnson, who I always really like as an actress.
She's really bad in this movie. It's just it just kind of sits there to me.
You know, everyone describes this as as the mall, even when you're watching, I watched that documentary about Kevin Smith, everybody's like clerks was the masterpiece that everybody was disgusted by mall rats and thought this guy lost his touch.
I disagree. I love mall rats, maybe more than clerks.
Yeah, I love I like loved mall rats. I still love same. It's like that to me, he did clerks with a bigger budget and it was exactly what you wanted.
This is like, oh, I, I connected with this low budget, little romantic comedy indie, which is really just two people walking around a college campus, shit house, kind of like a before sunrise.
But then for whatever reason, this guy started reading his great press or something and decided to just make a movie about how awesome he is.
And it got great reviews. I don't get it. The movie is annoying as hell. I don't recommend it says it says annoying as it's title, if that makes sense.
All right. Well, I only have one more.
I said I'd do it, Pat. I'm going to do it. The Wolf of Wall Street.
Here's a movie that when I first saw it, I really didn't like it in theater. I just, I don't know. It just didn't hit me. I didn't resonate with me.
I just, I was like, I remember thinking like, here's everybody's trying to everybody's acting to score sazy -ish in this.
Yeah, instead of just playing these characters.
I would say to me, they're acting Scorsese, Scorsese -ish because they've seen a lot of Scorsese movies.
Well, yeah, that's what I mean. The characters.
Oh, I like, I think they're acting that way because like they're, they're trying to be players. You know, that's how I take it.
Um, just like the soprano guys are always talking about the Godfather. They call them one, two or three. They, you know, look like they, they fancy themselves to be those guys.
You know, they're low red bombs who work at a strip club. It's possible. I would, I would agree with that if it wasn't for the last temptation of Christ, which is another movie where they act Scorsese -ish.
Even though it's a Jesus story.
It's, it's, but it's not on rewatch. That's not what it is.
The beginning of this movie hits a few Scorsese tropes, two on the head. And I remember it took me out of it.
The first one is of the little person getting thrown at the camera in the first thing. And it's the freeze frame immediately.
My name is Jordan Belford. And I was like, oh, come on. This is like a Ben Stiller sketch, right about Scorsese.
And then DiCaprio walking through the house like in the beginning, I take that, that, that, that, that, I drink all day.
I have a sex addiction, you know, like throws the drink over a shoulder.
That stuff I still find a little trite. But, um, it's an awesome movie. I, you know, I had to step back for a few years.
My buddy, honest popus was telling me he had rewatched. He's like, dude, it's so good. Like you got to rewatch it.
You trust me. So I was like, all right. I will. And I did. And I was like, all right. I'm glad I rewatched this. It was, I, I, I'm sure there's a deeper, as there always is with Martin Scorsese movies.
A deeper meaning to it than just the slice of this is what Wall Street was at this time. And this is what happened and it's nuts.
Yeah. Um, but I don't know what that is. The deeper meaning is, is he shows you the fun of it like he did in Goodfellas.
Maybe too close to what he did in Goodfellas, you know, but he shows you the fun of it. And then at the end pulls the rug out and shows you that.
This is not a way to live your life. I mean, Wolf Wall Street to me is a movie about anti -capitalism. Basically the, the flaw of it.
And I think the thing that critics of it missed is that yes, it shows you that this stuff can be fun because it can.
But it's not sustainable as a, as a lifestyle. I don't think he does a good job of driving home that second part.
I think the part of him in prison is very glazed over. It almost feels tacked on. Uh -huh. It's one scene.
You see no suffering whatsoever. It's literally like, oh, your wife was leaving you because you're an asshole.
No boo fucking who now you cut cocaine out of your couch cushion and you're doing it because you're so mad boo fucking who.
Oh, you went to prison and it shows you playing tennis in prison. And the voiceover says prison was a place where everything was for sale.
Like and wouldn't you like to know how to sell it? So you reinvented yourself and put like there's no part of it where I'm like, oh, what a, and then the end is him as this big.
So I, you know, you could argue the commentary is the sickness of capitalism that somebody that did all these horrendous things is still applauded in the end. I don't know.
I just all I'm saying is I don't think he views Jordan Belford as a great guy.
No, no, no, I don't think that either. I just mean when somebody is moral.
When the shim, that score says, yeah, I think would be disgusted by him, but I don't know about why I don't know about that. But that doesn't matter. It's it's my point is this when the shit when the shoe drops in goodfellas the shoe fucking drops.
True. Like you feel it. You're like, this guy is going to fucking get killed. Oh my god, like look at what their life has become. They literally look like fucking vermin at the end of it. They're all struggling out.
Like you feel it in the end. You really feel it. And then that last shot of him on the porch or the stoop in the, in the suburbs. You're like, oh my god, what a living hell. Like look at this.
And this doesn't have that. Now here's the thing.
A lot of people thought the Irishman didn't have a greater point either. You watch it a few times and you start to realize it's this dissection of death and all the, and it's, it hits me on a level that it didn't hit me the first time.
It hits me on a much deeper level every time I watch it. Right. A deeper level each time. This might do the same. I don't know. I've only seen it twice. But I will say this. It's a very well made movie. It's great. DiCaprio is awesome.
Jonah Hill. God, he hits it out of the park. Good. The kid is good. Margot Robbie is excellent.
And Rob Reiner is funny in it. I kind of think Rob Reiner is a little miscast. Everybody thinks he's like so funny and whatever. I'm like, I don't really bother by Rob Reiner as a hothead. I don't know. I just, it's not like, I guess all in the family is kind of hothead. But like his place in that movie is sort of like
the Foo Fighters song in that movie where you're like, what's going on for a minute? It's like, why did you shut this in here? Well, do you know why? Because the whole, you think of Wall Street, you think of the 80s. And then halfway through that movie, you realize, oh no, this takes place in like 1998.
Yeah, maybe that's why it seems so out of place. Yeah, they're playing like insane in the membrane. And you're like, oh my, like that, it's weird, but you don't realize it at first. You just assume
you know, it's a great, it's a great movie. I can't say any different about it. You know, I love the picture. My third for the day is a viewing, a reviewing of analyzed this speaking of people in the Scorsese world.
I just thought to myself the other night, it was on HBO Max and I was like, well, I guess this is going to be another movie I'll watch and realize it wasn't as good or as funny as I thought. Just real honestly, what I expected going in, I needed something mindless.
And I was just captivated right away. They used to just know how to make a fucking movie. The story homes along 90 minutes, crystal is a real person in it, which he was not doing at that time.
He's just playing like a nice normal therapist who's getting married. I love, I mean, Danero has done this, this character now so many times, it's become kind of old hat, but it was a revelation at the time him crying and all him crying in this movie is hilarious him doing the you and all that hilarious.
Danero is great. Don't get along. But this is one of the few Billy Crystal performances that is like him in when Harry Matt Sally where he plays a guy who's hilarious and can land a wisecrack.
But at the end of the day, you believe him as a real person and not as a Saturday Night Live character or something. So it's so well constructed. It was written by
what Jesus Harold ran us and then Peter Tolan, who did rescue me with Dennis Leroy and stuff.
But then the original draft was by Kenneth Lonergan, who wrote, you can count on me, who wrote Manchester by the sea. It must have been so dark.
Well, I read an interview with him and he was like, no, he wrote it to sell it as a big budget comedy. And he was basically like, if I'm going to keep making you can count on me, I'm not going to get rich. And for a while there, he was trying to do big budget things.
In fact, Danero loved the script so much. He brought him on to write the unwatchable Rocky and Bullwinkle movie was written by Kenneth Lonergan.
Terrible film. But when I was just sitting and marveling at how well structured it is, I was like, I bet that's Lonergan and the other guys sprinkled in all the laughs.
Could be right. Could be wrong. I don't know. But at the end, it is such a genius move. And you never question it. You never question a single move of anyone in the movie. It reminded me of, as I keep talking about honeymoon in Vegas, where the plot might be.
You know, sitcom, it might be weird. But as long as you believe every minute of it, it doesn't matter. And you believe everything in this movie. When Billy Crystal at the end has to impersonate a gangster, that's where the movie really flies into another dimension. It's like they somehow, because Crystal is so reserved. He's never doing his thing. And I guarantee he was like, shouldn't I do my thing at some point and it just led to that.
And it's one of the classic, watch it twice. It's one of those classic comedic turns. The best version of that type is her and for me ever is in a terrible movie called another you with Gene Wilder Richard prior where gene wilders trying desperately not to lie because he's a pathological liar.
Richard prior pulls him into a con gene wilders resisting resisting resisting and then all of a sudden snaps and start and becomes another human being in the scene. It's one of the funniest things I've ever seen.
That's the and Billy Crystal does that in this he can't do it. He can't do it. He can't do it. It's like the scene in.
It's a funny version of the scene in collateral when Jamie Foxx has to go in and pretend he's down cruise. Yeah. Yeah.
But when he's got when crystal has the guy by the he's squishing the fact guys face together. He's you want a fresh one when he's slapping him repeatedly and all that stuff.
So it's so great. It's so well that fact guys amazing. I listened to a little bit of the commentary and they they were like believe it or not a lot of the best comedic ideas for this movie came from Robert De Niro.
And when they watched the cut of that Billy Crystal scene. Apparently they were like we know we've got a classic comedy scene here.
And they were all laughing and loving it. And De Niro was like just shaking his head no in the back and they're like what's up.
And he was like he needs to he needs to slap jelly the fact guy. He needs to like be physical with them.
And they're like well the movie shot. So we we don't have that. And he's like call up Billy call up Billy.
And they got like a warehouse. They only shot. They spent probably 500 brand. They shot one thing which was Billy Crystal slapping that fact guy and inserted it in the scene.
And it's what takes the scene over the edge, you know.
No, that's great. That's really great. It's and then also to the thing that movie has that the second film does not.
And then a lot of watch that one again. Yeah, and then a lot of comedy slash whatever genres don't have that need.
It's got actual menace like the scene where De Niro is going to kill Max Casela with the pipe.
You believe it. You believe it. Like it's it's a frightening scene.
And you see that this guy is is awful. He's a bad person. And then you know, it just it really solidifies and validates the movie.
It really does legitimize this. That's that's the term I was looking for.
Yeah, it was also great because people forget it was the same year as sopranos.
No, I'm like Lonergan and David Chase both separately talk about how they heard about the other project and we're like, oh, I'm fucked.
Like because it is one of those ideas. That's like a million dollar idea. Yeah.
And they both had it at the same time. And it happens. And the fact that they're both really good is kind of amazing because normally they would both suck.
It was a different time. I marveled at how well constructed this movie was. I really did. It was so funny and well put together.
It was when people cared that an idea needed to be original, which is why David Chase and Lonergan were nervous.
Yeah, I remember that that Hulu show that lasted two weeks about the guy that saw dead people.
Like a comedy. And I said to a friend of mine, I go, this fucking show we saw a commercial for and I go, it's fucking show. I go, this is.
This is fucking six cents. Yeah. Just took the six cents and said, what if it was funny. Yeah. And she and my friend goes, I know the creator and actually that's how they came up with it.
They were high. And I know that doesn't make it okay. You're saying that they're owning that they just took the idea. Yeah.
Like like that, but that just became okay eventually. Then they did it again in ghost town. And then they did, you know, and like then all of a sudden it was just like.
Well, they on on sopranos, they pointed out they kind of had to, but they call it and again, there was a fucking comedy, you know, like they actually shot.
But yeah, I did a, I did a movie punch up once on this movie that was called sick day. And I was reading it like, wait a minute, this is Ferris Bueller with at the time Jason babe was attached and Vince Vaughn or something.
And I'm reading through it and I'm like, this is way too much like Ferris Bueller. Why don't they just call it Ferris Bueller part two and try to get broadric. I don't understand.
And then I get to like the halfway point and he goes to a parade in Chicago where the movie is set. And he's dancing in the parade.
So I go to this punch up and I was really nervous to do it. But I was like, hey man, I got a bunch of jokes here happy to happy to punch it up. But I go, I got to say.
Your movie already feels similar in spots to Ferris Bueller. So I think I would definitely remove the parade scenes since that's the most famous scene, you know, it might be a little obvious. And he goes, why are you acting so timid about telling me this he goes, you realize I outlined this movie pushing play and pause on a DVD of Ferris Bueller stay on.
Now thankfully that movie was never made, but I was just kind of like, oh, that's how people come up with stuff. Like you just the movies that feel paint by numbers.
Well, generally are follow follow playing pause just don't change the set piece at least. Right. Jesus Christ or maybe playing pause without the same plot. Maybe you go, hey, this is kind of like a Ferris Bueller except it's about a kidnapping.
But I'll share the beats. Sure. You know, you know, or at least change up the set pieces or something.
But let us talk now about our movie at hand or movie of the week weird.
The Al Yankovic story. Now there's not much to say here. It's a plot wise, it's a spoof of biopics.
As such, it is a far less in my opinion, successful spoof of biopics than walk hard.
But I would guarantee walk hard came up in the pitch for this movie.
And the problem with it in my opinion is that walk hard so perfectly satirized every single trope of a music biopic that to do another spoof of a music biopic, you know, it doesn't quite hit and they have to go after like targets and jokes that to me were less successful a lot of the time.
But you're watching Weird Al from a kid to the present a highly, highly fictionalized version of his life that also kind of reminded me of Norma Donald's book where like it touches on some of the actual things that happened, but by and large, it's made up.
For example, it's kind of a funny bit that he in the movie, he writes, beat it like are he writes, eat it as an original.
And Michael Jackson's beat it never existed. That's like a where the movie starts going.
And then Michael Jackson steals it.
Right. So it's like it plays with the facts, but it's not like it plays with the facts, but it's still a biopic. It plays with the facts in a jockey way to where everything is a joke.
And the sense of humor, I kept going, what is this sense of humor remind me of? And then I looked it up and saw Weird Al wrote it.
And it reminded me of, you know, my earliest comedic influence, I was obsessed with Weird Al. I was obsessed with UHF. I, you know, so I was like, oh yeah, a lot of these jokes feel like classic Weird Al for sure.
I thought it was, I really liked the movie. I thought it was very, very funny. My only criticism is if you don't know Weird Al, this would make zero sense to you.
There was a lot of inside baseball with Weird Al, but that's what Weird Al does. He spoof things and he made a spoof of a movie in the way he pairs does spoof of songs about his life that spoofed movie movies or music movies.
So I liked that he did that. I really enjoyed it.
You know, I was a lifelong fan of, I mean, lifelong, I was a fan as a kid, you know, as I got older, I phased out, but I've always respected Weird Al tremendously as a musician. He's an incredible songwriter, an incredible musician.
Yeah, an incredible vocalist.
You know, but just as you get older, sometimes you taste for comedy music, Wayne's a bit, but I was obsessed and I couldn't listen to him now. It's like I don't find any of his songs funny now.
I have a mix on my phone and my Apple music of Weird Al songs that aren't spoof songs and some of them are, you know, the lyrics, if you can just kind of get past a couple of the lines.
I really enjoy them as like legit, they're legitimate songs. They're just, they're not over the top funny. They're just so well written that I enjoy them. Anyway, I really like the movie a lot and you, but you have to watch it through the lens of I'm watching a Weird Al specifically a Weird Al comedy.
I think he does a good thing with movies like he's, he's good at it. Like, you know, UHF to me is, is a fucking classic. I love UHF. Yeah, and this made me laugh a lot. I wasn't in the mood for it when I turned it on. I thought I wasn't going to like it.
It started to feel to me after a while because I kept hearing about it, like another one of these like cool kids in Hollywood projects and it actually isn't. There was way, way, way fewer.
I thought it was going to be like Seth Rogan and all these, you know, people popping up and, and it wasn't it was a ton of cameos.
But oftentimes it's like somebody just kind of sitting there, you know, it's not like everybody gets a long scene or something. Conan has one line. Yeah.
Pat Nozzle has two lines, stuff like that. And it's people that email large. I like emo Phillips. Yeah, as Salvador Daly. I didn't even recognize him. I also didn't recognize Dimitri Martin as tiny Tim, which was funny.
I love that when he goes to the bookie night style party, it's all novelty X. It's like, yeah, you know, it's that he and Herman. Yeah, Frank's and I don't think Frank's app is a novelty act, but I get why he was there.
Yeah, divine, divine. Yeah, no. I was really funny. I definitely thought for right now, it's much better than average comedy on the whole. I thought it was too long.
I thought for a movie with kind of one joke, although they find a lot of very funny variations on it. It was too long, since it started as like a two minute sketch, no less.
I thought Daniel Radcliffe was excellent in it. He's great. I loved him. I bought him as weird out, but also just like him and the mustache and wig reacting to things was funny. He had really funny ways of saying things and I just dug him.
I liked his friends. I liked Toby Huss. Of course, as his dad, another home run from Toby, I mean, my God, I can't miss.
I loved when he's like, Dad, you keep telling me I have to go work at the factories. I can you at least tell me what they make at the factory and he's like, I'll never tell you what they make at the back.
A lot of like weird funny stuff. And, you know, this kind of movie is rare nowadays. It never happens. I'm surprised that this didn't get Eric Appell.
It was a guy I know a little bit. I'm surprised it didn't get him the naked gun gig or naked gun reboot gig because it certainly shows he's got a gift for that style of comedy.
Yeah, no, that's yeah. It was I got to tell you one other thing I didn't like and where I just has a hankering for this because it's the it's the third act of of UHF as well. Yeah, I didn't like when it turns into the action spoof.
I felt like there was more to pluck from the tree of the music biopic like when he's shit face drunk and he can't think of how to satirize like a virgin.
Yeah, I was like, I felt like they missed a joke there. I was like, he should be going like he should be pitching bad parodies like he should be going like like a sturgeon.
Of course, and they're terribly he sings a little bit of each.
Yeah, yeah, and the joke is my look would become of you because in the beginning he pitches the one out of the party and it's instantly brilliant.
Yeah, and then I thought to like the whole movie is him saying I'm never going to parody a song ever again. And then he does because he's under the evil grasp of Madonna.
And I thought that should have been a thing. It should have been that he fell from grace because he does a parody again and we see him hit rock bottom and then he makes a comeback with another original,
and quotes Amish Paradise. And it's it's the joke again from beat it. And then he wrote it first and cool yo didn't.
And so that that was one thing that I didn't get why it went into that whole like John Wick thing. And then I love that Madonna has him killed at the end.
I thought that was great. I love that he is dead. When I didn't think it was too long when he got killed at the end. I was like, wait, that's the end. And then I was laughing because I was like,
this is a really funny way to end this. And they play it so seriously that he was assassinated. Yeah. And that Madonna still at large. And I was like, does Madonna think this is funny?
I mean, to me, the first half hour is where it is at its absolute best. And Madonna's entrance is around the time I started checking out a little bit.
But I think all told it's a funny film. I remember it just occurred when you're talking about his originals.
When I used to watch the VH1 behind the music, they had Devo. And they talked to mother's body. He's a very serious guy. But they're like, what did you think of weird Al's sort of Devo parody dare to be stupid.
And he goes, which is a great song and a great out maybe his best out. He goes, well, Al didn't parody a specific song of ours.
He sent he sent me a copy. I had never met him. And he said, I just want to tell you I've always you're one of my favorite bands of all time. And I wrote this in the style of a Devo song.
It's not a direct parody. But I just wanted to show you, you know, how much your music meant to me. And they were like sort of that was that upsetting to you or was that like cool.
Or do you think that was like an honor? And he gets real serious and weird. And he goes, honestly, it made me feel as though the thing that I do.
The very specific kind of music that I make and that I really based my whole life around.
Could very easily be duplicated. No, no, that's not what he's you're way off on this.
I just want to know what I'm thinking of when I was I mean, I saw another he says basically out. We're now managed to write the best ever Devo song. And I hate him for it. He said he said he's saying it as a joke.
No, no, he's saying I was actually envious of how good of a Devo song he wrote. He's not like he reduced it. He's saying like he's a fucking genius. And it made me.
I don't know. We're saying the same thing. I just remembered the tone of it wrong, I guess, but yeah, it was just like it was interesting take on it. He was like it made me feel like my life's work could easily be duplicated kind of thing.
I didn't take it that way. I took it as this guy is the most brilliant man that's ever lived to me. That's so I mean, but maybe I, but whatever.
I don't want to fight with you about it. Well, let's leave it between those two, but did you did you see the interview with coolio that came out when he died about weird out.
Oh, dude, I remember when that happened. I know, but did you see the after thing? Oh, wait, when weird out commenting on coolio dying, you mean? No, when coolio died, this story made the papers. And of course you only heard when they were beefing with each other, you didn't hear about the update.
So there was an interview with coolio and they asked him about it. And he was like, yeah, and he's like, I'm so glad you asked me because I need to take this platform to say that I was stupid. I was a fucking idiot. This guy parody songs by Michael Jackson. And I thought I was too big. Are you kidding me? He's like, it makes me deeply ashamed.
I have since apologized to weird out about it. I think he did a hilarious thing with my song and I'm ashamed of myself. And he's like, and man across this country have a problem with apologies. And it goes into that. It's like, I'm not, I'm going to say here right now I was wrong and I was stupid. It's beautiful. Actually, that's awesome. It's worth googling.
And my favorite line in the whole movie is, and I loved, they didn't hammer you over the head with it. Yeah, they just put it in the movie when he's like, Oh, bad news. This is the new Michael Jackson song. And he's freaking out and the guy got the executive played by the actual weird out goes, it's not so bad. What could be so bad about being tied to Michael Jackson for the rest of your life?
Yeah, it's interesting that Michael Jackson clearly gave them all that leeway, but they kept that joke. And maybe it's slid by because they didn't catch it or something. But because he would have had to get approval. He says it very passively. It's such a subtle thing where I'm just like, that's, that's left to interpretation. That's very fun.
Yeah, well, the movie, you know, it made me feel good and I enjoyed it. I think I liked it less than Joe, but I liked the picture quite bad. My hogs up my hogs decently up for the weird flick mine as well. Check it out for free on Roku next up. We will be discussing speaking of Netflix original series.
The watcher starring the great Jennifer Coolidge amongst other people Naomi Watson. And believe it or not, Joe, Bobby Kennavali has a role.
Glad to see the guy working always good to see him acting.
You know, Steve, I went to and I went I'm not kidding. I really did this. I went to Andrew Dice Clay's surprise birthday dinner about a month ago at this.
You don't mention it to me. I'm sorry. All right. And who's there amongst 25 of comedians is Bobby Kennavali. Of course, of course this guy doesn't go home.
No, that guy must hate his family or something. Yeah, he I heard he came from one set, went to the party and then went to a second set postpart.
Good Lord. I, I folks in that the Patrick Walsh on Twitter and Instagram. We will be at coastal creative in St. Petersburg, Florida on December 8, which is a Thursday. And then Joe is doing solo shows there the following nights.
Yeah, get tickets after my website, Joderosinfo .com. Please come out, Helians. Please come out. Please come out. Please come out. We'll see you in Florida. And we'll see you in hell.