Bonus app, it's your bonus app, it's your fat fucking Christmas fucking bonus app, December bonus app, for Christmas, for Hanukkah, for Kwanza, for all of it, for the holiday, okay, it's for the holidays.
Are you spelling it D -A -Z -E as well?
Yeah, and that's an incidentally script I've been working anthology script, I've been working on for years, holidays, five Christmas stories, people whose lives seemingly connect, unbeknownst to them.
You know, I don't think anything like that's ever been done before, right?
That was the ice maker, is it all right?
It sounds like it just shit, but yeah, yeah, that's never been done, right?
Like a Christmas movie where five stories intersect somehow, so I say go for it.
All right, we're doing Q &A today.
We're doing a Q &A and...
No segments, no plugs, just straight up questions and answers.
Yes.
We will get right to them.
How are you feeling now?
I feel that well, that sneeze set me back away.
Pat's in pain.
We discussed it on the final episode of December, which you'll be hearing this first.
Pat heard his neck, and he's in a lot of pain, and he thought for some reason that going to a lady that put needles in it would make it feel better.
It didn't make it feel worse, but it did not make it feel better.
You know, she said it, she's opened things up.
Yeah, it's her claim.
Well, sure.
I mean, I could rub ice on your head and tell you that it opened things up.
I hope not.
So question one, or we even do, oh no, Pat, we don't do our segments.
That's right.
Yeah, that's why I just said no segments.
I was trying to look up these questions.
Here we go.
Well, David Belinger asks, if you guys could choose anyone to score a film of yours, who would it be?
Mike Patton.
Wow, quick choice.
And for me, I would say,
oh, good cute, good cute.
You strike me as an Elfman, man.
I do love Danny Elfman.
Maybe like Danny Elfman and Frank Black.
And they get together.
You know, it's not really an option, but I bet you could set that up.
I also don't think Frank Black scores movies.
He's probably done something.
I don't think he ever has.
You know, that's those Joey Santiago from the Pixie.
Yeah, but I'd rather have the other one.
All right, next question from Dan Black, our friend Dan.
Danny B.
I texted you a brilliant question two weeks ago.
Use it or lose it, baby.
I will choose.
Use it.
Let me just find it.
I know I'm going to lose it.
Yeah, you don't, you won't, I don't think you've seen this.
Okay, here we go.
Well, so I was interested in your opinions on where the line is between a movie being influenced by another movie and when it's just a ripoff.
Does the amount of time between films matter or is it just about.
Is it just about how slickly it's done?
The end of Mr. Robot rubbed me the wrong way.
It was just a straight up fight club ripoff and even played that Pixie song.
Terrence, he knows does it a lot, but I never know the references.
So I've been okay with it.
Mr. Robot was the first time I thought it was just a flat out ripoff.
This might be because I'm getting older and my references are further and more reaching.
What do you think?
I think there are tropes and then I think there's theft.
I think in the Mr. Robot case that's theft.
I thought in the case of the non versus demon night, which we discussed on this film, it was theft.
To me, it's theft when you're taking a particular device that was used one time somewhere else or two times or something like that.
And then you're using it.
To me, that's copying.
A trope is something that's obviously been used, you know, like a device that doesn't really weigh on the plot itself.
It just kind of helps the action move forward.
You know what I mean?
So like the point is, it's like, okay, you know, these three people need to wind up dead at the end of this whatever sequence.
How they die is not as relevant to the story as the fact that they do die.
So to me, that's where a trope comes into play.
Oh, they do the old trope where they blow up the house or they do the, you know what I mean or whatever it is.
Whereas, you know, theft to me would be like, oh, the way they actually killed that person was literally the thing I saw one time.
Ever before in this other thing.
And because they did it that way, it meant this for the plot, which is how it affected the other thing I saw it.
You see what I'm saying?
I do.
That's my take on it.
But I think the short answer to the question is, I think most people just steal and then they're fucking horseshit excuse, which I can't stand.
Well, it's all been done before.
Shut up.
Right.
Shut the fuck up.
So that means you don't have to try.
There's shut up.
There's certainly a great deal of stealing in movies outright and unconscious.
You are always ripping off somebody in film.
It's been around too long.
But some people are very creative about who they rip off.
Tarantino was always ripping off, you know, super obscure shit.
But then he would credit it and put it back on the market and help it out.
So we're a con just took a heart.
Did you read that?
I did see that.
He was like, he's a fucking hack.
He just steals.
I'll never work for him again.
Like he hated him.
I mean, I think if it's entertaining, who cares?
Life's too short.
I don't mind things being influenced by other things.
I don't want it to be exact, you know, but influences are influences.
Tegan McLeod.
Thank you, Dan.
Ask.
If you could each pick one actor to get the Travolta Pulp Fiction Treatment in 2019,
who would you pick and what kind of vehicle would you give them?
Good question.
That is a good question.
I would choose Rick Moranis.
And I would just put him in a sweet little indie like an enough said type romantic comedy.
Let him get his sea legs back.
But I miss seeing him on the screen.
Well, he retired.
He's done.
Well, I'm saying we, that's what this is.
We're going to try to get somebody out of retirement.
Well, I think whoops.
That's I'm taking it out.
That's fine.
Your answer is fine.
I don't have a problem with your answer.
But I think the thing is is Travolta was in a slump.
There's a difference.
Moranis has been invited back many times and said no.
Repeatedly.
He's like, I'm done.
I don't want to do it anymore.
But I still like the answer.
I'd give it to him like you do.
I liked it.
I'd give it to.
Jesus Christ.
Teach Marin.
Hey, look, I'll double down in the pulp fiction.
You know, I'd give it to right now.
Fucking Ving Rames.
That guy went from like awesome leading man to like,
I'm the third wheel in the mission impossible crew.
That guy should be doing like Sam Jackson parts and shit like that.
You know, I agree.
He's a fantastic actor.
He was great in baby boy.
Yeah.
I like the excellent movie, baby boy.
I'm very underrated.
Check it out.
Yeah, I'd like to see him back in like a gangster type thing.
Barbell and asks, I like, I love swinging Todd.
Would you guys consider covering it?
We'll see you in hell.
We will consider it.
I remember I saw it at the theater and I enjoyed it to some degree.
Didn't love it.
But I felt like it was Tim Burton trying.
And I liked it.
Jail your thoughts.
I've seen bits and pieces of it.
I can't see a world in which I say I'm going to purposefully sit down and watch
Sweeney Todd from front to back.
Sure.
But I appreciate your candor.
But I do agree with you that I think it was probably the last time Tim Burton appeared
to give a remote shit about what he's doing.
Fuck about his output.
I mean, it was that big fish.
And then it just, it just dipped off.
It sure did.
I have not seen the last two of his movies.
And that's really saying something because I used to idolize the men.
You didn't run out to see Mrs.
Pertigwee's home for the weird kids.
I think that was cool.
I think that was the name.
Mrs. Pertigwee's home for the weird kids.
Shane Nazarian asked, I found this podcast through Joe being on Never Not Funny.
Any talk of Pat going on and Joe doing another episode.
I love Jimmy Parto on Twitter and in life.
I've never been asked to do that show, but I would love it.
I don't know what else to say.
I would definitely go on again.
If Jimmy ever wants me to go back on, I will, I will gladly go back on.
I always have fun with Parto.
Extremely funny, man.
Next time I'm there, I'll say, hey, Jimmy, I got a name to throw at you.
But that guy's unavailable.
So how about Pat Walsh?
You got any other names?
Says Jimmy.
Whitney Abbott, who was an inspiration for you to get into the comedy world?
George Carlin.
Okay.
And for me, I would say early on, it was like a Steve Martin, John Hughes.
That whole world, John Hughes known again for Chicago, close to St. Louis.
You know, that's what I wanted to do.
Misty Zavar.
I'm always looking to add to my collections.
So if you had to recommend only one movie and one vinyl that you think everyone should own,
what would they be?
Also, would you all please make a trip to Texas?
I would love to.
I went to Australia.
Two years ago, we would love to come down.
We will make it to Texas at some point.
I promise.
One movie, one vinyl.
That's tough.
The hell have I been listening to?
My one movie would be, I'd have to go, good fellows.
You can watch that over and over and over.
I'm going to say Glenn Gary, Glenn Ross, for the same reason.
Okay.
It's the best cast film I've ever seen in my life.
It's the best acting I've ever seen in my life.
I find it a riveting story.
And especially now, as we watch the middle class dissolve in front of our eyes by the second,
I think a story about salesmen being fucked over by the company and desperation and what you need to do
to provide for your family as a pretty relevant tale right now.
As far as records go, I mean, that's a more than he asked for, Misty Zavar.
I'm sorry.
No, I'm saying enjoy.
I want to go back to the Rick Moranis thing now.
I'm saying enjoy Joe's thorough response.
One record you got to own.
I'll tell you, go go and get that.
Go go go.
You can yourself a nice copy of run DMC raising hell on vinyl if you don't have that.
That is a front -to -back hip -hop classic.
Sure.
One could argue the greatest hip -hop record of all time.
It is the record that broke the mold.
It is what put rap music on the mainstream map.
You know, they were the only rapper, but live aid.
Like it's, you know, that's a pretty monumental record.
And I'm going to, I can only say the only record I've been listening to for the last six months,
which is one, I've listened to a million times before in my life,
songs for the death by Queen of Stone Age.
And you know what?
It's not on vinyl.
So I don't know why I recommend it to you.
It's not on vinyl?
No.
Why not?
It's not, but you can get the one before it rated R,
but even that's not a great one to get because the pressing is bad.
But was it ever thought this through better?
I think it was briefly on vinyl.
I'm going to tell you why don't you get Fleetwood Mac Tussk.
It's got all kinds of songs.
Four sides.
It's a big one.
So you got like two hours of material.
That's my recommendation.
Kevin Marcinick, would either or both of you be game to dress up as Mrs. Claus,
cover yourselves in wrapping paper and let me open you as a gift under the tree on Christmas morning?
Nothing sexual, and you can leave as soon as I unwrap you.
I wouldn't even need to talk.
Just looking to spice up my holiday, let me know.
Why the hell not?
Deeply disturbing.
And reported.
What's your answer, though?
No, I know for you.
My answer is no.
I would hope I have other things going on on Christmas.
This is Christmas Day.
I'll tell you this.
Why the hell not?
And I might hang around for a while, whether you want me to or not.
Right.
So I was like, he shoving you right out the door like a prostitute.
I might want to stay for a bit.
Fair.
Sal, I'm Anders Astu.
Either of you believe in the Illuminati or Hollywood occultism.
Yes.
Yeah.
I mean, I've heard rumblings about the Illuminati for the past several years.
I never got too deep into it.
But as far as Hollywood cults and sex and weird shit going on,
SECTS and SEX.
Yeah, absolutely.
I think this is a sick town full of sick people.
Yeah.
Laurence Crazy Horse Anderson.
Patrick, I'm taking a trip to good old Reno, Nevada soon.
Reno, Reno, Reno, Reno.
Honey, what are your favorite games to gamble on?
And do you have any strategies you can be stowed on me?
You should have said you can bar stow on me,
which is an hour out of Reno, Nevada.
Much appreciated, my friend.
Keep up the excellent work.
Oh, and I love you too, Joe.
I play Ultimate X Video Poker.
It's got a big yellow X on it.
That's where I have won my most money.
In terms of tips, you know,
these are skills accumulated over many, many years.
I also love Blackjack, but, you know, be careful.
See if you can find a $5 table to start on.
Don't sit down and start betting $50 a hand if you don't know how to play.
That's my advice.
I saw a gameplay game there that was very interesting that I had never seen before.
He would find a card table or Blackjack table, whatever it was you want to call it.
Where there would be a woman with a skirt sitting and he would play a game.
He called it how far can I get my hand up her leg before she slaps me?
And, you know, you'd bet on the increments of time.
Uh -huh.
I won big on a seven seconder.
It went long.
Yeah.
I was in there a while.
The skirt, people.
The skirt.
Oh, yeah.
Um, can you, oh, can you both a rod dot asks, can you both name a picture or two that made you cry?
Thank you.
For me, it's the end of about Schmidt and 127 hours, or the two most recent and Manchester by the sea.
Say bohemian rhapsody, which I talked about on the last pot of this, of, of this month,
And on the last episode of this month's pod, I talk about it at length, but that's the
most recent.
And so I will say that Emily Marvel, are you guys thinking of doing any live shows
in or around Chicago?
If not, when do you think your next live show will be?
That'd be my number one spot I want to go.
I fucking love Chicago.
So yes, I would love to.
Yeah, we would go off like March 8th.
And Joe and I might try to do a little tour if we can if we can.
I would love that.
Probably end in Vista Cuffs, but so what?
Which state is that in?
Folks, Jesus Christ.
Michael Rose says, Copland is an A plus agreed, but you either of you guys find it troubling
that a scene is devoted to a great figure's monologue, where he tells Freddie to be smart
to zig to zag.
Freddie then proceeds to do the least amount of zigzagging I've ever seen a hero do.
It really eats at me.
It doesn't bother me because because I think that's the point is he's not smart.
He wants to do what's good.
I think.
Well, it's that, but I also think it's the point of the end of the movie is he finally
stops listening to everybody else and does what he thinks is right, including Vegas or
whatever his name is and brings closure to the story that way.
So I think that's kind of the point is he's not supposed to take figs advice.
Yes.
Heighten Davidson says career goals for the future, you all seem so successful already.
It's always great to hear what else you're still working toward.
Great question because it also compliments me.
I am enjoying what I'm doing.
My ultimate goal in television was to run a show.
You do it.
You're not sure it's worth the squeeze sometimes rough stuff, but I'd love to get a movie made
before I die.
You know, and I haven't really been working towards that.
I would like to more same, except I'm not running a TV show, but I'm doing stand up and I'm
putting it out there, which was what the main goal was and I've gotten to do it for many
years now.
I'm very grateful, but I'm also moving towards the film area.
Kyle Kinsland asks, what is the scariest situation or story from your personal lives?
What is it?
What is the scariest situation or story from your personal lives?
For me, it was getting held up at knife point.
This guy in New York held a knife to my throat, mugged me, one of the take me to an ATM, obviously
horrified.
One to take me to dinner.
Yes.
Went to dinner, dinner was pretty good, then continued mugging me.
Mine, I mean, I'm sure there was a worse moment than this and one that actually has levity in
my life, but without wanting to get too sad or dark here, we were really high in college
and we were driving.
I was driving us to get a bond for our new apartment, and because I was so high, I stopped
dead, stopped at a green light and almost made a biker fall off of his motorcycle, and
the biker caught up to us on the highway or on the street rather, giving us the finger
repeatedly.
And at the next light he pulled over, walked over to my car and hit my window as hard as
he could with his helmet.
And when you're high, that's not fun, right?
Real scary.
Did you deserve it?
Well, yeah, I stopped at a fucking green light.
I mean, I don't mean like I was stopped at a green light, I mean, I came to a stop like it
was a red light and he almost like crashed into me because of it.
What are your and Joe's top five comedy movies of all time?
It could probably be its own episode, but I need less damage, happy holidays, thanks for
the laughs.
Top five, arguing my number one right now.
Okay, go for it.
Kingpin.
I'd have to say minus Kingpin too for just straight straight up comedy.
I've never seen Kingpin too.
Come on, Joe.
Is that a good one?
Kingpin plant strands automobiles, you know, probably either are waiting for guffin or
mighty wind, depending on my mood.
Big Lebowski is my number two odd couple sure is my number three.
Fatso is my number four.
I put raising Arizona slightly above the basket, but I love them both.
And my number five is maybe the naked gun movies.
Sure.
Couldn't argue that.
Can't handle it.
Ask who is your favorite Weasel -esque movie villain?
Not the main villain, but more along the lines of Burke and Aliens.
You're going to trigger Joe with Aliens, Tom.
Weasel, I mean, oh, not the, oh, Paul Reiser and Aliens, Paul Reiser and Aliens is a perfect
example.
I'll just steal that one.
I assume that's who you mean.
Burke is Paul Reiser.
Well, yeah.
But I mean, is he saying this?
Oh, he's, you can still name it.
I thought he was saying you.
I mean, I, he's given the perfect example as far as I'm concerned.
Weasel -y movie villain.
But not the main villain.
You know, Fredo's.
Fredo's way up there.
villain.
He tries to have his brother killed.
Oh, amongst us.
You know, but he's, he's way up there for me.
Eric Law asks if you had to cast each other in a romantic comedy, which one would it be?
I'd like to see Pat in a sort of home for the holiday style movie where he's a big city, big shot, and he has to go back to the country.
And it first he hates it, but at the end, he's learned a lesson about himself and about love.
You want me in like a hallmark, hall of fame kind of movie?
Yeah, and like maybe a Reese Witherspoon vehicle.
And quite frankly, I'd like to play the small town grease monkey that you fall in love with.
Okay.
And realize it's not about that guy in the suit who buys you all that stuff.
It's about the boy from high school that you haven't seen.
Okay.
That's my casting.
And I'd like to see Joe.
It's like Joe Deroso was always angry.
And then it's like Joe taking a sip of coffee at a New York City hot dog vendor.
And he goes, it's fucking cold and throws it in the guy's face.
And then the guy's face burns.
And it's not it's not actually cold.
Then, you know, they were like, he's bad with women.
And then you see a lady like throwing her drink in his face.
But then, and then I go, and then I go, that coffee's cold.
Yes.
Right.
But then, and then a record scratch, they say he met someone as bad as he was.
Gang, gang, gang, gang, gang, gang, and then a lady actress yet to be cast is like you but a woman.
And it's you guys are just like breaking balls.
I'm seeing a Sarah Gilbert, somebody with some dude.
I'm seeing Leslie Jones.
Yes.
Yeah.
And then of course it turns romantic.
Adam Loundsbury asked, are there any movies that truly scare you as jaded adults?
And if so, have the chills worn off after multiple viewings?
Are they still scared you every time you watch them?
Of course, I get scared all the time.
Hereditary was the most recent.
But the actresses will always be that movie for me.
And it's a re, there's, even though it's my favorite horror film ever made, there's a reason I don't watch it frequently.
And it's so that it will remain scary.
I never want to get used to it.
Bill Dawes asks, have you seen the Christmas Chronicles on Netflix yet and what do you think?
We reviewed it on an upcoming episode, or I reviewed it.
I saw it.
But yeah, it wasn't my favorite.
Chris R. Goodnight says, if I go to Vegas and bet my ass and lose, does the casino pay for LIPO or do I?
It's a casino, my friend.
It's a casino.
Thank you for your question.
If I bet my ass and lose, does the casino pay for LIPO?
You wouldn't need LIPO, you just lost your ass.
I think you're saying to suck his ass off?
Oh, I see.
I think.
Okay.
I was looking at it more figuratively.
Umur Kalakidna, I'm sorry.
Umur Kalakdina asks, when will you fellow's review the Alejandro Joderowski vehicle?
Alejandro Joderosa vehicle?
Santa Sangre on the show.
I have not seen Santa Sangre.
I despised Joderowski's holy mountain.
I love that movie.
Absolutely hated it.
And I never need to see anything he does ever again.
I'd see it.
Let's see it before fucking Sweeney Todd.
I'll tell you that much.
Sure.
Tristan Smith says, think I remember hearing you guys talk about being a marked duploss fan.
Really?
I don't remember being...
You never heard us say that.
That's never been said.
I don't think anybody's ever said that.
Nothing against the guy.
But I don't think anybody's sitting around going, man, I can't get enough duploss.
Right.
Well, he's got a brother.
I don't remember them being mentioned.
But either way, did you guys enjoy Creep 1 and Creep 2?
I only saw Creep 1 and I liked it quite a bit.
And I don't have strong feelings either way about marked duploss or his brother J duploss.
What do you guys think about mystery science theater 3000?
Do you like the old version or new version or neither or both?
I have only seen one episode of the old version.
I enjoyed it very much and I've never seen another episode.
I have not seen the new one.
I've never been a fan of the show.
I'm Jonah Ray's a friend, so I'm happy for him that he loved it so much and got to be a part of this reboot and all that.
I think that's really cool.
But the show is just not for me.
I'd rather watch the movies they watch without the riffing.
And just kind of, you know, taking how bad the movie is.
But it's just not for me.
Okay.
My dear friend Michael Curry, who I'm excited to see next week in Missouri, asks,
how do you rank the Indiana Jones movies and why?
For me, it's quite easy.
My number one is Temple of Doom because for what this franchise is supposed to be,
which is non -stop action, Temple of Doom brings the most non -stop action.
And I like the darkness of it.
I have a blast.
It's my favorite.
It's fucked up.
It's great.
My second one would be Raiders of the Lost Ark.
One of the best pure action movies ever made.
Incredible scenes in it.
Here's the Forwards Gray and it introduces the character.
Little slow in spots, but really it's just part of like a big old kind of classic old -fashioned entertain.
Last crusade.
Matches.
Almost.
Raiders.
Kind of an older little sluggisher version of it.
River Phoenix was a great addition.
Sean Conner was a great addition.
They're all three great movies.
I could see anybody having any of them as their favorite.
And then 45 miles behind them.
I'm putting the kingdoms of the crystal school.
Joe.
You said that just to piss me off.
I didn't know I said it because it's the truth.
It's not even it shouldn't be in the same breath.
For Christ's sake, you just put Temple of Doom as the best one.
That's right.
I go one, three, two, four.
And I recently rewatched Doom.
And I love Doom.
But I've also recently rewatched Crystal Skull.
And the similarities between the two films are staggering.
They go with you on that.
Equally as ridiculous.
They are equally as absurd.
They are very similar stories.
It's a very pointed, a point B kind of story.
Where they have the thing they need.
And they lose the thing they need.
And they have the thing they need.
You know, the nuke, the fridge sequences is, you know,
they jump out of a fucking plane and a raft in Temple of Doom.
And don't even break a finger after they fall.
600 feet or something.
They're not that dissimilar.
But that's what I love about the franchise.
I find that there's a pattern to them.
The first one and the third one are very much based in like sort of
Western lore.
You know, the sort of idea of the religious aspects of what
Westernized Christian and Christianity thinks about,
even though they don't take place over here.
And believes in.
And then the other two are based in different,
a different type of religious cultural lore.
And I find that interesting.
And I hope that the fifth one is great.
Luke Henderson asks, when are you going to do noises off?
I'll loan it to Joe and we'll do it.
I just rewatched it last week.
I had a blast with it.
I think it's very funny.
It wasn't as funny as when I was a little kid, but what is really?
I loved it.
Drew Tiberius Pull says, tell us your thoughts on Jeff Goldblum.
I'm a big fan, but I don't like it now that he's like in on the joke
as same with Christopher Walken.
Yeah, I agree with that.
Brittany Ferguson, you guys have any good Christmas traditions?
I see a movie every year on Christmas Day, wondering if you guys do
or have a favorite holiday movie you watch.
Mine is just a wonderful life.
No question.
I also do enjoy always a scrooge to Christmas occasion.
Try to get a grandma's in.
And I used to see five movies on the day after Christmas.
Now I got no traditions.
I go home.
Day after Christmas.
I go to the river Bocasino with my grandma and mom, my sister.
That's all I got.
That's a tradition.
My tradition is EV.
The night before Christmas Eve, me and my four best pals that I grew up with
get shit faced by doing a mall crawl.
And then we give each other presents.
It's the best night of the year.
It's a blast.
Pat, maybe one day I bring you home and make you a part of it.
You know, I'd love to be.
Christmas movie.
Look, every every Christmas day.
Rich little Christmas Carol.
You've heard me talk about it before.
And I'll be watching it again this year.
I got to see this thing.
I love it.
Alex Shipley, what's the latest in your record collections?
Could be recent stuff or old finds?
What's the what in our record latest?
I don't know about the latest, but what I've been listening to the most is
the music.
I was blown away that they just got into the rock of a Hall of Fame.
I listened to a ton of rock music these days.
It's great stuff.
I just got an original pressing 12 -inch of a song called It's Yours by
T. LaRocke and Jazzy J.
It's an old school rap song from the early 80s.
And I never had a copy of it, but they were talking about it on hip -hop.
Evolution or revolution, I can't remember the name of the show,
but Russell Simmons was talking about it on there,
and I immediately ordered it, because I wanted to have a copy of it on vinyl,
and that's my latest edition.
Timothy Atkins, why haven't you guys watched the DVD?
I sent the Joe Garth Merengue's Dark Place.
We've talked about this.
No excuses about regions.
It's Matt Berry's finest role.
I would love to watch it.
If the regions don't matter, I'll watch it.
I want to watch it.
No, the regions matter.
You can't play.
Joe says the regions matter.
You can't play it on an American player.
It doesn't work.
I tried.
It won't work.
That's a pretty valid excuse if that's true.
That's an extremely valid excuse.
Jake McAlvin says, if you were trapping a desert island together,
how many days would pass before you had sex with each other?
I think it'd be a while.
I'd say three, four hours.
Well, if somebody said, look, this is it.
Don't hold out hope.
Right.
You're here.
Three, four hours.
That's too fast for me, Joe.
I'll tell you that right now.
This is, of course, after I've treated you to a wonderful island dinner.
Okay.
You know what I mean?
I make little plates out of coconut shells.
You do kind of under the sea performance.
Yeah, yeah.
You guys.
Yeah.
I romance you.
You see that I've made a cage out of bamboo to catch our dinner is in.
Like that.
You know, that's sort of thing.
Right.
I'm not going to just go right for it.
Okay.
What's your favorite movie that takes place all in one day?
I'll say clerks.
Top of my head, I'd say do the right thing.
I will say Glen Gary Glen Ross.
That two days.
It's 24 hours.
It starts the night before around like six p .m.
And then it ends around one p .m. the next day.
So it's less than 24 hours.
Okay.
As look, Vince Lund.
Top three movies TV shows of the year.
I know you said everything stinks lately, but there should be three good things from 2018.
Oh, boy.
I haven't seen much folks to be honest with him.
My top three from 2018 solos.
My number one.
I absolutely loved it.
I still do.
I'll say Bohemian Rhapsody.
I really, really loved it.
Surprisingly, I didn't think I was going to.
And I will also say.
Mom and dad.
No, Mandy.
Mandy.
I'll put Mandy up.
Yeah.
Mandy's probably my number one.
Black Klansman.
Oh, yeah, shit.
Yeah.
That beats Bohemian Rhapsody, actually.
You know, maybe hereditary would squeak onto that list.
Stayed with me.
Oh, come on.
As far as TV shows.
I don't feel like I'm watching enough stuff.
I liked sharp objects.
I liked insecure.
You know, uh, Kaminsky method.
Big fan.
Cool kid.
Cool kids.
My favorite.
And anything Gordon Ramsey.
Okay.
Ever.
Anything.
Maureen Finn to the two of you ever go back to see if that
Bert young play got any better.
We did not regrettably.
But I did go back and read the last review that was ever posted
where somebody said.
Uh, at one point during the production, they saw the director
went on stage to stop the play and said we need 15 minutes.
And, and had to take the actors away and like regroup with them.
So I don't think I got better.
Okay.
AJ Madden says what was Pat's dad's reaction when he received
the infamous brown speckled North Face jacket.
Uh, he loved it.
He loved it.
He still wears it.
Chris Mugiel.
Any chance of doing the movie over Lord on the pod?
Yes.
But neither of us have seen it.
I came to win it seemed like.
I'm shocked we haven't seen it.
Yeah.
But yeah, it came out like.
Well, Joe, you and I have been a movie in six months.
We haven't, we haven't been anywhere in about six months.
True.
You come home from work.
It's, you know, you go, you go, you go right to the bar to make
yourself a drink.
You barely talk to me anymore.
Drew.
I've said it before in this podcast.
People I'm living with a ghost.
Drew.
Uh, when are we going on tour?
Mama's ready to start planning.
Uh, look, I'm going to need a little time off when I get off in
March.
But I'd love to do it after that.
I can't speak to it yet because I need to see what my schedule
The New Year is, but hopefully in the New Year.
Yeah.
Heath Kane says who can do the better Vincent Price impression between
Pat and Joe?
Here's a line to try.
The foulest stench is in the air.
The funk of 40 ,000 years.
Joe, you want to start?
The foulest stench is in the air.
The funk of 40 ,000 years.
Not bad.
The foulest stench is in the air.
The funk of 40 ,000 years.
Mine was terrible.
Uh, Joe wins.
We don't need to vote.
Emily rook.
Sometimes I try them and they're there and perfect.
Sometimes I try them.
I don't got it.
That was just one such example.
I don't got the prices wrong.
Yes.
Why did you two start the podcast as Emily rook?
What's the origin story?
We'll see you in hell.
We've told this bad boy on the show for sure.
But basically our old friend Pete Holmes took us out to dinner one night.
I hate when people are extra at dinner that I did not invite.
It makes me uncomfortable and anxious.
But Joe is one of the only success stories I've ever had with that hung out.
Continue to hang out, start a podcast.
It's a little more complicated than that, but yeah.
That's how we became down.
That's how I met Pat and we became friends and then Ken Hanley.
Yes.
Was asking me if I wanted to do a podcast with Fangoria.
I said, I want to do a movie commentary podcast.
Right.
And then I said, I can't do that alone.
It's too much talking.
Right.
Pat, you love movies.
You want to do this with me.
You said, sure.
Right.
And thus the show was born.
Wait for podcast companies later.
Here we are.
Tim Calb, Calb Flaish says, Joe, why don't you have a car?
He does.
I don't.
But.
How do you not know this?
I sold my car six months ago.
We've talked about it many times.
I just thought you were getting another car.
Now I sold it.
I didn't want the bill anymore.
I was like, I'm just going to Uber from now on.
And then my license expired.
I didn't know this was an official decision.
And my license expired.
So now I definitely don't have a car.
Okay.
That's why Leo Lopez says Hollywood is littered with needless sequels
and remakes.
But which horror movie would you personally feel you could add to
and try to make better as writers and directors if someone
threw a bunch of money at you?
I would love to remake evil speak.
Okay.
The Clint Howard movie.
I think it's got a really, really cool premise.
And I think that it hits pretty good in places in that movie.
There's a good atmosphere to it.
But overall, I think it kind of falls short.
And there's a lot more they could have done with it that they don't do.
And I love the idea of making one of these movies about a bullied kid
who gets his revenge by making a pact with the devil.
I love 976 evil.
Yeah.
You know, I like that premise.
So I would love to make that movie.
Look, I don't know how good I'd be as a horror director,
but I would love to do a version of it that is neither the CBS version
or the version that we just got.
Because I don't think either or anywhere close to as good as that movie should be.
So far, maybe part two will dazzle me, but I have my doubts.
Richard Howenstein asks, what podcasts would either of you most want to be a guest on?
Hope to hear another commentary episode.
We are putting one out.
You will enjoy it, dammit.
I hope.
Podcasts, I'd want to be a part on, you know, Jimmy Pardo.
I would have a blast on his show.
Love him.
I'd like to go on the Joe, the new Joe Dante podcast trailers from hell.
Yeah.
I'd very much like to go on that.
Steve Reinas asks, well, the new Godzilla movie starring 11 and the hand of the king be a piece of shit.
Yes.
I hate to rush to judgment, but I thought the first one sucked.
And this one even everybody raised about the trailers.
I'm like, you know what it's going to be guys?
Maybe you don't.
You know what I never realized was look at the posters and all the different monsters?
Yeah.
They all fly except Godzilla.
It's kind of a lack of variety for me.
Yeah.
You know, maybe you put like a crab monster in there.
Sure.
Something low to the ground.
Like give me some levels here.
It's three flying things and then Godzilla.
I don't give a shit about that movie.
I think it looks fucking stupid.
Yeah.
I think the trailers are not even a little bit intriguing.
You know, I'm just happy to see Thomas Middleditch in there.
You know, fresh off the charismatic turns and the Verizon commercials.
Now playing some sort of government expert on monsters or something.
And just nothing.
Nothing makes me die from my remote faster than one of those commercials.
It's the worst things I've ever seen.
Yeah.
And then like I'm watching like his is a clip him on Larry King where he's like McDonald's
took a parody song you did and actually used it.
And he's like in the middle is like, yeah, I made fun of this.
McDonald's songs.
I thought it was like super tramp this ad they did because I thought it was super transparent.
Like how hard they were trying to play the urban crowd.
And it was just ridiculous.
So I made fun of it.
Then they bought it and used it.
And it's like, I'm sorry.
Did McDonald's not delve as deep as the Verizon ads where you're buying a Sunday.
On a truck.
Where does it go in my belly?
Never met the guy.
Probably never will.
I saw him in the improvised Shakespeare company thing in LA and I've never hated something more.
Never hated something more.
Yeah.
And I mean, like, and also another casting thing with that Godzilla movie.
And it drives me nuts.
It's like they throw Millie Bobby Brown like in the forefront on the foreground of this fucking trailer.
And they have her doing nothing.
And it's one of these things where you're literally supposed to just be excited that you see a face of a kid from stranger things.
Right.
And it's like, I'm sorry.
That's not enough to make me want to see a movie.
Right.
It's just not enough.
You know, it's just, it just looks like a dumb, bad fucking movie.
And the Kong skull island stunk.
Godzilla one stunk.
How is this going to be any better?
And then they're going to cross the two over.
Oh, fucking joy to the world on that.
Can't wait for that fucking universe to happen.
Every version of King Kong sucks.
And I might go back to the original 1933 classic.
It's boring.
I like the original.
It's got a charm to it.
I like the Peter Jackson one.
It's not bad.
Oh, Joe.
I only saw it once in the theater.
Sucks.
I got to say I never wanted to see it ever again.
No.
Jack Black.
The hero.
It was beauty killed the beast.
Will Potorff asks, do you think it's possible to ever make a decent video game movie?
Or should they leave well enough alone?
Also, Joe, I wanted to ask, what was it like to be in Grand Theft Auto 5?
I have no interest in video game movies pretty much ever.
And I can't think of one that I ever thought was great to be honest with you.
So, no.
I have little, also have very little interest in adaptations of video games to screen.
I have a little bit more interest in adaptations of movies to video games, but not much.
Look, I'm sure it could be done.
But, you know, you're, you're, and I'm not the first person to make this observation.
I have a lot of the, some of the people that I, I follow a lot of video game channels on YouTube.
And this observation has been made by gamers more astute and informed than I am.
But, you know, the argument kind of always is.
It's like, look, you're taking an immersive 40 -hour experience that you're involved in.
And then they try to translate it into a 90 -minute thing that you spectate.
It's just never going to work.
It's just not going to be anywhere near as cool or as interesting.
And being in Grand Theft Auto 5 was awesome.
That was a dream come true to being a game like that.
That series, even though they're not my style of game, you know, that series is like the Godfather of video games to me.
You know, it's up there with Mario and Donkey Kong.
And, you know, it's a classic.
Tuben.
Mappy.
But, no, it was, it was an amazing, amazing experience.
And super fun.
They're good guys over there at Rockstar.
Luke Physioc says, best non -sexual nude scene in a movie.
I mean, one for like the pure shock value of it was that dude chasing Paul Jimati and Thomas Hayden Church out of his house in sideways, naked.
That's pretty great.
That was like before when Dick Comedy was in.
You just didn't see Dick's on screen.
And it was crazy. Funny scene.
That's pretty great.
The dick scene in Hall Pass is pretty great.
Which is just like hanging next to Owen Wilson's face.
Right.
Anything with the dick really is just, it's very funny to me.
Yeah.
Steve Murdoch says, Pat, will you ever have Joe on Cool Kids?
I would absolutely love to.
We'd have to get a season two.
It is difficult to get young people onto the Cool Kids, but I would love to.
Yes.
Maybe I could play.
Let me pitch you something here.
Maybe I play a guy who's out on his luck and he's trying to figure out a way to, like a scheme, like a bosom buddy style thing where he's trying to live in the home.
Okay.
But he's too young.
We discuss something like this.
So he pretends to be old.
He was doing it to bang old chicks.
But we were throwing around the name David Spade.
That's even better.
Well, I mean, let's not get carried away here.
Spades had enough.
Can I fucking get a piece of this fucking business already?
Yes, you can get a piece.
Jesus Christ.
I think we have hit them all except what's the scariest horror movie franchise?
Well, franchise complicates it because there's scariest films and then there's, if you're going to say franchise, you then have to say war all, you know, is the average movie in that franchise scary.
Right.
Which makes it tough because franchises, as we all know, really fall apart at the fucking seams, right?
You know, look, I'd put Psycho up there.
Yeah, solid.
Certainly solid.
I think as far as genuine scares created by a long -running horror franchise, there's very few.
Very few.
Psycho maintains, through the first three movies, maintains that creepiness of like,
is this fucking guy dressing up as his mother and then killing?
Like, it is, it's unsettling.
You know, look, if you, you know, I talk about creep show all the time on here and how I think that the first three, or that excuse me, that the third movie is official, is, is tells in the dark side of the movie.
I'd say all three creep shows have legit scares in them and legit dread.
You know, the first film, you know, you get it with, with the lonely death of Jordy Vero.
That, that, that haunts me terribly.
The second one, the raft is a really intense sequence.
And then the third one, like, lovers vow is, you know, so creep show, I guess.
Okay.
Did you answer already?
I forget what you said.
I, I didn't really.
I mean, I, I guess if we're gonna count manhunter, silence of the lambs, and Hannibal.
Sure.
And maybe toss Red Dragon in there, which was average.
I think that's a really solid horror franchise.
All right.
That counts to me.
Folks.
That's the bonus for this.
Happy holidays to you.
Enjoy your Christmas.
Enjoy your Hanukkah, your Kwanzaa, your New Year's Eve, your New Year's Day.
We don't plug on these.
We just want to thank you for your generosity throughout the year.
For keep throwing us a bone.
Let's keep this thing going.
We appreciate it.
We really do.
We're overwhelmed by the support from everybody out there listening.
Thank you for all of it.
And thank you for giving a little extra to get these special episodes.
And we, we would love to give back to you in some way.
I don't know.
It's getting weird.
Sorry.
I got swept up in the Christmas spirit there for a second.
All right.
Christmas only comes once a year, babe.
See you later.
Later.