a
Oh boy, we're back here and we'll see you in hell on the new and improved we'll see
you in hell where we now record with the Zoom Pro. I just got a really nice prompt when I hit the record button and it said,
would you like to record to your computer or to the cloud? That's never the cloud, but that's a new option.
That's what the pro life entails. You make the choices. You make the calls.
Yes, folks, we're talking today about the film Elvis, right?
You know, I'm you. I used to watch at Blockbuster video when I was closing up the store.
We would watch Elvis Aloha from Hawaii, which was a con. They mentioned it in the movie.
It was a concert that went out via satellite all across the globe. It's Elvis with his shirt opened about to his dick and a lay.
He's so piled out and sweaty that you feel like he's not going to make it to the end of the show.
At one point that part that made my friends left the hardest is he would pull his jumpsuit to the left revealing his tit.
Yeah, and then hit his left hit with the microphone. The sound would go just clearly the actions of a man who does not know how to turn on a crowd anymore, but it was amazing.
And then when he's doing suspicious minds, he keeps going lower and lower. He's going, I hope my suit don't tear up, baby, you got a sense of humor about himself.
I like it. Gross. And that's how I like it. They really in the Elvis film, I turned to the person I was seeing it with at about the two hour mark.
And I was like, I guess we're just pretending that Elvis never put on any weight because throughout Elvis looks like he's a trim 150 and then for a little bit at the end, they beat him up and add a layer of sweat and glazed to his forehead.
Yeah, they bring it in where it counts. They give it to you right when you need to see it. I was watching a clip on YouTube. Yes, by the way, I can't find the other half of the last episode we recorded.
So that'll be a fun cursing at the computer scavenger hunt. As soon as we finish here, you didn't have pro before. I won't be an issue going forward.
Well, what if it's gone? I swear to God, if we have to re -record the second half of that fucking episode, Joel, kill myself. I will kill myself. Then, then, then, let's hope we do. We had a great conversation about the film. No, I love every time we talk about a movie, there's somebody who's like, so you just missed that fraction of a second, second shot where we cut to the Daniel Kaluah character, remembering his child.
You know, that whole thing. There's always somebody in the comments who's like, so you just didn't pay attention during the incredibly brief moment where that was all explained. No, I didn't, I guess, I guess I didn't.
People really, they like to push, baby, they like to push. I just posted a review from taste buds. Yeah.
Somebody gave us a once. See, now, here's the thing.
It was just generally sour chicken versus beef and broccoli for our episode. What'd you do?
I got a good dig on Steve burn the other day. Okay. He said, we were on a good dig on David burn the other day. I said, you need that biggest suit to dance around in.
I said, Steve had a sick, I'm called solid and son, but we were to thread me and sell and Steve burn and Steve took a shot at me and he goes, oh, I can't wait to hear your take on Triskets this week.
Right. And I said, just for that, Steve, I'm canceling my Amazon order of Sullivan and son the complete half season.
Did he enjoy that? He did very much. It was a good.
But I've noticed some, some comedy people you joke about, something being canceled and they just don't get the laughs.
I, your, your, your boy, Bill Burr, I always reference this, this exchange where I was like, whatever happened to that show, whatever, and I brought up two different shows.
And he goes, Jesus Christ, you want to bring up every fucking failure? Have I had my fucking life?
Is that what we're going to talk about every fucking thing I ever did fucking wrong?
I was like, sorry, Bill, can I buy you a drink? I like your comedy.
He works, he's working through a few things sometimes.
Look, really, I love the man and he's been fairly nice to me. This was just a couple, we had a couple exchanges where I was like, okay, we don't joke about the projects that didn't go.
Which I get, it's never fun to joke about, even though your friend, you know, comedians are more used to that.
I have a very thin skin that I try, I try to get over from being bullied.
I hear you, I hear you, I, I, oh, oh, what I was going to say was, I will get annoyed at some comments that Helian's make at times.
But I almost always let it go because I'm like, you know, they're paying for the product.
They're entitled to their opinion. You can, you can.
Paying for the product gives you a little more room to criticize does, I'm not saying I'll listen to it.
I just saying it goes without, you know, vitriol, but taste buds.
100 % free is this show was for many years, right? So when I see a negative, I can deal with a negative comment.
This set me off, somebody leaves us a one star review and goes about the shows gone downhill.
They talk for 40 minutes before they get to the food battle. It's a food show guys get to the battle.
And I screen -capped it and I just put it on Instagram and I was like, you know, guys, I usually don't talk about stuff like this, but just imagine being this sad in life.
Like this miserable that you're going to leave a one star review fuck up our rating because you don't like the way we handled an episode of a podcast.
You get for free the entitlement of people. It's nuts. Yeah, it's nuts.
I mean, it's just and then most people were like, yeah, that's sucks. That's lame. And then one guy writes, he's got a point.
First of all, as a woman, he's got a point.
Worst episode yet. You guys are eating french fries a little time. He's talking about the wrong episode.
She was complaining about.
Also, it could have very well been an episode about eating french fries. Why would that have been so unusual?
Yeah, the episode we ate french fries on it was when they threw me a surprise McDonald's birthday party and bought us happy meals and we were eating french fries.
Because I talk about McDonald's all the time. He's actually very charming and sweet. And this guy's going to hate everybody so much.
But on a funny note, yeah, I saw an Elvis YouTube video. I didn't forget.
From a documentary they put out in the early eighties called this is Elvis. Yes.
And he's dead at this point, but in the video, he's not of the footage. He's in the back of his like car going to the show, I guess. Yeah.
And he's with his whole crew.
And the driver goes or Elvis is like, you know, how's everybody's day today or whatever. And then the driver goes, did you see the launch?
The missile launch and the and I was like, what launch? What launch? And then one of his friends goes, I enjoyed my launch. It was around 1230 makes a dumb lunch show. Right.
And then he goes, how was your launch, Elvis? And he goes, I was right in the middle of a beaver at about 1230 p .m. today, right?
Meaning he's fucking somebody. Yeah. Okay. And the guy goes, the guy goes, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, buddy.
They're recording us for the documentary. Yeah. And he goes, he goes, well, they're filmin' this thing. Got his mic. They can't hear us.
And the guy goes, there's a mic right above your head. And he looks up and sees a tiny mic. And he just goes, he starts laughing. And he goes, oh, you sneaky bastards.
And then he just goes, he starts singing and he's going, Jesus, say and start singing like a gospel song. Yeah, probably out of shame. God damn, he's really funny, man. It's really fucking funny guy.
The movie didn't have to pick that way. No, I adore Elvis. I've seen everything he's ever committed to film. I was big into him as a kid for whatever reason.
I read his, you know, there's a really great two -part biography of him basically devoted to the 10 years and the fat years.
And yeah, we'll get to the movie, but he was funny. And he was a great actor. And, you know, even though the movie was all about the Colonel not letting him do what he wanted to do, it still didn't quite cover how much he fucked up Elvis's career.
But I love Elvis. And my, my other favorite moment in one of the documentaries is that his band talked about his issues with eating.
And how he would just eat and eat and couldn't stop. And he would, he would get a dozen donuts and bring them on a flight and eat the donuts, you know, just like that was his thing.
So that was the story. This guy, his name was Charlie Hodge. He was mentioned in the movie. He's one of his like band guys. And guy with it. We know one of those giant heart attack guts as well.
But he goes, yeah, you know, he always brings a dozen donuts on the flight.
It's just down in first class. He couldn't have been more charming and funny. But then the mood darkened because it wasn't five minutes. We were up in the air. And those donuts were out of sight. He had eaten all 12 of the donuts.
And he goes, and this was a common thing that Elvis would say he pushed the donuts box away from him himself.
And he goes, ah, what the hell did I just do? What the hell did I just do? That is my favorite thing to say when I eat too much is an Elvis voice. What the hell did I just do?
That makes me sad that he did that. He had no self control, but he was piled out of his fucking mind, you know, because of the Colonel. He didn't care that he was in pain. Get him up on that stage, baby.
And honestly, this is what I talked about the Joe with Joe. We've got all these think pieces about how nope is about the only thing that I've really really seen people take a shot that they know that that's that it's what it's about is the entertainment industry.
Chewing people up spitting them out. Meanwhile, next door at the multiplex, you've got Elvis a three hour movie specifically about that exact theme, how the entertainment industry treats you like a prop. They don't care about you. They just want you up on that stage.
They pull the theme through from start to finish beautifully.
And I don't see Elvis getting a lot of praise quite frankly. It's doing well at the box office and I'm happy for it.
But it's like you're in critically decent. You know, I think it's doing pretty well. It's a it's a biopic. I'm not a biopic guy and they thought that after walk hard we wouldn't be seeing a lot more of these.
Because walk hard is a pretty brilliant parody of this kind of movie. But bohemian rhapsody, which everyone made fun of and granted could have been a better made film.
But I loved it. I had a great time with it. There's something about hearing 50 great songs tied to cool visuals that I'm not going to pretend I don't enjoy.
But Elvis I actually thought was a really good film. Maybe Bos Lerman's best film. We'll get to it. We'll get to it.
Yes, we will get to it. Now what are your I'm intrigued as to why you needed your own special movie corner. What what what what three is there is there a theme you have today.
No, no, I didn't need a special movie. No, no, no, I didn't mean I just meant I only had three things that I had watched. And if I blew them on that episode, I wouldn't have him for this one. And I felt like I had a lot more to say about nope.
Yes, and I did about Elvis. So so I wanted to save him for Elvis. I knew I had a scary stuff up my sleeve.
So that that's all I meant by that. But I'll start if you want.
Go for it. I watched I rewatched big. Yeah, you said I want to I want a Robert Lozia comedy.
Pat, I think I'm coming out of it.
And it could be that I transitioned off of my meds. And it could be that I was also turning 45 and it could be a lot of things. But I was in a stage there for a few weeks.
I was crying left and right. I couldn't stop crying. And anything in that I saw in a movie that was even vaguely sentimental or heartbreaking. It would set me off.
And I watched big one night I couldn't sleep. I threw it on the iPad. I thought I'll fall asleep to this. It's familiar to watch it start to finish.
Wept endlessly through the movie.
F .A .O. Schwartz scene got me there when they're doing the piano thing.
Because it was so sweet and innocent. And I'm just going this fucking shit world. We live it isn't like this.
It's a wonderful movie. It's it's much like I get up on the giant keyboard at F .A .O. Schwartz. They shoot me in the fucking head.
It's true. They would shoot you in the head if you jumped up on it now.
It's an odd. It's it's it's I have a lot to say about big. It's a movie about a 11 year old boy fucking a 35 year old woman for start.
But yeah, sale. Yeah. That's wild.
There's stuff in there I appreciate it way more.
There's directing choices that make no sense to me. That might have just been things because Penny Marshall is a great director.
But there are like there's like fade to black moments. You know, you're like that was the transition.
You know, Bobby De Niro actually shot scenes of big and they decided to go a different way.
That would have been a horrible movie. Yeah, I don't think that was his his project. I love Bobby. But that's like when they put him in Mary shells Frankenstein. That was yeah. What are you doing? Yeah, yeah.
This is nuts. Anyway, um,
that first of all, they nail in that opening montage. They nail what it was like for me to be a kid in that time period.
I was 12 when I saw big. I that was it. Yeah, the baseball cards, the playing baseball in the in the park together.
There, the riding the bikes, the walkie talkies, the toys, like I was just like my God, the school yard crush, they just nail that friendship and what it was exactly like to be a kid in the suburbs at that time period.
I loved, you know, Tom Hanks is wonderful in it. Obviously Penny Marshall is great. I don't know who wrote the script. I choose a great director.
Elizabeth Perkins is is lovely and looks freakishly like Millie Bobby Brown throughout the move. It's very strange to me. Elizabeth Perkins was a big star. She I guess her TV great success was weeds where she was very funny.
She was in every movie for a while. She played fucking Betty Rubble or Wilma one or the other in the Flintstones.
But like she's on Barry. I didn't even realize that was her on Barry. So she's been acting for ages. But really a true character actress. Nobody knows the name Elizabeth Perkins. You know what I mean?
It's not a household name. She's had a very interesting career because as I'm looking here, she's worked endlessly a lot of voice work.
And at the same time she never really had her day in the sun. She followed big with nothing. She didn't act for years after big until the Flintstones and anything major.
I just looked her up on Twitter and while she loved to see it, you and Elizabeth Perkins follow each other.
Oh nice. You follow Elizabeth Perkins. I think she followed me first. Why wouldn't you? Yeah, you got to follow back.
And she's like tweets that I've put up. You know usually like ones that are a little more political based. Still a lovely, lovely looking woman and still acting.
But you know, it's interesting. She's in like she was on curb and she didn't play herself. She played like fun counselors new girlfriend. Remember? Yeah. Yes.
So anyway, she's, she's wonderful in it. But I got to tell you I missed it the first time around first few times around on big.
John heard is so fucking funny in this movie. Like on her. Okay. All right.
That's seen where they play racquetball. And Tom Hanks is like, no, you said if it goes on the point, there's no way it's not funny. And John heard it's like, I never said that.
Give me the, give me the goddamn boy a little bit like he is so fucking funny. That's seen with her drunk on the martinis at the Christmas party.
He's bitching about the company. He's so funny in it. Love it's home run. Love it isn't big. Love it's places cubicle mate. Okay. The guy that sits right next to him.
Okay. Yeah. Love it's as hilarious. And then Kevin meanie.
And he was in it either. I got to watch I own it in a nameless role just executive number whatever. Yeah.
Has one of the funniest lines in the movie. And it's not a funny line. But it's testament to how funny Kevin meanie is that he gets a laugh out of this line.
There's a scene where John heard is pitching a robot that turns into a skyscraper because they're talking about how transformers are so popular. Yes.
And Tom Hanks is like, I don't get it. He's like, why does it turn into a building who wants something that turns into a building like I don't know.
Like why wouldn't you have it turned into like a prehistoric bug or something with big claws and it could like kill stuff.
And everybody in the meeting starts going crazy and it cuts to Kevin meeting.
He just got this. It's this is what comedic geniuses. He knows the inflection that's funny. He goes. Yeah.
So the robot turns into a bug.
And you're like, of course, a stupid, more on executive. Yeah.
The simplest fucking thing in the world. You know, discovering it as he says it.
And you're just there was just so much shit in it that I caught like that. I love the kid that plays the friend.
And, you know, the kid that plays his best friend. Yeah, he plays an asshole in every fucking movie he's ever in.
But he's great.
And just wild scenes where they're put the emotions they're blending.
He calls his mom and pretends to be a kidnapper.
So he can tell her that he's okay. Yes.
Which is wild. And then they play it for jokes. And then he goes.
She goes.
He goes ask me something that only he could answer and I'll answer it.
And she goes, what song did I sing him when he was little to go to sleep?
And then time I was like, isn't there anything else you want to ask besides that?
And then the joke is he has to sing the song at work. And it looks like an idiot. Right.
So then he does it. And you're like supposed to think that's funny. Obviously. Yeah.
And then it's cutting back to by the way, Mercedes rule who plays the mother, which I forgot love Mercedes rule.
She was on dog broke girl. She was fantastic. She's great.
Cuts back to her. She's crying her eyes out Devastating because she thinks her son has been kicked back. Right.
It's heartbreaking. Then it's cutting back to Hank singing the song and love it's looking over at him.
Like what the fuck is wrong with you? Wild stuff.
Yeah. Wild. Like wild, wild stuff. And then of course, as you pointed out, he's 13.
And he fucks Elizabeth Burkins at one point. Right. And when she accepts that he is a kid and he's telling the truth, she's not like.
There's not a second of oh my god, I can't believe I had sex with a 13 year old. It's just straight up just like.
You know, your life's tough. And I love you. And I hope I wish you the best. And that's it.
But man, when he started walking down the street and then turns into the kid again.
It was water works. It was water works in the bedroom that night. And then.
You're a jack. Oh my god. I almost started crying just now. Just talking about it.
Then the two of them walking together as friends again. Yeah. Yeah.
It devastated me. Well, you concerned me because I was going to see Elvis. And you were like, I wept throughout.
And then at the end, you talked about having to run ahead of your parents because you were crying so hard.
I've only had a run of run ahead of the group experience twice. Once was about Schmidt with my friends in college.
At the end, I was I was overcome with emotion and it was bad. And then out here in LA was 127 hours. Both movies about emotionally closed off men.
Learning a lesson about how to connect and both destroyed me.
I did keep it together for Elvis. But I, you know, it was a really moving movie. And we'll get there.
I rewatched a film that it's strange with each viewing. It sort of gets funnier to me. And yet it also gets more sad to me. I rewatched waiting for government.
It does to take a different tone as you get older. It does when I think of all of my friends who were so talented who never had their day in the sun.
And I'm from Missouri. You know, when I think of my friends back when I live there would be in these little theatrical productions. And there's the kids who would think that who would believe that like they have a shot of getting to Broadway.
Like that everybody, you know, the only negative reviews of Christopher guest stuff is always like that he's mean and looking down on his characters.
I just think it couldn't be farther from the truth. I mean they they do put them through the ringer. But there are people like this. And I love all of them. They're delusional.
But, you know, the the will, sorry Fred Willard and Catherine O 'Hara marriage with each viewing becomes darker and darker to the point now that I'm willing to call this one of the darkest marriages in film history.
Willard and Catherine O 'Hara. She's talking about the extensive two hour note sessions he gives her when they do scene studies at home. This is his wife and they do community theater.
So that's that's very funny. And at the same time, Oh, Hera is playing nothing throughout the film except absolute misery at the marriage that she is stuck with and the goon that she is with.
And it's funny as Fred Willard is making jokes to you know he makes fun of Eugene levy the whole movie and levy when you watch it again and again is at first he's doing a big fake laugh to fit in with everybody.
And by the end he's like, Oh, you and then Willard makes fun of him and you just see him like break. It's a it's an amazing move. They took it to its furthest point in terms of the sadness of the comedy in a mighty win.
Mighty win does make me cry every time I watch. But this movie that the stuff they're doing with these characters is so fucking dark and depressing.
And also super, super funny. I just the quirky St. Clair character the guy who's in love with quirky St. Clair who works as the pharmacist, but he's also a councilman who was also married with a kid and you can tell he would give anything to suck quirky off.
I mean it's a I couldn't believe this thing. I've seen it so many times, but it just keeps taking on like added depth. I think it is an excellent comedy one of our great comedies one of our most influential comedies and the cast is just nothing but ballers.
I mean, Parker Posey almost steals the thing out from levy guest Willard. She's incredible. Oh, Hera.
And as they got bigger and added more people to the cast, you know, I love I love a lot of what guest has done. Don't get me wrong. But there's something really pure and wonderful about waiting for government. Have you never seen check it out, baby?
I watched a movie. I finally, I think I've talked about it and scary stuff, but I finally watched my blue ray of death trap.
Never seen it. Don't spoil it because I know it's got a big twist. I don't spoil it, please. I own it.
It doesn't I won't spoil it. It has a decent twist. Oh, okay. It's not that crazy of a twist, but I did ruin it for myself because I was reading about knock knock, which is the remake.
I think I think I'm going to make.
You like raw feed with me on a remake of death trap. Yeah.
Keanu Reeves and then what's your name Marilyn Monroe?
Marilyn Monroe.
The chick that plays Marilyn Monroe. Oh, Anna the armist. Yeah, yeah.
Wait, are you saying there's a lot of fucking in this movie in death trap? Yeah.
Knock knock was all about fucking. It's the same exact thing basically. It's a remake, but I mean, I was reading it because I was like, you know, it's a pretty sadistic crazy movie.
And I was like, how much did they change? I wonder in this Hollywood remake and I was reading. I was like, Oh, not much.
And then I read the ending thinking, well, clearly they're going to change that. Yeah.
And then I, and then when I was watching death trap, I had already read the ending of knock knock, and then I was like, Oh, it's not that different. It's kind of the same thing.
But so I don't, I don't have much to say it's, it's a really great little cult movie.
And it's got a much bigger following that I knew than I knew it had.
You know, I bought it because I read about it in.
What's it called? Rumorg magazine.
Okay. And a Fangoria type deal.
Yeah, it's Rumorg magazine is a.
It's a, it's a, it's a, yes, yes, like a Fangoria, there's nothing more to say.
I know why I'm trying to cap, you know, explode on that.
I like it better than Fangoria because Fangoria seems to only focus. I even read Fangoria in years, especially now because it's 1999 an issue, which I'm sure is not all Fangoria's fault.
I'm sure a lot of that has to do with this crumbling fucking society we live in.
Yeah.
But Fangoria that I know focused almost primarily on movies.
That's where I was kind of a big deal and Ken Hanley was like, I'm going to, we're going to start a podcast thing like right.
You know, but it was mainly movies. Rumorg, there's a section about like horror relate. There's a music section and it'll focus on like metal releases that month and all that.
There's a collectible section. There's, there's a movie section. There's like breakdowns on like cult classics. It's awesome.
But they, they always highlight. There's a thing called like unearthed or something where they highlight.
Here's a movie that everybody thought was lost forever.
Uh -huh. That is actually getting a proper release finally and death trap was one of them and it stars.
The lady that was married to Clint Eastwood.
And then it starts the lady that plays the maid in.
Clue.
She plays the French maid in clue.
What, what movie are we talking about? Death trap.
With Mike Kane and Chris Reed. No.
Oh, death game. Oh my God.
Dear God.
Death game.
Death game. It's called sorry, excuse me.
Hell's death game.
It's it's the movie knocked out because we make up with. Oh, now I understand. So this, this is why I was confused. Joe, you were saying the wrong title.
I was like, there's no way knock knock has anything to do with death trap.
Uh, okay. Yeah. That's why you said there's a big twist ending. I was like, that really.
This is cool. I mean, but, yeah.
Well, looking now, uh, a contributor to the story of death game, Don Bluth, the animator of secret of them.
It's crazy.
It's a crazy little picture.
Uh, I got it right here. Hold on.
If I didn't mention it on a different episode, it's Grindhouse releasing is who did it. They did a really beautiful job.
If you buy the, the special release Blue Ray, you actually get a key chain. That's a hatchet.
That sense or cleaver that says death game.
Um, it's what is her name.
Okay, see more castles stars. Love them. Also a great tiny part in honeymoon in Vegas, telling an Asian Elvis to shut the fuck up.
Yes. Sandra lock and Colleen camp. Yeah. Colleen camp, who was quite a like sex pot in her day.
Used to get her mixed up with Donna Dixon, the divorce Danny accurate.
Uh, and, uh, it's about a married, a happily married man.
Who his wife goes away to, to, to, to, to nurse their son through, uh, getting his appendix removed, I believe it is.
Okay.
And, uh, he's home alone in their big, beautiful house. These two lovely, young, intriguing girls show up, soaking wet during a rainstorm.
They ask if they can use the phone. He's very nice. He lets them in. He's like, hey, um, you're soaking wet.
I'll, you seem like nice girls. I'll dry your clothes for you, whatever.
They disappear into his house. He doesn't know where they are. He goes upstairs, new his bathroom.
They're in their naked in the tub. And they're like, come on. And he's like, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, girls get dressed.
And they lure him in. Eventually he breaks as any man would and has a wild threesome with them.
And then the next day, they won't, he's like, what have I done? Right.
And they won't leave. And they're being really gross that I'm not just during breakfast and he freaks out and he's like, you guys are out of here.
And then they start the game of, you know, they, they, he gets them out of the house. They come back and they're like, we're fit. We're only 15. You're fucked. Yeah.
And then they tie him up. And it's just, it's a wild flick, but a hell of a hell of a ride.
Sex, nudity.
Oh yeah.
You get to see Colleen Camp in all their glory naked, which I've wanted to see since I was 11 years old. And they're first or clue.
Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. It's, it's, it's, it's a, it's a fun movie. I mean, fun. It's dark. It's, it's a creepy movie. But it's, you know, it sounds great. I, I, I, I'm glad we got past that confusion and it reminded me that I need to watch death trap before somebody spoils it for me.
Yeah. Oh, good.
I saw a criterion picture I've had in my collection for a while. It is streaming on the criterion channel. It is called Valerie and her week of wonders.
Yes.
It is a checkle Slovakian horror film. So it is horror because it's sort of horror is fairy tale is, it's got a lot of different, you know, I wouldn't put it closer to a fairy tale, but there are several encounters with a demon like man who looks like Nosferatu with like the freaky teeth who's trying to rape a young woman throughout.
Valerie is having her sexual awakening while also being pursued for these magic earrings that she has that is where the fairy tale aspects comes in.
There are some like demon type creeps who are always trying to like come up behind her and take these earrings and it also seems like maybe they're trying to take her virginity.
And you know, it's a horny strange uncomfortable movie.
I looked up the young lady and I was like, you know, we're seeing a lot of this young girls flesh and I'd love to just look up and confirm that she was of age when the movie was produced.
I went to the Wikipedia page where I learned that she was 13 years old at the time of filming, often totally naked in the movie.
And I don't know criteria on it seems a weird thing to be coming out with.
Maybe criteria is doing it because they get banned. I don't know they also have salo in the collection.
But yeah, I don't see that salo.
How would you say it, Salo?
I thought it was salo. I'll take either. I'll take either.
So will I, Pat?
It's just I will.
An hour into a 70 minute movie. You don't want to learn that the naked girl you've been looking at is 13. It was a weird feeling.
I had a much better experience with red rocket where I'm watching this girl have sex for an hour and a half.
I look it up and realize that she's 24. It's like, okay, great.
That's how they do things now and I think a better way to do things personally.
But I agree.
The movie is weird. It's like a hallucination of sorts.
There aren't a lot of answers online. There's a lot of the movie doesn't really make sense. It's a fairy tale. You got to go with the fairy tale logic, etc.
You know, there is a lot of cool shots in the movie and in terms of something I haven't seen before. Yeah, I'll give it to Valerie and her week of wonders.
It was a really weird movie and very short and felt like an adult episode of that like Shelley Devall fairy tale theater in a way.
I'm not upset. I watched it. Not something I'd watch again. And not something I'd recommend to anyone because you don't want to be recommending movies with naked 13 year old girls to people in your life.
It's just not a good look.
Speak for yourself.
Yeah.
But you know, kind of cool in spots. Nothing you need to say.
Which brings us to wait. I had one more. I'm sorry. I'm sorry, but I don't actually don't want to do it. I just want to mention it. I watched the blob my criterion of the blob.
But I don't want to review it.
I was going to, but I'd actually like to do an episode where we do the original blob and the blob remake.
I own them both and I'd love nothing more.
Good. Yeah. All right. Anyway, let's get down to the nitty gritty.
We're talking Elvis.
For me, just sort of a casual realization I had this morning when I woke up and thought about Elvis is that I think it's my favorite movie of the year, which is not even necessarily some big rave.
I just thought that it really worked.
It is a biopic that embraces the form.
It's not trying to reinvent the wheel and not certainly in the way I thought bas lerman would.
My experience with with the man in the past is I kind of like this first movie, strictly ballroom, put him on the map.
You know, Romeo and Juliet.
Look, I admire you going out of your way to make it not a boring retelling of that story, but it was so hyperactive that it eventually made me exhausted.
Mulan Rouge made me exhausted after two and a half hours in the theater.
I was like, it's too much. It's too much. Too many cuts.
Too much food. Not enough rouge. I used to say exactly.
There's great stuff in it, but it just like when a movie will not relax for a second, it bothers me. It's too much.
This movie is sort of a more, I mean, then you got Australia, which is not a good film by any stretch.
I didn't really watch the get down on Netflix.
The man's got a career of things I sort of admire, but nothing I really loved.
I did love Elvis. It is shot and edited in a very kind of cool, frenetic way.
But you always know where you're at in terms of the timeline, even as it jumps all over the place.
You've got a truly incredible performance from Austin Butler, who is not somebody I'm familiar with.
He's a beautiful looking man, and it's kind of crazy that you just accept him as Elvis.
Even when Kurt Russell played Elvis, you knew you were watching a guy play Elvis.
He just becomes Elvis. His impression is amazing.
It's similar to what Jamie Foxx did in Ray, where it is an impression, but it's also like, you feel like you're watching the soul of the guy.
Tom Hanks, there's too much Hanks, frankly, as this kind of job of the hut -esque representation of the disgustingness of the entertainment industry.
But that's its story. The story is how these gross talentless hacks in their pursuit of money,
steamroll, any sense of art, even in people who are unquestionably among the great artists of their generation.
I loved everything about it. Joe, your thoughts.
I, as you know, initially had no interest in seeing this movie. We made quite a bit of fun of it.
Yeah, especially. Yeah, and my buddy Steve Verne, who I was just talking about, he said, did you see Elvis?
And I went, no. And he goes, dude, I saw three times. And I was like, what?
Three times. He goes, I saw three times. I go, what are you talking about? It's good. And he goes, it's fucking amazing.
And I was like, it is. And he was like, dude, it's amazing. Yeah.
And he kept saying the end, the end. I was like, all right. So I was like, that's perfect.
I'm going to see my parents in a few days. I'll take them to see Elvis. I took them in. I was excited.
And from the jump I was in. I loved every minute. He did so much shit that I hate usually in biopics in new, new -fangled biopics.
Yeah. Using music from a future error, like putting hip -hop into the Elvis movie.
Yeah. It works so well in this. It really did. And when they do the triple diploma screen of Elvis singing, that's all right.
Elvis as a boy, seeing a black blues artist play that's all right. And then the black blues artists play it.
It's like, we're not showing away from the fact that Elvis made black music pletable to an entire generation of people.
And that's why he was as successful as he was. But they acknowledged it, but not in the preachy shit way that I fully expected it to.
They just were like, watch, look how Elvis being raised around black music changed and shaped the way he performs. And it was done beautifully. And I thought.
I like to I like to that he's met with the racism.
They show that he's met with racism for doing it. I like that he that he continually champions the black artists that influenced him that he did remakes of their stuff.
But anyway, there was there was tons of stuff that I hate a character addressing camera.
Like you said, that the split screen stuff sequences where all of a sudden it's like a parody of like a movie opening. Right.
It's all these things they do in modern biopics that I usually load.
He did them with perfect execution every minute of it worked.
I loved every waking second of this. And I knew I was going to love the movie.
When they did the build up to the first time you see Elvis, they build up to him like he's like Batman or something. Yeah, like you only see him in shadows and like all this stuff.
And then the first time you see him is on stage. And he chokes in front of the audience and everybody's like heckling him. And then he like has that moment where he grabs the mic.
And goes where they show it a little bit up in the trailer and it launches in and it's so awesome. And you're just like, this is awesome. I'm so in for this.
You know, there were exaggerated things in this that that still have me scratching my head a bit.
The main one being Tom Hanks' take on how the Colonel spoke. I looked up some interviews of Colonel Tom Parker.
He's just sounds like a normal guy from America. Like he doesn't sound. He doesn't have this weird hybrid accent. Why do you think then he made him like a Dutch weird gold member type character.
It was it was very gold number. It was that I think I tell him the crypt quality to it.
But I loved it. I didn't feel like I was watching Tom Hanks. I was like, I'm digging this this thing that Tom Hanks is doing. I love the kid.
Yeah. He was amazing. I love the girl that played Priscilla. Oh, yeah.
Boy, I love the one night stands and Elvis life or some of the sexiest babes I've ever laid eyes on. Oh, yeah. That was that was good stuff.
I love the dude that played the dude to play BB King was awesome. But the guy that played little Richard.
Oh, yeah, I wanted more a little Richard. Yeah, I was like for like five songs. I was like, just give us a biography of him.
I swear to God that I was thinking that too. I was like, please do a biopic about little Richard with this guy. Yeah.
And there's an acknowledgement in that scene where all this is like, oh, I could never do anything like this.
Meanwhile, he's having a hundred times the success. They did a lot of really nice subtle stuff like that.
The whole thing felt like if Oliver Stone in JFK mode made a movie about Elvis, that's what it felt like to me. It was a wild ride.
He was clearly exaggerated in places. When he pulls out that for you to feel like Elvis, just take this baby is like five minutes into the movie.
I was like, we're getting him into pills in the 50s. Like, what are we doing here?
I thought they were going to just have him like, you know, pilled out and miserable for three hours. That's not the case.
He hits the drugged out point right about what the time when you expect and want him to.
But there's just all this sadness like he was supposed to be in stars born with Barbara Streisand.
And from what I had always heard, the Colonel fucked that up. They keep, they kind of say his death fucked that up. But no, he says he says in the car that the Colonel fucks it up.
So he just went about a star's born and he goes, and they laugh. He goes, yeah, Barbara and the Colonel.
Oh, I like they'd never get along. I got. I didn't know they had already discussed. Okay.
But yeah, the Colonel kept him from anything artistic, anything challenging. He just wanted money, money, money.
The very, I would, I've been a lifelong fan of the Elvis comeback special in 68, the black leather suit comeback special where he was like, I'm still fucking good.
Fuck all of you. I had no idea that started as a Christmas special that the Colonel wanted to put on some lame cash.
Yeah, Christmas special. And there's all these executives in the back freaking out because he's singing no Christmas music. He won't put on the Christmas sweater.
And the whole time they're freaking out. He's making arguably one of the great concert films of all time. And there's a lot of that. There's a lot for people in entertainment.
It's a great sort of feeling of like, boy, people have just been wrong about everything for a hundred years.
That was the part I was most excited about was like, how are they going to do the comeback special and like when they're like, when the he hooks up with the new producers, one of them is played by the kid from stranger things that played the asshole brother in season three.
Who I really like.
But he's like, it's opening up. We're going to open with you in front of an audience. Right. And he's like, I haven't been in front of an audience in years.
And like he comes out and like, they just do it so well when the audience is like, yeah, what are you going to do? You fucking has been he grabs the mic and starts doing like the hits medley.
And the place is going fucking crazy. And then, and then the whole thing is it's he's supposed to close with this Christmas song and the kernel is furious that he's not doing it.
And then he writes that protest song. Here's where there was heavy tears coming out of me.
Yeah, well, that's an amazing song to yeah, it was just it was fucking incredible. It was incredible.
You know, I never in a million years that I could give two shits about a biopic about Elvis Presley, but here we are. And I loved it. I just loved every minute of this thing.
And the way it builds to the end.
With that voice over of the kernel going the last time I saw Elvis saying he could barely stand and it's him playing unchained melody and it's like, but he couldn't stand, but he's but he but he nailed it when I cut to the real Elvis singing unchained melody there at the end.
I was like, who I was emotion. Yeah, I was devastated. It's cutting back and forth. And then it's showing you the text of what where everybody ended up.
And then the last line I'm of course you knew it would be the last thing you hear is Elvis is left the building right like you're killing me.
Yeah, no, I I love Elvis always have and it seemed like sort of the dream biopic that somehow has not been made ever.
It really is a great kind of warts and all biopic. I think this kid all I don't know who the contenders were, the final contenders for this part.
All I could think is what if Zach Efron played this role, you know, and be really.
I guarantee you the toss and it got I guarantee they toss and I could have done it. Yeah.
But for me, having honestly no idea who Austin Butler is, I assume he was on some sort of CW show at some point or something I'm not aware of, but he he enters the discussion of of a best actor win this year.
I mean, I think he is the deserving best actor winner. He is Elvis and it does help the fact that I had never seen him in anything.
I didn't have any preconceptions of him, but I felt like I was watching fucking Elvis. The kid is so good.
The lip syncing is incredible. I don't know if he sang.
No, he sings it. That's his that's him singing it. He didn't sing all that. He did. They confirmed it. He sang all of it.
Like he worked tirelessly on perfecting the kids incredible. Then they should give him last year's best actor award and this year's best actor.
If he actually sang that's fucking incredible. I thought that they had pioneered some new style of lip syncing that made it seamless. You know, I thought it was that good.
No, he sang all this stuff, especially on that protest song.
I thought for sure I was just listening to her recording. That's amazing. The kids amazing. The kids great. I'm really impressed by the movie. I love tanks.
I loved it thematically. I loved it visually. I'll probably watch it again. It's a great movie. I don't know what to tell you.
I want to watch it again, but I don't want to because I'm going to be a fucking blubbering mess again. So I need to be ready for that.
Did you catch? I thought I noticed a few scenes and this seems exactly like something bads would do.
I thought I noticed a few times that he sort of superimposed Elvis's face on top of the kid for like a few brief fleeting moments.
I could buy him doing that. I could buy him doing that. I'm pretty sure that happened a few times in the movie.
But then there's a great interview on YouTube with the real Priscilla Presley and the girl that played Priscilla Presley.
And Priscilla Presley giving it her thumbs up. Yeah.
And like the guy being like when you watch that scene with you and him on the tarmac and the car and you're asking him to get help. And he says no. And Priscilla's like.
Basically saying like yes, that happened and it's fucking heartbreaking and they nailed it.
Like yeah.
Oh god, it tore me to pieces. Jesus.
Yeah. Yeah. That scene is rough. I mean, the last half hour really is just an assault on the old emotions.
You know, and it's it's beautifully done.
I loved it because what I thought all these Lerman movies was missing were missing is any sort of emotion.
They were so bombastic that I never felt anything. And this really got to me in a big way. Big fan.
My hog is out erect and gorge and ready to fuck, you know.
The hog way up the same. I will say that so far, this is my when I think when we say movie of the year on this podcast, we were.
You got to narrow it down into categories.
As far as a as a traditional theatrical movie that's been distributed and put out there, this is my movie the year so far 100%.
It's mine too. I don't I can't think of anything I really love this year.
So it's not that great a thing to say, but it is my favorite movie of the year.
We love you guys. We are doing the live show September 10th.
We're doing two shows in New York City. We hope to see it.
And if we don't folks, they'll be more live shows.
We love you. We appreciate your enthusiasm. We appreciate all of Emily's help.
Yeah, we are on see you and help pod at Instagram tell your friends that they don't know that we're on Patreon.
Show anything you want to talk about.
Now I plugged in the last episode next steps.
We'll be prey and then we probably will do some sort of specialty episode of a top five or something, but definitely pray is coming up at the second half of the month.
We'll see you next time.
And we'll see you and hell.