Summer is here, and Bed MDM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer, or check out
our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz, only available at Bed
MDM Casino.
Spend on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 Fortunes, Mystery of the Lamp,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand!
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action!
Bet MGM in Game Sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 plus to Wager, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and West Virginia
only.
Games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as normal -durable site credit slash bonus best unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
The football season is full of guarantees, and here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October, if
your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning or winning money back in fan
cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
Winning hits different here.
Must be 21 plus, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gambler, offer not available in all states
terms apply, see Fanatic's fourth book app.
Hey everyone, welcome to a new episode of We'll see you in hell the podcast where we watch
movies and talk about them while we watch them and then give you the chance to either listen
along while you watch or just listen to us.
It's up to you.
Sounds like a lot of fun to me.
That's Pat Walsh.
Hey guys.
I'm Joe DeRosa.
This is now a part of the Fangory of Podcast Network for more information about the network, including
other programs, how to follow the show, and find past episodes of We'll See You and Hell,
or episodes of any show for that matter. Please visit Fangoria .com. Now, let's get down to it.
Today we are watching, we have chosen, I want to say Pat has chosen leprechaun, Warwick Davis,
Jen Aniston, pre, I guess, is that pre -friends? Yeah, this is, yes, it would have to be
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Jennifer Aniston didn't ask for a release from friends to shoot leprechaun. Sure.
This is the original, as Pat has mentioned, where we, by the cast, where we, Davis, Jennifer Aniston,
this is not the remake, which somehow managed to be worse than the original. I don't know how the
fuck they pulled that off, but God bless them they did. Anyway, you know the deal if you've
listen to the show before. If you don't, now's the time to go to your Netflix and find
the movie itself. If you are watching, we will give you a moment here to pause and do
that. So go ahead and hit pause. Okay. You got the movie is a three step process. Right
now what you're going to do is you're going to hit play and the second you see frame one
of the movie, we need you to pause it again. Second, you see frame one of the movie. We need
you to pause it again. Why do we do this? Because everybody is different load times on their
Apple TVs or whatever their devices are that they're watching. We're waiting for ours to load
now. As a matter of fact, we've got a spinning wheel here today. Okay, we're paused. Do you
got a black screen on pause? And I guess on, we'll go one, two, three, then play. So we can start
together. Black screen on pause. Was that brief enough this time? It was. I wasn't near as annoyed as I
was the other two times. All right. One, two, three, play. We're rolling. I'd like to start by
congratulating the lovely Jen Anderson on her recent marriage to Justin Thoreau. They got married
because I'm sure she's listening to this. They did get married a long time coming for Jen. She said
a hard road to hoe. Road to hoe? Road to hoe? Or rope? Roadline to hoe? Okay. I heard it was
splitsville. Courtney's been looking at us weekly. Yeah. According to when the checkout line
did it have the tear mark down the center of their photo? Yeah. I like when there's the tear mark.
I do too. I think that's a nice effect. Every like erotic thriller of the 90s also had that like a
family photo with a big crack down the center. Like hand the rocks the cradle and that kind of shun. Yes.
Now, if you've never seen the movie leprechaun, you know already by our conversation,
how much you need to pay attention to anything. We're just completely ignoring the opening of the film.
If it does open with the instant reveal of the leprechaun himself, it's the first thing you see in the movie, zero mystery.
Yeah, I got to tell you it now. If I'm sitting down to write leprechaun where it says in the description, there's a mysterious leprechaun living in the basement.
Look at this. Warwick Davis top billing over Jennifer Aniston. This was a different time.
But wow, that's a cheap graphic there too.
you. Uh, mysterious leprechaun, they don't start by having a family move in and there's
a strange knock or they find a gold debloon in the microwave or something like that and
go, what is this? They show you a leprechaun. Immediately. Counting gold. Very dumb. I bet
that was a producer with a big cigar. And he was like, the picture is called leprechaun.
You got to show him a leprechaun first five minutes, baby. So now we got where we're in
got out of his limousine and then threw it on the ground.
I just haven't drank in a couple of weeks.
And when I saw that Jameson bottle, I started to salivate.
It always looks delicious on screen, doesn't it?
It really does.
When you see a guy guzzling whiskey on screen,
when you see a handsome, successful guy like this,
he's wearing a nice Colonel Sanders suit,
a beautiful hair piece.
It arrives in a limousine to this shack on the Irish countryside as a butler or a limo driver.
Yeah, maybe both.
The guy seems to be doing everything.
Sure.
I would dare say that this guy has found some of the leprechauns gold.
Right.
And that's that's our setup here.
How is she not recoiling from his breath?
Because they're Irish that's, you know, that's that's Jameson is like toothpaste.
That's true.
Sent.
Uh, anytime you see a, uh, uh, uh, and I, uh, and I don't know, just not any guy guzzling the was, you know, there's always those scenes in like movies where they go up into like the executive's office and he's got the, the glass to counter things.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And you, they pour it out and have a drink and always looks like it's like what tastes like iced tea, like a peach snapple.
Well, they're definitely drinking iced tea.
Yeah, never tastes like that when you get it.
Yeah.
At old J's bar.
I think there's a rule in film and television that you can't actually be drinking alcohol because I remember
That final drunk an interview with the cast of cheers. They said they were never drinking actual beer because they weren't allowed to
But they were drunk in the final interview the final interview
I which I hope you can find on YouTube. It's Leno trying desperately to control like 14
black out drunk actors on the set of and cheers are on the
tonight show he does the interview on the set of cheers and they are so messed up
and I guarantee that they've probably tried to scrub it from the internet but I
hope it's still out there well Kelsey grammar has claimed publicly that he doesn't
even remember shooting the final episode he was so drunk I love that that makes me
happy now I love it too what made you take a drinking break well you and I are
are similar in that we drink too much sometimes, and also I'm very Catholic, which there's a lot
of punishment to yourself that goes on, a lot of guilt, a lot of self -loathing. And when I hit one
of those pockets, I usually abandon all drinking. I eat incredibly healthy. I just clean things up
for about a month. I do feel much better, but I'd be lying if I said I didn't crave the occasional
I think I'm approaching one of those breaks myself as we were discussing before we almost didn't do the podcast today folks
I was in quite a mood
And I got to tell you I'm happy that we're doing it. It's always great to see Pat Walsh's face
Oh, and he picks leprechaun, which I love
I'm already feeling great. We're laughing. Who went a good time. There's a voice coming out of a suitcase right now on the screen
And I'm not sure if that's the leprechaun's evil magic or if they're just drunk
No, that's what they're hearing a voice come out of a suitcase. I
Watched this on VHS. I guess I must have been 12 13. I have no real recollection of it. I
I
Remember the aforementioned drinking. Well, I remember when I saw this. I remember seeing trailers for it when it was in the theater
I wanted to see it
Desperately wow, okay. I liked at the age. I don't know. I was
That's probably 11 when this came out 12 something like that
Uh at that age
I loved any harder thing that had to do with a little goblin sure or a doll that came to life anything small
I like I like tiny horror in those days
You know, yeah, uh, and I didn't get to the theater. I think because my mom wouldn't take me or something
And then uh, it was I remember going to the like west coast video
in my neighborhood and they had the dry erase board behind the counter to let you know what was coming out soon.
And I remember seeing leprechaun on there like a month before it came out and I counted the days.
Wow.
Reserved it.
Rented it the day came out.
Watched it.
Don't think I got even 25 minutes into it before I turned it off.
You didn't finish it?
I finished it in like in like sections.
Okay, I just even at that age I was like this is not a really a great movie. I'm always very committed to finishing a movie regardless of how shitty it is. I have a
Twinge of OCD with that and I'll watch a movie for two and a half hours even if I hate every second of it because I got to get to the end of it. So I can say I've seen that movie.
I fast what I do is now is I'll fast forward sure and I'll get the gist of each scene
At the top of it and then fast forward and go okay. I know what's happening. Yeah, and then I just go to the end
I watched bison teniel man and like five minute increments over the course of maybe six months. It was one of the hardest moves
I've ever had to sit through
I
You know, I attest that's tougher to get through than awakenings. Oh, I love awaken. I love awakenings
I'm saying for different reasons.
You find that a sad man.
It's a hard fight by Centennial Manmore, heart breaking and gut
wrenching the awakening.
No, it's pretty pain.
Now, if you are watching the guy, what's this guy's name?
Colonel Sanders, that's probably one.
Shamest McSanders is trying to kill the leprechaun with a gun.
But he's yeah, but he's, but he's holding up now a four leaf
clover which massaging his head because he murdered the leprechaun murdered the guy's wife
yeah and now he's rubbing her head as she's dead to be like I murdered your wife so he you know
it's taunting yeah demon taunts as they say but the four -leaf clover is what repels the leprechaun
but now his gun heard it which I haven't seen this movie in a while you'd think something
with magic. Usually the gun is useless against whatever bill and you're trying to kill
in a horror moon. I remember this, he puts the four -leaf clover, he puts the leprechaun
in a crate and then puts the four -leaf clover on top of the crate and the leprechaun can't
fight it. Is she the size of that clover? It's a big old clover. It's a big clover. I used
to spend, to give you a little taste of how exhilarating my childhood was, I would spend
hours and hours looking for four -leaf clover. I would try finding him too as a child.
and now I don't I don't think kids even go outside it was it it was a simpler
day did you find any I think I found one once I would always like like find
like a three with like a little brown chunk on it of dirt and pretend that I
had found one and my mom was like yeah that's really good that right right even
your mom couldn't be bothered yeah with your bullshit I had nothing to do I worked
to blockbuster video for many years. I hate to brag. And I was there during the leprechaun
in the hood days. Oh, yeah. Have you seen that one? I've seen all of them. Okay. Does
he talk in a hip -hop petois? Not in this one. Well, no, no, he still talks like the leprechaun.
He doesn't make any like rap jokes or like I'm picturing some vaguely racist things. Leprechaun
in the hood is sort of like sort of a comedy.
Okay.
It hopes on us.
I think that's back to, no, snoops out in it.
Iced tea is in it.
Oh, sure.
Or is that the second one?
There's leprechaun back to the hood
and leprechaun in the hood.
One of them has iced tea in it
and it's a sort of like a comedy, okay.
Now this is what kills me.
The guy does all this trouble to get the thing
into the crate, puts the four leaf clover on the crate
so it can't escape.
Then he's gonna burn the crate.
Why can't the leprechaun escape because of the Forleaf Clover?
Yeah, I thought leprechaun's loved Forleaf Clovers.
This is real simple writing, Pat.
Like you said, the executive said
you got to show him a leprechaun in the first 30 seconds.
What's his weakness?
Well, it's got to be a Forleaf Clover.
Okay, I mean, I...
You're looking at Lucky Charms box.
It's a leprechaun holding a Forleaf Clover.
I agree.
I think it's a bad move.
I think it's like if you made a My Little Pony movie
And you said the weakness was rainbows. Yeah, I mean, you'd think a leprechaun's weakness would be like silver or something like the opposite of gold silver bullets or rain because he loves rain. Let's roll play. I'll be the executive and you pitch me ways.
Better ideas for the leprechaun to be weakened, you know, it's weaknesses and I'll be the executive. Okay.
So I'm thinking maybe because, you know, we know leprechauns love gold. I'm thinking that silver is his weakness. Let me ask you something.
Walsh.
Uh -huh.
Are we making a vampire movie?
Oh.
Are we making a werewolf movie?
We're making a leprechaun movie.
I'm sorry. That's a good point.
Mr. Weinstock.
Bold move.
Well, some Jewish. He's a studio executive man. This guy is matching his truck, which is a cool move.
The look at the shirt is the exact same color as the truck. For a second there, I couldn't tell if you were talking about the executive that you'd created.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, or the guy on screen. You're talking about the guy on screen. Yeah. Yes, he matched his shirt to his truck.
Aniston dating a significantly older man, it's her father. Oh, okay. This is her father in the movie. Well, you know, this is not she's not dating. We do live in the city of angels.
Joe lipstick city. Yeah, but this is not this doesn't take place in the cities of angels takes place in Ireland. This take are they in Ireland? She was just driving for the Irish countryside with like.
Oh, that's well, this is the shack. This is where a shame is just died. Now they're taking it over. Okay, boy, Aniston's
Good looking gal. I don't know if I'm the first to say that
This was what was she had she been on the edge. Do you remember the fox sketch showed the edge?
I
Don't pat I got out of the house once in a while as a child
I did too what I look for four leaf clovers by myself, and then I went back inside and you this is the guy that said it was sad
that I counted the days to leprechaun came out on video.
Now there was a sketch show with Julie Brown,
but not downtown Julie Brown.
Oh, I know.
The other Julie Brown.
Yeah.
And the goofy.
We're talking goofy Julie Brown.
That's sassy.
Exactly.
And I think maybe Wayne Knight or something.
I used to love it.
It was a bad sketch show.
It was on around the same time as Ben Stiller's show.
I love Ben Stiller's show.
Of course you do.
I own every episode.
I do too.
Who was Wayne Knight?
Oh, Wayne Knight.
I knew him. He might not have been on it. I'm going to talk about my answer. I think he was on the Kelsey grammar green screen sketch show.
Ever that one with Paul Tompins and Caitlin Olson. I think so. It's always something about him. I wasn't way night on that.
That sounds right to me. That sounds right. Was that show funny? I never saw it. I love Kelsey grammar. So God damn much. I always want him to be Frazier though.
Yeah, it's terrific and boss, but I just want them to be dainty free.
Did you watch all of boss?
No, I watched, I watched some of it, it's a good show.
It was a little over, a little over my head, it's very political, I mean I can't even keep
up with VEEP.
No, I feel the same way.
It's too deep for me.
I feel the same way.
I don't know what the fuck you're talking about after, I love VEEP and I laugh a lot, but
there's times where I'm like, what?
I know nothing about the government or politics.
Yeah, West Wing kind of threw me.
I don't I don't care there with that word and here's here's what I think and this is a terrible attitude to have I
Always feel like whatever I think about politics whatever I do about politics
It will have zero effect on what happens. I agree. That's the most apathetic terrible attitude to have
It's what they worry about the young people having but my vote doesn't matter my nothing matters
It's like whoever's going to be president, whoever's going to be city comptroller is going to be city comptroller.
Yeah, Patty, I got the same exact take.
I do both.
And I thought I never voted.
Okay. The difference between you and me is I thought it would be well received to express that to Jeanine Garafalo a week ago.
Oh, no.
Yeah, that's not the person to say that.
We had a great discussion afterwards.
words, and I learned a lot during the discussion, and I actually thanked her after, but I didn't
realize as it was coming out of my mouth, yeah, this was not the right person to say that.
You know, why I vote is I feel like, okay, like when I'm at a concert and there's a thousand
people applauding at the end of each song, it doesn't matter if I applaud, you know, and I
I feel the same way about voting.
But I do applaud because I'm not an asshole
and I want to feel part of the event.
And that's why I vote to.
The argument, I don't vote.
The argument is always, well, what if everybody felt that way?
Well, but they don't.
And that's when I retort to that.
Exactly.
Now, this is a little movie trivia here.
We're now into the scene if you're watching along
where Jen has met the hunk.
I love how we're on a Jen basis.
Yeah.
Well, I feel like if I met her,
She'd say call me Jen. Yeah, I've met Kudra. She was lovely. She's the only other friends. I've met
She's the only of the friends. Yeah, I thought you should the only other friends the only of the friends that I have met
I'll tell you what I could go for a met La Blanc once in a while
I'm glad to meet him. He was always my least favorite of the friends. He just seems like a fun guy in real life though. Yeah
I I don't know I've never seen the episodes or whatever. I I haven't followed his career outside of it
I think he's had the least luck movie wise, definitely, but he's had one of the better
careers.
He had to spit off.
And now he's on his that show, uh, that show, uh, episode, I just, yeah, but I mean it's
been going strong.
Yeah.
I mean, he gets nominated for Emmy's every year, even though not one person in the world has
ever seen an episode of episodes.
Did you just, you said episodes before I said, I said it maybe 20 seconds before and I'm
starting to feel unheard and unrestricted.
I didn't hear you and I do respect you and I do listen.
Now is this guy gardening in a grimace colored vest. Oh, it's a guy from Pewie's big advantage. Yeah, would kill two in gum
Is that a nod? It's great because I'm glad my movie trivia things got pushed back to the scene because I forgot
This guy was in it. Is that a nod to Pewie him to and gum and it's no he plays like sort of a borderline retarded man in this movie
I bet it was a nod to Pewie and I don't like you just dismissing it. I don't think it was he's supposed to be like a guy a man with a child
Child's mind
like I think, you know, and that's the kid from from what? Well, that's the kid. Uh, I don't know. That kid always played a kid that looks like white trash, though. Yeah, I've seen he's never never seen that kid cleaned up with always a respectable haircut.
He looks like the kid from Poltergeist, but it can't be because this is 10 years later.
Wait, is it the kid from Poltergeist?
No, I just saw, you know, it's 82 and now he's the same age of 93.
Is this from 93?
Yeah.
This movie's from 93.
I was older than 12 when this came out.
Oh God, I was 12 when this came out.
I was 14 when this came out.
Okay.
The guy that we just saw, the purple shirted Gardner Hunk.
Yeah.
That's the guy from summer school.
Mark Harman. No, that's not Mark Harman. No, no, no, I'm saying the movie summer school with. Oh, I love summer school with Mark Harman and Kirstie Ali. Yeah, that guy is from summer school. If you say that's the guy from summer school, Mark Harman. No, I was saying that's the guy. I mean, obviously, I know that's not Mark Harman. Okay, that's the kid that sleeps at the clock during class because he strips it right. Yeah, yeah, that's right. So he's he's gardening in that lavender vest at a home that an abandoned shack that Anderson's moving into.
It's not a lavender vest, first of all, for those who aren't
watching, it's a purple shirt that he's cut the sleeves off of.
Oh, pardon me.
Now, maybe no, no, I was talking to Tommy Hilfiger over here.
Maybe that's a nod to summer school.
No, I was talking to Jay crew over here, you know?
Maybe they were like, this is what a stripper would wear on stage.
Right. You chew the gum.
They're not in everybody's other movies.
They might be.
And Anastin is on edge because of the leprechaun.
She was coming hot off the scary looks in the crate. Did you see that? I saw she is ice. I saw scary
Does Aniston pop the top in this one or no? She never pops the top
Well, now people say like Sandy Boyk never pop the top
But there is that movie called like fire on the Amazon that nobody knows about where she popped the top
Well, I don't think I'm sure you see brief nip on Aniston in the good girl
Yeah, I remember that when Jill and Hall is
Uh, man, that's like 22 after this is also a pre -nosed job.
Yeah, you could tell she had a little, a little bit of work done.
I mean, she's still gorgeous in this one.
Well, now you see her and she still looks great.
But there you can tell there's kind, it looks like maybe like a mattress cushion
in her face like a, her cheeks look real puffed out.
I think she's getting a little of the talks.
It's getting something.
I mean, little bow.
See, now this is a crazy thing.
I, I work with very wealthy people and they talk some about plastic surgery here.
in there. I never knew that anyone had plastic surgery unless they looked like
John Rivers or something. I assumed that everyone else was just aging beautifully.
Oh my sweet my sweet boy. And then people started saying like and I'm talking
like very recently like two three years ago. People were like no everyone has it
everybody's had everybody's getting it. I had no idea. What what work have you had
had done, Pat. I had my penis shortened. Come on, that's somebody's bit. I was frightening
people. I had my taint laser. Why did you have that done? So there's no hair on it? Yeah,
it looks great, but it was covered by hair. I like to showcase my taint. And then I had
my eyes switched. I put the right in the left socket, the left in the right socket. Okay.
Because I just wanted to kind of mix it up. And no one really notices. See, this is
Well, you're good. I can throw you a premise. You run with it. You criticize me immediately. I know I wasn't criticizing. I was saying I appreciate that about you that I can throw you a loose. No, you said that somebody's bit. You accused me of stealing a bit. Somebody's doing a dick shortening bit.
The dick shortening bit. I think I've heard, but the other one's waiting for me. Talks about how he got a stick. Sure.
I, yeah, there you go. One of the fun is never meant. Hey, if you're going to steal steal from the best paddy Willard. That's what I say.
Um, yeah, no, I've never had anything done. I've never had anything done either. I
I'm not above it. No, I'm not above a lipo one day, which I don't think is out of the realm of possibility
Well, now they're freezing that off. It's the thing now. How's that work?
You like squeeze a clump of fat and then they freeze it off your fucking body
And it's like very expensive and a lot of people do it apparently. Is it painful? I believe it's pretty painful. I
Wait a minute, doesn't it take your skin off?
Look, I truly don't know how it works,
but it's called cyber -sino -siro, something like that.
Sounds terrible.
It's, I heard it disgust at work, so I don't know about it.
That sounds terrible.
My dermatologist does, I go to a dermatologist once in a while.
You want to make sure that thing on your knee isn't cancer.
Sure.
And are we human?
He's dead.
Oh, are we human, sir?
See the slow man just pushed the shamrock off the right off the thing's gonna get gone
But he does he does life on plastic surgery and he has had so much work done
It's insane your dermatologist. Yes. Now. What does he look like does he look like like a Martin short character a lot?
No, it's not absurd, but he's had a lot of work done. I shouldn't say the leprechaun's had like four facelifts. It looks like
Leprechaun's doing well
just eating a bug off his arm for some reason. Now Warwick played the leprecha, well I guess
there aren't that many roles open to what is the word little people, little people. How is
little people better than Midges? I don't even want to touch it, Pat. All right. I don't know.
I don't know. That's why I don't want to touch it. I'm afraid I'll say something wrong and
it'd be a blog up tomorrow. It's blow past it. Uh, like he did, he did
willow and the star of like this multi, multi million dollar
action movie. And now five years later, he's in this bargain
basement. Well, I mean, was this considered kind of a bigger
title at the time? The first two were, the first two were
three were theatrical releases. They made a lot of money. And
then they had a long run. I mean, look, it did well enough
that they felt the need to reboot the franchise. Yeah, that's
So I mean I didn't even hear about that that was the theatrical release or the DVD really straight to VOD as it's called these days
And it was it's terrible. Yeah, it's terrible. They they took away the leprechaun's
Personality that's the thing. I was always like if they would have made this movie correctly
This would have been a really scary movie like where would Davis is legitimately scary in that costume right he's he's a good actor
It's a it's a cool idea for a movie monster
But they just made the movie shitty. Yeah
You know, whereas the new one they kind of made the movie half decently
But the leprechaun is just like this literally like almost like faceless monster. Who's portraying the leprecha?
The guy from WWE I want to say his name's fizzy wig, but that's not his name
Who is the guy first?
Yeah, that's the guy from Christmas care.
Yeah, I know.
Fuzzy Wigs, the guy from Muppet Christmas care.
And yes, Pat, it's a little person.
They don't have the Undertaker playing leprechaun in the WWE.
Because WWE produced it.
The movie films, that's weird.
What's that guy's name?
Horn swagger, horn swagger.
Okay.
Now here's the thing, I was on the Opian Anthony show
years ago, one day with Ricky Jervase came in. It's the only time I've ever met Ricky Jervase.
I think you mentioned this on the last one. Did we talk that I mentioned leprechaunter?
Yeah. Maybe that was just me and you shooting the show. Why would I mention it on the,
we were probably just shooting the show? Okay. Well, yeah, I asked him because they were doing that
life's too short show. Yeah. And I said, after we went off the air, I said, there's a lot of fun.
And I got to ask you a question goes anything I go why didn't you a shit on leprechaun yeah and life's too short
I go it's it's I mean I would just think it was a treasure trove sir you've shit on everything else the guy did yeah
Yeah, and and he goes he goes. Oh, I don't remember he goes
I think we probably didn't it just got cut out right so there's your answer
He said it was a really amusing. I thought I like that show a lot. I really liked the finale. Yeah, the movie wrap up
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Have you watched Derek?
Yeah, how's Derek? I like it. I like it. It's it's a little it looks like I wouldn't be able to take it now
It's good. It's it is a good show. It's a little schmaltcy at times. Yeah, it's a little too melodramatic at times
But like I like it though. I think it's a very good show. I like the low ladies too. I like everything those guys do
I love the low ladies. Yeah, and obviously
The office and then extras were both fantastic
Extras is my favorite. I think it's a masterpiece from start to finish. I
Completely loved it, but I love the office much more. I would say the finale of extra is makes me cry without fail every time
I watch it. It is great. I can't I can't get through without crying now. How did the guy?
Frances from P. We's big adventure. How did he get away from the leprechaun? Because he's I noticed now as we drift
lazily back to the film
he's still running around in one piece look at that a rainbow just went up which
is the doing of the leprechaun oh because he's got to find his gold so that's
the leprecha the goals at the end of the rainbow right they're really we've got
a really low body count already for a horror movie well I'm saying you could have
killed the the Francis from P .W. right off the bat they didn't kill him right now I
wrote I hate even saying this publicly but I wrote a movie for the sci -fi
channel before I became a known writer. I'd be bragging about it left and right. I think that's
such a good credit. It's a it's so bad, but I co -wrote it. We rode a draft that was like tremors.
It had a great sense of humor and it was it was scary and they have a rule there where you have to have
a kill every 10 pages, you know, like that. And we pitched this movie with a moth man and wrote it.
We got, I think, 15 grand or something, which at the time was much needed, and they were like,
guys, this is great. This would be the best movie we've made here at the Sci -Fi channel, but we
don't make movies with any humor. We follow a very strict policy of just kill, kill, kill, kill,
no jokes, no tongue in cheek. That's what our audience wants. So, it stripped it away. It was
unwatchable. It'd be odd and watchable. I would never recommend anyone watch it. It has nothing of
me in it. It's a terrible movie. What was it called?
Mothman. Just Mothman. And it airs in the sci -fi channel. And now
their whole brand has changed and they're doing Sharknado. Just five short
years later or whatever. Well, here's what I propose repitch it.
You repitch it. And you in you reboot Mothman. I don't think I need to go
back there at the stage of the game. But it was kind of fun to
right? I mean I would love to make movies like that. Yeah well it's just like
you're like oh well it's a sci -fi channel they're paying me 15 grand obviously I
can have fun and do whatever the hell I want to do it's got no budget and then
sure enough even they have network people who are like no can't do it can't do it
can't do it that sucks and it winds up being a terrible product. Now do the do the
listeners a favor because you've told me this before tell them the final line of
that film when they kill the moth man. Oh, yeah, that survived. So yeah, he goes, uh, he holds
up. I don't know. You know what? The truth is, I don't know if this was in the movie.
Might have just been in the script. I think it was in the movie. But, uh, he blows the moth
man up with fire. Then this crazy old man goes, like a moth to a flame. And that was kind
cool to see that. But we were like, let's get Gary Bucy. Like, let's get some star power in there.
And then when they came back, we can't get Gary Bucy. We don't have the money. Right. I was like,
OK, this is going to be real bad. Who'd they get? It was all nobody's. There was a girl named
Jewel State, who's a beautiful actress who has been in like firefly and stuff, but nobody else.
Are you telling me the cast of leprechaun had a higher profile than the cast of Mothman?
I'm a hundred percent telling you that Wow, but it's a nice one wasn't a theatrical release
Well, that's fine, but I mean you could have got one of those other people maybe get the guy that played chain song
It from summer school. I had no say in casting or any or really even in the script
I was just sort of forced at gunpoint to turn in exactly what they want and this is why I don't have a big movie career
Because I think the writer gets to pick the actor sure sure
Well for a while, you know, I read 8 million comedy scripts when I came out here
TV pilots and stuff to try to get a job and
every pilot for at least five six seven years said
Enter Jimmy
parentheses events Vaughn type, right. It's like that's that's all anyone was going for back sure and now
Vaughn's comedy career has died and then I was like oh very smart move for him going to the drama with his true detective and boy
That was a swing in a mess
Uh, although I liked it more than most, I liked the sex party episode.
I was entertained throughout sometimes by how bad it was, but I always had a good time
with it.
I still find Vince Vaughn very funny.
I fucking love Vince Vaughn.
I mean, who doesn't love Vince Vaughn?
He's just not, not getting the projects he deserves.
Do I ever tell you about the time I met him?
You did, but you can share it with our listeners.
Let's share it with the listeners.
All right.
Because I'm working on a script with a friend of mine, Steve Bern.
Okay.
And we will meet over it their production company not Steve and Vince's which I mean Vince Vaughan's production company
Their production company is behind my parking spot at my job. Yeah, Wild West. Yeah picture show
So anyway, I just would go over and go to some
ambiguous boardroom and just meet Steve and we'd sit there and write and that was kind of that right and then I got to meet Peter Billingsley
Which was very cool sure because I'm a huge Christmas story fan
Well, who was it?
And you know, that's a piece of my childhood.
I'm meeting this guy in real life and he's a swell guy.
Hell of a guy.
Very nice guy.
By the way, we're changing the name of the podcast
to name droppers.
It's just me and Joe dropping names.
You're going to hear stories about the sci -fi network.
Yeah, the names I'm dropping are like the head of the sci -fi
channel.
Well, you said you met Kudro and she was nice.
She was great.
Yeah.
Anyway, one day I show up, I said I'm here to meet Steve
and the person in reception said he's playing video games with Vince in his
office and I immediately collected myself and said okay I'm about to meet a
guy that I've watched in a million movies sure that I think is really funny
that I also really want to like me yeah don't you know so don't act like a 16
year old teenager right now and but anyway I went into the room they were playing
hockey on PlayStation and it was literally the scene from
swingers. Yeah. They're playing hockey video games. And
Vince Vaughn is just, he's almost doing the lines from the
actual movie. Right. And I was like, they, whoever found this
guy was just like, just put a camera on him and just let him be
himself. Yeah. Somebody's asking is that's almost 20 years
later. I mean, it's amazing. His, his assistant came in at one
point and said, you have a call in line one. And he said, I don't need attitude from you.
There's a nice way to do that. I was like, I see him do that in actual movies. Yeah.
It was really funny. Uh, my, my boss is Michael Patrick King who did Sex in the City. And he,
Vince Vaughn, I guess was in Sex in the City on a show. He was on an episode. And he tells the story.
Yeah. So he tells the story about Vince Vaughn came in and uh, he reads the lines and then he goes,
all right now we're gonna do a couple takes my way if that's cool I'm gonna just
kind of have fun with it kind of mess around with the material and they all
kind of look at him and he goes wouldn't it suck if I was that guy made me
like him as well that's why wouldn't you let him improv he's a very fun again that's
really great wait wait are you sure it was sexy in the city yeah yeah I mean
they had the big stars pop in no it would definitely wasn't a comeback they had
I mean, I own the pink velvet chief box set of sex in the city, the complete series.
My mommy bought it for Christmas for me years ago.
Wow.
But I've never seen that episode.
But then again, I haven't gotten deep into four and five yet.
Seasons four and five.
That would have been when the show was at its hottest and when he would have come on.
Well, then I got to check it out.
I watched them all when I moved to New York.
So I've seen them all, but never since.
I got a I was like this is what New York's going to be like and then proceeded to not have sex for several years
I had a very sex in the city experience in New York, which is why I got into the show
What I lived in New York. I wasn't that into it
I never really watched it until the very end of my stay. I started to watch it
Turned on season six on HBO on demand as a goof yeah
Because I had only seen the movies at that point sure all I had seen the sex in the city one and two in the theaters
And I did not like them
But then I said, let me watch season six as a goof, hooked immediately, asked for the
box set for Christmas God.
It started watching it from the beginning, watched the first three seasons pretty rapidly.
Yeah, it's super entertaining.
It really is.
It's a younger golden girls, really.
It's a younger golden girls.
It's an older girls.
Yeah, it's almost the same age, hot and cleavly.
Yeah, exactly.
All these shows have connections.
There's a thread here.
It's a slightly older female entourage.
This guy, I thought was Bugger, but he's not Bugger.
It's not Bugger.
Bugger does show up on think.
My favorite role that Bugger ever played was the lawyer on moon lighting.
Sure.
Remember?
I remember my parents loved moon lighting, but I never was allowed to watch it or anything.
My mom loved moon lighting.
She would make me watch it with her.
Oh, okay.
She entrusted it was funny.
I was too young to get any of it.
I didn't get the nuances of a romantic comedy at 11 sure a lot of will they are won't they kind of material rent. Yeah, but Bruce Willis is
Apparently potentially championing a moon lighting movie really. Yeah, I've heard he's
Exceptionally difficult person to work with which I can't even believe but I guess it's true
It bums me out because I love Bruce Willis so much, but yeah, I mean you listen to those
Listen to those Kevin Smith podcasts about when they were doing cop out. It's yeah
I guess that's really only who I've heard it from so maybe he's nice to others and cop out was so bad maybe he was just depressed
Well, let's think about it Tarantino worked with him did but he never went back to the well
Well, that again, there's a lot of guys Tarantino never had back. It doesn't mean they're difficult
Let me say this to you. I just saw a trailer for the hateful eight can't wait
Nice Ron. I was very excited about the hey. I'm excited for any quantum to move the man makes amazing moves
But I saw the trailer and I was like
You know, haven't we kind of been down this road before?
With what?
With everything.
It's like he just did the Western with Django and Shane, which is, I had a lot of Western
elements.
Right.
And then I'm like, he's worked with all these people.
Like when I'm looking at Madsen, when I'm looking at, and I like them.
I like that.
I love Kurt Russell.
I love Sam O 'Jackson.
But I'm like, same way I feel about Scorsese making every movie with DiCaprio.
I'm like, I just want to see him work with other people.
Well, this is why I'm excited about the movie Tarantino's last few movies kill Bill volume one and two. Yeah
Umu umu was in that, but you know, he didn't have a lot of his usual players in it. I'm a madson and others were in there
But yeah, that's true. Yeah, Madsen's in it, but it's not a huge role, right? Yeah
In glorious bastards
Not not a lot of his usual suspects. I would argue Brad Pitt does not do a good job in glorious past. I loved him in it
I thought he was way too cartoony for that part.
The movie was incredible, and he was fine.
I just sometimes I was like, you're not quite good enough to be doing this over the
top character.
I'm not quite buying.
I thought that was the point.
I kind of thought that was Tarantino's sort of like graphic novel approach.
Perhaps.
You might have been directed into that.
Anyway, if I could finish my point, Pat, before you want to critique everybody's performance.
I feel passionately about this.
Django and Shane none of his usual players.
Well, Sam allow him.
Oh, yeah, yes.
OK, let me rephrase.
I'm not saying this correctly.
First off, Walter, just been an angler.
Right.
We haven't seen his usual players doing
the Tarantino thing in a while.
Samuel Jackson played against the Tarantino type.
I'm excited about that.
Well, not Samuel Jackson stole Django and Shane.
He's amazing in it.
But he doesn't play the Samuel Jackson guy.
We all know and love from him.
earlier Tarantino if that is true. He played the ultimate uncle Tom. Exactly. So I'm excited
about the hateful late because I personally feel like this is Tarantino saying I'm going back
to the roots. Original script about a bunch of criminals stuck in a cabin. It's very reservoir
dogs and it looks like they're all doing like the snappy Tarantino dialogue. So I'm like I think
this is kind of a gift to his fans like I wasn't going to make this because it leaked but come on guys
This is too fucking cool, and he did bring Jennifer Jason Lee into the mix who I love and she looks like she's crazy and fun and it
She looks great in it. I'm excited to Roth back on screen. Yeah, see like Roth doing like a little like
Snidly Whiplash like mustache character. I'm like I don't know. I just always I'm like
Terrence you know can get whoever he wants. What the hell is a whiplash mustache character snidly whiplash is like oh
Snide I thought you meant doing a snide. No, he was saying he was doing a snide
You mean the character's deadly with his like his line in the trailer was like oh we're gonna have quite a bit of fun
Not we hear something like that. It's like come on. I don't know. I just I just coming from the guy that wrote in moth
Don't hold it against me now
I couldn't be more excited to see it and I will see it before opening day because I will seek out advance screenings of it
I'm saying I wish he would expand his casting a little bit.
But I think the whole fiction, everyone in that, it's like, wow, you never expected
to see any of these people.
And it was very exciting.
I think he did.
I think he had, he had yet another breakout, like hit star actor with, with Kristoff Waltz,
just like he did with, with, with, with, uh, uh, in Jackie Brown, uh, what's the ladies
named Jackie Brown again?
Pam Greer.
just like he did with Travolta, you know, he's done it consistently for his entire career.
I think this movie is simply a gift to his fans.
Sure. I think this isn't the all art. They're all a gift to anyone who enjoys it.
But I mean, like, I don't think this is him saying, like, hey guys, look what I did this time.
I think this is him saying, like, I'm going to give you something you're going to really enjoy.
Yeah. Okay. Like he did with Grindhouse. Oh, I love Grindhouse. I love them all.
But that doesn't sound like it the way you're talking.
I love them all and I love all the Scorsese movies. My point is when I see oh like the Scorsese is making another movie now with
DeCaprio and I like DeCaprio, but I want to see him work with other people. That's all I'm saying.
I want to see him work with DeNiro again. And I don't think they're ever gonna make that Irish movie.
No, that's not your name. I'd love to see Tarantino work with DeNiro again because DeNiro and Jackie Brown is off the charts good.
He's great. Everyone.
one. That's a fantastic move. That's my friend Jim's favorite Tarantino movie. I'd put it very close to
Pulp Fiction. Yeah. Pulp Fiction is my favorite. Resort Dogs is my second favorite. I'll put Jackie
Browder. Yeah. I mean, look, they're all great. It's also like Windscore Saisy or Tarantino is working in
the past, a Western genre like, you know, our like Windscore Saisy does coon dune or he's doing some
movie about monks right now that's got come out like I'm just like and you know I understand
these people don't want to do the same thing over and over but it's like Terrence you know just
make an LA crime movie because we'd all fucking love the shit out of it. I wish I hope that at one
point he does what Scorsese does which is every 10 years go back and make a gangster movie again.
Yeah like I hope Terrence does his departed or something. That would be awesome or his good fellas.
Yeah, Scorsese's most successful film most praise film. Good movie of all time. Yeah, I mean, it's it's you know
And it's it was done during the period where he was trying to resist going back to that sort of stuff
Joe, what is your favorite movie of all time? It was good fellas. It was taken out by Glen Gary Glen Ross
Which was taken out by Hannah and her sisters. Oh, all right. That's my absolute favorite movie of all time
Followed very close second place by Glen Gary very close third place by good fellows
Now I'll take crimes and misdemeanors misdemeanors over Hannah and her sisters, but I love Hannah's crimes
And Mr. Meeners a wonderful film the reason Hannah and her sisters is my favorite is because it's got my favorite Woody Allen jokes
I've ever heard in it come I
Love the characters and it's the most insightful film I've ever seen
I've never watched a movie where so many characters say things that I've thought sure almost word -for -word in my head
Like when she talks about our date chat and her chest
Yeah, that because I've done it and received it and I've had that
conversation on both ends. Yeah. I know what that's all about.
I watched parenthood again last night, which I think is an amazing movie.
The original, okay, I was going to ask the movie, the original series, or the new series.
I've never seen the series any either of them. I love the movie. I really,
I've always loved the movie. It's, I think it's fantastic. And I watched
interview with the writers afterwards and they talked about how they were
completely inspired by hand or sisters. Really? Yeah.
How it was like four separate very legitimate stories and it was the hardest thing they ever wrote. They wrangled them all together
But they were like they walked out of hand her sisters and we're like let's do a movie about having kids like this. It's great. It's great
Apparently, it's a great movie. It is L .A. Starrick also Dianne Weiss brought her over from handers. She's a great actress. Love Diane. Do you think now look not being mean?
But do you think she's an attractive woman? Yeah, well, I mean, you know, I'm not currently attracted to her. She's all right
Don't I'm not being mean. I'm just saying I'm just saying like you know
But when she was you know in her 30s 40s 50s. Yeah
She still how old is she now? Oh, she's
She reminds me a little bit of my mom now in her older age
Which is where the attraction? Yeah disappeared, but I had in her sister. She's like smoking hot
Yeah, you know talking about plastic surgery that what annoys me so much and I hear it way way way more in Los Angeles
But people being like, oh, just see her. She looks so old and it's they're talking about like surely McLean who's 90
It's like she she's supposed to look old and you will look old. Is she really McLean 90? I don't know. She's 80
Sadie
Just like this whole thing. I'm like, do you see how old?
You know so -and -so looked like Bruce Dern. I'm like, Bruce Dern is 79 years old. You are going to look old too. People get old
Uh, real quick, back to the movie for a second.
Bruce Dernes and hit playtals.
Carry on.
Yeah.
I mean, what the hell are you complaining about with this movie?
All right.
I'm not.
Uh, this, uh, they're, we're in a diner scene where the, we, the keeps jumping back to this
diner scene between Aniston and the dancer from summer school, he's eating some kind of
meatloaf dinner.
It looks delicious.
I thought it was like a Thanksgiving meal, which is something I used to always order at, at
restaurants and diners.
I'd get they have a Thanksgiving special most diners have it. I love it. You get some turkey some stuffing some whatever. It's great
That's a meat loaf and mashed potatoes with gravy and then he's got a bowl of peas and carrots there. Looks fantastic
It looks so good. Jennifer's character is turning her nose to it saying it looks disgusting. I don't understand why but well
She's a snob. I think she's the her character in the movie is from LA. Okay
Did you notice that that cop just pulled over the leprechaun in his tiny car and was just
Casually addressing him like it was a normal situation a and that he was a normal person. He was talking to be
I I didn't I haven't been paying attention to the film. I the cops dead though. I saw him kill because that was a box of lucky charms
Was that supposed to be a little jump probably probably but I mean here's the I think he pulls it out and scales at it lucky clovers couldn't get the endorsement
So this is where he eats it and he spits it out and says it's disgusting.
Come on, let him have a little fun with the character.
But I'm saying, you pull over a guy who looks like that in a tiny car and the cop's
going to be like, hey, you think you're going a little fast?
Wait, give me a break.
Who's in the tiny car?
It just happened.
I mean, we've been talking.
Was the leprechaun in driving the car?
He was driving a tiny car.
No, he was not.
Yes, he was, Joe.
You know, have you not been looking at the screen at all?
I got real wrapped up in whatever the hell we were just talking about.
You know, wait a minute.
The leprechaun was driving a car, unless I hallucinated.
Are you sure it wasn't the paint that the Francis guy and the little kid?
Joe, the cop pulled him over and then he like tried to rip his face off.
That's why the cop was bloody and ran into the woods.
Holy shit, I missed that.
Why is, I don't think we're in Ireland by the way.
Nobody is an Irish accent.
it. They only did it at the beginning. But I think she drove for the Irish
show said why do you think this is an Ireland is probably because they don't
have the budget to be filming in Ireland. They're probably filming in Burbank.
Well, but nobody has an Irish accent. I think it's a beginning. That guy is from
Ireland and he's coming home from a trip to that to Ireland. We found a pot of
gold. Okay. I think that's the plot of this. And these green rolling hills that
she was driving through. I mean, that could be Northern California for Christ's
six. But why in a movie like this, would you have shots of her driving through
lush, iris countryside and not have it be Ireland? That's your question about
this movie. That's the decision that you're questioning about this movie. I have
many questions. When did he get hit in paint? Who the hell knows? I didn't even
notice the leprechaun driving a little car. Yeah, we should probably glance at the
movie once more. You know, and now Aniston is perplexed by the shoes on the
table, the leprechaun for some reason piled a bunch of shoes on the kitchen table and
they're trying to figure out why it happened or how it happened.
Where would Davis, uh, well, no, Bruce Dern, that's who actually wants to talk about back
to Bruce Dern.
What's your favorite Bruce Dern quote for a movie ever because I know I have my, um, Bruce
Dern quote, I mean, I, I used to obsessively know movie quotes and then eventually I had
to force them out of my brain to make room for more necessary things. I don't know. I live
when he screams in coming home, which is insane. I don't know. I never saw coming home.
Oh, what's that about? Look at the war, surely. Coming home from Vietnam. It's a
said he's been. I believe it was definitely nominated for best picture. Jane Fonda.
Sounds like a rough, rough ride. It's a great movie. But he's, she, let me try to remember. Oh,
So it's John Boyd in a wheelchair, and Jane Fonda falls in love with him and is like
screwing him, cheating on Bruce Darnett.
At some point Bruce Darnett goes insane and starts screaming at her, and it's some of
the craziest act I've ever seen, but I love it.
So Jane Fonda is cheating on her husband with a man in a wheelchair.
Pretty sure that's the case, yes.
Why would she be doing that?
It would be the other way around, shouldn't it?
Like I lost my legs and you didn't you cheat on me?
I think that's what the thing is, is that not only is it a masculating, but you're choosing
to go with this guy in a wheelchair, but he can still bone down. No, he can't. He goes down on her.
Very upsetting scene in board in the 4th of July when they go to the whorehouse and is it willing to
throw like like freaks out because the hookers making fun of him. Oh yeah, sure, because he can't get
it up. Yeah, I remember that. That's rough stuff, man. That's rough stuff. I was the time when they'd give
Oliver Stone $60 million a year to make a Vietnam movie with a lot of slides
and clips throughout the whole thing yeah he was I mean he was in a I can't even
say is anymore he wasn't amazing filmmaker for quite a while JFK well you told
me that you liked that last one he did I liked savages but it was hot trash but I
like hot trash but was the point that to make it hot did he try to make it hot
trash on purpose probably not probably not fair enough fair enough my favorite
Bruce Durin quote is from the Burbs, which is also my favorite, favorite horror comedy.
I believe Fangoria tweeted out the other day, what's your favorite horror comedy?
I responded to the Burbs hands down to Greg Graham, when he, uh, when Bruce Durin, when
they go to the neighbors house and Bruce Durin goes, all right, cut the shit clope, what's
the goddamn goofy noise you got coming out of your basement?
And as he's marching toward him, yeah, it's, the guy is just fucking great, man.
What's his relation to Laura during father father not brother always 30 at
years old or at least Bruce Dernan her mother is Diane lad and Diane lad
okay yes Diane lad who played her mom in wild at heart and other things I
sometimes get Diane lad and Barbara Hershey mixed up that's fair and also two
Debra Winger, I'll mix into there. I love Debra Winger. Now I pitched this to you the other day, my, my, my ideal movie. Sure.
I want to do a comedy, expendables. You said, well, oh yeah, we're texting about them. Yeah, you said
expendables. Well, let's get to the beginning of it. I want to make a movie with Dabney Coleman.
Okay. Howard Hesman. Yeah. And I figured out the perfect third guy.
uh coach Cregty Nelson yeah that is not the perfect guy yes it is he's not
even a comedian he's not funny Cregty Nelson's hilarious no he's just
plays it straight he's coach no you had a better person
I said John Lithgow but I think John Lithgow is really comedy either well
third rock he's hilarious okay Kelsey grammar we can get him all the
the expendables has 18 people in the cast and then you said if you're going to
It has been you got to get Martin mole. I want my point is is I want to get every funny guy that reminds me in some way of my dad
Sure into a movie again. Yeah, I get that being funny again
You mean like a guy with kind of a short fuse
Building
Yeah, it's had a mustache or does have a mustache. Right. I mean, Dabney Coleman is spearheading it. He's my Stallone
And as I told you, this movie would make maybe $60 ,000.
What's we could do it as a straight to VOD?
Yeah, those always make some money from what I hear.
Yeah.
Why not?
Like, you're picturing a trailer where it's like Coleman.
Mole.
No one's going to see this movie.
Not really like that.
A little more lighthearted.
It'd be a comedy.
Okay.
Well Coleman will but they're slipping on banana peels in the action. Yeah. What do they do? Are they doing it? Heist?
Now it's just a comedy. All right. I have no plot idea for it. I just I just want to get the 10 of them like
Sharing a box of donuts and like black coffee. Maybe there maybe here's a pitch. By the way, damning Coleman's breath
Always smells like coffee. That's a guarantee
I would go as far as to say the same for Martin Moe.
Well, pretty much all those guys, the breath smells like coffee.
How about this for a plot?
They're all gangsters.
They're all mob guys, okay?
Okay.
That have gotten, that are all, that have all been in the witness protection program for the last 30 years.
They're now so old, they're facing forms of dementia and forgetfulness and all this stuff.
The government or the whiteness protection program knows this could be a problem because
these guys might start leaking their mob secrets.
So they have an old man home just for guides that live too long in the whiteness protection
program.
And another actor who will name in a minute
pretends to have dementia to get put into that home to get all their secrets. There you go
And that's where you bring in your Ben Stiller your younger face. That's going to be your younger face. And that's your star
This could probably be a movie that we just shout out. It's better than it's better than most movie ideas that I hear on the regular basis
I think it's a really good idea. It's not bad at all
a guy pretending to have to mention he goes in and he's like, hey, tell me your secrets.
Now because he's going to write a book right now, ten old men with amnesia and Alzheimer's
doesn't necessarily make for a great comedic premise, but we could work with that.
Well, we don't have to use the term Alzheimer's, yeah, they're getting a little bit spotty.
We just kind of foggy, yeah, we just say like they got to go to this place because who knows
is what they'll blurred out in a conversation.
Yeah, like my dad's only 67,
and I mean, half the shit he says.
I mean, he's at a point where he's leaking secrets,
like he's bragging to me about things.
I don't even know what he's talking about.
Right.
Yeah, I like that.
Yeah, we call it witless protection.
Now that was, I think it was the layer of the cable guy.
Was it?
I think it was, actually.
I was going to make a point in what we called witness erection.
Okay, that's not bad.
I just thought of it just now.
But it gives it more credit if you say I always want it to if you lie makes it sound like you really had that idea
Perkin in there for a little while. I had right. Just you made a tattoo by the way
No, what is it? That is a vector graphic rendition of the Death Star from the Star Wars video game from the 80s
Pretty cool, right? What so like that's a huge tattoo. Yes
Do you how much thought you get that you wake up and go you know what I want?
I've been wanting something on the other side of this for a while because this
always looked too plain and stamped. Is that the Ghostbusters logo? Can somebody not
make that joke one time? It's not a joke. What is it if it's not the Ghostbusters?
No sign. No what? No. That's my personality. You have to ask that question. Your
personality is no. Am I a guy that goes with the flow? No. By the way my favorite
line in straight out of the Compton. Why do you always got to try to fuck that guy's
girls and DJ yellow goes why not yeah it was such a it's such a good line
why not I love so much and I think you know we're spacing these pockets out so
much that we're gonna be talking about movies that are like a month old yeah and
they hear it but straight out of Compton on our time came out yesterday we both
saw it for some reason not together I went in the day I went about five o 'clock I
loved it so much and it was long and I didn't care and I'll tell you I knew a lot
of the story already because I was such a fan of that music as it was
coming out. Yeah. And I was very obsessed with all that West Coast rap that
was coming out in the late eighties or eighties through the nineties and
right. So I know a lot of the story but I will tell you it was unbelievably
comprehensive. Yeah. I couldn't believe I love that they put in like the DOC
story that got in the car accident and his voice box got crushed. Yeah. And that
ruined his wrapping career.
Like, that was stuff I didn't think they would put in there.
I thought it was really just going to focus on NWA, right?
Yeah, it wasn't done in that way that like walk hard made fun of so good of,
like, two -pock, what are you doing here?
No, like, you know, these people were in it and they didn't need to touch on
everybody, but like, every time they brought in, like, Snoop or whatever,
you'd be like, awesome.
Yeah, the audience, when I saw it, the audience was applauding.
Yeah, they were cheering at times.
Like, two -pock, they were cheering.
like I just got chills it was really fun looks a lot more accurate than the
Snoop but Snoop sounded like snows. I saw the film with Matt McCarty and his
lovely wife Glennis. Yes. We walked out of the theater and Matt's words were
how the fuck did they get two puck to play two puck. Yeah, I thought maybe they
hired they signed the hologram. That guy was from Coachella. It was unsettling how
much he looked like. Yeah. Almost sounded like him. Yeah. Yeah. And he's really good.
Son looks exactly like a like cube. Yeah, they did you know what wipe out all the
severe beatings of women that went on but I'm okay with it like Dr. Dre beating the shit out of
D. Barnes. They cut that out. Probably should have been in the film, but I'm sure Dr. Dre was like they made Dr.
Dre look like he was a pussycat in the movie. And Dr. Dre is not a pussycat. They made easy look kind of like a pussycat. Yeah,
Like this guy seems like a great guy. Yeah, it was a little cleaned up
I also liked when he said I also really liked the line when they're at the party the wet and wild pool party
Sure, and easy he says are we done here and Jerry hella goes. Yeah, he goes. Okay. I am going to fuck them
Yeah, I was like I love this guy. Yeah, yeah, well the guy who played easy. Yeah, I think stole the show excellent
He was tremendous in it. Yeah, now did you by the way the leprechaun just got his hand cut off. Yeah, let's at least look at this movie
It's crawling up up a what powers does a leprechaun not have the fucking four leaf clover
That's the only thing that can stop the hand can crawl and then regenerate on its own watch
He's gonna reattach his fucking hand cuz he has a hand in the other movies
Anyway
the
The what's it called? Oh a Giovanni. Love Giovanni in it. Is he never not good playing that guy?
He's I loved him in the Brian Wilson movie too somebody had a great tweet today
I don't know who but it was like so what I'm gathering from every movie release lately is that Paul Giamatti ruins music
Shows up and ruined the beach boys ruins it, but uh
Yeah, he he was really great in it
And I also loved how even though I knew the story like the first half you're kind of like
Skas all right, you know, he didn't play it like you know the stupid white guy who doesn't get the music
He seemed to genuinely be a fan, genuinely like what they were saying, but just be, you know, some people who do those shitty business practices can't stop.
I read an interview with F. Gary Gray and they said, why we were surprised you didn't give it to Jerry Heller harder.
Yeah. And he was like, well, he's a boy. We didn't, we weren't trying to paint him out to be like a demon man.
Yeah. He's like, you know, we wanted to portray the guy with some fairness.
Yeah, yeah, if Gary Gray is a name that if you asked a hundred people
One person would know that man, right
He's direct he directed Friday. Yeah, the Italian job, which was like a massive hit. Yeah, he directed set it off
Which is a great movie. Yeah, he did the negotiator, which is a great movie. He did straight it up
Hampton, did he do the, did he do belly?
No, that was hype Williams, okay.
But it's like, how many great moves
does this guy have to make before somebody,
and this is the one that's gonna get him the recognition.
Yeah, this is being, this is being very talked about
and his name, it was shot awesome.
This is not like he was a higher gun director
to direct the movie and get a job done.
This is like, he developed this with Dr. Dre.
Yeah, like, you know, his name is all over this thing.
Like this is, he's gonna finally get his moment from this.
He should he's been a he's been a great director since Friday was 1995
Like his movies always have a lot of energy. They're always shot really cool. I love the guy
I also really spoil our alert if you don't want to hear this cover yours for a second
I always really I also really enjoyed the closing credits of the film. Yeah when they were cheering
Everybody in the theater was cheering like when they were showing the real clips
Oh, yeah, then you'd see the scene from Friday
Yeah, and the day
Yeah, and then like the Dr. Dre beats transaction and right Eminem and 50 cent being like we'd be nothing without Dr. Dre
Yeah, it was just really a cool movie man very inspiring to back when musicians were actually rebellious and yeah, you know
Yeah, I mean Q being that sort of politically aware was very cool
I didn't really know that aspect of it. No, you know from his lyrics, but it's kind of like I didn't realize him
like that interview was such a funny scene with that what we're talking about
earlier the Jewish defamation league yeah it was uh yeah the uh yeah when he
goes to shake the guy's hand and he goes what did he say what's your name
fuck get the fuck out of my house I don't eat a dick get out of my dick get the fuck out
here yeah it was uh it was a great movie yeah well great movie I uh back to
leprechaun. Yeah, I mean, uh, no, they're all still alive. But there's been, they, they, they, they, they, they, they brought in needless, there was clearly a decision made to bring in auxiliary characters to kill. So this core group could stay alive. Right. I guess because they thought maybe all these people would be in the sequel. None of them are in the sequel. Yeah, literally none of them. I mean, Aniston, the very next year was the one of the biggest stars in the world.
Aniston, do you think that she maybe in her contract was supposed to come back for the sequel and there was some heavy negotiations that had to go on?
No.
Okay.
Sometimes they do that.
No, I don't think so.
I think she, they probably, you know, I think she probably saw this as a very obvious stepping stone at one point.
Yeah.
And then got a gig and said, yeah, I would never do the sequel to that movie.
So many of our biggest actresses got their start in terrible arm. I mean, it's crazy.
We're reading it online last episode. All those people that started in the children of the corn sequels. Yeah.
By the way, I told you I had final sacrifice the part two on DVD as a bonus movie,
with Storm of the Century.
I finally watched it the other day. I mean, it's... I couldn't believe how fucking bad it was.
And it's only the second one.
I mean it was like so imagine what the fifth one was like oh man the leprechaun just appeared
So wait if he can teleport he appeared, but he appeared in like some sort of electromagnetic way what
He can also he also has
Telekinesis, but wait a second if he can disappear and reappear why didn't he just disappear when the guy was trying to shoot him earlier?
There doesn't there don't seem to be any rules and regulations here. That's what ever grade horror movie needs. What gremlins understands very well. You need clear rules.
Yep. I agree. Clear rule or else the audience is like what like you got to know what kills it. What strengthens it. Whatever else.
Exactly. Exactly.
exactly. Stablish what the weaknesses are, establish what its limitations are. That's
the most important part. Yeah. I mean, the limitations are the cleannest version of
that because that guy, the Chinese guy literally says it, he says the three rules as it fades
to black and then comes up on the credits. Yeah. Like you're like, okay, got it. Let's do
it, gremlins. And then it's amazing. Never never get it wet. Never give it daylight. Never
No matter what you do, never, never feed it after midnight.
That would always kind of bothered me.
It's always after midnight somewhere.
It bothers a lot of people.
Never bothered me until somebody said it to me.
And honestly, when the person said it to me,
I wanted to punch them in the face.
Because I was like, you have a brain
that then that isn't good for movies.
And sometimes people really bug me with that shit.
Just coming at, like with a purely logic way
to like some movie I've loved my entire life.
And it's such a bummer.
I mean, but I get it. I understand. I just don't I that's a weird rule, especially when they're coming from China. That means when you're feeding it in America, it's after midnight China. That is true.
So that bugs me a little bit. Also kind of bugs me that one of them that they still one of them somehow knows that it'll morph into this demonic Gremlin.
If it eats after midnight, so it purposely, purposefully choose the clock wire to trick
Zach Galligan?
One of the Gremlins knows.
Yeah, stripe.
Well, there's the, yeah, stripe was established as a very smart mischievous Gremlin.
But would it, but what a, my question is this a dog, like a dog or a, not dog, but a caterpillar
has no concept of its own evolution.
It doesn't know like, I gotta get in that cocoon so I can turn the little butterfly.
It's just what it does, but the ground ones. I think we're paying it as being fairly intelligent. That's obvious.
Never tell you the time I saw that Jack Galligan guy. No, how did you know? Is he still at the sun?
He lived in my neighborhood in New York. Okay
Two times I met him the second. The first time I met him at just a light and I said I love wax work
Really said thank you. It's one of my favorite horror movies. Okay. You should do it on here. It's not in demand on all right
his wax work like wax figures that come to life. So wax means well, let's save it for the wax work episode. All right, but essentially.
Anyway, that was the first time, and it was very whatever. The second time I was standing on my front stoop, he walked by.
I realize it was him. I jogged down the stairs.
By the time I got down the stairs, he was like half a block away, and I yelled, Zach turns around looks looked horrified.
I didn't know what was going on and he looks at me with these with this expression like do I know you yeah, and I go
I love Grandlands and he goes oh, I'm sorry. I thought I knew you for a second because you yelled my name
And I said no, he goes well, thanks a lot man. Yeah, and he just walked home. I guess I'm assuming walk to him
Does he still act or is he like an accountant now?
I bet he's like a writer or producer or like a TV director those guys all
Yeah, you're going to like T Andrew McCarthy does a lot of smart V directing now
For savage directs for savage fridge. I was also still an act starring in a new sitcom. I hear it's great
I a lot of friends working on a really success. Who else is in it roblo
And is it a one a single camera is it like a live audience thing? It's a single cam. It's called the grinder. It's about a
Guy who's been playing a TV lawyer for many years and then he goes home and thinks he has the skills to be an actual lawyer with his actual lawyer brother
I love it
I love it. Fred Savage is one of the best guys in the world yet another name
drop. I want to meet Fred Savage. I'm pissed you've never introduced me to the
guy. Well, you can come to one of my poker nights. He usually plays. We also get
lunch a lot. I could bring you. Now would he mind if I came to a poker night and
narrated it? I'll add Daniel Stern. He's got a pretty good sense of humor about
those things. He might tell you to shut up at some point. I'm kidding, Pat. I'm not
really going to do that. I just thought maybe it'd make us laugh right now. Yeah,
Well, I mean, I wouldn't go. Hey, Fred, I love little monsters. No, I'm going straight to the wizard on that one. Okay, Fred the wizard. You know, monsters scared the shit out of me when I was a kid, which is why I didn't watch a lot of horror movies. That was wrong with you. Sorry.
my pet monster scared me to cartoon are you joking no I was a pussy I'm not gonna argue that
that's beyond pussy yeah that's like emotional damage or something yeah I had a lot of
severe emotional damage but I'm still dealing with okay sorry take it back then it's a rocky road
to hell now they've broken yet another rule in this leprechaun movie they shot him and he jumped
right back up again. I mean at the beginning of the film, the guy shot him and he was knocked
out long enough that he could pick up, walk to the leprechaun, pick him up, throw him into
the crate. Look, I'm starting to think they didn't put a lot of work into the screenplay
of leprechaun. Yeah, I'm starting to feel that way too, Pat. I hate to say it. See, they
keep shooting him. Yeah. And then he just is gonna get right up again. See? The phone's ringing.
I had that phone. We all had that phone. I had to answer the phone. Hello, Walsh
residents, Patrick speaking. No wonder you were scared of my pet monster. Yeah, I know. Jesus
sounds like it was a metaphor for your family. My pet monster had chains. I had
metaphorical chains as well. Yeah. Yeah, the constraints. Yeah, the constraints put on you by
parents that wanted you to act too cordially. It is crazy. What is this now, Joe?
That was a complete rip of Nightmare on Elm Street. Yeah. For those of you
watching, Jennifer asked to answer the phone, which was the leprechaun
because he can just magically make the phone ring and be on the phone somehow
without using another phone. And then his hand came through the phone to a
tiny doll hand yeah so we can also minimize his body parts apparently is it is it that he's
making them hallucinate these things no I don't think so how do you do the I think that kid was
in like three ninjas or something how do you do the time check without stopping the movie with the
Apple TV hit the arrow no I wouldn't do that right get us off track with the down arrow I wouldn't do
it. I don't know. I need to know how much is left in this movie. I don't trust the Apple TV
remote. I have lost it one million times in the cushions of the couch. Peanows tapes his to a piece
of a big piece of cardboard, which is sensible, but it makes it look like white trash. Yeah, I've
been over there and I'm like, you guys got to find a like Velcro it to the side of the couch or something
that nobody can see. He's got it like a gas station bathroom key. Yeah it's
real trashy looking. Beat if you're listening. Your house is trashy. I need to know
how much time has left in this film. We got to have maybe 15. This is our third
episode. It's the first time I felt tortured mildly. I agree. This is not a good film.
It's a terrible film. I mean, Aniston is kind of caring me. I like that they
have her in a pair of shorts. My favorite
Aniston scene is when she walks naked
through the apartment in the break up.
Sure. Great stuff. Oh, God. And
doesn't she get a wax right before?
Yes. God, dammit. I love her in that
body with that German. She's perfection
in that movie. I love her so much in that
movie. I agree with her side of the
arguments. Yeah, no, I get mad at Vince
bottom. Like, why doesn't he get up and
help her do the damn dishes right now?
I agree. And he's so like, you know, so indifferent to her. And when she finally walks away,
it's like, yeah, which is kind of the beauty of the movie, because you see yourself in it,
whenever you look back at a relationship, you're like, why didn't I do this or why didn't I do that?
That's what the movie kind of makes you feel like. You know, in my head, they got back together.
They run into each other. Maybe they did. The movie and they had that really nice smile in exchange
change at Christmas time and I'm saying by new years they were humping again. I wouldn't
be surprised. They both look back at each other. They did. They did. He changed, you know,
what's the fuck? So now the leprechaun just reappeared on the back of their truck. By the
way, the last time his roller skates last time he appeared, it was blue light. This time
it was green light. No, it was green last time too. No, it was green when he moved the
pot, the bag of gold, but it was blue when he came. You see what just happened, Pat? He's
We're on a roller skate.
That's a looney tune shit right there.
They're doing looney tune shit.
Here's, and he went through a fence
into the shape of the leprechaun is the hole.
Yeah, in the fence.
Now here's my question.
If this fucking guy can disappear and reappear,
did a Benny Hill tape speed up?
They did, he just skated off all fast.
If this guy can disappear and reappear,
why doesn't he just disappear and reappear in the car,
instead of riding on the back of it,
like Michael J. Foxx and back to the future?
Thousand percent.
Also when he lost the car and crashed in the fence, why is he skating to get back of it to to it and not just disappearing and reappearing where she is 2000 percent agree?
The hell is going on.
Somebody just wasn't wasn't given the proper notes on the script, you know, I mean they were it's it's I mean these to me are clearly executive notes.
The old security guard asleep, but I just can't imagine any writer would be like this is a good idea.
Well, it's probably the writer director was like well, we should look them up
You know, maybe he made a horrible horrible prime. I'm gonna look him up, but
narrate narrate what's happening here because I believe what's going on is she is
She is going to now find the Irish guy that trapped him at the beginning of the movie
I've own this house before they lived in it. It's ten years later. He's now in a nursing home or something, right?
So let the people know what's going on
So we don't have dead air while I look up this shot reminds me of that great scene and exercises three
you what you showed me which was a horrifying scene with the sit the sheers yeah when that
nurse comes running out that was extra history is one of the scariest movies I've ever seen
it was great that was one of our first hangs Joe it was our first hang yeah we we got
breakfast at a diner yeah yes I had some kind of goddamn egg plate with beans and annoyed
the shit out of me I remember giving you a very critical I had a Mexican because we're
Like this Philly style diner. He's like clearly you get the pancakes. Yeah, I got the wave host red chair
I tried to not eat like a loaf of bread in the morning
All right, uh, I'm looking Mark Jones wrote and directed this yeah
All right. Well, that's not a good sign. No. Maybe these were his ideas and maybe he did the others. I don't know
Oh, and he did he did all of them anything else
Okay, so this is just a guy
Yeah, I did he was just gonna go down a road and not get off of it. I'll say Joe. I'm 46 writing credits 46
Yeah, leprecha all the leprecha I'm all just read with the
No, I am all the leprecha at least rumpel stilt skin, which is essentially that was also world Davis, right?
I don't think so. Okay. It's a variation of it's it's it's leprecha. It is leprecha basically the same thing
So she found the old guy, so obviously this guy has his back to us. Is this a me the leprecha? Yeah, yeah
yeah, so where's the guy? Yeah, where's he? Where's O 'Grady? Did he kill O 'Grady? I would
assume. Why don't you teleport to her side and slither throat, leprechaun? He's not chasing
her in a wheelchair. Yeah, like he's in the wheelchair. And they're doing the Benny Hill
thing again. Yeah, speeding it up. This movie is a lump of shit, man. I'm sorry, I don't
to criticize other people's art, art. Yeah, I don't, I really don't like to do that.
Where'd he done prior to leprechaun? Was there a hit that enabled him to write and direct us?
Well, a lot of TV work. A couple episodes are rip tied. Rip tied, what's that about?
You don't remember rip tied? No, it was like a sequestie SV. It was like a boat show with cops.
boat cops two Vietnam vets now work as private eyes and sunny Southern
California. Oh, that sounds good. Nick and Cody are the muscles and Murray is the
computer wizard. All right, that sounds great actually. Yeah, it was like one of
those like, you know, scarecrow and Mrs. King kind of thing. Sure. You know, a lot of fun
lot of fun. Yeah, a lot of last eight episodes of the 18. Okay. Two episodes of
Hunter. All right, we'll get for him. My grandpa was obsessed with Hunter. I loved
Hunter as a kid. Hunters that like a bold. Fred Dryer for again. There's another guy we'll get in our football player. Yeah, another guy that looked just like my dad. Yeah, my grandpa. I think loved Hunter because he kind of looked like Hunter wrote an episode of Al.
The animated series. Oh,
Oh, wrote an episode of police academy, the animated series.
Wasn't it weird that there was a police academy cartoon?
That movie was like all tits and bush.
Yeah.
Well, there's less nudity than you think
and the other ones don't have any really.
But the running gag through the first three
is Leslie, I forget that lady's name.
The big blonde, getting tossed repeatedly into pools.
Yeah, oh yeah.
And her tits, showing through her t -shirt.
Right. Yeah, I remember some early jerking to those movies.
I don't think I've ever told you this.
I when I was an NBC page at 30 Rock in New York, I gave tours of the studios.
And one morning I was like so hung over like every blink kind of hurt.
And I had a eight, I think at 8 a .m. tour and I was taking this tour group around 30
Rock. We get to the control center and they show you on like 20 TVs,
what's being aired currently on NBC right and I look in there and there was a
talk show and I've looked it up I know I wasn't dreaming it it actually happened
it was an alph talk show oh yeah I remember that it was alph conducting a
legitimate seemingly serious interview with Dennis Franz about his craft and for
two minutes there was no jokes and alph's just like so now what brought you to
NYPD Blue. Was it the script? I was blown away and I laughed so hard at this because I was so hungover
that Alph was basically like Charlie Rose. Alph's always really hit my funny bomb from when I was
a little kid. One of my early bits was and this was true that I turned off an episode of the Cosmos
hosted by Carl Sagan. Yeah. Because during a commercial break I stumbled upon the Alph talk show.
Yeah, and the bit was this is why I will never achieve anything in my life like I was more interested in the
There's a picture of me to go back to my emotionally damaging childhood
I my birthday is January 5th and every year
I would invite a bunch of people to my party and it would get snowed out every year and
My family wouldn't come my friends wouldn't come no one would come because of the snow and just ring after ring after ring on the phone
my mom would answer it look over at me sadly and be like oh it looks like
Keith's not gonna make it either it looks like grandma and grandpa are gonna
come either so just one after the next oh and there's a picture of me crying
into an alf cake that my parents have did they at least get you presents yeah
they got me I mean they did their best got me presents but like there's a full
alf cake with not one slice cut out of it and I'm crying with my head in my
hands at about age seven. Which is really that picture, if I can track it down, is my
childhood in a nutshell, me crying into an earthquake.
Would they risk it? By the way, the leprechaun just got shot again. And now he's out this
time. Now he's out. He's dead. He's out. But I don't know if he's dead, but he's out. He's
out. They did find out that they need to get a fully clovered to stop him. She heard
that from the guy. So, yeah, the leprechaun kills him, hangs him from an elevator shaft,
and he's like, hey, you should find a four -leave, he's still alive. The leprechaun doesn't
finish the job. With his dying breath. You've got to find a clover.
Laddie. Lassie, probably. Lassie. Yeah, so now they're in the field looking for four -leave
clovers to stop the leprechaun, like much like a scene from Patch Childhood. What is this
guy up too. Bucks them. Bucks ton. Bucks ton. Francis. I want some of the other day too.
Actually coincidentally, I was like, I was wondering what. Francis. I was wondering what was
happened. What had happened to him and what happened to the guy that played, uh, uh, uh,
in Beetlejuice. Oh, the fact guy. Worth a. Worth though. Yeah. He died. Did you know that?
They didn't know that one. Yeah. He died because he had some mobility issues. It's very
He said he fell in his house and hit his head, died.
Yeah, that sucks.
I love that guy.
Yeah, I loved him.
I love Captain Harris and the movie and Jeffrey Jones.
Everybody in the movie.
It's a home run.
It's a grand slam, I would say.
It really is.
Tour de force.
Peyton in that movie was just like inventing shit.
Like that was like one of the craziest performances of all time.
Jeffrey Jones.
Jeffrey Jones was arrested for child pornography.
Yeah, he was.
And the guy could still make me laugh.
Yeah, the first bill was day off and Beetlejuice. That's how funny. I know I feel bad even saying that out loud now Jones
It'd be a controversial pick, but he'd fit right into our movie because I guarantee his breath smells like coffee and he has a mustache
I agree, and he was funny in the 80s. I agree. Let's get him on board. I agree. We'll make him promise not to look at any child porn while he's filming our movie
The look again. This is the third podcast now. We've discussed child porn
didn't didn't think we could get it in, but here we are.
I didn't even realize we were doing it.
Mark Holtin is the man who played Francis.
Okay.
He was also in Teen Wolf, if you remember.
I do indeed.
He also played Casey in the John Wayne Casey movie.
Oh, I bet that's horrifying.
Our friend Vince Avril.
Yeah.
Good friend of ours.
Love Vince.
He is very frightened of horror films.
he does not care for them. I want to get him on the podcast just to watch how scared he gets.
Okay. I've had him leave my house when I put on something scary before because he couldn't handle it.
I was, I, I respect that. Uh, but he said the last time he looked at anything horror related,
he goes, I turned on Showtime. There was that movie Gacy on and that fat guy from Peewee's big
adventure played games. There you go. And he goes, he's trying to push this child's head to a bear trap.
It disturbed me. That sounds really disturbing. Yeah, you know what I don't think it's fair frankly. What's that is that?
When you go see a comedy
like I saw a train wreck you go and
You're forced to watch three four really horrifying horror movie trailers
I don't think that's fair to people who don't want to see that, you know?
I usually find that the genres of the trailers reflect the genre of this is not always the case though really it's not always the case and when I saw vacation I saw one of the scariest horror movie trailers I've ever seen I don't I wish I remember what it was called but it was really freaky what was the trailer.
You know it was just like real torturing kind of vibe and it was very intense. He had a red band instead of a green band at the beginning.
really in front of vacation yeah and it was a horror movie trailer and I was
like well what about the people who came to see this family comedy uh what's
not a family comedy it's a comedy about a family our rated comedy comedy about a
family uh family this is the credit on actor Mark Holton's IMDB that I'm most
intrigued by okay uh oh by the way they slingshot it at Fort Leif clover to
Capricorn's mouth and he's melting. Now he's turned pink lights and some green. Very reminiscent of the Gremlins death here. Yeah, when Spike falls into the pond or no in the daylight.
Except somehow Gremlins filmed 10 years earlier had better special effects. This is the actor the credit. I want to see Francis from Peewee's big adventure.
And he was on Tim and Eric's awesome show. Great job. Played a character one episode. His character name was BM Farts.
No, I don't remember that I don't remember either I want to see it though. That's funny
Yeah, well, I guess he still works occasionally that's probably a guy who had to find another career
Now he's
2008 up till 2008 looks like steady work. All right
That's kind of cool makeup effects there
It looks like well it again it looks like the grandma's yeah, it's the exact same effect
It looks kind of like remember that fruit and vegetable grandma and grandma's too. I hate grandma's too
I fucking love Grimmons to you're out of your fucking mind. You know, it's
Hailed as like a lost classic now
It's got a whole lot of respect these days, and I've always loved it explained to me. I mean, I get that it's a tire
I mean, it's a comedy. It's kind of like a loony tunes type deal. Yeah, why but why did they go that route and they're making fun of trump
25 years ahead of its time. Why did they go that route with it though? I think Joe Danty
Who it was a great director. I like Dantie. What is he directly lately a lot of like straight to the OD shit
But I really loved him for that 10 years stretch. I loved all his movies
And I think he kind of leans more towards
Comedy, you know, like I think he wants his movies to be kind of fun
Well, I mean, it's it was certainly a bold choice for a sequel. I just wanted another Gremlins though
I also love that the projector broke when you saw it in the theater because the Gremlins were fucking
with it. And it felt really real and it was really cool. And then when you
rented it, they shot a different version where it seemed like your VCR tape was
being torn up. Now in that was pretty cool. In the version with the video tape
being ripped up, just Hogan still jump up somehow. Yes. Yes. That's pretty cool.
Hogan's in there. Yeah. I remember that. What people sure got over that Hogan
scandal quick. These things flare up now for like 30 seconds. Everyone's like, oh,
fuck Hogan. Like they ever gave a shit about Hulk Hogan to begin with. Because he
He said, what did he say?
I'm not going to say what he said,
but he said some pretty outlandishly racist stuff.
I mean, I get it.
It's just, I'm kind of like,
why are you allowing yourself to get so upset
about whole Kogan?
But wait a second.
He has no effect on your life.
Why, that tape came out eight years ago,
and nobody said anything, did that part not come out?
I think it was part of maybe his divorce hearings.
This came out or something, I don't.
Oh yeah, okay, I think I heard that.
I've never been so relieved by the way,
the credits have been rolling for about 20 seconds.
Yeah, we were paying no attention
and yet you just felt that you wanted the movie to be over.
Thank you.
It was really bad.
This guy's name is John Overacker.
Can we make a pack right now?
Yeah.
No more leprechaun movies on the podcast.
Yeah, obviously, Joe.
None of them.
No, but here's the thing.
a few months goes by you think I'll be funny like we thought today it'll be funny to watch it
because it's not that great yeah no well he had had one and a half stars from the very very
loose standards of Netflix viewers so that tells you that yeah well anyway
patty I still had a nice time Joe as I always do and I hope our listeners did as well
I had a great time I had a great time it's always nice to sit on a love seat with you and watch
You've been listening to We'll See You In Hell.
It's been a presentation of the Fangoria Podcast Network.
Produced by Thomas DeFail,
and Executive Produced by Ken Haley,
of Fangoria Entertainment.
For press opportunities,
advertising, inquiries,
and information about We'll See You In Hell.
Please contact Ken via email.
His address is Ken at Fangoria .com.
K -E -N at Fangoria .com.
Thanks a lot, guys.
We'll see you next time.
In Hell.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry