Summer is here, and Bet MGM Casino is coming in hot with casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer, or check out our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz, only available at Bet MGM Casino.
Spin on spectacular slot favorites like Cash Eruption, 88 Fortunes, Mystery of the Lamp, Rakin' Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand.
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action.
Firestone Complete Auto Care's epic savings event is the sign you need to stop putting off your car's maintenance.
And you can save up to $100 on tires and services while you're at it.
Don't wait. Call Firestone Complete Auto Care for an appointment.
Hello, everybody. Welcome to Wolf, See You in Hell.
Oh, the Tales from the Dark Side episode. You know that. You read it before you downloaded it. Am I wrong, Pat?
You're not wrong, Joe.
This is Joe DeRosa on one side of your head.
And Pat Walsh on the other.
That's right. We're on either side of your head so you can watch the movie up the middle if you choose to do so.
The We'll See You in Hell podcast is now part of the Fangoria Podcast Network.
For more info about the network, including other programs, how to follow this show, how to follow those shows or to find episodes of any show, please visit fangoria .com.
Let's get on with it. I'm excited about watching this tonight.
By the way, people at home start queuing up your Netflix.
Do you want to tell them about how we're going to be at the Mile High Horror Festival?
Why don't we? Yeah. Yeah. Well, we'll tell them about that.
Well, you find Tales from the Dark Side, hit play, pause it on as soon as it starts so we can all start together in a few moments here.
Yes. Why don't you tell them, Pat?
OK. I'm just a little concerned I'll get the date wrong.
But we're going to be in Denver, Colorado, doing the podcast live.
We're not 100 percent sure we're allowed to tell you what the movie is, so we're not going to.
We will closer to the date.
And that date is October 3rd, which is a Saturday.
And we will be, if I'm not mistaken, 820 in the morning.
I think we can tell them now because this is going to come out the week of the festival.
OK, then let's do it.
It's we're doing Maniac Cop 2. Maniac Cop 2, which I have never seen.
I'm going to watch it ahead of time. Yeah, I'm looking forward to it.
You haven't seen it either. I have.
I have not seen it. And I'm embarrassed to say that I've seen Maniac.
I've seen Cop and a half. I've seen Stopper.
My mom will shoot. I've read Maniac McGee.
I've seen Mr. Magoo. I never knew.
I never Maniac Cop 2. I always thought Maniac Cop was I didn't I didn't know it was like so lauded as a as a as a series.
But I wouldn't have even thought horror necessarily.
I thought I would have thought Maniac Cop was like a extra violent, dirty, hairy kind of thing.
Well, yeah, they told us that what we were doing is Maniac Cop 2 and beloved.
And we're going to seem like buffoons because it's apparently very beloved in the horror community.
Well, here's the thing. We're not going to seem like buffoons.
Number one, have a little. I hate seeming like a buffoon.
Have a little more self -esteem than that. We're going to do just fine.
OK, there's nothing wrong with vulnerability.
That's what I've learned in this business. Sure.
Is is you got to have a little vulnerability.
The only comedians I like are vulnerable and let you in.
Who wants a conceited comedian? Yeah, exactly.
You got to go out there. You got to say, hey, folks, I'm not perfect.
I'm sorry. I've never seen this before.
But I just watched it last week and I loved it. Right.
You come out and you're like, hey, I had a threesome last night.
Then everybody's like, oh, yeah.
Come out and you're like, hey, I don't know how to talk to a girl.
Then everybody loves you. Exactly.
That's my advice for upcoming comedians.
And I would also say Goyle. I agree with that.
Let's start this movie. Right.
And we can, you know. Oh, and that was the one other thing I wanted to say was when I when Fangoria told us eight
thirty in the eight twenty in the morning.
I was like, what? Who the hell was going to come to a live podcast?
They tried to write and their response was people will always come for maniac to.
Yeah, that's when a maniac cop to excuse me.
I love it. That's when I knew we had a goodie on our hands.
Yeah, I can't wait to watch it.
I'll be drinking at eight twenty in the morning that day.
You know, you think it's insane.
How could I possibly drink at eight twenty in the morning?
And then you remember old friend Bloody Mary.
Well, I go for screwdriver. That's fine, too.
There's a whole line of breakfast drinks that you forget about to help the alcoholic who might enjoy a brunch.
You should have an aisle for that supermarket.
All right. You should be all queued up by now and paused on the first frame or so of the movie.
We'll say one is the stars starting to come into the Paramount logo, which is my favorite logo of all time.
We'll say one, two, three, play and we all hit play on play.
Here we go. One, two, three, play and we're rolling.
The stars are swirling their way around the mountain.
All right. This is Tales from the Dark Side.
The movie came out in 1990, turned a nice little profit for Paramount Pictures.
I thought I had never seen it, but as I watched it earlier tonight,
I started watching them ahead of time because otherwise I focus on the plot and I don't talk as much.
I realize I had seen the opening, which we're about to see, where Deborah Harry has a young Joey Lawrence.
It's not Joey Lawrence. Daniel Lawrence. Yeah.
The kid from actually Planshine is one of my favorite movies.
They are brothers. They look exactly alike. Yeah.
And he's locked up in the kitchen.
And I remember being horrified by it. I watched it.
And now it's it plays as a comedy, if anything.
Yeah, it's it's it's like the lighthearted wraparound story, even though the premise is that she's going to eat him.
Right. But I like a movie with a good reach around story.
Folks, these are the jokes, folks.
But yeah, I saw this in the theater on opening weekend.
I couldn't wait because I was such a Tales from the Dark Side TV show fan and I was mesmerized to the entire thing.
See, now you've one part of it scared me. I loved every minute.
OK. Yeah. See, you said one of your favorites of all time in the horror genre.
I'm I'm nowhere near that.
And I think it probably has to do with when you saw it.
For example, I showed you Tremors, which I would consider one of my favorites of all time.
And you know, you enjoyed it, but were fairly indifferent.
I was I was indifferent. I enjoyed Tremors.
But to me, Tremors is more of a of an action comedy with horror elements in it.
It's fair. It's more of a canine, if you will, or a turner in hooch.
Tremors was with my style of scary when I was that age where I could handle literally not scary.
There's literally nothing scary in it.
Oh, there is a lot of monster attacks.
I'm saying I couldn't handle much and it was right up my alley.
No one would say like, oh, Tremors was fucking sick, bro.
I also like a monster with a hell of a lot of fun.
I like a monster with some personality.
I'm not a fan of just a big, you know, lumbering worm.
I think doesn't really mean a grab what?
Yeah, grab what? Sorry.
Are you going to see the new Tremors when it comes out?
Or I think it just did or it's about to.
They're up to like five.
And I've been talking about it for years and they actually just discussed it on key and peel.
But I went with the series for about three until they had them up and walking around like dogs,
which is the whole hook is that, hey, we got a movie about giant underground worms.
And they just make them walk around like little dogs.
Right.
Well, make Kujo again if you're going to do that Tremors people.
I don't have a beef with a worm dog.
No, it's one of the animals I'd like to see if I think was definitely definitely had the most effective worm dog.
Yeah, I'd like there's that Twilight Zone where the kid imagines the monsters.
Yeah.
And and like he always imagines them like with like eight eyes and stuff.
Right.
I imagine a dog with like eight eyes.
It's called It's a Good Life.
Then the kid will be like the kid will be like, that dog was funny.
I made it at eight eyes, but I got bored with it.
So I made him go dead.
So my point is, if I was the kid that could do that, I didn't vent the worm dog and then I'd make it go dead.
Well, I didn't really follow that joke, but I hope you enjoyed yourself.
I did the first and last.
There's three segments on this wraparound deal.
My favorite type of horror anthology horror.
I love it.
Yeah, I know you love it.
I like it kind of like it's fun.
I wish this movie had had three different directors like a Twilight Zone the movie.
It felt very stylistically similar to me.
Well, it's it's but it's it's what now let me tell you why I love the movie.
My favorite franchise and horror is Creepshow.
Creepshow one and two to me are masterful films.
This is arguably maybe the best of the three.
It's not called Creepshow, but it's the same group of people.
It's Tom Savini, George A. Romero and Stephen King were behind this.
One of the stories in this cat from hell was supposed to be in Creepshow two.
But they I guess because of budgetary reasons, they cut two stories out.
So it did make it into this and have the money to have a cat chase around a guy in a damn wheelchair.
Well, that's a little more to the story than that.
But I guess the one special effects.
For the most part, it's a guy in a wheelchair yelling Tom.
Tom Savini has gone on record as saying this is unofficially Creepshow three.
There is a movie called Creepshow three, but none of the original Creepshow people have anything to do with it.
It's an abomination.
So how did they get the rights then?
I think they probably the rights to the name were just probably up.
And it's not like they recreated any characters, you know?
Yeah. So but in my opinion, Creepshow one, Creepshow two and Tales from the Darks of the movie.
It's a it's a virtually flawless horror trilogy, which is very hard to come by, as even the most astute horror fan would agree.
Yeah, I think I find them pleasant diversions.
What is that?
You know, like they're they're kind of middle of the road.
Cool little scary stories to me, but I don't think of them as being great horror films.
You mean the anthology stories?
The whole shebang. Yeah, I well, look, I will say anthology is not for everybody.
Certain people get annoyed because it's too they feel like they can't settle into it.
Yeah, it's a little too short to get you to invest in anything.
And then right up my alley, it's right up my short attention span alley.
Well, for this MTV generation, Joe, you know, you're about 30, 40 years younger than me.
So give me give me a give me a hot 12 to 18 minute tale any day of the week.
I mean, I love it. Twilight Zone, about a hot 12 to 18 year old tale.
I'm not into that, but you neither.
I'm glad you squeezed in another pedophilia.
I certainly did. Yeah, there you go.
I held back a terrible joke just there that I guess I'll share with you.
Let's just say it involved the phrase squeezed it in.
I imagined I imagined as much folks.
Tales from the Dark Side, the movie, stars Steve Buscemi and Julianne Moore in maybe,
if not their first film, an early one for both of them.
Well, that was kind of cool for me. If you're watching along with us, the first story is starting now
called Lot two forty nine. Right.
It's based on Arthur Conan Doyle tale starring Buscemi.
It stars Buscemi, Christian Slater and Julianne Moore.
Talk about a different time. Slater's the big name in this.
Slater's the big name. When this came out, Slater was the guy.
The other two. It was like, who cares? Hot off.
Pump up the volume. Yeah. Which is still a great movie.
Still a big Slater fan. I get I like that Mr.
Robot show that he's in. I always get excited.
I haven't seen it, but I may check it out.
It doesn't. It's not jumping off the shelf at me, but I've heard a couple of recommendation.
It's pretty great. It's pretty great. But that's for another podcast.
All right. You want Mr.
Robot talk. Go listen to the Mr.
Robot podcast. All right. Fine.
Fucks. What would the name of that podcast be?
The Mr. Robot podcast.
I don't know what else. You're a classic Riff Meister job.
Look at these sweaters. Actual sweaters of the time.
Or are these guys just being painted as douchebags?
Well, they aren't. They're douchebags. I mean, this is very on the nose.
I think this is how douchebags dressed in 87.
Did they? And this is 1990.
Or were they just going off other movies of the 80s? Is this 90?
Yeah. Well, this is how douchebags dressed back then.
It was a lot of sleeveless v -necks. It was a lot of tennis rackets.
All right. Douchebags in school used to play tennis.
That was what the bullies used to do. I'm sure they still do.
Now, bullies now are real bullies. They'll beat the shit out of you.
The douchebags at my school, high school, all played golf.
You know, for your more fratty type douchebag guy.
And then the football players were all just wild degenerates.
Like, like, horrifying people to be around.
Yeah. I mean, sunflower seeds into your face.
Yeah. Certainly the frightening people at my schools that I attended were not tennis players.
Right. You know, right. Look, these guys are this is how it goes in an Ivy League.
Sure. That's how it is.
Buscemi, by the way, this was my introduction to him as a kid.
I had no idea who he was. And I remember seeing when I first saw Reservoir Dogs
about three years after this being like, oh, my God, that's that's the guy from Tales from the Darkside.
Yeah. It was so weird for me to see him in another role because I only knew him from this.
Pretty much always been one of my favorite actors, really.
Now, has he had a teeth like has he had his teeth done?
Because his teeth look particularly big and crooked in this.
And I don't remember them looking like that.
Oh, no. If anything, they look worse.
If you could say if you could look at a picture of Buscemi from today
and say that you think he said his teeth done, I'd let you out of the goddamn room.
What do they so they still he's still got those same teeth.
Yeah. Like open a tin can, you know, like not think anything of it kind of teeth.
Oh, hey, God bless him. Yeah.
Those teeth bottom a career like chopping over those old like cylinders of high C
like with one big triangle on one side and one small triangle on the other.
Like you just sort of chop in and down it in one disgusting gulp.
This would be this would be my response if I would.
I'm Steve Buscemi. Criticize my teeth. Yeah.
OK. Yeah. Big old teeth, Buscemi.
These teeth bought me a Ferrari.
That's what I would say to people.
He definitely drives a Ferrari. He seems like that guy for sure.
Favorite Buscemi, I'm going to go with a fairly obvious choice and say Fargo.
I don't know how you could possibly do better than that.
You're nuts. All right. What do you got?
You put Fargo over reservoir dogs.
Yeah, I put Fargo over reservoir dogs by about 5000 percent.
That's insane.
One of my least favorite Coen brothers, by the way.
How do you live with yourself?
There's no there's no one at home being like, yeah, he's right.
Fargo suck. There's no one at home doing that right now.
Well, it's no one. I didn't say Fargo sucked.
I just said it's I like reservoir dogs better and it's not one of my favorite Coen brothers movies.
All right. It's a good movie.
Were you a lady killers man?
Intolerable cruelty. Number one.
Lady killers has some laughs and so is intolerable cruelty.
I'm joking. My number one, obviously, is Big Lebowski.
Yeah, that's fair.
I would follow it with possibly maybe a Miller's crossing.
Those crossing is great.
Raising Arizona might be my favorite, but I love the shimmy in Fargo, which was the question because I said performance.
Now, Mr. Pink, I don't understand the hell you're saying.
It's fine. You're not a very tolerant man.
I'm very tolerant, which is a lot.
I'm sorry. I don't have the patience of a guy that watches the same movie back to back in one night.
I mean, I don't know what kind of psychopath you are.
Well, I'm not watching it all right now.
I'm talking and I had never seen it.
So I would have been like, what's going on?
What's going on? Why did they just do a terrible 80s wife?
The fact that you're able to just sit in front of it twice in a row is nuts to me.
You're a sinner. Well, I'm talking to you.
You're a cinephile.
I mean, an insult. If I if it had been a movie I'd seen a hundred times, I wouldn't have to do it.
But it's not an insult. I just said it's nuts to me.
Look at this refrigerator.
They're supposed to be really wealthy and they got that fifties Donna Reed fridge in the kitchen.
Maybe it's a classic. What happened to this guy?
I like this guy that plays Julianne Moore's boyfriend, who's like who's like the definition of a white guy.
I feel like he might still he looks like a character actor who's in movies now, but it's not him for sure.
Yeah, he's probably by this point either strolled into the porn waters or, you know, he runs a tire shop in the valley or something like that.
He's got a good porn look. I like it.
Yeah, I think even now, 25 years later, he'd be one of those kind of 50 fibers hanging in there.
Yeah. Coming by, you know, playing the neighbor who's visiting the babysitter or whatever it is.
I don't know. Oh, my sweet boy.
You think they still have storylines in porn?
They still do. And everything I watched, I'm usually fast forwarding it.
The hell are you seeing that has a storyline in it?
Uh, maybe it Bang Brothers where they put a girl on like a bus or something, you know, maybe I kind of seek them out.
But I tend to go for something a little longer.
I like to treat myself like a lady and those always have story in them.
I never like a clip that like opens on a gaping butthole or something.
I don't need that in my life.
I like to be romanced a little bit.
You'll still watch a thing where it's like, you know, let's turn this into a porno.
The guy goes, I inherited a mummy.
And then he opens the coffin and he's like, Oh, I know.
I mean, a mommy and a hot milk gets out like you.
This is a real milk. A mummy.
I'd like to fuck. Should we write this?
You would you would you would watch that kind of porn?
Uh, oh, no, I'm not talking about if the story is just ludicrous.
I just mean if it's a simple, uh, hey, you know, uh, your dad's out.
Uh, I'm your new stepmom.
You're home visiting for the weekend.
Give me a little back and forth.
That's a lot of the clips.
You know what? I'm going to say something kind of profound.
I like a little back and forth before the in and out.
And that goes for life and in the erotic cinema.
All right.
That's that's I get the stories you're talking about.
All right. I thought you were saying like old school, like everybody works at a hospital.
No, you know, no, I'm not doing that.
But I miss that, you know, nurse time to make the incision right here.
You know what I mean? Yeah.
And he sticks his penis in her vagina.
Right. You get it. I got it.
Looks like you need a shot.
Nurse, you head off down the hall.
Well, I think Mr. Herman needed a sponge bath.
I like my incision bit a little bit better.
I wouldn't know.
I was fucking competing with you, Jim.
You weren't. But I didn't just I didn't lift mine from Seinfeld.
That's all you're going to lift the Seinfeld bit from the famous episode of Seinfeld.
I don't know how you live with yourself.
Do you do this at work?
Well, I didn't know Seinfeld was a hardcore porno film.
What's that?
I'm saying, you know how they get this side nurses and doctors off down the hall on their own stories.
Sort of like a Pulp Fiction.
It also featured Steve Buscemi, which was an anthology film.
Well, sure. Yes, it is.
Three stories.
Yes.
Anything with three stories, I wouldn't say is an anthology.
I like Buscemi in Pulp Fiction more than I like him in Fargo.
I don't I don't know what to say.
I'm joking.
Did you also love William H. Macy in Fargo?
I loved him in it.
Yeah, he was incredible.
He's great. And so was McDormand.
And she's wonderful in it.
And so is that Austrian guy whose name I can never remember that played.
Peter Stormare.
Constance also in Seinfeld.
We're bringing it back.
He played the guy who got the Frogger thing across the street.
His name was slippery Pete.
Folks, Peter Stormare, a bit of a resemblance to our to our leading jock man in this short story.
I wouldn't argue that.
You know, what's your opinion of Julianne Moore as an actress?
She's wonderful.
I thought she was.
And then I hit a point where I never wanted to see her again.
And I've been there for five, ten years.
I think she's fantastic in almost everything she does.
I mean, she's unbeatable in Boogie Nights.
Boogie Nights was 20 years ago.
You're talking right into what I'm saying.
I'll name a recent one.
That David Cronenberg movie she was in about Hollywood.
Maps to the Stars.
One of the most upsetting films I've ever seen in my life.
She's fantastic in that.
She was.
I just you really see her acting these days.
She was terrible on 30 Rocks.
She did a Boston accent that just really, you know, sent me into my room for a couple of days.
I couldn't quite deal with it.
And then, you know, she's just a little hammy.
Even in that still Alice, I didn't like her.
I didn't see that.
She was great in Don John.
Yeah, I did like Don.
I like Don John a lot.
It's a great movie.
Still Alice is the amnesia movie or not amnesia.
Jesus Christ.
Alzheimer's.
The subject of Alzheimer's in it.
Yeah, it's the subject.
I want to see the least.
I have I really hate anything to discuss with Alzheimer's.
Yeah, it's a terrifying whole movie.
I think I talked about this on Pete's podcast was Alec Baldwin going.
But Alice, your your glasses are on your forehead.
Alice Alice, the cause parked right down here.
Alice Alec Baldwin talks in that English accent.
Yeah, you know, when Alec Baldwin's in like a drama where he's not supposed to be like a tough.
Yeah, he defaults to like almost like a 1930s.
Or accent now.
So the story of still Alice is she's a young younger woman that gets early onset Alzheimer's.
Yeah, it's so depressing.
And then, you know, Baldwin kind of.
I don't know.
He just keeps he tries to hang in and then he winds up leaving her.
Spoiler alert because the movie wasn't depressing enough.
Jesus Christ.
I used to work with people that at Alzheimer's and there was a woman who was in her late 50s that had she was she was gone.
She was off the map.
And it was very sad to see somebody that young.
I mean, it was sad to see anybody with it, but somebody that young with it.
It's my biggest fear.
Now we're really into a horror podcast.
Yeah.
What are your what are your fears now?
That's why a horror movie about Alzheimer's.
I might not see that.
I don't like anything to do with Alzheimer's.
We've established that.
Let's let's let's donate money to them.
You should picture people sitting in their cubicles right now wanting to slit their throats.
All right.
Well, let's talk about Christian Slater in a blue tank top.
I asked turtleneck.
Did you wear turtlenecks?
Now, my posture was always too bad for a turtleneck.
I look weird in one.
I know one looks cool in them, except maybe like Bruce Wayne.
Bruce Wayne looks fantastic in one.
But I always wore turtlenecks under a sweater was kind of my signature look.
I look real, real nerdy for many.
You look like one of these jocks at the Ivy League school.
But in a nerdy body racquet around with you.
Imagine the jock wardrobe, but with a real dorky face and body.
If I may say so, Pat and I had a poured ourselves a drink before this podcast.
I'm about halfway down my whiskey.
I'm so tired from working all week that I'm I feel completely drunk right now already.
All right.
Well, keep it together.
That's together.
I just feel I mean, I could I could go to sleep in your arms at this moment and not feel strange about that.
Not at all.
I would feel very strange about it.
I don't blame you.
I'm just trying to tell you where I'm at right now.
I think our listeners might enjoy a solo pod from me.
Or it might be like when Wayne left and Garth had to take over Wayne's world.
No, I don't look at it that way.
I look at it as the is like when Joe Perry did the solo album.
I look at it as a positive.
All right.
The fans are going to like it.
They're going to support it.
What was it?
What was Joe Perry's solo?
I can't remember.
It was the first thing I could access in my head.
One of my friends out here is his son.
He's a delightful guy.
He's at my house for the party.
I am friends with I'm friends with his stepson.
My friend Aaron is his stepson.
My buddy Anthony.
I'll just shout him out.
Anthony Perry Jr.
It was Anthony and one of the kids in the band.
The three brothers band.
Yes.
Tab the band.
Yeah.
Me and Burr used to hang out with those guys.
Nice guys.
I missed him at your party unless he was there and we just didn't recognize each other.
He was there.
I love those guys.
Yeah.
They're great guys.
Look at us name dropping again.
Folks, if it's your first listen themes that reoccur on this podcast pedophilia name dropping.
Yeah.
Both despicable.
Who knows which is worse.
But we're not dropping like fucking huge names.
We're saying I my buddy is the son of Joe Perry.
You were going on and on about about.
That's a great shot by the way when the camera goes past the mummy.
It's a great shot.
But you think that mummy might be a guy with a mummy helmet on.
Like could there be.
I guess mummies.
It's a real it's a real mummy that they brought to life.
Just mummies to me.
It's always like mummies.
I'm like even in the mummy.
I was just kind of like just push him over.
It's a mummy.
They're not scary.
We did a we did a monologue when Pete Holmes still had his talk show and it was about the what monster is the scariest monster.
Uh huh.
And I wrote a lot of the monologue and I remember the section on zombies and mummies is it zombies aren't scary because they just they just wander around slowly.
Right.
They all look like your grandfather got loose from his bed at the home.
Sure.
You know you just want to see if he needs if he needs somebody to if he knows where he is and if he needs somebody to escort him back to his room.
Right.
You know that's how I feel about mummy.
Did you not think that joke was funny.
No I'm with you.
What did you why did you laugh at all that joke.
It's a funny joke.
It's like your grandfather got loose from his bed at the home.
Yeah I mean we just get off Alzheimer's and now we're talking about a grandpa not knowing where he is.
All right.
Well you know these people got to get through this brains in the fruit bowl mummy pulled out the jock guy's brains and brains in the fruit bowl and the silver spoon mummy in the light of the moon.
Julianne Moore is hamming it up.
Now she seems kind of natural here and she did to me up until like Magnolia she's way way over the top and she's playing like a real coked out drugged out lady.
I've never seen her be hammy.
You said you thought we saw newer development for her.
We saw black mass the other day and and I thought Peter Sarsgaard was was phenomenal and you said he thought he was a little hammy and I didn't I thought he played it like a guy that was on a lot of coke.
I liked him.
I wanted more of him in the movie but he just was in kind of a different thing and it gave the movie some energy which I felt it really needed the thought black mass is surprisingly very slow.
I got to tell you I rewatched the documentary tonight about Whitey Bolger and it reframed the movie for me and it made me appreciate the movie more.
OK.
And I also think that Bolger wasn't an informant and I actually believe his story over the FBI story that he was.
I mean everybody was lying.
So it's really anybody's guess.
Yeah I don't know.
I just for some reason I believed his story a little bit more.
OK.
You got Julianne Moore sitting in front of a bloody fridge or boyfriend's been murdered later looking like a young John Travolta always doing a Nicholson impression in these early days especially.
They couldn't cliche this up more.
They're now at the funeral of the dead boyfriend and Christian Slater and his rich sister are drinking brandy out of Snifters.
Sure.
Would it have killed you to throw me a Snifters knife.
I don't even own a chair.
It's a terrible chair.
I'm trash.
I don't own a Snifter.
Who does this.
It's like an episode of Frasier.
Yeah.
It's ridiculous.
We had the guy on our show this week.
Gill.
Remember Gill from fresh.
Well you just watched the entire series for some reason.
I remember Gill.
Who the hell plays.
Who's the hell is Gill.
He's like the shit.
I'll do my impression of you and you'll know who he is.
So Gill.
Yeah.
The food radio guy.
I go where do I know you from man.
Like you know he's 70 years old now or something.
Where do I know you from.
Well I did only live in seasons of Frasier.
He talks.
That's how we know.
Yeah.
Really.
He was also.
Well no.
I don't want to say anything.
He was a little.
He kind of stayed in character.
Like he came out and he was like where's the bathroom.
My friend goes oh it's right over here.
And he goes I know we're like what was that.
I don't get it.
What's that.
It wasn't a joke.
I think you were just kind of like don't tell me where I'm going.
But why did he ask them.
Joe.
That's the point of the story.
We were all kind of like what's this guy's deal.
I don't know.
But what was his character.
Was it a man that would ask questions.
He was a snooty butler.
You know a very annoying butler.
He's 70.
Oh at least.
Yeah.
Really.
He's very funny on Frasier.
He was great.
Yeah.
He's got a very distinctive voice.
I love that.
I love the show so much.
I am rewatching many episodes of it.
Well outside of Seinfeld and curb your enthusiasm Seinfeld curb your enthusiasm.
The Golden Girls.
The honeymooners.
Mr Belvedere.
Frasier.
Those are my five where it's like Mrs Belvedere.
I'll rewatch him.
I don't care.
I love it.
Belvedere vodka.
All right.
We heard the Belvedere haven't seen Frasier in at least 15 years but I used to like it.
I would go as far as to say there are moments that are hysterical.
Oh wow.
It's one of the most.
Well they got a good farce thing going when they would.
It's great.
And hit it.
Yeah for sure.
And it's one of the most laugh out loud sitcoms to me.
Those five to me are like to me gutturally laugh out loud sitcoms for the most part.
If you were texting with Frasier you would text L .O .L.
I would text L .O .L.
All right.
I'd also text S .T .F .U.
Shut the fuck up.
Yes.
Mm hmm.
Because he'd probably say a thing like do you want to meet for a brandy and I'd say
shut the fuck up but not telling him like shut the fuck up like I hate you.
Saying it like oh Frasier shut the fuck up.
I love it.
You know what I mean.
I bet Frasier would have a lot to say about emojis.
What do you think you'd say.
Well now I'm just want to talk like Gil.
I got that in my head.
I can't really do my Kelsey grammar on Twitter corrects people's grammar which I love.
When somebody corrects my grammar I say thanks a lot Kelsey grammar and nobody laughs ever.
On the just like how when I order a drink at a bar I go I think I'm going to have a
little ditty about Jack and diet.
Never going to laugh at any bar ever.
I do it at least once a year because I'm like somebody a lot.
Even if I got a bartender I'm like this guy's got a good sense of humor.
I'll do it.
They always get it.
It's not like they don't get it.
They just never laugh and it hurts.
You want to hear my bar bit that nobody ever laughed at.
Sure.
As you try to do a guy that didn't know how to order drinks properly.
OK.
And I'd go give me a white Russian.
No line please.
You know stuff like that.
It's very bad material.
Do me a do me a favor.
Bloody Mary.
Easy on the whiskey and just a pinch of the Kahlua.
Like I would just drink water wrong.
Nobody ever thought it was funny ever.
Yeah.
I'm big.
I'm big on like at a party when you first get there.
These are all very bad material.
I love dead bits.
Sure.
Me too.
Any party like when you first get there and they're like you want to drink.
What can I get you.
I'm like I'm going to do a white wine and Red Bull please.
And you always try to get a funny funny blend.
Right.
But you'll never be tanker and tonic from Kingpin.
Tangeray and no it's not.
I'm sorry.
Tangerine tab sweets coming.
I got a long drive ahead of me.
We've talked about it previously on the on the podcast.
We think that is the two funniest drink orders of all time.
Tangerine tab as you just said.
And then later when the dickhead boyfriend bowler guy is sitting at the bar he goes hey sport Coca -Cola Coca -Cola.
What an asshole.
That guy is only in Fairly Bros movies and I think he was like an Entertainment Tonight correspondent who is not a great actor.
And throughout Kingpin is wearing eyeliner.
Yes.
Which I find very bizarre.
And in a movie where everyone is insulting everyone's appearance the entire time.
No one says a word to him about wearing.
But I will tell you that his delivery of hey sport Coca -Cola.
Yeah.
Oh no.
Like this guy.
This guy should have won an Oscar.
He was a very effective Jewish.
Yeah.
The now we're at the part in the movie now if you're watching along with us Christian Slater is about to use these putting lighter fluid all over.
Steve Buscemi because you know Steve Buscemi is somehow gotten this mummy to kill his sister and his best friend.
And now he's going to try to have the mummy kill.
Well not.
He's going to just burn Steve Buscemi alive.
Excuse me.
Now Slater in this scene.
Even if you're not watching I'd suggest you go watch it afterwards because Slater is really Nicholson.
Yeah.
Nicholson ing up the entire scene.
His most Nicholson he was probably Heather's or maybe cuffs.
But he was just doing straight impressions for like a 10 year period.
I find his pump up the volume to be incredibly super.
Yeah.
This is all in that same two or three year period.
All the great themes have been turned into theme parks.
Yeah.
I still love that line.
It makes no sense.
No it's a very 80s 80s line where you're like that's deep man.
But it's not.
Yeah.
Well he used to say that Nicholson was his idol.
Well sure.
And but here's the thing.
He naturally sounds like Nicholson.
Yeah.
And almost I mean a little bit has a look of a young Jack Nix.
So you know it's not all you know it's kind of like how it's kind of like how Action Bronson
sounds like Ghostface killer.
Yeah exactly.
Who in a video said that Action Bronson should be killed.
I saw that.
I didn't really approve Ghostface's response.
I didn't either.
Over the top.
I understood why Ghostface was a little upset but I didn't think he should call for a man's
death over it.
No I mean stealing somebody's flow that's been going on for centuries.
Patty I mean you know sometimes I think people in this town are stealing my flow.
They're not.
This I thought was this supposed to be a little blowjob bit because it sure felt that way
to me.
No.
Like the director wasn't like hey we've kind of framed this so it looks like that guy is
really blowing Steve Buscemi.
I never once in my entire life ever thought that and I've seen this movie a hundred times.
You're a pig with a filthy mind.
That's where I went.
Sorry.
You're a disgusting pig.
I just want to see Steve Buscemi get blown down.
Maybe they let that pig talk fly at CBS on your foul mouth sitcom you work on but not
on this podcast.
Did you like the mummies and the scorpion kings and all that garbage.
I'm sort of tipping my hand on how I feel about them.
They're OK.
I mean the first one's pretty good.
You know it's that's more of an Indiana Jones type of thing than a horror movie man.
OK.
I went on a date with this girl once.
I would say six minutes.
Sorry to break.
Six minutes into the meal she goes like so like you like movies.
So like what's like a movie you can just watch like whenever it's on you just have to finish
it.
I probably said Fargo you know or something like that.
And she's like for me it's the mummy.
I will always watch the mummy when it's on and I was like that.
OK.
But I was like losing interest rapidly but I'm going to hang in here.
And then this girl talked about that mummy a lot.
It went on and on and she thinks Brendan Fraser is so cute.
I think this is very endearing.
But it wasn't funny.
It was just like the girl seemed to have a real Jones for the mummy.
I think it's I think it's endearing.
I don't I don't think it's endearing because it sounds funny.
I think it's endearing.
A girl really loves the movie The Mummy.
All right.
It didn't didn't work for me.
Somebody being passionate about the mummy.
I don't have time in my life for that.
I'm not being passionate about it.
She was.
And you're a heartless bastard.
Yeah exactly.
That couldn't understand.
She's not into your indie house drama bullshit.
I like a wide variety of movies.
But speaking of indie house drama bullshit I did just like I saw Good Night Mommy.
Dying to see it.
I might go tomorrow night.
It is so scary.
You should see it because it's going to leave the Los Feliz up here.
Again tipping my hand as to where me and Joe live.
But it was really scary and really tense and I loved it.
Good Night Mommy.
It's a German horror movie.
Basically only three characters.
Some other people pop in but it's two twins.
They're like 10 years old.
Their mom comes back with her face all wrapped up in gauze much like a mummy.
Keeping it on story.
Was she in an accident or is it plastic surgery.
Well I'm not going to answer any of those questions but she comes back and the kids start to suspect that it's not their mom basically.
And it was.
That's the premise and it's very very scary.
You should see it.
It's great.
OK.
Very good.
Now isn't this cab driver in the scene somebody famous.
Is that Joe Pantaleone.
It wasn't right.
No but I know you mentioned I think he might have.
Was it.
I don't know.
It just looked like a way buffer dude.
I think I feel like that cab driver is somebody that I should record.
By the way that was another trope in 80s movies like the cab drivers were always like these S &M leather.
There's chains all through the cab.
They do that in a trip plane trains and automobiles.
The others.
Well the guys got porn all over his car.
Yeah.
Speaking of cab drivers the next story that's going to be on in a few moments.
Cat from Hell stars Buster Poindexter played a cab driver and Scrooge.
Yep.
You know it.
Yeah.
With William Hickey.
So he was in Scrooge.
No he's in Christification.
As you know Uncle Lewis.
Yeah.
But what.
Wait a minute.
Oh you're just saying they're both.
The next.
Yeah.
But one year prior they were both in some great classic Christmas movies.
And now they're in this together with a cat.
Scrooge could be my favorite Christmas movie.
I wouldn't argue with that.
I love Scrooge.
I have my favorite Christmas movie.
I would say it's a wonderful life.
It's one of my favorite movies.
Home Alone.
I love Home Alone.
I saw when I was 10 too.
But I mean for God sakes it's a favorite.
It's a favorite Christmas movie of mine.
Christmas vacation is a favorite Christmas.
I love Christmas vacation.
I love Gremlins is a favorite Christmas movie.
I love Gremlins.
I'll tell you what my second to Scrooge.
The disgust in your voice when we slightly disagree on something.
Look in the cat from hell stories opens with a cab.
Yeah.
I will tell you my second place to Scrooge.
I can't wait to hear it.
Love Actually.
Yeah I love Love Actually.
Makes me cry every time.
I think though that it's you know it doesn't feel at all Christmassy except for a few little sections.
I disagree wholeheartedly.
I don't know.
I think they covered the Christmas bases nicely in that film.
I think that movie would be a nice entertaining picture.
But I think that the Alan Rickman Emma Thompson story takes it over the edge into something better.
It's a wonderful film.
It's a wonderful life.
Wonderful film.
Cheers.
The Hugh Grant story.
It's touching.
My favorite story though is Bill Nye.
Is that his name?
Definitely not.
Bill Nye the science guy.
Who's the guy that plays the rock star in it that was in Shaun of the Dead.
Oh yeah.
Well yeah.
His name is Bill Nye.
Yeah.
Very close.
My.
That's my favorite story.
Him and his manager.
It's it's it's it kills me at the end when he tells his manager like you're my best friend.
I love you.
Yeah.
It's a pretty great movie.
Anytime.
Really anytime in a movie someone is telling someone something they have wanted to say
for decades.
That'll always put a little lump in my throat.
I'm a sucker for it.
Now William Hickey.
Yeah.
Bill Hickey.
Well sometimes he went by William.
He always went by William but I called him Bill.
My friend used to do that.
Like he'd he'd like refer to stars.
Like Bobby De Niro.
Movie stars like with familiarity.
Jimmy Khan.
Yeah.
He'd be like he'd be like that's the great thing about Mathow.
I always wanted to be like you're a you you're you're you're a social your social studies
major at a state school.
But you don't know Mathow.
Yeah.
I'm Walter Mathow.
You know a lot of things.
It depends on the person but there's so many things people will do when talking about action
stuff that bothered me so much.
But really like you know if you were to say to me oh you know Pacino was so great in that
movie that would.
But William Hickey I remember this when I studied.
I was a theater minor in college and when William Hickey died they had his obituary
up on like the bulletin board in the theater department.
So he must have gone there right.
No it was just like they would post when famous actors or whatever passed.
I think though I don't think he went there.
But anyway he was like when he died he was only like in his 60s.
He had like some kind of yeah he had some kind of physical looks like a goddamn cool.
I thought he was.
He was so funny in Crystal's vacation.
He's great.
I thought he was like 95 years old.
He was he was he was actually young.
He had like you know he had some kind of disorder or something and he just he looked he was
sickly you know I guess.
I like when his wife who was the voice of Betty Boop by the way.
That's who plays his wife.
I didn't make Estella the original Betty Boop from the 30s and she was oh dear did I break
wind.
And he goes Jesus did the room clear out Bethany.
Hell no.
She means presence.
Then later on she goes I hear something a weird squeaky sound and he goes you couldn't
hear a dump truck driving through a nitroglycerin plant.
Yeah.
He just makes kind of a lame old wisecrack seem new.
I like his voice.
So when he goes grace the blessing points to his mouth to his teeth.
Yeah.
That's the mark of a good actor.
Anybody can point to their mouth.
He points to his teeth.
Isn't that the guy that plays like Breaking Bad.
But as they also play his name the usual suspects.
Now I'm thinking of the other guy.
Oh yeah.
Well that guy had a huge role in Breaking Bad.
He was the guy who winds up with the bomb thing on his wheelchair.
Yes.
I like that guy.
Yeah.
I also like the Kobayashi guy.
He passed away recently.
Yes.
People always die unfortunately.
Eventually we all die.
So the times at the hands of an evil cat most of the time at the hands of an evil cat.
So this one was written by George A.
Romero based on a Stephen King.
Oh yes.
I'm sorry.
Based on a Stephen King story.
Yes.
And the first and third were written by Malcolm McDowell who I always mistook with Michael
McDowell from A Clockwork Orange.
Malcolm McDowell is from A Clockwork Orange.
And this is Michael McDowell.
You're right.
I actually was in the process of confusing it while I talked about how I confused.
Yeah.
Not to be confused with Roddy McDowell.
No.
Or Andy McDowell.
Yeah.
Hey I'm going to tell you my joke about Andy McDowell.
You ready for this?
How many people have a joke about Andy McDowell?
This is what keeps me big in the standup circuit.
Go ahead.
What do Andy McDowell and my uncle Gary have in common?
What?
They both ruined four weddings and a funeral.
Oh God.
Fuck you.
That's a good joke.
Want to hear a one liner I wrote for work the other day?
Yeah.
Well I'm not going to laugh at it now after I get an oh God from you.
This is a good one liner.
I had to write a one liner for like a borscht belt kind of thing.
OK.
They said either my cook is becoming one hell of a nag or my wife is becoming one hell of
a cook.
I mean maybe I had to be a part of the scene.
I think that's a good one liner.
OK.
It's a it's like a Milton Burley kind of thing.
Look I'm still a little wounded from the treatment of my Andy McDowell joke.
It wasn't a well crafted joke.
I'm sorry.
Well of course it was a huge hit on Twitter.
And if you're going to say that's all that really matters.
Well congratulations.
Thirteen and a half year olds think you're funny.
Our friend genius comedian Karen Kilgara.
She loved it Joe.
I bet I could get a different take out of it on her.
Well go ahead and try.
I'll call her tomorrow.
I'll ask her what you really think of that for weddings and a funeral tweet.
And then she like she'll be taking the phone away from her head laughing.
Michael McDowell.
Yes.
Also wrote Beetlejuice.
A masterpiece.
I'm concerned it is with somebody named Warren Scarron.
So which I would have to assume was some sort of pen name.
But I think the reason I was watching this is because I was trying to seek out other
movies the writer of Beetlejuice had done.
But this doesn't really have that feel to it.
Beetlejuice like and the guy hadn't done a lot of other stuff.
Especially nothing in that tone.
Beetlejuice is a real special thing.
I think Burton must have had a lot to do with it too.
I love Beetlejuice.
I'm excited that they're doing a sequel.
Yeah it's just.
What Pat?
What?
I'm going to keep my hopes at a 60 percent because why would I not?
Burton's directing it.
Keaton's in it.
Winona Ryder's in it.
What's not to like?
Well they keep going back and forth on it.
They got the guy who wrote fucking Dark Shadows to write it.
Which was a terrible movie.
It was better than I thought it was going to be.
You must have thought it was going to be real damn bad John.
I mean I don't know.
Hold on though.
I want to look up Beetlejuice and see.
Now why do you think the original writer isn't writing it?
Because he's dead.
He died at age 49.
From what?
I don't know.
I just looked it up and he was dead at 49.
I'm on the old iPad here and of course it's an iPad mini.
From however many years ago.
It's the first iPad mini.
And as soon as iOS 9 came out the thing doesn't work properly anymore.
Of course.
Unbelievable.
All right I'm looking up Beetlejuice on Wikipedia.
Glenn Shattuck's also dead who played.
Yeah.
Otho.
One of my favorite characters in the whole film.
I've probably.
I would say I've seen Beetlejuice.
Maybe more than any other movie.
Other than maybe Home Alone or Roger Rabbit.
They were.
They hit me in that 10 year old.
I'll watch something a million times.
Wheelhouse.
Warren Skerrin died at 44 44.
Sorry.
Not a screen name.
That's his real name.
Warren Skerrin.
No no.
I was.
OK.
Warren Skerrin is dead.
But so is 44.
So is Michael McDowell at age 49.
Well.
That must movie was cursed.
Warren Skerrin.
Uh.
What's it say here.
First success was getting the film The Getaway shot in Texas.
Oh.
Driving force behind the distribution of the Texas Chainsaw Massacre.
That's great.
Notable writing works include Beverly Hills Cop 2.
Very funny.
Batman.
Mm hmm.
Yeah.
He was in the Burton camp.
He also he had also written unproduced sequels to The Jewel of Denial.
Now did he write the Beetlejuice Goes Hawaiian sequel that was bandied about or did that
never actually go to script.
Well how about this.
He wrote a he wrote a Beetlejuice sequel that was never made called Beetlejuice in Love.
Did you know that.
No.
But Bealejuice Goes Hawaiian I think was offered to Kevin Smith.
Beetlejuice Goes Hawaiian.
Yeah.
There was a project that was like shopped around for a while about 10 years ago.
And what the hell was it about.
Bealejuice in Hawaii.
One of the worst things ever heard in my life.
Yeah of course.
I have no I mean Burton can't make a sea movie these days.
For my money.
I heard Big Eyes was good.
It was fine.
Look you know I hate to say it I'm a fan of Burton's earlier work but for the most part
Burton's stuff was a lot of was a lot of look and not a lot of substance.
Oh I completely disagree.
As always with you Joe.
McDowell died of AIDS.
Michael McDowell.
He died of AIDS.
Jesus Christ.
He was diagnosed with AIDS in 1994.
Well AIDS Alzheimer's were hitting all the fun topics tonight folks.
It's a real pick me up of an episode tonight.
It's getting a little dark.
No but I mean I look I'm going to say I'm going to say this right now and I don't care who I piss off.
You know I never thought Edward Scissorhands was that great.
Of a movie.
I don't know.
I don't know what to say to that.
You know I loved Edward Scissorhands.
I love Pee Wee's Big Adventure.
I love Batman.
I love Batman Returns.
I know you hate Batman Returns.
Batman Returns is not a good film.
I think it's an A plus.
Oh stop it.
That's idiotic.
All those early Burton's I think are just fucking classics.
But then again.
Batman Returns is an A plus.
For me.
Yeah.
Get out of here.
I don't believe you believe that.
But I do.
And I'm saying it.
And why would I not.
So you don't have a problem with penguins with missiles on their backs.
That is fine.
No.
Again.
This is a movie I saw when I was 12.
But when I watch it now I still love it just as much.
I saw it when I was 13 and I knew it sucked then.
I was like this sucks.
I saw it in the theater.
I couldn't wait.
Well no.
You would have seen it when you were 17.
Because you're older than me.
I was not 17.
So you didn't see it when you were 12.
It came out in 92.
I was born in 81.
And I saw it in the theater.
Let's look that up.
I'm going to look that up.
I know that is true.
I'm going to look it up.
Hold on a second.
So I was 11.
I'll tell you in a second.
And you would have been.
I was 16, 17.
That's a very different age.
I don't know why you wouldn't love it because Batman Returns was so fucking dark.
Like way ahead of its time.
First of all it wasn't dark.
It was weirdly dark in certain places.
It was like psychosexual and weird and awesome.
And then it was oddly, stupidly comedic in other places.
It's dumb that people go to the Penguin's speech and start throwing tomatoes at him.
Where the gag is, the Penguin actually says,
what kind of people bring fruit and vegetables to a press conference?
It's like, it's stupid.
The gadgets are dumb.
Like they're too ridiculous the way they work.
There's the thing where Batman pulls a chunk of concrete out of a wall.
See you always get hung up on this shit.
It's Batman.
So like your magazine is pulling a hunk of concrete out of a wall.
Mac Shrek, not even a character from the comics.
Why are they adding, don't add a character.
Well see I never give a fuck about that shit.
Batman Returns to me is so much better than any comic book movie made in the last 20 years that everybody thinks is so genius.
I think it's great.
It's in tone of what it should be.
Do you think it's better than Dark Knight?
Certainly better than Batman Begins.
Both of Burton's Batmans are better than Batman Begins.
And the Dark Knight, it's an odd comparison, but I'd say they're about on a par.
The Dark Knight is probably a little better.
But depending on the day, I might like Batman Returns better than Batman 1.
Pat, you're out of your, what are you talking about?
Sorry, I know I'm not alone here either.
They took so many liberties with it.
The way Catwoman becomes Catwoman, it's like ridiculous.
Liberty shit will never bother me.
Well, look, I guess it's the rest of the world's fault.
This is what the difference is for being with nerds who are super into comic books.
This isn't super into.
Which at this point is the world.
Everyone is into comic books.
I never have cared about them at all.
So when we go into a movie like this, you guys are all going in like, well, what's going to be different than my graphic novel?
And I'm going in like a child ready to be entertained.
And I'm not entertained by these.
I wasn't going into it like that.
But I was smart enough to know, by the way, I was 14 when this film came out.
I was smart enough to know that when this came out, Catwoman becoming Catwoman because cats chew on her fingers makes no fucking sense.
Now, whether or not they're making up their own origin story is a different argument.
Well, I would all bite her and she's, you know, what happens in the book?
Is there like radioactive?
No, she's just like a cat.
She's a cat burglar.
She's like an antihero in the books.
And she has no cat power.
And even if she did, why would cats chewing on your fingers give you cat power?
Well, they're like they there's a bunch of cats like attacking.
So stupid. So you can either go, OK, I'm in a ridiculous world.
And like this scene looks amazing.
That's the penguin, the penguin, one of the coolest, like sort of like John Gotti meets Donald Trump characters in comic books, like this super billionaire, like pulling the strings puppeteer kind of crime boss villain.
And they turn him into this like mutant, like it's fucking all that dumb Tim Burton shit.
Like I want to find beauty in the obscure.
I want to find beauty, prettiness in the I couldn't have dreamed of a better penguin.
Oh, God, it's terrible.
Burgess Meredith, that's a penguin for you.
It's ridiculous.
It's just and then they add this third villain and it's too much.
It's like Christopher Walken, Max Shrek and Max Shrek barely makes an appearance.
Oh, so bad.
You must like it more.
It's not so bad.
I can't even put up with the guy playing his son.
It's literally like daddy daddy.
It's stupid.
It's a it's not a good movie.
Do you prefer Batman and Robin?
No, those are dog shit.
Well, you're talking about Batman Returns as if it's dog to make your point.
It's not dog.
I will put this is this is the height of Batman returns to me.
It's Christmas time and I want to take a nap.
That's Batman returns to me.
It's Christmas.
I'll put it on.
I'll fall asleep to it because I don't care enough to keep watching it.
But it's Christmas enough that I find it comforting.
That's it.
The first Batman.
I'll watch.
I'll watch the first Batman.
I love them both.
Dark Knight.
I love taking a nap to Dark Knight.
I'll tell you that much.
This world allows for all these things.
It's a democracy.
I can't believe it.
I'm looking it up now.
It's got an 80 percent.
What does that return?
People love Batman Returns were stupid.
Here's another thing.
Let's have a whole new villain with the Penguin.
OK, cool.
I'm into that.
Let's make all the penguins henchmen exact ripoffs of the Joker's henchmen.
They're all clowns for some reason.
It's stupid.
It's it's not creative.
It was like a paint by numbers movie.
It's a bad movie.
I think it's a visually spectacular movie that gets into some really weird stuff about how we all wear masks and relationships.
It's very sexual.
It's very exciting.
The action sequences are great.
I love the winter vibe.
I love walking, though his part may be superfluous.
I really love Michelle Pfeiffer as Catwoman.
Nobody's ever done that better.
She's for sure.
She and I don't think anybody's done the Penguin better.
She plays a good catwoman.
But the the the the the writing of the catwoman, the her words and everything to me is stupid.
Well, it's stupid.
By the way, Selena, but it's all stupid.
Selena Kyle isn't a fucking raggedy, beaten down secretary.
I love that, too.
Her transformation in that.
I fucking loved it.
And I think a lot of people do.
Selena Kyle is like is like is like a borderline like prostitute.
But that's like like that lives in like the slums.
They made a different choice, which I think is a better choice.
Seeing a prostitute then put on a leather out.
That's not a transformation.
That's not an arc.
Well, you're the one that likes all the weird sexual stuff.
You probably like a couple of hookers running around that film.
No, I don't have any opinion on how hookers would have factored into that.
But I'm here while you expel all your perverted fantasies through one of my childhood heroes.
Batman.
Yes.
No room for your filthy thoughts in my Batman mythology.
Well, I said I liked her being a dowdy secretary and you said you wanted her to be a.
Perved out prostitute.
Now you're lecturing me on morals.
This looks terrible, by the way, this whole thing with the purple fringe around the outside.
What's the cat's perspective looking at?
Yeah, because all cats see things with a purple ring around the lens.
It's just a bizarre choice.
Cats have green eyes, at least make it green.
It's black and white.
It's black and white with the faintest yellow.
It's black and white with the tiniest hint of purple around the edge.
It's so it's like the I never even noticed the purple till you just said that.
All right.
All right, Joe.
But, you know, look, you've got a more student.
Are we going to make this trip to Denver?
I don't know.
At this point, I just have never.
Also, by the way, has screamed to me in a restaurant about aliens being a terrible movie.
No, I never.
That is a lie.
Oh, we call Alien 3.
No, you Joe.
As God is my witness, you're upset about aliens and you were very, very upset about Terminator 2.
Oh, yeah, I stand by that.
And these are just kind of movies that are just generally considered classics.
But there's no like fun back and forth.
You're always just like so angry.
My argument with you about aliens was I said some people make the argument that it turned the franchise
from being a horror suspense sci fi movie into an action movie.
And some people don't like that about it.
That was my only argument.
They made an interesting choice.
And I went with them.
And if we were having a discussion about the big picture of James Cameron's work, I probably said if aliens is I don't think we can survive that guy after that Batman returns.
Because we saw a Ford Fairlane and the writer of Ford Fairlane and Batman Returns was in attendance.
And we already had kind of an early version of this argument.
Now, that guy said that guy said they said you wrote The Adventures of Hudson Hawk.
Batman Returns.
And they need one other one of his movies.
And he said, yeah, that was my failing down period.
He said that.
That was my failing.
I don't think that guy would think that Batman returns.
He shit.
He said I'm one of the most hated men in comic books.
He said that.
Well, OK, I don't like comic books.
The writer said it.
Jesus Christ.
I don't like comic books.
Joe saying a movie about, you know, Jesus where he's a pimp is good or something.
If I could watch the fucking Avengers or Batman Returns 10 times, I'd watch Batman Returns 10 times.
Listen, I'm not saying you got to love the Avengers.
I'm just saying that everybody loves the Avengers.
I don't love it.
Everybody loves Batman Returns, according to you.
I love a movie that doesn't have to be three hours long.
Look, I'm not.
Do you hear me?
Do you hear me defending the Avengers?
People do love that.
I like the Avengers and they really don't.
All right.
Buster Point.
My friends love Batman Returns.
But I've met your friends.
Yeah.
Not a bright bunch.
No, they're dumb.
The cat is killing Buster Point extra.
This was pretty effective.
I guess this is what they couldn't afford in the original creep show.
I don't think it was that they couldn't afford one of the effects in the story.
I think they didn't have enough money to make five stories, so they only made three and they cut two.
Oh, OK.
That's all.
This is pretty gross.
Yeah, it's great.
I thought the cat would burst out the tum tum.
It's gross that it comes back out of his mouth.
But I like the cat crawls into his stomach and just kind of incubates in there for a little while.
Is that the right term?
It works.
Why not?
I'm very excited for the next story to come on.
First, we've got to get through the end of this story.
Yeah, the last story was the best.
I mean, it's fantastic.
And it's got a real dirty 80s New York feel to it.
Yeah, it reminded me a little of After Hours, which is a great Scorsese movie that is underseen, I would say.
It always makes me think of The Fly.
Mm hmm.
Similar to the Goldblum one.
Yeah, like these people live in these big lofts and they're all artists and creators.
That's what After Hours was as well.
And they have no money or anything like that.
I wonder, like, do you think William Hickey's like, all right, you got to spray him with blood.
Fine.
You got to do a couple of takes, whatever.
Or is he like just a miserable guy about it?
What do you think?
I bet you I would be willing to bet William Hickey was probably a joy.
Maybe.
I would think.
I would think he was probably a joy to be around.
He's got a Burgess Meredith vibe.
I bet you Burgess Meredith was a joy.
He was also William Hickey was in.
What?
Oh, My Blue Heaven.
Yep.
As the mob guy hiding out.
And he was in.
You're under arrest.
Yeah.
My Blue Heaven does not hold up.
How dare you?
OK, watch it.
I own it, Pat.
I do, too.
I watch it frequently.
No, it does not.
It's a wonderful film.
Steve Martin, Rick Moranis, two of my all time favorites.
Steve Martin is so miscast in that part.
He's great in it.
He is so unrealistic and not even attempting to be realistic in that part.
Watching it as an adult, I was like, this is one of the few movies where I can just say I was wrong as a child.
I disagree.
I say Steve Martin walks a fine line between cartoonishness and realism.
Oh, sure.
Well, then watch it again.
I watched it a few months realism, Joe.
I always watch it.
Realism.
He's ridiculous.
It's a broader character than most of his comedic characters like his non mafia character.
I like the role.
I think he makes it somehow believable.
Oh, I buy it the whole time.
Oh, because the guy was a pastor.
What are some of the lies he's telling when he's like dribbling that basketball?
Why do we find all those stolen textbooks in your truck, your car?
Because I was delivering them.
This whole thing is that he's always lying to get out of stuff.
I can't remember any of it, though.
I forget.
Oh, that's because it's a very forgettable movie.
It's structured terribly.
There's like no story to it at all.
That's stupid.
You're stupid sometimes.
Look, I would have loved it as a kid.
It's a horribly structured and plotted and acted film.
I love Jane Cusack.
And the music is bad.
Her name is Joan Cusack.
I always love her.
She's always a bright spot.
But come on.
I love the soundtrack.
My Blue Heaven is a wonderful song.
Yeah, well, that's fine.
You can like the song My Blue Heaven.
There's a wonderful version of it in the film.
It's the version.
That's the version of it.
Well, there are many versions of it, Pat.
It's a standard.
Well, it's the big one.
The biggest one.
For sure.
Sinatra did a version of it.
Many people.
I don't know if there's one that, you know, you know, what's that?
When this might be the final episode, this might just be the final episode.
Why are you getting angry?
Never like this guy stand up.
I'm just going to say that.
Robert Klein.
Yeah.
Every time you're there, any comedian over 50 is like, well, obviously, Robert Klein
was a huge influx.
All right.
Great.
But he's not funny.
I think he was like the first of he was like sort of like I think the first like all comic
like he was the first guy to kind of like, yeah, be casual and wear sweaters.
And yeah, I've never seen a full set or something.
Even I just I never I own his box set.
I own every one of his specials.
And it's you know, it's not totally for me, but I respect what the man did.
OK.
You know, sure.
Can I tell you that?
Sure.
And he plays a good agent in this story.
Kind of the right looks like Neil Brennan a little bit to me.
He does.
And I can't remember what else I've seen him in when bars like this existed.
Look at this bar they're in.
Well, they just sit in these movies for sure.
They also exist everywhere in St.
Louis, Missouri.
If you want to come home with me this Christmas and get involved in a darts tournament or
you'd never ask if you ever wanted to play a three hour game of darts while Papa Roach
plays, head to St.
Louis and go to a bar.
But this is a great little dive bar.
Look at this.
This is what you call your local spots like this.
This guy has been in a thousand movies.
James Reymar is in so many movies to Django Unchained.
He's always fine.
You know, I love James Reymar.
Yeah.
He gets the job done.
Plays a good when they when they put him up to it and he plays a dirtball.
He's very good at it.
Yeah.
He's about to make love to Ray Don Chong, who was a big eighties babe.
I think she might have a body double in this.
What the hell happened to her?
She's a good looking woman.
Still?
She fills out a sweater.
I'll tell you that much.
I dated a girl briefly that looked like Ray Don Chong and it didn't work out, unfortunately.
She's right on gone, you know.
Oh, Jesus.
Yes, she is.
I'm looking her up right now.
I tell you this, Joe.
You say to me she's right on gone.
I'd laugh and we'd have a nice time.
You're just in this mode where you've got to shit on everything I say.
I don't think the listeners want that.
I'm just teasing you a little bit, for God's sakes.
Don't get all sensitive on me.
She's right on gone.
She's right on. She is.
Maybe, Pat, do you ever think maybe it hurts that she's gone?
It was like a...
And I'm not ready to joke about it.
Sure.
Have you ever thought about that?
No, I didn't.
I don't think that's the case here at all.
Now, did she die right on Chong?
I believe she did.
Did she die?
I thought she died.
I might be wrong.
No.
OK.
All right, Joe.
I don't think so.
So, wonder why Radon left.
Jesus.
Oh, I'm all worked up.
Every sentence I say is squatted over in shadow.
Now I'm worried that she died.
Give me a second here.
No, she's not dead.
How about Maria Conchita Alonso?
Did she die?
Another tri -named 80s babe?
I believe that she did die.
OK.
Yes.
How about Mary Elizabeth Mastro Antonio from The Abyss?
No, she's alive.
The Abyss?
No.
Oh, fuck.
The Abyss is such a great, great movie.
You don't like James Cameron.
I'm not a big fan of his work.
And I hate Avatar.
I'll give you that.
But, I mean, The Abyss?
Terminator 2 and Aliens?
What more do you want?
Terminator 2 sucks.
All right.
Well, let's move past.
I can't do this tonight.
When was the last time you watched it?
I watched it a lot.
I mean, you want to shit on My Blue Heaven.
Watch Terminator 2.
It's just as ridiculous.
But it's a science fiction movie.
My Blue Heaven was the anchorman of its day.
It was supposed to be ridiculous.
Joe, I will slap the drink out of your hand.
My Blue Heaven should have starred.
And he was the perfect age at everything.
It should have starred Alec Baldwin.
Coming off of Beetlejuice and a Miami Blues.
And he could have done it all in that movie.
There's your Radon.
Yeah, she's beautiful.
She's hot.
No comment on Alec Baldwin being the perfect choice for My Blue Heaven.
You never comment when you know I'm right.
Listen, I didn't say you were wrong.
It's an interesting premise.
I haven't really thought about it.
Yeah, sure.
It'd be good.
All right?
I'm just kind of getting sad now because I'm looking at Radon
and thinking of that girl I dated that looked like her.
All right.
That didn't work out.
Give her a call tonight.
She'll appreciate it.
Radon naked for real.
OK, then maybe they're the real deal.
She looked in this movie.
I paused it.
I'll be honest with you.
Also, this is a great monster for a three million dollar budget.
That's her now, though.
Oh, all right.
She's an old, you know.
I hate that I had that reaction.
She's not old, but she's an older woman.
I'm sorry.
She's probably in her 60s at this point.
None of us would want them 25 years later
to put up against a photo of them from back in the past.
She was born in 61.
So what is she?
56?
Yeah.
So there you go.
No, 54.
This demon is really scary in this one.
Yeah, I just said it was a great demon on a low budget.
No bullshit.
I also dated a girl that kind of looked like that demon.
You dated a girl who looked like that demon?
Kind of looked like that demon in a weird way.
Like, if there was a pretty version of that demon,
that's what she looked like.
And once I realized that, I couldn't get past it.
Had to break up with her over it.
A lot of relationships I've had are just something
that I've been like, hmm, and I get fixated on.
I think a lot of that might be growing up with Seinfeld.
I called my buddy out on it the other day
that he finds something with every girl like date two,
and they're always ludicrous.
And I think it's growing up with Seinfeld.
And these start to seem like normal reasons to end relationships
every week Jerry having.
She has got man hands.
She's got a high voice.
She's got a low voice.
Whatever it is, they start to seem like good reasons
to end relationships with beautiful, intelligent women
because of Seinfeld.
Well, I believe that those premises were written
because they are good reasons to break up with somebody,
and that's where those jokes came from,
and that's where they're so relatable.
Yeah, I mean, but in order to survive
and be in a relationship that goes anywhere,
you have to be willing to look past stuff
that's a lot smaller than Jerry and George threw away.
Yeah, it's slightly...
The women that George Costanza threw away
looking like he did are just mind -boggling with no money.
He's worse in Shallow How,
where he dumps that really hot chick
because she's got the weird long toe.
And then all along, he's hiding a tail.
A tail?
He has a tail.
That's the final gag in the movie.
He has a vestigial tail.
Is that a real thing that people get?
Maybe one or two, probably.
What the hell is that?
What's a vestigial tail?
What does that mean?
You don't remember this?
He shakes his tail.
You start talking about Shallow How,
then I chime in with another fact about Shallow How.
I'm just asking a question, Pat.
We can't go on like this.
I'm asking a question.
No, I don't know the Fairly Brothers process.
What does that mean?
What's a vestigial tail mean?
I don't know what...
What's the word vestigial mean?
You're holding an iPad,
looking up pictures of a topless raid on Chong.
Why don't you Google vestigial?
You use the word, you...
I think vestigial means like you have a little bit of a tail.
But in the movie, he has an actual tail.
How long is it?
It's like a very small flaccid penis.
And he wags it at the end of the movie.
I spelled vestigial wrong first.
I wrote correct.
I spelled it correct first try.
Maybe it's a tail that falls off.
Oh, that can't be a real photo.
No, of course not.
It's like an elongated spine sort of situation.
Here we go.
Human vestigiality.
It says that involves those traits occurring in humans
that have lost all or most of their original function through evolution,
although I don't fucking know.
They've already lost me with this description.
Speaking of Shallow Howl,
I went the other night,
a buddy of mine had floor tickets to see the Foo Fighters,
who I loved in high school and really haven't liked their music since.
That's the real vestigial tail.
Why did you show me that?
It does look like a little dick coming out of the guy's back.
Go ahead, sorry.
So yeah, I went to the Foo Fighters show.
I knew I didn't like their music anymore, but it didn't matter.
They played a lot of the old classics.
They were great.
And Jack Black came out and sang a full and pretty amazing version
of Russia's Tom Sawyer.
Oh, that's pretty cool.
And it was great.
And then Stevie Nicks came out with Heim,
and they did Stop Dragging My Heart Around and Gold Dust Woman.
And that was really awesome, too.
Heim is sort of our modern day Fleetwood Mac.
It's three very young girls,
and they make awesome pop dance kind of music, and they're great.
And the Foo Fighters played the Tom Sawyer music, and Jack Black sang it?
Yeah, and it was spot on.
And Jack Black was looking heavier than I've ever seen him,
and he's a heavy guy.
Really?
I hope he's okay.
Tell me, give me the Foo Fighters shit.
You know, they played from their entire career,
but they definitely picked the songs from their later albums that are pretty good,
like A Best of You and Pretender and those songs.
I'm not interested in them anymore, but they kept the hits coming,
and they played enough of the first three albums that I was interested in.
Look at that.
That's Ray Donovan.
Is that all Ray Don?
That's Ray Don's Chong.
They're making my Ray Don long.
There you go.
You think Ray Don Chong could get a job on Ray Donovan?
She's two -thirds of the way there.
Ray Donovan Chong.
Is this something?
Is this a hot sketch we could pitch over at the UCB?
Now, this is the 80s, and they just had sex after meeting 10 minutes ago.
I didn't see a rubber.
In his warehouse loft.
If I lived in New York in the 80s, I wouldn't have had sex with anybody.
It just felt like a living STD, the whole place.
Yeah.
You know?
And it was during the scare of everything.
Oh, God, I would have been terrified.
I guess now, I mean, obviously it's still a big, frightening thing,
but you never hear anyone say, like, oh, my buddy got AIDS.
I'm just talking any STD.
But you heard it a lot back then, I would imagine, from people I know who lived there.
It's just like, oh, another friend of mine, another friend of mine.
Hopefully, we're kind of out of the woods.
You hear about this douchebag hedge fund guy who bought the rights to the AIDS pill,
jacked it from $13 to $750?
$750?
Wait, what?
Look up this story once we're done, but it's this hedge fund dude.
The picture they have of him is like with two thumbs pointed at his dick.
He's like the ultimate douchebag bro frat guy.
He bought the rights to the AIDS pill that takes care of the most serious form of AIDS.
Not ATZ, but another very, obviously, it's a very important pill to people with the AIDS virus.
Sure.
He bought it, and he raised the price from $13 .50 to $750 per pill.
And they confronted him about it, and they were like, you're a monster.
What are you doing?
And he's like, you guys really shouldn't be mad at me about this.
You guys should probably calm down about this.
Just like these weird deferring methods.
What?
But he's just kind of destroying lives.
He's like, if you want these pills, $750.
He's a sick, sick man.
And how many do you need?
He's the most hated guy in America, if you get on Twitter or whatever.
How many do you need to survive?
It's for a certain symptom of AIDS that more serious patients need, I believe.
I want to look it up right now.
Well, I would look it up after.
It's just an interesting fact.
All right.
I'll look it up after.
And by that, I mean sort of now.
There's interviews, servicing with him, and shit.
It's a big news story.
Jesus.
I didn't hear about that.
Yeah.
I think I'm terrible at reading news.
You know, I often go back and forth.
I anything related to the news, the world, whatever is so depressing that I avoid it.
And I realize that makes me one of the head in the sand kind of people.
But also, like, what do I need to be more depressed about other things, too?
Like, I know everything sucks.
I don't need to read all about it.
It's I mean, look, I listen to the news every morning and I try to read a bit, too.
I know enough.
It's a lot of bad news.
You know, it's all bad.
I mean, that's the game they're in.
I ask people at work, hey, what's going on this weekend?
Well, you know, it's supposed to be 110 degrees out.
Why are you looking up the weather?
Just live your fucking life.
You're going to on a Wednesday be dreading the weekend because it's going to be hot.
I got to admit, I'll often I'll often look up the weather early.
I mean, and we'll do on vacation to go on vacation.
It's like, oh, well, you know, it's going to be this like, oh, man, it really sucks.
Yolo, it really low, baby.
But the but, you know, the weather, the weather can impact your weekend.
You know, maybe you say I want to go outside on Saturday and then you see it's going to be 110 degrees.
Yeah. What are you doing this weekend?
We had a wedding with somebody, Sean Clements,
who does a great podcast called Hollywood Handbook that I recommend.
I was on it, but they're all very funny.
And that's it.
Saturday, Saturday at the National History Museum, Natural History Museum in town here.
Yeah. All right.
Well, that's I love an in town wedding.
All my friends have weddings on Saturday.
I don't. The hell am I going to do going to any of them?
I'm going to sit around with my dick in my hand on Saturday.
Sounds like a good Saturday to me.
Hey, am I wrong?
Hey.
That's my reaction to that.
Am I wrong?
I'm giving you the hey.
I'm more than you are, dude.
I'm giving you a hey.
That was a that was a that was an affirmative response.
There's an element of right of a Walter Sobchak, John Goodman and Lebowski to you.
To me, not certainly not in the weight, but just in the hair trigger temper.
Oh, the anger about a lot of things, the argumentative nature.
Who's got a heart?
Listen, when I first saw the big Lebowski, I said I related to that character actually.
So I can't argue with you.
Totally hilarious.
I just read a great fuck.
I think it was on film drunk.
I always hate this when I read a great article and I want to give the person credit, but I don't remember who it was.
But it's about this big giant theory is a giant article about how they thought that Big Lebowski was about how the real way to be is to just be like a sponge and absorbing what people say and not engaging with their bullshit.
Sure.
They talk about the dude is very just like any time anybody's yelling at him or whatever, he's just walking away and he's like, I don't need this or whatever.
And people talking too much is what drives him nuts and like what the downfall is in the movie.
It was all about how the movie is about the needless talking that people do.
And whether it was what Cohen's intended or not, fascinating article.
I urge you to look it up.
All right.
I would like to I would like to read this article.
I love that cash.
I think I talked about this podcast.
I had a I did first one.
I had a film professor who would find the gay agenda in any movie.
And even though you knew it wasn't intended most of the time, it was just fascinating shit.
I like people's theories, people's weird ideas on stuff.
That's it.
Nice.
All right.
Fair enough.
I'll look it up.
If you're watching along with us, we're really like a goony or Neil Brennan.
The guy does.
Yeah.
If you're watching along with us, the weird looking Neil Brennan guy is on screen again.
And they're at James Remar's.
I can't remember his character's name.
They're at his art showing.
He's he started drawing pictures of this demon thing.
And but not showing them to anybody.
But but the process of doing that inspired him and invigorated him.
And now his art is doing well again.
And he's with Ray Don Chong, who's super hot and yet sleeping with this man, even though it looks like he fell into a vat of Crisco.
Right.
Earlier that day.
Uh, I mean, is now is Remar?
I mean, I'm not trying to shit on the guys.
Is he a good looking guy by 80s standards?
He looks greasy.
Remar, I think, has given me a poor man's Mickey Rourke 80s vibe, you know?
Right.
He's just kind of there nowadays.
He's much more of a character actor type dude.
Yeah.
But yeah, I mean, he's all right.
You're not bad looking, but it's a this is definitely a time where everyone could have fucked up teeth.
I mean, RDC, though, is like a 10.
Sure.
But I buy these two as a couple.
And I like the casual interracial vibe of it without calling attention to it, if I can be honest with you.
That's you know, it's something I always admired about this film.
My mom said that to me when she took me to see this.
Did she really?
No.
No, Pat.
I mean, this was very unusual for the time period.
Didn't strike me as odd when I saw it.
That's good.
You're a very enlightened kid.
I was always very open minded.
I remember going to see the Pelican brief at the Dollar Show with my dad.
And that was kind of my first discussion of race with my dad because I was like, so wait, like Denzel Washington and Julia Roberts for two and a half hours are like running around together.
And in any other movie, they would have been a couple.
They would have hooked up at some point.
Right.
Why did that not happen?
And my dad was like, well, you know, I think it's just hard for a mainstream audience.
And I was like, oh, OK.
All right.
But your dad was for it.
He seemed to be.
I mean, any discussion of sexuality caused the car to become isolated, silent.
So we kind of stopped talking about it.
Right.
But you got the you got the idea that he saw the flaw or fault in the public.
Yeah.
Not not that he agreed with it.
I mean, it was a pretty shitty thing.
I mean, like obviously any movie like that, especially a big John Grisham kind of thriller, the two incredibly attractive leads are going to fuck.
And in this movie, they were like pals.
Denzel Washington and Julia Roberts.
It was kind of fucked up.
Now, who does Tom Cruise bang in the firm?
Does he bank with a firm?
That's it.
I love the firm.
I just rewatched it.
And I was saying we're talking sex and it's called the firm.
Exactly.
What what does he do?
Does he bang in it?
His wife is Jean Triple Horn, who used to be Ben Stiller's wife.
Jean Triple.
I always think that's the lady from all in the family.
No, it's Jean Stapleton.
But no, he cheats on his wife in like the Bahamas or something.
And it's one of my favorite scenes ever in the movies.
Is Wilford Brimley.
That movie has the best cast of character actors ever.
Yeah.
Holly Hunter's awesome.
And Jean Ackman, all these amazing people.
Tobin Bell, who played Jigsaw down the line in the Saw movies.
But Brimley has pictures of Tom Cruise fucking this woman on the beach who they like set
him up to fuck the blackmail.
And Brimley starts going through the photos and he's like, you know, wives by nature
tend to be OK with the occasional slip up early on in a marriage.
But these are the kind of intimate acts.
Oral and such that a young wife won't forgive.
So if you can imagine a tight shot of Wilford Brimley saying oral and such.
It's just such a fantastic scene.
I was cackling when I watched it recently.
Oral and such.
He's got one of the best scenes on Seinfeld ever when he goes.
Oh, he goes post again.
Yeah.
I work for the post office and I also happen to be a general.
You also wonder, like, did he know he was funny because he seems to be humorless.
Him in In and Out, the great Kevin Kline movie in and out.
Yeah.
Who does he play in that again?
He plays the Joe Cusack's father to bring it back to Cusack.
And the best line of that.
So it's based on that Tom Hanks speech where he outed his high school drama teacher when he won for Philadelphia.
But Kevin Klein is not ready to come out.
It's a very funny movie if you haven't seen.
Yeah, I love it.
And so it's on the Oscars and he's like, you know, the reveal that Kevin Klein is gay and they're all talking about how outraged they are.
They go around the room with how outraged they are.
Then Wolford Brimley goes, he mowed my lawn once.
Never again.
It's like talking about an Academy Award winning actor.
Really cracked me up at the time.
He I that in and out was was a special genre of comedy that came out in the late 90s.
It was a very specific type of comedy.
I saw it on a double feature with the game starring Michael Douglas.
Loved it.
Those comedies in the late 90s is mainstream.
I was very, very glossy, shiny look to them.
Yeah.
Very whimsical, quirky soundtracks.
A lot of horns and things and and people sneaking around and stuff.
Yeah.
Grumpy old man is one of those shows like, you know, like an orchestra.
I actually hate that style of music and comedies.
It bugs me.
Most comedy music bugs me.
I like a silent, awkward comedy most of the time.
But yeah, 80s and 90s were bad times for scores and comedy.
Planes and Zonobils is pretty much my favorite comedy, I would say.
And the music in that is really fucking annoying.
It's like this weird digital.
At one point, they do a remix using Steve Martin's dialogue from the movie.
Like a rap song.
It's so terrible.
And I just block it out.
And I love the moment when they turn that digital music sad.
It's I mean, it's just it's horrible.
Yeah, it is.
Boom, boom, boom, boom.
That's so sad.
God, it's because it's so cold.
Yeah.
Detached.
I we talked, I think, on this podcast about how I sold this old copy of Gator Bait.
This like VHS movie, like how I used to sell things once they go out of print.
And I because I love the movie so much, I had a copy of the soundtrack to Planes and Zonobils, a used copy.
Soundtrack was terrible.
And I sold that for wait for it.
Five hundred dollars of a CD.
It had gone out of print.
I found it in a used record store and I was like one dollar.
Yes, I love the movie.
I'll buy the soundtrack.
And five years later, I'm like, I wonder what this is worth anything like that.
I hear a lot of people talking about the Planes, Zonobils soundtrack.
It was on Amazon for five hundred dollars.
I put mine up for like, you know, four ninety nine and it sold the next day.
The next day, the next day at a time when I really fucking needed money.
And that's something I'm going to recommend to all of you out there.
You got a big collection of anything.
Hop online, see if it's worth any money.
It got me through some really rough times.
This is a strong recommendation for the audience.
You heard it here first, guys.
Try to find things that are rare and out of print.
Settle them for.
I'm saying I don't say try to find them.
I'm saying you might have them.
That's what I'm saying.
And then sell them online to people.
I guess that culture has become bigger now.
At the time, I felt like I really stumbled upon something great.
That's the only way I made rent each month was doing little scams like this.
Criterions are great to buy and hold on to.
They go out of print.
Now, here's my question.
We're at the big twist of the final story here, where James remark was attacked by the demon.
Then he meets Ray Dongchang.
The demon makes him promise he'll never tell.
Great effects.
Ten years later, he's got a beautiful family.
He finally opens up to Ray Dongchang and says, this is what attacked me the night I met you.
Did you see this twist coming?
Yeah, totally.
You did?
I did.
From the jump of it.
No, not from the jump.
But I knew that once he was like, don't tell anyone that obviously he was going to tell someone.
But I mean, did you think he would tell her and she would be the demon?
No, I guess not.
I thought the demon would pop in through the window or something like, hey, guys.
Right.
Sure.
Did I think the demon would have that rack?
No.
Do I appreciate it?
Now, pretend you're a single man.
Yeah.
Well, actually, we could just do this with your current girlfriend.
OK.
Your girlfriend comes to you tomorrow.
She says, Pat, here's the deal.
I'm actually this demon.
Uh huh.
But you love me.
And as long as you never mention it again, we can just stay together and always look
like this to you.
But just know that deep down underneath on this demon, and if you ever mentioned it,
it'll come out.
Do you do you do you go?
Is she cool with it if we break up or does that trigger the demon?
Yeah.
No, you have the option of breaking up.
Do you break up or do you go?
Why put me in this position?
Out of sight, out of mind.
Why put me in a position that's going to jeopardize my relationship?
It won't jeopardize your relationship.
It's such an absurd thing.
I'm truly curious because I wonder how I would react.
I don't want to be with a demon.
You figure she's got contacts in hell.
But there would be no part of you.
I also figure a demon's not going to be very trustworthy.
There'd be no part of you that's like out of sight, out of mind.
No, not with a demon.
Here's the sad news.
You're saying she's a demon with a heart of gold?
No, it's it's just she's like radon.
She's like a nice girl.
And, you know, unless you say something, then she's just a yeah.
Then she turns into a demon.
Well, it's real sad when the kids turn into the fucking demons.
That's rough.
Isn't it?
I think that's why they made them cute.
So it would seem less rough.
I guess they're kind of cute, but then they all turn to stone here at the end.
They're gargoyles.
Here's sad news for the guy that paid five hundred dollars for your.
Oh, I bet it's worth nothing now.
You can just download the soundtrack or stream it for free on Amazon Music.
How much is the CD, though?
Well, I'm only seeing the cassette for forty five dollars.
Still, that's pretty good.
Because that's just an example of a movie that was kind of like an OK thing.
And now it's become like a beloved Thanksgiving classic.
Yeah.
Well, we're like, oh, I'd love the soundtrack.
And then they go up and look online.
If they get a lot of money, they're like, all right, if that's what it costs, I'll pay it.
Forty five dollars for a cassette.
I mean, you know, God bless.
I mean, the weird thing is only would you put the iPad down?
Pat, it's my job as it's not as trying to connect with you.
I'm connecting with you.
I'm the information guy on the podcast.
I look things up.
Deborah Harry, we didn't mention as the lead singer of Blondie.
Who didn't know that?
Hopefully you would know.
She was so hot, man.
I imagine a lot of people didn't know that Joe, who are listening to the podcast.
Not everyone knows that the lead singer of Blondie is Debbie Harry.
I think everybody knows that.
Is this is one of the Lawrence's dead joke?
We're probably talking to half the people who don't even know what Blondie.
What is with you with people dying tonight?
You thought Ray Don Chong was dead?
She's fifty four, for Christ sakes.
Well, I know Jonathan Brandis killed himself.
Yes, I'm going to look up.
I thought one of the Lawrence's was dead, but I might be wrong.
And don't yell at me now.
Why do the iPad?
This is why you ask a question.
Is one of the Lawrence's dead?
What are we going to just let it hang out there?
But when I look over and you're perusing, you know, Etsy for a, you know,
nothing of the sort is happening.
A new blouse.
Nothing of the sort is happening.
A new blouse with a print of Ryan Gosling's face on it.
Hold on a second.
Let's see here.
Joey Lawrence.
Whatever happened to him?
Whoa.
George Lawrence is alive and he's on the show.
Joey and Melissa or something on the kids network.
What is that?
Like a like a Nickelodeon sitcom?
Yeah, it's like a, you know, well, Disney Channel or one of those.
He looks weird.
Look at Joey Lawrence.
He looks like he's made of claymation.
Yeah. Why?
Why does he look like that?
I had filler plastic surgery.
Is that what that is?
It looks like filler to me, which I learned about very recently.
What's filler?
Filler is similar to Botox, but you're basically putting a skin like substance
into the wrinkles in your face and then you wind up looking very strange.
Oh, God.
And a lot of people do filler.
He looks so weird.
Yeah.
The movie's over.
It just ended because I'm looking up and I missed the endings.
I'm looking up this goddamn Joey Lawrence question you had.
You don't have to.
I know Joey Lawrence is alive.
I don't know about Matthew Lawrence.
No, I know.
I know Joey's alive.
Matthew.
Matty Lawrence holding it together.
Look at that kid.
Looks sharp.
Looking really good.
Good for you, Matthew.
Who's the other one?
Andrew Lawrence.
Matthew Lawrence is in Plants and Automobiles.
He's Steve Martin's very cute son.
Yeah.
Matthew Lawrence was also on Boy Meets World, was he not?
No, that was Fred Savage's brother, Ben Savage.
No, but Matthew Lawrence played his friend, didn't he?
No, that was Ryder Strong, which is a gay porn name if I ever heard one.
The other friend.
Hold on.
I'm looking this up.
I don't think so, but maybe.
Television.
He was on Give Me a Break.
OK, that seems right.
He was on Blossom as Young Joey.
OK.
Drexel's Class.
I bet Joey went into the producers and he was like, hey, you've got to get my brother
on the show.
Boy Meets World.
He looks just like me.
Boy Meets World, 68 episodes.
Played Jack Hunter.
You want to talk about another gay porn name?
Jack Hunter and Ryder Strong.
He also was on Drexel's Class to bring up our old boy, Dabney Coleman.
Dabney Coleman.
I used to watch Drexel's Class.
It was on at the same time as The Sinbad Show.
I think I was watching The Sinbad Show.
And during a period when The Simpsons was on Thursday, if I'm not mistaken.
Patty, we got another podcast center about here.
We did.
I hope you guys enjoyed it.
Again, we're on iTunes.
We're on all those little fringy side podcast places.
We'd love a review.
You click the stars.
You say Joe and Pat are great.
We love the show.
If you do, I don't need you to lie.
If you're listening to the fifth episode, you probably like us.
We love to hear your suggestions and we love your tweets.
I'm at the Patrick Walsh.
Joe is at Joe DeRosa Comedy.
And that goes for all social media.
And we'll be at the Mile High Comedy Festival, October 3rd.
Whatever the Saturday.
Saturday, October 3rd.
And we're at 820 AM.
Maniac Cop 2.
Come on out.
We're going to drink with us.
We're going to drink.
Basically, Pat and I's plan is we get up at 7 a .m.
to do an 820 AM podcast.
And then we're just going to drink all day.
I'm going to say this.
I am at my funniest with a drink or two under my belt.
And also at my funniest when I wake up way too early and I'm in a bad mood.
This could be a real funny combination.
I think it's going to be a great time.
I'm probably going to break Joe's balls a lot.
I think we're going to laugh and have a real nice time.
I think it's going to be great.
I'm looking forward to it.
I've done a lot of morning radio on my day.
I'm good in the morning.
OK.
Especially if I'm drinking.
You like morning sex?
No.
No?
Big fan.
All right.
Well, that's another time.
Big fan.
And another discussion.
All right.
Save that for the Mr. Robot podcast.
You're fresh, you know.
You feel fit because you just woke up.
It's not fresh.
I feel like it's sleeping all night.
Things are caking up and going stale.
I'm a sexual being.
If that's a crime, light me up.
You've been listening to ladies.
We're coming to your town, Denver, October 3rd.
Yeah.
And I would consider having sex with you even if you're secretly a demon.
I do believe in the out of sight, out of mind.
Sure.
This has two stars on Netflix, by the way.
It's ridiculous.
They're so harsh with the Netflix ratings.
It makes me furious.
Everything is two stars.
It's absurd.
I bet my returns doesn't.
You've been listening to We'll See You in Hell, a presentation of the Fangoria podcast
network produced by Thomas DeFeo, executive produced by our friend Ken Hanley of Fangoria
Entertainment for press opportunities, advertising, inquiry, inquiries, and information about
We'll See You in Hell.
Contact Ken at fangoria .com.
Thanks, guys.