Summer is here, and Bed MDM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer.
Or check out our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz.
Only available at Bed MDM Casino.
Spend on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 fortunes, Mystery of the Land,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand!
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action!
Bet MGM in Game Sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 Plus to Wager, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and West Virginia
only, games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as non -mustrable site credit slash bonus best unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
Gambling problem, call 1 -800 -Gambleer.
Howdy y 'all. Welcome to that there. We'll see you in hell podcast.
This is where you go to here to talk about the horror movies and the scary things.
My name is Joe DeRosa.
And I'm Pat Walsh.
I'm done with the country western bit.
We got dressed up for this.
Come on.
You're bailin' on a flannel shirt.
You were heading into sort of a Walter Brennan territory.
I don't know who Walter Brennan is an old prospector from the old Westerns. I got to admit I lost faith in it
Almost immediately and didn't want to really commit to it anymore. Yeah. Yeah
How are you Joe
Pat I'm well good. I'm well. I have a show this evening. I'm I'm looking forward to it
Glad to hear it. I'm gonna go down there and do some of this shit. I call comedy
Glad to hear it. I'm going to a picture with a friend and I, because we get sent all the
screeners of the Oscar movies, I realize just how bleak it is, like that January slate
of releases that come out. So we're like, he's a writer too. We're like, well, what are
we going to see? Going through the list. Here are our options. Paddington too, which I do
You see raved about every day on Twitter.
People seem to love Paddington too, but I can't do it.
I did see Paddington one.
Was it good?
It was, you know, visually cool.
It was like a Wes Anderson movie for kids, except we already had a good one of those fantastic
Mr. Fox.
And I don't get the huge appeal, but Paddington two is supposed to be incredible, guys.
Haven't seen it.
Of course.
The commuter with Liam Neeson.
The title of that thing.
barely passable.
I mean, who was, I guess his counterpart now, Liam Neeson,
the man who played Oscar Schindler.
He is like our modern day...
Who, Charles Bronson?
Yeah, yeah, he's become like a Charles Bronson
where it's like he was an actor that did all types of stuff
and then suddenly it's Death Wish 7.
Yeah.
I mean, I'm sure they cut him 5 million for each of these things
and I'm happy. And I think he's exercising some demons about the death of his wife.
He's always avenging the death of his wife. But I do wish the guy would make something
up to his talents once in a while. I've raved about the gray on here before, a great movie about
fighting wolves. And I love them on extras. He has said he's not done with drama. He's just like,
okay, yeah, I'm just doing this. I'm excited because he publicly said, if they do make the Obi -Wan
Kenobi movie. Yeah, he wants to come back as Qui -Gon and I would love to see him and you
him a Gregor in those roles again in a movie that was a little more focused on them and
a little less focused on trade disputes. I thought he was real boring in those movies and real
boring in Batman Begins. I thought he was such a lame fucking villain. He's just like a guy.
When you have the access to all those classic Batman villains and it's like,
like, hey, Liam Easton's playing a guy.
Well, he's Ray Shaugul.
Ray Shaugul wouldn't be a flamboyant villain.
He's a mastermind.
He's not, you know.
Well, it was a shitty villain in my opinion.
It's batman, he's arch enemy.
Anyway, Paddington to the commuter and Jumanji,
which I have heard is funny too, but I don't know guys.
It's, listen, you're gonna go see the commuter.
I think we're saying the commuter.
Cause I won't talk to you if you see the other two.
Yeah, I just tried looking the other night for something to see and it was the same thing
And I was like if the commuters the best I can come up with I don't give a shit if it is under my movie
I know I'm not going. I don't feel like it. I know, but your man who's got Jack Black who I always love and the combo of Jack Black
Kevin Hart and the rock is certainly intriguing to me. I didn't like it the first time though. Look
I
Like Kevin I know him from comedy. Yeah, he's a friend. No, he's
not a friend, but as a guy, no sort of like if I see him, we say, hello, yeah, always
been nice to me.
We started at the same club, punched up a pile of his wants very nice, very nice, nothing
bad to say about the guy, Jack Black seems nice enough.
Yeah.
Uh, I'm sure he's a delight, yeah, huge fan of the rock from back in the day.
That being said, no interest, zero interest and why?
Why? Because these men don't make good movies apart from one another.
That's true.
Throwing them together is not going to make a good movie, especially when, in my opinion,
it's just for...
For a mega.
Uh, well, no, Steve Martin was in the zone, and Chevy Chase was still, you know, he was.
All right. And especially when the movie is suitable to a movie, that they clearly wanted
to make with Robin Williams, and couldn't, so then they had to figure out this other
way to do it. You think they would have done it again with Williams? Why wouldn't they have?
I guess so. I guess I don't remember what was he a dad or something in that? I don't even
remember what was a game from when he was like every other fucking right Williams movie like
he was a boy and remembered a thing and then the thing was real and it came to life.
I was always jealous of the kids in jimagy because when I was a kid I got sucked into boggle.
folks. I was just spelling giant words with blocks for weeks at a time. I, um, and then
what was Zathura? Zathura was also got, they got sucked into a board game. Favaro did
that one. Yeah. I saw it. I just don't know. Look, I just, Zathura, I got as far as deck
shepard. I know. Well, I checked out of that. I am friendly with deck shepard. He's very
nice man. Is he nice? Look, I never met that guy. The first time you took a crack at him
like three weeks ago, I let it go. Now, I have to tell you he's my friend. So, uh, and
if he's a friend in the same way, Kevin Hart is your friend. Listen, I'm not saying he's
a shit guy. I've never met the guy. I'm just saying I've never seen one thing he was in that
I wanted to watch. Sure. He's good friends with Michael, honey, and them. He's funny in an
adiocracy. Jack Shep. All right. Some people don't get the material they deserve. You know,
I don't know what to tie, but I think I think somebody could have done a lot more with
that chips film.
I watched chips on the right hand.
You didn't see chips.
Did you see chips?
Tell me it was good.
I talked about it on the show.
I said it had a few big laughs.
A few big laughs.
What doesn't anymore?
The state of the union had a few big laughs.
Oh, politics.
All right.
Speaking of Trump, an ex -girlfriend of mine in New York and I used to love the Apprentice.
and early, early apprentice, and one of the hardest I've ever left, we were both drinking
like a bottle of wine, and Trump was on there, and he was so awkward, he used to do this
all the time.
He would clearly have taken a million dollar check to promote something, but he's such
a clumsy oath that when he would try to be a businessman and promote shit, it was so
authentically done and he just couldn't just gradual like you know slip things into
conversation like like you know we sponsored quip right the toothbrush company
now I'm gonna come free advertising they sponsor us they sponsor for this
sponsor if they were to say you know hey this week could you talk about quip on the
show we'd find a way to do it you know and and nobody would know we were doing an
ad because we're smart people here's what they were like why are they suddenly
talking in the middle of the show that's true that's sure yeah but I hear you Trump was
trying to promote Zathura and my god it was funny because he did it like 10
different times and he would go you know this reminds me of something something
I saw in the new Columbia Tri -Stuff pictures of Thura and if you see this
thing I mean the kids go into a board game it's it's a it's a new Columbia
Tri -Stuff pictures Zathura every time he would say Columbia Tri -Stuff our
picture. Oh my god. It just cracked me up. That's a tough look. I'll give him this much
of a break. That's a tough plug. It's hard on a show about being a business man to
slip in Zythora. I grant you. Yes. But I'm not I'm never going to cut that man any slack
at this point. Well, you know what I mean? I just you know, I'm just I don't know how would
you do it? This is a thorough plug. Well, this show would be incredibly easy. We just randomly
I started talking about Zathura a second ago, but all right.
That's a good point.
I told you.
I know I've told you this, but I ever tell you about when
I got interviewed to write promos for the Martha Stewart show.
No.
Oh, okay.
Here's a funny little story.
So, I was an NBC page, as you know, for a year in New York,
at 30 Rock, and you're supposed to get a job during that year.
It's like your goal, and I didn't.
There was a hiring freeze at NBC while I wasn't page,
which really is just my luck in a nutshell.
And I didn't get a job and you know I had worked on Conan and SNL and I had done very well and I gave great tours
And I was well liked and how does the page job pay by the way $10 an hour
Living in New York City and you were capped at 40 hours a week. All right
Well, I'm but that's doable the year that you were there the time the period you were there if you were out in Brooklyn
That's doable now lived in a story. Yeah, I was your 1600 bucks a month. Oh actually now what am I talking about that's that's rough
Yeah, no, I, and I went there with $700 in savings.
I mean, I never had any money and I accumulated a ton of credit card debt,
which I brought out to Los Angeles with every dollar I made on
always sunny went towards my credit card debt.
Okay. For both years, I was there part of that.
Because I'm sure that you have nothing, but what's up?
How much did you rack up total?
When I made it to LA, I was at 20 grand.
I think, you know, it was, it's, it sucks.
And then of course the interest piles on it does pile on doesn't it now I I'm I'm scot free, but
Not gone wood folks anyway
So I'm a page I didn't get the job and then I started really panicking because once it ended
I'm like now I have no income and credit card debt and everything else and I wasn't sleeping and I was distraught
So I'm like I'll take anything and Martha Stewart had the daytime talk show and
and at the time, she was also doing her apprentice,
like the weird Martha Stewart apprentice.
This is like when she just got a prison, right?
So, and she had her daytime talk show.
So, we went down and I met for the promo department
and so, I met with them and they were like,
okay, it went great.
They were like, so you're assignment then
to see how you do because we got to test you creatively
is go home the night.
And, but tomorrow, this time, noon,
send us a promo for the Martha Stewart show.
And I was like, okay, just a promo for anything.
And she goes, yeah, she goes, well, actually let's say
Donald Trump's gonna be on the show tomorrow.
So what would you do for that?
And I said, what if I told you I didn't need to go home
and I can do a promo for you right now?
And she goes, okay, what would it be?
And I said, Trump may rule the boardroom,
but nobody Trump's Martha in the kitchen, right?
She puts her hand out and goes,
welcome aboard. It was a real thrill for me and then it turned out and this look I'm not telling
tales outside of school here they were offering me a salary of like $19 ,000 a year to write for
the show and I was like this is New York City like that's I was making more as a and glorified
intern and I eventually had to turn it down but anyway it all worked out I got a job at NBC marketing
I used to do I used to do power points that had bring a tear to your eye
The office with Steve Carell in ages 18 to 49. It gets great in the demo
I did all that shit for a long time. You've got a great way with the words. I'm a word Smith, Joe
Yeah, your personality whatever it leaves to be desired. It's not great
You make up for it with your words. That's right on paper. That's right
I'm the exact opposite meaning that I'm not desirable and either place
No, and physically it's not great either I think physically I've got I refer to it as a hard body
Not a beach body, but a hard body not a beach body, but a heart. Yes
Let me take you to the movie corner. Did you get on with the you know?
I didn't so almost fucking missed it again. Well, you know, we're not I can always go back circle back to it
It's because you never put it after movie
This is madness, but it'd be like weekend update coming before the first musical performance. Yeah, what I'm crazy.
No, I'll do it. It's I hadn't thought of one as always. I have not planned one. So I'm just gonna start talking and see if it comes
Do the tower Jones one. I already did it. No, you didn't do the Howard Jones one. Joe. I did it. It was a huge success. Everybody loved you.
You did the Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe. No, I just told you to do I sang it to you. It said my friend used to sing it to me.
You never did it though.
Well, I can't do it if you did it on the show.
All right.
I got one.
I'm ready.
All right.
Anyway, let's just try to make the same natural.
Let's go on with the show.
Uh huh.
Whoo.
Let's go on with the show.
And at the same time, on with the JoA tonight, late December back in 63.
Right?
That was good.
I wish you guys could see the way dancers and like shimmies around.
You know Frankie Valley of the four seasons plays a mobster on sopranos and a couple episodes and he's fantastic
Yeah, I remember oh wait, no, that's a lie. I was gonna say I remember him being a good actor
But that was Frankie Avalon oh from back to the beach. Yeah, well, he's a good actor. He was a good kid
He did it remember y 'all know yeah back to the beach was the one where where they go back in their like 60s, right?
It's a bit of net food. A chewy hermins in it. Yeah, what's the premise of that? They got to save the beach or something
It's yeah, safe to be back to the beach had a little it was smart
It was kind of funny and Peewee's in it. That's why I watched that's why I watched it to as a kid
Speaking of Peewee, let's go to the movie corner and jerk off in the theater that I was talking about this was that was I think it was with you the other night
They ran Peewee Herman out of this fucking town Paul Rubens for
masturbating his own penis
in a porn or theater yeah and look at what's going on now it pisses me the
fuck off the hypocrisy of this town and then we talked about Fred Willard I
looked if you saw that third pee -wee movie you know I wish they didn't let him
back in jerk off Netflix executives on that one anyway and we talked about Fred
Willard and you he recently got caught jerking off and and Hollywood nobody cared
again he didn't have a kid's show no it's a couple years back oh that one yeah but
But what did you say he said when they asked him?
His tweet was because everybody's pressing him
for some kind of response.
Yeah.
And he goes, everybody's asking me to make a comment here.
And folks, if you ask me, it was a lousy picture.
It's a very funny, funny man.
And he kept working just fine.
Because I mean, what did I say?
You're now gonna do bit parts in Christopher Guest movies anymore.
Right, exactly.
Christopher Guest doesn't even make movies anymore.
He's on our friend's show, Jake and Matt Corporate.
He does a little part.
Guest is?
Or Willard.
Willard's gonna be on an upcoming episode.
But Ingerbredson and my buddy Bridger, Winniger, was a great follow on Twitter, by the way,
but they did a, they both are.
They did a short film that I saw once at a comedy show, it was five minutes long, you
know, some little thing they did for fun.
And Fred Willard did that really like, you can get, you can probably do his podcast if
we go.
You do, I think he just likes getting out of the house.
All right.
Anyway, about Paul Rubens, I love the man I always have and he's got a good little part
in a new HBO mini series that I just watched all of this weekend called Mosaic, which was directed
by the great Steven Soderberg, one of my favorite director.
So, Soderberg does not take a break, dude.
He doesn't.
He's got that new iPhone movie coming out.
Well, that's what I learned is that this whole thing, you're supposed to interact with an app
while you watch the thing, but it's not like they never tell you like open the app at this
part or something.
Right.
Something like an interactive thing.
And they also said it works if you don't use the interactive experience.
I did not. I don't know the patience for that kind of shit. But mosaic was great. And Paul Rubin's
plays a really flamboyantly gay guy. Usually he kind of plays it coy with his sexuality is.
Right. I guess he was gay and blow too. Uh, but he's, he's playing a similar role in mosaic.
Sharon Stone is awesome in it. And it's just like a five part murder mystery, uh, set in the snow.
So it was really good, really funny, and who steals the picture, Devin Ratray, who portrayed
Buzz, the older brother in home alone, who I raved about for his performance in blue
ruin on here.
And the guys become just a great fucking actor.
He's so good in this.
No, great.
He's a big fat loser, you know, and he's a cop, and he's, well, he's not a loser on the
show.
He's really good in the part.
I loved him and I recommend it, although don't go in expecting closure.
It's one of those mysteries where you're kind of like, you be the judge, right?
But I really liked it and it was, as always, with Soderberg very well shot.
It felt very original to me.
I liked it a lot.
All right.
I watched the entirety over the past month or so of the British multi -cam sitcom.
um, the IT crowd, which I had never really seen.
I hear good things about the IT crowd.
I'm a big fan of, um, gram lineman.
No, line of hand, sorry.
The, uh, son of a bitch, the guy that, uh,
from Toast of London.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, I don't know his name, but he's very funny on the show.
He's fucking hilarious, so I need to watch IT crowd.
IT crowd, you know, it is really funny.
It's a great, like classic old -fashioned sitcom.
I think people, what always fascinates me
is people that just shit on multi -cam sitcoms in general.
Always love British sitcoms,
and you're just being fooled by the accents.
It's the same shows, the same premises,
the same like forced situations,
but British thing, the accents make people
seem smarter than they are,
and they make the show seem smarter than it is.
IT crowd is just a big dumb, funny show,
Oh, and it's, you know, uh, the whole cast, Chris O'Down,
and then Richard Iadai, the guy from the,
your favorite, the watch.
Oh, yeah.
I like the watch.
Iadai, it's just, it's a very funny show.
Yeah, he's kind of famous over there, right?
He's, yeah, I think I feel like he was supposed
to pop over here and it didn't happen.
The watch was his big chance.
Yeah.
He directs and his movies are kind of well received.
He did submarine and some other things.
But he's kind of the cramour of the show you would say.
It's it's very funny and the guy who ever we're talking about from toast of London, I could look him up
I'm not going to but he's great on it
There are some big big laughs on the show and the funniest if you want just to watch
It's one of an ex -girlfriend who loved the show showed to me and and
It's it's the one to show somebody if you want to try to get them hooked
Is season two episode one okay? They go out to a night at the theater
just a real, like a, like a signfeldian kind of many, many plots coming together in a beautiful way.
It's great. It's great. I recommend it. And I watched the entire run of the IT crowd because
British sitcoms are so short. Watch the whole thing in a day pretty much. I saw one movie this week.
I saw the legend of Boggy Creek. What the hell is that? Well, it's a classic horror film from the 70s.
It's a sort of mockumentary style thing.
It's sometimes described as the Blair Witch Project of its day.
It's presented as being real, but it's not real.
It's staged.
And it's just, it's like a Blair Witch Project
except about Bigfoot in this place called Bogy Creek
in our Texarkana or something.
So it felt so much like an actual documentary
that I wasn't that intrigued or scared it felt way more like a almost like a
nature show than a horror movie okay it was it was just too it was like too
lighthearted the music and everything but it is pretty cool it's way ahead of
its time way ahead of its time and it is a classic so you know I don't know for
research purposes maybe you check it out but all right I wouldn't run to see it but
but it's classic hard, so it fits right here, fits in right here.
Did it, was it convincing in any way or no?
Yeah, there were shots that were convincing where you're like, oh, that looked like a big
foot.
But then the problem is you saw, if you saw the time, it was probably super convincing.
You see it now you're like obviously it's not really bigfoot this movie would be legendarily known
We would have seen bigfoot
As the movie that proved bigfoot existed right
So, you know I watch also Strant newly streaming on Netflix of a stupid and futile gesture
the story of the
Harvard Lampone national lampone I
Sort of wanted to see it. I don't know
No, I'm not, those things never really pull me in.
I had seen the documentary about,
which was called, what the fuck was it?
I think it was called Fat Sick and Nearly Dead,
which is the line from Animal House.
Right.
But I like the documentary.
I am as a comedy nerd going back to when I was a little kid.
I knew all this stuff.
What was interesting about it was the way it was shot.
there was some really cool shot David Wayne did it your old boss yep yeah
David's a very good director yeah it was shot really well and I just it
kept me at a distance because they made up so much stuff and there's so much
fourth wall breaking and yeah that's kind of why I didn't want to see it and like
Martin Moll being the guy yeah it was still alive but yeah not so live yeah did it
get dark at the end at least did it go into like a little bit I mean Doug
Kenny's a very dark guy who they're focusing on will forte plays him the cast is essentially
everybody in in comedy is in the movie and in some capacity.
Our boy David Crumholz about a hundred pounds fatter has a very small role.
I mean I couldn't believe how huge he was in the movie but it's it's it's good it's worth
watching it's it's good I I wouldn't you know I don't know what to say let me down a little
but it's coming so close to the heels of the documentary.
I just sort of felt like, I guess I get why they went
for this unorthodox approach, but I never like a movie
where you have no idea at any point
of what you're watching happened or not,
when it's supposed to be a biopic type thing.
But, and they go on to the set of Caddy Shacks,
and then there's certain points where it's like,
you know, John Daly is playing Bill Murray,
and John Gemberling is playing Blushy,
Yeah, you're just looking at all these people and then they make a point of it, you know, Martin Moles
like obviously none of these people look exactly like the real people or whatever, but it's hard to
wrap your mind around like Joel McCale being Chevy Chase and that kind of stuff. That was the one where
I was like, this seems a little silly. Yeah, but but my enlarge I was never bored. It's a very
entertaining movie and as a as a comedy guy, I of course had found a lot to like. I'd rather I'd
Rather it had been a dark, gritty, sad thing.
I mean, the fucking Wikipedia,
I read this thing on the guy's story
and we could be, it's fucking horrifying, so sad.
And I'm like, I don't know,
that's what a lot of the reviews were kind of,
well, some of the reviews were saying that,
they were like, they were like,
it's another story about how being funny
isn't funny at all, and blah, blah, blah, blah.
But I don't know, I'll watch it at some point.
I mean, I'm just it's just really not my thing. Yeah. And they did. So I know in the
spirit of the lampoon is very like anything goes and and no taboos and whatever. But like
the way they handled the fact that this, the entire staff of this thing for the entire
run of it was all white and all that. Like at one point, a black couple walks up to Martin
Bull and they're like, so there were no black people on this. And he's like, not a one.
But it was a different time. You didn't have to hire black people back then. And I was
I was like, boy, that's weird, you know?
Like, that's a weird thing to put into this fucking movie.
Well, I gotta be honest,
that's the main thing that made me not give a fuck
about the movie is that it's based on National Lampoon.
Harvard guys, yeah.
Yeah, and it's like, it's like, look,
National Lampoon gave me vacation.
Thank you very much.
Oh, thank you very much.
And gave me Caddy Shack, thank you very much.
Yes.
National Lampoon has done little else that I've ever found funny.
Right.
The magazine is like guys with elbow pads on their jackets, you know, uh, snickering
to one another.
It's all very like white bread, high brow bullshit, and, you know, look at us being naughty,
the rich kids, right, and then I saw the trailer and that, that repeat shot of Matt Walsh walking
out of the office going, uh, uh, we pissed off the Jews, yeah, we pissed off the Catholics,
we pissed off the feminists, we pissed, uh, it's like, yeah, it must be really tough.
to do whatever you want when you come from money, but so I don't know that puts a bad taste in my
mouth. But that all being said, a lot of people I know were involved in it. A lot of people I like
were involved in it. So I'll probably watch it at some point. It's an entertaining flick.
Can't deny it. And I love, I always love Will for today. I'm sad anytime he's not playing McGroober, but
I do love. Or the Falconer or I mean that man had some funny fucking shit on, on SNL. I'll tell you
Yeah, I see his spelling bee sketch. Yeah, it was I was in the audience. I was a Jack Black
Neil Young show when I left New York and since I knew people there, I went to it and it
is so fucking funny. They get the word is like, let's say the words like benign or something
like that. And he's like, he's like the super intense kid, but of course he's a 40 year -old
bull for it. And he just says letters for like five minutes, just various letters. And it
on and on and on and on and on and that shouldn't be funny but he's a man who
commits to a fucking bit and it's very funny it's a it's a sketch to look up
yeah he's great he's great shall we move into scary stuff I have something for
it this week go for it I have been eyeing that over there I went to Franken
Sun's pop culture flea market this week or last week it's the one you
Vincent and I've talked about it. It's down in like we talked about all going together and then you didn't invite us
Does that what happened? No, this is what happened. We all talked about going together
And I said my friend John has been asking me to go there for years
Okay, so I'd like to go so then I went with my friend John who's been asking me for years
Who quite frankly thought a little insulted when I said can I bring other people to I understand that so I went finally
It's all pop culture. It's all pop stuff. Yeah, it's all it's it's it's not a ton of movies
surprisingly, but memorabilia toys, video games, it took me 40 minutes, maybe to get there.
Video games, records, you know, all that kind of shit. It's great. Toys. But I got a newly released,
and I usually don't buy these types of things, but this box is so beautiful. And the figure was
so well done that I bought it.
Nekka, N -E -C -A, and real toys, R -E -E -L toys.
Put out a new nightmare in Elm Street set of figures.
One is from the first film and one is from the second film.
The first film I think that figure is already
a guess out of print because it was far, far, far more expensive.
But you can get the second movie film figure
for $24 bucks roughly on Amazon, if you can't get to frankinconsons, and it's
actually cooler. I never thought I'd see the day where I said the nightmare on
Street 2 figure is cooler than the nightmare on Street 1 figure, but it is. The
box, beautiful artwork, one of the alternate poster images is on the front, on the
back, you got this cool bus shot of Freddie on the school bus, you open it up, on the
inside, there is a very cool, I'm opening as if anybody can see this, but they're also really
like modeling it and showing it off to just me. Yeah, I know. Sorry. Inside, you got a very cool
Freddy figure comes with three interchangeable heads. Of course, one of those heads is the exposed
brain head. So you can say, you got the body, I got the brains. There are two interchangeable
glove hands, once the standard glove and one is the when the knives are just coming straight
out of the fingers. They're two of the demon dogs from the pool party scene and his hat,
which is also removable, and then also flames that you can detach or detach from his back
so you can reenact the whole, you're all my children now, which you know, look, I get that the
pool party scene is where the Nightmare on the Street series kind of jumped the shark there
for a minute because Freddie was in real life, but that scene is fucking awesome, so I don't
care.
Anyway, Nika Toys, I believe it's pronounced in real Toys, what did it set you back?
What?
What did it set you back?
I got it for 20 bucks.
Some people were selling it for 30, some people were selling it for 25, I looked on Amazon,
it was selling for 24, 99 in Amazon, I said all right, I'll go back to the guy selling
up for 25 and put money in his pocket instead of ordering online. And then I before on my way to
go back, there was in another shop that had them. And I was like, how much are these? And he's like
20. Well, you can't. Well, if it's not a lot of movie stuff, what is it? Music television? No,
it's movie stuff. It's just not a lot of movies for sale necessarily. But it's tons of movie stuff.
It's tons of star wars figures and antique toys and not antique but like old toys from the 60s and like collectible figures and he -man shit and
Is that all you bought records? I got that I got they have tons of people selling like old tops themed trading cards from every movie whatever
So I got these
hard -earned trading cards from the late 80s.
I bought a bunch of videos to make this apartment
terrifying to a woman.
The ladies love me, girls adore me.
And I mean, even the ones that ever saw me.
Did you tell people that I got you
a B. Arthur Dorothy's Mornack figurine?
Did I tell people the frankincense?
Did you tell people on this podcast?
No, I didn't.
Well, that's a little something for scary stuff.
well you didn't it's not scary stuff it's not a scary thing
i think i think she's scary she's certainly intimidating
uh... it's it's amazing that at this point after having participated properly
several times you still don't understand how this
uh... well like i mean half the time you're talking about video games
scary video game not always no it's always something with a fantastic element
or a monster element or something something that would be if it was a movie would
be a movie we could do on here.
I'll be honest, I'm still a little hazy on the details of the segment, which is why
I often don't don't don't participate in it.
Let's do a quick cranes crane shot.
I was called a cranes corner.
Sure.
Uh, I'm still figuring out this segment.
Now I will say last time it was just kind of a lengthy recap of the episode.
I don't know that people need a synopsis of.
Oh, I was.
I love you.
I was just going through the old episode.
That's what what do you think that was more fun because it was like we were
incredulous and how stupid they were. I mean, this was just like boy,
this was a great episode. All right, then I kind of sing a lot of favorite,
but it would also help if you're going to do a segment.
If you knew what the episode season or name or number was, how about
I just tell you for this week, one of a great line. That's what I should say.
I would love it. I should say this episode and then here's my favorite part
in this episode. Right. So here's an episode. Can't remember the name season. I'll get ready
next time though. Okay. But this is a line I texted you. I believe Frazier was speaking to a
garbage man who had garbage stains on his shirt. Uh -huh. And Frazier goes, oh please, let me recommend
you to an excellent dry cleaner. I once spilled butter on a pair of white velvet pantaloons.
Yes, and then Roz goes and he was wearing them at the time
White velvet pantaloo. It's I love that it's an it's an amazing that it reached the huge audience it did
You know like if you think about Joe six pack or whatever the audience is that these shows kind of go for
I mean, I guess unless it's just making fun of these buffoons
I guess the dad is kind of the voice of the every man telling them there be very much show
Yeah, so is Ross and so is Daphne. Yeah, and eventually Daphne's Anthony LaPaglia comes in as right right right, brother
You know the original choice for Tony's Prano, which would not have been as good a show by a million percent even though I like him
That is interesting and I do remember I
Forgot to mute the TV and the that's all right. That's your thing. Just went off. It's kind of a bitch. Let's give him some more promotion. I
I can remember briefly an episode to recommend to people.
They go, I don't remember the title again, but it's the crane,
it's the crane boy's mysteries episode where they go back,
they go back to their old house that they were evicted from at one point.
And they talk about when they lived in that house,
they used to write their own mystery series called the crane boy mysteries.
Yeah, and that's like that's like the dream of like I've been in this position a few times
Where you you are so excited to get to work when you're in a riders room
Yeah, you know, you've got something that's just gonna light everybody up
Yeah, imagine being like oh shit like the hearty boys, but with Fraser and not yeah
And they the great idea the gag is the the landlord still owns a place and they they decide they're gonna buy it
And then they decided to buy it they go can we just pick up this one floorboard and look at our our time capsule that we
put here. I remember that one. The guy says no. They sneak back into the house at night
to dig it up. They find a skull in the floor that they set up at the top of the episode
was their skull for when they put on a backyard production of hamlet as children. They don't
remember that. And then they the whole episode is them becoming the crane boys again. How
do they set? How do they set it up? But don't remember it. You see a flashback? It opens
with a flashback. Oh, I'm doing as children doing hamlet. It's them just a
deconstance entire mystery like how this guy's murdered his wife. That's why
they were evicted. Right. And there's a really funny line where he goes the wife
who's the wife was worth millions but it had to come through her and she'd
never let him live it down. And he goes and that's why he killed her in
tiles. And now it goes. But that wouldn't be insurance. That would be inheritance. I'm
excited to keep going. I stalled out at a certain point on treasure. But I'll, I gotta
get past the first season. It's a great. It's so good. All right. There you go. Was that
brief enough for you? Well, it was. It was good. I'm glad to hear it as long as you're happy.
Hey, that's my Tony half fast impression.
Yeah, let's get into this movie, Pat.
But to this week's movies, before I wake and folks,
let me tell you, this thing should have been called,
please just let me sleep.
Yeah, I mean, to call a movie this slow paced before I wake,
it's just dangling chum over the shark's mouth.
I don't know what people think of this.
I think it's been pretty well received.
But so this is Mike Flanagan who's, you know, hot shit.
He's become the go -to Stephen King guy.
He did Gerald's game.
This is the guy that did Gerald's game.
Correct.
It's the same director.
Oh God.
And he did Oculus, which I did not see.
Oculus is, and my book passable, but very forgettable.
He is doing the shining sequel
Mike Flanagan like he's all right. He's become a big deal people love him. I
Am finding now when I watch it now. I understand by the way why as I was
Almost spitting at the screen at how much I hated this movie. Yeah, the AV club for some reason gave it a nice glowing review
But of course now it makes sense. All right, you know what I'm confused by does the AV club like to show the good place?
It's probably, it's not clear, they probably do, because they write 18 articles about it
every day.
Well, I was trying to do a bit.
You didn't do it.
I didn't know that.
Oh, wait, they really like it.
Every episode, it's like the good place blows fucking minds.
Like they'll say fuck in the title.
It's the most earth shattering reveal in the history of television on tonight's good place.
That fucking publication has become so transparent.
It's sad.
It saddens me.
I've always enjoyed the AV club.
It's the only place really to get kind of a,
a sensical view of things.
Their TV reviews do drive me crazy.
I disagree, I've always thought they always played
up the underdog when it was cool to do that.
And now that all the underdogs are making mainstream crap,
they just praise that.
Well, I mean, they do have a segment called PODMAS,
where they've never, of course, mentioned this podcast.
No, I've never reviewed one of my albums.
I don't give a fuck.
You'd hate to alienate them, but they have their favorites
and it's all they write about, but.
That's what I'm saying.
I got I've become online acquaintances with Nathan Rabin is it we used to my favorite writer on the
AV club because they used to have a lot of great personalities and you'd read all their stuff. That's
cool. They edged all these people out. But yeah, because they were like I'm not giving a good review to
the fucking good place. Right. Well, he would respect disrespect to Ted dancing, by the way. I haven't seen
the good place. I'm just saying they they could back off its nuts a little. But Nathan Rabin used to
He essentially was the AV club.
He did my year of flops, which is where he'd review a notorious flop.
And they were like, I have a book, a collection of my year of flops.
So it's the only time the, one, a few times the AV club had book release.
That's how popular as columns were.
You know, he'd write about Freddie Godfinger, and then he would say it was this, uh, it was
this worthy of flopping, was it as bad as they say, right.
He had all these great columns.
And he said at one point, he wrote them and he was like, look, I had to move back in with
my parents. I'm married. I have a newborn baby. My columns generate a great deal of traffic
for this site. And he included the email. He posted this to Facebook the other day. And
it was like, can I please have a raise of $50? Right. And not only did they not respond
to it, they pulled his column. And he was essentially fired from the AV club for asking.
Oh, what are you dancing around saying nice, I guess I guess because they're a site that you need to like your shit going forward and I'm a creator in this business. Wait
Anybody usually I try I have to play the game a little bit. I play the game a little bit like they're gonna give my show and F regardless.
If they even review it, which they probably won't he did hush which we went to Netflix. I thought hush was very cool. I never ended up watching where she's
death and the guys out, so very cool.
He did Ouija Origin of Evil, Ouija Board 2.
I love that movie.
I thought it was fine.
I liked it less than you, but it was well done.
He did Gerald's game and he's got six upcoming projects, including a new, apparently, reboot
of, I know what you did last summer.
But what I'm finding, and maybe it's the Netflix, you know, the Netflix machine or something,
but the movies all look kind of the same and they all feel kind of the same.
So yeah, he's got kind of a style, I guess, but I guess that style would be like
Kind of depressing horror in a weird way and I was texting you last night
This movie it tips the scales too far. It's
So depressing that there's none of the joy or the fun of horror
And the scares don't hit because you're still thinking about how this kid's mom died a cancer. It's it's very depressing. I don't like
I mean this this was an uphill fight for me from the jump because I didn't let
But as soon as it starts, it's playing the somber piano music, for Christ's sakes.
It's so paint by numbers, every literally, every scare in the film is a jump scare.
And guys, here's the thing, jump scares aren't scares.
Startling somebody isn't scaring them, all right?
That's surprise.
Okay, there's a difference.
You have to create atmosphere.
year. The exorcist is scary when he walks into the room, nothing is going. Right. There's
no stupid fucking 808 based sound effect. It's much harder to not use these jump scares.
On the fifth time, Kate Bosworth walks into that bathroom towards the tub, and it's silent
for a full minute. And you're just like, when is the kid going to pop out of the tub? And
And you know, I'm watching it at midnight,
so I'm turning the TV down,
and then you can't hear the dialogue.
So you turn it up, and then,
and somebody jumps out of the fucking tub.
I'm like, not only is this not scary, it's annoying.
And, you know, like...
I was in the same position,
and it's like, the whole, I can't hear the fucking movie,
so I'm turning it up, and then every time
one of these stupid jolt's happens,
my subwoofer sounds like it's gonna go through the wall,
into my neighbor's apartment,
and I feel like an asshole.
So I'm trying to turn that down and it's like,
just fucking, anyway.
And it's literally the same sound effect
at every scare, same sound effect at every scare.
And not just in this movie, in every fucking horror movie
anymore.
And it makes sense now with Origin of Evil
because when the kid goes like creepy,
when the imaginary kid goes creepy, whatever,
I was like, that just looks like the Origin of Evil thing
that happened with the girl, like that's been done already.
like, that's not interesting to me.
Well, I think, I mean, he thought this movie was never going to get released
because the company that financed it went under.
So he might have just been like, I'll just use some of the stuff from Weegeboard, too,
in this movie. But let's, we got to talk about Thomas James hair.
Oh, by the way, the plot of the movie, we'd never been said.
Sure.
A family who's lost a son.
That final reveal, man.
Oh, God.
Yeah.
The family who's lost a couple who's lost a son,
adopt a new kid or a foster kid,
who's been from house to house.
He's a great kid.
They don't understand why he's getting bounced around.
They find out rather quickly that the kid has this unique ability
that whenever he dreams when he's asleep,
the thing actually appears in real life and whenever he has a nightmare that thing also appears which
you know you're in trouble because the trailer literally has the line whatever he dreams happens for
real yeah unfortunately so do his nightmares right there you're like all right so that's the plot not
Not a premise that couldn't have been made an effective movie.
It could have been, but once you have, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's diet nightmare
in Elm Street.
That's all it is.
It's like, it's, it's a much younger kid.
It's a much less scary monster.
The kid doesn't want to sleep.
I mean, this is a fucking absurd thing in the, Kate Bosworth, this kid's like five.
Kate Bosworth finds like that he's got like stay awake pills in his bag
Which how the fuck did he even get them first of all but he's got them and she goes well the opening scene
Is the is a guy creeping in to shoot the kid
Which I guess is a way to open a movie. I was like okay
That that kid was in room Jacob Tremblay. I loved room and I loved him in room
I'm not I'm not I'm never gonna pick on a kid actor
But I mean, he was a kid in wonder as well with the face. I mean, that's the same kid. Yeah, he's just
There's something about him and I I guess I am gonna pick on I just don't like now. I
He's he's got this way of acting where I'm like he's annoyed me. I don't know what to say
He's very much a modern
He's very much a modern day kid. Yeah, like he's very there's no personality. There's no personality yet
There's a ton of emotion and I'm just
Everything is like I'm sorry. I'm just trying to be special. Yeah, you know, it gets annoying
But I mean she finds these pills that he's got and then she goes. This is the line that Kate 40 -year -old Kate
Bosworth says to the five -year -old
I found some of your stimulants. Yeah, this is what she says to the kid
And he knows what she's talking about somehow
Thomas Jane plays the husband who I loved in 1820 whatever 1922
Another Stephen King adaptation, and I thought it was great.
Yeah, Thomas Jane, I think, is great.
He's in the midst, which we've said many times is a contender for best adaptation of
a Stephen King film.
He's in Bougainites, folks.
He's in Bougainites.
The fence rests.
His hair in this fucking thing is outrageous, ridiculous.
I feel like, I don't know what could have caused it, really.
I don't know who decided on it.
They got him dialed up like, like, uh, comment.
Satan church in sideways yeah, like but with greasy or hair even like it's like what are you doing?
It's not a period piece right takes place right now. Yeah, it looks absurd. He well
he he makes no impact at all in the movie and Bosworth. I mean Kate Bosworth's a pretty lady,
but did anyone see this coming that she would have some 20 -year career? It's like what what is she
bring it to the fucking table very little very little these are very wouldn't
performances through the entire thing particularly from the the lady that
plays the the you know the foster care lady oh yeah yeah yes yeah excellent
show that used to be on showtime called brotherhood if you want to look that up
and she was awesome on it she's a good actor but she really it's this really like
I mean, the script sucks.
It's the same with all of them.
It's a very, they're just very wooden performances
because the emotional depth is not written into the text.
It's not in the language or the dialogue.
It's just not there.
For people dealing with things that are this weighty,
you can only take so many support group scenes
before you say, all right, I get it.
They're hurting but show me in some other way.
I don't need to see them sitting in a circle
five different times to understand that they're in pain.
Write a good fucking scene about it.
That never seems to come.
Bosworth's character starts manipulating the kid and making him sleep
so he can make their little boy appear to them.
That's basically the premise.
And then an evil thing appears.
The evil thing turns out to just be the little boy
because of his, because it's a vision of what his mom looked like when she died of cancer,
which, which I found a little weird. I tell you, man, when they, when they cut to her and it was
like, oh, canker, you think cancer is pronounced canker, it keeps calling the canker, man. I mean,
like, you know, maybe it's just having been touched by cancer in my life as I'm sure most people
have at this point. It just felt weird. That's I guess the best way to put it. And that's
the final reveal of the thing. And I was just like, fuck you after all this misery,
you're going to double down on the misery with this like ending that just makes you wish
you were dead kind of well, then also too. I thought it was a little bit of an odd choice
to say this little boy thought his mom looked scary when she was dying from this
horrible disease that takes so many people you love and your life away from
you. So that's what the monster is based on. And look, above all else, I'm
always wanted to defend within the confines of art. It's art. I'm never gonna say
something shouldn't be a certain way. Do whatever the hell you want in the name of
entertainment. I don't care. I think everything is okay. So I will tell you the thing that offended
me more than that was the schmaltz factor of the whole thing. I mean this movie was, I mean
on Robin Williams' worst day, he didn't hit this level.