I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell
And when the sound of your screams becomes a thing of my dreams, you know I'll say
I'll see you in hell, you know I will
Folks, it's We'll See You In Hell. It's Halloween. This is, well, it's not Halloween yet, but this is almost Halloween,
and this is a special Halloween episode we're doing to hopefully help you get prepped
for your Halloween experience by us telling you our picks for good Halloween watches.
When we say prepped, we don't mean that you take the anti -HIV drug to prepare yourself for risky sex.
But why not?
But why not? But why not?
Better safe than sorry, I always say.
Has prep done away with the HIV virus? This is a question I would never ask a gay frist.
But asking you is probably not the best use of my time either.
No, it just, I mean I'm sure it's reduced transmissions, but it prevents transmission.
Yeah.
It doesn't like, I don't think it affects the virus itself, I think it just prevents transmission.
I see.
I think. But yeah, I'm no expert.
I mean, when I have heard people talk about it, it's like, we just fuck whoever now.
Raw and prep made that like world possible.
That's great.
But I can't imagine there's not still some danger. But what do I know?
Well, they say in the commercial, they're like, just keep in mind, it's not 100%.
But I feel like whenever, and again, I'm no doctor.
Yeah.
But I feel like whenever they say that, that's bullshit. It is 100%.
There's like a half percent chance that it won't work.
I feel like I have to say.
Oh yeah.
Well, then I wonder when prep slides over to the straight community.
I think it, you can take it. There's nothing saying you can't.
They just seem to be clearly marketing it in a specific direction. But I mean,
there's nothing saying you can't take it. Take it.
All right, I'll start taking it.
Take it and bang all over the place.
I will. I did have, believe it or not, folks, a positive, I shouldn't say positive,
Jesus Christ. What a word to choose there. A good date experience last night.
Oh, good.
Fun, nice, laughing.
What was this one? Grandmother with, you know,
you got to eat with grandkids before the sex or something?
No, and I did call that off. Thank you very much, ladies and gentlemen.
I had reached out and was like, hey, in best case scenario of dating you,
I go completely insane. So I can't pursue this. And she was nice about it.
This was just, as far as I can tell, a normal girl, but you know,
things will change, I'm sure, over time.
All right. Well, I wish you well.
Thank you. I love that just simply because I had three months, I didn't want to lose on hinge.
I'm going on like four dates a week. It's just, the behavior is absurd, quite frankly.
I love that you're getting matches, man. I didn't do very well on field.
I didn't really get many matches.
Yeah.
You know, they were like out of the area. I'd travel somewhere and it would redo my location,
which I didn't realize I had that feature turned on. So then the matches I would get,
I wasn't even there. And even by the time I saw the damn things, I'd be like, oh, cool.
And then I'd be like, oh, that's, this is a woman in St. Louis or whatever.
Yeah. 3 a .m. you're driving to Columbus, Ohio. Try to get laid.
Yeah. Yeah. So we're today, I had something I wanted to tell you.
I don't remember what it was. I have no dating. I have no dating news.
I have been spending more time alone than I think I should be.
Sure. That's where I was, hence the dating.
Yeah. Rageful stretches alone. Yeah.
Resentment, fury, you know, and I'll be like, I should get out of the house. I should go
be social. That'll be good for me. And then I go out and get barreled.
Yeah. Yeah.
I'm off the hooch, which helps in terms of my spiraling. Almost immediately my spiraling
goes away, which is a lesson to avoid. The lesson I learn over and over again.
Yeah. But refuse to commit to it.
Folks, when Joe presented me with today's theme, I thought it was another scary stuff sort of
on what the hell he was talking about. But then he finally said the sentence that made me get it,
which is today we're talking about movies you throw on around Halloween time
that aren't about Halloween. So basically I guess horror is allowed, spooky is allowed,
but we're talking about autumnal films. The type of film you want to watch
in that window between like October 1 and Thanksgiving before you switch over to your
Christmas holiday favorites. That's what we're talking about today.
Well, Pat, I want to congratulate you that you still have it wrong.
But it doesn't matter.
I hope my picks aren't wrong.
It's fine. No, I was saying five movies to get you in the spirit for the holiday. That's all,
you know, it's Halloween time. You watch, you pull five movies off your shelf that get you in the
mood for Halloween. And then I added the caveat because you said, well, wait, movies about
Halloween. And I said, no, no, no, it doesn't have to be a movie about Halloween, but you know,
scary movies that get you in the mood for Halloween time. All right. Really tough concept.
I say we should probably be more specific so you can't pick Halloween, the movie. You said,
I agree in my head it's top five movies that get me in the mood for Halloween that aren't movies
about Halloween. Yeah. So, so, but five heart, you said, I guess horror is allowed. The horror
would be top genre. Oh, see, I tried intentionally to avoid horror because I was like, that's all we
talk about. Yeah. Well, this will be an interesting episode. See, I, I have a feeling the type of
movies you picked for today will be. These are the, the now I'm, I don't know your picks yet,
but those are the movies I started picking in November. So I have my, my Halloween stuff get
spooky, whatever. And then when November 1st hits, that's when I moved fully into,
as you put it autumnal, you know, that's when I pull out a, when Harry met Sally or Manhattan
or something like that. And I go, now it's getting me in the mood of fall New Yorkie.
You watch autumn in New York with Dick gear and went on a rider autumn in New York. Uh, I w I'll
your movie about a Yorkie. If I can find one, just they're tough to come by these days, but
yeah, well, you get it. You can find bad ones on every street corner. You can find a bad movie
about a Yorkie, but a good quality one. It's hard to find. Yeah. Um, I, I pulled,
I pulled, well, I got, I have five movies here that, that get pulled myself today.
And you know, it was funny. It was actually harder than I thought to not pick movies that
were directly related to Halloween. Yeah. Um, I thought that that was easy. I was like,
there's like two horror movies about Halloween. I was very wrong. When I went to the shelf,
I was like, Nope, that's kind of about Halloween. This is kind of about Halloween. This is kind of
I've been, uh, I've been, we have, we have, um, I know I mentioned this at the end last time,
and it's not, it's sort of a plug, but I'm very excited that salsa windfall is now
performing on December 7th at my show in summer bill. And, uh, I've been working very hard
on the new record and we're going to record in January. And, uh, I'm excited about all these new
songs for the next record. Uh, I don't know why I want to say that. I just want to say it. I was
working on it before we hopped on today. Yes. Um, it's about the only thing that brings me joy
anymore is sitting alone, working on music, chain, smoking cigarettes. It's not probably a way I'm
going to be able to retire, but you never know. It could be a producer laying down tracks.
You know, I keep thinking, go ahead. I'm sorry. I was going to say, I keep thinking I'm going to be,
18 typewriters and two computers. And I keep thinking I'm going to sit in this office of
mine and start to really become a writer in heavy quotes. And God, it's real hard.
Yeah, no, I bought this antique writing desk, you know, super nice. I have what is essentially
an office where I'm like, it's all my records, but I also got the headphones so I can listen to,
you know, the best quality sound while I'm writing and this is my own little oasis in here and I can
let the sun in and whatever. 99 ,999 out of a million times I wind up writing, uh, like with
my legs over my head on the couch, bashing my head against the floor, you know, in some awkward
position. I never use the office for anything. In fact, when I sit down at the desk, it stifles
my creativity. If anything, I will say, um, I was working on, I'm still working on it very slowly,
but I will say the, for whatever reason, when I started using the traditional typewriter,
it started to come out, maybe it's the distraction free thing or whatever, but it started to come out
a lot more quickly, but that was not a script. You could never, I mean, you could write a script on a
trial of insanity. Are you getting typewriter ink and stuff? Like they all are working models.
I, there was a store in New York that sir sold refurbished typewriters and you know, they,
you know, there's a ribbon in it and you know, that's it. It's just, you know, it's not like a,
um, yeah, it's, it's, it's much simpler than you'd think, but, um, but you know,
you gotta get used to like, you made a mistake. The mistake is just going to be there on the page.
Yeah. You know, which is a little hard for me because I have a little OCD, but,
but I have a lot and I don't think I could handle that. I'd be thinking of
Kathy Bates looking over my shoulder, watching each typo.
You seen that clip of her going around this week? It was kind of an amazing clip. It was really cool.
She was on 60 minutes or something. She's lost a hundred pounds. Won't acknowledge the Ozempic
like everyone else. I was like, all right, Kathy. Yeah. Yeah. Kathy, you were doing a bootcamp
classes. You know, you were over at CrossFit. Okay. Anyway, um, I love Kathy Bates and they're
talking to her about winning her Oscar in 1990 for misery. One of my favorite performances ever.
Certainly one of the all time great horror performances up there with Nicholson and the
Shining. She walks up, accepts it and she's talking about how her mom was a narcissist.
Okay. And she's like, boy, my mom was difficult, but you can tell she like loved her and she
really misses her. She has this very complicated relationship with her. She was like, she never
once let me forget this, but I did not thank her in my speech. And until her dying day, I had to
hear about it. And God, it's one of the biggest regrets of my life that I couldn't have just
and thanks mom or whatever. And the guy interviewing her goes, Kathy, we've got a clip for you.
And he shows it and she's accepting her Academy award. And she thanks her mom very clearly.
And she immediately starts sobbing. Oh, wow. She's like, you could tell what you can tell.
She's like, oh my God, my mom was so fucked up for giving me shit about this. When she just,
she was just mad about nothing. You know, it's an amazing clip. Wow. Um, and of course you can see
the relief wash over her. It's like her whole life is better now because she knows this,
but it's also kind of like, why not watch the speech again?
Yeah. I get that. It's not like I'll ever watch my wedding video or something. You know, you don't
go back to this. Yeah. She's cringing from it. Yeah. That was like Eddie Vedder in that Pearl
Jam documentary, whatever it was. Um, you know, they did the thing, they, they did the, the concert
when singles came out. Yeah. And like, they were really on their shit back then.
And that's the best song is the single song. Yeah. And he's wasted or at least he seems
wasted. And he's like this fucking industry thieves. He's screaming. Uh huh. And like,
they bring it up to him in this thing, 20 years later, whatever it is. And he's like, he's like,
well, I will not watch that clip. I will not watch it. Like, you know, like it's hard to
watch things that are documentations of regretful moments. Yeah. Sure. I get that. I get, I get that.
No, not at all. She's retiring. She said Matlock is it, which by the way, but she's going to do
five years of that for sure. This Matlock. I hope you have the same issue I have just from watching
one second of it. You probably do. Yeah. It's the moment in the trailer where they're like,
you're like that detective from the old TV show. There it is. Joe,
what the fuck? We're doing a meta Matlock on CBS. We're doing B and John Matlock over on CBS.
Insane. I did not expect that at all. So like he, this fictional character,
I guess they're playing it like he was her real grandfather and they made a show about his
exploits or something. Oh, Jesus. You went deeper than I did. I didn't even know. I didn't know. I
was just like, I just thought it was like, oh, her name is also Matlock. And then I was like,
well, maybe in the episode, the joke plays out where they go Ironsides or some other famous TV
lawyer. And then that's the joke, but yeah, maybe. I don't know. I I've never seen an episode of
Matlock. Never. And even I've never seen a second of Matlock. I think for a lot of people, we know
it from grandpa Simpson being obsessed with it on the Simpsons. Yeah. I need my Matlock.
One of the best theme songs of all time though.
Oh yeah, that was a good one. And then what was the theme song to In the Heat of the Night,
which in Missouri came on after it. It was like, in the heat of the night.
Yeah. It was like steamy. Yeah. Sultry. Yeah. I was talking to a friend recently about that
because I met two different, well, one was a friend and then one was somebody I had met recently,
but they both were, they both were obsessed with Murder, She Wrote and they were like,
it's the best show. I love it so much or whatever. It was, it was weird to meet
two people really into Murder, She Wrote that close together randomly. But
I was talking about it. I was like, that was a weird phase in television. We were real obsessed
with elderly detectives. Yeah. Like In the Heat of the Night was Carol O 'Connor. Matlock was Andy
Griffith. And Angela Lansbury Murder, She Wrote. I feel like there's another one in there that I'm
not remembering, but people really loved like senior detectives back then. Perry Mason was a
lawyer, I guess, but that was a whole nother. They liked seniors thriving at their jobs,
which I guess these shows were targeted for old people, so that makes sense. But Perry Mason
in his prime was like 40. They just came back later. Yeah, I'm just thinking of the old
wheelchair Perry Mason when he's like 80. That's Ironsides is the wheelchair. But isn't Perry Mason
Ironsides? No, no, it's two different shows. I used to confuse them myself. Well, who's Ironsides?
I don't know who plays them, but - Perry Mason's Raymond Burr, right? Joe, I think they're the
same man. Well, it might be the same actor. It's two different shows. Ironsides was also Raymond
Burr, but he was a different. Yeah. So that's the confusion. It was just two different men named.
That's weird. Which came first? Please tell me Perry Mason came first. So then the second
time around, they're like, we got to do something here, guys. Put them in a wheelchair.
Raymond Burr was 67 to 75. That was a wheelchair fella. And then they remade it with Blair
Underwood 10 years ago, which I'm unfamiliar with Perry Mason. Perry Mason was not in a wheelchair.
And that was 57 to 66. So there was the 10 years before. So that's what it was. They said,
we want Raymond Burr for this lawyer show. And they said, you have to change something. And they
will make him in a wheelchair. Right. And we'll call it Ironsides, which seems not okay.
Ironsides to the wheelchair. I never even thought of that. Yeah. Yeah. Anyway,
not one of my Halloween picks. Ironsides. Oh, never seen any of it. That whole daytime TV world
was never my thing. Once mama's family ended, I fell into a deep despair. And then at night,
of course, when you heard the MASH theme song, it was like, I'm going to bed. I don't need this shit.
God, I hate MASH. Suicide is painless. It was what I listened to every night before going to bed. Now
I wonder why I have a problem. I fucking hate MASH. Jesus, I hate it.
Yeah. God, it sucks. It sucks. It does. It really sucks. Let's get to the task at hand.
Oh yeah. All right. Hit me with it. Let's talk our movies. Mine were mostly just kind of on feel.
You know, I got a little anecdote maybe for each that can get you there, but I really thought
we were doing kind of non -horror autumn vibes. My number one pick or one that I always turn to
around this time of year would have been Ordinary People. But I just talked about it a couple months
ago when I saw it at the theater, but that's the vibe I'm with. You know, leaves, maybe there's a
Halloween scene in there, but just the vibe is very autumnal. My number one choice, no particular
order, new to 4K, looks beautiful, is The Addams Family. It's a spooky movie. There you go. You're
right. It is fun, spooky, but I was 10 when The Addams Family came out and it really was the first
like, I think it was the first movie my family saw as a unit. I think there's maybe been three
movies that me and my sister, my mom and dad saw together, which is nuts. But The Addams Family,
I think was the first one. We always had to wait for The Dollar Show, which meant sometimes like
in the case of Batman, it meant I saw Batman two years later than everyone in my graduating class
with children. My family just didn't have the money really, so we would just wait for The Dollar
Show. But occasionally I would be adamant, I would be passionate enough and insist that we go see
something. The holiday season prior, that movie had been Home Alone and really a dream family
movie. It's what you want. We all laughed. We all still love it, still remember it, still watch it.
Those movies don't seem to exist outside of Pixar where like parents and kids can go together.
And then Addams Family the following year, I remember the world just felt like fall.
Us going up to the mall to see it bundled up. The movie is spooky. It opens on a Halloween scene or
it's where they're, I guess that it opens with them dumping that cauldron onto the carolers.
But there is a little bit of Halloween in there. It's the best Burton imitation we've ever gotten,
I think. It's as close as we've come to somebody else capturing the magic. And Barry Sonnefeld
actually brings a lot of his own flair to it as well. I love the way he shoots a movie. He shot,
of course, Raising Arizona and Miller's Crossing and many beautifully shot movies. And he's a great
comedy director. I don't know if he, I guess he had too many bombs. I read his book recently,
which is really good and fun, but he doesn't really direct much. I thought he was great.
And I think as far as TV to movies go, this is a pretty, especially considering this was the era
where like Beverly Hillbillies with Jim Varney was coming out and the Shitty Litty Little Rascals
movie was coming out and they were trying to exploit just every property from the past.
And this one really not only nails the spirit, but it's genuinely funny throughout. You'd be hard
pressed to find a more carefully and perfectly cast adaptation. That's lost as well. Like I
haven't seen Wednesday, but we're talking about Catherine Zeta Jones and what's his face? Louise
Guzman? Yeah, that's not terrible casting, but it's no Raul Julia and Angelica Houston.
I'm with you. It's not terrible casting, but yes, when you're casting Angelica Houston and Raul
Julia, when they're not two of the biggest stars on earth by any means, you're going for who's the
perfect person for the part. And they got it. Obviously Christina Ricci is incredible.
Christopher Lloyd's Uncle Fester, I think is better than the original Uncle Fester.
I love what he did with it. Christopher Lloyd, sometimes you're like, you're doing this guy again,
Chris, but Fester is definitely its own weird creation. I love this movie. It makes me think
I plan on watching it this weekend and I'm also even more excited for Addams Family Values,
which is about to drop on 4k and is an even better movie and an equally great fall movie
with a great performance by David Krumholz and an all -time supporting role from the amazing Joan
Cusack. I love both of these Addams Family movies a lot. Well, here's a poll. It's not a movie,
but it's a special. But every year I pull the, off the shelf, I pulled the Disney
double feature animated of The Legend of Sleepy Hollow and Mr. Toad and the Adventures of Mr.
Toad, whatever the hell it's called. These are both animated classics and I'm going to
from the heyday of Disney back before they became a global terrorist conglomerate,
back when Disney could still inspire a bit of magic in your heart.
You had some belief in the shit they were talking, but it's a great watch. It starts
with an intro by Walt Disney himself, which makes it all very charming. And the animation in both
these, but particularly Legend of Sleepy Hollow, it's unmatched. These guys were top of their game.
They were doing innovative stuff that nobody really seemed to be doing back then, or at least
at that high quality level. And I think that this version of The Legend of Sleepy Hollow to me
is the definitive version. Burton pulled a lot of inspiration from this in his movie.
Burton's movie is great, but he also makes it a much bigger story. There's all kinds of elements
in it that are not in the original story at all. But if you go for a straight adaptation of the
original story that trims the fat, of course, it's not a long watch. I think it's only 30 minutes, but
it just gets you in the spirit. There is a Halloween party scene that leads into the
It's spooky. My only regret, or not regret, but disappointment is that I don't know why.
Hey, I'm racking my brain. Why did Disney World not make a ride of this? They made a ride of Mr.
Toad and it's really fun and it's kind of scary in parts. And like, why would they not make a
Sleepy Hollow ride? It would have been incredible, man. It doesn't translate to year round in the
same way as Wind in the Willows. It would only be a Halloween feature. I guess, but I mean,
imagine sitting in one of those Disney metal carts on the track and going through that forest
and like an animatronic headless horseman. I mean, it would have been awesome, man. So,
I strongly suggest watching this. It just really nails it. It puts you in the spirit. And then Toad,
which is the second feature in it, that sort of swings you right into the vibes of Thanksgiving.
So, you can't go wrong with this thing at this time of year. I think it's only available on DVD,
but it's worth grabbing. Probably Disney Plus, right? I'd love to watch that.
I don't know, to be honest. Actually, it's a good question, but I would assume it's on there.
But definitely check it out. It's a great one. It's a great watch.
It is. I remember loving that as a kid. It was second to me only to Mickey's Christmas Carol,
which I find still one of my favorite tellings of that story.
I love Mickey's Christmas Carol. I hate that it's like 19 minutes.
I know. Is that not like a half hour? It's short, but Mickey's Christmas Carol,
that's something where I'm like, no, get into this, guys. Give me an hour here.
Give me some backstory. What do you got? Right. By the way, Adam's Family and Adam's Family
Values is a perfect way to go from Halloween to Thanksgiving as well, as Adam's Family Values is
wisely a Thanksgiving movie and a intense satire of Thanksgiving in a great way.
My second choice is going to be Major League,
written and directed by David S. Ward, who also did The Sting, which of course won best picture.
People love Major League. Of course, baseball people love Major League and I still find it
to be about as underrated as it gets. I don't like sports at all. I don't care. There are times where
a sports movie can really get me invested and cheering because it cuts away all the boring shit
and gives you just the best of the best. That's about as much sports as I can watch.
But to me, this movie, so this guy did The Sting. He also wrote The Sting 2.
After Major League, he did King Ralph, which is not a good movie. He wrote Sleepless in Seattle.
Efron wrote that. He co -wrote. Oh, okay. He co -wrote. He's got credit. There's three writers here.
He did a lot of good work in his career, but to me, even superior to The Sting, I think,
is Major League. There's no finer baseball picture, really. It's so funny,
but it's also like I am on my feet at the end of it every time as if I'm watching a World Series
game. I love Major League because it feels very autumnal because it's dealing with the pennant,
the race to the World Series. The Cleveland Indians have never won the World Series
in this movie. It's been ages. I forget what the specifics are.
It's wild, by the way. They took a real team that hadn't won and they were like,
we're just going to make a movie about this and we're going to make fun of it.
And the Cleveland Indians were like, cool.
See, you think you could never do that now. You always say you could never do it now.
The actual truth is my dear friends, and I don't think they'd mind me saying this,
but my friends who do Cobra Kai, so it's not like they're nobodies, but they were like,
hey, we're pretty good at reinventing these sports things from our childhood.
And they had to pitch Major League Baseball on doing a Major League TV show. They had,
I want to say, Sean Williams Scott. They had a good cast. And the Indians were like, fuck no.
We were already a laughing stock. That movie made us an even bigger laughing stock.
You can't do it. So like they were talking about doing it. Like we play for the Cleveland
devil raise or, you know, some made up thing, but it just didn't feel right. Major League is Chuck
Sheen. It's sort of easy to forget if you're like me and never saw two and a half men that Charlie
Sheen is an extremely gifted comedic actor, but of course he was in the hot shots and,
but he can also do genuine comedy. Like he wasn't always the Frank Drebben.
He was a really like talking about him like he's dead, but he is a really funny comedic actor.
You also got Tom Barringer. You got Wesley Snipes as Willie Mays Hayes. I play like Mays and I run
like Hayes. Wesley Snipes is an immediate star. It's one of those performances where you're like,
holy shit, like this guy's going to be huge. He was so huge that they had to recast his role for
Major League Two. You got James Gammon, the guy, the coach who had one of my favorite movie voices
the guy who was like, what are you talking about? You know that guy? Yeah. Oh yeah. Big mustache.
Yeah. And it was kind of the harder edged Sam Elliott. Renee Russo, the love story in this
works incredibly well. In addition to the sports story, a great Corbin Birdson as a douche,
a great Dennis Haysbert as the guy who's a little bit racist, but the black guy from the islands
who's like obsessed with voodoo. Let's, let's call it what it is. A lot racist, but it's pretty funny.
I love this movie so much. I think in terms of like an underdog sports movie, you really
can't do much better. And I also want to shout out, if I may, wait, what the hell was I going
to shout out? I do this all the time. I start a sentence and then it just goes.
I tuned out. I don't know.
I had nothing else to say, but major league. I love it. If you've never seen it, check it out.
I do think it is oddly underrated. I know what I was going to say. Who steals the film is the only
non -actor in the film. Bob Euker. Oh, Euker is always great. I do say non -actor, even though
he was on Mr. Belvedere for several seasons, I still feel confident enough to say a non -actor,
but if you've never heard Norm MacDonald tell his Bob Euker stories, Google those.
Euker is one liners in this movie are the stuff of legend. Like they talk about how they showed
the movie to people and the crowds were like, we love this. We want more of the 68 year old Bob
Euker. So they wrote in like extra quips for him to make. He's so funny. I love this movie. If you
haven't seen it, check it out. Joe Euker is the line is just a bit outside, right?
A bit outside. Yeah. Tried the corner and missed the ball. The ball gets thrown completely out of
the strike zone. You save that with the race for the pennant part because when you first said
major league, I was like, this is the most insane pick. I predominantly played in the summertime
sport. This is a fall movie and it's one that I watched every year around this time because
I was pretending to like baseball to humor my friends and family, but this would always be
played during the pennant race. It reminds me of the weather getting cold. And like right now,
I was out last night on a date and the bar was playing the Dodgers and I don't care. I don't
care what the score is, but like the playoff games is something that always puts me in that fall
mood for sure. The world series, blah, blah, blah. My second pick here is, you know, man,
a movie that I think doesn't get its propers. It's dismissed quite often, particularly because
I think the director is known for not making the greatest stuff all the time. And the fact
that it takes place in space, I feel like it does not get its propers.
A fall space movie. Now I'm even more confused.
In the mood for Halloween, though, Event Horizon, it's a great, it's a haunted house movie. It just
takes place on a spaceship. I've seen -
Terrified me when I saw it, as a young man.
It's often, there are internet theories that it's connected to the Hellraiser universe and
it is very Hellraiser -y. Because it's about this dimensional portal where these demons come
through. Sam Neill.
And it seems like the demons fuck.
Yeah, it's got a sexual, very of the flesh kind of vibe to it. This is a movie where,
this one just made the Variety, was it Variety's top 100 horror movies?
Was it on that list? I don't know.
It was.
Yeah, Variety just put out a new list of the top 100 horror movies. That's pretty good,
pretty solid.
That could be an episode, by the way.
Sure, yeah.
I mean, it may be a two -parter because it's long. But I just think it's, if you're looking for a
spooky, fun, again, haunted house kind of thing, that once it's going to get you into the mood
for the scary season, I think you'd be, you could do a lot worse than Event Horizon. You got Sam
Neill in there doing the Sam Neill thing. We've talked a lot about Sam Neill.
His vacantness really works in possession and it really works here too. He's got this sort of
deadness of the eyes that really works.
Yeah, I always like that scene where he takes the paper and he's explaining how the time travel
works or whatever. But it's just a fun movie. It was directed by, and I would say it's not a
fun movie, but I think it's fun in a scary way. But it's directed by the other Anderson.
Is it, well, I always get this confused because there's P .T. Anderson who is,
you know, the good director, let's just say. This was directed by Paul W .S. Anderson.
And again, that's nothing against Paul W .S. Anderson. I like him and I like what he does.
But his claim to fame is really the Resident Evil franchise, which I'm not a big fan of. I don't
think it's bad. It's just, to me, not the best adaptation of what that game series is.
But, you know, he directed those. He directed Mortal Kombat, which again, a fun movie, not a
great movie. I think he did Alien versus Predator. Yeah, he did. My point is, I think he kind of gets
pushed a little to the sidelines when you talk about horror greats and creators, because he's
done a lot of these sort of passable horror movies that some people love, some people hate.
But I think that Event Horizon doesn't get its just due because of that. You also got
Laurence Fishburne in this thing. It's a good movie, man. It's Jason Isaacs,
Jolie Richardson, Kathleen Quinlan. It's a good cast. Sean Pertwee.
It's a good cast. It's a good movie. It's fun. It's spooky. It's alarmingly frightening in places.
But people hate it, man. It's got a 35 % on Rotten Tomatoes. I don't understand.
This movie was one of the ones on the variety list that Pinkstone, when I talked with him about it,
he was genuinely pissed that this movie was on it, which I disagree. I think it deserves
its standing. I think it's an unsung classic. And I think, again, if you're trying to get into the
mood for the season, this is a great little flick to watch. Was it Paul Anderson or Uwe Bull who was
threatening critics to boxing matches? Uwe Bull. You just illustrated my point. The fact that
you're even confusing the two of them is what I'm saying. This guy gets really marginalized
for whatever reason, but he does good work. He did Resident Evil, at least the first one,
and maybe more. I think he did all of them. Yeah, he's solid. And he's married to Jovovich.
Yeah, yeah. All right, good for him. Folks, my number three pick,
and it's another sports pick. Maybe I do secretly love sports, but
I'm going to kind of cheat and pick all of them, but really I mean the first one, Rocky.
Rocky, right up through at least the first Creed, and maybe the other ones too. I just
are fall. These movies immediately put me in that mood. Creed, when it came out, I just loved
that it came out around Thanksgiving. The vibes were Thanksgiving, fall, coats, jackets, scarves,
hats. There's just something I love about that. The reason I always watch Rocky right around this
time of year is kind of an odd one, but my father would always go into essentially hibernation over
the winter months. I guess a lot of people do, but he would just stop whatever he was doing in terms
of bettering himself, working out, whatever, and just become this TV guy who just stared at the
television. Of course, we all have that in us. We could all be that person very easily.
I try to sort of keep myself active and working out throughout the winter months and not fall
into that trap of, ah, but it's winter. Maybe I'll just chill in bed all day or whatever
by throwing on Rocky. Rocky out there every morning, the breath visible in the air,
it's freezing out. He's out doing pushups on steps. He's jumping into fountains. He's running
upstairs. He's throwing his fists in the air and it's just very inspiring. Rocky always gets me
going. Rocky 2 is sort of the same movie, but in some ways I like it more because he wins. I love
the first two Rockies, probably the best, but all of these movies just feel like that time of year
to me. They feel like Philly East coast. I like that vibe a lot and I do use it as inspiration to
get up, get out. It's more fun to run in the cold. It's just nearly impossible to get yourself out
there to do it. Rocky, I watch as inspiration, but I love the whole franchise for this vibe,
the fall vibe. I think there is something, yeah, because you see, especially in that first one
when he's training, it's cold. You feel bad for him. You're like, this looks like it sucks.
He's running around and especially when he's got to go in the meat locker and punch the meat
and all that stuff, you're just like, God, man, this looks terrible right now. I agree. It does
feel of the season. Who amongst us hasn't beaten our meat with an old man screaming in our face
to do it harder and faster? That's true. That's true. I was just talking about the Rocky movies
the other night, or actually it might've been to you on the show. I don't remember, but I was
saying that I thought Creed, I hate Creed 2 and I think Creed 3 is fucking pointless, but I think
that Creed 1 is awesome and I think it is a perfect ending to the Rocky franchise. He comes full
circle. He becomes Mickey in the final movie and he honors the man that made him, Apollo Creed.
He honors both people that made him. The third would be Adrian, but it's really great seeing
the character go back and become the coach honoring Mickey and all Mickey taught him
and doing it with Creed's son, the son of the boxer that made him, that was his best friend,
and just seeing where the character finally ends up after all those years. It's a perfect ending
that the franchise should have just stopped there and unfortunately it didn't, but I think Creed
belongs as basically Rocky VII and then you're good. You're good to go after that.
All right, third pick for me, sort of another haunted, I wouldn't say it's a haunted house
but Fright Night. When I think of Halloween,
I often think immediately, and it might just be because of the years I grew up,
or it might just be because this era of horror is truly synonymous with it. I don't know which,
maybe it's both, but when I think of Halloween, my head usually goes immediately to 80s and late
70s horror and it also goes to supernatural. Look, I think the movie Halloween is a great movie
and I love it, but there's a reason why that's not one of my favorites ever and it's because
despite me saying if I had to put a list together of the great movies, it would be on it,
but is it one of my personal favorites? No, because Slasher to me is not as fun. I like
a supernatural aspect to a movie and that gets later with Michael Myers, it gets into that,
but initially no. When I think of this season, again, I think 80s horror, I think late 70s horror,
and I think supernatural. Fright Night ticks all of those boxes. Another thing I always think of
too is kids or young people getting into the dilemma and having to face the monster and this
movie also does that. It's a kid living next door to a guy who he thinks is a vampire and it just
goes from there. Roddy McDowell playing a horror host and being the guy that has to eventually help
him is just another beautiful layer of icing on this cake. Our main character being in love
with a young Amanda Burse, who I'm a big fan of, and exploring those aspects of teenage
romance and sexual angst and all that. Every part of this is great and then of course the
show stealer in this thing is Evil Ed. Stephen, I'm blanking on his name. I want to look it up now.
Stephen Hopkins? Not Hopkins. I don't know why I can't remember anything ever.
It's getting old, Joe. Yeah, Stephen Jeffreys. I mean, my God, man,
this kid is just, he just knocks it out of the fucking park in this thing.
Everybody's great. Chris Sarandon is a great villain. William Ragsdale is great as the innocent
kid in the middle of all of it. But it's just, it's awesome. It's awesome. And it's everything
you'd be terrified to experience as a kid, but also what you fantasize about. What if I got to
be the kid that spots the evil before anybody else, saves the day, I get the girl, all of that
stuff. It's just an awesome movie, man. And of course, the great Tom Holland at the helm.
This is really his, this is Tom Holland's white album. He was behind the script. He directed it.
This is really, to me, the definitive Tom Holland movie. And he's a legend in his own right. So
I can't imagine anybody that listens to this show has never seen Fright Night, but check it out.
And the remake is no slouch either. The remake is great. I like the remake. Joe gave me Fright
Night 2, which I have still not seen, I don't think. It's not great, but it's one that's cool
to own because it's hard to come by. And it's fun. It's goofy. Uncle Rico plays the guy from
Napoleon Dynamite. He plays a werewolf in it and there's a cool scene with him.
Yeah. But it's a fun, Fright Night is fun, man. Check it out if you haven't,
which I can't believe anybody hasn't, but. All right. Thank you very much, Joseph,
for your time, for your energy. I had Sleepy Hollow on my list. I'm going to push past it.
I've talked about it on this show and Joe did another version of it. So why not move on?
And so I will replace it with, what did I have here? Let me find my list.
Let me find that list. What do you got? Any given Sunday next? I'm off sports.
I'm off sports. Tennis movie with Zendaya. I like that one. No, here's, my pick is this, The Fugitive.
I love The Fugitive. It is set at St. Patrick's Day.
You know, it's an odd choice again. I'll grant you. Which is in March.
It's in March. The movie came out in August. I remember seeing it theatrically in August.
So there's really no reason that I'm saying The Fugitive, except that I recently watched the 4K.
I think it's a masterpiece and it is a movie I watch in the fall. It's a jacket movie.
Chicago at St. Patrick's Day. I think they shot it at the actual parade, but it's just, there's a
that makes me want to watch it this time of year. The Fugitive, people forget at the time,
you know, it was a huge, massive hit, but it was nominated for best picture.
And that was a shocker at the time because action movies were about as ghettoized or whatever you
want, whatever term you want to use as horror in terms of Academy recognition. But The Fugitive
really is, I think one of the great action movies ever made. Ford and Tommy Lee Jones are both
beyond perfect. Supporting cast is completely stacked. You'll forget that all these great
people are in it. You know, Julianne Moore plays like a nurse in one scene. Joe Pantoliano.
It's an amazing movie, The Fugitive. And for me, sometimes it's just seeing an actor's breath
the entire run time that put me in this mode. I don't know how to explain it. This is a fall
movie for me big time, even though nothing makes sense about that pick. Joe? I'm at a loss that
the picks, you keep getting crazier. Well, it's because I was so adamant about not picking horror
because I misunderstood the assignment. It's a movie that makes me think of fall. What can I say?
I also almost had the ice storm. And then I was like, well, Pat, that's ice. That's winter.
That's a Thanksgiving movie. I found that assignment very difficult because I couldn't pick
horror, I thought. No, no, no. The five movies that get you in the mood for Halloween. It's pretty,
it's right there. I basically did Autumnal. Yeah. And I stand by all my picks for Autumnal.
Right. With a movie that takes place in almost spring. Correct. But a March in Chicago is colder
than any autumn in LA. Sure. So winter. All right. Well, what are you going to do? It makes for
interesting conversation. That was a Sleepy Hollow replacement pick. Oh, because you were going to
you could have done Sleepy Hollow. But I felt bad, A, because it was horror and B,
I've talked about it on the show extensively. My fourth, yeah, fourth pick,
Tales from the Dark Side, the movie. Folks, you can't go wrong here. I mean, it is the third
unofficial installment to the Creepshow franchise. It is George Romero. It is Tom Savini. It is
Stephen King. Every story in this thing is great. They're all fun. They're all spooky. They're all
supernatural. And then you've got this wonderful wraparound story starring Debra Harry and one of
the younger Lawrence brothers, where she is a witch who lives in the suburbs who has kidnapped
this boy and she's going to cook him for dinner and her and her witch friends are all going to
eat him. So even in the wraparound story with Debra Harry walking into this beautiful suburban
home she lives in and preparing to cook the meal, which is going to be this boy, even that feels
sort of Thanksgivingy, givingy and weirdly autonimal. The stories in this are awesome
and they're perfect for this time of year. You've got the first story about a mummy
starring Steve Buscemi and Christian Slater and Julianne Moore. The second story starring Buster
Poindexter about the cat from hell, it's called, about an evil haunted cat and what's his name is
God, man. Boy, oh boy. Buscemi's in the first one. The second one is the old man, William Hickey.
Yes, thank you. And it's Matthew Lawrence is the Lawrence brother in this one. And then the third
story about starring James Reymar and Rae Dong Chung and Robert Klein about the man -
Nothing spookier than Robert Klein, baby.
About the man, the struggling artist who is confronted by a demon and he has to swear to
secrecy. It's called lover's vow and when he breaks that secret he finds out the woman that
he fell in love with on that very same night as the confrontation is actually the demon
It's an awesome, awesome, awesome movie. It does not disappoint and -
New to 4k by the way.
Yeah, I just got the 4k. I'm very excited.
Traded mine in, yeah.
But yeah, you know, check it out if you haven't seen it yet. I can't recommend it enough. It's
music for Creepshow 2. But he, you know, he's, what does it say? Yeah, no, he was, I'm sorry,
he was a composer for Creepshow 1. He's also the composer for Tales from the Darks of the Movie and
the director. You know, this is, as I said, this is the unofficial third installment of the franchise.
I don't know why, I guess it was a rights issue or whatever and by this time
Tales from the Darkside, the TV show, had had come and gone and had been popular enough that
it called for a movie adaptation and Tales from the Darkside, the TV show, was supposed to be
Creepshow, the TV show, but they had rights issues there so they had to retitle it and whatever. So
this movie is awesome. It puts you in the mood. Wrap around setting, sorry, wrap around story
is set in the fall and, you know, three great ghost stories to get you going for Halloween.
Love it. My last choice, I wanted to pick a back to school feature
because what makes you think of that fall time more than the bus heading back to school,
buying the school supplies up at Target, wherever you went, and I had some options. I think The
Breakfast Club is super autumnal. I think Rushmore feels that way. Election feels that way in spots
and they're all great movies. I considered Go, the teenage pulp fiction. I think one of the more
underrated movies ever made. It feels very autumnal to me. If you've never seen Go, it's,
I just recently learned my Blu -ray is out of print and worth over $100. I'm sure it's very
difficult to find, but it's an excellent movie and worth seeking out. I also almost picked Rules of
Attraction, another one I felt people had slept on unfairly written and directed by Roger Avery,
who used to be Quentin Tarantino's writing partner, so he's pretty good. I love Rural Attraction.
Yeah, he co -wrote pulp fiction. Rural Attraction is super dark. It is probably my favorite adaptation
of a Bret Easton Ellis novel. I like it even more than American Psycho. I think it's a great movie.
But I ultimately chose probably the most autumnal movie there is. It's not horror,
though there is a lot of Halloween sentiment feeling in it, and that is Donnie Darko.
Donnie Darko, first time I saw it was in New York on Halloween night. It was an all -night horror
movie marathon. Still one of the most memorable moments of my life. I had just moved to New York.
I was at Travis Bickle levels of loneliness. I had no friends and a psychotic roommate whose
dogs raped each other all day and night, leaving ass blood all across the kitchen floor. I was not
in a good spot. I had yet to become an NBC page. That would not happen for a few more months,
so I was just temping, and I went to this all -night horror marathon. They also showed
a super underrated movie that's not horror, really, called King of the Ants with George Wendt,
directed by the great Stuart Gordon. That is an intense and very, very good movie. More of a
thriller, but with some horrific shit in it. I'm not sure I remember what else they played. They
played Maniac, which is that super violent New York grindhouse movie with Joe Spinell, whatever.
But Donnie Darko was played at midnight. I had already seen it, but to see it at a theater with
a lot of first -time people because it was still kind of a video hit. This was clearly a very
carefully curated Halloween fest. It's what you want when you go to these festivals in LA and
rarely get. Joe and I famously went to the shittiest horror movie festival of all time,
and it cost $60. Still one of the most disappointing days of my life out here,
and not just because Joe was my date. What to say about Donnie Darko? I think
you'd be hard -pressed to find a better debut film that led to less, sadly.
Um, this guy just made a perfect movie on his first time out, and it's, I'd say it's perfect in its
imperfections. The weirdness about it, the things it doesn't tell you, the ways it leaves you out
of reach. It reminds me of like a teenage Mulholland Drive, and maybe it's because I saw them both
around the same time. But I think Donnie Darko is such a masterpiece. I think it shows somebody
with an insane way above his age mastery of telling a challenging and difficult story.
The time travel stuff in it, I think is even more sort of researched and fascinating than it is in,
say, Back to the Future, which is the best time travel movie. But I just, I love this more every
time I watch it, and a big part of that is the Halloween party, the hoodies, the 80s vibes,
the Stranger Things vibe. When they go to see The Evil Dead and The Last Temptation of Christ,
double feature at the Arrow Theater. Um, there's stuff I find in this movie every time I watch it.
I love the supporting cast. I think it's the best Jill and all has been. And I, I don't pray ever,
but I hope in my heart of hearts that Richard Kelly comes back out of the blue and shocks us
with something great. I hope it's not a Donnie Darko sequel 25 years too late. I know there have
been straight to video fake sequels that I never saw, but I just refuse to believe somebody could
come out with something this fresh, fun, funny, exciting, scary, suspenseful, original, and never
do anything of value again. I know people like Southland Tales, but they're wrong. I know some
people like The Box, and okay, that's fun. But I want Richard Kelly back. And to me, this movie,
whether they acknowledge it or not, I never read an interview with the creators,
but to me, the Duffer Brothers, what they do on Stranger Things, of course, it owes a great debt
to the 80s and to The Carpenter and the Spielberg films of the 80s, but I think a massive, massive
influence on Stranger Things has got to be Donnie Darko, at least in terms of the vibe,
the fall vibes, which is what we're talking about. I love it. That's it. Joe?
My final pick, this is a movie I get excited about in January when I'm thinking about the
Halloween, and I say, I'm not going to watch that until next year or again,
but it's The Fog. We've reviewed it on the show. I don't think there could be a better movie,
horror movie, to put you in the spirit of Halloween that has nothing to do with Halloween
than The Fog. You got a New England coastal town. You got a lighthouse. You got fog.
You got ghosts. You got Tom Atkins. You got Jamie Lee Curtis. You got Adrienne Barbeau. You got
John Carpenter. I mean, we're off to the races here. You got John Housman opening this thing
by telling a ghost story around a campfire with a bunch of Cub Scouts. Every element of this movie
is perfectly suited for the season. John Carpenter has said he originally made this
as a kids movie. He wanted it to be a scary ghost story movie for kids. I believe the studio
interfered and said, no, you got to come on. We need blood and whatever. You got to go heavier
than that. So it is, I believe it's R rated. It is. I think they did a bunch of reshoots to make
it R rated. Yeah, that's what it was. You got a whole brick in this. Every actor in this
is perfect to the genre. They're actors that synonymously make you think about the season
because of the bodies of work they have and what they've done. The director, of course, obviously.
This is one of the ones written by Carpenter and Deborah Hill together.
Again, ghost story. It's great. You're dealing with shipwrecked ghosts,
which feels piratey or whatever. All of this feels very fall, very Halloween. Janet Leigh is in it.
This is it. To me, this is the epitome of the movie you pull off the shelf on October 1st and
go, it's time to get ready for Halloween. I want to get excited here. I think it's just a perfect,
perfect pick for the season. Here's something I never realized. I mean, or maybe I did and just
didn't ... I don't know. Maybe I realized it and just never thought about it, but
the lead character in this, Tom Atkins' character is named Nick Castle.
I feel like I never realized that, but Nick Castle is the actor that plays Michael Myers
in the first Halloween movie. That's an interesting little nod. That's pretty cool
if you're Nick Castle and John Carpenter's like, yeah, we called the name character,
we named him after you. That's pretty neat. Nowadays, Nick Castle would sue John Carpenter.
The Fog, not the 1980s. I mean, I'm sorry, the 1980 Fog, not the ... The remake is a fucking
dog show, but this original is truly tremendous and worth your time. Again, this is one I can't
imagine any of our listeners haven't seen already, but if you need something to find on the shelf
or to stream that's going to put you perfectly in the mood and you're stumped one night, revisit The
Fog. That I will as I have the 4K and can't wait to. Folks, that is our time. I hope we gave you
some good picks. Love to hear your picks in the Patreon comments, which we enjoy reading. What
makes you think of fall? Maybe it's The Fall, the new Tarsim re -release. You ever see that movie The
Fall? No, I don't think I've ever heard of it. Well, they got a new 4K release of it, but it was,
I always mixed it up with The Cell. I think it's the same director. The Fall,
I definitely saw in theaters. I know it lost a ton of money. I think David Fincher helped pay for
it because the guy went broke, but it's worth checking out. It's been re -released. It's like
very visually spectacular movie. If you want another quote Fall movie. Folks, we'll be back.
I'm not sure what we're going to do. I think if Joe sees The Substance, we'll check that off. If
not, we'll probably wait until that's on Shutter or Mubi or wherever that's going to wind up.
We love you. We are at See You in Hellpod on Instagram. We thank you for supporting the
Patreon. I am at ThePatrickWalsh on Instagram. Joe? Joe Derosa Comedy on Instagram.
I think it's Joe Derosa Comedian on TikTok. I can't remember. See you in Somerville on December
7th and touring all next year. Go to joderosa .com for tour dates, tickets, all that stuff.
Happy Halloween and we'll be back with one more closer to actual Halloween,
but we will see you next time, folks. And we will see you in hell.