Summer is here, and Bed MGM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer.
Or check out our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz.
Only available at Bed MGM Casino.
Spend on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 fortunes, Mystery of the Land,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand!
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action!
Bet MGM in Game Sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 Plus to Wager, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and West Virginia
only, games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as non -mustrable site credit slash bonus bets unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
Gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gambleer.
Firestone Complete Auto Care's epic savings advantage is the sign you need to stop putting off your car's maintenance.
And you can save up to $100 on tires and services while you're at it.
Don't wait, call Firestone Complete Auto Care for an appointment.
Hey folks, welcome to Will see you and how this is actually the second take of our fine
and trusty intro that we do here.
The first time I tried to sing it, I sang the intro and Pat made me rerecord this whole
You should be thanking me. It was depressing. The singing was obviously bad, but the content was
dark, not funny. Joe sounded mentally ill, I would say. And I was like, nobody listening to
this would keep listening. It seemed appropriate to me. I let Joe do his little thing for 30 seconds
at the beginning. And it's never good. But tonight I had to really step in. You have to say what
you do need to say in the intro. Yeah, I'm about to. All right, please do. I just wanted to see if you want
to cut me down anymore. No, I'm good for now. Before I do my job, folks, the podcast, as you know,
it's part of the Fangoria podcast network. You want some info on this show or the other shows,
you go to the website, it's fangoria .com, and you can find all the past episodes and all that jazz.
there, speaking of jazz, this is how I sang it. I went, I went, well, welcome to the podcast.
We'll see you at hell. Why are you doing it again? I just want them to see what they missed.
Now you see what you missed folks. Do you feel inside? Did you miss them? Pat, how are you? You good?
I'm good. This week we're going to be talking about...
about. Well, don't, don't, don't blow the lid off it yet. Let's do our recap first.
I do think that generally in a podcast, you, you wouldn't say what you're going to be
talking about. I don't think that's crazy. Okay. That's right. We're going to be talking
about one of our first true comedies. You can't even really count it as a horror comedy, even
though it's Halloween themed. Um, but it's called Tyler Perry's boo exclamation point of
Medea Halloween, I think, and those three phrases might be in a different order.
It might be Boo, Tyler Perry, Medea Halloween.
It might be Tyler Perry's Halloween, Colin, Boo, exclamation point, Medea style, I don't
know.
I think in either order, the Boo is used with a comma, as to say, Boo, it's Medea, Medea's
Halloween, Boo, like you're talking to somebody you love.
And we will look at just the disgust on your face. You're in a surly mood tonight. Well, what's the matter tonight? Nothing nothing?
I do you know I had to get off an eight hour day of work and then it's like let's go right into being funny
Being an uncle funny. Your job is to be funny. That's what you do all day
Yeah, so then when I come home, it's like the gynecologist who doesn't want to eat pussy when he gets home, you know
I don't want to keep sprinkling gold when I'm done sprinkling my daily dose of gold at work
Well, you know I work today. I do it in eight hour it, but I five -hour it. What'd you do? I added it my special today
With the editor, I mean not just me, but you know
But you know, that was tedious looking at gorgeous shot after gorgeous shot of myself. It's you know, it's not easy
I know. I've seen the special. Yeah, so we will get to Tyler Perry's booth. There's much to say. There's so much to say. Oh yeah.
But as far as the weekly recap of what I've seen or the biweekly recap, I don't have as much as normal, but I saw the accountant, the Ben Affleck vehicle.
It looks great. It was pretty fun. It's basically a superhero movie without, you know,
without the, anyone being a superhero. But it's a shoot.
Wait, so the accountant is the superhero? In the way that unbreakable,
was kind of a superhero movie without necessarily being one, or a grounded version of one.
This is even less of a superhero movie, but it definitely followed those
those same structural patterns of a guy, you know, you get his origin story, et cetera.
How I don't understand how it seems like people are outraged about every movie and every
TV show and every song that comes out, I don't know how more people aren't upset about
this movie's portrayal of people with Asperger's because it is completely insane.
They basically have an app like a mental institution with some other kids who have Asperger's,
One of whom is going off the rails
like she's in some sort of asylum,
like shutter island style.
Right.
There are kids with autism.
And then Affleck's autism basically gives him
super power needed to be a hitman.
And he's like an amazing shot because his dad trained him
and his brother to like be violent killing machines
to overcome the weakness that was their autism.
It's really nuts, like it's a ludicrous movie.
An athlete was kid at a time,
they weren't diagnosing autism back then.
Exactly.
You should bring that mic up just a little higher.
It's ludicrous, it gets more ludicrous as it goes.
Look at that volume jump.
These people at home now are gonna have to turn their thing down.
So what do you want me to do?
No, that's where it should have been the whole time.
All right, here it is.
Where people had to turn it up the whole way and now they got to turn it to it's
My my arm is weak from jacking off your dad
Anyway, the account I really can't stress enough how crazy this movie was although it seemed very mild in comparison to the film
We'll be talking about later in the show
But the account was it was a lot of fun. I think there was a lot of really cool
born style action and it had a very dry sense of humor that I like. It's got
Lithgow, JK Simmons, Anna Kendrick and a nice little cast in there. You know,
it's a BB plus. She carries out on this Anna Kendrick for me still. I'm not
sold. I think guys are always torn just because she's not traditionally hot.
She's extremely likable. If she... I like her a lot. I think that if she was a
Little hotter than guys would all love her. I don't think no that's that's that's not what I'm saying
I think it's it. I think that's it. That's not what I'm saying at all. I think she's an attractive woman
It's got that if she was hotter it would be more annoying to me. Okay. I you know, what do you think I want another?
Fucking Kardashian running around out here. I'm saying I just don't see what the what the entry is with this girl
It is yeah, she's not your traditional
Star I assume you didn't see the pitch perfect films. No, I missed those Pat
Yeah, that's kind of a, you know, that's kind of where she should be at.
She's very kind of cute and charming and funny in those.
In this, you know, she was a little out of her element, but I liked her in this too.
I think she's likeable.
I think that them hinting at a romance between her and Affleck was kind of nuts throughout
because he's 25 years her senior.
She reminds me of Mike, like a cousin or something.
She looks like you're cousin that made it into the movies.
That's it. It's about her looks folks. I'm not it's not about her looks. It's about just her energy like there's something about the whole
Package she reminds me if a cousin
Got famous and you couldn't see her different than that. You just go. That's my cousin girl next door
Well, I got a girl next door quality about her. I guess so. Yeah, I don't know. I think that whole that stupid fucking
Billy and Mike need wedding dates or whatever fucking that turn of a movie with, I mean
it was just four fucking strikes in that and those leads.
Did you see it?
No, I didn't see it, Pat.
Joe, what are we talking about them?
I'm just saying, you know, I've spoken on the show about it.
I thought that was a very solid comedy.
Of course you did.
So you're also about to defend the movie on today's show.
So well, no, I'm going to defend aspects of it.
I don't think everything has to be, you know, an hour of saying something is garbage.
I look for good and thing.
Sure.
This is the man that has chastised me for three years because I said I enjoyed tower
heist.
I said I enjoyed it.
I thought it was kind of funny.
That's all I said.
Three year crucifixion over that statement.
You're going to defend Zach and Mary need wedding dates.
Zach and Mary make a porno was the very bad Seth Rogen movie.
I thought that movie was fun. Smith movie
Elizabeth Banks there's your star. Yeah, she cuz she's hotter. Oh stop it. I'm talking about you talk like trash sometimes. I am talking about
Mike and Dave need wedding dates, which has really good jokes on it. Not a fan of Efron
Sure, not a fan of Kendrick as we've established
Right not a fan of old fucking sleepy eyes
What's her name? The one that ran up on stage during my friend's girlfriend?
So I'm not gonna answer that question. It's your friend's girlfriend. Yeah. Oh, now we get to why you like the movie. Oh
No, not at all. Oh, I know how you would wash in here. Neither of them listen listen to this. What's your name?
Aubrey Plaza Aubrey Plaza and then sleepy eyes folks and I'm divine. Who is funny?
At one point, I thought he was kind of funny. He's funny. He's doing Jack black. He's doing that's my point
He's doing Jack Black.
That's what I said when we talked about this movie,
he should use Jack Black some of his money,
but I think he's funny.
You know, I texted that to a friend of ours the other day
and didn't realize I was just stealing your opinion.
I didn't even realize it.
Well, I mean, it's a pretty funny movie, I think.
Well, in any case, I already had it in for the other three
and then that sealed the,
so I'm hoping I can't.
The movie you haven't seen was one push over the edge
for you on Anna Kendrick.
He said, you know what, I didn't see this,
But now I really don't like it looked like a piece of man. You factored trash
Everything that comes out as manufacturing trash either roll with it or you don't I don't my
Dave has if you watch it on a plane you'd really enjoy my condes I can almost guarantee it. I don't roll with it, man
I don't roll with it, man
I mean I would certainly never say something was terrible
But I hadn't seen or that it broke me on a human being that I hadn't seen
But uh, I also saw
our hacksaw ridge that you return to directing from Mr. Mel Gibson a polarizing
figure we've discussed on this show Mel Gibson what very wisely laid low he
stayed behind the camera he returned to his strength which is extremely
exciting and well shot battle action I think Apocalypse is one of the most
underrated action movies of the past ten twenty years sure he probably at this
point. You know, Brave Heart, of course, I love I haven't seen it in ages, but I loved it.
This is like really good action. Vince Vaughn is great in it, playing the role that Mel
probably wanted to play. And they were like, Mel, we're going to put this up for us, Chris. How about
you stay behind the camera? I hear the movie is a masterpiece of Valor, if you will. Yeah, I mean,
a masterpiece is a little strong. It's got a real corny Ra Ra America streak as a lot of
War movies do. Andrew Garfield is like, there's a guy I've never been huge on. He really
won me over in this. Just playing like a guy who wants to go into battle but refuses
to use weapons as the gist of the movie. Soft chin on that kid. A real soft chin. He's
never done much for me. I liked him in this. And then there's weird questions like, okay,
I'm going to go into battle without weapons. But then there's like several scenes of him
Kicking a grenade back into battle. I'm like well, then you are using weapons and through he's minimally, you know, give a guy a break
Pat but there's some really exciting stuff and it's you know, they're going after the private Ryan
It's extremely gory a lot of battle action. I liked it. All right
But not no, that's not a superhero film like the accountant
No, although it could be read that way too. I mean a guy who wants to not use any weapons and I'm sure there's some superhero who already has them
power. And was there any Asperger's in the the Hacksaw Ridge film? It could
be argued that Andrography was on the spectrum. Okay. Okay. Now it was it was a
fine film. I'll be curious to see if it's raved about and pushed for Oscars
or if they're like begrudgingly admitting that Mel Gibson has made like a really
exciting movie. I'm curious to see what happens with it. Okay. Very good. I didn't
think it was a masterpiece by any means. I'd give it a B -plus perhaps. But I liked it.
Okay, and other than that, I watched the 13th, the Netflix documentary on race relations,
which I think has also been a bit overhyped, it's by the lady that made Selma, which I
also felt was a bit overhyped because it's, you know, I guess maybe I'm just well informed,
but nothing in it was surprising to me, perhaps, it's about how our prison systems are fucked
up.
And this is often how you'll talk about a film that was directed by a woman
You'll make these kinds of statements. Yeah sure sure
Look, it's a good thing you didn't offend Aubrey Plaza
But took a shot at the Martin Luther King by O 'Payton. I've met Aubrey Plaza
And I get very uncomfortable whenever I talk to her because she's not she doesn't there's not one to make you feel at ease
It's the sleepy eyes, you know, but she, you know, she's fine.
I raved about her movie that's coming out soon, Ingrid Goes West.
I made her years ago doing comedy.
She was very nice.
I certainly didn't fucking rave about Dirty Grandpa, starring Aubrey Plaza, and your boy Jack
Efron once again.
Yeah, but between those two films, between the drags of Dirty Grandpa and what I think is a truly
excellent movie, Ingrid Goes West lies Mike and Dave, which there used to be these kind of
average sex comedies, raunchy comedies, they'd come out one a week. Now we get one
every season maybe. There aren't comedies made anymore. So when one comes out, I
go to it kind of like, all right, I'd like to laugh. What do you mean there aren't
comedies? There's comedies constantly. They don't come out. When did they come to
the theater? We just last week we talked about keeping up with the Joneses. We talked
about, I mean that movie almost didn't get released. But my point is they are
being made they're just not very good. Yeah, but outside of a Kevin Hart and then that's obviously a
very weird out like where did that come from because I don't even know that move was being made.
That the concert movie where he's in front of like 60. Oh, no, no, no. I get the concert movie. I'm
talking about keeping up with the California Accuses with Joe and Arthur, right? No, no, no. I'm
saying that's a that's a fluke. Like I don't know where that movie came from or how it even got made.
That other movie came out to what was it called masterminds. Yeah, masterminds was bad kind of came and went and I discussed that here
I'm starting to wonder if you listen to anything I say on the show I saw masterminds
I know you did and I remember you discussing in here and saying it was bad. It was bad
All right, so there are there are many more comedies than I'm saying. Yeah, they make comedies
I guess I'm saying they they don't make any money and they're they're just like
Almost too bad to even be worth discussing well
which, you know, I'm not gonna keep stumping for Mike and Dave.
It's not that good, but it was funny.
Good.
All right.
I want to, can I go over what I saw,
or did you see even more than this stuff?
I think that's it.
The 13th is a really good documentary.
It just wasn't breaking any new ground for me.
Uh, I have one classic and one new thing.
I finally saw a fistful of dollars.
I've never seen any of the spaghetti westerns
by Clint Eastwood by Sergio Leone.
I saw it finally.
I enjoyed it. I look forward to watching the other two in that trilogy. I mean the best by far is good the bad and the ugly
That's the third one. Yeah. All right. Well, I look forward to seeing it by far. That's the best. Yeah, but you know, it was fun
and
The thing I'm very excited about and I this because this is a tone or an opinion change for me on the pod I
Returned to the exorcist TV series now. I believe we initially discussed it when it first came out briefly you had not
seen it and I still have not seen it. Well I talked to you at one point after I
saw the first episode and I was a bit lukewarm. I said I didn't really know
if I was feeling it or not. Episode five just premiered and it's got a twist at
the end that took it into a whole new whole new stratosphere of a TV show. I can
spoil it Pat unless you don't want to hear it. Go for it. Well maybe our listeners
I don't know, that's why you say spoiler alert and then you plug your ears.
All right, it's all over the internet too.
All right.
All right, so this is, I'm gonna spoil what happens.
But, you know, you're kind of watching the first four episodes of the show
and you're like, wow, this is interesting and there's a possess girl
and there's priests and demons and there's gonna be an exorcism involved.
But you kind of start getting the idea like, well, it's clearly just called the exorcist
So people would watch it. Okay, because it was called the possessed girl. People would just be like who cares, right?
Gina Davis plays the mom she is very very pro exorcism through the entire movie or through the entire first four episodes. She is desperately
Desperately, you know, pleading with doctors, police, everybody this has to be done. Everybody thinks she's crazy
typical stuff with this kind of story. In the last episode I saw, which was five,
here comes the spoiler, the possessed girl whispers something to her father. The father immediately
becomes infuriated with his wife, Gina Davis, and keeps throughout the episode saying,
you got something you need to tell me, and you don't know what it is.
He finds some weird things around the house about her past or that are hinting at her past but it's all very vague.
Finally, she goes to see the priest at the end of the episode.
Father, I have to confess something.
She starts talking about her past.
She's like my parents split up when I was young.
My mother carted me around because of her job from city to city.
Something happened to me when I lived in DC as a young girl.
She reveals she's Reagan McNeil from the exorcist. She's the girl from the exorcist grown up
And she has changed her name because of all the publicity she got after the incident happened
And how her mom tried to make a basically make a buck off of her with a book and stuff like that. She ran away changed her name
Took up a new identity
See I bet they came up with that after the pilot stage because that would seem to be your classic end of the pilot reveal
I don't know so maybe they were like what if she's this but you you think that should be in the pilot
But maybe I'm crazy. No, it was worth them sitting on it
All right, because it was a pretty mind -blowing twist and then also the demon keeps saying to the girl
He your daughter. Yeah, he keeps saying bring her to me and you don't know what the fuck he's talking about, right?
So here's this demon who's hell bent on the fact that
The mom got away and who is Alan Ruck Cameron fry the first bill. Okay. He's the dad
Is it good in it? I love that. He talks in the voice he does in Ferris Bueller the whole
time when he does the prank crawl.
He's one. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. No. Yeah. He's great in it. He plays a guy that had a scaffolding
accident. What in my French? But you're an asshole. It's very cowardly lying. Yeah. Almost
right. Yeah. Uh, he's the dad. He had a scaffolding accident on the job. Uh, so his brain is damaged
Did he has good days in bad gets almost like he's got a like a dementia or something like that. Okay
Well, he himself that they found him like knocking on doors in his neighborhood. He had some weird brain disorder
Almost like wandering the streets looking all fucked up. Is it in real life not five ten years ago?
Okay, no. I mean apparently they felt comfortable casting on the extras as TV show Jesus. That's terrible. Yeah guys a hell of an actor
Well now he's back. He's fine. Well, that's good. I'm glad he's back and I'm glad he's fine
And it's a show worth checking out.
You know, it's going to, look, it's a TV exorcism show.
It's, there's going to be some cliche stuff in it.
I don't think any of it's necessarily going to scare you,
but it's an enjoyable story.
And now that it's this direct sequel to the original movie,
that's pretty interesting now.
Things just got much more interesting.
Well, let's get to the matter at hand, Joe.
Well, that's the second thing.
That's the third thing I saw.
Yes.
Which you also saw.
And we need to get a few things out of the way.
Was this for you your first Tyler Perry movie?
No, no, what else have you seen because I haven't seen any of them. I saw diary of a mad black woman
Now what how did you wind up watching diary of a mad black because I see everything and you really don't
Well because it when it came out it had all this hype around it
And I was like what what is this movie? Who is this guy? Yeah, let me check this out and
I watched it and I remember not thinking it was very good
I think Medea is in that somewhere.
Yeah, well, really, I have never seen a Medea movie until now.
What blows my mind is that sometimes he does serious dramas,
like including plot points such as babies being raped.
Right. And Medea is in the movie.
Yeah. Like that is mind blowing to me.
Yeah, it's, it's Medea, you know,
she's ranging anywhere from a coen or from a fairly
brother's character yeah to a Spike Lee character yeah it's a wide range
there he's shift shuffle around it I so I I but I saw some other ones too I
so it goes to jail okay I've heard Christmas is kind of the one to beat that's
the one I do want to see next I saw and the fact that I'm saying next obviously
tells you folks at least I found something worthwhile about boo I watched many
episodes of House of Pain. Okay and meet the Browns. Well, yeah, I mean, I saw a clip of that
Tyler Perry sitcom, the one he makes like a hundred episodes a year of. They, the people were
bumping into the cardboard sets and the set would be wobbling throughout the scene. Now, these
things were like maybe, you know, first take at best. I will say this outright at the top of this
portion of the discussion. I do not, I'm not a fan of Tyler Perry, I think that he's
a good actor. Did you like him in Gone Girl? That's, that's the only topic I'm ever seen.
Yeah, I think when I see him play straight roles like that, not straight, not meaning straight
man, just straight, dry drama stuff, whatever. I like to be in Gone Girl while also thinking
somebody could have brought a lot more to it. I thought, I like, look, I liked him a lot
and uh... the t -in -a -t -in -a -t -in -a -t -in -a -t -in -a -t -in -a -t -in -a -t -in -a -t -in -a -t -in -a -t -in -a -t -in -a -t -in -a -t -in -a -t -in -a -t -in -a -t -in -a -t -in -a -t -in -a -t -in -a -t -in -a -t -in -a -t -in -a -t -in -a -t -in -a -t -in -a -t -in -a -t -in -a -t -in -a -t -in -a -t -in -a -t -in -a -t -in -a -t -in -a -t -in -a -t -in -a -t -in
are like by definition bad I mean there everything I've ever seen about them
and now this movie of course and I want to make that real clear before we get
into this Tyler Perry's boo on the Deah Halloween is without question of bad
movie look but I found it bad in a fascinating sort of Edward way and I found
myself laughing a lot at it but also with it at some of the jokes and I was
very surprised by that. Now because I think that Medea is funny, which I was blown away
by. I'm like, you know what? Medea is funny. But even more funny was bam. Medea's sidekick,
the old woman, I'd like to get to that who wears a mask and then glasses over the mask,
which I laughed every time I saw that before we do, before we get to that. Hold on. We should
to give the synopsis of the film, which we are trying to be better and in the habit
of doing. And the synopsis of this film is, I have no fucking idea. That's where I think
this discussion needs to start. I walked out of the film 45 minutes in. I hung in there
as long as I could. Yeah, I don't appreciate that, by the way.
Well, yeah, you seem to know it and we had an assignment. You're sitting here now saying, you know, this is the first one
You've walked out on a juke you walked out another one, too. No, this is the first one. I won't do it. It was bad
It was bad. I couldn't I did that 45 minutes in we had gotten through three scenes. I saw three scenes in 45 minutes
These scenes were just going on and on I saw it with our mutual friends Scotty
I turned to him after through the second scene.
I go this scene, shit definitely just went over
the 10 minute mark and he was like, holy shit.
You're absolutely right.
That this is the longest scene I've ever seen
in a motion picture.
Yeah.
And they're improvving.
Why does it smell terrible in your house?
It doesn't smell terrible in here.
There's an egg smell that comes and goes.
It's only tonight.
I'm not saying you're at your place stinks, what's that? I'm saying right now it stinks
Pat nothing in this place has changed except you
So maybe the smell is coming from you. Oh, it is maybe you're the smell
I'm not the smell and Joe's home doesn't normally smell folks, which I think is why we have a beautiful
Polatial apartment here. Yeah, there's an egg smell. There's not an egg smell. All right. I don't smell anything all right folks
I could not believe how long, especially as Joe is correct, the like the second and
third scenes back to back are about 15 minutes long.
And these are the clumps style scenes, but now when the nutty professor table scene ends,
you're like gasping for breath because it's so fucking funny.
There's 8 ,000 jokes packed into like that five minute scene and you desperately want it
to be longer.
These scenes are improv so loosely that I guess Tyler Perry must go in with like a
curbure enthusiasm style outline, but the scene will start they recap what took place
in the previous scene like you're watching a multi -cam sitcom right then the
improv starts up and it's going going then Tyler Perry I guess in the editing is
like wait it's been ten minutes people probably don't remember what's
happening in the movie then they'll restate with no jokes what's going on in the
movie, even though of course you didn't forget it, then more improv and they keep getting
so far away from the plot that then they'll insert the characters just telling you what's
happening again and again and again to allow these extended rifts that are often disturbing.
And I guarantee you on a Tyler Perry set there is a term they invented for that.
Oh sure.
Tyler, we need a plotty in here, you know, something like that.
Well, and there is no plot, so by the time I'm certainly not going to worry about spoilers
for this fucking movie, but I thought in the trailer I was going to go see Ernest
Scared Stupid where you see a beloved comedy character, you're Ernest, fighting off with
ghouls and goblins, and when I was a kid at least I thought Ernest Scared Stupid was scary
and funny. Tyler Perry's Boo and I think this is probably after the 45 minute mark. There's like a
demonic clown that shows up. You were out by that one. I saw that the clown comes and it's her
neighbor or something dressed up and yeah I saw that part. It's these fried guys that are pissed at
Medea and they're dressing at clowns to like fuck with her and then she decides to fuck with them and
at the beginning, they steal the whole summer school bit of a character going, well, you
know, I actually dabble in horror makeup to like make me and you're like, well, clearly
that's coming back later.
Yeah.
It's all from summer school.
The plot of the movie basically is her granddaughter.
I think it's her granddaughter, but it's confusing because the main girl, she's way too hot.
Well, we'll get to that in a second.
And the main girl apparently puts her in these cleavage clothes.
Well, hold on. She's supposed to be 17. I was conflicted the entire time. Let's set this up. Hold on a second.
The main girl, this girl that Pat is referring to,
vaguely creepily. She's unbelievable. She is the main character. Her dad is Tyler Perry as a man, a character.
Yeah. Tyler Perry was convincing in every role except as Tyler Perry, the normal man. I didn't buy him in that role at all.
But then Tyler Perry also placed his dad and Medea,
the dad's dad and Medea.
So he's the great dad who coldly drops the N word
in one scene like six times.
Which, who cares?
I was fascinated by it.
It's a black guy saying it, who cares?
But I'm not saying I cared or was bothered
by him saying the N word.
I'm saying in the context of this movie,
people in the theater were that I was in were offended.
And I was like, why are white people getting offended
at a black person using the N word in a comical way.
Well, I think I must have been PG -13.
Yeah, but that's, but, and I know you can say it,
you just don't hear it in movies a lot,
and I was shocked at this movie with this light improv,
and when that comes into the scene,
it was a little crazy to me,
although I wasn't offended by it at all.
It's not like you don't hear that term listening
to any rap album or.
Any rap? I'm yeah of course tons of black stand -up comedians you say it all the time of course
I just mean with Tyler Perry while dressed as an old man saying this word to
incite a reaction from Tyler Perry the man it was a crazy scene and this was in the
middle of a 15 -minute scene where you've already forgotten kind of what's going on in
the movie I thought that was I thought that was one of the only well -written
and segments I saw in the whole movie because I thought this is an interesting commentary
that the old man thinks it's okay to say this.
The younger man, both played by Tyler LePerry, is offended and they're arguing and the old
man is getting his go by saying it.
Now here's the thing.
But now they don't go into anything interesting with it where like the old man might say,
you know, I grew up having to hear that word thrown in my face.
Now if I want to use it, they don't tackle any of those issues.
This is the point I keep trying to get at.
You're really barreling tonight though, man.
You're round up about this movie.
Are you all right?
Are you all supposed to be a spirited discussion?
It's a spirited discussion.
Now, I want to get back to the fact that for seven minutes,
I've been trying to say this.
I don't know who Medea is because Tyler Perry
calls the old man he plays dad who is married to Medea,
but then he calls Medea Medea.
He doesn't call her mom.
Now take it back real quick. Tyler Perry's mom is Medea. I don't know because he calls her
Medea, but she's married to the character he plays to who he calls dad. See now I'm gonna
disagree with you there. I think that Tyler Perry's dad is married to the horrifically offensive
Asian character. Oh, oh, oh, because he kept talking about fucking her. If he's not married
Wasn't he talking about fucking Medea and like getting I used to get up in that ass like that and all that shit?
I don't know in the Medea verse where this all falls
I thought he was married to the Asian woman who by the way and I did not look it up, but if that woman is not Asian
Holy shit, right the the woman with the voice and now what do you mean holy shit if that if though if the actress playing that woman is not Asian
And that is one of the wildest things I've seen in a movie in in
Oh, you mean it's like it would be the most like one of the most racist. I make you runie and brag for the Tiffany's. Yeah. Yeah, well
There is a woman who's who's going beyond like Mrs. Swan on
Mad TV that this brings she's got like the the the coke bottle glasses and she's like, oh
This brings me to my next shit my next point. She works. Yeah, this brings me to my next point the movie and
And this is despite of what I just said a minute ago when I say I don't have a problem of black people who use the N word, yeah, the movie
Is
Arguably one of the most racist films I've ever seen in my life
Towards whites towards blacks. It was not it does not paint anybody in a nice light at all
I mean some of the jokes where it's like I see white people and they all scream which was stolen from scary movie the idea of white people
Yeah, it felt more scary movie. No, it's in scary. I was like, that's because it was in scary. Yeah. I
Don't I'd love to have seen a screenplay for this because even though the man writes plays and all this shit, this felt like a movie that had about
10 sentences on a on a legal pad the Tyler Perry wrote while taking a shit and they were like, let's just see what happens because
because from a storytelling standpoint, I was blown away.
It was a number one movie at the box office this weekend.
Beating like Jack Reacher, which probably had a budget
of $100 million.
I heard it was bad.
I heard the sequel is bad.
I like the original Jack Reacher.
But people are obviously responding to this, and you can say
it's because there aren't a lot of movies targeted towards
African -Americans, and that's true.
But I went in expecting to be like, oh man, why would anyone
like this much like like like a Larry the Cable Guide type situation where you're like oh god and
I found myself surprised at I guess at how surprised I was by it I was surprised at how it was
bad in ways that I was just not expecting and it had something that compelled me obviously to stay
till the end and not you but I was sort of hypnotized by it from start to finish I almost
walked out twice the second time I did walk out the first time was during that
trick or treat scene at the beginning I mean it was going a hot 10 minutes I
didn't know what the hell was happening and then I genuinely thought it was
really funny when she was calling that fat kid biggie I found that very funny I was
like okay okay they got me they were being so mean that kid I worried about that
kid in real life. But Medea, and to my mind, the funniest character in the movie, BAM Medea's
friend, who I thought should have been played by Cedric, the entertainer. You got Tyler Perry
there in address, put Cedric in address. That would have been truly hilarious, but I
would have been fantastic. Now, they also got Bella Thorne in there who is a pretty big star with the
young kids looking insanely hot as well. That's the daughter character. No, the daughter is Tyler
Perry's daughter Bella Thorne is the blonde chick who was like kind of that girl's a big star. She had eight
Not funny lines in this movie. Well now here's the thing. She was let's get back to the high school kids
I worry about I'm thinking about Tyler Perry directing some of this shit like that girl
Torking and these long lingering clothes of her ass. I guess maybe I'm just getting older and you know when you watch a party movie
Of course, they're all probably directed by some 50 -year -old dude
But there was some way the way he had his daughter dressed in this movie
Is that his daughter in real life?
No, no, absolutely not.
Well now, but that's my point to when I said earlier,
I don't think, you know, I don't think the guy makes good movies.
No, they're not consistent.
You got this dad who is the whole thing
as he's supposed to be overprotective
and worried about his daughter and everything.
And then she's walking around like this low cut blouse.
Her skirt was barely cut.
And it's like, dude, you let your daughter dress like that.
You let your daughter dress like that.
It's not in my business.
But if you're gonna write a character
of a dad who's over -protective and he doesn't see that he doesn't get that part you know so it was
it was it was a little distracting how sexualized the girls that were supposed to be 17 were very
distracting and you know I'm looking now I'm trying to figure out who was related to who and let
me say this folks this is as Pat is my witness this is the first podcast ever come into with notes
I was feverishly typing notes in the theater.
I have questions and I'm trying to figure out who was related to who in the movie.
But I'm wondering if it's not, things aren't connected to the rest of the Perry universe.
Because I'm watching this thing and with like two minutes to go in the movie, the daughter
is mad at Tyler Perry and he's like, you know your mom cheated on me.
And they dropped this huge bombshell about how his mom, his wife cheated on him.
So I'm like, well that wasn't in the movie, they didn't allude to it, where is this coming
from?
I hop on Wikipedia and find out that's a holdover from like meet the Browns or something
Like it's Tyler Perry was playing a character. He's played in other movies. It's not it's not a good
But some of his movies don't tie into the other ones. You don't know which ones do and which don't jokes aside
or humor level or
Whatever aside
It's not a good movie. It's just not well -constructed the the these messages like you're saying are suddenly shoehorned in and you're
I mean you're sitting there. I was reading reviews before I went to see it that we're saying like
You know the movie's not great, but but Perry's heart and his message come from a good play and it's like message
The fucking movie is called boo a media Halloween. Why is there a message?
This should just be jokes. This should just be a comedy. There should be no but they but in all of them
That's what happened. Media goes to jail has like
Deathly serious parts. I think that's the one where he is Rudy from the Cosby show is the prostitute
Yeah, you know, like it's it's it's weird. It's just I don't understand it that living room scene
Which was the scene right after right right before I walked out where they're all in the we already talked about it a little bit
Yeah, that scene was easily 20 minutes long. Yeah for sure. Easily easily for sure and as you said as you said and so you're sitting there
I'm sitting there. I'm going okay. We're approaching 45 minutes the plot hasn't started yet
Yeah, the whole thing is and by the way the plot is just house party. It's a ripoff of house party
The daughter wants to sneak out of the house. Yeah to go to a party her dad doesn't want a letter the party's down the street
How she gonna pull this off and
You're 20 minutes into the film. I mean 45 minutes in the film the daughter hasn't even attempted to sneak out yet
The the grandparents have just barely arrived
To to watch her all night. So it's pretty
By the way, this movie made House Party 3 look like a Scorsese film.
I did not see House Party 3.
I saw all the House Parties.
I love the first one, and they get pretty bad after that, 3 being worse than 2 except
for the Bernie Maxines, but Patrice Lovely has only acted in Tyler Perry movies.
She played the Asian lady, but I'm looking now and she's African -American.
him. So he had a black lady playing the Asian lady in like Asian face. This just gets
weirder. And she's, she's only acted in his films. Well, now wait. Now they are saying
maybe she's, no, she's black. Oh boy, this is, this is hitting it from all kinds of angles
right now. And the woman who plays the, the, the old lady, bam, who I thought stole the
show is only 52 years old.
That's impossible.
And she looks like, you know, kind of like an attractive,
you know, normal looking woman.
So they make her up to look like BAM.
She's also in some sort of elaborate disguises.
Not just an old woman.
Wait, the lady that sits on the lawn and steals the candy,
that lady?
Yeah, exactly.
I thought that scene was really funny.
She's 52.
That scene felt to me like something out of like a Friday
outtake that went on too long.
How dare you.
This movie is nowhere near Friday, but I liked those scenes.
They had a certain appeal to me because they're almost experimental.
You know what I'm saying?
Well, I mean, look, Pat, you know, I could shit in my hand as an experiment.
It doesn't, you know, experimental doesn't give it credit.
They weren't hitting the mark.
Yeah.
It was just people just talking with, like, no, it wasn't driving the plot, it wasn't funny.
There wasn't any depth to the dialogue and then he's saying every place where they could
have gone into an issue like your mother did this to me or my daughter is I'm overly
protective of her or these boys are a bad influence or whatever all of that was glazed
over and in place of it was ten minute stretches of Medea just talking yeah with no jokes
in it. It doesn't make any sense to me. When I did, I saw the movie with our dear friend
Vince Averill and when we walked out of the film, I texted Pat immediately and I said
I walked out, I couldn't do it. Pat reacted, I think his text was, I laughed plenty, bit
a surprise that I had walked out. I told Vince that Vince's exact words were, wash, watch
that whole movie. He's a monster. Those were his exact words. Well, he didn't have to
watch it for a podcast.
You're right because it's truly the integrity
of this discussion has suffered that I only saw half
of the movie.
It probably only went another 20 minutes.
Now, how about the head frat guy who,
as far as I could tell, was in his late 40s?
Yeah.
All those frat guys looked older than the situation.
And then, but then again, confusingly, I'm sitting there
thinking these guys all look so fucking old.
And then Tyler Perry tells them they all look 60
As Medea, and I'm like, so are you in on this joke because you cast them
Now what happens at the end tell me the end what what's the climax?
Does she ever get to the party or do the kids just try to terrorize Medea like what happens?
What happens is she gets back at the I mean at first the clowns are chasing her in a seam where she goes
She goes help me Jesus help me Jesus at while she's running and that old lady's running with her and they run
Again for 10 minutes with her saying help me Jesus over and over until almost like a family guy style bit
The last stop and then little by little they come back because you're like does he know?
This is funny that he's saying that saying help me Jesus 500 times
Does he know that that's funny or is he just killing time right don't know right obviously he's a smart man
but it was a different kind of comedy that is not Tyler Perry's comedy where it's
like he's trying our patience I don't find I don't I find frequently that
smart does not make funny well no of course you know Einstein would have made
terrible comedies yeah I can guarantee you that but I don't know what his
intention was I also can't quite I mean the Tiger comes in at one point the
rapper, lip sinks a song so badly. He's got the microphone completely covering his face
to show how bad he's lip -syncing. So that there's that performance like trying to
get the youth in. At the end, Medea gets back at the frack eyes and like tries to...
But does the girl ever get to the party? She gets to the party.
And then Medea goes in, let me guess, Robin Harris style, like at the end of House Party,
right?
Yeah, or like, you know, or Uncle Buck's style is another way to look at it. And the plots identical to house party
That's where I say that. Okay. And yet tries to, you know, scare them off by pretending that a girl is dead
They they slither throat
The girl who knows a lot about makeup
To get back at these fracas who you never really believe as villains anyway because they don't really care
Like it's not like they they're really mad at Medea. They're just kind of having a little fun
So it winds up being like an elaborate prank war like on shears
Between the rival bar. So then the way then the way
That Medea finally makes her point about being protective of her
pseudo -granddaughter because of the violence in the world particularly towards women is staging an elaborate
Death scene of a woman. Yeah. Yes. It's very confusing to me now. I can't even find confirmation Joe
So that that lady was supposed to be Asian.
No one is describing her as Asian.
Am I craze here?
Did you also assume she was an offensive Asian stereotype?
I thought so.
There are no one's listing her as Asian.
I think she's just supposed to be a black woman.
She's played by a black woman.
But she talks with an Asian accent, doesn't she?
A horrific Asian accent, folks.
Well maybe she's part Asian.
I don't know.
What the hell do I know?
I mean, obviously, if you're still listening here, folks, I really can't stress enough.
We can't stress enough how insane this movie was.
Well, I texted you, because we had to see it separately because I was away, and then when
I came back, you were tied up with family.
But when I got back and I was making a plan to go see it, I texted Pat and I said, did you
see the movie?
and you said, oh yeah, just a wild ride was your response.
That's, I stand by that review.
What was Scottie, what was his take on it in the end?
Scottie felt the same as I did.
He had seen a couple of the movies as well
and he was like, that was a great intro.
It was completely insane.
But we both kind of laughed.
You know, some making fun of it, some not.
Would you see another Tyler Perry movie?
yeah I want to see Christmas because it's a Christmas movie or yeah no well yeah and because I've
heard it's the funniest one but what I what I am leaving out of the finale here is they find
the girl with her with her throat slit the guys all freak out they arrest the frat brothers put
them on a bus along with Tyler Perry's daughter and her friends then a riot breaks out because there's
actual
Prisoners on the bus. So there's like this giant scene of like a
Prisoners on a bus beating the shit out of each other while all these kids watch
Tyler Perry's kids the frat brothers, and then they cut to Medea being like I got taught him a lesson
Like it was like a scared straight type deal
But none of it is motivated earlier in the plot none of it really makes sense or holds together
And we're the frat guys at any point like bad guy. I remember them being stupid. Oh, yeah
They're all really stupid, but then so now where they lateral the actual Tyler Perry character
Medea's like, oh good. So these are just fake
policemen you called in right? Thank God and Tyler Perry goes, no, these are friends of mine. These are actual policemen
Medea goes, they are and runs away because she's
because Talopari constantly refers to the three older characters about how they all have
warrants out for their arrest.
That's a running gag in the movie.
So at the end, woman Dia finds out that their police officer she runs away.
Like they're going to arrest her.
Now here's the thing, why doesn't no character ever say, I'm looking out for you because
I have a warrant and I don't want you to make the mistakes I made.
Why doesn't the character just ever say that because I don't think the Talopari character
made any mistakes. He just got cheated on by his wife, which is awkwardly selected.
But any of the other people looking after the child? No. That's my point. It's these
glaring opportunities to make an organic point, and they don't make any of it. And then
he waits till the last five minutes to go, you know, your mother cheated on me. Which,
what the hell does that have to do with the daughter going to a party? I don't even remember
or how they tied that in to be honest with you.
Maybe it's a trust argument, I guess.
You don't trust me and he says,
well, I've bad trust issues
because your mom cheated on me.
Maybe that would be it.
That would make sense.
They're gonna throw her out of the house
because by the way, in that scene that I know you stayed
and watched, that scene is basically 15 minutes
of the older people trying to convince Tyler Perry
to beat his daughter.
Yes.
Then Tyler Perry's dad also played by Tyler Perry.
He's like, well, it worked for you.
So I threw you off the roof of a house.
You had a pencil in your pocket and it took off one of your testicles.
Then they all laugh and make fun of Tyler Perry who wrote this movie for only having one
testicle.
Then in my Wikipedia, I found out that on Meet the Browns or one of these other things,
Tyler Perry has a whole subplot where a different character is missing a ball.
He just goes back to his same bag of threats.
In my opinion, it's writing 101 when it comes to comedy.
You don't sacrifice content or substance for the sake of a joke.
And the movie really suffers from a slew of jokes that undercut every character executing them.
Which is why it doesn't really work.
It's a shame. I went in wanting it to be funny.
admittedly got few drinks in half a weed gummy or so in. I was you know I was
loose I was ready to have some fun yeah and it was see I can't believe you
know drunk and high you didn't have any fun with this movie I don't I almost
can't believe I left so you must have really had it. Listen here's the thing it's
not it's not I don't have a my irony barometer is one of my true I don't have a
high threshold for irony so it's like yeah it's not enough for me to sit there
and go well I laughed twice in 45 minutes and this is weird so I'm just gonna
stick it out it's like I don't I'm not enjoying this it's like not a good
movie it's it's it's I'm a little confused as to why it's constructed in the way it
is and I'm just bored now yeah and I felt that 45 minutes and I had gotten the
gist of you got the gist, you got the gist, you got the gist, you got the gist of you got the gist of you got the gist of you got the gist of you got the gist of you got the gist of you got the gist of you got the gist of you got the gist of you got the gist of you got the gist of you got the gist of you got the gist of you got the gist of you got the gist of you got the gist of you got the gist of you got the gist of you got the gist of you got the gist of you got the gist of you got the gist of you got the gist of you got the gist of you got the gist of you got the gist of you got the gist of you got the gist of you got the gist of you got the gist of you got the gist of you got the gist of you got the gist of you got the g
read a really funny review. We each read a really funny review of a movie from
Rotten Tomatoes, from one of Rotten Tomatoes Top Critics. I chose to read a review
of this film. This comes from Owen Gleberman at Variety. I'll used to
add it as I'm a liquid. It's another of Perry's raucous and slovenly
comedies, which I thought the word slovenly was very funny there, comedies of
responsibility, which means that its heart is in a very old and right place. If
only the message that was this solid, equaled solid laughs. Now I read this one
for two reasons. Number one, I just thought the word slovenly was funny, as I
already said. Number two, if only a message that was this solid, what fucking
message is this guy talking about? You know, the only message I could piece
together is at best, at best, half -cocked, and at worst, sexist. I don't see what message
this guy's talking about. There was no message. I mean, what I was just kind of recalling
is that the whole cheating on the wife thing that comes in, which feels like the end
of full house, like the violin's kick in and everything, is they're basically calling
out Tyler Perry for being too much of a pushover because I guess he didn't beat the shit out
of his wife who cheated on him. But they're all trying to egg him on and you could sort of
take a theme away that parents need to be more abusive with their children. That may have been the
theme of the movie. Oh, in any case, uh, Patty, you got anything to plug? Oh, wait, you got to read
your review. I'm sorry. What I'm getting here is on Roger Ebert dot com, uh, which is now obviously
not run by Roger Ebert, but I just found this interesting that the idea started as a joke
in Chris Rock's movie Top 5, which is a movie I liked a lot, where he talks about the
later Tyler Perry movie having Medea fighting ghosts.
Right.
It was a joke in Top 5.
Tyler Perry says, despite the mockery, he loved the concept and shot this movie in six
days.
That's true, shot a feature film in six days, one of them, and this is why the guy has
a giant compound in Atlanta because he makes movies real fucking cheap, real fucking
quick, and turns a huge fucking profit.
Because I guarantee that Gowel Phenak is John Hamm vehicle, terrible, I bet it costs $60
million dollars to make and this weekend it made five million I guarantee boo cost five million and
this weekend it made 30 million right that to me is very smart and I don't think that the people
going to Tyler Tyler Perry's boo want anymore out of it and I think that's why he doesn't necessarily
push himself and I have to admit maybe because of just like the weird rhythms it came up with by being
a movie that is trying so little that it held my interest in a way that maybe like a
David Lynch movie would you know where you're just kind of watching it like what am I watching now
David Lynch makes fucking amazing masterpieces sometimes but sometimes but Lynch also has one side
walk out of two sure I just don't want to deal with the horse shit anytime something it's too self -indulgent
it's like fuck off man this isn't what I'm here for yeah and you know what what would really blow me
way is to find out that these movies are not improvised because I don't know if they are
or not. They've got to be scripted. I mean, he's playing every character. It's like, you
know, it would be an impossible thing to improvise. And it really makes you go back and appreciate
and I'm not saying it because both men are black. But like when Eddie Murphy plays all those
characters in the clumps, they're all, I will say Tyler Perry was good at differentiating
the characters and good in those characters. He's not a bad actor. But he's just not a
good filmmaker no but Eddie Murphy as Eddie Murphy in the night professor is
fucking hilarious both as Sherman Clump and Buddy Love and all the other
characters Tyler Perry by himself is such a boring screen presence and he clearly
is having so much more fun doing the other shit you wonder why he wouldn't just
play those other parts I don't know I don't know well and you know Eddie Murphy
We also, it was like, hey, let's tighten this up and make this a scene where there's 100
lines of dialogue and all 100 of them are hilarious.
Tyler Perry is willing to let a scene go on for an hour with no jokes.
Right.
Well, that said, folks, if you've never seen a Tyler Perry movie, you should.
You should.
Well, I finally did, because at least you'll know what you're talking about.
And I was fast and admired and will watch another one.
And it wasn't like I was sitting there making fun of it like a fucking hipster on the crowd.
I had some genuine laughs some moments of sheer boredom some moments of shock
Some moments where I was laughing at it
But to me I had a better time than I generally would seeing a comedy in this day and age
I had a better time than fucking, you know, sausage party or things that are much better reviewed I laughed. I
Right, Pat. We get it. You thought it was decent for Christ. But it was interesting. Jesus God almighty
See now what didn't happen on Cisco neighborhood was that Iber would go Jesus Christ. We get your opinion on a movie
Well, yeah, it's a movie review show. I
Laugh twice. I walked out there you go. There's your synopsis. All right. I can't tell you how many movies I don't laugh at though. I know
But I didn't laugh at this one either
But but in a half hour there would be no in 45 minutes
I laughed two times for a comedy that's terrible numbers counting the 10 minutes trailers trust me when I know and trust
me when I tell you this there are other movies that would get
Lambasted on this podcast, but they're not horror comedies. So that's the only reason we're talking about this one sure, you know
Anyway folks Pat kind of enjoyed it. I
Did not go see it
Probably inebriated. Yeah, not a recommendation, but I mean when this comes to Netflix and you're a little drunk
Sit down with an open -minded and give it a shot because this guy is clearly doing something that kind of can't be denied.
Man's a phenomenon, and I think it's worth studying. I would take a class on Tyler Perry just to try to figure out what's going on there.
Well, you tell me when you sign up for that, I'll float the tuition.
All right, thanks.
Yeah, no problem. You got any plugs?
And I'll stay till the end of those classes.
You got any plugs besides Tyler Perry's films?
I don't. I'm going to St. Louis around Christmas and I'm going to be doing some stand -up on there, but I don't know where yet. That's a ways off.
Oh, that always helps with a plug.
Yes, no hard date, no location.
If you're in St. Louis, maybe follow me around. I'll be driving my mom's Mazda Pro de J.
And at some point with his Pro de J.
Yeah, actually.
At some point when I get out of the car, I'll be doing stand -up.
This comes out Halloween. I'll be at the New York comedy festival. November 3rd had
lining Gotham Comedy Club. November 5th. Can I kick it? Is happening in Brooklyn?
November 9th. Actually, there's two other things I can't talk about yet. So those two things.
So go see those. Details are on my website. You're doing this podcast live in Ireland,
well this will be out after that yeah so there you go see I know what I'm doing
with the plug all right Pat it was great to see you buddy great to see you