I'll see you in hell
And when the sound of your screams becomes a thing of my dreams
You know I'll say
I'll see you in hell
Folks, it's a sunny Monday morning
recording of We'll See You
in Hell. My name's Joe DeRosa
My name is Patrick Walsh. Speak for yourself
on the sunny, Joe. It's very gloomy in LA as it has been all year
which I like. We're talking about the Evil Dead
Rise. The last Evil Dead
remake was simply called The Evil Dead, correct? Just Evil Dead
Not The. Yeah. Okay.
We'll get to it. We'll get to it. Which is interesting because the original
Evil Dead is called The Evil Dead. Yeah. I believe.
Yeah. Meaning the remake is the
first time ever the movie was called Evil Dead
which could potentially help it
be less confusing because it doesn't, the other one
the original officially has the, I believe.
It does. Well because you know we talk about that where it's like they call like
the sixth installment Scream and you're like you already had one called Scream
so it's confusing. It's confusing and then I also
don't like that when you Google Scream it brings up the new Scream
it's like you didn't have to do this. You didn't have to erase
the original. And
it brings up
the TV show. Yeah. It's a whole
shit show. Yeah.
No it's always dumb. It's like
Friends might be big enough that it does away with this but it's like don't name your show
Friends because you Google Friends it's going to bring up a thousand things that aren't your show.
What is there a new show called Friends? No it was an example.
Oh. It's like what? This was for the
people back in 1993 who were going to name this show Friends. Name it something
else. Actually if they had named it like My Crew it probably wouldn't have been a
13 year hit so don't listen to me. Oh I see what you're saying. You're saying
just because the word Friends is going to bring up a million hits.
Yeah or it's like if you name your band Love you know
we're not going to find you first. There's going to be other results.
I'm glad you brought this up.
Thank you. Because I've been thinking about this lately.
You know I'm a big hip hop fan particularly that 90's
era and I was listening to Mob Deep
who spells it M -O -B -B Deep
and I was also listening to Gang Starr the other day with two R's on the
Starr. And I was like what a glorious time when there was no
name. How will they Google it? It's going to get confusing.
That's how we spell our name and when you ask about it in the
record store they'll point you in the right direction and that's it. It's all word of mouth.
But those are good names like
giving it two B's means it's going to be easier to find Mob Deep.
Well nowadays though if you know it has two B's
if it doesn't have two B's or you don't know that then you might run into
some issues because you'll get some article
where they'll be like you know. About Donnie Brasco who was
in the Mob. Yeah exactly something like that.
Well if you enter Mob Deep spelled M -O -B
the first result is Mob Deep. Okay well that's good. They did it.
Let's not get too hung up on the wrong aspect
of what I... Wait is this Prodigy of Mob Deep fame Fire
Starter Prodigy? No no Jesus God no. I didn't think so
I was like what the hell? But strangely
enough I believe both are passed away. Prodigy the rapper definitely
has passed away sadly a little while back. Yeah in Las Vegas Nevada.
And didn't the guy from the Prodigy band also die?
Keith Flint? Yeah he's
also dead. I mean I know he was a Fire Starter that
was it an arson incident?
March I'm gonna just see something here.
March 2019 is when the guy from...
Alright no I was gonna say wouldn't it be weird if it was like the same month
in year but it wasn't.
Pat. Yeah like you thought there was
like one month where all Prodigies died? Yeah.
Jodie Foster passed away. Yeah Bobby Fisher.
Whiz kid Donnie. Whatever
his name is from Magnolia. Donnie Smith. The Wizard the character
of the Wizard from the Nintendo film.
The Wizard of Oz who you know we only knew
as an old man but as a kid he was really good at math.
Didn't even have Wizard stuff. Let's just talk about how many people
in this current generation will only know the Wizard from the Wizard of Oz
as James Franco. Well wait till
that can you bear us one comes out who knows.
What do you think it means Pat when I'm in
such a sort of sad state that this is
the bright spot in my day is this exchange. Not
anything against you but knowing how dark these conversations can get sometimes.
Do you think that's a problem?
That you look forward to us
talking about death basically? Just that I look forward to us talking
even knowing it could go in such a dark direction.
I think that's nice. I think that's very nice. Weird I have
energy I've got all the energy to do what I need to do today but
you know yet still I look out at the landscape as a
good invitation to nothing you know toxicity.
The dance.
I'm doing alright. I got real rattled yesterday. I got a text
basically informing me of a pregnancy
scare after. Oh Jesus.
I was like okay so you know she got her
monthly visitor great but I'm like
how long did you think that this was a situation? She's like oh I've been
like a week and a half. It's like alright
I'm putting this thing on lockdown. If this was
if this woman was a week and a half late and that's how close I came I'm locking it
down. What does I'm locking it down mean?
I finished texting with her. I went and pulled both of my
dating apps and I don't plan on leaving my house
for a while. Why don't you just not jizz inside a woman?
Didn't jizz inside her.
Then you got a potential hustler on your hands fella. I got news for you on that one.
Look I don't jizz inside. You didn't jizz inside of her. I don't jizz inside
anyone unless there's a rock on that finger.
Where did the pregnancy potential come from?
See this is what another friend of mine said. I didn't know that my friends were so
uneducated on how pregnancy works. You can
get someone pregnant with pre -cum. Oh sure yeah that happens all the time.
Of course it does. Sure yeah you can get
HIV through kissing technically. It's come on man.
I got a friend who a lady friend not a
lady lady friend romantically but an old friend who got pregnant twice on the pill.
Doesn't sound like much of a lady in my book.
Well it was her husband but
a lady can spread her wares around town.
I'm kidding. Now there's a limit to how much spreading
that lady can do. And let's talk about the wear and
tear on that.
I know that you can potentially get
pregnant from pre -cum. But also too
pre -cum I don't know man. That's weird.
I mean I know you can. Yeah.
But it's always struck me as one of those things where it's like
if we don't put this in the pamphlet we could
get sued. So just put it in there.
Now online it says that the pull out method is 78 %
effective. I think it's gotta be more than that due to
the amount of times I have successfully pulled out. But
I know also that there are guys out there who are like
the cum's coming out when they pull out.
There are guys who like it feels so good. It's like in the morning when you don't
want to get out of bed when it's cold. That's what it's like. It feels so
great in there that you just don't want to come out.
And I pull out at the first time
there's a slight inkling that ejaculation might
happen in the next couple of minutes. And then just
crank it to victory. So I wasn't
necessarily concerned. But if this girl had told me
day two of missing her period I would have been terrified. I'm glad she told me
after. And she's on no birth control?
No BC. Yeah. I've done that. No judgment there.
I've jumped in the pool right after
eight. You know what I mean? I didn't wait that hour. I've done that.
It's hard not to. It's proof that God is a bastard.
Because he really, whatever
force created humanity
whether it was the bang theory or the planter's theory
or God or whatever the hell. I don't know. Whatever made us is a
literal bastard because you have no
concept of reason when you're
in that state. And you're right. You're just like let's let loose.
Let's have a family. Let's do this. And here's
the worst part. If like poverty and starvation and overpopulation
weren't a problem well then who cares? It'd be like
the most normal thing in the world. Of course you want to make a kid. That's what we're all doing. Make more
kids. Yeah. We got room. We have no room.
There's almost no margin for success in raising a child.
It's such a vicious scenario. It's so cruel.
And yet it's undeniable.
I mean my God is it brutal. Yeah.
I mean if this had led to, I've never thankfully had
the whole we're pregnant situation. I know that
my stuff works. I know that it's top of the line.
But I never knocked a woman up. Never got one past
the goalie as Kramer would say. I felt.
Jerry said it. Not Kramer. Just watch.
Jerry said to Kramer. You never got one past the goalie? Yes.
I'm out there Jerry and I'm loving every bit of it.
Yeah. My favorite
my thing that I most enjoy is to be
in a committed relationship where the condoms are pulled.
That's where I feel safe, comfortable and happy.
But when I'm out there in these streets and I'm banging
a lot. I don't know man.
Because you're always drunk early on when you're hooking up
with somebody or high or something because it's so nerve wracking.
I had a woman the other day. I was going downstairs and I mentioned
something about being a little nervous and she was like I find that so amazing that
you can say that. Like no one says that.
I just find that amazing. Especially a man saying that. I'm like what you're not
nervous going down here to have sex for the first time? No I'm very nervous.
I just think it's great that you say it. I'm like you're not?
You never get nervous? What the hell do I
care at this point? I was like isn't everyone kind of nervous?
I'm walking in the deer hunter at this point.
I don't want to go home.
Yeah. No I hear you.
It's just always weird. It's always weird.
I had a friend that was telling me
this was a very long time ago but I had a friend that was telling me
he went overseas to a place where
prostitution was quite legal and had
a lot of sex with a lot of prostitutes and wore no
condom. No way.
How do prostitutes allow that?
It's up to them. It's their call. Many of them were okay with it.
Not all of them but many of them I guess.
I said doesn't that make you nervous?
I didn't ask that. I just said doesn't that make you nervous?
He just went no.
The man had a hundred yard stare
and I was just like that is a
I couldn't do that. I'm not there.
I was just like that is a man that has accepted whatever
it is.
That's terrifying to me. That's scary and that is not to disparage a
sex worker in any way but
it would also be terrifying to me if I was going to just sleep with a person that I knew
was actively having like a considerable amount of sex.
That I'd be like sorry. Yeah exactly.
Amsterdam is considered like one of the safer
places where prostitution is legal and everything.
I walked through that red light district.
I saw the sites and I really did move along. I don't have it in me
to have sex with a sex worker and again no judgment.
For the same thing Joe said if somebody was like yeah you know I'm
ENM. There are women who were like I went on a date with a girl who was like
she had sex like every time she goes on a date. I was like if you don't like
the guy you do like the guy. She's like if I'm going to get out of the house and spend three hours I better get some
dick out of it. I'm like how many dates are you going on a week? Three or four or whatever.
Same thing. I wasn't pumped to have sex with that girl. I'm a scared person.
I would.
I wouldn't bat an eye. I'd rather you not tell me.
I'd rather not know. Sure I get that. Jeff Ross had a great joke
about he went on a date with a
porn star. I said what are you doing Thursday?
She goes I'm working. What do you say we get together Friday? I said what do you say
we get together Wednesday?
In Amsterdam
the most beautiful
of the sex workers had a line of about 40 guys.
That I wouldn't do. I wouldn't
pop eyes chicken sandwich with a sex worker.
I'm not going to wait in a line.
40 people in line. I guess they're all thinking
well hey Amsterdam is considered very safe. They are adamant about
protection. What do you got to lose?
As Lena Dunham said on Girls, a line that has stuck with me my entire life
what about the stuff that gets in around the base of the condom?
Because that is what I always think about. The condom should go to the balls
but it often doesn't and then with all the thrusting you don't know where it's
winding up. Your dick's touching vag at some point.
I don't know.
I'm not a 100 yard stair guy but I used to be deathly paralyzed
afraid of STDs. If I would hook up with somebody I would study my tongue
with a flashlight for about a half hour in the mirror.
And this was in my 20s. Now I just
don't think about it. Doesn't mean I'm not scared but I just don't think about it.
My Catholic upbringing led to me having very very
irrational spheres of STDs and things. I was the same way.
I'm now at a point where at 45
all I need for the woman to say is
I am on birth control and it's fine.
So you don't hit them with you clean.
Again it's like
look
if you read again the pamphlets
the things that I'm most concerned about are like I hope to avoid
herpes or genital warts or something like that. Because that's the thing you
can get though even if you have a condom on. So at this point what the fuck are we talking about?
It's true.
Some people have it, some people don't know it, etc.
The best thing a woman's ever said to me
ever. We were hooking up, we were naked
she took the jimmy
and slid it in. She did the slide in.
Initiated the whole thing and we start going and I go
okay, okay, okay. Are you on birth control? And she goes
no. So you're going to have to watch yourself.
I was like wow.
Wait I thought a jimmy was a condom.
A jimmy hat is a condom. I was just trying to not say dick.
But she took my dick and shoved it in her pussy. There you happy Pat?
You happy? You got the real talk?
What is this the Morton Downey Jr. show?
By the way I don't love that move the grab and shove.
It needs to be a little discussion. I'm a big fan.
Take control, let's go. I got no beef with it.
I just like a little discussion prior to all I'm saying.
I have become the woman as a young
man I always dreamed of meeting. Who would just be like
yeah do whatever the hell you want. When I had no idea
how to have sex I didn't know how to approach it. I've become that woman now
for the women. Do whatever the hell you want. I don't care.
I'm for the first time in my life turning down
sex and feeling great about it. That's a real power move. I see why
women do it constantly. It's very fun to
just be like no I got no interest. Don't text me anymore.
Thanks. Absolutely. Let's get to
we should probably talk about some movies. Yeah suddenly we're
Loveline over here talking about pork and call me daddy
podcast. What is this? So call me daddy
they're always interviewing like
some YouTube star about a scandal where she fucked a
Vine singer or something and a TikToker.
It's the biggest podcast in the world. They sold to Spotify for like
a hundred million dollars. I've never met a single person who listens to it. They seem
insufferable to me. It's like
the female version of Logan Paul or something.
I'm just like oh god. Speaking of and I
watched since I pulled Twitter I watched like ten Tik Toks before Bed Now. I just like to zone
out to something a little bit and randomly you see
clips of things that you'd never seek out but they just pop up
one of them it was not call me daddy but it was another sex podcast
and it was this girl talking about how she had had a threesome with Logan Paul
and her friend went into the bathroom.
Friend comes out of the bathroom. Logan Paul
immediately sticks his finger in her ass
pulls it out and then the
girl this beautiful woman telling the story talks about how she licked
her friend's shit off of Logan Paul's finger.
It's a nice thing for her to share.
I'm like you're telling this and here I am
I worry about everything I say on this podcast. This girl's naming
names of whose shit she slurped off a finger.
Yeah well anything for clicks.
Anything for clicks.
I watched speaking of sex. Yeah.
Boy this is a sexy ep. I watched Paul Blart 2.
I like one
I don't like two. I gotta say I don't like one
I think after the first seven minutes of one there are zero laughs.
I put on two. You're right. You're right. The funniest thing
in Kevin James history in my opinion are arguably
is that opening dinner scene in Paul Blart 1 where he's
where he talks about he doesn't get the job. The mom is sitting there
she's like do you want pie? He's like yeah I'm gonna want pie and then he goes I mean now
get the pie. Mid -dinner he's spreading peanut butter
on it and he's going peanut butter fills the cracks of the heart.
It's a perfect Kevin James scene. It's hilarious and then after
that it's not very funny. I put on Paul Blart 2 because I
just was like I was on the road I was feeling kind of down. I was like look man
I just gotta put something kind of brainless on that might put me in a good mood.
Maybe I was in a good mood or maybe I was just in the mood for this I mean.
But I thought it was funnier overall than part one.
I laughed like quite a few times through it and I was just like I don't know
this is funny. I was also surprised at how many edgy
jokes it did. Like the joke right at the top of the mom getting killed
and like the wife leaving him and I was like
I don't know this is taking some chances. It's
funny. It had a lot of good you know
the scene where like he finds the lost kid and then the kid
hits him in the face and runs away and he's like I'll go find him again.
It was just funny man it just made me laugh. It's not a great movie obviously
but you know it's like half baked or
Tommy Boy or any one of those movies where you're like yeah.
It's not winning any Oscars but it's got laughs in it you know.
That was my take. Tommy Boy is significantly above those films but I hear you.
Let me just real quick sorry. I
read reviews recently of Tommy Boy because we've disagreed
on Tommy Boy and I do like Tommy Boy but the reviews
of it are horrible.
That's always the case with comedy yeah. No but
Cisco they really hated him man.
Cisco's like he is no Belushi. I don't think fucking Belushi
was funny. I think Farley is 20 ,000 times funnier than Belushi.
I totally agree. They hated Sandler, Farley,
all these people but they loved Kingpin so I always
give them credit for that. They said Chevy Chase didn't have a good movie until Funny Farm.
I was like Jesus guys. Yeah I remember Ebert raving about
Funny Farm then you watch it and you're like this is about as good as other shit guys.
There is a five minute scene where he eats sheep's
balls you know. I don't think we're talking about a masterpiece here.
Anyway I, wait wait
oh Paul Blart. Me and my buddy Ian always
we saw Paul Blart 2 and the theater and we couldn't
stop marveling at how much Paul Blart's
daughter looks like a 50 year old woman.
I didn't think so. She looks like she's like 18.
What do you mean? We were like why is
we thought like Paul Blart's daughter was his wife.
Am I crazy? Yeah
We talk about this often. Maybe it was the big screen or something
didn't do her favors. I don't know but I hate. I mean I look I think
she was a little older than she was playing because of the time lapse between
the two movies so they did the thing where it's like she's probably
24 and she's supposed to be 18 but no I didn't think she looked that old.
Paul Blart 2 is a 6 %
unwritten to me.
Listen I watched
How to Blow Up a Pipeline. You want to talk about a movie with reviews. This thing
has amazing reviews.
Sounds like something you'd watch at a Upper West Side cocktail
party. Oh exactly. The New Yorker is throwing. Oh my lord.
Exactly.
This movie sucks.
It's like a heist movie about some young
kids. The most famous of which is Lucas Gage
who was the guy who eats
the hotel manager's ass in the first season of The White Lotus.
Or was he getting his ass. I think he was getting
his ass eaten. Excuse me. Anyway that's the biggest name. Lucas Gage
who was not a good actor.
And this movie
is supposed to be an Ocean's 8, Ocean's 11
whatever of young environmentalists who want to blow
up an oil pipeline in Texas. This requires
a very long scene that I know is supposed to be
suspenseful of them trying to like strap a homemade
bomb to a big piece of pipe. That's the action center
piece of this movie. And I mean the only
suspense they can generate is they accidentally drop it a few times and it's like
it like slips and slides. You're sitting there watching it like
I don't give a shit. I don't know how people are loving this movie so much.
I don't understand what critics are doing right now. I think it's because
everything is so bad that anything adequate is getting praised like it's
a masterwork. But don't get this.
The characters were very thinly drawn. I didn't like any
of them. In that way that
and Joe I feel like you're probably the same. Super
activists whether their hearts in the right place or not they're deeply annoying
people. And that's what this movie is. It's as if
Ocean's 11 was a heist to
blow up some oil and with
characters you don't like. So I certainly don't recommend it. But
again I might be completely wrong because everyone else seems to love it. I just thought it was boring and
not interesting. I've heard of this movie a bunch of times.
I never knew what it was. I swear to God and this is why I made the joke I made when you said
you watched it. This entire time I thought this was a documentary
about the pipeline controversy that they were
going to put the pipeline in. And the title was based on here's how to prevent
a pipeline from getting put in. And here's why the conservatives are awful
or something. I thought that's what it was. I didn't know
No it's what you would call an eco -thriller.
Oh Jesus. Fuck off.
It's one of those deals where they go into the
backstories of each person for like 30 seconds.
So it gives you nothing. You don't care is the problem. Anyway
Go ahead Joe. Another sexy picture. This was a re -watch. I threw on
J. Edgar last night. Oh God.
What an awful movie. You know
Some of the worst makeup I've ever seen. The makeup's not great.
I don't think it's a
bad film. I don't think it's a good film.
I enjoyed DiCaprio almost always.
He's good in this.
Or good enough.
Oh for God's sake.
My fucking brain anymore. The female lead in it.
The King Kong lady. What the hell's her name?
Naomi Watts. I thought she was good.
I thought Dame Judi Dench was very good as the mother.
DJ Deet.
I'm not just saying this because of the controversy surrounding him.
I actually think he's good as the younger version of the character. When he's doing the older
version it feels very like Theater Kid to me.
Like here's how a Theater Kid plays like an old man when he's in his 20s.
You know the movie's
fairly well directed by Clint Eastwood. It's a decently written
script. It just doesn't really
come together. But I don't know. For some reason I was
in the mood for that sort of picture. And I'll
explain why when I get to my third picture. But
I don't know.
It was a Sunday night watch.
They certainly take a lot of liberties with
exactly where he stood sexually.
There were a lot of rumors. But none of it's ever been fully confirmed.
It's just a lot of hearsay. So it's probably true. You'd think
with all the hearsay. But it is kind of strange that they do take
certain liberties with
okay he definitely was in love with this other man. And he definitely
did like to put on women's clothes. But whatever.
I saw it. I remember nothing except when
DiCaprio was yelling. I actually thought that his cheeks were going to
fall off because the makeup looked so badly applied. But
is he shown putting on women's clothes? I think I would remember that.
Yeah there's a scene where in the darkness of night
he takes a dress and pearls out and puts them on and looks in the mirror and then has
a breakdown and he hates himself for it.
Sure. But then a guy walking by the window goes evening
miss. Yeah. And he shakes his tuchus around.
I always liked to tell when Bugs Bunny would
put on a wig that grown men would immediately be attracted to this two foot
bunny. Not just a
male and female clothing. Not just the drag element. A rabbit.
A rabbit.
I do think
it's interesting that such a complicated and you know
in certain ways quite terrible man
like J. Edgar Hoover is responsible for essentially creating forensic
detective science. Like that's pretty interesting.
Anyway I can't tell you that
it's worth a watch but I don't know.
It's a good, it's one of these ones, it's probably a good watch with your
dad or something on a Sunday afternoon. Yeah I like to watch
movies where a guy puts on a dress and pearls with my father. Well my dad
is usually already in his gown. So I like to make sure
that he doesn't feel out of place. Sure. By the way
as one of the few people who've watched the movie Wayne's World with commentary
the awesome scene, one of the best like friendship
scenes ever to me is when Wayne and Garth are laying on the hood of
Wayne's car while planes are flying overhead
and like talking and laughing and Garth says
do you ever find Bugs Bunny attractive when he would dress up like
a girl bunny and Mike Myers laughs really hard
and it was an improv and that's a genuine laugh for Mike Myers.
It feels that way. So know it next time you watch the film. It's a shared moment
between friends. Alright. I watched Joe
speaking of Clint Eastwood a much earlier, much better film of his
called High Plains Drifter which he directed.
It's new to 4K. Mamma Mia does it look beautiful.
It's a big outdoor landscape
kind of western and just some amazing landscapes, skies
you know. It's a beautiful movie. Very dark
movie. The tagline is welcome to hell which
could also be the tagline of this podcast but Clint Eastwood plays a man
who comes to a small town. He
guns down on three dudes right after arriving in the town.
Then a woman lightly
insults Clint and I mean lightly
and he takes her into a
abandoned barn and rapes her. Clint is the hero
of the film as well. This happens
15 minutes in. He rides into town, shoots some bad guys and then this
woman's like what do you think you're all that and a bag of chips?
He rapes her. I mean it's not funny. It's
shocking. This was the 70s. It was horrifying.
I had never seen this movie. From there by the way
there's revenge. I mean the woman wants revenge on him for what
she did to him but for the most part for what he did to her
excuse me. For the most part the town
loves Clint and they're like this guy needs to protect us.
It was always the Clint story. Protect us from these bad guys that are coming
to town and as it goes the movie gets sort of more
and more intriguing and more questions are raised. For example
is Clint a ghost? Is Clint the devil?
Those questions all come into play and it
opens with Clint riding into the town but he's riding out of like
this thick A's that suggest he's coming from like the
other side sort of. Very very interesting movie. Very well directed by
Clint Eastwood. Dug it. Check it out.
He's never seen it. It's one of his best westerns I think.
And I also like
movies he does that are about best western. The hotel chain
which he does better than anybody else.
My last one. Another
sexually charged film.
JFK.
A lot of sexual energy in JFK
with surrounding
Tommy Lee Jones character or the Joe Pesci character
and the Kevin Bacon character. Plot for
an underground circle of gay men having orgies to
assassinate the President of the United States. Somehow it connects to
Cuba. Guys I can't even call this a rewatch.
This is like a seventh watch attempt. I've tried to watch
this movie so many fucking times.
I can never get through it without dozing
off. I wake up at the end.
Costner's in the middle of that 48 minute courtroom
speech. I know I've probably said positive
things about this movie in the past. I gotta say. I don't
think it has. Well
parts of it are better than I remember them being.
And parts of it are much worse than I remember
them being. It's not a bad movie obviously. And some people would
say it's a great movie. I find it to be a bit of an
endurance test. I do not think Costner is good in this movie.
I think he's great in that final stretch. But up into
including that. I think he's quite bad. You know
there's a lot. I'm so ashamed to call myself an American
today. Like there's just so many bad lines. That scene
where he wakes up in the middle of the night. Don't you see it?
Don't you see it? It couldn't have been a. You're like oh god guys.
It's just come on. That opening voice over is terrible.
The Martin Sheen opening. I think it's Martin Sheen.
But other aspects I quite enjoyed. John Candy I really
enjoyed. I actually thought for some reason I thought that was like not as good as it
was. But I actually really liked it. The reason I watched this was because I watched
a made for TV documentary about John Candy
called John Candy Behind the Scenes. And it
was a really wonderful celebration of
John Candy. And they talked about
obviously the end of his career and how this was a huge turn for him.
And you know he was very well received. His performance in
this was very well received. And he was very proud of it. So it made
me want to go watch it again.
And I mean I don't know. I can't
figure out a bad thing to say about it. I just. These are the.
This is why I bought and sold the Oliver Stone box set two fucking times.
I just can't get. Aside from talk radio
the guys movies just don't hook me. They just don't get their hooks in
me. I don't know why. I'm just like alright get to
it. Christ almighty. I gotta say more than half of his
stuff works for me. I did his whole filmography once on a solo movie
corner. And I like JFK. Now there is a director's
cut that's an hour longer. I don't know if you maybe watch
that or what. But I agree Costner's out of his element in the movie.
You can't hinge a movie that long and with that much dialogue on a
guy like Costner. He's our Gary Cooper. Meaning
he's got a lot of presence but you don't want to hear him deliver
long monologues. It's just not his specialty. I do love Donald Sutherland's
long monologue in JFK. I think that's great. Sutherland is great.
Lemon is great. Love Lemon of course.
Asner is great.
Spacek is great.
I think Spacek might be the only woman. No no and Metcalfe
is in it too. She's great. You got Wayne Knight. I like Oldman
Pesci. Oldman's fantastic. Pesci
weirdly pulls off. I mean if you told me on paper Pesci
is going to play I would be like what are you crazy? That's not going to work.
And he pulls it off. He's really good. I truly think the star
of the show is Bacon. I think Kevin Bacon comes in. He's got about
six minutes on screen and he's fucking tremendous.
I always love him but he was on fire
during that period. He did that murder in the first which was like an okay movie
but everyone thought he was going to win Best Supporting Actor because he was so fucking good in it.
He's a great actor. Anyway JFK
I'm not telling you guys anything new. Everybody knows the movie.
You know what I love about Bacon is that at some point he
realized he was a character actor. He was you know like footloose he was
a heartthrob but he was never that. So like at some point in those early 90s
he was like I'll be the eighth lead in A Few Good Men. You know he kind of
did the McConaughey thing where he was like I'm just going to change up my career.
I commend him. I like him. I'll do
a quick one here. I watched Heavy Metal which I had never seen.
Speaking of John Candy again I'm trying to connect all your movies here.
Had never seen it. Got the 4K
for pretty cheap on Amazon and
I dug it. I've never been an adult animation guy. I never
watch anime. I never watch R rated animated stuff. Just not for me. Who cares?
But lately I'm kind of getting into it in a weird way.
This movie I loved for its soundtrack of course. You got
you know songs from Devo, Cheap Trick, you know all kinds of people.
But it's basically
ten -ish short stories. Some sci -fi, some
horror, some just basically softcore
animated porn. It's a lot of women with
huge jugs bouncing around. There's characters
voiced by John Candy, Harold Ramis, other people that you know.
Not amazing. Not amazing animation. Not
amazing anything. But as like a 90 minute cool
music video I see why this was such a big midnight movie for
stoners back in the day. I had a good time with it. How does that 4K look?
Great. It looks great.
I've been meaning to buy this one for a long time and I'm glad I waited
because now there's a 4K. This is one of the ones where if I had bought the Blu -ray
I would have been like you fucking assholes.
Yeah. No and I was telling Joe about this the other day actually. Criterion
was starting to become annoying because they would come out with a 4K from a movie that they had just
come out in Blu -ray a few months prior. Now it looks like that was just
kind of growing pains for the transition. Now pretty much everything they're coming out
with comes out in 4K and Blu -ray together.
Including one of the great lost titles that has
never been out on Blu -ray. Martin Scorsese's classic After Hours which is coming out
this summer. Not a big After Hours fan.
Love the picture. Yeah a lot of people do.
Alright. Let's get to the movie at hand.
Evil Dead Rise. I'm so happy I can finally talk
about this and talk about all the parts that were so thrilling to see
in the theater. But this is just a little back story. This is the
one, two, three, four. Well in fact the Evil
Dead remake is considered
sideline, sequel,
sidequel, whatever the fuck it's called. It's actually not considered a remake.
It's considered to exist in the same universe as the first three
movies. And so is this.
And that is explained in Evil Dead Army of Darkness
when Bruce Campbell goes to get the Necronomicon. They say there
are three of these books. And Bruce Campbell and Sam Raimi have
confirmed in press about this that this is one of those three books.
The Bruce Campbell storyline is one of the books and then the
remake in quotes storyline is the third book.
So this is actually a sequel.
And they justified why it has such a different darker
tone and it's because, well, it's one of the other books. So anyway,
it's the first to take things out of the woods.
It's the first, well no it's not, Army of Darkness did too, but you know what I mean.
It takes place in a high rise and
not a typical high rise, an old sort of decaying
Los Angeles high rise, which I liked. I thought it was going to be some modern
Poltergeist III high rise and it wasn't and I thought that was a good call.
The building itself looks like an old haunted house.
It stars a whole new cast of people
and it's basically the same
story, meaning somebody unearths a Necronomicon.
It gets read from in a very creative way in this movie
and all hell breaks loose.
Yeah, I liked how this one happened with the earthquake
in the high rise kind of exposing the book. I thought that was sort of cool.
And that also too, they say the
building used to be a bank and the earthquake
breaks open what? A vault
chamber down below where this thing was stashed away
by the priests that had discovered it years before for
safekeeping in a safety deposit box, whatever the fuck they
put in it. And when the kid, when the earthquake happens
and the children of the female lead find the book, they also find these records.
The son is an aspiring DJ. He plays the records. The records
have recordings of the priest talking about the book just like
they did in Evil Dead 2 on the reel to reel.
Him playing the record of the priest reading the book is what
awakens the book and the demons, which I thought was a cool way
to do it. Yeah, it opens
with the ending and flashes back and then it kind of
ends with the early stage of the beginning
if that makes sense. So it's a little confusing but
it opens with this scene
where it's very graphic, kind of cut scalps this woman
and then she
who was she in the end? She
was just, she was in the basement. I found that part confusing.
It's alright. So let's start with the opening.
I'm in the theater watching this. I wasn't expecting much because
the trailers didn't really do it for me. So I'm in the theater
I'm like here we go. I'm excited to see this because I'm here.
But I wasn't expecting a great deal. That opening starts
the girl in the bed starts acting creepy. You're not sure
what's going on. They're in a cabin. You're like well wait a minute I thought this didn't take place in the
cabin in the woods. But you're in a cabin in the woods and it's a girl and her
cousin in a bedroom and the girl's cousin is on the bed and she starts
acting weird. And you're like okay what's going on?
This is part for the course. The girl then turns
and rips the scalp off of her cousin.
Right there, that's your first almost kill.
The girl doesn't die. She's running around scalped. The theater
cheers. I'm like that's a pretty great opening. Alright here we go.
The possessed girl then goes to the lake where her
boyfriend is flying a drone around that they actually do a
gag with where the drone, you see the perspective of the drone camera
as soon as the movie starts. And they're doing the perspective of the evil
spirits that they always do with the camera trucking along. Love that
and I wonder why in the age of drone technology we don't see
more shots like that. To me that style of camera work that
Raimi did in the early days that the Coen Brothers do in Raising Arizona
it's the best. I fucking love it.
So it starts out like this and then when you realize that it is
just a drone I was like that's clever. I like that. Yeah that got a
laugh and then so the girl
the possessed girl goes to the she kills the boyfriend with the drone
she gets knocked in the head whatever she gets she falls in the water. I don't remember the exact
sequence of events but she literally rises out of the water
like a fucking demon in all its glory and behind
her in giant letters the title Evil Dead
Rise comes up literally rises out of the
mountain scape behind her that I just got chills that
opening sequence the fucking theater was going crazy
it was like and when I saw that I was like holy shit
like this guy's like this that was like the opening of pulp fiction
to me. I was like this guy's bringing his fucking A game right now like
what is he going to do because he's got to live up to this now
and then it jumps to your central location
for the movie which is Los Angeles
and you meet the family that the movie centers around
including the sister of the mother of these kids who occupy the apartment
who thinks she's pregnant and is going or is pregnant and is
going home to see her sister and her kids because
she clearly needs help because she's pregnant and
has dated two close friends of mine so it was very odd seeing her in this movie
Oh really? Yeah. Wow. Oh I guess you can't say who
I can't but I did ask the one if he wanted to go see it forgetting that they had dated
and he got very upset with me. I was like sorry let's pretend I didn't text you
I apologize. She is gorgeous. Congrats
to your friend. Anyway
I so and the movie goes from there
and were you as excited
about this opening as I was I realized part of it is the energy in the room that you're seeing
it in but yeah I mean I saw this in
a pretty sold out theater as well and I saw it yesterday at like
10 .30am but
you know there is something about these big like South by Southwest screenings
and these festivals and stuff and you're seeing it before everybody else
the reviews come out hot you know because you're seeing something nobody
else has it's exciting blah blah blah and I think anything that
premieres at these places gets a big leg up because everybody is so excited but
I enjoyed this very much what you're describing didn't happen
there was no audible reactions or applause or anything from
the theater throughout. I liked the opening quite a
bit that Evil Dead Rise thing popping up was awesome I'll grant you
from there it felt to me like
something in the world of
like a don't breathe a B plus above average
horror movie that I really enjoyed you know and since this was
continuing a franchise that I have nothing but love for
I gotta say they haven't missed yet I thought it was slightly better than the previous
Evil Dead remake not up to the original
trilogy but I had a great time with it and
certainly a well made horror picture and an honorable addition
to the Evil Dead family.
I thought that this was
the best installment in the franchise since Evil Dead 2
which I think even with what you just said is
still a fair statement I thought it was better than the last one and I think
it's certainly better than Army of Darkness which is more of a comedy
so basically
what happens here is the family the earthquake
happens the son finds the records finds the book
inadvertently starts the chain of events
you know by playing the records the mother becomes the main
deadite and I gotta tell you I'm watching this
thing and I'm like well this is really cool but there's a lot of kids
around they're not gonna ice any of these fucking kids
and I was 100 % wrong the mother almost
immediately kills a seven year old boy
and when you see that kids they're in the hallway
and you're looking through the people perspective and the fucking you see
a seven year old kid's body fly across the people and I was like
holy shit they are going for this.
The eldest daughter meaning 13
or whatever gets possessed they burn her alive
I love that the neighbor
wants to get his immediately is like when the shit
starts going down is like let me get my shotgun everybody kind of scoffs
at like we don't need you to get your shotgun he does go get his shotgun and
is kind of a hero with a gun which is it's like yeah I actually
I'm happy to see a hero with a gun in a movie again and
the theater cheered for that when they saw him come out with his gun because they were like
this guy's gonna save the day he gets fucking iced.
I loved this movie so much I
thought every kill was maiming whatever you want to call it
they were all they all made my blood run cold the cheese grater
thing really made my blood run cold
the son the DJ son
he gets killed well they all get killed and and my biggest the thing I
loved both most about this movie was they made the Necronomicon
scary the book itself the imagery that they show in it
is creepy it's unsettling and I love the trick they did
where they would show an image from the Necronomicon to tease what was coming
and they do this at the very end in the best way when you see
all the deadites are gonna form this like spider demon
and you see the drawing of that and it's fucking scary I was like
this is scary man like this is this is intense that thing is gonna come
and it does and the movie has a tremendous
third act payoff where the main character
well the second female lead or the other female lead
the woman that you said your friend dated she is wearing the blue shirt
she's wearing the same color blue as ash is the entire time
and she has the jet black hair that Bruce Campbell has so she becomes
the heroine she's the heroine basically through the whole thing but she really
becomes the heroine at the end and in the final sequence she's drenched in
blood like ash when they showed the chainsaw and she's
gonna grab it the place went fucking crazy and they do
a great final payoff where the demon says I'll swallow your soul
she says come get some they did the nods right in the
places you wanted them they did just enough of them that you wanted the not that you
appreciated the nods yeah they all them all pounding and screaming
dead by dawn was fun you know yeah they did just enough of all that
that you go oh this is more like connective tissue and not fan service
and then in the end
after all is said and done and there's been this slaughtering
of the spider demon and the ant character and the one
surviving little girl get away her niece
the next morning there's a tenant in that building who comes down
she sees the horror that's happened there
she gasps and then you see the demon perspective and it flies
into her and she's the girl that's the beginning of the movie she's going away
to a cabin for the weekend so I guess it sets up a sequel
in the very beginning where that girl could
wreak havoc in the woods or something like that that was my issue
is that our leads are like three very attractive women who are about
the same age I was just kind of a little confused as to who she was
and how she would keep the demon in check
all the way out to the vacation
well yeah okay it's a very mild quibble because I thought
but why the attractive women thing why is that an issue
sometimes it's just hard for me to keep people apart when they're all covered in blood and gore
and they're all our beautiful looking models they all look alike
I thought they all looked very I'm not trying to be holier than that
I thought they all looked very different they were very
different looking people to me I just was unsure who
that woman was but she's just a tenant in the building she has no ties to anybody that's why
I was trying to make some connection that wasn't there but then my real question is
how long does it incubate in you the demon aspect if they can make
it all the way out to a weekend retreat but a minor quibble
I think if I'm not
I could be wrong I don't remember but I think it manifests in
different time periods throughout the movie and maybe that's they address it
we're not realizing I don't remember but I
just thought this was especially especially and I got to see
because it was the premiere I got to see the panel afterwards and they talked
about how COVID affected the production how it stopped them dead in their
tracks for this movie to be as good as it is
with facing those obstacles and especially being released
now at a time where everything is
filtered through ultra sensitivity where they're saying you can't
look man and I don't mean this in a callous way we're clearly
no stranger to these horrific school shootings and things like that right now
I was shocked they let the thing
they let kids die in this thing I thought they were going to be like you can't do that
you know because it's to this or it's to that I thought they would say a gun
is to this or to that you can't this woman can't
get beat up because it's violence towards there's a million things
they could have put in the way of this movie being this Austin Splatterfest
that it was to say that's not inappropriate that'll be triggering that'll be this
I actually and I don't think I'm putting too fine a point in it I will go as far
as to say I think this movie did a tremendous job of leveling the playing
field of inclusion and equality and all these things and say
guys let's not treat anybody special like it's on
we're all here together and it's happening and like this is the flick
and I think that that's needed now in entertainment and I thought that this movie delivered that
I really do I agree I think that it got
it got a pass probably because the kids and the women who are having
violence done to them are you know become zombies
or are blood thirsty zombies so you're just kind of like okay
but yeah it's it's fun in that way it's
shocking and feels like it's like the
come in the syringe and don't breathe or whatever it feels like something you're not supposed to be
seeing it feels dirty and that's what horror used to be yeah
now you know even though I really enjoyed a movie like smile
it feels like a psychological thriller with a couple freak outs you know
this is horror gross out horror tons of blood
it's the it's the gallons of blood dumping onto somebody's face
and open mouth they don't even have to make it multicolored blood like
what Ramy used to have to do to avoid the X rating right
and it's nonstop it's a it's like a 95 minute movie
that just pump it pumps it gives it to you gives you
what you want I'd say it's a about a full star better than the other
evil dead but it's in the same kind of camp they just did a better job with it
the the remake Lee Cronin wrote and directed it
I thought that I had seen his first movie a hole in the
ground the hole in the ground but I haven't I saw a movie called
John and the hole both movies have
a creepy kid who like puts the family in a hole and both are somehow
not porno and both came out at the same time so
I've never seen this guy's first movie I've added it to my watch list I think he's
very talented and the movie was great
I liked it quite a bit John and the hole that is a
crazy title yeah yeah yeah I thought
it was I thought it was an excellent excellent film
my hog is way up and I'm excited to see what Lee does
next with the franchise he said he is you know he does want to return
and he did say he's got an idea for a prequel
that takes place in the 20s or whatever it is
from when the recordings are made on those records where the priest
the story of the pre and he goes I want to do like a
priest against dead it's like a John Wick evil dead where it's like
a killer priest with all I was like that sounds fucking awesome
yeah so who's the new Bruce Campbell let's say you gotta cast that
priest gun to your head right now
well I think you have to get an unknown but if we gotta go with a known
for the sake of the fun of the game right
yeah
like Vince Vaughn's too funny
I mean he would be awesome though he would be awesome Campbell's funny
yeah yeah he is but he's really yeah he's funny
we can think on it wait wait wait I want to try to
Sam Rockwell I was thinking Rockwell
but I it's it's not quite right
you know who else who else is
I don't yeah who's why am I like who the hell is in action movies now
well I mean people that are in action movies couldn't
land a joke to save their life that's the issue put a Statham in there
Statham I'd buy it
I just watched a bunch of bloopers of Statham in the movie spy
yeah and the bloopers are very funny and fun to watch
because it's funny watching Statham like crack up as Paul Feig is leading
feeding him these ridiculous lines to say
because if you didn't know anything about Jason Statham you would say
this man has no sense of humor he walks around frowning all day
yeah and it's it's it's endearing to see him like crack up
at like a ridiculous thing that you normally
would have like you know Melissa McCarthy
or somebody like that say in a movie it's just funny it's funny to watch
saw Statham once at breakfast he had two sunny side up
eggs put pepper on them ate them in
one bite each paid and left I bet
I bet he does that every morning just eats two eggs pays and leaves
yeah me eggs me eggs love
alright folks that's that's your fourth episode for this month
I don't know what we'll be back with next month do you Pat?
I don't know what's coming out but if I could just drop something real exciting
into the chat we are about a month away from a new
Indy Jones picture so you can certainly expect that when that comes out
we'll be in touch we'll be back
I am on just Instagram at this point
at the Patrick Walsh The Miss Pat Show is airing on BET Plus
that's all I got Joseph. Folks live shows
for the year are dwindling down I don't have a lot left
I'm probably taking most of the summer off if not all of it
but right now I got Baltimore Maryland which
is next week or this week you know it's coming
right up on the the oh god
what is the dates the 28th and 29th of
April Baltimore Maryland I think it's four shows
there and then I got some shows in Pittsburgh the following weekend
I also have the last installment of the residency
at the Crane Theater in New York City on May 3rd
for we I never promised you a rose garden and
also Sal Vulcano and I doing taste buds the live stream
it will be live we were going to do a live audience
component about with it we're not doing that now it's just a live stream from the studio now
but there's going to be a lot of surprises special guests etc. that's streaming May
10th moment dot co slash taste buds
is where you can buy your tickets for that I hope to see you at any or all
of these events that's it for me we'll see you next time
and we'll see you in hell