I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell
Hey, when the sound of your screams, there comes a thing on my dreams
You know I say, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell
You know I'll see you in hell, folks, we're back again
Patty Walsh and myself here to talk about finally, finally, finally, finally
the fall guy, the fall guy or while I thought the fall guy was only
available in the two and a half hour extended cut on peacock and then
sure enough when I'm halfway through watching it, I realized they offered
both cuts. Good way to tell which one you're watching is there's an extended
unicorn drug trip fantasy sequence that apparently is the biggest change
between the two cuts and then there's a bunch more like improv -y comedy around
the fringes but yeah we'll get there we'll talk about it. I did the same thing I
texted you and I said yes I was with it and what is this unicorn and you're
like you're watching the extended cut get off and I switched over and I was
like oh this is much better yeah well it's just like the old you know
apatow was probably the most successful practitioner of it but I hated this
they would release the fort for I think still to this day the only way you can
watch the 40 -old Virgin is in the 20 minutes longer extended cut which
includes such scenes as like a black transsexual sex worker being sent to Steve
Carell's house and it's not as ugly as the scene could have been but it's also
like oh god did this scene not need to be in this movie it just casts an ugly
light over kind of a beautiful movie in my opinion I love that movie but
apatow used to do that all the time you'd get the unrated cut the raunchier cut
or whatever so the only way you can watch this movie that you love is with like
some really out of place ten -minute scene we're like one of the heroes goes
down on a 90 -year -old woman or something and test audiences were like oh get
this out of there and then the producers go have people are gonna want to buy
it if we put in unrated and there's some crazy footage but you've ruined the
integrity of the film it's well and then eventually apatow got like that
final cut approval and the movie started to be two and a half hours in the
theater and then they'd be like funny funny people now the three and a half
hour unedited you're like guys yeah godfather yeah exactly well I just
rewatch both funny people and this is 40 and in both cases you're like no what
this should have been is a two -hour movie then you slap another half hour
a bonus shit on the DVD but you're right he would do the two and a half hour
cut then when it came out DVD there would be another hour in there and
you're like what what's going on like what story am I even following at this
point they don't do it much anymore because nobody buys you know social
social media physical media yes the weird thing in in funny people even in the
movie version is when like I can't remember is it you know at the 90 -minute mark
or something it's either Sandler or Rogan just disappears and then it becomes
about the guys it's family I think it's Sandler yeah well I just watched this you
know it's it's Rogan's movie he meets this legend Adam Sandler and you're
following it and it was kind of apatow's almost famous you know his real life
thing of how he got into Adam Sandler's life you know and it's absolutely right
with like 45 minutes to go Sandler goes to reunite with Leslie Mann who's
only been in the movie by phone up to that point and she's married to Eric Banna
and then suddenly you're doing long dinner scenes with Banna and Leslie Mann and
then Sandler fucks Leslie Mann even though she's married to Banna and Banna's
chasing Sandler around the front yard trying to kick his ass and that's exactly what
I'm talking about you're like where are we no one here is funny these aren't funny
people they're all mad
um anyway yeah um speaking of which I'll get to I got I want to do and when we get
to the corner Sandler's new special but yeah I've got a lot of uh is it a lot I've
got some news I goes here well what do we got we got trailers or anything I
this morning I watched the trailer for night bitch which is and as as it's not
interesting as as the movie looked I was like this title has won me over in a way no
title as in ages night bitch is the greatest title of the last five ten years
um it's it's it's a great title it's up there we can't believe they could call it I
had and I don't talk about my stuff anymore but I have a future film script about to
go out very excited about it it's a big r -rated comedy and it has a title that I was like this
title is perfect it's gonna sell it I know it's on the edge but like I was just pumped and sure
enough the teams like we can't call it this and if if you knew what it was I'll tell you Joe when
we get off the air you'd be like that's not bad yes it's it's a strange time because I love the title
but I'm worried they're gonna make me change it well I got a I got a new psycho here that that
rocked me well we'll get to it but first off you know what night bitch is yeah she Amy Adams
becomes a dog Amy Adams becomes a dog I don't from the trailer I don't think she gets bit I don't
think it's a full moon scenario I think she just starts becoming a dog and the by the way the tone
and vibe of it is like enough said it's like a Nicole Hall of Setner movie it looks like an
indie that cost two million dollars from 1999 it's Amy Adams in like rich people world you know
like it's hard being a mom and that kind of thing and then all the sudden halfway through she's
running on all fours I mean I'll be seeing night bitch I'll tell you that much I whether I like it
or not I'll be seeing it I'll see it all right what year's Joe sorry uh well me a Faro just said
in an interview yeah and I quote I watched thousands of wives last night crazy that you bring up me a
Faro CBS Sunday mornings I guess she was on that and she was asked are you able to separate the
experiences in actor in those films meaning the ones with Woody Allen from the personal trials
and tribulations that would follow Faro responded oh yeah yeah I completely understand if an actor
decides to work with him I'm not one who'd say oh they shouldn't what what what that's all you've
done is is publicly shit on people that didn't announce this man what the fuck is she talking about
I didn't know she's been doing that I thought your surprise was just that she endorses him as a
filmmaker that's what she's alleging that's what I'm saying I'm saying like like like that she and
the daughter both have made a huge platform out of right condemning him and and look at the people
that look the other way and all that stuff and and now she's saying I would never say that you
shouldn't work with him I'm like yes you would but also too it's odd that she's even it's uh that's
odd if you're saying it's odd me you think he did what would he would you do think he did what you're
saying he did yeah you would say yeah I would get it if you worked with him what it just doesn't make
any sense strange indeed yeah but there's another news psycho yeah I've been waiting to talk to you
about this this came from movie web .com which I mixed about but I keep reading web is one of the worst
these sites on the web I'm fascinated that you love movie web so much I tried to look at it
I need another website because I need something to procrastinate before starting my writing day
and I only have like three or four websites anymore I like to look at every time I try movie web I'm like
this story came out three days ago and the person writing this is either a robot or a literate
yeah it's it's not great it's writing with no personality um they're late on things I just don't get it
the only reason ain't it cool but shittier the only reason I keep visiting it visiting it is
they often will be the first to to the to bat with like this trailer just dropped finally or whatever
and I'm like oh cool you know but it's a soprano's article I sent you this because I said Pat
even as a guy that doesn't watch the show or isn't a fan I couldn't disagree with an article more
and I just wanted to hear your take on it 10 harsh realities of rewatching sopranos 25 years later
now there's a disclaimer at the top of the article the sopranos made efforts to portray life and
crime as it was in the real world during the time it aired without pulling any punches but that
doesn't make some of it any easier to watch through a 2024 lens these these characters are monsters
that's the point one of the most beautiful aspects of the show later uh heavily borrowed by
breaking bad is that you love and root for a man who beats women who they they made him worse and
worse and worse with each season they they made him an absolute monster but you loved him that's the
it's really pointing a finger at you the viewer yes um like Carmella when she's like looks the other way
because she's provided with this wonderful lifestyle I used to watch it with my ex and she would
like hate on Carmella and then Carmella has a flirtation with somebody not it not us never goes any
further than that my ex used to be like how what is she doing got what is she's gonna throw away her
marriage or whatever and in the next scene Tony's naked like a beached whale with you know two
strippers on top of them she didn't bat an eye that was kind of the beauty of the show
is the is is it tells you like what you accept in other human beings that's kind of the whole point
right yes go on Jim somebody's like a person you'll accept whatever they do anyway that's fine
you find some of these some of these are just you know just insights like like number 10 Tony's plot
armor and the fact that like he's never been captured to the feds not care whatever that's just more
of a note on writing or whatever but the feds are on his tail the entire show they do capture it says
you should definitely not be reading the shit everyone in the show for yourself Joe I do think at
some point when you're old you'll be like I should do this they're saying like why was there only
ever one serious attempt on his life the fed seemed less interested in capturing him yet they
ferociously go after everyone out that that to me is just whatever the the this number nine is
one of the ones I want to talk the blatant racism yeah well yeah that's he's a racist guy yeah
yeah there's blatant racism because he's a racist it's been said he was the character was heavily
influenced by archie bunker I mean they they give meadow in season three and not even a black
boyfriend a biracial boyfriend and Tony goes all in on it you know like that's the show they talk
again number seven I'll skip the ones that are whatever number seven gender -based violence
again guys that's a lot of that yeah they're mobsters
there are but but also too they're they're showing how flawed these men are in this life that
they're leading like that's the point that's the commentary well the I mean the most brilliant
episode is Joey Pants savagely beats this stripper at work he gets obsessed with the movie gladiator
and starts swinging he starts doing lines from and a winds up killing this woman and the whole
B story or a story depending on how you look at it is Tony struggling with like his daughter
becoming an adult and like he's so protective of her and so caring for her and a dumb viewer which
sounds like these people are is not going to put it together that we don't care about the sex worker
but we care about the daughter we don't understand that Tony is doing all this abuse and violence and
everything else but I was also a family man you're just you're not you're not look you don't
have media literacy if that's your criticism of this show number six little to no female empowerment
now give me a goddamn break Tony is ruled by his mother for the entire series even after she passes
away Carmella is one of the strongest female characters of all time although we point out her
hypocrisies at every turn um wrong bazar lg melfy melfy rules his life
bazar lgbtq storylines gay characters are handled too harshly by the mob
that I actually think especially because of the time it came out that is one of the most shocking
and incredible developments of the series and instead of it just being a joke that this 400 pound
mobster is gay there's an episode where we're at his country cottage with his boyfriend we spend an
episode with these two men and it's not like look at these queens it's it's presented as a serious
relationship um a couple of these are just you know they're saying like that there's storylines
that weren't resolved or whatever stuff like that but then number one is my favorite you ready yes
number one plenty of body shaming oh there is a tremendous amount of body shaming
that's true yeah guys their assholes yeah half the cast is like 500 pounds in addition one of my
favorite aspects of the sopranos is that everyone they never call it out but everyone on the show
is making fun of everyone else for traits that they themselves possess which is one of the most
accurate portrayals of how shitty humans are I've ever seen by anything and Tony loves having
Steve Sharipa as his sidekick because he's twice the size Tony hates himself because of how much he eats
and he can't stop so he surrounds himself with these men who look like houses and he makes fat jokes
that they're expense because there's somebody he can get the up on again it's like you're just not
thinking about and you're a you're a critic you got to think about what these things could mean
it's like it's like that book on goodfellas made man that I that I read that I really enjoyed
the making of goodfellas they talk about how now people call Scorsese or racist because a character
doesn't walk in to Joe Pesci and be like hey you can't call that guy an n -word right he's a man with
with dignity like no because then that guy would be shot in the face like they're simply trying to
portray the world as it is and they're showing that this because of this world you start to swallow
these little grievances you have or may have about human treatment and whatever and then you become
the monster that's the kind of the fucking point of a lot of mob movies but the example they use in
the body shaming is uh Jenny sack yeah well first Tony tells Bobby to stop leaning on his car because
he might accidentally flip it over but the most insensitive remark comes from Ralph who jokes that
Johnny sacks wife Jenny had a 90 pound mole removed from her rectum that body I don't even get it
because she's they don't I get I don't say rectum by the way that's your own weird addition he says
she had a 90 pound mole on her ass now this is what I love uh this is what I love about an article like
this is how much it misses the point and focuses on not just misses the point of the show
but if you want to talk about indignities and sensitivity and all these things
notice there's not one thing in this article that talks about murder yeah uh you know they
talk about violence towards women but it's um I thought it was going to be Italian stereotypes
that we're going to have a problem one yeah you know and it's like it's just this just this just
reminds me of Dana Gould had a joke I'm gonna kind of bastardize it but you know he thought he
used to have a juggernaut LA is a weird place you could drive by a guy at a fur coat masturbating into
a mailbox in public and the person in the car with you will be like that better not be real fur
it's just like yeah you know focusing on the absolute wrong thing Ricky Jervais talked in his
one special about how he posted the video from the dog festival in China where they were
skinning a dog alive it's horrible and he goes he goes you know who are the real animals in the
picture or in the video or whatever and then somebody's like way to be insensitive and say that
Chinese people are and he's like that was your take away that's what you thought I was saying here
that's what you thought I was saying like this hyper focus on all the wrong shit and it doesn't even
it doesn't even really matter for discussion ultimately even as we're discussing it because
that is the point of everything on the internet now is to get you to click on it and then start
getting angry about there's a term for this now like rage rage bait or something like that
well it was always clickbait I don't know if they updated it but yeah I heard the other day and maybe
this is an old term that I just heard but that like the concept of rage baiting where it's like no
they get you to click on the article because they know it will make you angry and that's just how they
get the click out of you so anyway also there's so many people scouring the internet with like one
obsessive thought in their mind and they see everything through that lens because they're
fixated on it you notice this like you see a hilarious video like some guy slips at the top of a
water slide and falls down whatever and you're laughing oh that's funny like America's funny as
some videos right then you check the comments and the first one is like typical Biden voter
it's like no no no stop now what's going on here and that's going to be on pretty much every tiktok
you look at if it's if it's an America's funniest thing where somebody gets hurt the comments will be
oh wonder who he's voting for oh I did he fall while running to the polls to vote for Trump
and it's like you don't even know if these people are real but can you imagine if you watch
imagine if you're watching America's funniest home videos like back in the day and every person
that gets hit in the face with a pie you're speculating on who they voted for it's like we've lost
the ability to have fun yeah it's it really sucks right now to be alive but what can you do
were you a funniest home videos guy excuse me as a kid I was yeah I I enjoyed it yeah we loved
and funny as people but to a way lesser extent yeah we that was a real sit -around gather
around the TV yeah every Sunday night kind of show I I got to meet Bob Saggett before he died
he was very very nice and I didn't assume it was after I go to his grave and I talked to him and
I hear him talk back and maybe that's in my head but no I fit the gym beam onto the grid
we did it we did a show together a benefit show he was a very sweet guy and um but he told me at
that thing somehow we started talking about America's funniest home videos I don't think I'm talking
out of school here um he goes he goes yeah we're we're bringing it back and I was like oh no way
you're gonna like do you're gonna host it again and he was like yeah we're gonna do
America's funniest videos after dark and he said it's gonna be like a more adult version
and it's gonna be like people you know drunken the street kind of shit and I was like
right like dude that is a fucking great idea man like in this day and age of internet and phone
video and whatever like and he also but it also exists I one of my biggest renters of all time when
I worked at blockbuster was America's funniest home video is uncensored it was only like an hour
but it was great I'm sure you can't find it anywhere but it's out there
yeah I was also excited about the idea because he was he's a dirty or comic and was an edgy
or comic and I was like oh that'll be fun to get to see you do this more as you now yeah yeah instead
of the full house version of you or whatever so um so I don't know maybe they'll still do it but
it was more exciting to me that he was gonna be the host of it again but um but anyway
is it still on with alfonso rebaro I think it's still on maybe I know it was burgeon on for a while
I didn't know rebaro took the the reins yeah he hosted it he was the third host and I feel like
recently I was like holy shit that show is still coming yeah so I just saw some some video online
of uh jaleel white who was on the miss patch show it was actually very nice he has his own weed
strain now you let me try but he was like it was this very somber music and he's like
yeah just uh not only did I never get nominated I was never even invited to the Emmy Awards
I uh I never even got to present and you're like jaleel baby
like you were huge man but like you're not gonna get a wards attention for pulling your pants up
to your nipples and asking if I have any cheese it's just not gonna happen he was really hurt too
although you look
he can see he was also saying like we just knew that that he was like Fred Savage always got to go to
the Emmys and there's a picture of Fred Savage and he's like so it was clearly just like black kids
weren't allowed to go which may have been true but I'm like when jaleel white who's older than me
is sitting there with in like black and white with dramatic music playing and then they put up
like a picture of Fred Savage like this beef's been going on for 30 years or something I'm like
jaleel you gotta get something else going in your life man you can't still be upset about this
I love excuse me I love I mean I don't love it meaning I like to watch it but I love the the
visual of late phase herbal and screech like when they both got too old for that character
and they still were doing it and they're like now in their 20s yeah like guys he looks like a grown man
this doesn't work anymore screech in the college years when he's still making his voice crack I was
like come on man he looks like a peer of Mr. Belding's he looks like they're going out to the clubs
yeah let's talk pictures uh sure I have seen some things you wouldn't believe
that's not true they're just movies you'll probably believe it um I rewatch let's let's go me a
pharaoh husbands and wives um I'm realizing the older I get I only love and respond to dark
fucked up what he owned oh yeah uh my I mean my top five without even really having to think at this
point is like husbands and wives crimes and misdemeanors blue jasmine a recent addition um I love
deconstructing hairy I just like when he's letting his freak flag fly if you will and this one is
one of the craziest I mean I remember my dad asking me to leave the room when a trailer for husbands
and wives came on like Woody Allen in my house it was like we don't say his name he he was on a very
famous 60 minutes around this time of husbands and wives people were wondering why me a pharaoh is
even in the movie because all these controversies were going on it happened during the filming of
that oh okay I'll be professional and finish the movie but that's where it all took place I mean
I'll be professional and finish the movie is insane um well word on the street is too that he would
actually offered her the part the Keaton part in Manhattan murder mystery right yeah uh and she
considered it yeah that's the that's the rumor uh and then the reason Keaton was brought back was
because me a pharaoh said I'm not going to do it and then he thought well why don't we bring back
Keaton and rekindle some of the old magic which they kind of did not have murderous reason it's not
I don't love it but it's not bad I like that one um love hand intersisters of course I mean the look
yeah masterpiece it's my favorite movie of all time the the looking at the the it's odd that we have
just wiped away his entire career when I reviewed husbands and wives or I just you know I gave it four
stars whatever on it on letterbox I immediately got texted by a friend of mine it was like you're still
watching Woody Allen movies I was like um yeah man like do you know what people do in this business
like do you you gonna watch Rosemary's baby ever again like yeah you know but also too this this thing
where I don't want to digress but just I just want to make the point this thing where you're not allowed
to believe he's innocent of this thing like like with Roman Polanski at least you could say no he
was convicted right right you know I think he admits it yeah well he did he did time he did like
he's like you know whatever but um that's the part that really irks me it's like you can think that
he did it that's okay I can think he didn't do it that's okay too can we just both have an opinion
on this but um you know the people that are just you know I hear you it's but yeah there's so much stuff
I was very adamant about the hypocrisy for a while of separating the crime from the artist
R. Kelly being my best example and I've switched now now I'm switched back to no I separate the two
because it's all become so crazy the discussion that uh I feel like you have to I separate the two
man's the man said a 50 year body of work you know counting some of the best most interesting films
ever made so I'm not gonna write the man off so did you like husbands and wives it's a dark it's a
dark flick man that's a tough one I absolutely love husbands and wives and there's something that
happens as you get older that movies probably more so than music I would say as you get older you can
return to a movie that meant nothing to you as a child that bored you as a child oh and you watch
it as an adult with all these experiences and you got a marriage under your belt and everything and
it's suddenly a whole new thing that means a lot to you um which is one of the many things I love about
movies I mean as you change the movies change uh husbands and wives is fascinating it is very dark
it's basically um Sidney Pollock who destroys in this movie uh I love Sidney Pollock Michael Clayton
eyes wide shut where he took over for Harvey Keitel Tootsie we're not even talking about the man's
directing career I love him as an actor but him and his wife Judy Davis they show up to Woody and me
as place they're like we're getting a divorce this spirals everybody out me a Pharaoh in particular
she's like well I wonder what could have been with my life if I hadn't married Woody and so on
and so forth everybody starts fucking around everybody starts being there were selves Liam Neeson's in the
mix a young Liam Neeson who's kind of like this uh fuck prize that's being passed back and forth between
Judy Davis and uh me a Pharaoh it's such a great movie it captures so many like little cruel moments like
me a Pharaoh is trying to set Liam Neeson up with her friend but me a Pharaoh is married then once
they start hitting it off she gets jealous and then she starts kind of trying to seduce everyone's
just acting badly and that's when I find Woody Allen to be at his best even if he doesn't take it
to a thriller level like a match point or crimes and misdemeanors I just love him in this mode
and um it's great he's trying to seduce Juliet Lewis who was a student of his this was right after
Cape Fear you get the strong impression that Woody Allen walked out of Cape Fear and immediately
wrote himself a scene where he makes out with Juliet Lewis um but it's great it's just when he taps
into the human condition um and the worst of people he's he's at all cylinders the scene where
Sydney Pollock who is dating a younger dumber woman that's one of my favorite scenes ever I think
he's dating this younger dumber like a robex instructor and he overhears her at a party talking to
his intellectual friends but she's being an idiot and she's talking about like um
the cap the zodiac signs and all that so he finds out in the other room one of his friends is drunk
and tells him that his ex -wife is now hooking up with Liam Neeson and Pollock starts going nuts
they keep trying to change the subject and he's asking like all these follow -up questions and they're like
oh it's not a big deal we don't have to keep talking about it and he's like no who was she dating what
she said he's driving him insane so then he hates his girlfriend all the more because he hears how well
his wife's doing and he winds up yanking her by the arm out of this party I remember him beating the
shit out of her that doesn't happen but he's it's a jarring scene he's yelling at her he's yet you
know yanking her around people come out of the party to watch great great great great great great movie very
intense stuff powerful stuff I loved it well as mentioned I watched the new Adam Sandler special um
the hell's it called love you I think so um oh god I can't believe I can't remember the name of it
I think it's love you well if it is I want to make sure it is because I want to address that if it is
um hold on Adam Sandler directed by is it directed by Benny Safty or it's directed by Josh
Safty Josh Safty and it's called Adam Sandler love you yes all right so first of all
I'll start by saying I'm a big good mire of Adam Sandler and a big fan of the guy I don't like a lot
of his movies but I love the ones I love very much I'm always rooting for him uh I've met him he's
extraordinarily nice um I've heard about word yeah he's just an awesome dude like he's a guy that you like
and you're happy for um I did not like the special um first of all title I love you you know
that bugs me I I'm big on like figure out if somebody else has already used that title don't
with you know my friend Jake Johansson had a special called I love you I thought that was a great
title for a stand -up special and it was a great special for Jake and I know I love you and love you
or two different I get it and I know that everybody is doing stuff now and there's you know buckets
and buckets and buckets of content out there and it gets harder and harder to figure out how to do
something that has a unique title uh I get all that so I'm not dismissing that but at the same time
I'm just like I don't know I remember when Jake put that special out and I was like man I love you
with such a unique title and I've never heard that and that's a really funny title and it was also
very relevant to Jake's special because his opening joke was in that was he go it was something
along the lines of like guys this might be too soon but I I love you and it was a very funny opening
joke or whatever and um for this special I didn't really see the relevance of the title maybe I
missed something but um so that there's that my bigger issue with this was I didn't understand
why Adam Sandler who is the most likable celebrity alive and a guy where if you go on YouTube
you can see video after video after video of him being so fucking normal like walking into a taco
place to pick up his own tacos right like and then like people being like what the fuck holy shit
he's like yeah yeah hi how you doing hi I mean he gets his tacos he leaves like people walking
up to his car and him slowing down to be like hey guys how you doing like and giving that
generous which he does not have to do no I didn't get why this guy and a guy also too that is helped
so many of his friends Rob Schneider Rob Schneider is in the special if you don't consider that five
minute Elvis performance in the middle of the special helping a friend I mean it's wild but um so he
did way too much to help a friend in the case of that Schneider bit I don't get I just don't get why
he would open this special I get why you open a special the cinematic thing I thought that was
kind of cool but the whole thing this first six minutes of this thing he's showing up and it's all
like famous guy annoyances it's like why aren't why are these fans outside the door I don't have time
right now to stop and give autographs going in the room we need you to sign these things for charity
I don't have time right now going into the control room his Willie Brown I think there's the comics name
and yeah Willie Brown and Woody I think it is they're like an old ventriloquist act I worked with
them at the laugh house back in the early oughts this isn't the ventriloquist from Tim and Eric is it
that's what I thought no no it's a different guy he's an actually like that's like L .A. guy his
names on the wall at the store okay he's a guy he's been around and that thing where Sam
there walks in and he says the director how's he doing yeah which is an insinuation of
sometimes he doesn't do well right now and I get that I don't maybe he didn't mean it that way
but it's like dude what do you mean how's he do you should be like oh this is great he's killing
and then he shows the guy doing his actual jokes and they're not really working and I'm like why are
you making this guy look bad and then it looks like oh here's another problem I the famous guy
have to deal with and then there's the whole bit with the I didn't I want it stevia in my coffee
not splendor you fucked me on this like and like I just was like I don't understand what the point
of any of this is other than showing a guy he it's just not a good light to portray yourself in and
and especially a guy that I didn't believe would actually do any of this you know here here was my
confusion on it you either do like did you ever see the Conan O 'Brien story it was a sketch they did
on Conan where Jim Kerry played Conan and it was hilarious it was like you're here to promote your
new movie it's a Conan biopic and it's Jim Kerry with the red hair the popidor and everything
and he winds up throwing a hot coffee in his assistant's face and all that and the bit is
Conan a notoriously likable fun easygoing guy is this monster they didn't take that bit to a
comedic extreme that's what I'm saying and I just played it like it's his life when we all know it
isn't so since we all know him to be a nice guy you have to at least push it into a laugh place
and they did well and that's the thing it's so it's either what you just said or it's them saying
let's show what it's actually like for you and it's like this is not a if that's what it is we don't
want to see this this is not a good it's just not it's just bad PR anyone I saw an interview and he's
going um he's talking he definitely didn't say that it was fake problems on stage he was like yeah
you know we just kind of had some problems with the with the set and everything and I'm like
that's why why keep this charade up and and I don't know it's like it wasn't funny enough
and it also wasn't serious enough to be dramatically interesting it was just kind of nothing
well that's the thing he enters the stage and then these fake hiccups happen during the show right
and the whole point is it's like it's supposed to be this Andy Kaufman thing where you're like is
this real is it not oh this is tense and whatever but in the back of your head you're going of course
this isn't real yeah of course the Adam Sandler Netflix comedy special didn't have monitor issues right
of course people weren't fighting in the fucking audience um and if you're going to plant these seeds
have some payoff but then there isn't payoff I read a review of it that said it was brilliant because
it created tension and then the laughter was the release and it's like no but it didn't feel like
that it just felt like there were a bunch of these weird scripted moments that didn't make anybody
look good the jokes were funny enough the jokes in the last few go on funny yeah they were funny
that I laughed it didn't you know what I played like was deleted scenes from the first special
which was super funny it played like stuff where you're like all right I think we can cut that
well in the first special too he's having fun he's you know like and there was none of that in this
and then the songs aren't silly enough anymore and I'm sorry I know it's heartfelt and genuine
that song at the end made me cringe man like where he's thanking everybody and say I guess that's
why it's called love you because he's saying like thank you Lauren Michaels and Chris Farley and
it's the farthest song at the end of the first special it I was cringing and then at a certain point
it got me and I was like this is a man singing about his dead best friend and I I couldn't resist
this one had me in full cringe from note one till the bitter end to the point where I was losing respect
for Sandler and almost turned it off I was like this is probably the end I should just not watch this
well him going with no jokes like thank you for the comedy thank you to Jerry Lewis
and also to the three stupid I'm like what are you doing man what are you doing
and that's for other confusion about the title because he doesn't say love you to these people he's
just thank you so maybe call the special thank you thank you for the comedy get it um but
it was lame as fuck and that's the difference between this and the Farley song when he went back and
hosted SNL he did the Farley song and it was a tribute to Chris Farley yeah and that was beautiful
and you're like this is cool this was just this to me kind of sappy I need a way to end the special
I'm gonna do this long fucking song where I thank every famous person I've ever known yeah and the
audience is gonna clap and you know it's special is 74 minutes and it's it wouldn't be perfect without
those 14 minutes but if you trim 14 minutes meaning the opening sketch the terrible final song
and the fake audio hiccups that aren't funny or interesting and we're left later singing Elvis
and Rob Schneider singing Elvis Jesus Christ like you would think all that padding would equal
up to an hour and it's like oh sound there's just rich and lazy but no you got an hour of at least
a quality special here get out the shears as Jiminy Glick would say thank god for the shears
you cut it you cut at least that that 15 minutes out and you got a pretty good special but that
that was my issue with it is the stuff that was good wasn't even particularly great hate to say it
anyway I'm not saying you won't enjoy it uh it wasn't I'm not against a cinematic
comedy special in fact I love them I just didn't quite understand why he made certain choices
with this but I don't know maybe that was the point um but I it wasn't I didn't enjoy it I don't
want to say it wasn't for me I thought it was for me I just didn't enjoy what the final product was
not here anyway what what else you got there patty um I rewatched for the first time since the theater
Charlie's Angels which one you're talking of course about the Kristen Stewart Charlie's Angels right
yes the somber Charlie's Angels where they cover their bodies in full that's the one I was referring
you know how everybody loves Charlie's Angels because it's a bunch of fully covered very intelligent women
solving crimes um with no humor or sexuality I didn't see that Charlie's Angels I did see both
of the Diaz Barrymore Lou and I remember seeing them in the theater forgetting them the second they
were over kind of enjoying them and I kind of enjoyed it this time around I mean I don't know what
do you know did Mick G get canceled no I think everybody was just tired of his name
and they said take care of yourself now he I think you have a couple of bombs you know he did
tell me your salvation yeah I forgot about yeah and I I think you'd do a couple of those and and
you know he's kind of Mick G to me is the um uh who was the guy from Clash of the Titans
Worthington he's the Sam Worthington of directors where it's where it's supposed to be real big
and you know yeah well he did just last year family switch with Jennifer Garner and Ed Helms he
did the babysitter on Netflix which I know people like I didn't see um okay yeah he had a couple
bombs this means war with with with her spoon but Charlie's Angels um I think he did a really excellent
job I mean he he created this kind of big fun music video vibe um he was coming from
music videos bright it's colorful it looks you know it doesn't look unlike a Deadpool versus Wolverine
it's it's a it's a good looking movie and it's fun it's interesting to watch now more of as a time
capsule because there are scenes where like they will fully zoom in on Lucy lose ass and watch as she
walks for 30 seconds as the cheeks bounce up and down in a parallel other pants you're not going to
see that in a movie nowadays yeah um and when you see it it's kind of shocking it's kind of shocking
that we all just were cool with it now I'll tell you this I'm still cool with it I'm still I
still I'd still be very cool if suddenly in a movie I was looking at Sydney Sweeney's ass for 30
seconds um I also get that it's a little creepy it's the male gaze I understand um so I like watching
movies from before we all became pilgrims it's kind of fun my ranking since also at the time
we had to rank women there was even it she's out of my league which was a whole movie about the
numbering system for women starring TJ Miller um I used to always go d as number one by a thousand
percent Barrymore number two and Lou an afterthought in third just barely even cut registered to me
now twenty twenty four years later Jesus Christ lose number one by a thousand percent
I found myself I found myself looking up everything she's been in I found myself oddly obsessed with
then Diaz a distant second and then Barrymore a for an afterthought I've never very
more has never been my thing but um there was a time where Barrymore was my number one yeah
Lou was my number two I was never attracted to Cameron Diaz but I always thought she was the
best actor of the three so I liked that about her quite a bit uh but I think Lou is Lou is
something else especially after that turn and kill Bill I mean she oh yeah sexy beast as they say
well just like how I talked about how you know when you grow up and have a bunch of serious
relationships and disappointments in your life a movie can change for you sometimes the women you're
you get you get boners from change too and that's a form of maturity as well um it's also progress
that now I lean towards the diverse angel you know I think it tells you a lot about the way things
have changed um no she's she's unbelievably beautiful it's also very much of the time that all of
her scenes involve her either giving a rub and tug massage wearing a kimono walking on her tiptoes
with a fan in front of her face well there's your article movie web write something about that exactly
no exactly no everything she did like uh we meet I forgot Tim Curry was in this I didn't even know
he was still acting in 2000 but he plays this creep who's getting a massage from her you got Bill Murray
um and Tim Curry in sumo suits going at it at one point you got Bill Murray looking like the second
they yelled cut he probably screamed in people's faces he looks so miserable and unhappy to be there
there was a 10 year period where Murray just couldn't hide his contempt for life and the world and
the movies he was in this is probably his lowest point he looks like he is having the worst time
they replaced him with Bernie Mac for part two uh rumor is he headbutted McGee on the set of Charlie's
angels and screamed racial slurs at Lucy Lou it's hard to hear all this stuff about Bill Murray
it is but um knowing it we if you're if you're gonna watch this movie again keep your eye
on Murray when there's he's supposed to be the angels friend when the three of them are like sitting
on a couch with Bill Murray the women look like they want to die having to be that close to him it's tough
man like he must have hated this fucking experience um you got Tom Green early on as as Drew Barrymore's
like one night stand and I'm like what the fuck's he doing then I remembered he was married to Drew Barrymore
at the time so much has changed since this movie came out you got Crispin Glover as the uh the thin
man or whatever the creepy guy who does like it's a weirdly stacked cast I'm friendly with Tom Green
and uh there are times where I've been hanging out with him and halfway through hanging out I just
remember yeah he was married to Drew Barrymore it's nuts it's nuts I mean the man never really made
me laugh I respect what he does he just never really made me laugh but swept her off her feet
yeah um I wanted to my friend uh dimmy who's great on letterboxed and and everything he attempts but
here's I agree with this wholeheartedly Lucy lose face makes me feel like a blind man finally seeing
the sunset wow that's how I found all right I was I was smitten I enjoyed Charlie's angels it's not a
great movie I bought the 4k for 10 bucks and I immediately listed it for sale but it was fun to
revisit something from that period uh I'll do one more quickly I watched Red Dog which is a documentary
about the famous Red Dog saloon in I think it's an Oklahoma city uh basically uh this guy who's now
he does a he makes a documentary centered around his mom's experience and then interviews all the other
women that dance there and uh the men that were in and out of his mom's life that were involved in
the Red Dog saloon and blah blah blah but I found it to be riveting I found it to be hysterically
funny I found it to be terribly heartbreaking at times uh but but beautifully hopeful overall um
and it's just a bunch of women who are now like in their 50s who used to dance at this place in the
70s and 80s telling the craziest fucking stories I have ever heard in my life and they're just
they they're talking about like they're like there were so much drugs they were like the guys just
would tip us in drugs and it got to a point where we're like we don't want any more drugs we need
money please yeah they said it was just a fucking free for all of it wasn't a prostitution house but just
the the lifestyle that surrounded the place at that time was truly sex drugs and rock and roll a lot
of tragedy uh but again followed by a lot of hope uh it's a movie worth watching and it's awesome seeing
a bunch of women in their 50s who are now mothers and who are now doing different things with
their lives and and living basically pretty pretty square lives just being like yeah we did it I don't
give a shit that's where we were at we had ups we had downs and life goes on and that's it like and it
was it was it was a riveting documentary I really enjoyed it I suggest Red Dog I think it's on Hulu
it is I added it to my list and intent to watch but the mom the guy's mom is really really fucking
funny like she's you're you're just like how is this woman not an Eastbound if they if this movie had
been out when Eastbound and down was casting they would have they would have been like you're playing
Danny McBride's mother just be yourself hold right at for you like it she's perfect she's amazing
I want to meet this woman so bad uh anyway I will watch it I saw a clip of Eastbounded down I think
it's from the pilot of Eastbounded down the other day but there's this woman coming on to
any powers and she goes uh she's where you've been living and he says I'm down in Florida and she's
I bet they don't I bet they don't got women like me down there and he goes no I'm pretty sure they
got sluts in Tampa oh made me laugh um folks speaking of making me laugh I think one of the worst
movies I've seen in a year at least is the bike writers uh with with Tom Hardy Jody Cumber Austin Butler
Michael Shannon this thing is ridiculous it's on peacock right now it's directed by Jeff Nichols
who made take shelter which is one of my favorite movies ever I am obsessed with that movie with
Jessica Chastain and Michael Shannon since then I don't know man I didn't like mud much with
McConaughey I didn't like midnight special uh I didn't like loving I haven't liked anything he's done
it's sad um because I really did dig this guy for a while I liked shotgun stories all his early stuff
with Michael Shannon is awesome that's how I was introduced to Michael Shannon but this movie is
ridiculous it is based on a photo book but so I'm like why is this movie so like pointless and
meandering and stupid oh it's based on a collection of photos they're a coffee table book you mean
yeah exactly of bike writers from that time from that time yeah so it doesn't even feel accurate I
mean Jody Cumber is doing like a Fargo accent that is real ridiculous Austin Butler he he was perfect
as Elvis and my prediction is he will never be good in anything ever again this kid is so he's
playing Elvis in his real life the way he talks like they're like they go hey so what's uh
what's the music that you like or whatever and he's like oh man you know I guess it all starts with
blind Willie McTale and you're like you're 24 like he's the least fun person what's a movie that you
really like oh I gotta go back to Charlie Chaplin you know he's definitely my you don't like Charlie
Chaplin Austin Butler he's doing this like old soul thing he thinks he's Marlon Brando
and I can smell your dumbness through the screen you're not fooling anybody you can't just whisper and
we all think you're smart you're dumb I don't like Austin Butler and I fucking loved him as Elvis
but he's so dumb in this movie and bad Tom Hardy as always he says what's the way I can say my line so
that no one will understand what I'm saying I actually refused to put on the subtitles I was like
I don't even care what you're saying Tom Hardy if you can't enunciate in one movie I'm not gonna
bend over backwards turning on these subtitles for you the movie sucks there's no story it's guys in
like necker chiefs and and shitty biker wardrobe and it seems like everybody spent the entire time
trying to make sure that they're closed match the photos and nobody wrote a script and nobody
said to the actors hey you're coming off like a real idiot in this movie I would and I would not
do that stupid voice you're doing it's a bad bad movie all right well let's get onto the movie
the day the fall guy is it a bad bad movie or is it a fun watch this is a remake
or adaptation of the old Lee Majors and Heather Locklear TV show the fall guy I love this show as a kid
where they romantic in the fall guy yeah I believe so she was the she was the Emily Blunt character
and cult seeers was the main character which is Lee Majors not 30 years older than Heather Locklear
I don't I mean he might do you when is that ever been a story in a Hollywood but yeah no I don't
think he's that much older than her he maybe 20 years older 15 years I don't know but anyway
but you you were a fan of the show I've never seen it I loved it as a kid man I loved it as a kid I
loved the song that opened the show and I loved it it was the first time I had seen as a child and
I don't know if it had been done before this or not but this is also one of the things that makes
Indiana Jones so cool or one of the things there there was a thing and they did a call back to it in
this there's a thing in the opening credits of the show where Lee Majors punches a guy in the face
and like knocks him out and then like shakes his hand and goes like like that hurt my hand
and as a kid I'd never seen that I'd never seen a flawed hero like he was a tough guy but like
he got hurt and like he showed it yeah and he was a little vulnerable and whatever and I and I
I just loved the show as a kid it was you know it was it was right in there with the 18 and all that
stuff so I was excited what's the what's the burnt Reynolds movie you and I saw where he was a
stoopers hooper okay yeah hoopers yeah you know so I was excited when they announced this adaptation
I was excited that it started Ryan Reynolds because Ryan Reynolds is becoming a guy that's really great
at comedy and he's our he's our best comedy star I hate to say it's we's our funniest guy and the beauty
of it and what he does that that almost nobody else does is he's satirizing masculinity while being
very masculine that reached that reached its obvious you know apex and Barbie where that was the
whole point but he's doing it again here he's he's so awesome to me because he is genuinely funny
he's the action hero that everybody wants to see when you go to an action movie but he's also
giving you a wink where he's like I'm not really this guy I've never seen it it's awesome to me
somebody was saying the other day that Glenn Powell is going to be bigger because men and women
like him but only women like Ryan Gosling I was like you're so fucking wrong I wanted to it's first
time I wanted to write a letter to the editor in ages I wanted to be like what are you talking about
every man I know loves Ryan Gosling it was the dumbest article but um it's a good time for
Ryan's we got Reynolds we got Gosling I'll take a couple of more Reynolds any day of the week
um well so so the plot of the movie the plot of the show was you know he was this stunt man but
did then he would have to like solve crimes and he'd get roped into action scenarios in his real life
and that was the plot of the movie he's a stunt man yeah cult severs uh and he gets brought out of
retirement to work on a movie that's being directed by his lost love played by Emily Blunt yeah
and he gets to set and he finds out that the leading actor who he's the stunt double four has gone missing
and he needs to go find out where this guy is and it doesn't quite make sense spoiler alert it doesn't
quite make sense at first why he's being sent out to find this guy until you realize that they are
setting up Ryan Reynolds to pin Gosling or Gosling excuse me to pin an accidental murder
that the actual star committed on him and it goes from there it's a you know it's a it's a cat
cat mouth is the wrong term but yeah it's a caper he's he's being chased by bad guys for the whole
movie while trying to reclaim the his lost love um and I mean that's basically the plot it's
it's it's it's not reinventing any wheels here um pat as you said to me in a text it's dumb fun
I agree I think my my overall take on this movie is it is dumb fun and if you're in the mood for it
you're gonna really enjoy it and if you're not in the mood for it you'll just kind of roll your
eyes and go there whatever there's nothing bad about it um and and and there are some things
that it does quite well I think it really is just gonna pertain to are you in the mood or not
I will say it is a movie that made me realize while watching it how shattered I am as a human being
because I would have moments in this movie where I was like oh god damn it I don't care about this
at all and then next moment I'd be weeping uncontrollably as he's professing his love to Emily
Blunt so um okay well that's that's that's what it's all about if I can quote the hook you poke for a
moment the movie is not perfect it's not excellent but it does a lot of things pretty well at a time when
most movies do everything badly and I think people's love for it was not necessarily oh this movie is
amazing it was just like we used to get movies like this all the time this would have been like the
average movie back in the day and to me it felt like something a little special something they put a
little more time into um the reason it works so well I think it's what you're saying I had moments where
I was getting a little emotional it's Gosling and Blunt their love story is fleshed out it's given time
to breathe but then what sells it what brings it to life is you have two really wonderful actors
who you totally believe have this big complicated romantic history and that makes every beat in the movie
hit harder because you're rooting for them and you like them now all movies like if you go see the rock
in whatever have a love interest but it's given absolutely no time attention fleshing out at best you
got a wife at home who's on the phone like don't let me down baby you I know you got to come home
today I'll see you at I'll see you at five baby whatever whatever it is you know um this they give
them both funny shit they give them both a real believable relationship and they play it great and to
me that made everything hit all the harder the supporting cast comedy nothing quite hits the lady
from Ted Lasso is not very funny Winston Duke the guy from us is not very funny the
Asian girl assistant is not very funny you keep getting these character the other guys not super
funny the other the real actor Aaron Tyler Johnson or whatever his name is it's all about Gosling and
Blunt Gosling yelling at that guy that he needs to eat carbs because they make your brain work better
while he's trying to pitch the movie I'm laughing hard and to be laughing at like the two hour 15 minute
mark I was like all right movie did a good job he enjoyed yeah I uh the first scene that made me
truly laugh is when he gets to set and he's being directed by Emily blonde for the first time
and she's pissed at him because he disappeared on her for a year after he gets injured at the
beginning of the movie and she's explained he's he's like doing this stunt where he keeps getting
thrown repeatedly into a set on fire and then thrown to a rock yeah and he's like he's like what is
what is this about we have to why do we have to do the stunt again and she's explaining the movie she's
written to him and it's the dumbest fucking plot you've ever heard it's so funny when she's
explaining the plot but it mirrors their relationship and that was clearly the inspiration for it
and like you know as she's making points about what a fuck up he is all the aliens in you know
in costume nodding and agreeing with it like that whole sequence was really funny to me um I thought
like what satire stuff was good and funny I like the mimoa bit at the end that barely made me laugh
yeah and then and they do an interesting job throughout the movie of dissecting a Hollywood movie like
this and making a commentary on it as as that type of movie is reflected in the plot of what's
happening to the actual characters in the movie so that was all very funny um and very well done
and they also did a lot of good plays on the term the fall guy he is a stunt man he also breaks his
back at the beginning of the movie because of a fall uh and then he's the guy they're trying to pin
the murder on so he's literally that he's taking the fall and then he saves the day at the end by falling
from a helicopter so they got all they could out of the title um and yeah it was funny my my one
disappointment was and this is my fault it's not the fault of the movie you see action comedy
Ryan Gosling I will I was hoping for a little more um nice guys I wanted him to be more of a
fucking idiot and like he he he's not he's he plays like a genuinely good guy that has made a mistake
or two but like that's again that's my fault I was bummed that it wasn't like that he that there
wasn't that there weren't as so many scenes of him getting completely frustrated yeah uh part of
his own stupidity yeah it was they were in there but um but uh it's it's it's an enjoyable film it's
you know and and you get your Lee majors and have their Locklear cameo uh mid credits which is nice
and it's hilarious because it's it's literally the nor McDonnell joke where he did the thing about
Lee majors having to do the hearing aid commercial when his agent calls him and he's like oh you calling
me about the remake of the six million dollar man starring Ben Stiller were I'll play a judge for a minute
and the actual this is actually a version of that basically but um I didn't even see that part I
didn't make it to the credits it's mid credits but um and then that the other cool thing is in the
credits because there's a whole thing through the movie about how the stuntman is the unsung hero of
any movie especially any action movie and then in the credits for like 10 minutes they pay tribute to
every stuntman in this movie they showed them all the all the actual guys doing the real stunts I was
crying I was literally crying I thought it was such a beautiful tribute yeah so the movie had a lot
of heart they played on movie tropes very well they played on cliches very well and there are some very
funny moments my my my biggest thought was oh they they clearly said would have John Wick was a comedy
I felt like that's what they because he does John Wick shit throughout the movie and I was like
I don't know why this guy would know how to beat up seven people like this in a
yeah that's true I mean and use like the cork from a champagne bottle as a weapon or whatever but
it was very John Wick at times like you know the stuff he pulls off and whatever so
again if you're in the mood for this sort of thing I think you'll enjoy it and if you're not
at worst you'll roll your eyes but I don't think anybody would watch this and go oh this was terrible
I don't think anybody watch it and go oh I loved it it was my favorite movie but uh
it's a really great plane movie I would say um and David Leach the director also did
co -directed the original John Wick he also did well then there you go yeah he also did nobody
and atomic blonde and all the movies that are following in John Wick's footsteps so yeah um
but visually which I did not comment on I thought this movie looked really fantastic
and yeah it's just sitting there in 4k on peacock for you check her out I thought it was a good time
and if they made a sequel I would go see it uh it really just works though because of
Gosling and want and again to I really don't like Glen Paul look up uh Chris Fleming's very very very
funny stand -up bit on Glen Paul you can find it um look it up I like Chris Fleming I'm a fan
and I don't know that bit bothered me for some reason because you love Glen Paul
now because he also didn't want about Colin Joost uh -huh and it's this whole like
Chris Fleming's very funny but it's like it's just this attack on Holly I've got a problem with
watching attack on Holly would happen from guys or girls that perform a lot at Largo
nobody sucks at the teeth of Holly would and I'm friends with the people at Largo it's fine
but every Largo show is big famous person and friends true the lineup is over bloated with like any
fucking notable person they can shove on to it you know until they're bringing up like the third
bass player from the darkness or whatever it is like just to say he was there yeah it's a little like
guys you're in hot you're in Hollywood you're doing the most niche not niche but like exclusive of
all the Hollywood venues blah blah blah you're gonna you're gonna turn the guns on Hollywood you are
that you are the machine it's great it's rage against the machine you're gonna shit on the machine
you are the machine guys you're multi -million dollar you're a multi -million dollar global fucking
a band at this point you are an industry in and of yourselves and you're gonna get on stage and go
here's the problem with capitalism it's like okay I'll say this I know Chris a little bit
he's not a rich man no no I'm not saying he's he's always punching up
but I do hear you Largo is a very were holier than now kind of venue for sure
but but it's a holier than now venue that is part of the vow yeah for sure that's my point
like it's like yeah elitist yes but I am a fan of Chris and I like his comedy I just I don't know
it's the same thing that um like I think Tim Highdecker is is funny but it's like why is everything
pointed at somebody else now like I don't know it's like don't don't do that just be just do your
thing that's fun I hear you it's like you're you're being mean also you know the whole old comedy
thing is like we're we're not like that mean punching down you know nasty hateful comedy you are
though yeah yeah like it is mean you're definitely excluding people from whatever your little
fucking vision is but anyway I'm saying to finish my thought from 20 minutes ago you put you put
no and I don't mean for you I just mean we got off on attention but you put Glenn Powell in this movie
it doesn't work he doesn't have he doesn't have anywhere near the charm and charisma to carry
something like this off and that's that's what Chris's bit is about is how we're we're generating
these stars who have so little edge to them that they like they couldn't offend anyone and that's why
the movies have gotten so boring and it's certainly one of the reasons and then he talks about how all
the big actors of the 70s 80s and 90s you meet them at the beginning of the movie behind a dumpster
and they're like like you know they're like feral creatures like Bruce Willis you know the
beginning to die hard with a vengeance is basically like if I recall correctly hung over in a gutter
somewhere and now it's Glenn Powell it's we've lost something and we've lost like relatability
Gosling for being one of the best -looking men alive he's got it you relate to him you root for him
and he understands that being as good -looking as he is is kind of funny he doesn't take it so
seriously that's the beauty of him and I think the small beauty of this movie which is pretty fun
we are going to be back with Immaculate Starring Sid Sweeney we are going to talk about
whatever that movie's called with Channing Tatum and Zoe Kravitz yeah we we're probably
do blink twice I'm assuming beetle juice is going to probably cut the line I'm seeing beetle juice
tomorrow night my excitement is at a total low I have no excitement about it but I will go see it
the progressive ad campaign isn't getting you more excited beetle max no no there's a progressive one
now too wait but isn't oh the car max beetle juice tie in is the worst thing I've ever seen beetle max
it's horrible yeah there's a progressive one as well you know beetle juice wasn't doing that
shit back in the 80s look I would never think to have him as your spokesperson he eats bugs he's not
but he none of the characters in any of these commercials it's just them referencing yeah they didn't
get keyed so it's like his head on a popsicle stick being like come to car max yeah I'm not
uh look I'm I'm excited enough to see it that I'll probably go tomorrow if not Friday yeah I'm not
very hopeful at this point the what's happening is what always happens with these movies the initial
reviews are through the roof or at least solid then the heavy hitter reviews start coming out like
vanity fair whoever and vanity fair was like this should have been left alone the second I started
seeing like it's fun and there are enough enjoyable moments that you'll kind of forgive the fact
that it's a little bit of a plot mess and I'm like this is there you go here we are once again with
this so I maybe I'll be wrong but yeah we'll see the original beetle juice is kind of a plot mess too but
it you look past a lot it doesn't matter if like you have everything that movie had beetle juice is
coming in way too late a dollar short maybe it'll maybe it'll dazzle me who knows I'm concerned
let's try to sync it up Joe let's try to see it at the same time all right uh come see me in December
in summerville with the crystal ballroom tickets are on sale now joda rosa dot com and then tickets
for all of January uh into the new year are on sale the joy stick tour kicking it off going back
to the comedy clubs and doing more jokie jokes uh this time around little less of a one -man he kind of
thing but uh Fort Worth Texas in January Toronto Ontario in January San Diego in January Tampa in March
Rosemont Illinois in March Stanford Connecticut in April Timonium Maryland in May and there's more
dates being added joda rosa dot com and uh come on down to uh Joey roses if you will if you're in
New York Joey roses dot com the Patrick Walsh at Instagram see you in hell pod at Instagram
we will see you next time and we'll see you in hell
you