And a happy, happy new year to you.
I've been doing this thing where I...
Let's just stop right there.
You have a beautiful singing voice.
Really, it just takes my breath away.
This is Joe DeRosa.
This is Pat Walsh.
Good morning.
It's Christmas Eve.
Joe and I basically logged on a few moments ago.
Agreed that this was a deeply depressing Christmas and then hit record.
So we don't know where this is going.
But we're both known for Christmas.
Long, isolated, separated.
I actually can see others.
I'm not ill. Joe has COVID -19.
Yes, I do.
And I feel fine.
I thought I had a cold all week.
Took a test of the tail into the week before going home just to be safe.
Came back positive took five more.
They all came back positive.
So yeah, as of today.
I'm not leaving the house.
I'm praying to God I get a negative test sometime later today or maybe tomorrow morning.
And then maybe I could see a friend or two.
You know, I told you to get test.
A couple weeks ago.
Well, it wouldn't have mattered.
Would it?
Oh, you mean no, no, no, I mean a negative.
I'm saying a negative result.
Yeah.
Did you use my trick to get the free ones at the pharmacy?
No.
But had I gotten your test, the recommendation to go test a week ago wouldn't.
I haven't left the house anyway.
Let me be clear to everybody.
I started to feel sick Monday night.
I was around two friends.
I went home.
And I said I'm not going to leave the house again until Christmas because I don't want to get more sick.
I thought it was just a cold.
Yeah.
So I haven't they know that I had this.
I did all the right moves.
And now I feel 100 % fine.
It's been six days.
Symptoms have been gone now for a while.
And you know, I'm just waiting for that negative test.
And even with that.
So I guess I can't like go into public public.
But like I can at least hang out with some friends that say a negative test is good enough for us to whatever I don't know.
Right.
Anyway, go ahead.
Am I seeing things or do you have sunglasses atop your head like a bookie?
This is my regular glasses.
Oh, okay.
All right.
But now that I'm 45 when I wear them.
Yeah.
At times I get dizzy from certain distances.
So I can't look at.
I don't fucking know.
I used to need them to see the screen.
Now I can see the screen perfectly.
And if I wear them, I get it.
It's almost like I've inherited some sort of super power.
Like in the movie where the guys like wait a minute.
I don't need my glasses anymore.
You know, like I drank flubber or whatever.
Right.
Yeah, that wasn't really a superpower.
That's a flubber on a on a date.
And I think what about the movie though?
I think that well, goodwill hunting was sold out.
I recall the perfect date movie.
So we went and saw a flubber.
And I just remember the chemistry going out of the two of us with each passing moment.
Flubber is one of the worst movies ever made.
And at the end, it was like we just kind of win our separate ways.
You can't start a relationship with flubber.
That was from the Robin Williams period where even he was like, what do you,
what do you want for me, people?
Yeah.
Even in the poster like his eyes are just dead.
You know, he's like, you want to come see this shit or what?
You know, I got a family.
I just rewatched.
I just rewatched speaking of goodwill hunting.
The Ben Affleck scenes on YouTube by YouTube this.
The Ben Affleck scenes from Jans Island Bob strike back.
The good Jans Island Bob.
Yeah.
Because I really liked the Ben Affleck scenes in it.
But that scene is really funny when they're shooting goodwill hunting too.
Like the back and forth between him and Matt Damon, where Matt Damon's like,
I can't believe you talked me into doing a sequel to this.
Yes.
He's like, oh, I'm sorry.
What?
I forget the exact quote he's like.
What gay period piece swordsman did I pull you away from portraying this week?
And he's like,
I don't do this for the money.
And Affleck goes, I keep trying to tell you, man, you do one for them and one for you.
That's how you do it.
And then there he goes.
And sometimes you just do reindeer games.
That was a dark period for Affleck.
He had, well, phantoms, of course, which Kevin Smith also made fun of.
But man, he had a lot of bombs in a row.
No, they give props to Finn.
They went.
When Affleck props.
Yeah.
When he's playing the character, not himself.
Yeah, Jay goes, but Affleck was the bomb and phantoms.
I saw phantoms theatrically.
That was when I saw every movie released.
And I got to tell you, I remember enjoying reindeer games.
I rewatched it last Christmas.
It's not bad.
Not terrible movie.
It's not a great movie.
By today's standards, as we find ourselves saying, frequently in the show, it's probably a goddamn masterpiece.
Yeah.
I mean, I, I, I think standards are just done.
You know, I was, I was texting with Joe this morning watching.
You got mail.
And just like, you know, it's a, it's a 20 character deep bench of actors.
You love story works.
The chemistry is there.
It makes sense.
It's, it's a lovely touching story.
It's funny.
And, and I was saying to Joe, at the time, when I saw it, it was considered a disappointment after sleepless in Seattle.
It was not critically acclaimed.
Critics were like, it's another retread of this Meg Ryan Tom Hanks thing.
I saw it.
I enjoyed it.
I moved on with my life.
You watch it now.
It's like, holy shit.
We didn't know how good we had it.
You know, you knew when you went to a movie that you would see a complete, a completed film.
That's not even a guarantee anymore.
I, uh, what the hell was it going to just, oh, oh, and by the way, as you said, a 20,
um, a 20 person deep bench, I'll rephrase it of actor of great actors.
By the way, the actors that are great, just because they're great.
Yeah.
Like, not because it's the same seven people, they're, they're swapping.
I mean, dude, you want to talk about sad.
So this, you know, I'm sorry, real quick, though.
At that time, it was like Dave Chappelle, new on the, Steve Zahn, Parker Posey, all these exciting.
Now, Tom Hanks, his friend would be Keegan.
You know, you know, you know who everyone would be.
Yeah, it would be her boyfriend, uh, Meg Ryan's boyfriend would be Adam Scott.
You know, it just goes down the fucking line.
It's they, they, they make the most obvious choices.
And that's why nothing is surprising or funny.
Gene Stapleton in this thing.
Yeah.
Just because like because she's great.
Like they wouldn't even do that now.
They'd make it like Helen Mirin.
It would have to be a old person that you're familiar enough.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, well, you know, all in the family was about as big a show as you could have.
And you know, the comparison now, let's say cheers.
So like they, they go, well, let's get Shelley Long for this part.
She's an old lady and they'd be like, no, you got to get a box office bankable old lady.
It's so stupid.
Um, they, uh, well, what I was going to say is this is just, it's just so pathetic anymore.
So by the way, I love, I love what James Gunn is doing as the head of DC.
I love that he was just like making some decisions.
He was like, no, it's under woman three scripting going to fly B.
I'm a fan of Henry Cavill, but I like that he was like, where are we're going to recast?
We're going to go, yeah, you're getting out of here.
Anyway, yeah.
But this is black Adam got the boot, which I think has led to the rocks complete breakdown online,
which we can get to shoreline.
Well, and the rock won't even confirm that it got the boot because like that would be like a loss.
An admitted admitting of what it says.
Here's the, here's the thing with the rock.
You know how, when you're coming up in, in comedy and writing and anything in the entertainment industry.
Joe, you'll know this feeling just as well as I do could be talking about it all the time.
Social media has made it so you always know what everybody's doing.
You always know what everybody's up to.
Their successes, et cetera.
You know when a friend is fronting about how well things are going in their career.
And, and you know, you just feel the desperation behind the post a little bit.
And the rock is somehow there, even though he's the biggest star in the world.
He's doing these posts with the dentist of us.
It's rough.
And then it's the, it's a sick business.
So he won't, he won't, he said very vaguely like that.
He didn't say in his post his big announcement post about what was going to happen with black Adam.
No.
And then by the way, these other people and Cavill did this or Kaville did this and they all do this.
This is gross now.
They all get fired and then they go.
But as always, I wish DC to keep kicking ass and it's like, can anybody just go, you know what?
Fuck you.
You told me I had the job and now I don't have it.
Anyway, that's, this is the thing I'm trying to get to.
The rock should do that.
What's the last time that people liked supported and were like pumped about the rock.
You know, normal people was when he told off Vin Diesel for being a fucking prima donna.
It's like, I don't mean you've got to be an asshole or you got it.
You got to cause drama to get everybody to like you.
I just mean people are craving a morsel of realness from their celebrities.
And we're getting nothing.
It's like these people are in these plastic arps that you just, you see no humanity in them anymore.
They're just zombies.
So Cavill gets the boot and then immediately on movie web, which is just, I don't know why I keep looking at the site.
It's just become essentially a tabloid site.
But anyway, immediately a movie, movie web, they put, you know, fan art and the article is like fans imagine Henry Cavill is Mr. Fantastic.
You know, fan art, whatever.
And that's not that's not out of the realm of possibility.
Yeah.
Like because now these actors, it's so sad.
It's like they get passed around like Sharon Stone and casino.
It's like, Jesus Christ guys like DC got rid of me.
So then Marvel is going to hire me now.
I'll play this guy and just change the color of the cape.
I'll go over there and do it.
Who cares?
It's just Jesus fucking Christ, man.
Can anybody, not it, I shouldn't say can anybody.
Can any of these a listers exist out?
It's one thing to exist within the machine.
I get it. It's the entertainment business.
Can any of you breathe without utter reliance and codependency on the machine anymore?
What the fuck man?
It's crazy.
It's fucking crazy.
Like it's sick.
No, it totally is.
It totally is.
Anytime anyone takes a stand on anything, I'm always like very impressed.
Like Jamie Lee Curtis today talked about the nepotism baby thing that's going around on Twitter.
And she's obviously one of the more famous nepo babies.
And she was just like, I've been busting my ass in this business for 40 years.
And like, please be kind to people.
It's a really long post.
And I thought, why would you take this swing?
And then I thought no good on you for taking the swing.
Even if I don't agree with somebody, just voicing an opinion is kind of novel nowadays.
And of course, everyone was like, oh, you know, wait a stand up for the disenfranchised billionaires, Jamie Lee or what?
Oh, shut the fuck up.
By the way, that's all people that are pissed off that they're not getting something for nothing.
Of course, that's all those people are like everybody shut up.
I love the post, but I got to say, and I do want to get to the rocks Instagram and a bit here on the show.
But like Jamie Lee Curtis, for having a career with massive successes in the genre of action, horror, comedy, drama, romantic, sitcoms, she has done it all.
She has been really great in almost everything she's ever been in.
And she's up there feeling the need to defend herself at age 75.
The day before Christmas, it's this, this business destroys people's brains.
And it does.
Like she's sitting there and she's like, I got to defend myself.
You know, it's like, no, Jamie, you don't.
Everyone loves you.
Get off Twitter.
Well, also the same.
Also to you.
Yeah, she doesn't need to defend herself.
Number one, number two, the business destroys people.
Number three, this internet life is destroying everybody.
Why is why are 75 year olds?
Why are 45 year olds participating in this ship?
But we are all of that.
And then lastly, you got to imagine at the breakfast table, Christopher Guest would be like Jamie.
Shut your fucking phone off.
He's supposed to be a miserable man.
No, I feel like he was just like, baby, I batted way out of my league.
Yeah, he probably does.
That's good.
Whatever you want.
Yeah.
But uh, the, uh, but here's the thing.
Jamie Lee Curtis.
Nepotism of who?
Like, like, I get it.
Her parents were actors.
She's, her parents weren't wildly fucking famous.
And Jamie Lee Curtis.
Tony Curtis was.
I mean, so Tony Curtis was.
But, but, but.
But here's my point.
It's when she came on the scene in the 70s.
Their name is Matt Moore.
That's sure.
Of course, but here's my point.
It's like saying Carrie Fisher was a nepotism, baby.
Jamie Lee Curtis.
Was considered a set of tits.
By this industry.
Forever.
Yeah.
It's people are like, oh, you had it so easy with what?
You, she starred repeatedly in the same movie in and out of the, of a franchise.
Yeah.
You know, and movies that mimic that franchise.
She, she's in a, I can remember four movies that weren't Halloween related or horror related
that she was in that, that, that made a mark.
Maybe.
Like, I mean, well, she's going into places but, but, but her role there, she still has to stand in front of a mirror
and take her shirt off.
That's what I'm saying.
Pointless tits in movie history.
I, I've paused it a billion times.
But it was really, in my opinion, fish called Wanda where anyone treated her with any respect.
They were like, oh, she's really gifted.
But I didn't even remember she was in it.
Like, but my, that, and that's not, I'm not disparaging her.
My point is is people are talking as if she's like, Katie Perry or something.
It's like, the average, I got news for you.
The average young person these days probably doesn't know who the fuck Jamie Lee Curtis is.
The business and Halloween brought her back.
Sure.
To, to, to, to an extent, to an extent, but my point is it, but, but even that Halloween,
it's like a direct -to -paramount plus or whatever the fuck it was.
A sequel series.
Yeah.
It's like, my point is it's like, what are we talking about here?
Like, she's had a pretty regular style career for people that get into the business.
And the only reason she's been allowed to work into her 60s and 70s is because
into her 50s even is because she was in a famous horror franchise.
That's it.
If it wasn't for Halloween, we would not hear a goddamn thing from Jamie Lee Curtis.
Yeah, that's true.
And I think, you know, this, this bacon daughter who was in smile and, and a few of these other
new on the scene up and coming nepotism babies.
It's like, yeah, I don't think after smile, unless they do smile too with her.
And I, well, I don't want to say what happens to her, but I mean,
we're not going to be seeing a lot of the bacon sedgwick daughter, you know?
It's like it, it doesn't make them, it doesn't mean because you have parents that are famous or rich,
you're going to be Julia Roberts.
You still have to excel.
The big argument now is, but the hardest thing is getting your foot in the door.
And these people were born with their foot in the door.
That's valid.
Sure.
But have you never gotten a job because somebody recommended you, you know?
I guess it's like, it's like being mad.
I understand the initial sentiment, but when you really step back and look at it, yeah.
It's like being mad.
Look, the one positive thing I had to say about clerks three, and I can't remember if I said on the show was,
look, I guess Kevin Smith putting his daughter and all this stuff is like his version of like, honey,
I'm leaving you the carpet cleaning business here.
It's yours now.
And I think that's actually cool.
I don't think it's in a big bar with him is probably guilt about being away from his kids.
So you bring them on set.
I get that to.
So either way, it's like, I don't think it's a particularly good business.
It's lucrative, but so I can knock that part of it, but like,
I'm not mad at the guy for like handing the keys to the kingdom to his daughter.
I just wish he did it with a better product.
So I like a better daughter, frankly.
Well, she's, I don't got no problem with.
I said, she's not a movie star, Joe.
Well, I don't think, but I don't, but here's my point.
I don't think she's going to be, and I don't think anybody is saying to us, she's a movie star.
I think she's going to take over Kevin Smith's thing.
And like, that's, that's what it is.
That's fine.
My point is, is Tony, Tony Curtis doing bring your daughter to work day.
But his work is the set of, you know, whatever.
Some like it hot.
And the kid is Jamie Lee Curtis.
And that's how she learns the way of dad's job.
Yeah.
Who cares?
Like, that's what everybody does.
If I wanted to do what my dad did, I would have had a way to get into it.
I didn't want to do it.
So I didn't do it.
Kind of agree.
You know, and I would guarantee.
Good.
A lot of the people complaining yesterday are working with or for their parents.
A lot of people.
A lot of people's dads turn their business over to them.
Or they make a call.
You know, it's just all the.
I don't know what to say anymore.
I feel all our industries and society is collapsing around us.
And it's Christmas.
You, we have, we have created.
A capitalistic, fully curated, pampered society.
Where everybody across the board, no matter what their social status is,
feels they deserve the absolute best of everything at all times,
regardless of work or effort put into the equation.
Yes.
They think that their pity is equal despite how bad their situation is compared to others.
They think that everything that they are gifted is deserved and not earned.
Or, or not a privilege.
And here we are.
And that's the end of it.
And the grownups are no better than the children.
And, and we're all on the same boat.
Mary fucking Christmas everybody.
And that boat is sinking bitch.
She's sinking fast.
So anyway, I'm drinking.
I'm not.
It's 11 a .m.
But I might get there at some point.
I was sold this bill of goods every year.
You know, obviously I was, I was married and, and you go up to her neck of the woods for some holidays.
And I would go home to Missouri for some holidays and blah, blah, blah.
Last year I went home for Christmas.
But everyone always says you see it on Twitter.
You hear your friends rave about it.
Oh my god, Los Angeles, when everybody goes away at Christmas, it's what you always dreamed the city would be.
You can cruise, you know, put the, the top down and just cruise down the streets in the highways and you're waving at cops and there's, you know, beautiful thing.
I drove because I wanted to experience this magic.
I've mostly been staying in the house, but I called my buddy up yesterday and I said, hey, let's go see a movie.
Let's go cruising.
Yeah.
I go to the movie theater that is 10 minutes from my home and it takes me 48 minutes to get there.
Well, all the sides are canceled to bumper traffic.
And then I got trapped in the parking garage because you get on, it's like there's only spots on P8.
So then you get stuck on P2 going up.
You can't leave and you can't go forward.
We wound up seeing a movie that started like an hour later.
It's just, it's.
You just get no peace.
You know, and then I realized, well, okay, because this.
Yeah, every flight canceled.
I'm glad I didn't wind up going home because I would have to deal with all that shit anyway.
And I think it's four degrees and snowing and Missouri.
But.
It was just a huge.
Let there was traffic coming home after the movie, like at 10 p .m.
And I think a lot of people came to LA because there's honestly seems like more people.
Like, let's get out of this snow and cold and go to the sun.
And then you wind up.
If you could see this in my zoom, I mean, you can't see it at home, but you could see a pet.
This illuminated stack.
Yes.
I wish the people at home could see this.
The, the illuminated stack sounds like a terribly boring Sundance movie.
These are all my gifts for my family that I can't see.
And just by some sort of strange artistic chance.
Yeah, the sun is coming in in a way that they are completely washed out and they just look like non -existent.
As if to say, you have no family, you have nobody for Christmas.
These gifts never existed.
It really looks like a ghost is there.
Yeah.
I'm about to start opening the gifts I bought for other people.
And just having a party by myself in here.
I was wondering what this was going to do to my mental state to be isolated in Christmas.
And we're seeing it after that capitalism rant.
Yeah, no, it's, it's not great.
I mean, I think I might have a friend or two coming over later and I might go out to a bar or something.
Oh, good for you.
I've done my best, you know, to like try to try to try to not give into my vices.
My therapist is always lately.
He hit me with something.
He was like, why do you want to feed your, because we do a lot of inner child stuff.
Look, it helps me.
Why do you want to feed your inner child.
Drugs and alcohol.
Oh, shut up.
And I'm like, oh, that's a valid point.
But to go fuck himself.
Yeah.
Well, maybe because I was like, I'm not going to molest him.
I'm not trying to like liquor him up and molest him.
I'm just, you know, give me a break here.
I would soothe him, calm him down a little bit with a couple glasses of jack.
You should be like, I'll tell you what would help me not do that doc.
Maybe a gig where I con people for 700 bucks an hour to spew bunch of bullshit from a leather armchair.
Say that to him.
Yeah.
Uh, no, he's a very nice guy.
He doesn't listen.
I don't know where I care.
He's done, done a lot for me.
Um, no, but, uh, I've been trying as, as I say, as you and I both say every week,
we're always at some different point in our struggle with, uh, our various vices.
And yes, or two days ago, I was sitting at home.
I was having a real rough day.
You know, you get to the end of the year.
I just want to get to 2023, as I was saying on the solo movie quarry yesterday.
I know it's stupid and meaningless, but like there, I need that fresh start of the new year,
because this year's just not doing it, not getting it done.
So I'm sitting there in a really bad mood.
And I was like, I don't think I'm going to be able to make it to the new year without drinking or doing some weed.
Yeah, no, no.
So I walk in after a pretty long hiatus.
I got to say, I drink with Joe and Florida because you have to drink with Joe and Florida.
But I take the edible.
And I take a pretty good amount and I hadn't done it in a while.
And I sit in the couch and I'm like, just watch some Christmas movies.
This feels like a rough anxiety day.
Just get high and chill.
And as it's kicking in, I get a delivery from St. Louis, two different relatives, my sister and my aunt,
both sent me gooey butter cakes, full cakes from.
So if you're from St. Louis, you'll know this.
It never made it out of St. Louis.
It's the most delicious cake in the world.
My mom makes the best one ever.
And my mom is a terrible cook.
But it's a delicious, delicious cake.
And I got sent two of them.
It's basically made with like four sticks of butter, you know, like that's the driving force of the cake.
And I'll tell you, Joe, I had one piece.
I walked across the street to my neighbors, whom I love.
I gave them the cake.
They were touched.
We hugged.
It felt great.
And I think last year or even last month, I would have devoured that cake.
I would have flipped it into the air like a peanut and eaten the entire cake.
I felt proud of myself.
Oh, good for you, Pat.
And then what did Joe say to me?
Eat those cakes.
Yeah, I mean, that's the text I get.
That's my support system.
There's my sponsor.
I'm on my six cakes.
I'm on my second glass of wine after a three donut breakfast.
I'm not the guy to tell me what donuts you got.
Make me hard, Joe.
I got a, I got a half dozen from Duncan.
I got two Boston creams, two sugar candies.
Duncan's the king in my book.
Let's not argue about it.
We shut up.
Make it your own donuts in your own head.
All right.
But you know, I like Duncan.
The Boston cream.
I'm trying to get a taste buds spin off.
Go and try to get some of that cash.
The.
Duncan is my favorite.
The Boston cream at the Duncan is my favorite donut of all time.
I got two of those two pow two sugar jelly, not powder jelly.
I hate powder jelly.
I got a glaze and a glazed blueberry.
So I did that.
I was blueberry.
Yeah, I did the jelly that the blueberry and the.
And the.
It's a.
Yeah, it's right.
The Boston cream.
Or the Boston cream rather, I would have done.
If, if I'm going, I do an apple, fritter and a coffee to me,
there's just nothing better or.
That'd be great.
I like a cake donut.
And especially a cake donut with a little butter, scotch icing.
On the top.
I like that.
I like where you're talking.
I like it where it's like just a.
You know, it's heavy.
The heavy pussy.
Weighty, girthy.
Donut, that's what I like.
And when that cream hit, no, Okay, and I'm buying a Atari game on eBay today to dress
myself for Christmas.
It's called.
So Atari, my favorite system to collect, where out of all the systems I own is the Atari
2600.
I just, it's just very nostalgic.
And I really like playing the system and blah blah blah.
I have fun.
This is Joe's time.
I'm going to get a coffee.
Wait, I know I want you to hear this.
Oh, well, Joe, this is generally where I tune out.
No, no, no, no, you'll like this.
You trust me.
Just trust me.
That's the only reason I'm bringing it up.
No, come.
But the Atari, when it was out, it was the Wild West.
There was no like, you'd have to be licensed
to make a product for the system.
You could just make a game for it and like, that was it.
There were no laws in place.
So there are some very strange video games
for the Atari 2600 and I found onto very accidentally
on eBay today.
I found a guy who's selling a lot of unopened,
never opened, never played Atari 2600 games
from 1983 of an erotic nature.
What?
Yeah.
I'm buying one called beat them and eat them, right?
So like, and it's got a woman on the front cover,
like, it's never released.
No, no, they were released.
They're just rare.
They're like adult in the adult section or something.
Like they were born or what?
I guess.
I didn't know.
I don't know.
Like, is I don't remember?
Anyway, I was like, this looks, this looks interesting.
I want to see what this is.
It's, I'll never see this again.
I should buy one of these.
I look it up on YouTube.
Yeah.
It's a real game.
Beat them and eat them is a game.
I'm not kidding.
Where you control three women on the bottom of the screen
who are naked and have their heads turned to the sky
with their mouths open.
As a man up top goes back and forth with his full dick out
shooting loads down.
And you have to catch the seabed loads.
Okay, that's the game.
And you've ordered this.
I'm going to order it.
I mean, that's nuts that that was a video game that came out.
That's fucking crazy.
Yeah.
Well, isn't that incredibly rare and valuable at this point?
The guy has three of them.
He's selling them.
You can buy one.
You can buy one or all three if you want.
He's selling them for like 90 bucks a piece.
It's not that valuable.
But it's like valuable enough that I had to make a decision
about whether I wanted to spend the money.
Oh, I don't think it's just valuable just on the street.
But to the right by.
I feel like it's a it's a bragging rights thing to pull off the shelf.
Yeah, she's kind of weird.
When you're trying to romance a special young lady.
Yeah, I say, baby, let's play this in real life.
Yeah, okay.
If she wasn't swept off her feet by the Atari collection, folks.
The the jizzing game really brought her to her knees.
I don't know.
Shit.
Oh, I got to say I went and saw Metallica with our buddy Vince Avril.
This.
Well, I was excited.
The only time I ever saw them, they opened for Stevie Wonder,
which was at a festival, but it still was like not quite ideal.
But they were fun and I was so far in the back that it was weird.
So I was excited.
It's a small venue and it's a charity show.
And I went with my buddy Tim, my buddy Vince.
They're like the tickets were at pricey, you know,
but I'm like, look, an intimate concert with a rock and roll
grates before it's too late to see them.
This is going to be great.
Go in.
The openers are Greta van Fleet.
Who are the they are like 19 years old.
They're doing a Led Zeppelin impression and they pretend they've never heard of Led Zeppelin.
You know, one of those guys, who's Led Zeppelin and then they're like,
they'll play stairway to heaven with different lyrics, you know.
Little brats.
Yeah.
But you know, honestly, I hadn't heard their music outside of their SNL appearance.
And they're good showmen.
I didn't I don't remember the songs, but you know,
Katie had a good voice.
I'm not standing up for them.
I'm just saying, compared to what's coming,
I had I appreciated that they tried because then out came.
For we think it's going to be a Metallica,
but first we watch a 20 minute filmed piece about their charity.
What is their charity?
I don't it's, you know, helping kids off this.
Metal for life.
Yeah, exactly.
It probably lines their own pockets, you know,
it's one of those write -off deals clearly.
But then outcomes.
Jimmy Kimmel, who's hosting the night.
And I'm like, you know what?
That like I realize,
Metallica is not going to be like seeing them at CBGB's or something at this point, you know.
You're when you're seeing a band of this size,
there's going to be a little corporate element to it that you're not thrilled about.
But for me, Metallica is those first four five albums.
Up through the black album.
That's, that's where I love them.
That's what I want to hear.
That's what I'm there for.
So to have Jimmy Kimmel in a suit,
fucking come out.
It's like,
all right, this is not going to be the night I envisioned at all.
And then Jimmy Kimmel introduces Robert Downey, Jr.
Who comes out.
He gave, I swear to God,
the same speech he gave about Durand Durand on the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame ceremony
that aired on HBO.
He just changed the name.
He changed it from, you know, pop to rock it.
But the same exact speech.
Folks, give it up for the hardest rock and band and show business.
Robert Downey, Jr.
You know,
and I'm happy about had it with Robert Downey, Jr.
I got to say I've had it.
I've had more than enough Robert Downey, Jr.
I hate that he has just given up on acting.
He's just doing only Marvel now.
It's like what or do little.
This is not what we wanted you back for Bob.
Anyway, he's in Oppenheimer.
Maybe that'll be good.
Crumbholtz is in it too.
I'm excited to see it.
But I'm very happy for Crumbholtz.
Am I excited to see a four hour and 15 minute Nolan dream sequence epic?
I don't know whatever they know.
Yeah, I hear you.
I'm being nice.
But David has a big part in it.
Yeah.
Very excited for David does.
Very much.
Metallica finally comes out.
And by the way,
I don't I don't want to sound obtuse.
I know some of you are probably thinking,
oh, it sounds kind of cool to see Robert Downey, Jr.
I get it.
L .A. is just a place where these things happen a little too much.
And they celebrities kind of decool things a lot.
So already the night felt,
I felt like I was out at like a charity gala with my mom and dad.
You know, that's that's the vibe of the night at this point.
And we had, you know,
we had gone to have a great night.
And we were all just getting grumpier and grumpier.
Then Metallica comes out.
And sits down.
And out comes the acoustics.
And you don't realize how dumb those lyrics are till you hear them stripped away
from all the,
the excitement, you know, the music.
When he's up there like,
I'm like,
I dub the,
how did I look past how stupid that sounds for all this time.
But stripped away these millionaires up there,
billionaires probably.
I got to thinking about the old Napster days and fucking Lars.
And you know,
even if I agree with some of their points,
it's just how smug and awful they were throughout that period.
And I just started to hate these guys.
And then they left the stage after four songs.
They're gone.
We watch another clip package.
Outcomes Kimmel to do some more stick.
There's like a bidding that goes on like an auction.
The Metallica comes out plays three rockers that were great.
I'll give them that end of show.
Did they play the new song?
Probably.
Did they play?
I was too busy screaming.
St. Anger.
I can't believe you wanted that song to take up real estate in this.
I'm obviously kidding.
I never heard the album.
And I don't like the song.
Oh, well, then you you.
So you were joking when you texted me that you said,
I hope my old friend St. Anger makes an appearance.
And I almost was like,
what the fuck are you talking about?
I thought you were serious.
No.
Also St. Anger is my alt ego that comes out various times throughout the day.
All right.
We need to get to this movie corner.
Let's go.
I got Christmas stuff to discuss.
All right.
Folks, yesterday the movie that I drove an hour to see is called Babylon.
Yeah.
It's the new one from Damien Chazel, which I was excited about.
I think Whiplash is amazing.
I liked first man.
And I liked La La Land.
So.
Man's man's three for three.
You know.
This movie.
I didn't know much about.
I saw it.
It was a trailer.
I had no idea what it was about.
It's Hollywood in the 20s, the early days.
And then.
You realize that they're just doing the same shit that so many other movies have done,
which is telling the story of how sound.
Came to the movies.
How the talkies came and people weren't equipped for it or whatever.
Who cares?
But you're also like.
I would, you know, I was like,
that's the plot of singing in the rain.
And then they start referencing singing in the rain all the time.
And you're like,
OK, so he knows he's ripping off singing in the rain.
Then there's things that are such rip offs in this movie that I was like,
OK, then this is all like a love letter to the movies where he's ripping shit off.
It felt like that.
And I know Tarantino early Paul Thomas Anderson.
They used their influences pretty heavily.
But they had their own take on it.
This thing was a God damn mess from start to finish.
I said to my friend,
it felt like three hours of deleted scenes from a movie that we did not watch.
You know, like when you watch like a,
like the other cut of Anchorman,
and it kind of doesn't make sense,
but it's still kind of funny and you hang in there.
That's what this was.
There's so much sex and nudity and disgusting shit in it that it holds your attention to the end.
I mean, it's, it's nearly x rated,
which I was not expecting at all,
because this guy's movies are kind of square.
La la land and shit.
Margot Robbie from,
she's teetering for me on the Adam Scott thing we were talking about earlier.
It's just like, I'm just see it's Adam driver is way down that road at this point.
I can't look at Adam driver anymore.
I hear you.
Robi, I'm just like,
Oh, enough.
I totally hear you.
She can still, you know,
hate to mail gays you,
but she can still kind of take your breath away.
She's a beautiful woman.
Cares.
I mean, yeah,
but in this movie and in most movie,
Amsterdam and Wolf of Wall Street and all this stuff,
she's doing like,
oh, wait, she's in Amsterdam too,
which is the other movie I keep confusing with the other three hour movie
that you don't know what it's about.
Yeah, they look,
it looks like one big movie,
and she's in that one too.
So,
Amsterdam is the one that opens with Chris Rock, right?
Yeah, Amsterdam is terrible.
Air, Amsterdam is worse than Babylon.
It may open with,
that trailer kills me because it's the first six seconds is Chris Rock.
And then you never see him again in the last six seconds.
It's to near over about of nowhere and you never see him at any other point.
That's, that's what the movie is.
Taylor Swift walks into frame and then gets hit by a car.
And you're like,
why was that girl Taylor Swift?
It's all ridiculous.
So Babylon's better than that,
just because of how hedonistic and crazy it is.
Margot Roby,
a big running thing in this movie is that she keeps icing down her nipples.
So,
I gotta tell you Joe,
it does kind of matter that she's that hot because
that'll hold your attention.
Margot Roby walking around with iced nipples for an hour.
It's,
and it's,
the movie starts with,
it seemed like the exact same scene from licorice pizza,
where they're trying to get a truck up a hill.
In this case,
they're trying to bring a truck with an elephant up a hill to get to a party.
And then it loses control and starts to go back down.
We just saw this scene in licorice pizza.
That's how this movie starts.
Then the elephant,
we close in on its anus.
Like it's Freddy got fingered.
It opens and starts spraying them with shit and turds.
And I'm like, what's going on?
Because the movie's three hours and 15 minutes.
So you're just not expecting a big elephant shit gag at the beginning.
Yeah.
From there.
There is a,
and that's when you said,
oh, this is about the talkies being invented.
Yes.
That was the giveaway.
There's no story at all.
Really other than that,
the talkie thing.
There's 45 minutes of the movie is at this big party at the beginning.
We go from the elephant to a morbidly obese naked man getting pissed on.
Uh, she's pissing on his stomach.
Then she walks up and pisses into his mouth.
We are one minute into a three hour, 15 minute movie.
So from there, you know,
this party is a lot of people fucking a lot of nudity.
It's like an orgy.
The big producer of the time is played by Jeff Garland,
who feels very kind of out of place.
But he does look like an old -timey producer.
How is Garland?
I'm always a fan of,
he's a friend,
but I'm always a fan of seeing Jeff and stuff.
Is he, is he good?
He's good.
He's got a nice part.
Five lines,
but he's, he's in and out of the movie.
Does he get to be like.
He has just won an explosive thing.
The most,
he's like the calm,
cool, collected guy who's like,
let's, let's move it along.
Let's move the production along.
Okay.
But,
there's this actor who I know from a lot of HBO,
shit, a character actor named PJ Byrne.
I want to say,
but this part should have been Geomodys,
but there's this director character.
Oh,
Geomoddy was busy shooting his Verizon commercial.
Yeah.
Exactly.
He plays Ebenezer Scrooge in a new Verizon commercial.
It's one of the saddest things I've seen all year.
I hope he got handsomely paid.
But,
that's the scene that works is the first time
they're trying to do a scene of Margot Robbie.
They're trying to keep her nipples hard.
They're trying to introduce sound,
but it keeps blowing out the speakers
because they don't know how to work sound.
So, there's a 30 -minute sequence in the middle of it
that is,
kind of a masterpiece with this actor,
the director guy yelling at everybody and screaming.
And there are scenes in this movie that are awesome.
Some of them are lifted out of other movies.
They do,
Toby McGuire is in it at the end,
playing this like completely,
cooked up,
drugged out dude who lives above a cave
where people have orgies basically.
And Ethan Supply,
who you'll remember from the Kevin Smith universe.
Yes.
I'm a fan of Ethan Supply.
They do this for him by the way.
He's talking about physical transformation.
Yeah.
He got in shape.
Right.
Wow.
Yeah.
He's doing this hacking bit.
That's his whole bit.
So, while they're there to try to try to buy,
or they're trying to pay Toby McGuire back
or negotiate with him,
I won't spoil the details.
You spoil.
I don't give a shit.
Well, anybody listening can pause.
And you know,
you can't really spoil the whole thing.
There's nothing to spoil.
But this scene goes on
and you realize it's the buggy night scene
where they go to Alfred Molina's house
with the kid with the fireworks.
In this scene.
The kids got a musket.
Because it's what is it?
1915 or whatever.
It's Ethan Supply hacking.
So every time he goes.
And the hacks, then they jump instead of the fireworks.
And you go,
Oh, he was ripping off this scene.
And that was a small thin Chinese boy.
I'll just make it with a big fat white guy.
And nobody will tell the difference.
Or maybe it is an explicit homage.
I don't know.
It's not a robbery scene, right?
A drug robbery.
It's Joe.
That's basically what it is.
It's drugs and money.
And they're bringing money.
So you're like,
like, give me that bottle of H.
It's 1922, see?
It's not like buggy nights.
It's very, very weird to start your movie
ripping off licorice pizza,
which came out a year ago.
And Andrew movie ripping off buggy nights,
which came out 30 years ago.
And they're both made by the same director.
And I don't know if he's doing interviews
where he says this is intentional.
I'm not sure.
But it felt weird.
The movie doesn't really get boring even at three hours,
15 minutes.
I got to give it some credit.
Like it's just so crazy that you keep watching it.
But this is the same thing that happened in Amsterdam.
I think what happens is they tell these young white guys.
These white writer,
writer,
writer directors, writer directors.
Hey, we like your script.
We want to make it.
You need to write in a sizable,
meaty role for a diverse performer.
So in Amsterdam,
it is John David Washington,
Denzel Sun.
In this movie,
there's this big jazz subplot
where there's, you know,
the black house band and the guy who is leading the band
is, is quote, not black enough.
And they make him put on shoe polish and et cetera.
We follow that story.
We follow the story of this Mexican immigrant.
Really, it is his story.
So I'm mentioning characters or who I haven't even talked about yet.
They all get their own little movie.
But it's too much.
It was the same in both cases that you're not following any real story
because I think they're trying to shoehorn in too much.
And obviously at three hours,
15, we could have cut this by over an hour and not lost much.
I don't think.
But it is about the excess of Hollywood
and how it'll chew you up and spit you out.
Interesting movie.
I'm tired of hearing about.
I'm tired of having the finger -wagging lesson
of Hollywood's dangers being told to me
by the most successful people in Hollywood.
I've about had enough of that.
You know what I just realized?
I just talked about that movie for five minutes
and I didn't mention Brad Pitt,
the star of the movie.
That's how fucked up this movie is.
Like you don't know what you're watching,
moments a moment.
It's insane.
Yeah.
I love the people that have the power to change things potentially
or work outside of the system
with their millions of dollars telling me how bad this is.
Yeah, exactly.
Fuck off.
A system that gave you $150 million to make a movie
that will lose easily 100 easily
and not win any awards
and just kind of be a weird failure.
I was going to do all Christmas movies,
but I'm actually only going to do one Christmas movie.
I'm going to save it for the end.
But I'm going to move into.
One thing I want to ask you before you do, Joe.
There's a scene in the speaking of Pitt
where he screams that it is a wife.
Raises his hand to.
Fuck you.
That's my name.
You go out to another homage.
No.
All right.
But he raises his hand to hit her
and he's screaming at her.
Fuck you.
And that's what he's in the tabloids about now
for hitting Jolly and the kids.
I'm like, do you think Pitt made the call
to have that scene cut out of the movie?
I would if I was Pitt.
I didn't even know he was in the tabloids for it.
Oh, yeah, like it.
There's, I mean, it's not ruined his career, I guess.
But I was thinking the other day,
has any star at his level had as many flops?
He said multiple huge flops.
Roy and Astra.
Maybe Troy made money.
I don't know.
I actually like it's, you know,
I look, I can't say whether he did it or not.
Hopefully he didn't.
It doesn't help the case.
When the woman accusing you of doing this,
painting a mural with Billy Bob Thornton's blood on a wall.
True.
But I mean, I, I believe, you know,
I don't think he's made any denial of it.
He was drinking too much and screaming at his kids.
And Joey goes, excuse me to the reporter.
Excuse me, go back to making out with her brother.
Yeah.
Yeah, exactly.
That was a weird period for her.
And he goes, by the way,
I don't talk to my father because he's a Republican.
Rob.
You think Billy Bob Thornton sees Brad Pitt's movies or not?
I wouldn't.
Billy, if it was anybody else,
I would say he definitely know hard feelings.
Billy Bob is the guy that there's,
he carries some feelings around.
Yeah.
I miss him.
I guess he's doing that fucking Goliath show.
It's like, you know, it's, it's just the same as Marvel.
Once they go to TV,
you lose them too.
Because we lost,
will you make me see when he started getting that sweet money?
We lost GMati when he started getting that sweet billions of money.
And now this, it sucks.
I'm not.
All right.
I'll save my Christmas thing to, to the last one.
But I'm going to review.
Because you mentioned a movie of hers earlier.
And, and this is on theme of a movie at the time that bombed.
And that everybody said was forgettable.
And everybody said was one of her worst things that she had ever done.
But you watch it now and you go,
we'd be so lucky to get a movie.
This will put together.
Nora F. Ron's lucky numbers.
I enjoyed it.
Lisa Kudrow.
John Travolta.
The great Adam Resnick, who wrote cabin boy with Chris Elliott.
Yeah.
John Travolta.
Lisa Kudrow.
Tim Roth.
And Michael Moore in a dramatic role.
Well, comedic role.
But it, you know, very, very interesting.
I mean, this is a film about, you're waiting for it to say,
based on a true story.
It never does.
But it's a film about a local weatherman played by John Travolta,
who is the big fish in the smallest pond.
The initial gag.
Where they translate that to you is his opening voice over.
And he says, and I've got my own booth at the hottest breakfast,
bistro in town.
And he pulls into Denny's.
You find out that he's actually in financial straits,
because he doesn't manage his money.
Well, his boss is played by who?
Oh, wait, somebody.
Somebody notable plays his boss at the station at the TV station.
I'm blanking on who it is at the moment.
I haven't seen it in 15 years.
Anyway, Lisa Kudrow plays the lottery woman at the station that he works at.
She is.
She plays sort of a very fun turn from Lisa Kudrow.
She plays like a very duplicitous plotting, like,
skipping sort of money -grubbing demonistic type of woman.
You don't see her play that very often.
I'm going to say it once more, Jonah.
And I know your lost cause on sopranos.
I want you to watch that first season of the comeback
before the year is up.
You can be obsessed with it.
All right.
That's what I watch.
I watch.
I can see he's not before the year season is a true masterpiece.
I'll watch.
But anyway, she's great in this.
He's Travolta's great.
I know I've said it about Travolta before.
I'm like, you forget what a good actor the guy is.
Like, when you see him in a decent movie.
You're like, God damn, he's a good fucking actor.
Yeah.
They're both great.
And it's a fun movie.
They rigged the lottery to cure their financial.
You know, we're at woes.
And, you know, of course, things go wrong.
Every single thing that could possibly go wrong goes wrong.
Tim Roth plays a strip club owner, proprietor slash possibly pimp.
Michael Rappaport in a great role as like the hitman.
Sort of, you know, gun for hire that they get wrapped up it with.
And everything goes awry there.
It's just a fun movie.
It's funny enough.
It's got some more in tone to the the ice harvest with Billy Bob
and John Q.
And Randy question.
It's like that.
It's like what's the it's like the what's the downy junior movie.
Where he loses his fingers in the door.
Remember, remember, there's the there's the gag where the door shuts on his hand.
He loses a finger.
Kiss kiss bang bang.
Yes.
It's like, yes, sort of like this is bang bang.
It's kind of like, you know, it's that kind of thing.
But yeah, so fun enough.
Enjoyable.
Efron.
I would say at the helm takes it to from being.
She puts the the the layer of she not or she puts the sheen on it that takes it
from being a forgettable movie to a memorable one.
And again, just just a can't stress enough.
This is a movie that came out and I don't know early odds or late 90s or something.
And, you know, considered a bomb and considered a.
Considered a a blemish on her on her pretty sterling record.
I feel like I killed a great run for Travolta to and his career never got back.
He had he's had so many ups and downs throughout it.
But it killed his pulp fiction heat.
I remember.
Yeah.
But you get it now.
I mean, it would be like this.
This would be a fucking treat to get something.
And it will straighten.
And O 'Neill.
At O 'Neill plays the star manager.
Yeah.
And then Bill Pullman plays the dumb cop.
I forgot about that.
Pullman plays the cop that's like on the case.
And he's so fucking stupid.
He doesn't even realize like what's happening.
I don't like.
I like Pullman.
Just always have.
It's very.
It's like this.
I remember when I was watching this.
I was like, I've never seen Pullman play a dumbass before.
And this.
It's a great.
He's really good at it.
He's really good at playing dumb in real life.
Which is why I.
It's like he honorees.
They excel at playing dumb.
Yeah.
So.
No offense to you.
Bill Pullman.
I'm sure it's listening.
Anyway, lucky numbers.
Lucky numbers.
I saw a picture.
For my consideration.
And for yours.
Bones and all.
Directed by Luca Guadaguino.
What a.
Yeah, I guess.
I got the screener on the shelf.
Tell me it's good.
And I'll watch it.
But.
It's decent.
Guadaguino did call me by your name.
And this is the one we've been talking about where it's like.
They made these movies with Army Hammer.
And then suddenly are doing a movie about cannibals.
Yes.
That's what this is.
It focuses mostly on a young woman.
At first.
Who.
Lives in a world where cannibals are around.
You know, it's it.
This movie's been compared to near dark.
And I think that's a very smart comparison.
Both in terms of it's vibe.
And also in terms of.
What it's what it's doing.
It's just doing it with cannibals instead of vampires.
So like you accept early on that it's a world where some people have this and some people don't.
Is it accepted in that you in the movie?
Is it like okay to be accountable?
No, no, no.
So, you know, you sort of discover this stuff as it goes.
There's not like a lot of action or much of a plot per se.
It's a movie about vibes.
And that is.
To me, why near dark is not.
You know, I don't consider it the masterpiece.
Many people do, even though I really like it.
Sure.
It just kind of sits there for me.
And that's what this did too.
Timothy Shalamay comes in at some point.
And basically him and this girl have a little cannibal love story where they go across the country.
And.
You know, it's.
I liked it.
You know, it's, I wish I had seen it in a theater.
It's clearly very well shot.
But it really is just a lot of shots of young beautiful cannibals driving a fine young cannibals, if you will.
Driving around.
Listening to cool music.
As the sun sets, you know, that's the kind of movie it is.
It's not really anything too deep, but I enjoyed it.
All right.
Did I talk about this?
In Florida, a gene shallot.
So I can pitch him a fine young cannibals to say in his review of bones and all.
Did I talk about this in Florida?
I don't think I did the world's end.
I rewatched the world's end.
Simon Pegg.
Oh, so did I, Joe.
What if we watched it on the same night?
What if we did?
That's really weird.
That's how we're working these days.
Is synergy, baby?
Yeah.
I got to say, man.
I know that Sean of the dead will always be considered the masterpiece of this trio of Nick Frost, Simon Pegg and what's his name?
The director.
That's right.
But I got to say, man.
This is the second or third time I've watched the worlds end.
I think this movie is awesome.
The first time I watched, I thought it was forgettable.
The second time I was like, God, it's a little better.
This third time, it really all kind of clicked for me.
Like, oh, wait a minute.
Like, this is what it all means.
And like, this is how they connect all the themes and the dots.
And God, damn it.
It's so good.
It's so funny.
It's so you got Pegg.
You got Frost.
You got Martin Freeman.
And they're at their, to me, it's them at their best.
You got Pegg playing.
I love.
Which one's constantly.
Well, then you got.
Eddie Marzahn.
I don't like that guy.
I don't like looking at him.
You know, which guy is which though?
Because I don't know who Marzahn's like the short squat.
Yes.
He's great.
I'm not a fan for some reason.
But, uh,
Patty Constanine is in.
One of my all time favorites, which is in America, which is a movie that is really slept on.
And not a lot of people have seen.
But he's the other friend.
He's the other friend.
I just love that guy.
And he was in Hot Fuzz as well, which.
To me, you know, it's a pretty flawless trilogy.
But I actively did not like the world's end when I saw it.
I saw it with Pete, the theater.
And just when I revisited it, I had your experience.
I was like, Oh, this is way better than I remembered.
But to me, it falls apart at the end.
I didn't agree.
The first half I love.
And to me, it falls apart at the end.
That's how I get more out of it on a third viewing.
But it lost me.
That's how I felt in the first two viewings.
And the third one.
I was like, Oh, this is the whole thing is the end.
And.
So anyway, it's, it's, so first of all, it starts with a pub crawl concept.
You've got peg playing an obnoxious asshole.
That's, he's excels at that.
Frost.
It is arguably.
It is in my top five, at least, if not top three, if not number one.
Favorite turns in movie history is frost playing the guy that is now sober.
And during this pub crawl, they realize that none of them want to be on accept.
I'm in peg who wants to relive the youth is glory of his youth.
And once I'm to complete this pub crawl, they never completed his kids.
During this pub crawl, they realize their town that they've gone back to that they grew up in has been infiltrated by these androids that are trying to take over.
And you don't really know why.
And that they're basically going to have to fight these things.
And they have a huge showdown with these things in the bathroom.
And frost who is vehemently sober through the movie.
That scene where they have the shots on the table.
And frost is like, I'm not doing any shots.
I've told you I've stopped drinking.
And then they go in the bathroom.
They realize what's happening.
They fight the roads.
They come out.
And as Simon Pegg is trying to tell them like, what do you think they need to do?
Nick Frost takes the tram shots and does all of them.
Yeah, breaks the sobriety.
And he's do after each one he makes this noise.
He goes.
It's one of the funniest fucking turns I've ever seen.
And then frost suddenly mid movie is shit faced.
And now they're working together.
It's awesome.
It's just seeing this duo that works together so beautifully in shot of the dead come back together.
In this movie, which this feels very much like an unofficial sequel to shot of the dead to me.
Because it's them against the world.
And you know, it's, it's, it's just a perfect balance of a movie to me that starts as a comedy about friends.
And, and, and youth and all that stuff.
And turns into a sort of horror adventure.
And through that hard adventure becomes.
About the deeper themes of reliving your youth and regaining glory and moving on from that and letting it go and why you should and why you shouldn't.
And showing all those different perspectives and.
I just fucking loved it, man, like I this last watch out this was I was like, I got to own this movie.
You know, that said it's, I would think it's going to take anybody a few watches to potentially get to that point if you do or don't, but I just really, really, really liked it.
And I think Simon Pegg is truly impeccable in the movie.
Like he impeccable, impeccable.
He, he nails that like he just get he just knit.
You're watching it. And I'm like, well, I didn't grow up in link London or wherever the fuck town in outside of London.
They grew up in in this movie or whatever he's playing a guy from, but he's playing a guy where you're like, I know this guy.
Yeah.
We all know this guy. We all know the guy that does this.
I think actually when I watch him, I'm like, am I this guy?
Yeah, you are.
Yeah, of course, we don't realize it, but in our groups of friends, yes, of course, we would both be that good.
So I just really loved it. And then I was what I was saying was was everybody's playing their best, like frost.
Playing a stiff who comes apart of the seams, like, that's my favorite type of Nick Frost.
Simon Pegg playing an obnoxious assholes, my favorite something.
Martin Freeman playing the like wound, like the way to buttoned up guy.
Is my favorite Martin Freeman.
I mean, who else is in this pierce Brahman?
What's your name from?
See that that's getting your name, but she's great.
The lady from the liberty.
Oh, yeah.
That element to me, the Brahman and the, you know, the special effects stuff at the very end of the movie.
That's what doesn't work for me.
Again, on a first and second watch, I agreed on the third one. I was like, Oh, this is.
This is kind of what it's about the fact that at the beginning of the movie.
And this is going to be spoiler, but the fact that at the beginning of the movie, it's about Simon Pegg's character calling himself the king and not being able to let go.
And everybody around him, particularly Nick Frost saying, let it go.
You're not a legend, you're a loser.
And Nick Frost being the guy that's like, I don't drink anymore because of what the damage you drinking did to us and all that stuff.
And he drinks water and Simon Pegg is so offended and blah, blah, blah, blah.
And then at the end of the movie, when the world has been ravaged and everybody's living in the post -apocalypse.
It's Nick Frost telling the story, the legend of Simon Pegg and saying they, you know, he's out there somewhere.
And now he reveres this man more than anybody else.
And then the final scene is Simon Pegg walking into a bar with the robots because now the robots that tried to take over have become the minority.
And of course, he's always going to be with the minority and him saying, we want four waters.
And then the guy going like, who are you? And he goes, they call me the king. I just, it gave me chills. I was like, this is awesome, man. I just really, really dug it. I really, really liked it.
I see myself revisiting. I love Sean the dead and hot fuzz.
And I like Scott Pilgrim. Beyond that, I've had some issues, but not fuzz upsets me because I don't like seeing Nick Frost playing a dumbass.
I don't like seeing him play dumb. I like him when he's more flippant and you know what I mean?
I do. I do. And Pegg's not any fun in hot fuzz. He's so like by the book. I'm like, I don't want to, I don't, I like peg when he's being a douche.
Like that's like the fun thing to me with him. Yeah, it's just, I mean, I need to rewatch it, but I just some of the action for as far as an action comedy goes, it's like the action is awesome. And I remember it being very, very funny. And they're being a great twist.
Joe, I move that we cut it at two and we get to our movie. And I think that movie should be violent night because I don't think we have the bandwidth to talk about three silent night deadly nights.
That I disagree with you. I mean, I know we got the energy. We got some fans rented and watched it.
What's what the silent night deadly night. All right. Well, let's do that. Okay, fair. I'll kick us off with this because this was going to be my third movie corner, but let's start the discussion.
And we will we're next movie, next episode in early January, we'll review violent night, David harbors violent night. Yeah, we saw it in Florida.
I watched the silent night. It's just called silent night, the remake.
Oh, okay, silent night deadly night. I texted you at the beginning of my watch. And I said, this is not a good movie.
And then about 30 minutes later, I texted you again. And I said, Pat, I was wrong. This movie is wild.
I didn't realize when you sent me that that it was a remake of silent night, deadline.
Oh, yeah. It's a it's a loose remake. And it's just straight up and down like a crazy Santa Claus is killing people. Yeah. And in the remake, they make everybody he kills.
This is why I was like this movie's dumb like because in the beginning they set up these characters who are the most obnoxious characters on her and you're like, what is this?
Like there's a 12 year old girl that's yelling at her mom. And she's like, get your fucking ass in the car and go buy me and you're like, this is stupid. What is this? And then Santa goes to the house.
The crazy Santa and murders the 12 year old kid and you're like, oh, now I get it. You're making everybody the kids killed awful. Right.
And and and all of their it's like a Rambo style thing where all of their deaths are so insane.
And it's it's a very, very fun goofy wild splatter house drive and remake recommended to me by one can't handle it.
Oh, okay. I don't.
But that's not what we're here to review. I would strongly suggest if you haven't seen Silent Night, go watch Silent Night.
We're here to review Silent Night, Deadly Night 3 and 4.
And and I rewashed 5, which I I just need to say again, I think Joe and I did a commentary on it once, but we did what a troubling film that is.
That not cracker assault is something I'll not soon forget.
Not cracker. It's how I referred to my third wife.
Oh, all right. So Silent Night, Deadly Night 3, we.
This is the plot of this. So, well, wait. Now, now the original is a young boy in the backseat watch as a man dressed as Santa.
That kind of run his family off the road sexually assault his mother murder his father and mother and and it's all right in front of him.
He grows up to be this Santa Claus killer. He dresses up and goes around town and kills people.
And he grows up in an orphanage with his baby brother where the nuns are also fucking in the orphanage and there's all kinds of physical abuse.
So he has this very charged traumatic childhood.
Something makes him snap a Christmas. He goes on a killing spree that movie ends with his brother witnessing his death.
And then in the second movie, it's supposed to be that his brother is now the in the sanitarium and is going to escape and become the killer, which he does.
As far as I can tell, it's not even on Christmas in the second movie, it's sunny California.
Right. But the second movie using huge chunks of the original in part two.
It's it's 45 minutes at least of footage from the original film.
But the second movie has the classic garbage day line.
They actually found the guy finally he was unreachable for years.
And they found the actor and the actor actually goes around now and does Q and A is about the movie, which I think is very cool.
And he dies at the end of the second movie now in the third movie.
We're in a again, sanitarium of some sort.
And we've got a doctor doing experiments on a man who's got played by Bill Mosley whose top of his head is cut off and he's got a.
He's a glass dome like Franken style ish Franken style ish excuse me.
Yeah, dome bolted onto his head that where you can see his brain.
You don't know who this man is. There's a girl.
If I may just say.
He was shot in the chest at the end of part two.
Okay. Why is his brain encased in a glass dome outside of his head in this one?
I don't know.
Shoot him in the head.
I'm shocked that this is the detail you're honing in on, but God bless.
Oh, it's the first of many.
He's got.
I'm going to get a little more wine, but tell them about the blind girl who has telekin.
I mean, it's just absurd.
It is a sadistic doctor.
A doctor giggles type, if you will.
Once to get inside the mind of Ricky, the Santa killer who is in a coma.
So naturally he brings in a blind clairvoyant girl who is the lead of our film.
This girl is an awful actress.
Awful.
I think she took the note that like to act blind, you need to just be listless.
It's like when somebody tries to act depressed and they're not a good actor.
It just comes off as boring.
This girl is such a bad actress.
This blind clairvoyant.
Joe, did you did you notice how terrible her scream was?
Terrible in what way?
Like, I mean, I've watched a lot of horror for this show through the years.
And on my own time, I have never heard a scream in a horror movie as pathetic as this girls.
The first one out of the bag, she's like, uh, I made me laugh out loud.
I can't believe you did not notice this.
I thought that girl who were basing this whole movie around is a terrible actress being asked also to play a blind girl and a clairvoyant.
And she's not good at just being an actress in the first place.
The blind part is so not committed to that it's literally in every scene they have to have a character go like, I'll help you with that because you're blind.
It's really just kind of like a secondary thought.
Yeah, she'll like open doors, you know, like just it's just that comes and goes.
Yeah, and then I'm convinced that they added the telekinetic part just so they could be like, it's not reading that she's blind.
And we have to like, how long does she know how to cook dinner?
They're like, she's got mental things that she can do.
It's never really quite explained or explored as to why there's this mental connection between her and Billy.
Is it all is it Billy?
Billy's the killer and Ricky black Christmas.
Okay, Ricky.
Yes.
I did also just rewatch black Christmas, which is a, if you haven't seen it, folks, Tyler Perry's, I'm a Dia's black Christmas. It's very good.
Sorry, I was going to tweet that yesterday.
Go for it.
No, but no, but it'll have a problem with that.
Yeah, canceled.
Anyway, it's interesting, but they never really quite explain.
So at the beginning of the movie, she's, you know, the doctor is putting her into through these tests, right?
Right.
So he can awaken the brain of Ricky.
Because they've reconstructed his brain and they, they, for some reason, want to bring him back to life so they can understand the killer or something.
So, so that part, I was like, okay, this is a wild wild.
It's what I just told them.
Sure. Yeah.
Yeah.
Um,
but well, I'm just, I wasn't here because I was getting one.
Because you were, because you have a problem.
Say it.
Just that, you know, later in the pockets, I'm just singing on my end.
Oh, you're so very, like, see shanties.
But my point is, is, is the connection is so strong that he goes to her grandma's house.
He gets there ahead of her.
Like he, he knows where she's going.
And like that's how deep their mental connection goes.
And they decided that they just didn't have to explain any of that.
So he does get, that's right.
He does get there ahead of her.
So is that okay?
So I guess it serves as more of a device that I'm remembering.
Like, it's just a pointless device.
You don't need it.
Like, it's crazy.
Like, it could just literally be, we've got this killer here.
We've got his brain hooked up to a fucking computer.
I mean, Jesus Christ.
The national ambulance vacation, the original, they, they, they have the computer map out.
Video game style, their vacation route.
Right.
Just, just hook the guy up to a computer and say, we've awakened him through fiber optic, whatever the fuck.
And, and he's awake now and he's a killer.
And then he descends on the town.
Instead, they really go out of their way to establish, because you think the whole time it's going to be that she then becomes the killer in the end.
And the disease has passed along.
And that's not what it is at all.
It's just now.
Well, thank God, because that girl couldn't have played a twist in that character, since she couldn't do anything.
Do you think that that was the original?
It had to be, right?
It had to be the need to like open the door to continue this story.
Well, I had to be in reading the Wikipedia.
They had a script that became four, or you know, with some rewrites became part four.
And the director, Monty Helman, hated it.
They did like a one week rewrite and shot the new script.
So I think we're, we are seeing a very rushed production here.
Monty Helman, Monty Helman, yes.
Who has a movie in the criteria collection called Tulane Blacktop.
Oh boy.
What is Tulane Blacktop about?
It's a racing movie.
I haven't watched it.
A racing movie has made it criterion.
Get it get over yourselves.
Christ.
Anyway.
Yes.
Okay, so when I walked away, what part did you get up to?
No, we're good.
We're good.
But the original, I'm reading here, the original script was thrown out and rewritten in one week.
So basically the whole movie was put together in a matter of like a couple of months through editing and release.
Why are we having a hard time in this business getting our projects made?
Why?
That kind of stuff just doesn't happen anymore.
But how do you get into this part of the business?
How do we get hooked up?
Listen, we're too talented guys.
We know how to write something.
How do we get hooked up with full moon features?
Where it's just like guys, just pay us 10 grand and we'll bang out a script in a week and go make it.
We don't give a shit.
Well, it's about a werewolf that lives in a castle.
I don't care.
How do we get that gig?
I mean, the closest we could get would be like a shutter, I think.
And I don't know from what I hear.
I think their budgets are bare bones and that shows sometimes.
I'll take bare bones.
But now they're making cuts and stuff, which I mean, I'm really worried about.
They laid off much people.
Anyway.
All right.
So the brain dome guy, they're at the grandmas.
For me, this is where I realized I was just watching a very bizarre bad movie.
The first time this guy, we've been tiptoeing around the house and you never know what's where this guy's going to come out from.
And suddenly, his hand his fist comes punching through a door.
The front door.
The strongest door in the house.
The front door punches through the door.
There's no music.
There's no I've never seen a scare like that in a horror movie done just raw.
Just like it made it not work.
It just seemed like a mistake.
This fist comes punching through and you're like, what?
It wasn't scary or anything.
The movie does not work in any real way.
It's just kind of a sleepy mess.
It's it's a really.
You got to think this was not well, wait, no, because you just said it was rewritten in a week.
I mean, look, at first glance, you would say to yourself, this is not.
This was not meant to be a sequel for Silent Night Deadlet.
This was some goofy fucking sci -fi horror movie that they just shoehorned into this franchise, which quite frankly, three, four and five all feel like that.
But this was purposefully rewritten in a week's time to fit into this franchise.
So you can't say that.
Him punching through that door.
That really haunted me because throughout the rest of the movie, there are many times where after he has displayed the superhuman strength.
I don't understand why won't he just kill them?
The pinnacle of these examples being when a blind 19 year old girl is overpowering.
This guy punched through a door.
It's nuts.
It is so nuts.
And then her beefcake brother comes.
Oh my god, played by, as you pointed out, I didn't even realize the bad guy from Firewalk with me, I think, right?
Well, he's in the Twin Peaks show for sure.
I'm not sure he's in the show Firewalk with me too.
I believe he is.
He's the asshole boyfriend in.
In the show, right?
Yeah.
And I'm sure he's in Firewalk with me.
But the.
I think David Lynch, or at least his casting director, loves this franchise because in this movie, there's also Laura Herring, who I've rarely seen in anything else except Mulholland Drive.
She plays, you know, the other one Naomi Watts, she plays the busty Burnett.
And who did she play in this one?
The girl that.
The girlfriend.
The girlfriend who's introduced by bragging about how good her head is.
Like how good a dick she sucks.
And by the way, sister.
And by the way, when they get to the grandmom's house and the grandmom's missing.
Yeah.
They go.
She and the other Twin Peaks could person.
They go fucking the bathtub.
Because that's what you would do when your grandmom's missing on Christmas Eve.
It is wild with her, you know, with her sibling down the hall.
Why don't sister downstairs, you know, the.
Through both of these movies, three and four that we're going to be discussing, there are so many people that were in David Lynch.
Projects.
So I'm not kidding when I say I think that maybe he loved these movies.
The old lady from Winky's diner is in the next one who plays like Naomi Watts's mom from back home.
I read up on this and there was some.
And I don't remember exactly what it was.
And I don't want to try to pull it up now because it's going to take me too long.
But there was some sort of like kind of logical rational connection between Lynch and this franchise.
I forget exactly what it was.
It was something like.
It was something like Lynch's actor.
This person was the daughter.
And you know what I mean?
Like it was.
It was something like that.
But.
But anyway, this movie ends with Ricky dying.
Multiple times.
And then finally dying, I guess for real, which by the way, this was also clearly an attempt to, because I was saying earlier, maybe it was going to be to make the girl the new killer.
But maybe it wasn't.
Maybe they were doing the nightmare and I'm street four and five thing.
When nightmare and I'm street four and five brought in Alice as a character where Alice had a sort of visceral connection to Freddie, which was she had his dream baby in part five, but they were, they were connected, you know, in a, in a, in a greater way than any character had been connected to the killer.
I think in this one, actually what they were trying to do was make this young girl, the new, you know, they're Alice.
And they were clearly trying to make Ricky a new like sort of Freddie or something.
Because it's like, yeah, like let's have a crazy care.
What could make him distinguish?
Oh, well, what if you could see his brain and, you know,
that's his sort of Freddie claw or hockey mask or whatever, right?
Right.
And then it's just so bad, they never, they never brought it back.
Yeah.
Well, it looks stupid.
And like I said, he got shot in the chest, folks.
I gotta say, for a movie, this bad in this shitty.
Yeah.
It looks convincing.
Come on.
That's Bill Mosley's brain.
Like how they do that.
I don't know.
He also, he's got a thing like, like you would expect it to be like above his head.
You know, but it like, no, it's like symmetrical and everything.
It looks like where his brain would be.
I love that he was typecast as a guy whose brain was outside of his head
in the the 80s.
Excuse me.
Texas chance ought to as well.
Yeah.
And I think that's some stupid nod that they thought.
Oh, I see.
I don't know.
It's a, it's a bad film.
I would much rather talk about.
Silent night, deadly night for directed by the great Brian, you know, who did society.
It's time that society has gotten its cult.
You know, but it's time they give this man another shot at directing.
He's clearly what he does with a limited budget and and of screaming.
Mad George, who's this guy who does his effects.
Just some brilliant genius shit, especially.
For the fourth movie in a very shitty horror franchise.
I thought the creativity on display here, whether the story works or not.
And it doesn't.
He just, he gets better performances.
He does more with the money.
And I thought some of the gore and gross out stuff in this was.
Awesome.
Insane stuff.
It's one of the things I miss about the 90s and the 80s is they would restart the franchise in the middle of it.
Yeah, but it would still just be a sequel.
Yes.
So this is what Yuzna does because five is a loose continuation of four.
There is apparently what Yuzna rewrote and is doing here is a script that he turned in to be the third movie in the franchise, but that they didn't want to do it.
So it became four.
And it's a way better move.
Yeah.
So, but I liked when they did this instead of just nowadays, they would just go.
What's it been 18 months?
We'll just call it silent night, deadly night and start over again.
Right.
Yeah.
I like when they did it like this where it's like, no, we're just going to reset in the middle of the franchise and keep going here.
So this is a, this is an example of that part for outside of you see like a Christmas tree in the background.
It's got nothing to do with Christmas whatsoever.
I mean, they are.
You hints.
I mean, the lead is like proudly Jewish, which I thought was awesome because it's like like, like, Yuzna.
That's he, he makes the movies feel alive in a way that, you know, like I said, for being part four, I just, I was really impressed by.
But yeah, they talk about they, there's that anti -Semitic dad scene and stuff and their house is decorated with Christmas lights and stuff.
But for the most part, you're right.
It's a movie about giant bugs.
It's not a Christmas movie in any way.
Great cast in this thing.
Clean Howard, right off the bat.
Clean Howard.
You can't go wrong with clean Howard.
It's just, he's just so good at, he's just, he just, he just, he just has a thing about him.
Do get to see him sexually assault someone here, which I did not enjoy.
I didn't care for that.
But the guy just, the guy just got has a vibe.
I mean, when it starts, he's basically eating trash, if I recall correctly, and then a woman's body falls out of a window and spontaneously combusts.
And I was like, now see, that's how you open a picture.
This is a movie about a young woman, excuse me, who wants to, she works for a newspaper.
I would have married this woman.
She's not knowing anything about her.
I fell in love with this woman throughout the movie.
She's in a bunch of stuff.
And I got to just, I got to pull her up here and see what else she's been in.
Well, born in East LA, of course.
Nith Hunter.
I think she was a playboy bunny.
She was in, in the name of love, a Texas tragedy.
How I met my husband.
You know, these films.
These could be her big, her big fiction.
Any of these could be in the criterion, by the way.
Anyway, the lady for moon lighting is also in this.
Yeah.
The civil shepherd, the sidekick.
Who's great?
I always enjoy her and stuff.
But anyway, this is about, she played this, this, not the moon lighting lady.
Well, they became, you know who became the moon lighting woman, Jane Adams.
You know, look her up.
Look her up.
The lady from happiness, the sister, the mousey sister.
That, wait, that's the actor I'm talking about right now.
No, I'm saying that lady stole the lady from moon lighting's vibe and got a much longer career out of it.
Oh, I got you.
Okay.
See what I'm saying.
And she was just in, you've got mail flirting with Greg Canere on the interview show.
Oh, yeah, she plays.
Oh, okay.
She's Niles's girlfriend on Frazier.
Correct.
Yes.
Great actress.
She is great.
She's something new.
She's in tons of shit all the time.
She's great.
Yeah.
So niece Hunter plays this young.
Like she's like a newsroom girl at a newspaper.
Or a mailroom girl.
Excuse me.
And a newsroom.
And she wants to be a real reporter.
She wants to report on this girl who has spontaneously come to the street.
The boss is at work.
Why are you trying to bury this story about a woman spontaneously combust?
And I love all the, all the show vanistic mail bosses being like, that's not a story.
Come back to me when you got something hot.
Yeah.
One of the show vanists at the newspaper is played by you think who you think is a,
is a legend or a career comedy writer.
And you think is a stand -up comic that I grew up watching that I,
and who had one of my favorite jokes, he used to play on stage with a fiddle.
Okay.
He would do.
He would do bits in between fiddle licks.
And it always made me laugh.
He's written for SNL for a long time.
But one of my favorite Hugh think jokes he would do an impression of his dad.
And he was like trying to explain the time difference of living in L .A.
to his dad.
Uh -huh.
You're like, my dad calls me and he's like, hey, you.
It's four o 'clock here.
What is it?
11 o 'clock there?
Uh -huh.
Hey, Hugh.
It's 1982 here.
What is it?
1967 there?
Uh -huh.
That's a dumb joke.
But it, it really very loud.
And then he would do any young men losing, like getting slow.
Okay.
And he would get any young men just doesn't have it anywhere to go.
Take my wife.
For example.
Anyway.
Hugh thinks very funny.
It's weird.
Give me his email because I want to pitch him a game show that he hosts called.
Who do you think you are?
Beautiful.
Just put him back on the map.
I agree.
Uh -huh.
It's just funny seeing him in this playing a fucking asshole.
He's like.
He's the most harmless guy ever.
But anyway.
Um, so Nathan Hunter,
Nathan Hunter wants to break this story.
Reggie Bannister plays the editor in chief of the paper of Phantasm.
Okay.
That's Reggie.
It's good old Reggie from Phantasm.
Okay.
I don't know that.
So anyway.
Um, they don't take her seriously.
She starts to investigate it herself.
Um, she goes to a bookstore that is in the ground level of the building where this.
Um, you can go.
A long story about a boy named James Suicide spontaneous combusting thing happen and she meets a woman who runs the bookstore, played by Laura Laurel Lockhart.
Um,
who I've seen and other stuff.
I just can't put my finger on it.
Um.
And Laurel Lockhart.
Uh, sort of.
you slowly seduces this woman into her world
and you realize that this woman is actually
the headwitch of a covenant of some sort.
And why do you always meet witches in bookstores?
It's always where you wind up stumbling upon a covenant.
It is true.
It's either a witch, the occult books, et cetera.
The witch or some guy that wants to give you a book
that never ends.
Remember the page master?
Remember it, I lived it.
Christopher Lloyd and McCauley Culkin.
And it was half animated, I want to say, all animated?
Not a good film.
I never saw it.
Let's move on to the story at hand.
There are bugs in this movie.
Yeah, she gets, I mean,
let's get to the point here, too.
There are giant bugs.
There are bug, there's a bug puking up scene
that was so disgusting and crazy.
There's bug, you know, a birth that goes on
and like that scene is really disgusting.
Like she's sloshing around on the floor
in like vaginal goo and bug juice
and wild shit goes on in this movie.
Yeah, it's, it's, as she, as she,
as our main character falls deeper unsuspectedly
into the throes of this coven.
Yes, grosser shit starts to happen.
And she learns that she's there to birth.
Isn't, is that what it is?
She's there to birth.
She's there to bring them a new boy to lead them.
I don't fucking know or something.
But it's pretty irrelevant.
Yeah, and if she doesn't do it,
she will spontaneously combust, right?
Right.
And up until this point, when that reveal happens,
it's a pretty forgetful isn't even the word.
It's a pretty nothing movie.
But then when she does realize this,
now all of a sudden, we get into the good stuff
because this is where it goes and this starts to shine.
This is where all your practical effects come in.
And as you said, you got a bug coming out of a vagina
that shoots goo everywhere, the vagina shoots goo.
I mean, not the, not the bug, right?
You start to see some really, really gross
and disgusting practical effects.
There's that Rosemary's baby -esque scene where they like,
I think Clint Howard has sex with her or something?
Like they approximate something like bug or some shit?
Or yeah, pretty wild stuff.
Pretty wild stuff.
Nuts.
In the end, she's supposed to go abduct the younger brother
of her boyfriend whose parents are,
or whose dad at least is anti -Semitic
and whatever as we already said.
And bring the boy to them.
Oh, that's what it is.
So they can sacrifice the boy for whatever reason.
The boy is scared.
He doesn't want to be sacrificed for obvious reasons.
And she is left with the, or faced with the decision
of does she sacrifice the boy or spontaneously combust?
Typical stuff.
Folks, I'm quite, quite frank, I'm tired of seeing this story
over and over again.
It's a wild picture, but I'm a huge Yuzna fan.
I do love society.
And I think him and this, this screaming mad George,
when they team up, you get some crazy awesome shit.
This and the original are my favorites of the franchise.
If you want to listen to our episodes on one,
two and five, you can find them in our archives,
which by the way, are still up and earning money
for somebody on iTunes or any place you listen to podcasts.
One of our hellians at the St. Petersburg show
said that she heard our podcast as a listening option
on Philippine air, on a flight to the Philippines.
We were a listening option.
She's somebody's making some money office, not us.
Who knows?
And I'm gonna go in there like ice cube
and straight out of Compton and beat the shit
out of their office and say, this is mine.
These are mine and make love to his wife.
This is mine now, consensually.
When I walk in, she's like, oh, this is the man I want.
Screaming mad George, not me.
Screaming mad George, effects work.
Oh, include we hear some Asian guy, correct?
Yeah, we're trouble Japan.
Okay.
Big trouble, little China, predator,
nightmare known street three, nightmare,
nightmare known street four,
which might be the effects height of that franchise.
It is arena.
Never say he's worked with Yuzna on society.
He worked on Tales from the Hood,
which has amazing visual effects.
Looks like he worked with Yuzna on Beyond Reanimator.
Very cool.
He's in film.
Freaked, which is not a good movie.
I don't think I let it.
I remember loving it when I was 13.
I used to watch it all the time.
He did Silent Night Deadly Night 5.
I think that movie has a flashback from a hammer
in it if I recall correctly
that made me laugh really hard.
Um, so what do you want to say about five
before we wrap things up?
Well, what was about thumbs up or thumbs down on?
Hogged down definitely on three.
My hog is decently up on four though.
My hog is definitely down on three,
and my hog is definitely up on four.
Literally, I was very aroused by this movie
and I love that Brian Yuzna is just a pervert operating
in plain sight.
He clearly has some sick.
That's shit.
And his marriage, the guy for the script, he was good.
I don't mean he's a pervert in real life.
I mean, he's got proclivities.
Doesn't mean he acts on anything.
He likes a spicy film.
I can't believe it.
A spicy and so do I.
I'm not ashamed of that.
There it is, there it is.
We don't need to get into five
because we did a whole episode about it.
But I will say there's a nutcracker sexual assault
that will stay with you until the day you die.
Yes.
And there is a really wild performance
from Mickey Rooney who's committing
like it's the MGM back lot in 1939.
It's a crazy movie and it's not good at all, really.
I mean, I like five.
I would argue that five could be my second favorite
over four.
Okay.
Just because it's got more of a Christmas theme to it.
Yeah.
And I like that Mickey Rooney is a toy maker
or Mickey Rooney is a toy maker
and it should have been Mickey Roark honestly
before being.
Now it would be Mickey Rooney.
Yeah, I'll do it.
I like that Mickey Rooney is yet Mickey.
Is a toy maker in it?
I like that Mickey Rooney betrayed his own ethical stance
on the franchise by doing the film.
And I like that in the end.
You find out that Mickey Rooney has a robotic double
that he's constructed.
I like five.
Five brings me a bit of joy.
And Yuzna was involved there too.
He I think he co -wrote it or something.
So yeah, it's not a great franchise,
but it is kind of trashy fun.
You can what currently watch the entire franchise
on Shutter, which I think is still the bargain price
it always was at $4 .99 a month.
I don't know why we give them all this free advertising,
but we love them.
And you can also buy three, four and five
in one of those multi -DVD packs right now
for like $7 .99 on Amazon if you're interested.
I have that DVD pack.
They are also being re -released.
It might have happened already on Blu -ray by,
I think it's Vestron.
Is it doing it?
Like now, it either just came out
or just about.
That's what I'm talking about.
Okay.
If I said DVD, I meant Blu -ray.
I was gonna get that,
but I have them on DVD already.
And as far as I can tell,
they didn't do anything to the Blu -rays to make them.
I actually, maybe they did, but I was like,
do I need high death?
No.
Silent night, deadly night, three, four and five.
Like, you know, you just.
Anyway, folks, we're back with violent night.
Early Jan.
Merry Christmas to you, happy new year.
Thanks to all who came out in St. Pete.
Thanks to all of you for listening and supporting.
And we'll see you next time.
We'll see you in hand.