Summer is here and Bed MDM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer or check out
our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and the Wizard of Oz.
Only available at Bed MDM Casino.
Spin on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 fortunes, Mystery of the Land,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand!
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action!
Bet MGM in game sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 plus to Wager, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and West Virginia
only, games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as non -mustrable site credit slash bonus bets unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
This episode is brought to you by LifeLock.
Between two -factor authentication, strong passwords, and a VPN, you try to be in control
of how your info is protected.
But many other places also have it, and they might not be as careful.
That's why LifeLock monitors hundreds of millions of data points a second for threats.
If your identity is stolen, they'll fix it, guaranteed, or your money back.
Save up to 40 % your first year.
Visit LifeLock .com -podcast for 40 % off, terms apply.
We're rolling, Patty. Welcome back, folks. We'll see you in hell. Here we are.
I'm here in hell, hearing you. You're hearing us. I'm Joe DeRosa, and I'm Pat Walsh, and this
is the podcast where we do hard movie commentaries. It's brought to you by the Fengoria podcast
network for more information about the network, including other programs, how to follow our
show or other shows and find episodes of all the shows. Go visit
fangoria .com. But enough of that. Here we are. This is a special
Halloween episode where we will be doing Halloween six. No, no, I'm
sorry, eight, eight. Well, I see why you might be confused, Joe,
because there's so many of them. We are, I think there's six. Then
there's H2O, then there's resurrection. And that's what we're
tonight. Yes, we're watching Resurrection tonight. Why? Resurrection. I'm sure you're wondering
without question one of the worst of the Halloween films. It's because the only two Halloween
films on Netflix are this one and six and six, which is the worst one. Now, I haven't seen six.
I thought it would be too odd to be like, yeah, we're just gonna watch Halloween six. Resurrection
you're getting a fresh start, but I just watched H2O and Michael Myers' head was cut off with an X.
Well, they explain what happened here. I mean, is it like they attach them to electrodes? Now,
I know I saw this in high school. I don't remember anything about it. When I watched H2O, I did remember
that. I remembered LL Cool J's masterful performance as a guy writing erotic fiction until he gets shot
in the head and then he's like hey I'm back he does come back at the end it's shot repeatedly by Adam
Arkin and he's like am alright kind of crazy yeah and then I think there's like a there's like a
a comedic beat on the way out with him and the wife oh yeah he's like I'm gonna write an erotic
thriller yeah yeah yeah he's like totally fine yeah and then as you walks off you hear a very
ADR line you goes ADR and in the biz means you looped it in after the fact well to say what looping means looping means you're
They do it in comedies, too like if everyone has their back to the camera. You can add jokes for them
Like like awkwardly loop in dialogue to get extra laughs, and it's always very obvious
It's like a completely different. Yeah, or you'll see their lips frantically moving and then it'll say like three words
Yeah. Yeah. But, uh,
LL Cool Jersey's walking off goes,
yeah, I'm fine. The bullet just grays me because clearly the audiences were like,
yeah, could we get some explanation as to why he gets shot nine times and he's fine?
I'll tell you, I always had a problem with those sort of explanations for things.
Yeah, but I have spent the first portion of this week.
I'm spending this entire week for the first time writing a script.
Yeah, I've written for TV shows,
but I've never received a script assignment so I'm home. Well, thanks, Pat. But I'm home about 20
produced apps to my name. And of course all the residuals that that entails. But go ahead.
That's very exciting. I've, yeah, I'm doing it for the first time. And that's very exciting. Well,
it's, it's, I'm not bringing up to be exciting. I'm bringing up to say I
I get those, those half -assed tie -ups now.
Like, oh, Christ, just put a fucking sentence,
one sentence explanation on page 28.
Yeah, especially for a minor character like LL.
And in resurrection, we have Buster Rhymes
inheriting that role.
Buster Rhymes, by the way, if you're home
and you've heard the podcast before,
this is the time, get Halloween Resurrection,
all cute up on your Apple TV or whatever your device is
on your Netflix, it's always Netflix movie here
We'll see you in hell so you can watch along with us if you choose
That's why we're hard -panned. I'm in one ear pets in the other
If you don't want to listen or if you don't want to watch along you don't have to but
Find that now because we're about to start
You got look at this cast. We got we got Daisy McCracken
Sounds like a made -up joke name. It's like if I were to pitch in a comedy and her name her name's Daisy McCracken
What is this? Joe dirt three? That's not a real name, but it's our actual name.
I was so excited to see this film when it came out because I loved H2O. I thought
H2O was amazing. I saw it opening weekend in the theater. I think I did too. It's good,
and the last half of it is very good, I would say. I loved it. I truly think it's a
more or less flawless sequel. All right, down, but it's pretty good. I really like it.
I think it's the third best Halloween movie.
Well, I know Ken Hanley agrees.
He just did a, or for Fangoria, representative
who put this whole thing together.
He did a Facebook post where he ranked them all,
and he went 3 -1 -H2 -O as the top.
Wait a minute, he put Season of the Witches
the best Halloween movie?
I thought it was kind of crazy too.
I just watched Season of the Witch and really enjoyed it,
but I don't think it has any business
this being called a Halloween movie, but he ranked that as the number one Halloween movie.
Yeah.
And to me, and I know you were saying two is up there, which I think is really crazy.
Two is my favorite.
To me, one is so, so much better than the other ones and it's not just because it's the
classic or whatever.
It's just a million times better in every regard, but okay, well, I don't know if it's
that.
Pat just laying it down.
It's a million times better look the first one I'd say the first one is the
most film like out of all of them what we're talking about films sure but you
know I yeah I would say yeah the second one can't exist without the first one
the first one has a certain style to it right that the others potentially don't
have or at least in the amount that the first does but I just I love the second one
because to me the second one feels like the third act of a movie it's it to me
it's when the story really gets going.
It starts right at the end of one.
Yeah, I like that.
It's where all the mythologies reveal
that their brother and sister and it's just very exciting.
Good deaths too, his death at the end of two is amazing.
Like he's on fire.
And it's also like a woman sitting in a hot tub
and like a scientist lab or whatever.
That makes it feel very cheesy
and not like any sort of classic movie time.
But I love that hot tub death.
That's a good one.
Look, she's a fantastic looking lady, but
What do you say we start this yeah, let's start it up if you're watching along get yourself booted up hit pause as
Soon as the picture comes up there on the movie and then we'll count it off all right everybody's paused everybody's set
Yeah, here we go. One, two, three, play.
Now, H2O, I did a little research, ignores all the events of everything except one, two.
So it goes one, two, H2O, essentially.
Yes.
And then does this pick up after H2O?
It must.
Resurrection.
Just picks up after H2O.
This is why.
And how did they get it so bad?
That's why I was so excited to see it because all the promotion for the movie showed Jamie Lee Curtis.
Yeah.
I said, they knocked it out of the park with H2L.
This was a fairly recent follow -up to it.
It wasn't like years and years went by.
And I was like, okay, they're riding this heat.
Right.
The Buster Rimes thing to me, I was just like, well,
I guess they're just thinking like it's potentially good luck to have another rapper in the chest and I Katie Sackoff of Fatal Star Galactic.
Yeah, I was there opening opening week and you know, as we'll soon find out spoiler alert,
Jamie Lee Curtis dies within the first five minute tie revansions.
I didn't remember that. Thanks. Thanks, Joe.
Oh, I wonder why they didn't list her in the cast.
So really she's really lining this film as Busta Rhymes. Yeah, well, and I didn't know that until watching a Busta Rhymes movie right now. Yeah, and the minute you realize that in the theater, when Gimli Curtis dies like six minutes in, you're like, oh, shit, this is like a tire of banks Busta Rhymes movie now. Yeah.
Which is not what I signed on for.
That's not that's not my bag. It also has Thomas Ian Nicholas, who was the rookie of the year. Who funky but love him. You never saw a rookie of the year.
The movie about that kid that plays pro baseball kid that plays pro baseball. It's a great movie actually. John Candy is the announcer.
Come out at the same time as little big league where a kid inherits a major league team and that kid is the kid
Is in this? Yeah, he's in this. All right, and he's an American pun
Now wait can we I we discuss this and then we forgot it again turn on the subtitles. I
Don't think I can now that we're rolling. Oh, I think you have to do it before no, you can't do subtitles on Netflix. You definitely can
All right, well, we're out who the hell cares. Yeah, I guess not
I just follow the plot. You're right, though. We should be watching Pat make it so ludicrous that we haven't been watching these with subtitles, so we can see what everyone's saying. We don't have to like listen and talk. It's just crazy that we didn't think of this. Yeah, I got a very similar raggedy and the situation. My sister had raggedy and never never liked it.
Buttons for eyes like you'd be sleeping and you'd cut your cheek
Patch referring to the fact that Jamie Lee Curtis's character Laurie Strode in this has a
Raggedy and dollum top of her pillow. So wait, she's in an asylum. She's in an asylum
But she killed them now. This is well her nightmares are over. This is what bothers me
Okay, she's in a this is let's start where the problem started for me
When I saw this originally you open she's in an asylum
immediately you're like what a kid she had a boyfriend yeah like she was
going all right she's a drinking problem but who doesn't yeah she was I am I
imagine it's somewhat traumatic to or scarring to the soul the cut of man's
head off sure especially if he's your homicidal brother right but it seemed like
closure at the end of the last film it seemed like the end of it for her you know
But uh, apparently not. She's back and she's in worse shape than when she was in the last one.
Now, did you like a season of the witch? I've never
embarrassingly, I'm about to admit, I've never seen season of the witch. You should have told me,
you gotta come over the other night. I thought it was really fun. I heard it's great. I
Here's the thing, the reason I never saw it was because when I was a kid and I would watch the Halloween movies,
which my mom
I got me into my mom was always like part three was dumb. It didn't have anything to do with the other ones.
That's completely true.
So I just never wanted to see it and then like all my friends that weren't hard movies would say the same thing.
And now recently and by recently I mean within the last maybe eight months.
I've noticed horror fans often say it's a fantastic horror movie.
it's just not yeah and I knew that going inside of the give a ship yeah it is
truly crazy that out of like this twelve -part series the third one is just
its own thing it's kind of insane did you catch what happened there why
Michael Myers is still alive switched switched his body switch put his mask on the
paramedic as it's so Laurie Strode accidentally decapitated the paramedic but oh and then he put
the paramedic in the body bag he yeah so when he stands up in the thing and all that and walks
exactly like Michael Myers and reaches out and touches her hand and does everything exactly like
Michael Myers and she looks into her brother's eyes that was actually some randa yes that's fucking stupid
Same size, that's fucking stupid. It is stupid. It didn't need to be done. I'm realizing now
I did see this and I fell asleep in the theater, which it tells you a lot about a horror movie
There's a reason I poured a double black coffee before we started this podcast 10 pm at night where we are yeah
and
Late for our usual recordings, but the city we're in Los Felas
just like I know you didn't fully come outside to greet me which I thought was
rude you should have come out in the lawn with your arms spread wide but it
smells so skunky out there tonight and I'm not talking about the usual Los
Feelas weed smell. It smells like a truck hauling skunks overturned on the street
outside of this house. What do you think that is? It's skunks. It's Griffith Park
skunks. Like when I go running at night, I always see like a giant skunk. Oh, I didn't
know that we had a skunk issue over here. Yeah, it's a big problem. I also at my house,
I'm going to sleep some nights and the light sensor on my deck will turn on, which is horrifying.
Like two in the morning, and I'm like, oh, somebody is on my deck. And I looked out the
other night is a skunk that must have been 80 pounds waddling across like
bigger than most dogs waddling across my deck just like it owned the fucking
place so I'm like every night when this light comes on I guess they just
sit out here and have a party. It's terrible. It's like it's like the great
outdoors. Yeah, it's subtitles. Yeah, we're outdoors man. It's got some really funny
stuff in it. I'm a big fan of the movie. The problem is the love story between the
Which I was clearly kind of forced in but sure for the kids. It's a really funny movie
I mean John Candidant Acroid. What do you want? It's a great movie. I've told you this before but I once on top of my trash can outside
Not in the can lid was closed. Yeah right on top of it
perfectly like new
Spotless copy of the great outdoors on one side of the disc and
and Uncle Buck on the other side.
Oh, oh, oh, spotless disc.
Just sit in there.
That's amazing.
Didn't know where I thought you were gonna share
your own raccoon or whatever story
when you said trash can.
I got kind of excited.
I saw, well, I will say this.
I did.
Uncle Buck's one of my favorite movies.
It's fantastic.
I saw, when I was walking the dog and I got home
and there was a skunk sort of in front of my house.
Okay.
But that he scurried off.
And I just remember thinking
if he sprayed my dog right now that would be a moment where I'd have to really
rise to being a dog owner I'd have to deal with it and I was like what I deal
with it drop the dog in the trash and move on with your life that's I'll tell you
when it's 11 30 and you're tired yeah that's not that crazy even idea what do you
got to do in that situation you just violently scrub the dog forever no he's
been the rest of your days scrubbing a dog I think I would have had to like leave
in the yard for a minute, go inside, look at all up on the internet. It would have been a two -hour
process. I mean, it's not a one -and -done -er patty. What the hell did he just get out of that vending
machine? All those choices and he gets some non -descript on a bond? He's...he's a chunky guy.
I don't, you know, he looks sort of like a key in peel character. He does.
us. He uh yeah he did get that weird that was odd like you couldn't read what it was
probably because he couldn't shoot. They have all these rules with product placement like
if he chooses one then you got to pay the company or what they pay you. Yeah they clearly
shoved some kind of half -eaten donut into a saran ride. That tells you the kind of penny pension
operation we're running here with Halloween resurrection. Now for all intents and purposes the
beginning of the film here. It's not terrible. I don't like that it starts with
her and the asylum as I said, but you got your security guards creeping around
the basement. It's a little eerie. It's a little spooky. Michael Myers is
somewhere in there. You know that he is. See in that washroom. No, but the
washer machine just wanted a slow motion, which means he's gonna find something
in there. Yeah, I believe it's ahead. I remember correctly. We just hit our dog
Cruelty quota for this pumpkin. There he is here. I love that now by the way the mask in H2O was not great
And I looked it up and I was like is this the mask I remember because it's not the mask I'm seeing now either and they said
People complained about the mask and did reshoots and they also did some CGI frame -by -frame replacing of the mask
Because people were like what is this?
Wait, wow, how do you mess something like that up?
I never noticed anything out of step with the mask.
It's a different mask than the first, you know, one and two.
And it's a different mask than I'm looking at now.
This is the most, not this clown mask I'm talking about.
What's the difference?
Not a major difference, but the one and age two old
looked a little goofier, I think, and a little less scary.
I do remember looking a bit more crisp or something.
Almost like he bought a Michael Myers mask.
Yeah, and I guess, you know, maybe he doesn't always use the same mask. They probably took it away if they put him away
But I mean, this is basic movie trivia. I'm sure you know, but it's the original mask was a William Shatner mask turned inside out
Bill Shatner. I didn't know that
What's Billy up to he's in a new horror movie? How it tells Halloween supposed to be great. I didn't know
No, but I'd love to say no. I'm sorry. He's not he's in another horror movie the Christmas one
Christmas horror story
Oh Christmas horse, which also has a Krampus story in it.
Yeah, but then their Krampus is like evil Santa?
Yeah, Krampus is, there's a Krampus movie coming out.
I believe by the guy that did Trick or Treat.
And then Trick or Treats is pretty good.
I like Trick or Treat.
I thought that'd be a phone one tonight too.
And that's not on Netflix then.
But I know all these movies were at some point.
I almost suggested and then I forgot because I'm not prepared.
that we just go off the grid tonight and not do a Netflix or but do a DVD so we could actually pick a
Halloween movie we wanted to watch. Yeah, I do think it's smart though just to reach the masses most people
have Netflix since then. Of course, but I mean, we didn't have a brand new shoot. Yeah, that's true. Yeah, there wasn't
people kind of rolled with that. People rolled with it. That was a fun event and as always, we love you guys
speedback. Also, can I discuss the star ratings issue? Oh, I don't care. All right, so tell them very
briefly what happened with you and the opian Anthony showing why the racists of America hates you.
Anthony and I had a bit of a public falling out. It's been very quiet for quite some time now.
know, uh, I don't know what his stance on it is currently. I have since everything
what happened said publicly that my regret was that grown men and I included myself in
this, resorted to Twitter and online fighting or something. Right. And didn't handle things
privately. And I again, I included myself in that blame. There has been no noise about it.
everything has been quiet. As far as I know, it's more or less behind us. But there's still
some angry fans out there that are just crazy. I think it's one guy lives. Yeah, I think it's
one guy. So it seemed like one guy wrote all these reviews. Yeah, all said roughly the same thing.
And also had one sentence different to make it seem like it was a different person. Yeah. So
And she was our podcast had five stars or four or whatever it was doing really well. Yeah, and then somebody comes in and
Gives it eight one star reviews in one day and each review is like Jotaro said hates women. He's a racist
Antisemitic was another one too. He's an anti -Semitic and they all said the same basic thing and none of that's true by the way
it's obviously ludicrous and
so now this podcast
hovers around like a three star and it does matter to get people to hear it so
like congratulations your voice is being heard and this fun podcast about horror
movies that we do now looks like it's not popular and you're shitting on it so
thanks man well because why because Joe had a falling out with a guy that you don't
know and will never meet what's wrong with you so I'm asking you if you like the
podcast and you're listening, it takes 10 seconds to click the five star rating and try to get us back up because now we're
Going against all this shit and now the guy's gonna hear this and now I'll be a target
And it'll be like oh, that's also a racist one star, you know, well it happened
Get a life it happened to I'm assuming it's the same person or small group of persons
Behind it, but I it also happened to my album ratings and all this other stuff
Everything I have online basically has like one star
Yeah, I mean like so why would you try to bring a man's career down for like what's wrong with you?
It's wrong with America. It's look. This is social networking. Why did she just kiss him? Oh
She said I'll see you in hell. I don't like that Jamie Lee Curtis kisses him on the lips. It's very weird
I definitely saw this movie because I remember that moment and this is where I checked out
Jamie Curtis falls to her death and the whole movie, there was a tiny part in the back of my head where I was like, she's going to come back.
Like he came back and then she never does and I was furious. Well that moment in age two, oh, when she and him come face to face, not the indie pop group, but she being Jamie Lee Curtis and him meeting Michael Myers.
when they first lock eyes, she gets on the other side of that door and slams it.
That was a very exciting moment. It's one of my favorite scenes in horror movie history.
It's iconic. It's two iconic characters. It's the reckoning day.
They're having the face -to -face moment where she realizes this isn't all my head anymore.
This is really happening. I get chills at that part.
You got in the background Josh Harden that looking like he's missing a couple chromosomes as always
You got Michelle Williams with
Bizarrely drawn on eyebrows. Yeah, it was a different time. It was a different time
Back when we just thought Michelle Williams was gonna be a Dawson kid
And that was gonna be the end of it went on to academy award nomination
Yeah, and then I guess to not act for what seems like about six years now. Yeah, it's either anything
She seems like a sweet kid. I wish she'd I wish she'd come back to us. I fucking love blue Valentine
when my favorite movies never saw it it seems too sad and oh it is man anytime I have like a
pretty serious argument with a girl I'm dating or whatever I'll sit down 2 a .m. fire up a glass of
bourbon and watch Blue Valentine which is very healthy but I'm just like hey I hear you folks this
is terrible now I do appreciate that they go 15 minutes before they show the title screen they do
but here's the thing. Here's the thing is the other part in H2O that I get chills from is the
when when she when Jamie Lee Curtis shuts the gates she tells her kid and her friends to run
yep she shuts the gates and she realizes that she's locking herself in with Michael Myers
But now she's gonna go and confront him. Yeah, and it's literally the moment where the hunted becomes the hunter
And she starts screaming Michael and the music starts playing goose bumps
I remember I was dating a girl once and on Halloween. I showed her that movie and I
Remember she didn't quite get why I thought that part was so cool and it wasn't long after that
Let me tell you how this play that night. I don't understand
And, it's Laurie Strode, 20 years late.
Yes, that was her, her, her vagina getting so dry
with each word that you say.
Just drier and drier as you rant on and on
about what this iconic scene means to you.
Just a paling, drying, slab of skin,
to look like, like the Michael Myers.
Yeah, chafing. Oh, we should tell the listeners about our real life. Well, my real life,
Halloween moment this week. A true terror come to life. I had a dream about our friendship. I
text you about this. Yeah. And a nightmare about our friendship that we were... I haven't heard
this yet, so I want to know what it was. This was the nightmare. We knew a nightmare on friend's
There was a third friend that we had, but we didn't like him.
Did you see him in the dream or it was a non -destructive?
He was like a guy in the dream, but like he wasn't like a guy in real life.
But he was this guy and we, I knew in the dream that we hated him, right?
That was backstory though.
That wasn't happening in the movie, you know what I mean?
So I was with the guy one night and I go what do you think Pat's up to and he goes I don't know we should text him and we both texted you separately and didn't say we were together but just like hey what do you have to and then you only texted him back and said like hey man I'm around if you want to hang out and I was sitting there like he texted the guy that we hate he didn't text me back he must be furious at me and I woke up
realized it was a nightmare was was shaking still went to went to the grove
bought some corduroy slacks and a Kindle fire and then texted you and said I
said just that I had a nightmare it shook me up so bad I had to buy something to
take my mind off it right and then and then I didn't hear back from you and I was
like my god it's happening in real life it was the nightmare come to life and then
And I have not been receiving several texts lately and I get a lot of texts from unknown it'll say unknown message
Not received I'm having submissions with my service. Yeah AT &T can you help me out? Yeah, so when you texted me last night
And I said did you get that text and you said no, what are you talking? I was the relief that washed over me Pat
Well, that's that's very touching that you care so much about the friendship. Of course. I do of course
I do that's a sick thing that I've heard of people doing and I've often I've
had a couple of friends be like, hey, we should both text this person at the same time.
I don't remember who it was, and I wouldn't say on there anyway.
But somebody who was like, this friend of ours is such a starfucker.
You text him because it was as a friend of mine who was kind of famous.
And then I'll text him and we'll see if he only responds to it.
And I was like, I don't want to know how this plays out.
I wouldn't want to know either.
I don't want to know that, you know, it's sick.
And we weren't doing a test in the dream.
We were just like let's both text Pat. We just failed to say hey, we're hanging out together
Right, and then that was it and I was oh god. It was all kinds of who I
Remember once Pete was doing his podcast Pete Holmes was doing his podcast. Yeah, and
He had pat n' Oswald on right and I don't know what they discussed before this happened
But my phone rang I saw it was Pete. I didn't answer
Did my phone rang a second time and it was some weird 310 number? I answer and
He's like this voice goes Joe to roast it's Pat Oswald and I go, oh, hey Pat. What's up? And he goes can I ask you a question?
I go, yeah sure and he goes, why did you answer my calling? Not peace. I heard that actually. Yeah, and I said
You're I didn't this must be a new number. I didn't have it. I thought it was work calling right
I think I also did say obviously to patent were at you
it still would have probably answered. Yeah, uh, that sort of shot at Pete. I talked to Pete
every, every day too much. You know, anyway, Jen Kirkman and a supporting role. It does look
like Jen Kirkman. Look at this guy. That's, they couldn't get the guy from that 70s show. They tried.
That's a guy who when you cut to as we just proved everyone at the same time says, look at this guy.
who who he's still going up in bars being like hey I don't know you ever see
this movie Halloween resurrection I was in that it was like my god how hot was
Tiger Banks she was right our bags are still incredible I haven't seen her in
years yeah so I don't know there I'm not saying like she lost it I'm just saying
like right there I'm like like she still looks great should I mean she has a
talk show and she seems to have a screw loose but she was very hot she still has a
Talk show. Yeah, that fucking talk show was doing. I don't know if it's still on but I remember when she had it
I don't come out every couple weeks and be like this is what fat looks like America
Yeah, that was like a big thing
Which was Oprah's bit first was it Oprah'd come out and be like I lost a hundred pounds like two weeks later
She'd be like so I
gained that hundred times back
Which I can relate to I'll probably do the same thing a couple times a year not a hundred
This kid by the way in Hollywood resurrection is going for the Jason Patrick circa lost boys. Yeah, yeah look alike award
Yeah, law suppose would have been a good one too. I mean really we were like let's do a Halloween episode. We got to do a Halloween movie, but what?
Well, this is feeling very final destination here right now. Well, that girl just screamed so loud a glass broke, which is absurd
Well, let me ask now. So obviously H2O had a compelling reason to be made and it was released on the exact 20th anniversary of the original Halloween, which is very cool and they did a fantastic job.
Yeah, you never Williamson did not get he got credited as a co -EP on it and apparently he rewrote the script pretty heavily and he just got that credit as like a thank you.
but he didn't get credit as a writer on the movie.
He didn't?
He didn't.
It's two other guys.
He, you know, Jamie Lee Curtis got that movie made.
I didn't.
She knew it was the 20th anniversary coming up.
I saw an interview once.
And she said, she said, I thought to myself,
I can still get something done in this town.
I picked up the phone.
I made a call.
And they say, yeah, I love Jamie Lee Curtis.
Always have.
Who does it?
I was watching Trading Places.
Oh, God.
Earlier today.
How about the new scene and that?
Holy shit and I remember I mean I've always been obsessed with Christopher
Gaston his movies and when I found out he married her I was like dude you're
the best yeah and apparently he's just a complete like asshole like so like
bitter and angry which I also really and he landed like the most positive happy
woman there is Jamie liqueur is he bitter any interview I've seen with him he's
just like he's angry in a very hilarious way. That's great. Very quiet. I can relate to that.
I read Martin Short's biography and he's got a lot of really funny Christopher guest stories.
So he told I think he made the first like spoiler alert joke. I think before spoiler alert was a thing.
But he was talking about he was like even some of my friends were critical of my career choices
during this period. I can still remember sitting at a bar with my friend Chris Guest.
And I told him what I was working on this new movie called Captain Ron and he said what's it about and I told him
Well, you know, uh, Kurt Russell and his family
You know me and my family are on a ship and we bring on Kurt Russell who plays Captain Ron and he is kind of a wild card
And shakes our family up
And he's in the middle of saying this Christopher guy goes whoa whoa whoa. I didn't say ruin it for me
Just like, you know, a funny asshole, which I like.
We should also mention Jamie Lee Curtis in True Lies,
a scene I masturbated to eight million times,
even though it features no nudity.
Which scene when she dances with a Schwarzenegger?
That was, I mean, that came out in 94.
I was 13, 14.
I was not able to see our right of movies.
I did not have the internet.
That scene was huge for me.
mildly disturbing story from Walsh. Not really from the sidelines. I'll tell you what
is disturbing is that Arnold sits there and watches his wife do this elaborate
strip tease and doesn't tell her like hey it's me your husband I've always found
that scene very sick and fucked up to me. There was a there was a movie called Fall
Time with William Baldwin I believe it was familiar with it Evan Cena. You know
know, bank robber would ever move to place like the 50s or something, but they take a hostage
and it's he's got like this younger like teenage cohort, okay. And it's like the kind
of good cop bad cop thing with the two crux and the kids actually being kind of like nice
to the hostage. Yeah. She's like this gorgeous blonde. And there's like this scene where
She seduces him and they start making out and she gives him a hand job
Mm -hmm, and you she puts his hand her hand down his pants
And you see her kind of work it so it looks pretty real. Anyway, I masturbated that on the spot
So there's no nudity. I'm assuming no zero
Just simply a hand down a pen and you're telling me masturbating to Jamie Lee Curtis looking amazing in a in a bra on panties is
disturbing
Pat, I never said I wasn't a hypocrite.
All right.
No, it's not disturbing.
I'm just giving you shit, but I can tie some disturbing
tails, but I'm not going to.
It was such a realistic depiction of a hand job.
Sure.
It just got me.
It probably get me if I saw it right now.
You know, it does kind of work that way when you...
I stumbled one night upon Hamburger the Motion Picture, which
was the first news that I ever saw.
And it's a movie about...
It came out, you know, the same time as, like, ski patrol and that kind of shit.
And yeah, I remember hamburger is like, I think Jim Varney, who played Ernest, isn't it,
maybe?
Yeah.
It always kind of upset me that he was in a movie that was sort of brandy.
And then he wasn't playing Ernest, but anyway, it was the first new today I ever saw and
I stumbled upon it at age, like, 27, one night on cable.
And I was like, just rock hard.
And it was scenes that, you know, shouldn't have had any effect on me, but it took me back to a time of innocence.
Yeah, I remember my roommate in New York was one of the roommates I had in New York.
We were well barreling towards 30 at the time.
And he still was like, he'd be like, oh, there's some good...
I think there's going to be good tit in this movie.
I was like, who cares?
We have a porn machine sitting on a desk over there.
put you do care. I didn't care. I just watched the full season of Red Oaks on Amazon
Instant, which is a really great show. I think my friend Rachel's in that show. Who
does she play? If it's the show I'm thinking if she plays like a sort of, I think maybe
like a kind of fluszy girlfriend to somebody. Okay. Well, I mean, there's plenty of fluszy
girlfriends on the show. I think I think it's that show. I gotta watch. Anyway, whatever.
It's a great show. I liked it a lot, but I mean
What compelled me to keep watching aside from really enjoying it would maybe be like yeah, I'll watch the fourth in a row
Was the nudity if I'm being honest it could just kind of it's an extra thing that keeps you hanging on
You know how much nudity is it ample ample is it like sort of like a take on like a catty check kind of thing?
It's a complete and I will say homage and not rip off
It is a full homage to those kind of movies
They even do which I found very bizarre a body switching episode between the kid and his dad like it's an 80s homage
Oh, okay. I don't think this is the same show. It probably is though. It's at a country club in the 80s and
Yeah, and the show I'm thinking I really made a sloppy capuchino there. She did
I think that's part of the charm of this scene though. She's dancing around being cute. Is this really something to Aliyah?
I couldn't tell you. By the way, the theme song of Halloween H2O is Creed's What's This
Life For? Which is a song I believe about giving your life to Jesus Christ and an insane
choice. It plays over the credits and everything. I heard that Creed guys living in his car.
You know what? Good. No, come on. Good. I mean good. Fucking Creed. I remember all this
Shit about creed and him doing that fucking shirtless Jesus shit in the video
And I mean the guys are too. I don't wish every song is about Jesus and then what comes out?
But a video of him and kid rock getting blown by 20 groupies in the back of a bus
No, you can't do it both my friend. Yeah, you can't do it Tiger Woods proved you can you can't be on your knees on Sunday
And then get them on your knees on Friday night
people
I thought your knees was used for praying, see now I had this giant Halloween box set
and I've been going through it and loving it and watching like these feature length
documentaries on the movies and I realize I can watch hours of documentary footage on
any movie whether I like it or not and if it's a failure all the better you know everybody's
talking about season of the witch like yeah we messed up like it's a bad movie.
The documentary comes around and it shows you that people now love it and it was it was like a it's own little rocky the documentary
Yeah, it was very inspiring about how things can just take 20 years sometimes before they catch on
so I loved it and
the
Documentary on H2O I haven't watched yet, but like that's awesome that Jamie Lee Curtis got it going again
And so now, they're like, yeah, let's do age two.
Oh, why would they kill off Michael Myers, where they just thinking, they killed them in
such a way that they cut his head off?
Like was Jamie Lee Curtis, like, I'll do it once and never again and we got to kill him.
But then the movie was a fit and then they're like backing up the money truck, because you
notice you made at least a million dollars to be in the first five minutes of this movie.
I think it was probably, yeah, I think it was, I think it was either that or it was just
They said if we want to keep going here is how we'll justify it, but I don't think that I think it's probably the former
I don't think that was the case nobody from H2O is involved in this one
Yeah, that's true except I mean every money's money, and it was a big everything down to the titles
I mean the titles in this film look like the like video game titles like it's like it's everything
Everything none of this was done with the value of that looks terrible on predecessor
Well, that's supposed to that's supposed to be like right when H2O starts like the opening five minutes
It's kind of a stupid scene nothing seen, but
When it starts with Joseph Gordon Levin
And that woman you know the the loomis is nurse gets out of the car wherever it's shot so cool great
It's playing Mr. Sandman the titles look just like the original titles everything's perfect and then you know that very next one
I'm like, yeah, we'll just cash in with some dog shit.
It upsets me that Jamie, I mean, look, who am I to judge?
If they said to me, here's a million dollars
for a day's work or whatever, like, yeah, okay.
But it upsets me that she's in this
because I wish she wasn't,
so I knew she was like disapproving of it or something.
Shit, well, you know, the woman's doing yogurt
that makes her shit commercials now.
But does any genre treat its,
Fans shit here then the horror genre. It's it's especially when you get into sequels and stuff like that and
And you and many other horror fans reasonably so allow themselves to care
And it's got to be so devastating for people to be like you know the other night
I almost watched tremors 5. Oh, that's a nice instant now. I was like I tried I can't Jamie can I can't do this
I shut it off because of Kennedy. Yeah, I was gonna watch it. I shut it off because of Kennedy
I can't stand Jamie Kennedy he almost ruined screen for me. Yeah, but I so I shut it off
But I try I was game. I was gonna give it a shot
I like the opening where the guys like lowering into that pit and falls and I haven't seen it yet
But you know the they actually explain to how the different types of the tremor creatures
Like how the cycle of life works with them. Okay, which I thought was pretty cool
And it made me understand why there was a land one an underground one a land one and then a flying one
Yeah, so I thought that was cool. I mean, it's just there's only so many times you can you can we can watch them like
Destroy the mythology of something before it's like
Well, is the original still great or has it been tarnished and I can usually treat the original as great
But they just announced like they're gonna do a die -hard
prequel yeah
Well, like I can't I don't know what to do about that die hard. I don't know what to do the last die hard to me
Was the level was equivalent to this type of sequel die hard live for your die hard was fucking awesome
It was it was solid. I loved it. It was solid. I'll give you but I felt like they were rebooting the thing
It was it was a true sequel. It felt like die hard. That's fair. That's fair. It was great. I thought it was great
I think one two and three are all A movies. They're just I mean I love the first
classic three you corner me at a weird time I can be like yeah almost as good as
the first I love I love to the blast I love the first four ran out to see the fifth
one when it came out couldn't wait so these guys haven't steered me wrong yet it's
so clearly I was so bad it's like they took it's like they I personally my
my theories is because they didn't even have movie with Bruce Willis on the boat striking
this one. That was supposed to be die hard for. Yeah. And I guess they were like, this
isn't a die hard movie. And they just made it in a striking distance. Yeah. Well, my theory
is with die hard fire. Cool. What they just did there. Yeah. I was scary. No, I just mean
like, yeah, the man's good to us. Do you guys reservoir dogs? Yes. Nice little mirror.
No, it's Pulp Fiction Pulp Fiction.
Okay, go ahead, sorry.
Die Hard Five.
I was like, this is a script through another movie
and they just changed it to Die Hard Five.
This isn't Die Hard.
It had known none of the tropes or elements of Die Hard.
Yeah.
And it had nothing.
None of it was the same.
It was terrible.
That's the kind of thing used to do all the time.
Like, this movie is gonna be a dirty Harry movie
and I'm like, nah, nah, we'll throw it to somebody else.
It's not good enough to be a dirty Harry.
There were rumors forever that Gran Turino
was gonna be another dirty Harry movie. Well that honestly that would have been amazing if it was
like the Rocky Balboa of dirty Harry. I would have loved it. And I think we can still get that in
before Eastwood dies and I would fucking love it. Yeah I'd buy it. I mean look they're doing Indiana Jones
five. They've said now come on man listen I mean I mean they said they're gonna have four in it and
they're gonna he's he said he'll pass the torch yeah but it will not be like a James Bond thing where
a new guy will play Indiana Jones right I'm in quick a grant quick
grand terino story I don't think I ever shared with you I was in New York and I
was visiting from LA but I was trying to do a long distance thing I had a
girlfriend in New York I went and when she would work I would go to all these
screenings Academy Awards screenings because I was in the writers guild so you
get you get to go to movies for free around Oscar time sure one of them was
Grand Torino. And I was like excited to see it. I think
Gran Torino is a pretty ludicrous movie, but it's very
entertaining.
It's an absurd film. Is that it? Find it absurd. Yeah, no
question. It's it's confusing to when he's saying all the
racist stuff, I'm like, this is supposed to be funny. I can't
plan it for laughs. They are right. And at the end, the funny
as part of the whole movie is Eastwood sings a song about a
Gran Torino over the end credits. And so it's like the movie
and I was like wow that was crazy and then you hear this green to Reno he sings it's insane
any who I'm sitting in in New York and they have this these tiny screening theaters that make
you feel like a king and they're like 30 seats big cushy seats so I go in I'm watching the movie
And there's one chair like taped off and as the opening credit start in comes a I don't want to tell tales out of school
But I think you can only say he was extremely drunk minimum
Philip see more Hoffman, okay, and he's like I
Feel like he probably smelled he looked homeless
He was drunk and I was just like whoa like this is a big sighting who doesn't fucking love Phillips and we're Hoffman
And you know when he died I was like I thought of that day and I was like yes guy had some demons
You know whatever but he comes in and he's stumbling and whatever and
he
laughed so
hysterically throughout Gran Turina like the Joker like De Niro and Kate Fear with a cigar like
He was maniacally laughing at Gran Turino and it was so infectious that I had a like the whole theater was like dying laughing
And how funny he found this movie and I wanted to ask him like are you laughing at the racism like do you think this movie is
So bad that it's funny. Are you just drunk but it was such kind of like a joyous experience
And that's what I always think of when I think of Phillips I had an experience with him in the in New York too, please tell
So a taxi cab crash into scaffolding
Um, scaffolding collapsed on the text you can't bloody kid got out of the back completely disoriented because he'd slammed his head he's bleeding actually got his blood on my coat because I tried to help him. Oh, wow, sit down.
You slept in that dry cleaning bill.
Uh, crazy, uh, crazy big crowd forms.
It was the craziest accident I've ever seen. There's smoke everywhere. It was insane. Okay.
crazy crowd forums. My friend and I are just standing there in disbelief. We
can't believe we saw this thing happen. And then through the crowd comes
Philip Seymour Hoffman again looking quite homeless on a 10 speed bike. Okay. Just
kind of looking over his shoulder like what the hell's going on here stops for
a minute and then keeps going. And my friend Joanne goes only in New York. Yeah. I
thought you're gonna say he was okay. He rescued the kid or something. He got
their way after it happened. So he was just kind of like what the hell is
everybody looking at and then saw like the wreckage but we saw the actual accident
happen. We saw a cab drive through scaffolding and the scaffolding collapse onto the
cab. Now in a movie there before like building painters up on that scaffolding.
It was nuts, dude. Thank God it happened at night. I mean, I can't believe nobody
died. Yeah. Now this is, I mean, is this pairing
Can't wait more unbelievable that this no way to make this a big perv and they dubbed they dubbed that dialogue
Is this PG -13 or something?
Yeah, sorry his mouth just moved and somebody dubbed in big perv completely off
Maybe it was
Maybe they just didn't get it and it was just a bad dub job. Well, that this movie is pathetic
What are we looking at this is that's the first time this has been said on this podcast and we watched leprechaun
And we're supposed to believe that chump was bringing that girl into a room that's what that was what I was focused on was a lot to deal with
This this kid that looked like a reject from like the Hogan family. Well for a minute
I thought it was buzz from home alone. That's that's what I was going for
Yeah, I couldn't remember the ref and then I realized he would have been like in his early 30's bus from home alone by the way
Well, he was in an episode of Louis as the guy driving Louis to
to, uh, a gig and it reminded me of the guy who drove us in, uh, in Denver.
Why would it, what was he doing? Uh, well, the guy who drove us was great.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. You know, I, you know, I don't do those.
I don't like tour the globe or whatever like you do, John, but the, the, the
premise of the Louis episode, I, I know you were on a Louis episode as well.
Yeah. But, uh, the driver, uh, is just super chatty and he has to tell him,
like hey man I don't want to talk and the guy like starts crying and has a breakdown but he was
awesome in that and he's amazing in a movie for you Netflix instant users if you want a recommendation
called Blue Ruin and I was watching Blue Ruin which is kind of like a simple plan type joint
you got buzz from home alone and I was loving it and this actor comes in and I was like man this guy's
like real he was he gives an amazing performance and about 10 minutes in I was like where have I seen
and where have I seen him?
And when I looked him up and made the buzz connection,
I about fell off the couch.
Good for buzz, man.
Like, I love that.
Nothing brings me greater joy than like,
okay, your buzz and home alone, by all accounts,
by now you should be working at an amaco state.
And he's like, you know what?
I'm gonna do some indies.
I'm gonna be on the Louis.
And now he's probably, he's like a great character actor.
I love that ship.
That's great.
I'm happy for buzz.
He's my favorite line in home alone.
Look what you did, you little jerk.
Buz is awesome obviously that's the best line and I loved what coley
coconut hosted SNL and Chris Farley did that right yeah it was one of the
funniest things I've ever seen buzz your girlfriend woof I'm going to see
home long they're bringing it back to theaters for one night one night only I
mean I I couldn't love it speaking of which it's Halloween week very
Disappointed in the options for what's screening in L .A. This all nothing nothing nothing that interest interest to me at all
Nothing I missed it. We missed the dawn of the dead one that would have been good downtown
And I missed the thing which I wanted to see at the arc line. I would have seen that
Yeah, we just fuck the arc light have anything this weekend. That's good. I think they might be doing like cycle Halloween night
But you never want to go to a movie at midnight on Halloween night. You're at a party or something. Well, what about tomorrow Friday?
It's conceivable. It's conceivable. If you haven't figured out, folks, it's the Wednesday
before Halloween. It is. And we're hoping to hopefully this is dropping Saturday. Halloween.
It will give to the fans. We talked to Ken. I think it's actually going to drop Friday.
That's great. That's great. So the fans will get it. Here's Buster Rhymes trying to bed tie
her banks. God can you imagine even being in a position where you might have a 1 % chance of
having sex with Tyra Banks in these days. Are you kidding me? It's I would blow
that immediately. I would just be a disaster. It's a different it's a different
too much try to be charming. It's a different it's a completely different
machine. It's it's it's not it's I don't mean like the mentality being able to
flirt with somebody like Tyra Banks. I mean the mentality of people in that
position they just think differently male or female yeah you're just in a
status place where your ego your your confident whatever it is it's all just
designed very differently yeah well it's like a girl walk into a bar and
especially in LA a girl walk into a bar whatever and like it's almost like a
cartoon where your jaw hits the floor and like your tongue rolls out like a
staircase or like you can't believe what you're seeing but it would never
occurred to me to approach that girl now put to some guys it's like yeah I'll roll the dice
I mean I saw a girl tonight on the street that was so hot
and so cold to me as she walked by she made me ashamed of myself now I felt like
some sort of she was cold or you just got a cold vibe I was walking with the dog usually you'll
get a smile from a girl when you're walking your dog they think the dog is cute right
walking with the dog walk pastor just gave a nice friendly smile I mean ice I
felt like some sort of but then again a form troll that had crawled out from
under the bridge it might be getting a lot of lecherous shit you know and
that's how she now treats the world we don't know who knows you can't take it
personal path that's what they'll tell you in the four agreements you've
ever read it I bought it and didn't read it I bought it on your recommendation
It's you could read it in like most things that would probably greatly help my life. I ignore them
That's what I did. I am working on a new bit about therapy
About how 90 % of the reason I ever go to therapy is to work on my problems with intimate relationships
Yeah, yeah, I've never left therapy where I didn't treat it like a weird breakup where I just slowly fade away
It's no different than I then a relationship exactly
It's every reason that brings me there
I that's how I end the therapy. It's I had so much tension with my
This week that I was like, okay, so now therapy is really no different than like just a relationship that I'm trying to work on
Like I I went in and she starts every she'll never listen. I she starts every one by looking at me and being like so
What's going on? That's how we start each week and it
It like it's like throwing a bucket of ice water in my face. I can't and I'm like
and I wind up talking around the issue for 50 minutes and then we finally latch
on to something and she's like that's time. Every single week because it's
that and I told her I was like you can't start with me anymore with so what's
going on? It's like it's this general shit and it makes me freak out and I don't
like it and she was like oh okay and we got tense and we got weird then when we
leave usually she's like have a great week and this week she goes so I
guess have whatever kind of week you want to have this drop this lady it wasn't
it wasn't quite as confrontational as I'm making it and I told her I was like I
know why you say what's going on it's a device but I felt exactly like
Tonus of Prana being like, I know what you're doing here, I know you could try and outsmart me like what like there's by the way
The therapist you see on TV shows where you go in and they go
Okay, so last week we were discussing your father would it you know, and it picks right it. That doesn't exist
I've had therapists my whole life. I've never had a therapist where it felt like there was any
You know like I've had great therapists. Yeah, but I've never felt that level of continuity
Maybe that's all that's what you get when you pay five hundred bucks an hour
I don't know but see my therapist too much tragic and I think it's my father
I'm like yet. I just mean like the continuation of the discussion. Yeah
Yeah, have you ever had a therapist that picks right up where you left off?
I never had that now
You know, I mean my favorite this is wildly politically incorrect
And I know you don't even like the sopranos. My favorite line in all the sopranos is
She talks to him for like a minute and like
like kind of like nails what he's like she nails him kind of and he goes this
sounds very gay to me and I I cackle laughing at that because it's like he it's
such a defense mechanism and he's such like a child yeah and that's how I am when
I get in there I'm like I go into therapy like please help me and then I'm like
quit trying to fucking help me yeah yeah I know what I'm doing it's it's a terrible
pattern of behavior as is most of what I do.
My favorite therapy scene ever is in Curb Your Enthusiasm.
Go and see him in the thong.
No, well that's great too.
It might be the same episode but he's in therapy and he walks out of therapy
at the beginning and Richard Lewis is there and he's like,
how are you doing?
Erts Rob Reiner and he's like, how are you doing?
Oh yeah.
It's like, I'm good.
And he goes, he goes, how was your session?
And he goes, this, it's ridiculous.
It's pointless, but you can't bother your friends
with this crap.
Yeah, I'm just like, that's truly what it is.
It's just, it's the room where you go
to be like, I hate the world, you know?
And then they go, it's okay to hate the world.
Well, it's what I always say, I go to therapy
because it's somebody listening to me
for a full hour without checking their phone.
That's the reason I go, I'll pay the money.
I don't care. I'll tell you what I do. I got to work this in the way because I have some bits on therapy, but I
Wrap it up half the time
You wrap it up pre -time. Oh, yeah, I'm staring at the clock. I'm like you might if we bail out. I'm done
I've said enough. I don't care anymore. I like I wrap it up myself. That's that's got to be
Something dysfunctional
This is a big kind of frustrating thing for me like you have an R rated movie. I know we're saying some boob aren't
Halloween 3, I noticed how carefully they were coming up this girl's nipples, and it was like a very tactical move that kind of annoyed me, and then I watched the documentary, and the girl was like I had a very strict, no nipple clause in my contract.
That stuff's really fascinating to me.
Yeah, I mean, you know, I'd call you a centipile. I've called you that before sure, but I'd say that's a mark of your
Cinephalia. Well, something a failure for sure. But now she this girl's covering up again like from and from my money you have an
R rated movie. Make an R rated movie. I mean, she's covering up because she's just about to have sex. There's a killer on the
and they just got what they think are corpse parts dumped on them.
I just can't let the flashback the 10 -year -old me waiting up all night to see
the nude scene in a movie.
Oh God, I would just...
Showtime used to do a thing called After Hours on Saturday nights.
Do you mean USA Up All Night?
No, no, no.
Showtime.
But showtime already had nudity, right?
Yeah, but they had a thing called pet, you know.
There's more details coming.
The story doesn't end at after hours.
They had a thing called After Hours in Saturday nights and it was right around the same
time that's in L was on.
And they would show like, you know, soft core porn basically.
So they'd show like Lady Chatterley's lover.
Whoa, you just blew my mind there because I have seen Lady Chatterley's lover.
Yeah.
I watched that many times.
That was a staple.
Yeah.
As were Emmanuel in space they why they showed all the Emmanuel sure there was always the originals like the ones that were committed to film
Yeah, something with it maybe a John Holmes at times would pop up right anyway
It would show at the same time as as as SNL and I had a TV in my room
That you had that I had showtime on and I would I
Would you were lucky put one channel the SNL and the other to show time and and have my finger on the fucking
in the flip to the last channel button.
Sure, and my dad would come in,
and I flip it real quick.
And my dad would be like, what are you doing?
You better not be watching one of those movies.
Yeah, on showtime.
And I was like, I'm not, I'm not Jesus' dad.
And as soon as you leave, I'd flip it back.
But I never masturbated to it, I would just watch it.
I used to masturbate endlessly to scramble porn,
just like an American pie.
Completely scrambled to where you could barely see
what was happening, didn't care.
Yeah, your kids don't know how lucky you have it. You really don't I
Also, I don't think I've discussed this on this podcast, but I used to sneak out our rated movies from the video store in the Tucker the man in his dream box
Because I was like nobody's ever going to rent Tucker the man in his dream and they never did so
Finally like 20 weeks in it doing this because I would switch the barcodes peel the two barcodes off and I also wasn't trying to rent porn
I wanted to see like good fellows and shit. I couldn't see our rated movies
So I would switch the two barcodes and I would put good fellows in the Tucker the man in his dream case and
Put Tucker in the good fellows case and hope nobody rented it and vice versa
Why would you switch the barcodes because they scan it like it had to be completely legit
Right, but if they scanned the barcode was on the cassette itself. Oh, okay
So and I wanted to make sure I covered on my basis because in my mind when you're that age you're like they're gonna call the police if they find out
Yeah, they'd be like, oh, we got the wrong tape and yeah, and they put it on themselves. Yeah, we're just rent you the R rated movie in that car
Yeah, they probably would not have cared if I wanted to do that right but finally one woman goes boy
You really must love Tucker the man in his dream. I was like a 12 year old kid, and I'm like I love cars
I can't believe you keep going back to the Tucker well. Yeah, well, I said I love cars
It's about the Jeff Bridges and he invented sure of course
So one night, I remember I came home, my dad was sitting next to a bag of videos from Schnooks,
which was the grocery store, Missouri, and I would rent six at a time on my bike and then
ride home. And he had all six in his bag sitting there and he's waiting for me. And I was like, God,
damn it. And this was during one of the few times where I had tried to rent some nudity and I rented
like basic instinct. Right. So and I'm probably 14 years old and I had already seen porn
over at a friend's house but he's like I walked in the door and as the door shuts he goes
what's next, Patrick? What's next? Am I going to go into your room and find the video tapes
where you actually see the penis going into the vagina? I couldn't have made that anymore awkward.
It couldn't have been worse. I was and I remember that by the way
That's a verbatim quote and I'm a thousand percent sure of that and that's 20 25 years old
Because I remember it very well when I was like good. I'm sorry now when he would run our rated movies
Yeah, and I knew that he wouldn't leave the house over the weekend. I would come creeping out on my room
4 a .m
Bring the tape downstairs once he went to bed at 3 .30 a .m
Bring the tape downstairs and watch it with my ear to the speaker. I did that for Pulp thick.
That's the first time I saw Pulp Fiction. One of the greatest movies ever made. I watched it with my ear to the speaker looking up with my eyeball touching the screen.
Because I was so terrified and I was 14. I saw that in the theater with my friend and we enjoyed it. I'm happy for you.
Good God, Pat. This is like a prison camp scenario. It was terrible.
I remember when I was 19 I was home from college. I had a I had a porno movie called anal honey pie part two
Bright red tape sure right red cassette tape
I had it in my room in like, you know, soccer or something my mom goes. I come home one day. I'm home for the summer and my mom goes
I hope I'm not embarrassing you. I was cleaning in your room today
I found a tape a red tape and I obviously know what it is and I go mom
Stay out of my room, you know because I'm mortified yeah, she goes
I just have one question to ask you and I was like what she goes are you gay?
You can tell me and I was like it was called anal honey pie and I go no, I'm not gay
I'm just it's important movie and then I told my best friend that night the story my friend Jim who you met
Yeah, yeah, I told him that night that that straight at night and he goes and we were really high and he goes
You realize what you were saying to your mother was I'm not gay mom. I just love watching chicks take it in the shit
Yeah, which your mom was probably very relieved by the announcement
My mother my friend
I'll just say Ben Ben a because they're he might listen and I want to I don't know I want I don't want his name out there
but one of my best friends, he wrote down word for word, this pen house forum, he had got his
hands on a pen house forum and he copied word for word, the story for me and this yellow spiral
notebook to jerk off to kids. Do you understand how lucky you have it? I want you to step back.
I'm masturbating to something my friend copied down in a spiral notebook. So he wrote down this
erotic story and
My mom did the same shit. I was cleaning your room. By the way, my mom never cleaned my room
I had to clean my room. She was cleaning your room and I found this yellow spiral notebook and
Pat what's going on here and she thought that I had written the story and it was an original story that I had written
It was insanely graphic. She must have thought this kid's got talent
He's a little pervy, but he's got a gallon. It was very it was beautifully written
But I said mom, a friend of mine at school and I started to say Ben and then changed the name. I go wrote this down and gave it to me and he was like, check out the story I wrote.
I read a couple of words and I was like, whoa, this is not for me. Right.
And, you know, the pages were probably stuck together. And I don't know if she believed me or not, but it was a pretty good cover on the fly.
And then what happened she was very very angry and crying and etc. Oh boy you made her cry
huh and then it's like now you know like you know I can go out to get drinks with my mom and she
gets wasted and I'll be like oh fuck this or you know like it's so sick and I hope I'm not that way
with the children I may or may not have you know I remember I'll tell you a double whammy I was in high
school, came home, had a tape in the VCR. I'd been renting spice. Remember spice? Did you have that?
I know what it is, but I didn't have it. I didn't know. I didn't know. There was, you know,
back when you had pay -per -view, where you had to really pay for the movie on the TV. Right.
On your through your cable network or whatever. Well, I guess you still kind of do that, but it was
it was a different system. There was its thing on the spice channel and it was porno. They'd cut out
the insertions shots. Yeah, but it was porno. I think that's what I was watching scrambled.
And yeah, and I would I would lie to my mom because there was enough there was enough in the price
difference. Right. It was close enough that like the Spice movies are like $5 .99 and the regular
movies are like $3 .99. So I could get away with like getting a couple Spice movies if I carefully
pick the titles of the films, you know? Yes. So I'd find ones that didn't sound too suspicious
suspicious, and I'd rent them, and then I would tape it on a videotape. And then I'd masturbate
to it later. Okay. And shit hit the fan one day because I was, you know, I did it one day,
and then I left the house, came home, got caught. My mom was waiting for me, had the cable bill,
fresh out of the mail, with like $35 and spice charges on it. Plus she found the tape and the
VCR and knew what I had been doing. That was a bad day. But like, moms, there's no moms listening to this probably, but moms,
why would you do that? Why, like, I still deal with these effects to this day of the, like, shock and horror my parents have with anything to do with sexuality or me being 13 and having some interest in sexuality, like that fucks you up for life.
Well, I was more in trouble I think for the money aspect. I mean my mom was mad about the porn too that I brought it into her house
Whatever, but like the money thing you know, like the perfect way to handle it is like Dan Weiston parenthood
I don't know why I talk exclusively about parenthood on this horror movie pocket and Dan Weist and Weist
But yeah, she finds the bag of porno and she's like let's talk about it, you know blah blah blah. Yeah
Isn't it like Joaquin Phoenix or something? Yeah, it is a young Joaquin Phoenix young Joaquin
And she's like, well, you know, I know you must be interested in sexuality or filmmaking, you know, one of the other. It's a good job.
So Ken Hanley, because I feel like we need to at least talk about Halloween for one second.
Ken posted, it's a great post on Facebook. I'm liking it now.
Fact, the three best Halloween, Ken is the thing is our Fangoria guy, and you should follow him on Twitter.
And he knows you're shit, man.
He's a he's a horror expert fact the three best Halloween movies in order are Halloween three
Halloween and Halloween H2O Halloween 4 ain't bad. Halloween 2 is overrated. I agree
Halloween 6 is underrated
Halloween 5 and Halloween resurrection are both mostly garbage as we're shissing right now
Rob zombies Halloween 2 is better than Rob zombies Halloween
I can't believe he's putting six over five. I think that's ludicrous. Well, I got to watch both of those. Those are the two I haven't seen. I mean, other than, other than being introduced to a young Paul Rudd in part six. I mean, I don't, I, I don't see the value in it.
Six is also the one where they it's called the curse of Michael Myers, and they make up this thing where like this is some ancient evil
Indian spirit thing it's it's stupid. Yeah, yeah stupid. It's like it. It's not I don't know
They really go back to those ancient spirits and these things. I
Owned now every Friday the 13th moving. I've only seen the original and the the recent reboot
And I'm excited to go through them there. They're fun. The original in my opinion is one of the worst ones
One is one of the is one of the least exciting his Kevin Bacon and one. Yeah Kevin Bacon's in it
He gets a good kill too. Have you seen sleep away camp?
I've never seen sleep away camp. That's fantastic and even 30 years later. I
Will not reveal the twist of that movie because it is so
incredible. Is it a comedy? Beyond incredible for its time. It would be incredible now.
I think it was a comedy. Subway camp, you know, it's got a few comedic elements, but it's
no different than Fred at 13. They just have an amazing twist in it.
All right. And they do it in like a crazy way. So if you haven't seen it, say it.
I just saw a speaking of slasher films with Jamie Lee Curtis. I just watched terror
Train enjoyed it thoroughly never seen it. I did see prom night his love prom night is territory and set on a train
That would be why it's called territory. Okay. I thought maybe they were running a train on J. M. Lee
Great great flick man. All right. I'll say Leslie Nielsen. He's in prom night
Leslie Nielsen. Leslie Nielsen is in prom night. Yeah, he is. Yeah
I don't remember who's he playing prom night? I don't know. I don't remember that per date
I don't know. Yeah, no, Teretrain I'd highly recommend to any fan of the Slasher genre or the
scene that hurt his catalog. I just bought because I had never seen it and it fell off Netflix
instant. The blob remake. Have you seen that? I love the blob remake. I believe I own it on DVD.
Yeah, shit. I should have borrowed it. Yeah, I'm excited to see because I've always heard it's great.
It's fun. Kevin Dylan introducing Kevin Dylan in that film. Yeah, that's right. Yeah.
Yeah, I was Johnny trauma. Yeah, actually, that's not his first movie. His first movie is heaven help us. Oh, yeah, which he is tremendous in his things going to do the movie originally.
I got this Johnny bananas cartoon coming out with dice. He's got the best one of the best lines and deliveries I've ever heard in a movie is the kitty picks on and heaven help us. This kid sees her.
they get in trouble for a prank they pull up school and this fat nerdy kid
Caesar goes, I'll never get into Harvard now. I'll be forced to go to Queen's
College and Kevin Dylan goes, you want to fit right in at Queen's College? Not bad
cab. It's a nice zinger from the side. Sure. He just lands it, man. All right. He
is a master. Yeah I like that Kevin Dillon but yeah the blob remake is very good. I think it's
I think that I think it's one of the few remakes of a classic horror film
that actually the story in the original film or the original idea were serviced by the remake.
Like they were able to do things technically that they just never could have done in the fifth.
Right. And it could obviously get rid of who's like a darebons old rally partner. They did, I think dream warriors love dream warriors. One of my favorite horror movies for sure is the mist. Love it.
Talk about it. Yeah, I was so blown away by the ending of it. And tonight I think I'm going to go home and watch the black and white version because I have not watched it yet. And I've heard it's the preferred director's cut. Yeah, the black and white's great.
speaking of we've been sort of talking famous horror franchises on here
steal the other night at Best Buy steal steal you might guess I got a
Steal dry white oh I gotta wait but what is steel not spawn no no I'm saying I
gotta steal the shack superhero movie yes okay all right let's move fast I but
That's not what yeah, I didn't buy steel
By the way, this is in Halloween for this is like the cool part of Halloween for she has to climb out onto the roof
And then they just kind of ripped it off half -ass regurgitated in this one. Anyway, I'm
What do they do? They're watching this on a video feed the Omen all four original trilogy and remake on blue ray Iona
799 whoa
brand new I own it
but I think I bought it for like 15.
You can find shit like that.
Tinker around Amazon, like this thing I bought
on Amazon is like six bucks
and it's the blob Christine, the seventh sign
with Demi Moore, which I've never seen.
You see your boobs in that.
It's pretty sweet.
Pre -job, though, right?
I don't remember if it's pre -job,
but she's...
I think she got the job for strip T's.
She's pregnant in it.
Okay.
But you do see your baby.
With the devil's baby.
And it's still kind of hot, I think so.
Yeah.
Something like that, I don't remember.
I almost bought a Stephen King one the other night at best again at Best Buy it was 10 bucks. It was misery
Needful things carry and the dark half but I already owned carry in misery
And I didn't really care to own the dark half and dark half is terrible. Needful things is
Barely okay
Misery is a masterpiece and carries a masterpiece. Yeah, I wanted to get it for needful things
I thought well then I could sell the other DVDs, but I didn't pull the trigger on it
It's okay and a lot of times you buy those four packs eight packs or whatever and the quality is really terrible
Well, that's I I feel like these Omen blue rays are not gonna be like true blue ray. They know that they are Greg's I watched them. Oh, yeah, yeah
799 I mean, which that's a steal. I gotta go into best
But I mean best buy at this point should just be like bartering with you like you're an India or something
I mean, they should just be like, yeah, what do you want for like you know like the deals? They're going under DVDs are amazing
All right, I'll head up there. Are they going under like in every department or just with media?
Yeah, I mean, I guess if you want a TV although I got my TV on Amazon, you know, I think I think probably for electronics
They're still doing okay a washer dry or that sort of thing. Some say Amazon's the devil. I love it
I do support the the physical stores. I go to a Meba I do two records once every week. Maybe every two weeks
by DVDs wherever I can, but I do love Amazon as well.
I mean, it comes in very handy when you can't find the thing.
It's great, and then I do feel really bad about it,
but they're offering things,
they're almost immediately to your door,
and they're always so much cheaper,
but we are supporting the destruction of the small business.
Well, I'll tell you, for one thing,
it's, I started painting recently,
Yep, and I got this stuff on Amazon because I was able to get like a
15 color acrylic paint set for eight bucks
Yeah, I was looking in art supply stores and a single tube was $10
Yeah, I can't
For some throwaway bullshit hobby. I'm gonna do like just to kind of relax
I'm like I'm not gonna spend $300 on it
Yeah, it's gonna stress me out. It's a really sad thing, you know like I eventually well now
I mean here it's not an issue but in Missouri I was like fuck Walmart, you know like my dad was like never go to Walmart
They're they're disgraceful. They're terrible people etc
So I stopped going but Walmart was kind of the in -store Amazon of its day, you know
Like they just did everything you get everything there at the cheapest price and it's hard not to go, right
But you are destroying businesses when you do it. I love a target. I'm not gonna lie
Target's great. I love target. I'll do a target for a lot of my
Yeah, and and target if I'm not mistaken doesn't have it's a little more expensive than Walmart
But it doesn't have any of the bad rap that Walmart has right no target has a very clean wrap
Yeah, they're like the nice Walmart by the way this is always a sign of like a
Really bad horror movies when you're in like the final
Yeah, the final moments here and Busta Rhyme is doing like a stereotypical shitty karate high -yah voice
Well, do you know why he did that? Because at the beginning of the movie, this is all the foreshadowing they gave you that the beginning of the movie he was watching a Kung Fu movie and in his hotel room and getting excited about it.
And then in this final showdown with Michael Myers, Buster Rhymes, Karate kicks Michael Myers and literally goes, hey, hey!
And I think it's supposed to be like kind of funny. I've seen like a meme or
some sort of video of Busta Rhymes kicking off the door and going trick -or -treat
motherfucker. Look I'm a big Busta Rhymes fan. We haven't gotten there yet. I'm
a big big Busta Rhymes fan. Oh his music is. I don't approve of the movie
casting of him in this now. I like him in movies. I liked him in higher
learning a lot. I fucking love how to learn it. Yeah and I'll still put on
Buh -ha got you all in check which look when a guy's got you in check he's got
you in check yeah there's something you can do about it higher learning is a
very good you know what it's singleton where's singleton come back baby I got
today speaking of Academy screeners and that's probably what your FedEx thing
wasn't your door I got the Academy Awards screener of Furious 7 oh really and
you flip it open and it tells what they want to be considered for. Best picture, best
actor, Vin Diesel. Oh boy. Come on, guys. I like Furia 7 and I'm like, come on, guys.
I haven't taken that home. I haven't seen it. I look forward to getting
the screener. I was very excited to get the straight out of Compton screener the other day.
Straight out of Compton is amazing and Furia 7 is really good. Yeah, I'm looking forward
to it. Furia 7, it was kind of funny. I saw it with Pete actually, Pete Holmes. We went
up to the Vista here. And we got up and we're like, that was really fun. And you looked
around and like, I bet half that crowd, and I'm talking about some bros and that crowd,
some dudes head tears streaming down their face. They handled the pull walker shit really,
really well. Does he die in the movie? He does. And basically they have him like driving
off to heaven. And they handle it kind of beautifully. And I was like, they handled that
really well, but when I looked around and somebody crying, I thought, well, this franchise
must mean more to these people than it does to me, I guess, but look, people love that
front. There's a reason there's seven of them, man. And they are fun. And I think seven
is about the best, really. That's what's so crazy to me is that they got up to seven and
seven is considered amongst fans. It seems to be like the best one. Yeah. And five is great.
You know, there's no real slip off like they they keep it pretty tight Tokyo drift is probably the low point
No, that's the one I didn't see
Not nothing to do with
I was just going with that marinate disliking Asians. I will see Tokyo. Well, I didn't know it had anything to do with the others
And then I was reading stuff about seven and they were like this is the first one to take place
After the events of Tokyo
I was like they were they were it was I was like I didn't know it was that deep. All right. I
Went
This year I was on a hiatus for my job. I got like three months off a year, which is great and I
Went up to the movie theater and they were showing all seven
It was the day the new one came out and they were showing all seven and a row and I was like
I'm gonna do this and write like a funny article about I used to write articles all the time for different
Movie websites stuff. I'm gonna do a funny article. Get it published
you know really do this and as part one starts I was like no I can't do this I
can't watch seven fasten if you're moving I walked right out I'm like I
write a little funny snarky article and I've given up 14 hours of my life
that's not that's not 14 hours that's probably 16 hours I was gonna do it with
Star Wars I already got my tickets for the Force Awakens are they doing all
You're doing all seven and it's dig this. It's the Force Awakens premieres at 7 p .m. on the
December, the Thursday, December 17th, whatever the hell it is. Right.
So the marathon is only that day and it leads up to that. So the marathon starts at 1 a .m.
with Phantom Menace and then you're just there all day and I couldn't get
anybody to do it with me and I was like you know what this is ridiculous I
can't do this but did you buy tickets for the new one? I have tickets for
just the Force Awakens. Did you get one for me for your boy? I'm seeing it in
Pennsylvania because I'm gonna be home for work and then right into Christmas. I
made fun of everyone who bought them and then I was like wait a minute I don't
want to wait a week to see it I should probably buy some. I mean if I were you I'd
hit that 10 a .m. Friday screening when everybody else is at work. Is it
available? Well, I'll be at work. You're not, you're not on break yet by
then December what? 19th or whatever. Oh, yeah, I'm, I'm going to break. I'll buy it.
You're right. Yeah, nobody's going to be at that. Go to that. There's going to be
screenings around the clock. You can go in the morning on Friday. Yeah, that
sounds. I mean, I am really excited. I almost went up. They did it at the
Sinorama dome here in LA. They had all three back to the futures on that back
the future day. And I wanted to go. But then I was like, you hit a certain age and like,
you just start to feel so stupid doing it, you know? Like I used to be like, you know,
I'd watched the whole back of Future Trilogy on a Friday night and have the best time and drink
some sodas. And now it's just kind of like, you feel like such a waste of life if you do that.
Also three is, you know, come on, that's a half trilogy right there as far as I'm concerned.
What are you saying? I'm saying one is a masterpiece and halfway through two three quarters of the way through two you get kind of stop caring
Because they oh and I disagree because then you because you know that there's my problem with the second the second one is
The whole time once you get to the part where they go to the 50s again
You're like well, they're now they're just going to the 50s again even the makers of the film have said they didn't like that aspect of it because it was just a
retread and I was like so now we're just seeing the events of the 50s of the
first movie in a different perspective. I think here's trick or trick. Oh bus
surround just a trick or treat mother fucker. Look. I just watched two
because eight million people were talking about it this week for the whole it was
the day he went to thing. It is genius that they go back into the first movie.
You've never seen that really. Oh, but it's too soon to do in the future. Yeah, I agree. I completely have I told you what my lay
Out for the third what for how it should have went what should have been. I don't think so
This is what it should have been
The entire god damn second fucking movie should have been in the future because we waited five years to see that
Yeah, it was so exciting at the end of the first one when he goes when you're like oh my god
they're going to go into the actual future now. Yeah. The whole movie should have been that. By the way,
end of the. Hold on. Okay. Yeah. Go ahead. End of that movie should have been them going back to
1985. The camera pulls up as Marty steps into the town square and realizes Biff has taken over 1985.
And it's this dystopian reality, whatever. Then part three is them trying to rectify 1985,
25 come to terms with all that then they go back to the 50s
Yeah, the second half of part three and then didn't you're tying it back to the original and then it ends and you don't want them to ever
Go to the old lab. Oh god almighty. No, it's fucking terrible. That's fourth. I've sent it a million times that third movie to me
Felt like when they would do like the facts of life goes to Europe
Like you know, I need to watch three again because I that's the one I've seen by far the least terrible
I watched to this week and I I fucking loved it
one is a masterpiece, no questions.
Perfect.
But three is kind of a question mark for me.
I need to rewatch it.
Three.
I love it as a kid.
Loved it.
Yeah, I just, I just, I, I hate three.
I hate it.
I've never sat through it in it's entirety.
I tried a million times.
I can't throw it.
You've never finished it?
I know it.
I've seen it out of sequence.
Like, you know, I know all the parts.
I know everything that happens.
But I've never sat through it and viewing it
and watched it straight through.
I've tried to really wrap to it. They really wrap victims of things in blankets like they do in movies
I don't know. I've never been on a murder scene
Seems only when there's a murder. Yeah, that happens. Well, then they do it in die hard
I guess a lot of people do get murdered and yeah, it's some sort of traumatic if any of them
There's been an explosion. I just don't see cops having a lot of blankets on hand. Well the paramedics do that
They've got the cop you know, and I think it's stupid. This is the best part
Buster rhymes description of Michael Myers here at the end
Yeah, actually here we go. Here he's
Michael Mars is not a sound bite. He's not a tie -in. He's not a scandal.
He's a killer shark. In baggy ass overalls.
Did you hear that? That's fucking terrible. He's a killer shark.
In baggy ass overalls.
This was the end. This was the end of the Michael Myers legacy.
It's just a wrap. They never made a movie after except for Rob Zombie.
Yeah, and I hate the Rob Zombie ones. Holy shit. That was terrible.
That's that's the end of it. They're doing part three now.
Rob Zombie. They're doing another Halloween. I don't know if it's going to be a...
They keep... they won't say if it's like part three or if it's another reboot.
you know they're fucking rebooting the leather face again and the rebooting
Fred of the 13th again it's like why would I reboot it just make a sequel I
don't know you know what I mean like yeah I don't know I was watching because I
I'm sorry Joe but this is the back of the future podcast that we're doing not
Not a poor movie pocket.
I was watching back in time, which
is this new Netflix documentary.
How is that?
I haven't watched it yet.
It's very solid.
There's a lot of great stuff in it.
But they seem pretty happy with the trilogy, I would say.
Like, they don't talk shit about two or three, really.
No, they seem happy with it.
They seem happy with it.
You know, they like that the third one is the old west. They were like we thought it'd be a lot of fun. Yeah, my problem with the third one is it the focus shifts. It's not the whole point in that movie about that series to me is is the salvation of the McFly family.
Right, that's the whole point of the movie and the third one suddenly is like a sweet. I got to go save doc
That how does it have to do with anything? Yeah, like it's like it's it's just a separate story
That should be a short story in an anthology of fantasy. Yeah, exactly
Yeah, they were saying
They see
Back what we're just talking about back to the future they you said they see you were watching the documentary and they seem happy with it
No, I know they do seem happy with it. I don't remember what I said. I had something important
about that future. Now, see pop up here. There it is. His eyes open at the very end. He's still alive,
which it's just stupid. Oh, I know what it was. So, did you see back in the future one in theaters in 1985?
I mean, my parents took me and I was
traumatized because I only knew Michael J. Fox from family ties and that's why they took me to see it.
Right, and I loved him so much and to see him being to see him swearing was traumatic for me. Oh, wow because I was in like second grade
Now it upset me very much
But I love the movie. I love the movie. Sure
They were basically saying which kind of blew my mind is that when it first aired in theaters, and I would have been four
I did not see it in theaters
That they did not have the to be continued at the end of it
That was added for the VHS release.
No, I saw it in the theater.
It said to be continued.
No, it's in the documentary.
They didn't have it in there.
And well, if it did in between one and two,
VHS came to light and they put that on
because they knew they were going to make the sequel.
I can tell you this.
If that wasn't in there, it was glaringly obvious.
It was in plan.
That there was going to be a sequel.
Well, my parents and I left going.
I can't wait to see the next one.
Oh, okay. Well now because they didn't have a whole lot of faith and it didn't seem like and they're talking about
Gail who co -wrote it with some necklace in the movie and he's like, oh yeah, nobody knew and he's like
We just thought they were heading off to the next adventure, but we never thought there was gonna be a sequel
Yeah, well it was five years later and then they did parts two and three together
Yeah, like Lord of the Rings style and which I had never heard of at that time
I think that was one of the first movies to ever do that
There's also and they go into this in the documentary because I remember this vividly because that's a mechus talked in like a a
Press kit type thing about how the hoverboards were real
Yes, and there was like a I think it was on TV like probably after you know
Probably after the fucking facts of life or whatever, but
There's a mechus is saying
and hoverboards are real and we just haven't quite released the market yet.
He's like, fucking with kids, like having a little fun.
But they talk about how there's this whole generation of kids who's like,
let me see these hoverboards.
Yeah, I remember trying to make them and they had this guy going in like a half pipe
and it wasn't as far off the ground, but they were off the ground.
They are trying to make them.
Yeah, no, I know.
Did you see the sketch on Kimmel where they show up?
I waited the whole night to watch it and then forgot.
It was great.
Yeah, all right. All right. I'll watch on. Yeah, he's doing his monologue. He's talking about how he's like today's the day that they go to and back to the future to and then the time machine shows up in Doc and Marty get out and they do it.
It's a little bit. It's a pretty long bit and it's a very actually very funny and he's great. It was great. Okay, and the whole thing was them being like, you must have hoverboards here and you know,
No, no, like that was the gag like we don't have any of that stuff
That's good and you know at one point Marty's like doc two thousand future sucks. This is terrible. Yeah
It was funny anyway
I'm happy we were able to bring you this special Halloween edition. I think I think we
even talked about leprechaun more than we just talked about Halloween resurrection. I'm
sorry. But some weeks you just don't give a shit about the movie, all right? And I hope
you just like us. This is a couple of men. Even though Joe is anti -Semitic and racist and
hates women, I hope you come back for me and my quips. Where are they getting these things?
It's just terrible. And please, I'm not kidding. If you're listening, we heard what our fan total is,
what our listener total is, it's really good. And thank you all so much for listening. You can
told us we're doing really good numbers. Thank you. If, you know, if a couple of you go and pop us
off of five stars, we'd be sitting pretty.
Yeah, guys, we'd appreciate that.
We would appreciate it.
We'll keep bringing you the goods here on We'll See You
and Hell presentation the Fangoria Podcast Network
produced by Thomas DeFail, executive produced by Ken Hanley
of Fangoria Entertainment for press opportunities,
advertising inquiries, and information
about We'll See You and Hell contact Ken via his email Ken
at Fangoria .com.
Thank you, everybody.
Thanks, everyone.
And what I want to say each week and haven't I only answered somebody on Twitter about this is that the opening song is written in
Performed by one Joe DeRosa
People love it. Very nice Pat. Thank you very much.
People should know.
All right. Happy Halloween. Be safe.
Don't eat any candy with razor blades in it.