I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell.
Hey, wait a minute, yo's great, it's big problems.
I think I'm a dream, shit no, I say, hey, hey, hey, hey.
I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, you in hell.
Oh, welcome to we'll see you in hell.
Oh, it's the podcast that talks movies.
My name is Joe DeRosa.
My name is Patrick Walsh.
Hello everybody.
Welcome to a special episode of We'll See You In Hell, where we are going to discuss
the 550th annual Academy Awards.
What was it?
80?
80th?
94th.
Holy shit.
You know, the 100th, they better do some big shit for the 100th.
If society is still alive, if Hollywood is still alive, if movies are still being made, but
we're coming up in that 100th.
This was the 94th.
It felt like I watched 91 through 94 in one sitting because I fell asleep multiple times.
Now I've watched it all.
I've watched it at work, but I would wake up and be like, oh my god, like I thought I was
excited to watch this and I just, I missed the first hour.
Then I, you know, I was not watching during the infamous slap, but then I felt like I
needed to go back and watch the whole show awake because I wanted to see if anything in
the air was leading us to the slap.
Was there attention?
Could we have predicted one of history's greatest events according to Twitter?
And no, I thought it was overall a very boring show, but we're going to discuss every detail
of it.
We'll get to that later.
But more importantly, Joe, how are you?
I'm fine, Pat.
Well, you know, I'm better.
I'm better than I was the last time we spoke.
I'm working on me.
Same.
Yeah.
And I finally started eating a bit better, and I don't know.
You know what?
I don't even want to talk about what I'm doing.
So when I fail at it, I'm not like I failed.
I just, I'm doing, I'm doing a few things to make myself feel better.
And I thought about how many times on this show I've said I'm done drinking.
And I just like, I can't say that anymore, because there's a lengthy record of me saying
this 700 times.
Yeah.
It's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's a, it's a haunts and tunts all of us.
That's tough.
It's a tough give up.
Yeah.
I definitely took a bit of a breather this week because I was, I was at a point where I
I had, I think it had been 12 or 14 days where I had been completely shit faced every single night.
And I finally, I was like, Jesus Christ, dude, I got to take a breather here. This is insane.
But, you know, as much as I felt like I was making excuses and whatnot,
the first article I saw two days ago when I woke up in the morning was from the Atlantic.
And it said it was titled Why is everybody acting so weird right now?
Right. And it's, it's, it is addressing all of this like everybody has like this PTSD from COVID.
So it's tough. And I think we saw the culmination of the PTSD on the 94th Oscars this year.
But unquestionably, I mean, I, I think so many people, myself very much included,
need to stay busy. So the demons, the brain, the self hatred, et cetera, doesn't attack you and get the better of you.
And everybody having to spend two years with nothing but that noise in their heads and nothing to do, drove people nuts.
I'm actually surprised I'm not in a worse mental position than I am right now.
But there's a, there's a bunch of, and I was trying to think, is this just something I didn't notice before, but no, there's a, there's a big rash of 50 year old men dying now.
You know, Sagitt Taylor Hawkins now, like Taylor Hawkins was in better shapes than anyone I know, granted he had a big drug problem. Don't get me wrong.
But it's just kind of like for me, why he died.
Drugs, he had 10 drugs in his system.
And Colombian hotel. Now many of the drugs were antsy depressants and so forth, but also, you know, your, your heroin and other shit.
I can't believe the guy could do heroin and then get up and, and drum with that energy for three hour shows. It's kind of impressive, but I don't think rolls spoken out yet.
It's just sad as hell, you know, he was a guy who.
Had so much love for what he did so much joy. I still remember I saw them at the pageant, which is a pretty small theater in St. Louis.
And that was when I was most obsessed with them. There is nothing left to lose had just come out their first two albums remain two of my favorites.
And I still love the third actually, but they had him on like a drum riser, Tommy Lee style and then they did, they still do this, but him and roll would switch places.
His role would draw him and he would sing and man, it was just a blast. One of the best rock concerts I've ever seen.
Queens of the Stone Age opening, you know, just incredible evening.
But, yeah, it's, and it's scary, it's scary as hell because everyone is seeing all these people die who are in seemingly great condition.
And then of course, there's all the rumors about the vaccine causing shit and then everybody's like, oh boy, are we all just waiting to drop dead from weird complications of the vaccine.
Is it just depression? Is it people being fucked in the head? Of course, there's no way to know.
But it just seems like a lot more beloved figures dying lately than I'm used to are comfortable with.
Maybe it's just that when you get older, you're, you're people you love are going to be dying and you can't do anything about it. I don't know.
But like Danero, but you know, all the, these people are all still alive. So it's odd to have people at our level our age group passing on.
It's probably not that unique.
It feels unique because it's our experience, but you know, you look at the 60s.
They're going down left and right, you know, mom's pass and Jimmy Hendrix and Keith, and you know, so it's probably just but, but, but it certainly does.
It was, um, amplify what we're all feeling, uh, just the gloom and doom, uh, everything.
Counselor, terror.
No, did you see that? Oh my god, I sent it to you because it was the worst joke of a person being seriously making a joke that I've ever seen was the, um, what was it a Trump junior joke I tweet. I sent you last night, the tweet.
Yeah, yeah.
And it was, I can't believe the guy wrote this seriously.
Regardless of you can't believe Donald Trump junior did something.
Well, that's not what I mean, he's on Coke 24 seven.
I've seen the guy in interviews.
And he's, he's well spoken. And he seems like he has his own way with words.
I just can't believe he tweeted.
I can't believe he tweeted this unironically. I don't mean because of.
I actually thought you were sending this to me like, I agree.
No, no, no, it was funny.
Donald Trump junior tweeted yesterday April Fool's Day is canceled because nothing could be a bigger joke than the joke that's running our country right now with three exclamation points.
It sounds like a like one of the jokes we would make like folks.
Right. Yeah.
But I don't think he meant like that. I think he thought that that was like an original funny joke to make. It's terrible.
He did. And I've been talking on the solo corner a lot. Me and two buddies of mine watch Bill Maher every week now and make fun of it.
It's like kind of the highlight of my week because I'm out here with no real close friends or anything.
And Bill Maher does jokes worse than that every week.
Most of them.
Oh, stop it.
Joe, I swear to God, I swear to God, he's doing jokes that are they're older than the GI Jane joke that caused history to fall to its knees.
But they're also just lame and terrible and he sits in stairs of the audience until they they're not going to laugh, but until they applaud his goal is applause.
And he bites his upper lip like who wait till they get a load of this one. And it's some joke that you would have heard Billy crystal make in 1984.
The only reason I just I don't.
I'm not trying to be difficult. The only reason I'm not going with you on this is because.
And I won't say who it was, but you sent me another thing from TV recently and you said audible groans in this thing.
And then I watched it and I was like, he's doing really well.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
No, not Mar, not Mar, something else.
No, you're talking about Jeff Foxworthy.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Something I think that I think you would care enough to not talk shit about.
Okay.
Because God knows you might have a connection to it.
I'm just saying you set me a thing and you said audible groans. It's horrible.
And I watched.
I was like, he's doing really well.
Like he's just going over well. I don't know what he meant by audible.
I felt like you were maybe exaggerating how it went over a bit.
I don't mean that in a shitty way.
I just mean, okay, I got to find out who that was.
Oh, I know you're talking about.
Yeah.
In fact, I've kind of started to like that one a little bit.
I should have been embarrassed to admit I wanted to hate it, but.
Wait, we talk about John Stewart.
Yes.
Okay.
I was talking about silence.
You know, the clip.
No, no, no.
No, I know.
I'm saying I watched the clip though.
And I was like, he's doing well.
Like he's getting laughs and people are clapping.
And I don't know.
It seems like it's going over well.
Oh, I don't.
I mean, I, I what maybe people digitally remove claps.
I don't know.
I watched a five minute silent clip of John Stewart.
I watched a five minute silent clip from Trevor Noah.
And.
Ever know I think it's still doing it from home.
I think there's no even back in the city.
Oh, maybe that's the reason.
I don't know.
No, but I mean, it's crazy.
Like when I see Daily Show clips, I'm like, guys, you know, you can.
You can be in a room together now, right?
Like I guess I haven't seen any recent clips.
I mean, look, nobody nobody does it for me.
Any better than what's your name?
Samantha B.
No.
And that she's a favorite of yours.
No, the fucking got to do a code switch.
Oh boy.
Amber.
Roughkin.
Whole.
Yeah.
Sorry.
Talk about rough emphasis on rough.
I'll lips with the best of clips of rough and end of.
What's your name?
Lily Singh, who was way beyond rough and the clips of those shows that that are.
Their best foot forward are just shocking to me sometimes.
I would argue.
Roughin.
I mean, having.
Drunk.
Standing in a corner to party the way you argue greatest metal band of all time.
Like I would argue that's how much I believe she's stinks the worst out of anybody I've ever seen.
It's just a terrible.
Terrible show.
It's terrible.
They've a packed audience.
And it's like, and you're like, wait.
Wait, is it a small audience because of COVID and then you hear that when they have to applaud at the end, you're like, no, that's for.
And they're critically acclaimed, you know, that's kind of the other issue is like what, what is happening, but so be it. Also, you know, never met anyone who's seen either show.
They canceled the, the sing show and then she immediately had like a three year overall deal for several million dollars.
It's a wild time. It's a wild time. Yeah. Well, that's the thing. That's what'll happen now is you'll have like, you know, four episodes of a comedy central show.
And then it bombs and then they're like, we're handing the reins of the Transformers franchise over to you. Yeah. Okay. I guess so.
And look, you know, sometimes people get a bum deal and they're really talented and you get it. Sometimes you don't, you just don't know, but that's the nature of the biz.
I got here's a story about the biz in a way. And then well, more about Twitter, which is the biz anymore, but I got blocked yesterday by my own fan account.
Okay. What did you do? I assume you did something. What did I do? I assume you did something. What they do.
So you have a Joe to roast a fan account?
Well, I do, but that's not the one that blocked me. I have a band with my friend Paul Shell called salsa windfall.
And we put a record out years ago. Yeah, I never talk. I don't talk. I don't really talk about it to anybody. Okay.
We don't play out. We just record stuff. But we put an album out years ago on it was iTunes. It was before the streaming music services. And you know, it came and went. Nobody knew it was there. I wasn't really proud of the record, to be honest, I didn't like the way it sounded.
And I just didn't think it was a good representation of us or anything, but whatever it was out there. I thought Jeff Lynn overproduced it if I'm being honest.
You know, so let the music speak for itself, Jeff. Everything ain't yellow. You know, I was pissed that he added so many strings. I also thought you overpaying him at $1 .5 million for an iTunes demo. We blew the budget. But what are you going to do?
Anyway, it came and went and I did. That was it. Like Paul and I over the years have met and he's come to visit me and we'll record and we'll make like fun stuff together. And that's it. I don't really talk about it. And I know I never really knew what to do with it.
So cut to now.
Last Christmas, I wasn't on taste buds and Brian Quinn from impractical jokers sub hosted for me with Sal.
And on the episode Brian brought up like do you know what the Rosa has this band I found out like I never knew about.
And so I was like, no, what are you talking about? So they played some of it on the episode.
And they were like, you know, it's pretty good. Whatever, you know, they didn't trash it. They didn't praise it. They just played a little bit. So the fans of taste buds started writing to us and writing to me and saying like, I really like the band. I really like this.
Are you guys ever going to put something out again?
What style of music?
It varies. The new, the new, the new thing we're going to, the thing online is like pop rock, which is why I'm not crazy about it, but there's an irony to it. It's a little tongue in cheek.
The next thing we're going to put out is, is, is very weird digital. It's very cool. I'm very proud of it. I'm excited to get it out.
But anyway.
So I said, hey, guys, you know, it's funny that you, that this comes up because Paul and I have had an album on the shelf for years that we, we never were going to release and we never had a reason to.
And now that, you know, a few of you are showing interest, maybe we'll put it out now. That'd be fun.
And people are like, yes, please, like we want to hear it. We want to hear it. And I was like, okay, that's really uplifting. Awesome. I'm going to try to put this out.
But as this is all happening, somebody, boy, girl, man, female, I have no idea, makes a salsa, windfall Twitter account and starts tweeting as if it is us.
So at first I'm flattered. And then I'm like, wait a minute, people think this is me doing this.
So I DM the person and I say, hey, you know, thanks for doing this, blah, blah, blah, blah, do me a favor.
A lot of people are thinking this is me. Please make it clear that it's not me. And that's all.
And they sort of flippantly did so, but we're like kind of like, I thought it was obvious, but you know what I mean? Like with a bit of an attitude.
So they write buried in the bio on Twitter, because you know how everybody reads your bio on Twitter, buried in the bio on Twitter.
The last line is this is a fan account thought that was obvious, which is a fuck you to me, but I let it go.
And then from there and out, anytime somebody said, are you Joe, they would go, no, it's just a fan account, but they would wait for that person to say that.
Which most people don't, they just kept assuming it was me. So I'm like, what are you going to do? Who cares? It's not, it's not.
We don't need a wage war here over this. It's a fan. They're excited. No harm. No foul.
But the handle is at salsa windfall. So he got the good handle. She, he, whatever got the, I don't know who it is. Got the good handle.
We're shocked. That wasn't taken. Yeah. Yeah. Thank you. They say you insult all the time.
I'm saying, how did you come up with that name? My, my issue is with the name. What's your issue? It's abandoned.
No, no, no, no, no, no, it's not a bad name. I'm saying, where did you come up with it? And I'm shocked it wasn't taken because those words have never been combined before.
I know. I know. I know. I know. I'm breaking balls. Anyway, it's another story for another time in the name.
But anyway, so you spilled some salsa on your Netflix account and it landed on Jesse Plemons and the Jason Siegel new original film, windfall.
Yes. We traveled into the future. That happened. And, uh, anyway.
Can't answer your question. What kind of music? All the original stuff we did was on four track with Cassio keyboards. It was like very, it was like varying the vein of like wean.
And this thing that's online, we did with an actual band and the recording sucks. And I don't think the true nature of the songs comes across that way.
Anyway, that's the new thing we're going to put out. It goes back to what we, what we used to do. Anyway.
April Fool's Day. I wake up not realizing it's April Fool's Day. I see the first thing I see on my Twitter. It's from the salsa windfall account salsa windfall has officially disbanded.
This is two days after I'm on the phone with a friend of mine, who runs, I think I can say this is special thing records and I'm seeing if they're engaging interest to see if they might want to put this out and whatever.
Maybe they will. Maybe they won't. I don't know, but I'm talking to everybody like that that I know that has like a decent size little label that it's like maybe somebody wants to put this out like I'm trying to get momentum here.
So I see that tweak go out and then everybody that's been following the account, which isn't a ton of people, but it's, it was about 450 people being like, no, no, no, why what happened and all this stuff, right? Yeah.
So I see that I'm like, what the fuck, man, why the fuck would this person write that and I'm pissed off.
And even though I'm pissed, I very nicely write, hey, I appreciate the love. I need you to put something in the handle that says you're a fan account because people now think that the band has broken up and that's not the case not really sure why you would tweet something like that.
So then I quote tweet the thing about us disbanding and I write this is not the case quite the opposite. In fact, I'm in the process of trying to get the new record out.
It's coming soon in the meantime, follow us at and I put out a salsa windfall official account, which has to be salsa underscore windfall because this person has the other way.
Can I ask why you didn't do salsa windfall official because it was too long.
Okay. And so it was salsa windfall band, apparently, it was too long. Anyway, I scrambled to do that yesterday morning because I'm like, now I got to rectify this, I was going to do it eventually anyway, but whatever.
So that's it. I put it down, I walk away, I go do what I got to do all day work, whatever.
And then at like five or six PM, I'm like, oh, I wonder how the new salsa windfall account is going. I wonder if anybody followed it.
I log on to my Twitter, I see comments from the fan account bashing me.
Oh, he woke up in a mood today. Yeah, he could have just been nice, but instead he threw a fit.
Yeah, he just wants to handle from me, but I'm not giving it to him. Like, I'm like, what the fuck right then I go into my DMs and I got DMs from this person.
All I've done is promote you for free, never asked for a dime.
And this is, you know, how you thank me and blah, blah, blah, all this stuff, right?
Here's the average response to what you wrote today, and he has a screenshot of somebody writing to him.
I don't know why Joe's making such a big deal about this. We love when he's an asshole, but not to you.
You know, and all this stuff, and I'm like, I don't even know who this person is. No idea, right? Yeah.
One screenshot, one screenshot of one fan saying that to him, and he goes, this is the average response, which I know is not true.
Otherwise, he would have put several.
So with 400 followers, how many people are actually responding, right? Exactly. So I DM him, and this is what I wrote.
Oh, and he goes, he goes, it was an April Fool's joke, like get over it, you know.
And I'm like, yeah, but it's an April Fool's joke that people think I'm making.
And then also they're taking it seriously, and it's not your place to do that, right? So I'm trying to like.
I'm trying to like think of ways to say that to him.
And all this, you know what I mean? And, and I'm like writing all these funny replies to him in my head, and I'm writing all these angry things.
And then I just, I just stop, and I'm like, you know what, I'm going to be a human being, and that's it.
So this is what I write to him, earnest, earnestly, I write.
I had several drafts in my head of what I wanted to write here, all of them fairly flipping and somewhat funny, but I'd rather go to the human being route.
I appreciate the free promotion. It's always nice when a fan is excited about your work, and let's others know that you have stuff going on.
None of that is ever taken for granted ever.
But you have to understand where I'm coming from.
I woke up this morning to see a bunch of tweets of people saying they were bummed to hear that my band broke up.
I sent you this message with the, I sent you a message with the request to modify your handle, not because I want the handle, but because I keep seeing people confused and thinking that it's me very frequently.
The new account went up today in response to the fact that that keeps happening, and it wasn't, and it was going up sometimes soon anyway, I could care less that somebody else has the best version of the title handle for the band.
It's just at times it works counterproductively towards what I'm trying to do with promoting us.
It bums me out after I DMed you with what I thought was a very respectful and rational message.
I saw you taking passive shots at me to other fans, but it was worth it to explain myself instead of blocking or firing back or whatever on a personal level in the hopes that you understand where I'm coming from and react in a similar vein.
And then I wrote April fools go fuck yourself.
Okay, I was going to say this is way too mature for job, but all right, right.
So he she I get I don't know.
This is how fast they turn this is this is how thin the line is between fanatic control ready.
Yeah.
It's kind of pathetic that you would take time out of your day to write back, but it was okay.
A C minus. So first of all, don't you love that how a troll has such a pathetic how you take time out of your day.
You've created an account for a man.
Exactly.
It's amazing to me.
That's the first defense of a troll.
You're pathetic for taking the time with me.
I have no dignity.
So it's okay that I do it, but it's pathetic that you do because you're supposed to be right.
Right.
I pray you find a different medication because whatever you're taking isn't working.
Your band is a joke.
It's always been a joke.
It's person dedicated.
Uh huh.
And then this could just have been one of these opian Anthony people who like still try to shut you down or anything.
No, absolute positive to activity coming out of this thing.
All that's okay.
Yeah.
By the way, he spells band.
I keep saying he, because I can only can picture a man being.
No, this is a, this is a guy.
Right.
Your band.
That's a compliment to women.
Women don't know this.
Yeah, yeah.
Your band is a joke.
Why are you apostrophe.
Why are you apostrophe are you?
Right.
Right underneath that.
Yes, I spent your incorrectly.
Uh huh.
Treating the few fans you have left.
And train the few fans you have left is definitely a good strategy.
Best of luck to sound.
As though you're a band who like.
Like smash mouth, who had a long storied career.
And now you're not popular anymore.
You know, it's like.
That's not what this was.
It's so.
It's so crazy, so.
So I tweeted out, oh, and by the way, he wrote that to me after I tweeted out what my response
by April Fool's response was to him.
And I said, I just posted this DM between me and this person because I wanted to show everybody
that sometimes positive can come from negative, scroll three times to read the whole thing.
And it was like, it's funny.
It's fucking funny.
And you know, this guy could have been like, ah, you got me, fucker.
All right.
That was April Fool's.
So then I post this and then I go and I look and I'm blocked by, it's also windfall has blocked you.
And I just wrote, well, by golly, on Twitter, I wrote by by golly, this is the damnedest turn of events I've been blocked by my band's own fan page.
And they can't take a joke.
See, but yeah.
So, so there you go.
That's where we're at with this with with this stuff.
It's not enough now that I have provided this person with countless hours of a free podcast with taste buds.
If he's a fan of our podcast to hundreds and hundreds and hundreds of hours of a free podcast online that is available outside of the paywall stuff.
Clips all over YouTube records that you can stream with any if of my stand up that you can stream it and on any service if you have a membership.
That's not enough.
That's not enough that I've given him this much entertainment for pennies.
He now deserves a part of my life.
And by the way, the account still exists.
So now there's an account called at salsa windfall.
It is not affiliated with my band that was created in honor of my band that is blocked one of the members of the band that is going to continue functioning under the band's name.
So there you go.
Well, can you say to Twitter, hey, these guys have my fans name? Well, you can't they got the first thing I'll do is I'm going to somebody will direct this this gentleman to this podcast. No, here all this.
I'm sure I hope he does.
But I hope he hears money.
Yeah, he's going to have to pay for him.
I hope you hear this.
And I hope it hurts your feelings. And just in case you can't afford this, which you probably can't.
I am going to recap all of this on the very free podcast taste buds, which you are a fan of and you will hear.
So I and I hope it hurts your feelings because you are a bad person.
This is like, but it's just crazy to me that this is the line.
We're walking now of that somebody can can praise you and go out of their way to praise you for months and months. And then the second you give the slightest criticism of like, hey, I think you're a little out of line here.
Yeah, I never liked you anyway, you're trash.
It's like, with this is saying something about you, not about me, right, there's something wrong with you, like, like, you have like, I don't, you know, what, what can I say that's not.
Obviously, but, you know, I got off Facebook helped a lot getting ready to get off Instagram.
Sure, that'll help a lot.
I missed, I missed the Facebook fan page, but I just was always one of those people who would see one negative thing and spiral me out.
Can't deal with it.
Like Twitter, I just tweeted the other day, because I spilled a bunch of coffee all over my dick and balls.
And I tweeted for the first time in about six months, because I had had a funny take on spilling coffee on my dick and balls.
And for a while now, my Twitter account has been hemorrhaging followers because I don't tweet.
But I saw that I went down another point, something or whatever, and it hurt my feelings. I was like, damn, how am I losing these followers?
It's because I haven't tweeted in six months, and because a lot of them were probably bots anyway.
But everything finds a way to hurt my feelings. I'm too sensitive, and I don't want to go online anymore.
Nobody's talking about me. I mean, I don't give a shit, but it's just like, what a, it's just, it's rude.
I think more than the pandemic, the internet has ruined brains for sure.
Access that people have to their people they like and enjoy and they feel they know you and, you know, sometimes that can be beautiful as in the hellions, as in people, you know, getting together and becoming friends and starting relationships out of being fan that can be great.
We love hearing from you guys because it's generally all love.
But man, it's just when I see the things people will tweet at or to somebody or about somebody. It's just like Jesus Christ.
I used to be that way too. I think a big part of the reason I don't tweet is not fear of cancellation. It's just like, you can really wound somebody by making some snarky ass jokes.
I said 10 years ago. I never do now. And it's not because of the fear of being shut down. It's just because what's the point of me getting online and hurting somebody's feelings. What's the point.
It's, it's terrible. It's terrible. And, you know, I have a couple of things to say to that. The first is, you know, you bring up the positive, which is the, the, the Helen group.
Yes.
And that is, that is positive. But look, look how, look at how small a sliver that is or that type of thing, as I should say, on the internet versus the mass hysteria of everything else.
It's like anything else. The minority of it is wonderful. The majority of it is awful.
And I was saying to my friend the other day, who was very upset about internet stuff. And, and she was, she was like, I can't, I don't know what to do. Like I have to use it for my work.
It makes people want to cry and all this stuff. And I was like, yeah, I go, look, I'm in a similar boat. I have to use it. And I said, if I didn't, I wouldn't have it at all. If I had no reason to promote anything, I wouldn't have it at all.
But then people say, well, just go on to promote. And that's fine. And I said, but that's, there are studies that say internet users brains heavy internet users brains resemble the brains of drug addicts.
It is an addiction without a doubt. So when you say to somebody, just use Twitter kind of for the reasons you can, you need it and then get off of it, just use Instagram kind of, it doesn't work because it's like having the first drink after the abstinence.
That leads eventually to two, which eventually the next time leads to three, which eventually leads to drunk, you're back in it.
Yeah, you can't do it. The only way you can do it is if you can afford to pay somebody to do it for you. That's the only way you can maintain it and be good. And even then, though, you have to tell that person.
Here's what I'd want you to say here's what I don't want you to say I have to vet what you're writing to make sure you're not misrepresenting me in any way.
And oh, how did the, how did the thing do for the post about the shows are people looking, you know what, it's easier for me to just check, why am I going through you all this, you know, and then you're back on it again.
So I don't know what the answer is, these, these fucking, fucking third party things that I've tried to use, you can't use them unless the apps are on your fucking phone.
You know, like, yeah, I used to be addicted for sure, probably 10 years ago, you know, maybe less I was addicted to Twitter, but at the time Twitter was just reading tons of really funny jokes for people.
Now, now good lord is it not that. And I had a good kind of Twitter community of people that you, you can't help it. You start to view the measure friends and you've never met them. And it's, it's all gross.
But the times when my mental health is the worst are when I'm really into Twitter. So like now I'm out here in the middle of nowhere in Georgia, I have no real close friends, got a lot of shit going on my personal life.
And I find myself to distract my brain reading Twitter, even though I hate what I'm reading for an hour before bed.
And I just keep scrolling and doom scrolling as they call it, going, going, going.
And it is very much an addiction. It's just like you're, I don't know what I'm doing, but it's keeping me from thinking about things, I guess, and also making me feel better because I see how completely off the rocker everyone else is at this moment in time.
But, and we can transition here now reading the, the takes the amount of tweet, the amount of tweets from the trades variety Hollywood reporter, et cetera. I finally had to unfollow the amount of squeezing this orange until like the pulp is just disintegrated into nothing.
Like, you've got a glass of juice, drink the juice, but they keep going, no, there's more from the slap, the will Smith slap, we've got one to psych's opinion on the slap, we've got Amy Schumer's opinion on the slap. And you're like, yeah, as we're scraping the bottom of the barrel here a little bit.
But then you've got sealess celebrities who had nothing to do with the Oscars and their takes on the slap, we've got to the minute reports of what actually happened backstage.
Did they tell Will he could stay? Did they say you have to leave? Did they say you can leave if you want to? These are hourly half hourly news stories.
And I found myself clicking on them even though I don't care and we all know what happened. If you watch it and you're not an idiot, you know what happened.
Will Smith is being cocked by his wife, frankly, you know, they have an open marriage, so be it. Nobody is reporting that rebel Wilson the night before or two nights before whatever at the BAFTA Awards went up and she goes, Will Smith's nominated for, you know, best performance by an actor this year.
Interesting. I thought his best performance was pretending he's okay with all his wife's boyfriends. A thousand percent more cutting joke. Nobody's discussing it.
And he didn't hit her exactly. And I think we all would have been happy if he had hit Rebel Wilson, but was he there?
Who the fuck are you? Why is Rebel Wilson giving a platform? Nobody is giving a shit about anything you've done in 15 years. Shut up.
Oh, I hate Rebel Wilson. And she by the way, by all accounts, I know several people who worked on her very short live sitcom. Me too.
The worst human being in a Hollywood.
Yeah, she's a monster. She's a fucking monster. She's a monster that hides it well on the surface, but she's a fucking monster.
And by the way, if Chris Rock made that joke, if Chris Rock said, I thought your best, by the way, that's, that's the kind of joke that you used to do at the Oscars all the time. That's the kind of joke Ricky Gervais does at the Golden Globes.
And if Will Smith had gone up and slapped him, then I think everybody says, okay, this is a much more even argument, a more fair and balanced discussion.
Chris Rock's joke leading to this slap is, is, is Mania. If you're citing with Will Smith, you're incorrect. Frankly, you're just simply incorrect.
I have a lot of, well, I have a lot of opinions. I, I, I agree that on the one side of degree, I agree that the discussion is, it's ad nauseam at this point.
It's crazy. It's a lot.
I'm not, but I have an assassination hasn't been analyzed this much. But here's the thing with what they do now with the news story. I think it's a theory, but I think it is what they do.
It's like a writer. It's like a writer that when he has a good twist, you know, he has a good mystery on his hands for, for screenplay.
It's like, okay, I know the three points of this of this story. There are three points in this story that I need to hit and their big points.
I have to, I have to divvy out the information slowly. So I keep the viewer intrigued. So that's what they're doing with this story.
But I was, honestly, I was interested in hearing what they did afterwards, why he was still sitting there, why he wasn't escorted out what the aftermath would be.
And I feel like it's sort of come to an end now with him resigning. If you, if you guys don't know, Will Smith has resigned from the academy, which I see a Hollywood resigning means they told him, hey, we have to throw you out. So we look good.
We'd like to offer you the chance to resign and make you look good too. That's what happened.
And I think it's publicist value. It is always a lie. And I think as they'll say, hey, we're going to fire you, but we, we're going to like to offer you the opportunity to say I'm quitting. You know, this happens every day.
I agree. And I think it's publicist obviously too. It's like, Will, this is the, this is how you keep decent optics. Yeah, step down.
But, you know, it's in it. Look, I keep describing this moment as America, obviously, it's a symptom of a much bigger problem we have in this country and it's a problem that's been going for years.
You know, and it goes beyond Trump. I'm just so fucking stupid ass Howard star. I was like, I blame Trump. It's Trump's fault. This shut up, Howard.
Shut up. People could blame. People could blame Trump on you. Do you know what I mean? Like, like you in the 80s, I could, I could make an argument that that shock jock radio and acting like a pig in public and having women sit on speakers and come all over them while you blow into a microphone.
Is the, is the thing that led us to having a president that fucking brash and gross that there's an argument to be made there. So I love our certain. I think that's a valid argument. He certainly contributed to it.
So my point is is like, I don't blame any one person. I don't blame Stern and don't blame Trump. I blame the country. It's a collective thing that's happening. It's a collective deterioration.
And I think that this country's been in a state of alcoholism as a metaphor for quite some time now. And that moment. And not a metaphor, right.
Right. They're saying more people are dying of drinking now than car accident, because everyone got hooked, you know, hooked or re hooked on alcohol drugs over the pandemic.
And that moment at the Oscars, to me, was daddy's always been a drunk and been embarrassing. And we just saw him hit mom for the first time.
That's exactly his Scientology came out, you know, that I told a friend that I was like, yeah, his Scientology slipped out. It's like, it's like when crews hopped up on the couch, you're like, okay.
So this guy isn't just a little odd and there are rumors and whatever else, he's revealing to us now that he's completely kind of lost his mind when you do something like that, in my opinion, you've lost your mind.
And the friend I was talking to said, we'll dismiss a Scientologist. And it's true. He's kept that close to the day, close to the best, but that is an organization that provides us with insane celebrities.
They think celebrity already has this heightened thing of nobody can ever step to me. Nobody can ever speak about me. I am the best. That's that's all celebrities. I, you know, nobody has a right to criticize me, etc.
The Scientology thing takes it a step further and it becomes this manic wild energy. And I think that's what happened. You're right about the dad thing. It's great.
Is this the, when he was walking up to Will Smith, let me say this though, let me just say this really quick. I'm not saying it just on the literal level. I'm saying it on the level as the metaphor for the country. That was the moment.
We saw the cut our culture.
Dad slap our culture mom in the face. I don't mean because of those two men. I mean because of what that meant in that moment. We can't even get through.
We can't, things are so tense and horrible and divided now in this country. We can't even get through a bullshit, phony award ceremony. That means nothing.
Nothing without two millionaires being involved in a physical altercation. It's not Chris Rocks fault. Some people say it is that's bullshit.
Near billionaires, near billionaires. This is this is the moment at your at your where you always knew your family was trash.
And your sister is getting married and her husband to be gets into a fist fight at the wedding. This is where you're like, this is a bit of a long time coming and it finally happened.
And like, and I honestly think that's why people are for lack of a better way. I found it traumatic is a strong word. I found the incident traumatic though. I found it very like disturbing.
It's very sharp as well. I was mocking all the people who called it traumatic and they haven't been able to shake it. And then here I am a week later and it kind of chills me thinking back on it like.
Just it's not you don't sympathize for Will Smith. He's in extreme pain. His right is marriages collapsing and everybody's making jokes about it. But the thing is, we used to even Billy Crystal as toothless as he was would get up there and there'd be 10 to 20 jokes that they've cut to, you know, Meg Ryan or whatever and she'd make a face and it would be really hurtful.
And everybody go, but then you need some laughing Chris rock. He did he did a bit at the Oscars years ago. I saw Jude Law talk about how much it hurt his feelings where he was like, why is Jude Law in every fucking movie? I see now, he's like, every fucking move. And then he goes, um, you know, let me just say you guys, if you can't get Tom Cruise, just wait.
You don't have to cast Jude law and Jude laws there. And I remember laughing at that. And Sean Penn came out and it's like, for the record, you laws one of our finest actor. Yeah. And he's not one of our fine. I love you. Now I love him too. Yeah, but it's just Jude law talked about how much that hurts him and I bet if he's willing to admit that, it probably hurt him way more than he's even letting on.
But that used to be the culture. Now we're in a place where you can't joke, you can't they say, I mean, it's not punching down when it's Will Smith and Chris rock that there is no down or everyone's down from there. But we're in a place now where you can't joke, you can't say anything offensive, you can't piss people off, everything hurts everyone's feelings. So this real innocent mild joke, regardless of her alopecia status, like it's fucking cancer.
Blows people up and it's nuts. It's like in a world where jokes are more commonplace, then a mild joke isn't going to lead to a slap.
I think it's also a part of us being so sanitized now and not able to laugh about anything so the tension just keeps building and building and building.
You've got to be able to laugh at yourself, laugh at the world, laugh at the celebrity culture that is so toxic. I actually thought Jim Kerry had a great take on it, believe it or not, but he was like this was the announcement to the world that celebrities are not the cool club anymore.
We're not people to emulate. We're not people to respect. He's just like it's it's gross and it's always been that way, but this was kind of like saying, hey, if you guys idolize us, you're just frankly wrong. We're broken.
Right. And that's true. Yeah, that was that was that was I felt that I felt like I felt that that was the case too, but I felt it went farther than celebrities. I felt like it was like this is where this culture is at.
And look, I feel terrible. I have friends of alopecia. It's horrible. I feel bad for people. It's terrible.
Sure, but you know what, get me wrong, but I want to tweak this week from someone who said as a proud alopecia.
No, no, no, yeah, I know it's it. People will use anything to say we're, you know, to amplify what side there are right or the stance that they're taking.
But you know, we did an alopecia challenge on taste buds and put it out and people were where you had to slap your front in the face to raise awareness for alopecia.
And people thought it was funny and people that had an alopecia were writing to me and going, thank you for doing this. This is so funny and my condition is terrible and thanks for bringing a funny light to it and awareness and all this stuff, which is, which is heartwarming. But I'll tell you what.
For everybody talking, this is, this is not about anyone group of people. This is about everybody out there on the internet for everybody talking about this for everybody talking about this.
I'm not seeing a lot of, you know, pointing to raise awareness about the condition, even the people complaining about it.
I'm not seeing a lot of links posted of where you can donate to try to help cure.
I'm not seeing a lot of that, even from the people that think will Smith is right. I'm not seeing a lot of that. I'm seeing a lot of it will like with everything else, the personalization of it.
Why you think so and so should have done such and such because of how it reflects on your life.
Right. You know, I'm seeing a lot of you don't talk about a man's wife and I would have done x, y, and z or you should be allowed to take jokes make jokes about anything and fuck you if it hurts your feelings and x, y, and z.
I'm not seeing a lot of what it really means to these two people at all.
And you're right. You wouldn't. And you know, look, I tweeted out about Will Smith, I said, look, the guy is having a mental breakdown. He needs help for anybody standing and applauding for him as an enabler.
We saw a man go from laughter to rage to violence to tears in a matter of minutes.
And when he got up there and sort of talking about how he his first words out where I have to protect.
I find myself called upon to protect the women in my life.
It's like, come on, man. And they said his publicists went over to him like 10 times before he went up to win the Oscar to tell him what to say.
But it's like, don't compare yourself. Don't bring fucking Venus and Serena into this and say just like their father. Now I'm going to be controversial.
What are you doing, man? I don't throw everybody else on the bus. You have to own this.
The real guy had to come out and be like, of course, I don't condone. Thank you, Will Smith.
And he shouldn't have to, you know, and to not get up there and immediately go, I am very sorry to Chris rock. I lost my cool.
You had the end with Denzel, the greatest man on earth.
Denzel pulls him aside. And I watched these as a mirror this morning. And I love those guys.
But they were, they had just interviewed Denzel the week before. And it was a fantastic interview.
You can, you can just see Denzel loosening up with those guys as opposed to being on with Colbert or something, you know.
And they were like, you know, we talked to him for a couple hours. That's just how he is. He has a piece of wisdom.
They're like, you could be peeing next to him. And I'll turn to you and say, hey, by the way, and give you the piece of advice that changes your life or whatever.
But yeah, yeah, at your highest moment, the devil will come and get you. Okay. After that, you need to say, I am very, very sorry to Chris rock, because the devil just came and got me.
And I don't know what that was. It was a accumulation of a lot of things going whatever.
But to do the apology days later or whatever, it's like, it was, if I'm not mistaken, he didn't thank Jada in the speech.
No, well, I'm sure right now he hates Jada because not only was she having a long term fuck fest with a much younger man.
She for some reason talked about it on their show. And these open marriages. That's another conversation.
But this is, this is what Lee, this is what it leads to. I saw some tweet that was like, open marriages seem really chill right after the Will and Jada thing, which I thought was great.
You have to be Nina Hartley porn star extraordinaire of 60 years or however long she's been doing at this point to be down with the open marriage.
You got to be Nina Hartley is the Al Capone of open marriages. It's like, it's like, buddy, you're not that part of you that gets shaken, ain't getting shaken in me.
Right. I got this. And by the way, when Nina Hartley cheated on William H. Macy and Boogie nights, look how he handled that.
You know, like, you can't make it work with everybody.
But you know, it's, it's, it's, it's, what was I going to say?
Did you know that was Nina Hartley and Boogie night?
Oh, yeah. That's peak Nina Hartley. She's my favorite porn star of all time. I love Nina Hartley.
I, I really want to meet her because I think she's an extraordinary human being.
So if Nina, if you're listening.
Anyway, no, Denzel, I went directly directly to Amazon and bought equalizer one and two, two back after I saw the clip, the Oscars, because I was like, I love him.
He's full of wisdom. I can't get enough. And I need to now immediately watch two movies where he's the coolest baddest dude, like on earth.
Denzel's eyes were a little glassy when they cut to him. I noticed this morning, you know, like because it's, it's, it's hard for me and Joe to sit here and talk about it.
But I think this all this way more than it shook us up. It had to really shake up the black community. And I am working with an entirely black staff right now.
And to hear all their opinions on it was terrific, you know, because it's obviously going to be different, but yeah, it's just, it's not great for, for the black culture. It's, it's on the, this big state.
Everybody talks about how it's like on on the biggest state. Nobody watches the fucking Oscars for starters. Everybody's going to see this clip.
But this was the second lowest rated Oscars of all time, you know, they're, they're going out of business like everybody else.
But it's, it's two of your biggest celebrities, but it's a shame engaged in this is bad news. It's a shame. It's a shame that the guy that boycott at the Oscars two years ago because of racism.
Yeah.
And the award show that's been under so much scrutiny because of racism.
And then again, it's all bullshit. If, if, if, if it wasn't profitable for them to, to, to put the focus on women or whatever it is they're putting the focus on this year or next year, they wouldn't do it.
That's just how they roll their pieces of fucking garbage. But the fact of the matter is it is a shame that the guy that made the stands with this woman, his wife, which Chris Rock made jokes about then too.
You gotta be invited to not come, you know what I mean, which is funny.
It's like me being mad about not getting access to Rihanna's panties. I wasn't invited. That was a joke, which, which, you know, while also not worthy of a slap, at least would have made a little more sense than, than this mild manager.
Do you think Chris Rock knew she had a lot of peace because everybody at work said, yes, he definitely knew.
I don't care if he did.
It's not a wrap.
That's it. I know what it changes things a bit, but it's also like, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's also address this.
Jada Smith does have alopecia. She's still smoking hot.
Yes. Let's stop acting like she's walking around with like a potato sack on her head like the elephant man. Okay. She's still smoking hot.
They don't put you in the front row of the Oscars if you're not smoking hot.
So my point is is it's a shame that this guy that boycott the Oscars to make a statement about racism finally was there to have his big moment.
And then did this thing that kind of, you know, look, it's not about race. Obviously, it's not about, it's not about, there's, there's not a microscope on one group of people over another in an incident like this.
I don't mean it like that. I just mean, but it's, it's somewhat about legs.
But it takes the lap record, but it takes the legs, it takes the legs out from under his cause.
It looked like the guy, it went from the guy who boycotted becoming the guy who was going to win.
And then this happens and it just stains the whole thing. It's like Jerry Seinfeld said about Louis CK.
He's like, I just think it's a shame because now that thing is always going to be on him.
It doesn't go away. And now this thing is always going to be on Chris Rock. It's not going to go away.
I agreed with Jim Carrey, so I'm for $200 million. That video is going to live forever. It's now a meme. Forget it. You're done. It's a meme.
That will go on. You know what I mean? Well, Chris Rock is by all accounts going to get his revenge through writing jokes and his act.
I hope so. And I hope so too. But it's like everyone came away. I think very impressed with how he handled the situation.
He was clearly a little flustered. He got off funny bit right after. And then he's kind of, he pulled it together, but he seemed a little flustered as you, as you would imagine.
But I don't think anyone's thinking what a bitch for him to not hit back or take that punch or whatever else.
Oh, I know people that think that.
No, I said, well, I don't agree, but I know people that think Tony, who I know pretty well, what was posting, who's Chris Rock's brother was posting some stuff like, you know, standing up for his brother, whatever else.
And I guess he had Tony rock had been getting a lot of stuff like your brother's a bitch for not hitting him back, whatever else. And he's just like, guys, guys, come on.
Because I know for a fact, if Tony, well, I shouldn't say for a fact, I know Tony pretty well. I feel like if Tony had been there, it would have Tony might have gotten involved.
Yes, I do. I do. He's very protective of his family. And he doesn't really pull any punches. So I, I mean, I'm surprised.
I thought it was a joke until the slap Chris is laughing. The audience is laughing. It's the kind of bit that in the 70s, Johnny Carson would have been like,
hey, you all think Jack Nicholson's getting enough pushy lately.
And then Nicholson would have walked up to him and kind of got done like a fake fist. The audience would have all laughed or whatever. And that's what it felt like until the slap.
I thought it was going to be like a fake headlock like, hey, all right. For sure.
Everybody was laughing. And it just firm enough that you're like, okay, sorry.
Even after the slap, I think the reason people thought it was a joke is because the audio went out and it's until you watched the foreign feed of it where it was him going, keep twice.
Keep my wife's name out of your fucking mouth. It was like, that, that to me and the way that he walked away after the slap, like, I'm a hero, like doesn't everybody love me now or whatever.
And then they rewarded him for the behavior by giving him a standing ovation. Now, whoopie Goldberg had a good point in the view.
Standing ovation's are weird. You're standing up and clapping before you realize what the fuck you're clapping about.
And that's true. It's a bit of a peer pressure thing. And maybe probably there were people in that room who had been insulted by Chris Rock or various other Oscar hosts who cheered him on for doing it and have wished they could do it in the past.
But everyone in that room clearly made a big mistake. I don't think we got to shame the man, but no, but by the way, I agree. I agree.
Or I'm sorry, I was not a critic of when everybody was when it came out when the Oscar now whether it's true or not, I don't know, but let's just go with the idea that it is true, right?
Yes, that they asked him to leave. And he didn't. And I know people that are saying, fuck that you kicked the guy I go, dude, they have a live international show in progress.
And the biggest movie starting the world won't leave. Right. You go sitting in the front. Yeah, you go let him sit down. Yeah, we will deal with this after we can't have cops on the fucking Oscars right now.
This is crazy. This is absolutely crazy. So, you know, that part didn't or it made sense to me. It made sense to me.
And, you know, it's it's and and just what you were saying earlier about it does have to do with race.
I didn't want to cut you off. I just want to finish my point. I could understand how it could.
If for, you know, I saw people online saying white people shouldn't even comment on this, but which I don't think is true.
But I also think that there's probably a very different discussion to have if you're not white, you know, if you're a black person talking about this, it's probably and probably has a different meaning for you.
Or maybe it doesn't. It doesn't have to. You know what I mean? But yeah, I could see why it might, you know, like I don't know, you know, but I, I mean, it's for such a mild incident.
There's so much world up in it to talk about. And that's why even though I criticize the news cycle, we've been talking about it for so long.
It, it involves all the big issues, race, celebrity culture, wealth inequality, all this shit. These people have too much money.
And they don't, like I, there was another great tweet I saw and I need to start writing it down so I can credit people.
But some guy was like, why is everyone so confused about Will Smith doing this? This is a man who hasn't been to the grocery store in 25 years.
Right. And that's 100 % true. These people are isolated beyond their, their wildest dreams.
And I do think Will, like everybody else, spent this pandemic, really looking at things, looking at himself, not getting his dick sucked every day by the Hollywood machine.
Just being there with his family and his family was having big problems that's unfortunate. Everybody knows about, you know, but I just feel like he's a broken person.
Yes. And anyone who, he was joking about having put on 10 pounds over the pandemic or whatever it was, but anyone whose wife is fucking a man who's 30 years younger than you.
When you've been married that long and then she tells everyone in the world about it and you don't divorce her and all your dirty laundry is there to out.
You're going to be a broken man. Regardless of how many high priced therapists you get, you're going to be a broken man. And he's a raw nerve.
And I'm not saying he's a danger to society or anything else, but the fact that he was out dancing to get jiggy with it afterwards at a party. It's like, how do you not go home after that and go what have I done.
I can tell you why I can tell you exactly why because I, I want to obviously much smaller level.
I have made major mistakes in public on stage.
What my shows, I've, I've seen your act.
I've gotten mad at an audience and said things and like destroyed the show where everybody hates me.
I mean, I've, I've blown up a fucking room before when it wasn't my room to blow up. I did it once opening for bar and bar was really, really fucking mad at me.
And the way you deal with that is, or at least some people, I know the way I used to deal with that because I had, I would do it.
I would, I did it a few times. I would go to the bar and get drunk because I couldn't handle what the emotions were.
And then the more drunk you get, the more you, the good you feel for the better you feel for temporary, even though it's temporary.
And the next thing you know, you're having fun and you're laughing about it. And it's a good joke.
Now, I don't know if he drinks or whatever, but I promise you that's what, I would put my money on that's what he did. He went to the party and he partied in whatever way he parties.
And his endorphins got going and he, he let him shut it out for a while. And then he's like, oh, it's not a big deal. And then the next morning when he woke up was when the shit hit the fan. And that's when he had to deal with it.
Not saying it was engrossed to see him doing that. It was, it was arrogant. And it also spoke even more to the bullshit, disgusting, whatever nature of Hollywood.
You know, it's, but I mean, that's the thing. It's like, people go, why would they even let him into the party? It's like, who the fuck do you think is letting him into the party? Do you think the king of Hollywood is letting him into the party?
You know, you think it's also, if we'll Smith wants to get into any party in the entire world at any time, no one is ever going to turn him away. That's, that's what creates this type of situation.
You know, people have never been told know about right. And you know why he's not going to get turned away. Not just be getting actors. Yeah, not just because no, you meant you were being racial, right?
The, no, I know I'm joking. But my point is it's like, you know why he's not going to get turned away for two reasons. Number one, he's Will Smith and the guy that doors enamored or number two, he's Will Smith. And the guy at the door is like, if I don't let him in, I will be fired.
Yeah, Hollywood is the only place on planet earth, maybe New York, maybe New York and certain circumstances accounts in this is the only place on planet earth where you will be a good worker and get fired because you didn't kiss the right ass at the right time.
You know, you're a fucking schmuck working a door at a nightclub that nobody fucking cares about other than they'll get their picture taken by the paparazzi when they walk out.
Right. And, and you know, you're hired to work the party or whatever and you just need your goddamn job. And Will Smith shows up.
You're going to be the guy that turned him away. You know what I mean? And then you go to your boss who's not the owner. And then he doesn't know what to do because the owner, you know, and the press is there. Nobody knows what the fuck to do.
No, because it's a town built on all on all the wrong values. And I truly hope that that there's more apparent now after this incident. And then it crumbles to its fucking knees. I really hope that.
No, it's starting to.
There's another guy whose name I do know, Julius Sharp, who I've met friendly a couple of times, but he's a very funny writer, family guy and stuff.
Had a beautiful take on it, I thought, which was beautiful.
It was, and I hate quoting tweets, but here we are.
It was like what happened tonight was is Hollywood in a nutshell. I'm paraphrasing, of course, what happened tonight is Hollywood in a nutshell person celebrity gets up does something absolutely unhinged and insane.
Everyone pretends they didn't see it. And then 10 minutes later, they're applauding the person.
That's great. That is, that has been my experience in Hollywood every pretty much every single job I have had somebody acts in such a toxic disgraceful disgusting way that you can't believe it.
And everyone looks away or goes, that was intense wasn't it? Let's him do it because it's it's it's him. It's almost always him.
And then they're back to laughing and celebrating the person later, there are no consequences for these people are people people in power.
I've had bosses do this actors do this, and it's just, you know, what, what, what are we telling them by there being no consequences.
I've been in situations where I have said this person is a big problem and is going to really cause even bigger problems if we don't do something about it and powers the big go, yeah, but, you know, we're not going to do anything about it.
Well, I'm not, I'm not an old man. This stuff has happened every year of my career. It's this, it's this simple. If you can make them money, you get to hang around exactly.
Even if you don't, even if you don't, even if you're some washed up hasn't it's like, well, we got to walk on eggshells around him. Do we, we're both human beings.
They put to take this because this guy was famous 30 years ago.
They put, they put Harvey Weinstein out to pasture when he was of no use to them anymore.
He turned a blind eye until he was of no use.
Whatever your stances on Woody Allen, they didn't give a fuck about Woody Allen until it was obvious that Woody Allen was not the cool kid that made the cool movies anymore.
They didn't give a fuck about Bill Cosby until Bill Cosby was 82 and no, it didn't matter anymore.
That's right. We're getting another Cosby show.
That Cosby documentary, you got the white show runner of that show being like, well, look, I mean, did we know he was a ladies man, sure, but we had no idea.
Dude, come on now.
If he's taking an extra to his or having that the extra sent up to his dressing room every day, what are you talking about?
You fucking know they and they nobody would ever report that or they'd reported and they'd go, I don't care.
Because they don't care. Right. Louis CK is the only example of somebody they took down that was still making them a lot of money.
And I think that was a matter of circumstance that at that time and at that moment they needed to make an example of somebody and it fell on him.
But Roseanne, you know, Roseanne would still be on Roseanne.
If it was, if it mattered for it to be Roseanne and then they proved in the subsequent years it didn't.
It could be just the Conners. Right.
They knew that they knew that otherwise it would still be Roseanne. Do you understand?
Like it's, it's they knew that now John Goodman, Laurie Meckeff are equal stars on a par with Roseanne.
That's what they knew.
He's one of the biggest, it's still one of the biggest actors out there.
It's a, it's bleak.
We should get to the rest of the Oscars if we're going to discuss it.
I mean, I'm now it'll probably be a bit anticlimactic, but I mean, let's just go through the winners and nominees.
Sure. I mean, just the big ones. I mean, look, look, first of all, I want to say, the biggest hosted by Regina Hall, Amy Schumer, one to Sykes.
Amy Schumer, one to Sykes. I understood Regina Hall. I'm still kind of scratching my head as to why she was the third host.
You know, I thought that was a weird choice to me. I don't agree.
It's strange. It's a strange choice. But anyway, but anyway, they were the hosts.
And for everybody worried, it did, it did come out that Amy's joke with Kirsten Dunst was planned and Kirsten did know she was going to be called a seed filler. So that's fine.
Yeah, by the way, after all this shit next year will be Billy Crystal again. I'll bet you money that they'll have because he's got ease on Broadway again with Mr. Saturday night.
I bet you because they're going to go now back to safe good old Oscars. They're going to try to recapture.
And Billy Chris, it'll be Billy Crystal. And you know, and he'll come out and do like a friendly fun monologue. And one of the jokes will definitely be.
And for the first time this year, no slapping. You know what I mean? Of course, a slapping category.
Or he comes out in a kind of catchers mask or something. That's probably what it'll be. Something like that.
So by the way, the Amy Schumer joke, I guarantee was pitched as plumbers being the seat filler because he looks like a seat filler.
And they were probably were like, no, that's too mean. We can't we got to reverse it. I guarantee that's how it was pitch.
Yeah, maybe, maybe.
I hate everything.
Let's go best picture. Let's go best picture. Now most of the world is doomed by the way.
All the technical ones did. Yeah.
Six awards.
God, best picture.
My what I find interesting is that my favorite of these movies, which I guess would be, I don't know, licorice pizza is about a bee bee bee bee.
Oh boy, BB plus.
It was a terrible year for films. And I don't understand any of these nominees really. We got West Side Story.
The power of the dog nightmare alley, which was a terrible film. I can't I don't understand how that's nominated for best, but that's insane.
No, that's it's a king Richard, which was a very average biopic. Although I will say shout out to Tim and Trevor white who are producing my movie.
Dune, Dune, drive my car, which I finally caught up with and thought was a really beautiful film that was stretched an hour too long.
Don't look up, which was a very bad, it's very bad movie. And bell fast, which I have not yet seen, despite it being about my people, the Irish.
The winner was Coda, which is I liked Coda quite a bit. It's a Disney Channel movie. It's the kind of movie that 20 years ago got released every weekend.
A $10 million movie that a family could enjoy together with a sweet message. I missed it up at the end of Coda.
But it's a very Disney Channel by the numbers kind of movie. And we're honoring that as the best we have to offer that I think is a real sign of where we are, you know, in terms of the culture, in terms of art.
This was a year where when I went back through my letterbox or whatever for the year to do our best of, I didn't have anything above four stars, which is kind of like a B plus.
It's tough.
Coda, you know, it's not even it's not the best of this list. It's not the best movie of the year, but I clearly people, the lesson that's going to give the Hollywood is more heartwarming, sappy shit. It's not shit, but you know what I mean.
And that's just not what anybody wants right now. I think I don't know. It felt odd to me, but then again, did anyone have a passionate favorite this year? These are average films.
Yeah. Best actor.
We know Will Smith won other nominees, Andrew Garfield, even though tick tick boom. And what I've seen of it made me sick to my stomach. He wasn't.
He was great.
Benedict Cumberbatch always bringing the heat.
He was great in that.
Have your bar damn great in being the Ricardo's a dog shit movie. I don't understand how bad movie can get a best actor nomination, but it happened.
And then Denzel.
Denzel always worth it.
Look guys, I know you all voted and everything. How the fuck do you at the in the eleventh hour not just go give it to Denzel pretend Denzel one and that's it. Let's get out of here.
I guess because your name's on it.
Yeah.
You're fucked, but you know, Will Smith after his. His good.
Mcbeth Joe bomb. He was like, you guys should see it. And that's the point. Nobody seemed to bet.
Nobody wants to watch these movies. They feel like homework.
By the way, Joel Cohen did that solo. Clearly him and Ethan Cohen have had a falling out that they're not addressing. But Ethan Cohen's next movie that he announced was written with his wife.
And it's a broad lesbian road trip comedy.
Like I read this and I was like, what? Like he's make.
There's always been kind of this weird like broad sensibility, especially in the lady killers and intolerable cruelty and stuff like big jokes and their movies.
So clearly Joel is the artist and Ethan wanted to do big funny stupid shit and good for him, but I do think the beauty of those two was the mix of the art house and the broad.
That's why everybody loves them.
And then separate. I found Mcbeth to be two artsy artsy to truly love it.
And who knows what this lesbian road trip comedy is going to be, but I'm excited.
Like any road trip comedy. It's even a few laughs for the most part you don't care.
Yeah.
That's the actress Jessica Chastain. I was happy to see her win for eyes of Tammy Faye. I thought she was great. Excellent.
The makeup was doing a lot of the work, but she was great.
Olivia Coleman, always great in the lost daughter.
Great performance in a very interesting movie.
We got to pump the brakes on Olivia Coleman though because it's getting like it's getting like Ryan Reynolds and who's the kid Adam Driver.
Yeah.
I am seeing too much of her now. I don't know. It's like, all right. Stop.
Kristen Stewart, in Spencer, a movie nobody saw.
I did. I'm one of the few that liked it. I thought it was a really good performance from her, but she had no chance.
Nicole Kidman.
That's ridiculous. Not only is the Nicole Kidman in these and the athlete serious diatribe set in the world of multi cam sitcoms.
Yeah. And she's bad to record. She was bad in that movie. I thought it was that movie.
It should have been Catherine Hawn or somebody, you know, like somebody with some chops. Nicole Kidman is one of the least funny people a lot.
Penelope Cruz.
Didn't see it.
Is this a foreign film?
It's a L mode of our movie. I Spanish. I haven't seen it yet.
Look, I'm going to get groans for this. Why now are the foreign language films mixed in with the English language film?
The whole point was to have the separate categories you could honor everything.
And now when you're mixing them together, you can't, it's like, it's not enough slots for everybody.
It's animation too. And then I don't know if you saw this part where the animation.
Well, you know, beauty in the beast was nominated for best picture.
And also then they have the best animated feature category. Like there is no real division anymore, whether that's good or bad.
I don't think Cruz is getting nominated for a voice performance. No, no, no, no.
I'm saying animation is the same thing. An animated animated film and best picture.
And at that point, don't you already know who's one best animated feature?
You know, like because they're the, if they're up for best picture, they, you're already saying they're the best. It's very strange.
All this stuff, of course, real stupid. And the fact that people take it seriously is crazy to me.
Even though I used to be obsessive about the Oscars, when I was a kid, I'd have Oscar parties and boats and everything.
I did this, not when I was a kid. I did that in my 30s.
But I've done it my whole life. I used to be obsessed with this shit. And as you get older, you realize just how deeply stupid it is.
They did a fan favorite announcement. Did you see that where army of the dead was voted best picture?
It's ridiculous. What a, and the toxic fans of that movie are replying to people's tweets.
Like, oh, I noticed you're not mentioning that army of the dead won best. And it's like guys, that is a MTV award at best something they would show during the commercials, you know.
Supporting actor, you got, oh, the winter was, what do you got? Oh, yeah, Troy Cotser from Coda was a great performance by a deaf actor. Of course, he was going to get the award, but he was really good.
Always loved Sierra and Heinz did not see bell fast. Clemens is always good. Power the dog. JK Simmons and being the Ricardo's is a pathetic nomination.
I mean, he was doing what he's done in every movie and doing it fine. But come on. And then Cody Smith McFee, who was also good in power of the dog.
Best director Jane Campion won for power the dog. She's a great director. I think she deserves the win, even though I didn't see power the dog. I'm sure I wouldn't hate it as much as Sam Elliott, although I did enjoy his commentary.
Keith Brana nominated for bell fast. I can't say the name of the director who did drive my car. I apologize. I can't.
Hi, I'm a Gucci. Oh, there you go. Spielberg for West Side Story, give me a fucking break. And then Paul Thomas Anderson.
Again, great director. My opinion hasn't made an interesting movie in 10 fucking years at least, but whatever. I disagree, but liquorice pizza is a middling film at best for him.
It's on the way lower end of his filmography. I just rewatched it. I don't want to digress into a Thomas PT Anderson debate, but I just rewatched punch drunk love. And I'm like the guy just doesn't do it like this anymore.
Like it's just deeply, deeply loved that movie. I felt very seen by that movie. Yeah, yeah.
Let's go to the supporting actress that we did actor.
Oh, no, actress.
On Janu Ellis from King Richard, Kirsten Dundes, power the dog. I love Kirsten Dundes, but come on.
So wait a minute. Then why would you make a seat filler joke about Kirsten Dundes if she's nominated?
It doesn't even make sense.
I'm telling you, it was pitched as plemons. I bet they pitched it to plemons as plemons. And Dundes was like, I'd rather we do it about me.
But the joke, the joke is you're more famous than your wife or vice versa. And here they are both nominated.
No, it's, it's a lot of this doesn't make sense. We didn't have one great joke over the course of the entire night. There was no A plus joke to point to.
It's because you know what it is, they stopped inviting Bruce Philanche to write. That's what it is. Honestly.
Judy Dench and Belfast, which I again have not seen, but the clip they showed almost missed it me up. I always love Judy Dench unless the movie is cats.
Jesse Buckley, who was excellent, excellent in the last daughter. And I like her a lot.
And Ariana DeBose won for West Side Story in a very good performance too. No question.
And that's it, huh? I think that's pretty much. I mean, I always say it when people leave off the screenplays as a writer, but wait, no, let's go best. Okay, that's the last one. Best original screenplay.
Worst person in the world.
A truly excellent screenplay. Shut out.
Likris pizza.
Not a good screenplay. I mean that, that movie gets by on vibes. It's not a good screenplay.
King Richard.
Average, you know, made for TV movie. Don't look up on a truly bad screenplay by Adam, okay? And then Belfast, again, I haven't seen an adapted. We got power the dog lost daughter.
Doon for screenplay, ladies and gentlemen, fuck off.
Drive my car, which is a masterful adaptation of a very short story adapted into a three hour film. So clearly a lot of work was done there.
And then Coda won for best screenplay, which is, again, strange, but fine.
And that's where we're at.
There's your Oscar app. There's your goddamn Oscar app.
Right there. We, it's the world.
The world is in an odd place, you know, and everybody is in pain. How I say it is our Oscar recap.
Well, should I like to say the world is a vampire?
Sentage.
All right, folks, we're going to come back next episode with our review of memory, the origins of alien, which is new to shutter a sort of unorthodox documentary about making of alien.
Until then, we'll see you next time. And we'll see you in hell.