Ladies and gentlemen, it's your podcast, your only podcast, and if you're
listening to any other podcasts, I'll follow you to where you're sneaking off
and listening to them, and I'll kick the door in and beat that podcast's ass
because I'm a jealous guy like that. It's you. We'll see you in hell with Joe
DeRose and Pat Walsh. Joe a typically smooth intro to the show. It seemed
folks, I gotta say Joe, let's put the professionalism down and just say hello
as friends. I feel like I haven't seen you in a month. I haven't seen you in a
month. Pat rolled in here tonight straight. It's Friday night where we are. Pat
rolled in straight from a taping of his TV show. I believe not wearing shoes at all.
I've left him downstairs. I don't respect. It's wet outside. After you could have
walked in with him, but I did seem that Pat rolled in that we walked here and just
saw it looked. I'm not far from wandering the streets and socks. I had I just
filled Joe a little bit in on my week. I would say I gave him the two out of ten
version of a story that goes all the way to 11 baby. I told him sort of the
groundwork of just one of the most nightmarish weeks of my entire life. I know it
was gonna be a heavy story because Pat fixed a drink and then waited to put ice in
it. Told the whole story then went and grabbed it because it clearly knew like
this drink. The ice is going to melt. Yeah, this drink. Yeah. But it was a
riveting tale. I don't say that with any sarcasm. That was a hell of a story. I
wish I wish we could share it with your kids, but we can't do it. But you know
we still made the true Hollywood story. I love them to pop by the set. You need one of
those or whatever the hell remember that show. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. I wasn't
golden girls one of them. Holy shit. That show was crazy. Yeah. It's good to see you
you you went on the practical Joker's cruise. How was that? It was everything I
forgot comedy could be. Yeah. It was four days on a boat with all New York
comics. Okay. People, the audiences were all salt to the earth regular American
people. Love it. Everybody's fucking with everybody. We're gambling. We're
drinking. Right. We're smoking cigarettes. We're eating food. We're laughing. Okay.
Inappropriate jokes as long as the day is, you know, it's it's it's it was beautiful.
It was a blast. It was a fucking blast. The fans, the inner, the inner
property, the impractical jokers are wonderful. I do love that. I don't know the
others. I met the other three guys for the first time. They were all lovely.
Sal's my name to sound. Sal's a good friend. As I asked you to do, even on air, I
asked you to do it. I forgot. I forgot. I'll mention it though. That's fine. I promise.
I promise. I'm sorry. It was a drunken phase. It's fun. And then you stepped on to this
thing. It was a blast. The practical jokers are really lovely people. Did a few
monthy podcasts, which also featured, which was Q from the jokers and then
Brian Johnson from comic book man, which I was a fan of, and Brian's a friend, and
he's from that whole Kevin Smith from the impractical. Yeah. Yeah. Okay.
Uh, you the winged serpent or a different. It's no, same. Same. Yeah. Yeah. He
found success later on in his career. Thankfully, usually a winged serpent, you know,
you pretty much tap out at that. But I'm glad to see he branched out. It was it was
a blast. And Brian's part of that whole Kevin Smith clicked thing. So it's
always fun getting to, getting to talk to him. And, you know, he's a real like
Jersey dude. Uh, sure. That was a fucking blast. Did the bonfire radio show hosted
by my dear friends, Jay Oakerson and Dan Sodor live. That was a fucking blast. Uh,
did, uh, my friend Bobby Kelly's, you know, what dude podcasts live. That was a
blast. A bunch of standup shows, a lot of gambling, a lot of karaoke in front of
Rabbit in practical jokers fans who are the nicest, sweetest fans on planet
earth. I'm sure congrats guys on having the best fans and congrats to you all on
being the best fans. Uh, and, uh, it was just a love fest, man. It was a fucking
love fest and nothing, it felt like you were around family. Nothing was precious.
Nothing was sacred jokes flew. You hook up. Uh, no, and bringing
one back to the cabin, little little stow away. I, I did say to say the door with
one of the, uh, you know, the, uh, life preservers covering only your genitals.
Mm -hmm. Well, I would say to every woman I passed in the, on the ship. Yeah. I got,
now I got something I'd like to stow away, honey. You want to see it? Yeah. And it
didn't work. You know, I like it. I'll give you my line. You can use it next time. Oh,
sweetheart. Dixie hoi. And I point to my deck so she doesn't hear ships. I want to make
sure she gets it. Yeah. I, uh, I'll try that next time. I, but I was trying. I'd like to,
I have something I'd like to stow away. That didn't work. Yeah. I said, I've been a bad
bully. I did try that one. That didn't work. Yeah. I yelled a few times full steam ahead to
your coach. Oh, no. That, that never worked. Yeah. Nothing worked. I don't know what's wrong
with these people about anchor. I barely know her. No, in all honesty, I did very little, uh,
flirting at all on the boat. Uh, it was more just like kind of hanging out. It was just hanging
out, man. It was, I hadn't seen these guys or staying out more on the port or the starboard.
Poop deck. Poop based on the name. So that's a real easy to work into a pickup line. You old poop deck.
I'll leave that up to your image. It was a, it was a, it was a fucking blast. It was a fucking blast.
Dallas was also a blast. Thank you, Addison Improv for having me amazing crowds and Addison.
Thank you all for coming out. That was fantastic. Went down to Austin for two days, saw the super
ball. Uh, you went to the super ball or just, you know, we watched it at a house. All right.
I mean, you said we went down to Austin, saw the super ball. It sounded like I was saying I went
to this. I didn't mean it that way. It just came out wrong. I don't even know who played in the
Super Bowl. It was our LA Ram, my LA Ram, my beloved LA Rams. And, uh, who were the St. Louis Rams
when I lived in St. Louis. Yeah. Well, there you go. And, uh, I do. God's only New England Patriots.
Of course, who always win and you hate them for it. Didn't watch, don't know anything about what
happened. I feel like I've been out of the loop. I feel like I, I feel almost giddy having human
contact that isn't related to my job. It's, it's nice. It's nice to talk to you, Joe. It's nice
to see you and nice to talk to you, Khan, who was looking his genitals as we speak. I've got a
fresh cut today. He's looking good. We should fire this up, Joe. Um, we are by fan requests,
because thank you to, uh, at least a hundred of you who signed up for the Himalaya app and Emily
who led the charge. Thank you. Of course, Emily Florence, who led the charge. Oh, and I hung out with
Emily in Dallas. Sorry. I should say that she came out to two of the shows and we drank both times.
Lovely. And, uh, we had a great time. I love it. Yeah. We had a great time. Anyway, go ahead, sorry.
No, she didn't, you know, she said if we get a hundred, the fans can request an episode, a commentary
episode and the winner was the lost boys. So that's what we're doing. And you might as well start it
up. And this is how this is how good Emily is to the show and to the fans and to everybody.
Um, she initially posed this as if I get you guys a hundred, a hundred by Sunday, can you do a movie
of my choosing? Uh -huh. We said, yeah, she very selflessly turned it over to a fan vote. Sure.
That's smart call, uh, which I thought was really great. We're in a fun one to do. I'm excited to talk
about the lost boys. So let's get on with the show. And at the same time, I'm with a Jew.
We're streaming this on HBO go HBO now. I have the HBO. I have the HBO add on on my hulu .com
subscription. That's where you can get it for free. If you don't have the HBO something, you're
fucked. Uh, one, two, three play and we'll do it right now. One, two, three, play. And we're right
at the top of the film. That HBO logo. By the way, very smart to say one, two, three, play. All right,
now here we go. One, two, three, play definitely not confusing in any way. Well, Pat, I'm not here to
hold anybody's dick through this experience. Well, then what am I doing here? Pat, I'm so excited to
get to the movie corner. Yeah, because I watched, we're going right there. Well, we don't have to,
but I've watched a ton of shit. But there's a thing that I'm dying to tell you about. All right,
that I watched. By the way, Warner Brothers presents up on the screen. Just make sure we're timed out,
right? Yeah. We're going across the water. Richard Donner production. Richard Donner, by the way,
director of Superman of the Goonies was originally slated to direct lost boys and eventually turn it
over to Joel Schumacher. And I'd like to talk about Joel Schumacher, but Joe, take the lead. Go
ahead. No, no, no, you can talk about that first. Then we can go to the movie corner. Well, you know,
the credits are a good time to talk. You get a lot of names and stuff. But Joel Schumacher, I thought
to myself, you know, that's a guy who's a massively successful director. If anything, his personal style
is like trash, you know, like Batman and Robin and shit. That's Joel Schumacher. But I was like,
this guy's a very respected director. He hasn't done anything in a long time. Did he ever make a good
movie? And I looked up his credits and sure enough, I forgot about falling down, which is a great movie.
He's made some brilliant films and he's made some utter shit. I don't think he's made some brilliant
films. I think he made falling down, which is great in lost boys and a whole lot of shit. And by the way,
and I'm going to alienate some people, I don't love the lost boys. You don't love it. I do know.
Just two seconds ago, you're excited to watch it. It's a good choice to discuss because I got a lot
to say about it. But this man directed, it's been a long time. The last like actual movie he made
that got any sort of release. And this must have clearly killed his career was the number 23 with
Jim Carrey, which is an absolutely terrible hormone. It ranks up there on the list with like Ishtar.
It's unwatchable to terrible film. Virginia Madsen, she doesn't know when to fold a man. That's true.
Made that huge comeback with the sideways Oscar. And then right into number 23.
I get it. I mean, Jim Carrey, Schumacher, you know, he's a, you know, these are successful people.
But really, Carrey's career kind of ended and Schumacher's career kind of had in terms of
that. Carrey was already teetering. He was on, he was on the way out. He was in the Mr.
Popper's Penguins phase. The Phantom of the Opera before that. One of the worst filmed movie musicals
all time. The one, the one that was, no, that did very well, didn't it? It didn't. I'm talking about
its quality. All these movies did well. The one with Gerard Butler. Yes, I didn't see it.
Veronica Garen with Kate Blanchett, which I remember being like a decent TV movie.
Phone Booth with Colin Farrell, which was pretty fun. I'll give it that. Never saw it. Bad company with
Anthony Hopkins and Chris Rock. F. Yeah, terrible. Tiger land, entertaining. Never saw it. Now that's
the movie about all the tigers that lived together, right? Well, there was Colin Farrell's
debut. Really? He plays a tiger? No. You never saw this movie? It's about the creation of Frosted Flink
stop at you. I really don't know what it's about. It's a war movie with Colin Farrell. Rob
Mackle, and he always tells the story about how he like started filming that movie. And Joel Schumacher
was like, wait, you can't act and brought it. Colin Farrell supposed to be his big break. Really?
Flawless with DeNiro and Philip Seymour Hoffman. It's a very bad film. I wouldn't say it's very bad.
It's a passable movie. It's not great. Eight millimeter. Okay, not terrible. I need to see it again.
I remember being disturbed by it, but it was disturbing. It was sort of like fake disturbing. Batman and
Robin about as bad as things get in terms of movies. It's, it gets no rougher than Batman and Robin.
In my opinion, Batman forever a little bit better. Slightly. A time to kill is a good movie. I
will give him a time to kill, and I will give him the client, which started Brad Renfrow on his
descent towards death. Falling down is an unquestionable classic. Then we've got dying young, bad,
flatliners bad. Is dying young? Oh, yeah, yeah. Flatliners, I'm going to get flatliners a pass.
Cousins with Ted Danson. I'm going backwards, obviously. I've heard it's good.
Lost Boys, St. Almost Fire, which I rewatched recently, and is abhorrent if that's how you pronounce
that word. DC Cab with Mr. T. Very funny movie. The incredible shrinking woman with Lily Tomlin,
and then we're, we're done. DC Cab is very funny. Look, it's a career. It's a successful career. I just
feel like the guy makes shit largely. Now, I did a show up in Santa Cruz. Yeah. And on stage,
I was making fun of the town. I go fucking place looks like a lost boys town. They're like, yeah,
no, it's based on here. And I go, they're inside a film there. I go, well, why didn't they call it
Santa Cruz in the movie? And they're like, well, the town didn't want them to use the name. And I was
like, yeah, because you know, that's real smart for a town's economy. No, no, change the name
in the movie. Well, people don't want to go to a town with vamps. I got news for you. Nobody wants
to go to Santa Cruz to begin with this. That was the one fucking chance they had to pull people up there.
Is Santa Cruz near Santa Barbara? No idea. Okay. But Dennis Miller lives in Santa Barbara. I believe
that. Did you know that? What do you see? You think he's got $50 million? Easily. Oh, that makes me sick.
Easily. I'm, you know, I'm a fan. You know, I'm a fan. The echo and the bunny men cover of
the doors when you're strange. Terrible. The soundtrack is kind of, it's very 80s.
Well, I like the, you know, they'll shout not kill song. Michael Chapman, an amazing cinematographer.
And I think that's to me, what makes this movie better than average. I think the cinematography
of this movie is fucking awesome. Now, how many times do you think the joke was made to
shoe macker when he was making this film when people would say, what's, what are you working on?
And he said, the lost boys. Yeah. And then how many times do you think somebody went, where are they
all in your basement? Or something along those lines? You know, because he's gay. Yeah. I'm saying,
how many times do you think somebody made that joke? Oh, like with the lost boys, I found them. They're
all with shoe mackers place. You know, I mean like one of those. I bet it happened a lot. I bet.
I'm saying it's right. I'm just saying, I bet you that joke was made a lot. No, I know.
Joe, take us if you will. Actually, I'm going to do a quick screaming in. The CW is making a lost
boys pilot. Oh, okay. And you know, if it's the CW, it's going to be great. Uh, okay, great. Well,
sure, they only make great jokes. Yeah. I have a huge screaming in. Okay. I canceled Netflix.
All right. What brought this about the bird box story about the, them showing the train footage,
their train wreck footage, uh, bird box during the disaster montage at the beginning of the film,
showed footage of a train wreck that many people saw and said, Jesus, that looks very real.
And it turns out it was real. It was an actual train wreck that happened in Canada recently.
That they just used footage from to pretend that it was the bird box of tragedy. Wow.
About 60 people died in this thing or something. Yeah. Canada reaches out to Netflix goes,
this is very traumatic. This was a terrible day in our country. Right. Can you please take this out
of the movie? Right. This is not something to be sort of fictionalized or whatever.
Netflix's response was, sorry, once the movie's up, we can't take it down and change it. Which is,
if you know how to work a fucking iPhone, you know, is a lie. Sure. Um, and I said, you know what?
Here's a company trying to monopolize entertainment. Right. I've been annoyed about that for a while.
I got more annoyed when they up the monthly rates so they could continue to try to monopolize
entertainment by releasing 18 movies a month. Uh, I find that the quality stuff on there is not
properly showcased because it drowns in a sea of, of banality essentially and, and, and, and, and,
and too much, too much content. And, uh, and I said, and now they're going to pull this fucking line
for the first time in my life, for the first time in my life, I said, I'm not giving this company my
money. All right. It's literally the first time I've ever done that. All right. Ever. I respect it. Uh,
I still have mine, but I respect it. It's, well, for now it's gone. Uh, and I think it's, I don't,
I don't miss it. I gotta be honest. I don't miss it one bit. I find myself not watching much, you know.
Yeah. Uh, if anything, it's a couple of phrases here and there. And I went over and, uh, you know,
I still have Hulu and, and, and Amazon and, and some other things. But I started using my Toobie app.
I think it's curated by maybe NBC or something. I don't know. But Toobie, pretty great.
Pretty great. Uh, Toobie is a free app, completely free. They show a couple commercials during
the movie. Very few, very painless. Everything is uncensored. Uh, and it's awesome. They've got,
they've got a connection with shop factory. Uh, so it's a lot of sort of cultish stuff,
lot of cool documentaries, a lot of cool old TV shows that you kind of forgot existed or didn't
know existed. And this is a perfect segue to the movie corner, Pat. All right. Because the thing I
wanted, the first thing I read, I'm dying to talk about is I watched a documentary called The
Complete Owl that I haven't seen since I was a kid. And it's the Weird Owl mockumentary mockumentary.
Yeah. It's a mockumentary that Weird Owl made right around the time he put out the Dare to Be
Stupid record. Well, now I was obsessed and I thought I had tracked on everything the man
had ever made. I don't know what this is. This was kind of hard to come by. I think I rented it as a kid.
All right. Uh, and it's a mockumentary. I had his video collection of all his videos on one of the HFs.
This incorporates the videos into the documentary. Okay. And it's sort of real quick. By the way,
this is one of the most famous scenes of the Lost Boys. These, these shirtless muscled saxophone
thrusting and also lead singer of the band. Yeah. I mean, just who did this? Now I played saxophone
and my favorite part of the sax player is he doesn't have you wear a strap around your neck.
He's just holding it. He's just holding it. And that's that's kind of like his big pose. I mean,
granted he's very strong. I just hold the sax. I don't, you know, but like, imagine a band where the
lead singer is just like, let me take a few hits off this juicy sax. Oh, God. Look at this. He's a
wrestler. Yeah. Jamie Gertz, though. Wow. Holy cow. Yeah. What a beautiful woman. I mean,
look, he's awful in this movie. I've liked her and things. She's terrible in this movie. You got
Gertz and Jason Patrick here at their primest. I mean, you could bounce pennies off both their asses.
Two just beautiful people. Uh, Jason Patrick, I consider the Joel Schumacher of actors. I get that he's
competent and sort of gets it done, but has never done anything for me. I think Jason Patrick is one of
the most boring good actors of all time. I've only ever seen him in two movies. I saw him in this
in NARC. And NARC thought was pretty bad. He didn't see speed two cruise control. No. I hated speed one.
What? Whoa. We've talked about it. I really thought speed one sucked. And I, and I, and I speed one's
one of my favorite action movies. The last thing I needed to do was go back and watch speed two.
Speed two is quite bad. Well, you don't get me wrong. On a boat going slowly. It's the same character,
right? It's sandy bulls, but then Jason Patrick's just the new boyfriend, but he doesn't play the
Keanu part. He does not know. And why does the same thing happen again with a boat? I don't remember.
It's like the cousin wants to fill. I honestly think they just do the, oh, I can't, like this
happened to me once before kind of. Oh, Jesus. I think they're unconnected, but I could be wrong.
Don't know. Hold me to that. So is it outlandish to ask for the lights out in here?
I don't think we need to do that while we're drinking together on a love seat. It's weird.
No, I don't want to do that. I'm weary. You know, my, my eyes are squinty and I, I'm tired.
Have I turned off the overhead and turned on that one? That's all I'm asking. A little bit of a dim.
Now the complete out. Yes. By the way, let's shout out real quick Bernard Herman, R .I .P.
TV fans know him from the Gilmour girls. I know him as the guy. All my friends said that my dad looked
like. He also looks quite a bit like John Hughes portrayed Richie Rich's father as well. And now
very funny and intolerable cruelty by the Collins. Good actor.
Diane Weiss looking cute as hell in this film. Love Weiss. And in fact, Bernard Herman kind of looking
a bit weirdly dashing, like a nerdy kind of way. I agree. Keep yourself in an actor who's also
never done anything for me. I'm a son of Bill or Ted Alex Winter. I forget which one he was, but
I'm a big Southern wind fan. Okay. Especially in this film. A little known movie fact.
Southern wind was the only actor they did not have to apply makeup to to make him look like a vampire.
I hate to, uh, to name drop Joe, but when I bought my house, the notary was none other than
Kiefer Sutherland's girlfriend. So I have spent time in my home with Kiefer Sutherland's then
girlfriend from four years ago. Did you make some joke about we've got 24 hours to close this
deal or something like that? No, she goes, here's how she did it. If you want to talk about a class
of Hollywood case, and then I'll stop interrupting every other word. She goes, um, I'm filling out
the forms. She's like, so what do you do? I go, oh, you know, I work for television. My boyfriend
kind of works for television. And I go, oh, yeah, that's cool. And I kind of go back inside of my
thing. Just, yeah, I mean, he's more like the acting side. I go, oh, cool. That's cool.
I can keep signing my stuff. And she goes, yeah, he's actually on like, you know, pretty big shows.
Okay, who is it? I mean, Kiefer Sutherland. Okay. Like, everything starts like, I mean, you know,
like, yeah, I hate to tell you. Yeah, sorry. I guess if you force me, I'll share this secret.
All right, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the album. By the way, Feldman top of his
fucking game in this movie, Feldman, uh, you a Feldman or a Hayme? I'm a Feldman 110%. Feldman is,
Feldman's unstoppable in this flick. You know, I never thought much of either one of them, uh,
watching this, rewatching this again for the podcast. I think Hayme is a good actor. Feldman is,
of course, you know, great comedy timing. I love them. I love them. I'm one of them. Everything
is so funny in that. Anyway, it's a shame, Michael Jackson molested them both. I'll tell you
this one last one. No, Feldman says he didn't. No, well, okay. He didn't name it everybody else. Yeah.
He could have a, he could have a, you know, restriction, a legal restriction. Uh, baby, but, uh,
the, uh, now I'm going to interrupt myself. I'll tell you one more before we get into this
complete out. Had the guy come over from spectrum the other day to fix the internet. Internet
wasn't working. This guy was hitting like a cable guy level of trying to become familiar with me
in this place. Uh, literally walks in, sees my Star Wars machine. Uh, wow. I haven't seen one of
those in a long time. I was like, yeah, man, it's pretty fun having one of those pretty cool. He's
like, yeah, I remember as a kid, uh, man, I used to love this game. This is, uh, and I was like,
yes, so the internet's right over here. Uh, take him over the internet. He's fixing it. He
goes, what seems to be the problem? I go, uh, didn't they give you the report? And he goes, yeah,
they gave me the report, but the technicians don't know what they're talking about. They don't
work out here in the field. Okay. I like to know from the customer what's going. It's literally the
cable guy. Yeah. Talk to me. What's happening? I tell him the problem. I tell him what's going on.
He's going through the whole thing. I think what you probably might be is your router and maybe we
got a reconnect, you know, the whole in one fucking air and out together. Yeah.
He goes over here. He goes, where's your connection? I point over here. I go, it's right there
right next to my movie shelf. He walks over, kneels down to inspect the connection, sees my Star Wars
DVDs. So, uh, would you think of these prequels, right? Yeah. Pulls out my deleted magic Star Wars
thing. What's this? Deleted magic? Uh, it's all the deleted scenes from the first movie and
hey, there was a reason they were deleted. Ha, ha, ha. You know, I'm just trying to move it on.
That's great. Now I got to tell you, I don't see what the hubbub was about the prequels. I'm just like,
dude, check the fucking fixes everything. And proceeds to, when he's leaving, I keep him $10. Thank
you. He's leaving stops in my game room. Sega masters. I'm behind the TV. Yeah. Like putting everything
back behind the cabinet. And I think he's gone and I hear Sega master system. I haven't seen one of
those in a long time. And I'm like, yeah, it's pretty cool. Can I get an age? Oh, 38, 40. Oh, boy.
I don't know why that makes it so. Yeah, you play these things. Yeah, I remember collecting this stuff
as a kid. And I go, yep, it's pretty great. So, listen, man, thanks a lot. Two more steps. So, uh,
you got myself in case you need anything. What? Just let me know if you have any problems.
Oh, boy. It was a cable guy. It was fucking crazy. Anyway, um, the complete out.
You know, it's sort of based on, there's some truth of the story about Al, his life, but it's
ridiculous. Right. A lot of funny gags in the, in the documentary. One of the repeat gags is every
time they, you know, they'll be like, Al, when Al star rose, he wasted no time courting the ladies,
you know, and then it shows like a series of still shots of him on different dates with
different women. And every, every shot, the woman's covering her face, trying to cover the lens.
You know, it's, it's, it's very funny. It reminds me of the, uh, Al's comic book cover that I used
to have on my wall when I was a kid and it said, people magazine across the top. And it said, Al,
the sexiest man alive except for, and the cover was a list of like every male celebrity in Hollywood.
And then it said continued. And then you open it up and inside was just a list of every man like
in the world. That's very funny. But I paid for it. I was like, Oh, it's a, a prank on me, the
comics buyer. That's very funny. I liked it. Um, this complete album film. Yeah. I had one of the
funny things I've ever seen in my life in it. Uh, do you wear the song state of shock by Mick Jagger
and Michael Jackson? Or you know, I'm saying a shock. That one. It was like, you got me all my
needs. Right. Yeah. So Al is, they show a clip of when he took over MTV for the day. Uh -huh. And he's
like, we've got an exclusive people right here right now. The new Mike Mick Jagger and the Jackson
song state of shock. This is the video premiere goes to the video. It's the song. But it's not
their version of it. It's a fat accountant sitting at a desk. And the little thing comes up
in the corner. You remember where it would say the name and the song and everything. It says Harvey
Leeds state of shock. Right. That guy directly to camera hangs up. He's on the phone. He's like,
yeah, we'll deal with that account. I got to go hangs up the phone turns directly to camera and he
said, uh, does the entire song, the entire three minutes. And he's going, you got me on my
knees. Uh -uh. Uh -uh. Uh -uh. I find this. It's on the 2bf. All right. I guess I'll get to laughing at
this fucking thing. Well, he and my wife watch this before I leave. It's a button smoke comes out of
the entire thing. It just goes right back to the show. Remind me to watch this before I leave.
We'll do commentary on the state of shock video. Yeah. Uh, well, I can't beat that. But, uh,
at least until the last few weeks, I have been watching a lot of movies. I sure
where to begin. Well, you know what? You and I need to do Susperia. Yes. I watched Susperia. I got a lot
to say. I think you'll have a lot to say. That that should be that your next uh, go to. Well,
lend me it. I'll watch it. I would also like to do the predator. I've got to finish. I've got to
finish watching it though. I was on the first half. You know what I'm going to do tonight is shout out
a very little known picture. Very little known. Uh, that I saw way too young. It traumatized me. The
other day I saw the DVD for like two bucks. I bought it and, uh, man, what a night I had watching
this thing. I think it's a masterpiece. And I should probably tell you what the name is. I've built
it up long enough. The movie is called Star 80. Have you ever seen? Oh, yeah, yeah. When I was young,
I saw it young too. And it's not a young man's movie. It's, uh, it was one of the smartest movies about
how women, particularly in the entertainment industry, but you could see it as a metaphor for
society at large. But just how women are treated as, as objects and fucked over could not have been more
timely. It is Eric Roberts. The reason I looked up Star 80 is because Eric Roberts auditioned for my
show. He was very good. He was wrong for the part. But I was like, he still has to audition. I know, Joe.
Jesus Christ. But I was like, oh, Eric Roberts. He, well, he, I think he was nominated, yeah.
But I was like, oh, I love Eric Roberts. And then I thought, huh, but other than Pope of
Granite Village, like, what do I really know him from? I, I bring up the star 80. It's him and
Maryl Hemingway. It's a true story of, and Hugh Heffner is in the movie, like, you know, like a guy
playing Hugh Heffner basically. There's a guy playing Peter Bogdanovic, who was also involved,
but it's not that they portray Heffner and Bogdanovic. As the people who made this movie despised them.
Okay. They treat them as like some of the, I mean, Bogdanovic is obviously a fucking sleaze.
But they, I didn't know that about him. They treat them as like predatory and weird. He was
dating civil shepherd, you know, when she was a child, basically. Okay. He was hanging in that
Polanski camp. Not to mention the man wears askouts every time you see him on screen.
He was hilarious in the sopranos that nobody has ever used him better because he plays a
pretentious therapist and he is incredible in that show. But the movie is directed by Bob Fossi,
who did all that jazz, which is another masterpiece of his with Roy Scheider. Fossi is great. I can't
wait to see that Sam Rockwell Fossi show. Absolutely. I am very excited. And Bob Fossi was just an amazing
filmmaker who doesn't get his due. He did Cabaret as well, which one does picture. But he made a movie
like every three years and you can tell they were just very carefully made. Star 80. I think it was his
last movie. I think blew me away. Eric Roberts is so fucking great in it. He did get nominated,
I think, for a golden globe, maybe. Mariel Hemingway is incredible. True story. She's playing Dorothy
Stratton who was a playboy, centerfold. And just this guy who's like a gas lighter, he's obsessed
with her. He's going to make her career, steals her away from her mom. And you're just really
watching this terrible toxic relationship and jealousy and it gets worse and worse and worse. And
these men are just worse and worse to her until, you know, I won't spoil it, but it's a true story.
And it's a very tragic story. And when I looked it up, it's an even more tragic story than I thought
and realized it's one of the most dark, hellish endings to a tale you've ever heard in your life.
Yeah, it's a dark, why don't I favorite faith in more songs? It's called Star AD.
It's sort of a nod to that concept of, you know, Hollywood and fame and the price you pay.
Eric Roberts is a, I don't remember very well, but apparently pretty tremendous in the film.
It was kind of the movie. It's one of the best performances I've ever seen.
And it was putting it on that list. I thought it was amazing. But I don't get, that's the movie that
was sort of made Eric Roberts and made Maryl Hemingway. Right. And then neither of them,
I mean, Eric Roberts, you could say, well, the guy did drugs and, you know, he could just
fucked up. Right. Hemingway seems like a lovely human being. I don't get why she didn't get to
continue to do stuff of that level or whatever, you know, and I like everything she's ever been in.
But yeah. I think she kind of just got branded a pretty face or maybe she walked away from acting.
I don't know, but she, she's a good actress. Yeah. She's great. I love, I love that old school
Roberts, like Pope a granite village robber. Oh, yeah. I didn't spin his that fucking face. Yeah.
He's so good back then, man. He's so fucking well, this is him and him and it's best. And I'm putting
it on my very short list. I watched it and, you know, this says maybe not great things about me.
But the next night, I was like, I'd like to watch that again. It's a kind of movie that really
appeals me like the wrestler where it's just like you're just watching a man just bottom out.
For some reason, I always love that. I would count bad Santa as the comedic version of that.
But it's a rough watch. I highly recommend my mom called me the other day about a, because it's a
sort of a similar story that stars born. It's about a guy that helps a woman find fame and then
can't deal with her fame. Right. But my mom called me the other day. She goes, we watched a star is born.
Have you seen it yet? And I go, no, I didn't see it. Joe, I don't know how they're going to pick.
I don't know how they're going to pick. They're all so good.
How they're going to pick the best picture. Yeah, just over the best, whatever they're all so losing
sleep over. Yeah. Um, I, why don't you fucking watch stars? I'm going to you'll enjoy it.
My mom didn't recognize dice. Uh huh. And she was like, forward when I was like, that was
Andrew dice. So now I want to watch it because now I want to see also my 12 recommendations
didn't do anything for you. But your moms did. But your ma ma. Uh, I'm going to stay on the weird
hour theme for a minute here. I rewatched UHF three times. Okay. It was one of those things.
Again, it was on to be, I would just have it playing. Like, and times I was sitting on watch
you get times I was just up doing stuff. Yeah. But I just kind of let it play over and over again.
I forgot a little bit how much I love it. I need to own it. I don't know why I don't own it.
They have a great collector's edition out that I own and have not opened. But I haven't seen that
movie since ages ago. First saw it at the drive in theater in Missouri, actually. I think that's
where I first saw too. I saw it with, I want to say house sitter. No, beetle juice. Oh, wow.
Beetle juice. That's a great double feature. Yeah. Uh, it's a fantastic movie. If you haven't
seen it, I don't know who hasn't seen it at this point. But we're down here. It's a UHF TV station
that's on the brink of disaster. And through through a dumb stroke of luck, uh, Michael Richards,
who places janitor, Stanisperowski Stanisperowski goes on the air in a pinch and becomes this
local hit. And all of a sudden, the station now is making money. And then there are the bad guys,
which are the network affiliate in town, right? Trying to shut them down. The network affiliate is
run by Kevin McCarthy. Great. Fantastic, actor. Yeah. One of the funniest, I'm a big fan of a,
like dialogue in a scene where it's like, they kind of like, it's sort of just kind of spot, keep
spiraling. Uh, one line just perfectly begets the next line. And there's a scene like that where
when we're now first meet meets Kevin McCarthy and Kevin McCarthy's an asshole. And he's like,
and we're not like, what's his name? The character's name is like CJ Walsh or something. He walks in and
he's like CJ in the whole office screeches to a halt because nobody dares call him. But you know,
right? And he's like, whoa, the hell are you? You know, yeah. And we're I was like, got some of your
mail. Uh, here it is where he goes stealing. I'll have you fired immediately. Get out of here.
And where it all goes, but I don't work here. Uh, dress passing. I remember that. I remember
everything about them. It's so psychotic. Yeah. The classic set up to where it's his, Kevin McCarthy's
opening scene is him screaming at three employees going, you idiots. Just screaming out and Vince A.
Row and I laugh about this all the time. Yeah. Just screaming at them. And then, you know, halfway
through this, the, the, the berating. One of them is like, but dad. Yeah. That's okay. You take
a wrong with that joke. I'll watch it this weekend. Uh, you should, you should. Uh, you know,
I watched a picture. I had much like the lost, but lost was this movie that has so little impact on
me that I've seen it probably four times. And every time I'm like, have I seen the lost boys?
We have, we have to remember to get into why what your thing is with this movie.
What am I thinking? After the movie corner, I want to talk about what you don't like about it. Oh,
sure. But I want to wait. Yeah. But uh, by the way, we're at the part where Michael just drank
the red wine that's the blood. And now he's like, they're on the bikes and they're going to the bridge
where they're going to drop into the fog. Yes. Sorry. Go ahead. Uh, it's a movie that, you know,
I could only watch PG and G until I was 13. I would rent every PG movie in the store.
And the one that I never rented, but looked at every time it was like, this looks boring,
was heaven can wait, starring Warren Beatty, which was nominated for best picture in 1978,
directed by Beatty Buck Henry, I believe. A lot of great character actors, Jack Warden, who I
can love, Charles Grodden, who is one of the funniest men that ever lived. And as I'm watching
this cast, let's go down. I'm like, I'm just going to fucking love this. Like a lost 70s classic.
Right. You know, the movie made a ton of money. It got nominated for a lot of shit. How have I never
seen this treasure? Folks, this thing is boring as shit. You ever see this movie? No, I don't think so.
Heaven can wait. It's got this reputation, man, that it's a classic. I saw the, wait, isn't there
Chris Rock version? I think I saw that. I see in the Chris Rock version. But this is Warren
Beatty as a football player. He gets hit by a car or whatever. And he like comes back to Earth and
another person's body. It's, I mean, we're talking about one of the most overrated movies of all time.
The amount of nominations and praise this thing got in its day. It is so dull. And Warren Beatty,
I, I, I define he wanted to disagree with me is one of our most boring actors. Warren Beatty and
Common are the two of the most boring actors of our time. Well, I mean, look, I can excuse Common,
Common's a rapper that acts sometimes. Yes. Warren Beatty is, is a regaled actor who I, he's fucking
boring. He's, he's the David DeCovny of the silver screen. Exactly right. I mean, you nailed it on
the head. Yeah, it's just not, there's not much going on there. And I'm throwing Redford in that camp.
I mean, get a pulse. You're on, you're on a movie screen. And then when Beatty actually tries to do
something different than his wheelhouse, like Bullworth, it's, it's humiliating. Well, Bullworth presses a lot
of buttons and you're just kind of, I am a feeling watching that now. My jaw would be on the
fucking floor. I saw it in the theater in 98. And I'm like, God, I like, this guy rapping is,
is this okay? Yeah. He's wearing a hat and drinking out of a 40 inch. It's a little upsetting.
Oh, boy. It's a little upsetting. Anyway, haven't can wait. There's no reason any of you are out there
thinking about watching it. But I just wanted to take this thing down. People have been praising this
shit for too long. I will say, though, Jack Warden, one of the all -time great character actors,
and he can't give a bad performance. He's amazing. All right, Carrie Anja. He's amazing.
I'm going to close out with a TV show that there's only a pilot for, again, on 2B. I guess my theme
here is 2B this week. The pilot is up on 2B. It's also on Shout Factory TV, which is an app you can get,
which is a great app. It's called Horror Hunters. And I guess they're, I don't know, waiting to see
if they're going to pick this up or not, or maybe they didn't. They just haven't. It's a 2B original
or something. I believe it's a Shout Factory TV original. Okay. Well, in any case, it's one of these
travel collectors shows. And it's awesome. It's two guys that are huge horror fans with extensive
horror memorabilia collections. And they visit the homes of people that have like sort of legendary
collections. And then they sort of try to bargain a trade with them. Like, dude, I saw your, you know,
your bust of the bride of Frankenstein when I walked in. That's a one of a kind. I love it. I'm willing
to trade you my original autographed Lon Cheney Jr., whatever the fuck, you know. Okay. As a horror fan,
I loved it. As a guy that legs a little knick knacky retro vintage collectible shit like that. I
really loved it. I thought it was really fun. I'm always impressed when people have an insane
knowledge of collections and collecting and that sort of thing. And then the history of anything.
And this is all horror based. So it was right up my alley, man. It was really, really right up my alley.
And I hope my good buddy, Matt, for Monster Party, shout out to Monster Party, one of the best horror
podcasts out there. Matt, if you're listening to this or if the horror hunters people are listening to
this, you got to get over to Matt's place and check out his fucking collection. I mean, it is,
this guy's got one of the most insane collections I've ever seen in my life.
So if you're doing this show, you got to, you got to have this guy on it. I mean, it's just,
it's just madness. But I really liked it, man. It was really, really,
it was just cool, man. It's cool to see people that have, you know, look, I got my little game room
over there. I like when people have a room in their house dedicated to something. I love conventions.
I love all that shit and fandom and it was just really fucking cool. And the other thing I'll say is,
the more this sort of culture gets exposed on television, the more that stupid myth of,
you know, if you're over a certain age and you buy certain products, you must be a weirdo or a
brainlocked, you know, it locked in a child state or so. It's fucking stupid. These are,
these are cool. There's some truth. There's some truth. As I look about your apartment, I must say
there's some truth. But anyway, monster hunters check it out. And, and if you are going,
you get over to Matt Winehold's house and check out his stuff and Matt, if you're listening,
check out this show because you'll like it. Folks, I will close the corner with one of the last
of the Oscar pictures that we did not discuss, one of the last, you know, for your, for my considerations.
It's called Ben is back. Not a horror movie surprisingly. No, it stars Julia Roberts and
Lucas hedges the son of the writer director of the film Peter hedges. Peter hedges wrote my favorite
novel of all time, What's Eating Gilbert Grape, which of course became an excellent movie as well.
Like sort of a dream adaptation of that book. But as my favorite book when I was a kid,
I still think it's an amazing novel. Check it out if you never read the book. But Peter hedges
after that went on to do Dan and real life, a very average sort of rom -com pieces of April,
kind of average family Thanksgiving movie decent. But you know, every movie you see playing at the
the Weird Art Theater that you never go to when you try to buy it. Just kind of not that exciting
a career post, Gilbert Grape, he's a great novelist. And this was his movie with his son, Lucas
hedges in a role. And him casting his son in the role is a little weird. Because it's a drug addict,
much like the other beautiful boy with Carell and Timothy Shamilai. But this one is the kid from
from Manchester by the Bay. Oh, yeah, man. Yeah, Lucas hedges. Yeah, I didn't know his name. I like
that kid, though. I did too. Better than Shauman. He's a good actor. He was in 45 movies last year,
but he's good in this. Julia Roberts plays his mom. He is a drug addict. He can't get off drugs.
He's back home. They're like, is he going to stay clean? It's that kind of thing they're monitoring
him sort of. And at some point, one of his drug -y friends from his past sees him at the mall. He comes home
and his dog is stolen. Somebody broke into his house and took his dog. So then he goes in the
night to look for the dog with his mom. The first place he takes him to. And then, you know, here's
where the movie lost me, which is almost immediately. I was also watching this with my wife, mom,
and step that is the same night that we watched Bohemian Rhapsody, which he thought was historical.
And we're sitting there watching this thing. The first house he goes to, she's like, who could have
your dog? They go to this guy's house. It's kind of old, creepy 50 -year -old man. And he's like
caressing Lucas head to his arm and like, you should come inside and Lucas head just throws his arm
away and gets back in the car. And he's like, he didn't have it. So she goes, who was that? Wasn't that
your old science teacher? And he goes, I don't want to talk about it. She goes, well, what's going on?
Sure enough, they used to have an arrangement where he would fuck his 50 -year -old science teacher
to get money for pills. And I wonder if you're going to say the science teacher,
like, breaking bad style made the drugs for him? No, no, no. So that's what they, that's the first
stop he, and he takes his mom to it. He could have gone to any of his friend's house. He could have
gone to the fucking drugie guy. He saw at the mall. Yeah, why would he go to the science teacher's house?
It's probably this guy's house. So they go over there. He basically confesses to his mom that he used
to get fucking science teacher for pills. But why did he go to the science teacher's house?
No, why would this science teacher steal his dog? That's what I'm saying. They had an arrangement where
he would fuck him for pills. Why would he steal his dog? And the second they did it, I was just like,
you're a good writer. Like, why would you do this? It enraged me. I couldn't get off.
Miss something. I didn't miss. I, I discussed it with everyone there.
All right. Me and Heather the whole night were like, unless it was some sort of like, I want to tell
my mom what happened to me thing. But that wasn't in the story. Then after they do this reveal,
he just goes on to the next house. He's looking for this dog. They never mentioned the science teacher again.
Strangely enough, this is where we're at the big dog scene in Lost Boys, where the dog bites Jason
Patrick. That's weird. It's a little weird, sure. Yeah. Anyway, Ben is back.
Wines up being an even more depressing version of Beautiful Boy, which was the not great depressing
Steve Carell one. I can't recommend it, but you know, the two of them, I guess, were pretty decent in it.
Let's talk about the Lost Boys. Well, perfect time to drop into the film because
which just transpired was Corey Haim going up the stairs, going, you're a vampire.
A goddamn shit sucking vampire. You wait till mom finds out. And I remember you wait till my
mom finds out was the big line in the trailer. Okay. It was like, you know, the voiceover would be like
Mikey's got a problem. His brother is a vampire. And then which, okay, you wait till mom finds out.
That's how they let you know, like, it's just kind of a comedy. I guess kind of a comedy.
It's certainly not funny. No, it's funny. The part where they invite, what's the guy's naming in?
The guy that died Bernard Herman, when they invite him over dinner and like, they do the whole thing
where they turn the lights out. That's very funny when they turn the lights out and they turn the lights
back on in his, his, there's the mirror right in front of his face. Right. And he goes,
you know, that, that stuff, you know, and then you don't realize when you're younger is the
frog brothers are supposed to be funny. Like Feldman and his brother, they know what they're doing to
kill the vampire, but they are supposed to be funny. Right. How they're like, there's towns,
the louds and bloodsuckers, you know, like, it's like they clearly told Feldman, like, do a
stalone thing. He's got a pen down around his head. Right. It'll be funny to watch a 13 -year -old
act like stalone. Yeah. I mean, it didn't really make me laugh. And I found that the
attempts, like when he's like, his brother is flying outside his window. So he's seeing his brother,
like, as a vampire flying for the first time. And he's like, what are you, the flying done?
It's like, really? That'd be your reaction. It just, I thought it was pretty stupid. And you usually
hate that sort of thing, by the way, Joe. You're a hypocrite. You're a hypocrite.
I don't even think I remember that joke. Oh, it's in there. It's in there. Like my soul is.
Yeah, I mean, look, I didn't say that every joke and the thing was a fucking home run, too.
Right. It also has, you know, and we're far from there yet, but the last line of the movie is
is pretty is a bit flippant. I really like the last one. That's the kind of thing I do enjoy.
If I like a little like the poltergeist, when they you think it ends and they kick the TV out
into the hallway, that's fine. Love a little joke like that. That's fine. I feel like this is a
similar joke. I'm not crazy about the grandfather coming in. That's always been the problem with
this town. Who made it goddamn vampires? It's like, you wouldn't tell your family that it's a little,
come on. It's a little like Dan and it. It should freeze frame right then. Yeah, and they go,
and you know, like it's a sitcom ending. Right. And it doesn't work for me. Okay. I'll tell you
a great sitcom ending to a movie that works for me. Sully? No, but that is a very sitcom. Sully,
we've talked about that. I'll talk about it. Yeah, the freeze frame. Yeah. What does he say? Well,
is there anything you would have done differently? Well, I guess I would have done it in August.
And they all laugh. And then freeze frame. The, uh, the best sitcom ending to a movie ever. And I've
talked with our friend Karen co -garrif about this at length. I miss you, Karen. So what are you
the flying nun? You just see it? I didn't see it. I believe you. Right as I brought it up. Sammy?
That's my Michael Patrick impression. Jason Patrick, Jason Patrick, Michael Patrick, King,
my old boss. Sweet. That would be more like Sammy. Wow. Uh, anyway, the, uh, what was I going to say?
Oh, oh, the, um, Karen, I was still caring about this. I don't think that she's ever seen the movie,
but uh, easy money. Rodney Dangerfields. I love it. I love it. Last one. I just did it on 80s all
over my, uh, the podcast I recommended. And they weren't high on it. I was surprised. I remember
it being so funny. That's insane. Yeah. To not be high. The end of that movie is Rodney Dangerfields
sneaking into a basement, uh, to secretly eat pizza and drink beer and gamble with his degenerate
friends. Right. After he just told his mother and wall that he had turned over newly for the last
year. Right. He's wearing a, uh, smoking satin, smoking jacket and an ass cut. Yeah.
Pulls the ass cut off. Starts wiping his mouth with it and using it to clean up the pizza sauce
off his mouth. Right. And he goes, my mother, for years, I wouldn't kiss her face. I ended up kissing
her ass. Freeze frame. Billy Joel's easy money kicks in, which literally go ban and it, do, do, do, do,
ban it. Yeah. It's, it's, it's, it's so, it's the best ending to a movie ever.
Well, except I'd, I'd, I'd cite another Rodney Dangerfield ending the ending of Caddy Shack.
What happens? What's the last shot I can? Somebody says, I believe so what? And he goes, so what?
So let's dance. He flips open a latch on his golf bag to reveal an AMFM dial, turns it on so that
Kenny Logon starts playing. I'm all right. And then starts dancing like, and Rodney Dangerfield dancing,
he does the thing where his like fists are up and he just kicks kicking. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, so then
him and all the people in the golf course start dancing and the credits roll. And then there's a go for
who starts dancing to it as well. Yeah. And back to me is everything. And to back to school is he,
he does the speech, throws the cap. And as the final song plays, it's him standing like this with his
thumbs up looking directly at the camera, completely frozen as hundreds of graduation caps
rain down on him and around him. And the man knows how to. I mean, him and John Candy, you know,
John Candy always does the freeze frame where you're like, am I going to start weeping now?
You got to, you got to know how to end a picture. We got shout outs coming up today to folks too,
by the way, we're going to do some shout outs during the movie. But yet, the lost boys, you know,
I never, I think if I had seen it as a as a boy, I probably would have loved it maybe held it in
the same regard as all these movies that everybody loves from this era. I mean, I saw this when I was
12, dude, it was awesome. That would have been the time to see it for me. I preferred, you know,
like adventures and babysitting and stuff. I lean more towards just straight. I like that stuff too.
But it's to me fit right in with it. I agree. And I bet if I had seen it, then I would hold it
in a higher regard. The fact is, I watch it every few years, I feel like. And I always ask myself,
did I ever see this? All I really remember is the opening and the rest of it, I find just nothing
just sinks, if you will, sinks its teeth into me. I find it all very superficial, very empty.
It looks great. The actors are fun. It's good to see all these actors at their youthfulness.
But add their youthfulness. I don't get into it. I don't get into it at all. I don't think it's either
funny or scary or exciting in any way. Part of what intrigued me as a kid was that you could move
to a beach town. If you'd be lucky enough that your parents got divorced, you could move to a beach
town with your grandfather. That was part of it. Part of it for me was that in this beach town,
you could have an underground clubhouse where you get to have sex with Jamie Gertz.
Part of it was that you would get to be friends with kids that ran a comic bookstore.
You thought all this would happen to you? No, I just thought it would be awesome.
It was just fulfillment. It just seemed awesome. As I said, I went to the actual place where it was
shot. I had a great time up there, everybody. It was a great show that people were wonderful, but it
didn't have the glitz of the lost boy. Joe, would you at least dim the lights so we can watch this
scene together? Jamie Gertz, tenderly stroking, Jason Patrick's chest while kissing him.
Always bothered me that you see more Jason Patrick's skin in this scene.
What the hell? When do guys get to see a little women nudity in an 80s movie for once? That did,
by the way, that looked like some very passionate kissing. I believe that they were in love with each
other. Now, what else was Gertz in? She was in a less than zero. Yeah, she was a big 80s queen and then
she did, I think she was in a sitcom for a very long time. She was married to the English guy.
She was in that sitcom, wasn't she? The nanny. The fat English guy who was all still standing.
That was Gertz, wasn't it? One of the biggest mismatches of attractiveness I've ever seen.
That was sort of the poor man's step by step. Yeah, it lasted forever. Mark Addy from the full
Monty somehow spun that into five seasons. They thought he was going to be like our
first -year race and it didn't really work out. Well, the man's never been funny in anything.
I can't speak to it. I don't think I've ever even seen an episode of that show.
Jamie Gertz was also like the woman that he shouldn't wind up with in Twister.
You know, she was kind of the uptight one in Twister. You want to talk about a bad movie?
At the time, I loved it. I'm sure it doesn't hold up. Believe me.
I knew it was shit. The minute I saw it, I didn't. I was just worried. This is why we don't see
it anymore. I was a kid. I was 14. A movie about tornadoes. You know, I'm going to see that.
I was 16. I thought it sucked ass. All right. Now, we were older than that, man. I was like 18.
You were like 97. I would have been 16. Yeah. Yeah. And Diane Weiss just so adorable. God,
she seems sweet. She was reminding me of my aunt, Sammy. God rest her soul. I love Weiss.
I was like about Weiss. Big fan. Parenthood is also from this era and she's dying a
minute in that movie. Hannah and her sister. Of course, she's had her sister. She's,
she's, she, I rarely use this term of force. She's the force.
Ed Siserhands. She's incredible. Yeah. She's, she's wonderful. If I'm being real,
I think her performance at Ed Siserhands is my favorite of hers.
I, you know, I get it. Dude, people love that movie. I'm not a big Ed Siserh fan, but I get the
appeal and I understand why people love it. And I don't think that's crazy that that would be your
favorite Weiss perform. I intended her sisters because it's my favorite movie of all time.
Sure. It's, you know, can't compete with that.
Hame in, uh, Hame here at the breakfast table in the class. I was, by the way, the grandfather.
I always thought this guy was art corny and he wasn't Bernard Hughes, isn't it?
Isn't that the name of the guy that died?
The boyfriend? Bernard Herman. Bernard Hughes and Bernard Herman.
Bernard Hughes, interesting fact for you horror fans out there.
Stars in, arguably, the best episode ever of Tales on the Dark Side,
Trick or Treat, the pilot episode. Okay. The episode that is essentially unmatched
in a horror sense by any other episode. It is very scary. It is awesome. He's awesome in it.
It also features the dad from Alph. Yes.
Before he became a crack.
Or maybe Doring, he just was holding it together better. Who knows? But that episode is fantastic.
Not my favorite episode, but arguably the best episode. My favorite episode was, isn't always
will be the odds starring Danny I L .O. You talked about it on here. Yes. When I met Danny I L .O,
he really appreciated that I knew that song or that episode. What do I try to say?
All right. I'm going to get another beer. Would you fill me up as well? Baby, don't.
Oh, you're drink. Hand on my zipper. Yeah, sure. Oh, you made your drink.
I must have thought, folks, the lost boys came out in 1987.
Uh, which I had when I was a boy, a book called Just the Films of 1987.
And for some reason, I would read it. There were these endless reviews,
like five page reviews of each movie that came out in the year of 1987.
Raising Arizona, you realize it's a really good year for movies. Planes, trans -automobiles,
raising Arizona. Right there, two of the best comedies ever made.
Um, and it brings me to, I have to recommend this. And I've seen some of you on the Facebook page
talking about it. I'd be remiss if I did not advertise my buddy Scott Weinberg and my guy I don't
know, uh, Scott McQueenies podcast 80s all over. You know, this thing has been guide me through some
long drives to and from work. Some very stressful days at work. And it comes me down.
It makes me laugh. It makes me remember things. It makes me seek out movies. And again,
the premise is a very simple one. Every movie that was released in 1980,
every with those released in 1981, they're up to 84 right now. Um, it's a great,
what like for me as a guy who walked through the video store for hours when I was a kid and
just like looked at boxes and wished I could rent things and snuck things out, whatever.
Like they'll say a title and I'll remember the box and be like, oh shit, like I never even saw
that or what was that. They're hitting it all. I love the show. They have a great chemistry.
Uh, I recommend you to check it out.
Now the lost boys is to me a fairly boring movie. And I wonder how it got such a reputation
that this was the most picked choice. I think what it is is people seeing it when they're young.
To me, because it's rated R, it feels like the cooler version of all those PG movies,
the goonies and so forth because it looks like it. It feels like it. It's got a lot of the same cast.
Um, and I get that. I love that genre that they try to do now with stranger things and super
rate. And real quick, yes. And as absolutely none of the same cast as the goonies, except Corey
building. That's, that's not a lot of the same. You know what I mean? Goonies got eight different kids
in the fucking thing. There's a, there's a 80s. Yes. 83 to 87 Warner Brothers lot. Like they just
put everyone in every movie, you know, and they all look kind of like this movie and they all feel
kind of like this move. Warner Brothers had a way of like all their movies look sort of the same.
It's very weird. I'm glad you brought up Stranger Things because I do think that this is a,
this film is a sort of one of the seedlings of, of stranger things along with, as you said, goonies,
along with it, along with, uh, you know, there was something very cool back then where kid, yeah. Look,
this movie contains a spirit that that I think has kind of been lost. And we are seeing an
stranger thing and I love Stranger Things. I think it's great. But Stranger Things is very safe.
It's very PG. It's, you know, it's, it's family friendly. Yeah. Nothing wrong with that. I like that
there was a time where they would do a movie where there were true kids adolescence in actual
R rated situations, you know, like, like, and, you know, the movies still got kind of violent and
still got kind of scary. And it made you fear for those kids. I will say this. I don't, I love
Stranger Things. I don't ever really fear that any of the kids are going to die or anything like that.
No. To say I even want to see that happen. I'm just saying like in movies, these movies that felt
like it could happen. I agree with you. So that's what I was building to. I had two stiff drinks on
an empty stomach and I was building to saying exactly that. These, these are rated movies kind of for
kids is a really cool genre. It doesn't seem like a very marketable genre because kids can't see it
and adults think it's for kids. We never get any movies that are anything like this anymore unless
their movies like super eight where it's such, it's so ripping off this genre that it doesn't feel
authentic. It feels like somebody kind of doing a cover song to make. Right. Yeah. No, I agree. I have
some respect for lost boys, but I mean, to me, it does, it has a problem that a lot of horror
comedy has. Here comes the mirror guy. It's not funny enough or scary enough. Here comes the mirror
guy. Hold on. This is very funny. Here comes the mirror guy. This is funny.
Somebody getting startled is always funny. All right. What are some other movies like this
that were R rated? Well, the gate never saw it. I think it's rated R. I mean, if it's not rated
R, it's pretty fucking dark. I mean, it's right night. What fits right into this category. Right night.
Rated R. Uh, Friday night too. That's college kids. They're college kids by that. But, um,
yeah, I mean, a few more. There's, there's more. Honestly, which stand by me?
Stand by me, which like which is a V -swig is not a kids movie, but to me, that feels like this kind
of movie. Warner Brothers, late 80s, dark lighting, big stars, big like juicy kind of cheesy
plots. I don't know. Yeah, some things afoot in the town of Eastwick. Right. Exactly. Yeah.
Uh, you know, even Gremlins too was kind of in this good play like, you know, uh, we told you the
rules. That by the way, that guy's death or the effect I is dead. Either that or they stop giving him
work. When he went away, movie trailers dropped in my, in my estimation by 50%. That guy's voice.
And I remember the Gremlins two trailers so vividly, which was we told you the rules.
Remember that guy's voice? I remember. I got you didn't listen. I got so obsessed with it once
that I found out who he was. Yeah. I don't know his name, but he's an actor. Okay. Uh, he was an
old actor from the 60s. And then he got into voiceover work. But the reason I looked him up was because
he was my favorite horror movie trailer voiceover guy. Okay. Uh, and then he also was the guy
that did the special edition Star Wars trailers. Okay. So here we go. Here we go.
If you've only seen it on the small screen, yeah, you haven't seen it at all. Yeah, I remember that. Yeah.
And a few old friends are back. You know, like, like all that shit. Like what a, what an amazing
voice. All the trailers I love that would get me so excited. I don't even experience these emotions
anymore. How excited I would get over that guy's voiceover certain trailers. Yeah. But, uh,
RIP if you're dead and he's got to be dead. He's got to be dead. He was like 65 or 70, like in the 80s.
Like he's, you know, he was an older guy. Uh, but don't get them wet. Don't feed them after midnight.
But you didn't listen. Let's do. Let's do a thing we haven't done in a while. Let's do, uh, that guy
we can go back and forth ordering food at Taco Bell. Hi, welcome to Taco Bell. Can I take your order?
I'd love a chalupa chicken, a poor for the. I'm sorry for a second. I thought you were the movie
trailer guy, but it went off the tracks there for a second. You're not, you're just a different guy.
Uh, coming soon. Yeah, no. Me to the window with money. Right? Yeah, no, you're not him. All right.
Well, listen, just pull around. I'll get you that chalupa.
Uh, Joe, after one of the hardest weeks of my career, asking me to improv at 9 .30 p .m.
Not wise. I did my best. Uh, I don't think I could have done better to be honest.
And I'm going to do with the roots. I can do that well. Yeah, you can do that. I wish I could think
of more trailers he did, but this would be good. Yeah. That guy doing the drive through at Taco Bell.
Because then the customer could go, uh, hey, it's, uh, 4 .30 a .m. Can I order some food?
And then he could go, we told you the room. Yeah, 4 .00 a .m. is the cuddle for third dinner. That's good.
Second dinner. What would he, would they used to call it? Uh, fourth meal. The fourth meal. That's
right. The, whatever, whatever, Hobbit name they gave that. Yeah. Basically obesity. Uh, basically
fucking no basic pretty much up in Sydney. Okay, but great line on I've been watching the Dennis
Miller reruns again. Yeah. I know you don't want to hear it, but it was, you know, they're from,
yeah, early 2000s. Uh, it was right when the traffic church thing happened. He does a joke about the church.
Yeah. And he goes, hey, priests, newsflash, stop fucking kids. Okay.
Note that sounds bad. I did, I did a note to sell from the room the other day. And it was so perfect.
We were all really tired and got this huge laugh, but then somebody very rightly after the
laughter died down goes, did you just do a note to sell? And I'm like, yeah, I'll dust off a note to
sell. That's kind of normal. Did you do itself, uh, like sort of ironically, I mean, uh, yeah, there was
a little wink to it. Yeah, that's great. I love a note to sell. Now to sell. Uh, this movie I wanted
to shout out Jeffrey Boom, who's a writer you never hear mentioned. He died at 53 in the year 2000.
But Jeffrey Boom, man, this guy wrote, listen to this run, Jim. Listen to this run.
Straight time with Dustin Hoffman, which was his debut film. That thing is an amazing movie.
But then you're going to really start knowing what he's done. And that was remade later with
Dabney Coleman, correct? Straight, short time, short time. I used to love short time by the way.
I know you did. Great picture. Yeah. He wrote straight time with Dusty Hoffman. Okay. Number two film,
The Dead Zone. Wow. Chris walkin, David Cronenberg. A masterpiece. Steve King. Yeah. Followed
that with inner space. Wow. Already short, which we should do for this product. I'm possessed.
What a great movie that is. They used to kill me when I was a kid. Yeah, I'm possessed. Yeah, amazing
movie. And I bet that trailer guy did the voice for that too, by the way. Uh, he wrote the lost
boys with a few other people. He wrote easily, easily the most underrated movie of Chevy Chase's
career. Funny farm. Oh, I'm a big fan of fun. Funny farm is hilarious. But folks,
where I'm just listing amazing movies of the 80s, but look at the range of genres here.
The Dead Zone is a deadly serious horror sci -fi movie. Straight time is an amazing character drama.
Inter space is sci -fi comedy. Lost Boys is horror comedy. Funny farm is just a slapstick comedy.
That's impressive. Everyone walking to the Dead Zone sketch on SNL. One of my favorite
altars. He could at least. Yeah, it was all Monday. You left your purse in the cab. Yeah. You're
gonna order a bagel. Yeah. Amazing. All right. Straight time Dead Zone Inter space. Lost Boys
Funny Farm. He followed that up, Joe. He followed up Funny Farm with Indiana Jones in the last
crusade, which Pat, here's what here's what you call Kismet. You know how happy I am? You brought that up
because when we were talking earlier about greatest endings to a movie. Yes. For my money,
for my money. And of course, you've got to, you've got to consider the build up of the first two
films into it. The greatest ending ever ever of a movie ever is Indiana Jones in the last crusade.
Oh, when when it's Sean Connery, formerly James Bond, right, and Harrison Ford, formerly Han Solo,
now Indiana Jones, debatably an even cooler character on horseback after basically saving
civilization from the Nazis again. Indiana Jones says to his dad, he goes dad, meaning right off
first, and he goes after you son, and he goes, yes, sir. And then he rides off. And Indiana Jones
movie cranks up. And the trilogy ends with the four of them riding off into the sunset. It literally
makes me cry. It's such a fucking perfect ending to that movie. Jeff Bumbam.
He also wrote lethal weapon two, which I like almost as much of the original.
Two is great. And lethal weapon three, which, you know, the age was starting to show.
Yeah, that's fine now, but two, two is great. Two's I would argue might be better than one.
Made it debatable to one's a little darker. Yeah. Then folks, he spun into television with a show
that I love so fucking much when I was a kid called the Adventures of Briscoe County Junior,
starring Bruce Campbell. Wow, I used to love that fucking show. Very good. And then Joe, maybe you know
this, he wrote and directed tales from the crypt episode 61 Creep Course. Oh, Creep Course is the
one with, is that the mummy one with Jeffrey Jones? Creep Course. Yes, Jeffrey Jones. That's
a great one. Michael Hall. That's a great one. Okay. That's a really good one. I like that one a
lot. And then he did the Phantom, which I've never seen with Billy Zane, and then he died.
What do you die for? Heart. That's a guy whose name no one, even die hard movie fans know, Jeffrey
Bohem, B -O -A -M. And I mean, with that run, this man should be, these scripts should be taught in
classes. Yeah. That's very good. That's very good. Pat, what do you say we do some shout outs?
Love it. Folks, you are the Patreon, you are the nucleus, you are the core, you are our hearts.
Here are your shout outs for February 2019. Anthony V. Manito, aka party McFly, Philip Rashad, Richard
Howinstein, Chris Larson, Casey Sturgeon, Mike Grant, Ben Wright, Jayden Brady, Ashley McCarty,
Patrick C. Brenner, Tom, Daila Ramam music, Patrick Driscoll, Tory Workman, Melinda Ring,
Shelby L, Rocky Hawks, Sousa, Mike Cook, Brian Morton, Alexander Thomas, Lara Johnson, Zachary
Martinez, Alice Ryan, Jack Matt Murphy, Joe Kennedy, Bessie Talley Eferro, Alexis Taylor Ackridge,
Nicholas Misk Kowzland. I always think I'm going to get through it without tripping it up and
never do. Yeah. But Kowzland. Sophia Anderson, Chase Ophus, Tanner Rollins, Samantha Dashanau,
Mike Willis, Michael Burke, Brooke Adams, Braden Love, Jeff Henry, Nick Beck Beck, Katrina Elise
Gosen, Andrew Telshin, Preston Anderson, Bryce Buchmaster, Rusty, Martin Murray, Marcus Pup,
sorry, Marcus Publish, the mouth of Alf. Oh, that's a wink at you, Walsh. I got it. Scott Riggs, Max
Unwreff, Camani Claudefelder, Nicholas Yu, Joe, fuck, John Deffers, Sinji, Derek
Klesmer, Nicholas Edward Fallon, Albeck, Evan Barrett, Neil Delby, Christopher Klinger, bug main, Thomas
Brielle Christians, Christians, yeah, Christensen, trust your gut. I read I was reading it right,
right? It's down in myself. Marcus McGay, Peeve, Jared Pacquan, Christopher Musil, Daniel Peshau,
Joe, I swear I'm not racist. I was just tired and nervous. Nicole Will Nolton, Jonathan Sprouls,
Brian Shactor, Taylor, Lindy West, Dustin Collins, Kevin Schwistowicz, not medium rare, Tom Holt,
Justin Tyler, Pat Walsh's dad, baby Bop and Barney, yeah, right, baby Bop and Barney and baby
Bops Blanky, David Crum Holtz, our old friend. Love you, Crummy. And by the way, if that Patrick
Driscoll is the Patrick Driscoll, I know. How are you old friend? And welcome aboard.
Alexander Monter, oh geez, Alexander Monter Rubio, Matt Chairs, Martin Dan Jarchau, Ryan Peahall,
of Rooster Teeth theme. How you doing, Ryan? Christopher Reynolds, Patrick Baxter, Julie Bailey,
Violet, you're turning Violet, Violet, Sam Elliott, Brett Urway, Patrick Weithin, Truth
Crab, Dave DeWitt, Sadie Bug, Cole Rathaker, Waffles, Steven Calpa, Sam Mitchell spends all his
money on Cheap vodka instead of paying H, Kelly Amoroso, Beth Gastone, Sharifa, David Denahee,
Devlow Trevor Gage, Joshua Christensen, KP Flynn, Elva Enriquez, Lesley Confin, Jackson C,
Lomire, Ash Ogden, Rain, Purple Peacock, Sterling Abrego, Christopher Sebella,
Oh, non -nemis, bone -her, I don't know, I get it. Drew Tiberius Poll, Tyler Lapointe, Steve Smith,
Lupe Pita Pacheo, Tancy Zonjic, Matt Robin, Will Foley, Kevin Ragati, Joseph, Christian Reynolds,
Josh Smallridge, Kurt Ziegler, Brittany Ferguson, Sean Florent, Danny Rudd, Natalie Hartline, Leo Lopez,
Emily Rock, shit, every time I fuck it up, sorry, Emily, Emily Rook, not Rock,
Southview, Dave Del Greco, Kurt Ziegler, Chloe Paget, Dennis Ormston, Travis Hines, Josh
Wyzengruber, Matthew McGuire, Angela Pokaro, James O 'Brien, Matthew Moon, J. Fisher, Sean Lyle,
John Hollywood, Jack McAlvin, nope, Jack McAlvin, Meredith McWilliams, Tanning Shadeham,
I don't know, he was a fan, Jesse Janicki, or Janicki, Mike Greenwood, Brianna Alcair, Matt,
supportive guy, oops, I said that last one wrong, Anthony Rodriguez, Chris Passmore, Casey Jones,
Sinji, Robert Haynes, Natalie Hatley, Will Pittman, Kevin McNannie, Kevin Driscoll, Jen Wessels,
Joe Hoffman, Scott Sweeney, J. Miller, Clayton Stamper, Amanda Lancaster, Michael Bolis, Ethan
Gammage, James Guy Rolamo, Derek Adams, Sean Hall, Adam Lownsbury, Vincent Franks, Joseph
Sarah Catherine, Paul Merchie, Scott Sweeney, Kara Konini, sorry, Cara Konini, Chuck Andrews,
Tom Laverick, Tucker Rouch, John Smith Andrew, Brian Belaureer, Will Helms, Jennifer Anna, T L
Mon Holland, Jack Jake Polick, SlaybodiesNotRainDeer, zerofoxtrot .com, Matt Crawford, Rich Deming,
Richard Deming, Brian Callis, Tim Drain, Michael Madrigal, I go to Mr. Shoot Records and Lancaster
PA, Bretton Fraser, Sean Luke Physioc, Karen Kilgarif, listen to my favorite murder, Nathan Baskett,
Gary Morone, or Myron, Dylan Law, Phil Barrell, Edmund Dillon, the Blackmagic Ninja, Scott
Pauline Surrell, Daphne Kellogg, Tristan Avery, Dabney Coleman, Matthew J. Brown, Julie Aguire,
Charity Ferguson, Hank from Dan Cakes, Nick Walther, Alexander Stein, Emily Marvel, John B Watt,
visit John Zombians, Harcraft Store, and Etsy, Mori Benjamin, Nicholas Burns, Alex Nelson, Jeremy
Cool, Duke of Swirl, Alex Shipley, excuse me, Sean Pinnock, Amanda Liebson, Timothy Letso, Shane
Nazarene, Smelly Bubbles, Hay Samantha Kiefer, we're married now, crazy, David Belinger, Hunter Mcdonald,
Justin Bohegger, Adam Benbenek, Mani Rios, Damani O 'Rubio, Brandon Gash, Shalom Brandon,
Jake Ferret, Rob Lines, Jacob Barrett, Jordan C, Maxwell Ashcroft, Ashcroft, Bar Ballon, Chris
Bowen, Mike Gibbons, Donnie Joyce, Michael Dawson, Jennifer Smith, Connor Dennehy, Anthony Jake
Wahardo, Annie Johanison, Timmy K, Megli Brandt, Scott Blikensdurfer, Brett Werner, Laura Sexton,
Anthony Wahardo, Jared Blair, Richie Verdugo, Chris Hooper, Emily Florence, our matriarch, hello,
Sean Al, Abby Manuel, Jonathan Galott, Michael McBee, Stephanie Power, Diego Campos, Stefan, Musau, Zoe
Blaskeweck, Aasley Kibbonsland, Dan McLeod, Lorenz Bungannears, Alejandro Salgado, Tracy Reddington,
Sean Thomas, Amanda Alzamora, Jason Weibel, Mike Curry, Andrew Koval, Sam Mitchell, Aaron Melanowski,
Scott Nolan, Ben, Misty Zavar, hey sport, Coca -Cola, that's a kingpin rapper,
Dajane Willford, hello, Dajane, Dajane Willford, hello, Michelle Gold, Dennell Duer, Eric Lamora,
Kevin Marcenek, Lawrence Anderson, Jared Smallridge, Will Platter, hello Will, Natalie Craig, Kyle,
Kinsland Monty, oh shoot, sorry, we're not supposed to say his name.
Ani Babaduk, Scott Patton, Sam Street, Kevin Stickers at PintServices. Kevin Stickers at PintServices .com,
the block watch, Rage Last Name Sounds, Asian, Michael Iolo and Reed Aesthetic, thank you all for your
support, it is insane, I can't get over it, we can't get over it, we're flattered, we're touched.
That is awesome to hear, thank you all, nice to hear.
It's a hell of a list, huh?
I was blown away, blown away, warmed the coccles of my heart as they say.
And the heart of the heart of the heart of the heart, it was gonna say that God damn it, beat you to it.
Gee, cheers watch.
Joe, what's your favorite film of the 80s?
That's a tough one because technically the Empire Strikes Back is an 80s film.
You know how I feel about Star Wars.
Technically Raiders of the Lost Ark is an 80s film.
So I'm not really counting those movies because I kind of put them into a different thing.
I know but you know when you say I don't know I'm trying to I kind of I feel like you got
a categorized.
Well it's also like there's a kind of horror movies I love from the 80s.
Creepshow is being the 80s and I'm obsessed.
Creepshow is in my top 10 movies ever.
They just did that on 80s.
They were taking one from Creepshow 2 and putting it they wish they could swap one.
One second.
The raft.
That's the yeah that's the only one we're swapping but I find Creepshow to be a perfect
film.
But that's very excited.
Shutter rap productions today on their first episode of their Creepshow series.
An anthology?
They're doing an anthology series.
They're reading on Creepshow.
I'm very excited.
That'll be great.
And King is going to be sort of involved to some extent I think.
So if I've never seen any and want to kind of get into them I need to do Twilight Zone
first probably right.
Before Creepshow.
I've seen Creepshow.
I'm talking like if like we're talking out of limits tales from the crypt.
All that stuff.
I don't think you have to do any there any first I mean.
They're all they're all their own sort of thing.
To me the Twilight Zone is the greatest television show ever made.
Okay.
It rains overall.
And I love very every rendition of it.
Including even a few episodes from the first Whitaker one.
Overall that's not a great one.
But you know the 60s Twilight Zone is to me is it's unmatched.
That's my opinion.
The outer limits I find I own the outer limits I enjoy the outer limits.
I find it much much more boring than the Twilight Zone.
The episodes are much longer.
They're much drier and they are very science fiction fueled.
Whereas where is Twilight Zone was more morality tales with a science fiction twinge to them or twist to them rather.
Tales in the crypt is a whole different bag.
Tales in the crypt is fun.
Goofy sexy.
Yeah.
That seems like what I'd like blood and tits kind of thing you know which is great.
I love tales in the crypt also almost almost front to back is great.
That's got way more doozies than the original Twilight Zone run.
But it's also got more seasons so it's it's you know I love tales in the crypt.
But I don't think one begets the other.
I think the only the only show that to me the Twilight Zone made more sense out of
was Tales in the dark side.
Because Tales in the dark side comes in that weird period before Tales in the crypt.
Which is sort of what it was based on because it's an extension of creep show and creep show was based on Tales in the crypt.
But it was before that TV show came out and it was but it was after the Twilight Zone.
So you can see moments in Tales in the dark side where you go.
Why the fuck did they do an episode about a girl whose brother goes into a computer?
Right.
Like who cares.
This is stupid.
And you go oh because the only model they really had to follow was was Twilight Zone.
And they thought well we should have some quirky ones.
We should have some sort of science fictiony ones.
We should you know it kind of bounce around.
But dark side out of all the ones we've talked about has the most misses.
Okay.
But I loved dark.
I love it.
I love all that shit.
But I mean you know a lot of it for me is you know look a big part of it for me is like that sort of that sort of Saturday afternoon rainy day kind of thing.
Like you know like like watching an old like Harryhausen you know claymation horror movie it's it's you know is the movie itself that riveting maybe.
But it's kind of more just the idea of what it is you're you're getting into you know.
Speaking of does Miller are you a Bordello of blood fan?
No.
Yeah.
I used to crank it to it but not great.
I think he's extremely funny in it.
But I but he's clearly have living most of his stuff.
And I think he's the only Feldman's in that.
He's got a great way in where because the girls looking for Feldman her brother.
Yeah.
He's missing.
And she shows Dennis Miller's the private ID shows her the picture of Feldman and he looks almost he does the lost boys like ridiculous.
Yeah.
And Miller does that Miller laugh.
You know when he goes.
Can I keep this?
I want to put it in a locket.
Which is a funny way.
Apparently on the was I have the shout our scream factory demon night which I fought for this for this podcast and I enjoyed very much.
But there's also a scream factory Bordello of blood which I have not seen but.
Apparently everyone on it talks about just what an unbelievable prick Dennis Miller was at that time.
I've heard that they despised him on that movie.
I've heard that.
I've heard he's I've heard he's not the nicest guy.
Yeah, I'll buy that.
Which is a bummer.
I'll buy that.
Anyone who his whole comedy is how much smarter he is than you like that.
He's definitely carrying that into his personal life.
I've never met him.
I have only I worked for I've worked for his brother for years and his brothers are very nice guy.
And I hope that if I remember Dennis he'd be a nice guy but I can't speak to it.
But I've also heard those stories.
I can't say that I haven't.
You know brother of course Barney Miller.
Barney Miller is his brother.
Yeah.
And the the oldest brother is Arthur Miller.
Okay.
All right.
Followed by Henry Miller or the author.
Sure.
It's a it's a powerful fact.
Then there's a big age gap.
Right.
The dentist the comedian.
Yes.
I'm gonna rich who I know.
Yeah.
Anyway.
The.
Hold it right here.
Holy shit.
It's the attack of Eddie Munster.
Somebody just yelled while their life's in jeopardy.
Like that's the kind of joke I don't care for.
Because to me this movie doesn't even really attempt a joke for an hour.
That's not a horror comedy.
Yeah.
It does.
Jokes to the whole movie.
Not not to me.
Not to me.
Horror comedy at this time.
This was not a was not very well balanced out quite yet.
Sure.
You know.
The prototypes were like the Abbott and Castellan meet Frankenstein movies.
Right.
Which is night.
Which I love.
And they're hilarious.
I heard Evil Dead 2 was 87.
So we're getting better for sure.
For sure.
But I mean, even Evil Dead 2.
Well, Evil Dead 2 is a great example of a horror comedy.
And you first saw that.
A blinded.
You get it.
Beetle juice is to me.
One of the perfect examples.
Although that's clearly more like comedy.
Yeah.
There's nothing scary in Beetle juice.
That's great.
Evil Dead 2 sort of has both.
And that's that's almost impossible.
And Abbott and Kasselmy Frankenstein is hilarious.
Right.
But it's a comedy.
It's 90 minutes of.
Right.
Bud Abbott going.
Or Lucas.
I'm going.
Right.
You know what?
To me, one of the scariest films ever made is Abbott and Castellan meet Frankenstein.
Are you joking?
Yes, of course.
Yeah.
I guess it does actually have some creepy parts.
But I mean, it's.
It's.
Sure.
You ever see Haunted Honeymoon?
Yeah.
That the scene where he's sitting on the dead guy and pretending the dead guy's legs or his legs is.
Is classic wilder.
Yeah.
It's got some moments.
But it's not good.
It's young Frankenstein.
Again, you know, you'd like to say it's the perfect horror comedy, but there's no horror.
No, it's just a comedy.
It's a great reproduction of like old horror movies, but it's just a pure comedy.
It often misses the vote on many people's best of Mel Brooks lists because Mel Brooks didn't solely write and direct it.
Right.
He wrote it with Gene Wilder.
But to me, it's the best Mel Brooks movie.
Nothing.
Don't disagree.
It's a fucking magnificent film.
And young Frankenstein is.
I mean, for a comedy to be that well shot is amazing, but my god is a fucking funny.
So funny.
What's your favorite joke?
Or gag or whatever?
Oh boy.
By the way, Keith or Sutherland just died because they put.
He just died.
I mean, so this is a big reveal for me.
The funniest moments of that are all wilder screaming.
Just anytime wilder is screaming, I.
To me, better than Willy Wonka, the setup of the setup of I'm going to go into this room.
Right.
No matter what you hear, do not let me out.
Yeah.
The second the door shuts.
Let me out.
You got the M Dirty Bastions.
I'll kick your goddamn dirty heads in.
Yeah.
Like the immediate flip flop of that is so fucking funny.
I would also put on the best performances of all time.
And I'm not just saying comedic.
I would put Gene Wilder and young Frankenstein.
Incredible.
He's incredible of it.
In it.
Excuse me.
Are you in drunk over there?
I know I am.
I'm a little tipsy.
Now what are you going to do about your car?
You're just going to leave it.
I'm going to leave it, but unfortunately I'm parked in a fucking one hour spot starting at 8 a .m. on a Saturday.
Listen, let's make a pact right now.
We both make sure we wake up at 7 .30 a .m. tomorrow.
All right.
I got a big day tomorrow.
So, you know, fuck it.
We're in this together.
At this point.
All right.
What do we do after this?
You want to go out?
Yeah.
Sure.
Jamie Gertz is almost super human in this movie.
Like just unbelievable.
Look at the face.
She's just a real light.
Now, this is the big reveal in the movie because he kills the head vampire key for Sutherland and Jason Patrick doesn't turn back to human.
What's the problem?
And then here is the big reveal that Max actually is the head vampire.
And for years and years and years now, my dear friend, Big J. Oakerson has done this line to me.
Which one?
And I laugh hysterically.
He will turn his head and turn back to me and he'll go, but I still want you, Lucy.
I haven't changed my mind about that.
And he's done it to me for years and years while we're drinking or whatever.
And it makes me laugh every fucking time he does it because he does a really good impression of it.
How did all the other stuff not work on him?
How do they explain that?
Because he's the head vampire.
So he has like greater, you know, he has different resistance.
Sure.
Yeah.
He's greater.
He can, you know, he can, he can, he can withstand garlic.
He can, he can keep an erection for longer.
Sure.
You know what I mean?
Did I tell you I saw you out in John again the other night?
You know, man, at the last minute Vince called me and asked me if I wanted to take it.
I had a show and I couldn't go.
Just phenomenal.
When I was right away, we had perfect seats, but we were like to the right side of the stage.
And he comes out and sits down and I'm like, oh.
We were facing his back.
Like we had just as good seats as the people on the other side, but they see the face.
We're looking at his ass.
But it wanted to be very cool because you had to see him play the piano.
What are you open with?
Benny and the.
He's doing the greatest.
That's right.
The final greatest hit.
He ain't none wrong with that.
The man deserves it at this point.
The man's got enough hits to fill up two hours.
My, my favorite Elton Song, someone saved my life tonight.
A masterpiece.
That song's three great songs in one.
Now, I thought your favorite was that Lion King tune.
Can you feel?
Right?
That one?
Or a circle of life.
Both of those.
And then all.
Just his parts in the Stan Grammy live rendition with M &M.
Oh, I don't know that one.
You don't understand when he.
When they did Stan M &M.
Yes, I do remember.
Yeah.
And Elton was like.
I thought there was a very cool thing they both did.
It was awesome.
I mean, clearly M &M got more out of it than by his person.
It's awesome because on the next record, M &M goes.
He's talking about him in Dr. Dre and he goes,
where the most feared duets since me and Elton play career Russian roulette.
And I was like, that's really cool that he calls out.
Like, he's like, yeah, we knew that it was.
Not the greatest idea, but.
It worked out.
Yeah, it was the hell of a show.
A great man.
And then whether this is true or not, he was like,
a lot of people have been asking me why I'm retiring.
It is to devote the remaining moments of my life.
To finding a kill for HIV and AIDS.
And I was like, that's a pretty good reason to retire.
Yeah, I've got the money to do it.
I'm going to work tirelessly.
But isn't that somebody was telling me that was there.
They were like, this is kind of like to make up for the fact that.
I might be 100 % wrong right now, but I don't think I am.
Apparently, he was kind of like sort of like flipping about AIDS at one point.
OK, like I think apparently one point is like, why I ain't got it love.
You know, like one of those things.
And I think now he's like being like, oh, I should have been like more active right earlier on.
I would ever get some.
I'm not knocking the guy.
I'm just saying like, I think that's.
I might be 100 % wrong.
All right, but I don't think I am.
Does this count as black face on these kids?
Why would it count as black face, Pat?
Well, it's a very, I mean, everybody's talking about black face.
Well, there was just an explosion.
Oh, right.
They're sitting on their faces.
Well, I saw somebody talking about Dick Van Dyke from Mary Poppins.
Is that black face because he got sup?
Look, people, it's offensive.
It's the last line of the film, right?
Yeah, this thing really, it's really moved.
It's, you know, it's offensive.
But you can't, you know, it was, when the fuck did Mary Poppins come out?
We didn't, we, we, we, we were learning, you know what I mean?
Yeah.
Nobody's saying it.
It was okay that they did it.
But you get it, you know, it's like.
Well, but Mary Poppins, he had sup in this face.
Was that, did they ever do a black face bit and Mary Poppins?
I'm saying if it was or whatever.
It's like people, you know, it's like, yeah, we were dumber then.
Like we, we, we were trying to progress here, you know, right?
I've a bit in my act right now about like, you know, terrified that somebody's going to come to me.
Maybe like, you know, if I ever get famous, I was going to be like, Joe, we, um,
we found out that, uh, you're three months old.
You're in the high chair.
You kicked your mother in the face.
Can you please explain that right now?
You know, it's like, sure.
I did.
Anyway, uh, well, look, if you don't got no skeletons in your closet,
then you ain't got no fun in your past.
I says, I says, I says, I says, you got nothing to worry about.
No, that's another way to go.
Now I know I'm just kidding.
This is come out of the rain.
When you're strange.
Now we can try to flip it over quick to.
I don't have to be on here.
We can't do the.
Oh, it was kidding.
We don't have to go.
It's going to be too complicated.
Yeah.
All right.
I'll just show it to you privately.
I'm sorry to watch it.
Uh, let's plug away real fast here.
Uh, I, uh, you know, Jotaro is a comedy on Instagram.
I will be.
What the hell day is it?
February.
I will be in Vegas and March at Bonkers Comedy Club.
Check my Instagram for details.
Also, I'll be returning to the Moon Tower Comedy Festival festival in Austin, Texas,
in April.
So come see me there if you live in Austin.
Uh, and penthouse dot com is now live the penthouse website.
And many of my pieces that I've written for it over the past couple years are up there
and many other very interesting things, including a very interesting piece entitled,
uh, Does Judd Appetal Deserve To Be Cancels?
And I, uh, I think it's a very interesting read.
I think you should read it.
Um, anyway, uh, check out the website.
Check out my stuff.
I hope you like it.
And also my second, uh, fiction, uh, horror story, entitled Menu Change.
We'll be show, uh, we'll be premiering in the March April issue, uh, on newsstands only.
Uh, and I guess that is, oh, and uh, the uninformed podcast is back.
Go to patreon .com slash burr, uh, two episodes a month for five bucks.
That's it.
My name is the Patrick Walsh on Instagram and Twitter.
And the cool kids is about to start a run of like eight new episodes in a row after a bizarre time off.
So, uh, really, this is, this is my favorite run of shows coming up the next eight Friday nights,
7 30 or 8 30 wherever you're at are on Hulu.
Uh, we will see you next time.
We haven't picked a movie, but watch the news.
The spirit because that's on the docket.
The spirit is on docket.
We might do overlord, which I saw, which I think you should see.
I will watch.
Sure.
It's pretty.
Yeah, I think that's a good one.
All right.
Uh, we'll see you next time.
And we'll see you in hell.