B
c
Oh boy, welcome to we'll see you in hell!
Hello!
Hi, everybody.
Again, second show in a row, you grabbed yourself a beer, didn't get me one.
Because you're drunk.
I am, I am.
We're over here at the bar across the street and Joe goes, man, I'm fucked up.
I got to get my shit together.
Pounds of jack and coke.
How's that going to help?
It's called evening out, my friend.
What you do?
Oh boy.
Could I have a beer just so I could sort of get even over here from the jack?
We had a bunch of wings over there at the black crescent, my favorite bar in the neighborhood.
My buddy Reynolds owns this bar.
You prefer it to yours?
Yeah, my own bar can't be my favorite bar.
That's insane.
But they're right across the street.
It's a great bar and he's letting us hang out over there in between the shows and stuff like that.
Thank you so much.
Isn't that nice?
I have one, too, which I stole and need to be credited to my tap.
We will pay for these beers we promise.
I'm doing dishes, P .W. Herman style in the back for days to make up for it.
But we went over, what happened to that?
Doing dishes to make up for Boeing at debt?
I feel like now you say, hey, look, I'm sorry I ripped you off.
Let me go do your dishes and they flip out about it.
It's like, no, I'm calling the police.
And you're like, I'm doing the dishes.
You've never been on a road trip where you've gotten stuck and had to do dishes to pay for your dinner?
No.
Really?
I can't wait to.
Happened to me many times on my road trip back from LA.
Yes.
Many times I was hard up.
I was in a jam.
And I washed my dishes to get by.
All right.
Yeah.
You know, that guy suggested that I suck somebody's dick.
Washington, dickist.
Mike Harrington is having a nervous breakdown over here.
What's going on, all right, buddy?
We too loud.
We too quiet.
Yeah.
We too perfect.
Looks good on the card.
Right on the machine.
All right.
How's the sound?
You guys write down your questions?
Yes.
I've got a question from Emily by the way.
No, no, no.
Relax.
Let me know.
Jesus Christ.
Who came from the farthest away?
Anyone from out of the country?
Whoa.
Canada.
Canada is good.
We didn't have any Canada last time.
Germany.
Oh, okay.
Two from Canada.
Hello.
Welcome.
That's very exciting.
You know, you're responsible for the extinction of a people.
I don't feel that now.
Not you.
Your grandpa.
And let's be real.
Grandma, who you might think is innocent.
Now we're kidding.
Are you from Germany, Germany?
You just live there right now.
Oh, yeah.
She's from Germany.
And you came all the way here.
Not for this.
Please, not for this.
Are you also going to see at least one site in New York?
Okay.
Have you ever been here before?
So what are you going to see?
Stat Lady Liberty?
How was that?
Yeah.
It kind of sucks, right?
We have a...
Let's be real.
Wonderful.
Also kind of sucks.
We have a wonderful Holocaust Museum.
You might want to check out.
Maybe you learned something.
Welcome.
I can't believe you flew from Germany.
I have a cousin that lives in Germany.
I wouldn't fly there for that.
You came for the podcast.
Official October Fest is in September.
Am I wrong?
It starts in September.
Okay.
So I went to a bar the other day.
Red lion.
German bar in London.
I love red lion.
I do too.
But they were like, celebrate October Fest.
Starting September 15th.
And I was like, that can't be right.
But I guess it's right.
There we go.
I would like to celebrate
joctober personally.
Sure.
Yeah.
You wear a rock strap and nothing else.
I go down to the locker room.
I'll tease the boys a bit.
Joctober Fest is the most peridede term.
Rocktober.
Yeah.
Rock.
This is shocked tober on,
Opie, Nancyne, when he said Opie,
they do shocked tober where they would make fun
of other morning radio shows.
Uh -huh.
Joctober of course is one.
I've heard schloctober before.
When I...
Joctober of course.
Yeah.
Somebody's...
When I was a classical radio DJ we did
October.
Oh, that's very good.
When I was a sailor we always had
October. Now we did October as part of my back -to -the -future fan club group. Yeah. I'm staying at the
South Street Seaport. Anyone familiar? Are you? Are you really? Yeah. Okay. That was part of your
that was like I was like what hotel is near the the theater there's nowhere near the theater just
over it's in try back theater did you just refer to this as yes a few theaters have a
a chai latte hot chocolate on the menu where's everybody staying y 'all in time square anybody wall
struck at you're by me then anybody in the M &M store by the way yeah do these M &M's have different
personalities I know the the woman is a bit of a slut but do the other M &M's have any characteristics
other than being green or brown what are they racist to me oh okay so they do have like
personalities all right I didn't know I didn't know wait a minute I'm just noticing you all have
3D glasses I don't think it's all come from
thank you loupa loupa had to make up for thank you loupa ruining our other life
you think you think you think you were drunk
I'm sure thank you very much these are awesome what happened with I don't remember she was just
drunk and yelling stuff out in Chicago we've all been there yeah yeah I don't remember a bad way I'm
thinking about Chicago if you were talking shit about Olivia Wilde we should have listened to you were
as I told everyone in the last podcast because I had a panic attack this morning and wound up
reading a profile of Olivia Wilde and Vanity Fair leasily a 45 minute read that I read for no I don't
even like this person but I learned as I said in the last podcast that she chose the last name wild
as a quote tip of the cap to Oliver Wilde Oscar Oscar Wilde yeah who's who's struck now buddy
Oliver Wilde I was thinking I'll live the Oliver and company that doesn't make it better Lauren
I saw Oliver company in the theater Billy Joel recorded the song by the way I never knew until I read
on movieweb .com or screen round .com yesterday the top six adaptations of Oliver twist did it make
the cut that Oliver and company was an adaptation of Oliver and honestly it was a five list and then
the last the the sixth place last place on the list was a movie called twist starting Michael
Kane in a modern was he fake like Guy Richie style retelling of Oliver twist yes when did this come
out I've never heard of it I think it came out like 2000 why not call it twisted because that's
the name of a rap group that runs around with the ICP well I'm sure I'm sure that's what stopped
no it was called twist and I might it was and she heard of the rap group it looks so bad I
didn't even know to twist it the rap group it looks so bad it was like an art heist movie yeah about
and but then they all have the name they have they have the regular names from the book right but it's
like the artful Dodger yeah it's like to that well they but they change it slightly it's like it and it
did the terrible like Guy Richie thing in the trailer where they introduced the characters and it
like freeze frames that goes twist the crook uh -huh and then it was like dodge the heist how do they
abbreviate Peragon careful careful hey I hope they went within yeah no Fagan was still just Fagan yeah
all right Dodger artful Dodger was the only one they abbreviated it doesn't even remember that I
portrayed Fagan and uh and fourth great please say Fagan I just did please put a harder A into it no
you're putting a short A into it and it's troubling it's the man's name Fagan don't say it again he
doesn't he he doesn't he doesn't remember that this was part of the podcast I don't remember much
these days won't I cry at least once a day lucky lucky uh Ken can we get the uh can we get the
uh Ken Henley can we get the questionnaire cards is that possible yeah but you don't have to he
was gonna collect all right thank you oh thanks yeah just pass them on up thank you thank you
okay all right all right let's just jump into it here yeah we got a lot of questions
answer wait a minute we did this last episode fuck Mary kill Richard Dreyfus Roy Scheider
Robert Shaw Emily you can listen to the last episode we already did it that was Emily oh she
was I Emily we had different answers I fucked uh I married Dick Dreyfus that's insane I fucked Roy
Scheider and I killed Bobby Shaw and I'll repeat it and then everybody at home is going to get mad
because we're repeating content but you killed Dreyfus because nobody wants to listen to that
post -coid is pre -coid is marital whatever you killed you don't get miss the house oh Shaw's gonna
fuck Shaw's gonna fuck you like a fisherman and you marry Scheider cheddar's at the light no Scheider
does seem like a good husband I'll grant you that I see your point of view yeah and I'm telling you
that's about as far as I'll go uh David Belinger asks
the applause should really wait he's not here what do you mean no we're only answering questions
of people that are here that was the point I know David Belinger all right all right he asks a question
that is far too deep for this what advice would you give to a future version of yourself
don't get married is what I was
yeah Ryan Sickler asked me this when I did his podcast the honeydew
but but that was tied much more into a like career advice or something yeah in normal advice I would
say uh just life advice I would say to my younger self learn how to love yeah try to figure it out
yeah it's hard uh because otherwise you're just gonna be 45 having the time of your life
yeah yeah you're not wrong because even when you learn how to love it can still
uh learn into love love into learning kick you in those nuts is that a real song it's
a Wayne oh yeah yeah it's a great song all right uh Brian Wigman asks which young hard director
are you the most hard hard you're the most excited about any new projects we should look out for
the best young hard director well you know I like with uh I like most of what that guy that did
Dr. sleep is doing which his name again Mike Flanagan Mike Flanagan he's pretty good uh I think that the
works of Ariaster or an abomination uh and I think I think that Thai West hits the mark sometimes
and and not other times but I like I like Dex and I think you know I'm excited to see the prequel yeah
but that's that's I guess that's my take on that what do you what do you think I immediately go
with Ariaster I think I know unquestionably one of the few people doing something interesting with horror
nowadays and um I hope we get more horror from a Nicholas winding ref in another gentleman you hate
well what do you make drive but he doesn't need me on demon but neon demon was horror ish I wanted to make
a horror movie and I want a horror movie from uh Luca Guadagnol the Susperio gentleman
yes because I love Susperio yes I would love another horror movie and he apparently has new movies
about cannibals and I would love but it's like a love and he did cast his boy army hammer a true
candle yeah that is interesting but it's like a true love story it's not like I did you ask army hammer
to eat those women uh more importantly why'd you poison that queen
why'd you poison that queen wait the queen of England yeah she poisoned I thought Reggie Jackson killed
the queen yes yes I must kill the queen how did they not how did they not run that clip on the news
I must kill even even as a zombie he acted that pretty poorly
now he's come on don't you uh Joe's defensive of Reggie Jackson all
oh it's your turn go ahead what phrase your character by the way I got on the mispat show
the pompous man talking to her and she goes who is this phrase your ass n word
very good very good uh miss pat likes to point out to everyone all the inwards that I wrote
which is very uncomfortable what phrase your character do you relate with the most says Sadie
she's going just by her first name uh well I I relate the most to phrase your because he's so troubled
the phrase your because he's so troubled honestly you know but I like to think I'm a little bit of
martin yeah a sprinkle of phrase and I'll dance in a bit of death me okay and also I got a lot of
rosin me yeah and between us she's got a lot of Joe in her no no bulldog I appreciate
the dog is one of the weakest characters in history yeah I he's the he's the Joe Rogan of news radio
you're like I like I want you oh you mean Joe Rogan's character but I like but here but I
doesn't think Rogan's character on news radio I actually like the character I don't like the
character of bulldog I like the idea behind the character I like they they they found a gay guy
to play the most showvinistic straight guy ever that's interesting but the character and the fact
that the character is in like the cast shots yeah is insane to me he's got nothing to do with the show
occasionally had a line on cheers in the cast yes you know like the bald guy you'd be like well I
don't think you should do that yeah Sam who gets who does get brought back into some of the reunion
cat cheers episodes of Frazier that's right yeah yeah I gotta say I'm I'm half marty half
frage okay you know I'm I'm half blue collar half wine snifter okay so I'd say half those two
no niles I never got niles I never I don't relate it all to niles but he's the funniest
care he is the funniest character all right Kevin asks Joe excuse me Joe have you changed your mind
about Ariaster no no he decidedly not he knows how to frame a shot he knows how to light a shot he
can't tell a story for shit he has no consistency in his movies and if you take away the shock
value there is nothing there to entertain you I will stand by that and oh I can't wait for his
new film disappointment boulevard isn't that what it's called if you're gonna call the movie
disappointment boulevard when you know critics are gonna review it it's gotta be pretty good
that is what it's called yeah oh I thought I was wrong all right no that's what it's called
and it's like Joaquin Phoenix put on 30 pounds so we give him an Oscar it's like no you need 50
plus baby and they all put on 30 pounds a year okay it's called the pandemic and then he's got a
question for you here Pat can we get in on with the Joe
yes yes you can and I did a song in the last one so it's only fitting that I should do this
uh let's get on with the show and at the same time on
all right you're welcome how this one says how much with three question marks is this a proposition
because it ain't much it's been a while but serious I met that guy once he was a fucking dildo
what is it stained yeah I met that guy yeah yeah Harvey stayed who created the band state
uh how much but seriously but seriously Joe oh geez why did you do what you did this person's drawn
there's not a question there best movie gang asks Kyle or so where's Kyle
are we talking gang like bloods and crypts all right best movie gang okay why are you interpreting his
question okay all right best movie gang is is good fellas it's good fellas well if they're a gang
sure yeah sure they're gang I was thinking like the warriors warriors are a great pick I got to go good
I mean it's that that crew of good fellas is yeah is to me you can't beat that all right fair enough
you mean the Lorraine Brocko and the women who were getting the face shit but on them yeah yeah the party
where they're talking what are you gonna pick the the cast of the kitchen with uh listen my
car theme the kid no I picked the warriors the what it's a great new york it's a great thing you know
what I'll give you a bonus one and I'm and I honestly think this lost boys frog brothers and
quarry him that's a great that's a great little that's a great little crew guys yeah okay fair enough
Matt Flynn asks what villain slash monster would you most want to be killed by also how big are
your dicks my god who asked this I forget already I love how that hand just went right up just like
yeah it was me I want to know we have to pretend we haven't measured yeah I Darth Vader I want to
be killed by Darth Vader I forgot the first part of the question would villain slash monster would
you want to be killed by would I want to be killed by uh species from the film species oh yeah
the beautiful woman who fucks you to death here you can go under the skin on that one that's true right
yeah or uh what's her name and uh golden eye who squeezes you but twix turd meaty thighs what was
her name Natalia piscino or something piscina on on a top yeah that's right and honestly I like
I like a lady on a top and how big is your dick was the second part you know I can't get
his specifics fair enough fair enough do they come on uh she's thick on a top or your dick
bowl all right it it has a feminine energy to attract females too do you have any bucket list things
you want to do was the Morgan Freeman Jack Nicholson film the bucket list the first time that's
arm entered the world I never heard yeah yeah they coined it that movie sucked do you have any bucket list
things you want to do before we see you and how asks mark den bison not all right have you talked
to the girl from germany because your name is den bison that's a german name you look german
you look more arm band than windmill I'll say that much bucket list things I want to do
before I die there's tons there's tons um what do you think
pet my bucket list is to see the movie the bucket list you're gonna be real at down that's an easy
one to achieve though feel like it's a nice easy deathbed watch yeah yeah um I would like to get
shot in the face by dick chaining yes by my boy dick there's no there's so many things on my bucket list
that I'll never do I'm like I'll get in shape I'll start to be a decent man I'll never do coke ever
again I'm not gonna do any of these things I've done the big ones I've skydove I've bungee jump
to I had a threesome long time ago long time ago I did all the things you're supposed to do I worked
at saturday night live oh it's things you wanted I was doing things I want to stop doing
can't you do it that way no a bucket list is things you want to do no I was saying like I'll give up
this I'll I'll stop eating in a certain way right things you want to do I mean it's not lent yeah
you really need to watch the bucket list just to learn what it is take notes all right fair enough
all right uh this is anonymous uh an episode 421 I didn't even know they were numbered
you talked about how you masturbated as a child how do you masturbate now
how that's a question standard way
hey I intentionally never involved a lubricant or anything because I wanted to keep it pure I
really never have just old -fashioned brick and mortar jacket I do it uh incredibly fast
it's just a means to get on with the day I like to treat myself like a lady no I don't care
anymore I like to undress it I'm like all right let's go let's come on anytime we have to talk
about this let's go uh you're not like you don't change videos 30 times you just grab it I
I lock it on one I get it done I gotta get I got shit to do I gotta get on the board I change
videos all day and then I'm like oh I've killed 17 hours to them and still have not spurted my
Stephen Murdoch asks
how does it feel to have such a great group of fans that became best friends
that's very nice it feels so good I dropped all the questions but it's great no when I was in
Atlanta I I popped in to see these like uh you know the group of everybody chatting on like a
Thursday night or whatever it was I know there's a couple of of these groups I don't know the theme of
this one but it was very moving to see that because of us people are united and uh less alone
it is very it is very moving yeah and it yeah it's very nice and it speaks to the
desperate state of this country honestly I I'm getting Malcolm X JFK I will see you in
dear lord and we didn't get shot either that yet not yet I uh popped into that and honestly felt
jealous of the group for being friends even though I had contributed to their friendship because
when I when I clicked off the phone I was just alone in an Airbnb in Atlanta no I'll be back I'll be
in style we're going to bin baby my favorite video game as a boy was toobin toobin's a great toobin's a great
video game so to see what old Jeff did to its good name is and toobin hard is hell yeah just like toobin
that's true it was a hard is hell yeah and wet yeah yeah yeah a lot of parallels just like tubes uh this
is anonymous as well it says I am here is a plus one and I don't know you hmm how would you describe
yourself in three words uh go fuck yourself those are my three words what is this fucking uh uh uh uh
vogue magazine or shit questioning what what what are we doing here it's I'm gonna quiz this
for the husband you know what I would say how would you say does that make any sense what I just said
I would say I'm not quite sure if it did I'm just kidding I how would you describe yourself in three words
brave uh no I mean I I don't know why we're talking to somebody who's just brought as a plus one
this is for the hellians this is for the hell you know I would describe myself as
love that queen I love that fucking queen goodbye England's rose right was that about her it was about
Prince Diana oh candle in the wind no it wasn't because it was written in the 70s but he made it
about Princess Diana yeah oh you're right it's about Marilyn Monroe who is coming to the screen and
that Netflix move NC 17 Marilyn Monroe move yes you want you want to see me jack off by the way
not for outrageous sexual content by the way language they said the sex stuff in it is not that crazy
I thought that is what it was that's supposedly what it is but uh what could it be
she came out what's her name do you mourness Anna de Armas she came out and she was like the sex
stuff in this isn't that insane I don't understand why we have been in this because she likes it so and
saying could be Christ see this he's fine afflex with jayla again they're they get married twice
they weren't married the first did jayla marry mark anthony and you sang to me you sang to me
that was on the blockbuster trailer tape mark anthony so I had to hear it billions of times he quoted
jeely in the vows did he really no he no he did I'm sure he never saw jeely what is what is a high
panic and your mom your mom has the in high sides hollywood scoop so I've never heard it from
anyone I've never heard this from anyone worked in hollywood 15 years but your mom yeah who calls
heroin hype has the inside scoop a afflex drug of choice is booze you can tell that by looking at
him when I look at affleck on the beach with the towel wrapped around his body stark so
because of your eyes I've never felt like a kid ship to a man in my life I met him at a party once
I met him at a party once yeah and I will say I met him at a party once and I will say second only
to Chris Hamsworth who I saw backstage at the MTV movie awards he is the best looking man I've
ever seen in my life affleck it was the best looking person wherever you backstage at the MTV
movie award Judd Apatow when Judd Apatow was making crashing with Pete yes he took
Pete and he was like you ring somebody and Pete brought me and we went with Judd Apatow to the MTV
movie awards and they were honoring the Avengers with some award and we went backstage and I was
standing two feet away from Chris Hamsworth and Scarlett Johansson and I couldn't stop looking at Chris
Hamsworth he was the best looking human being ever seen he looks like a god in real life he looks like
a god came down from the heavens all right it walks amongst us he doesn't need this he's fine these two
questions on this card or so disturbing I don't want to read either I want you to read him Pat
are you becoming your father you didn't want to hear that one
but let me hit you with the one he he just visited and if the answer is yes I'll kill myself in
front of all of you all right here's my question the answer is no yes here's my question Joe have
your platonic friendship has been fulfilling enough that you can make peace with dying alone
oh my god this is like this is like in a Batman movie when Commissioner Gordon is making a public
address and the riddler slips a question into it yeah yeah Pat do you ever worry that you're not
good enough I just start weeping um yeah let's not answer those questions Jeff B asks favorite movie with
your least favorite score music I know my answer mr. Walsh I have a feeling you'll agree on plans
trains that was my answer plans trains on bills is the best movie with the most 80s shit score for sure
good good good good honestly I don't we we review on the last episode we did today the live one
we reviewed jaws I gotta say I really hate that like bubbly
pie it is John William like like and it's odd the theme from jaws is so menacing and so amazing and
so incredible and so beautifully John Williams but then there are so many times when they go into
that flighty music and it takes me out of it for a second all right all right but comedies especially
and they date immediately comedies in the 80s and 90s felt like they had to have score over every
single moment and they makes them very hard to watch the comedy does not speak for itself lethal weapons
another great example awesome movie terrible score that's sacks yeah it's terrible yeah every
speaking of heroin every score back then with some guy on heroin playing a electric guitar note and then
somebody playing a saxophone at all sucked I remember my friend my my college roommate Mark Schneider
pointed that out to me we were really high and we were watching lethal weapon and he just turned
to me and he goes why does he got so much saxophone in it man and I was like it was like one of those
high bro which we're like yeah all you hear is a straight saxophone for the rest of the move
all right do you actually heard that movie was rated R for violence and sacks
this says again it's anonymous do you think that the HBO discovery situation
will have any negative impact on their service or will the
bean or will the bean counter app roach take over the industry I don't understand what this means
and is this the first sign of doom for HBO originals do you understand any of that
well yes the guy who owns Warner Bros is bearing bat girl in their other movies
which I don't give a shit I was not going to watch back girl anyway but it's going to be the one
other thing that had keyed in it is Batman again which makes me nervous that they you know they're
blowing the key Batman return well the question is asking like you know basically are we on the way
out as a industry absolutely yeah that's all we talk about on this show though everything's falling
apart I as I discussed in the last show they're doing an origin story for the when you wish upon a
star star Disney plus is making that movie an origin story for a star look it up it's happening
Ariana Du Boes from what west side story okay I mean that's where the star she's playing I think
the first person to be moved by the star Jesus I only want one story about people being moved
by a star and it's a story of Jesus Christ ladies and gentlemen
Mary the wise men Joseph I think there's a new video game now called I am Jesus Christ where you
play Jesus really yeah and you get to commit the miracles you get crucified of the end it's you
couldn't the trailer first person point of view Cruiser is it a religious game no Pat it's not a
religious game we played Jesus yeah of course what do you think it is sorry I didn't know they made
religious video games uh yeah no it's it's not like make it's not like comment yeah okay it's not
like making fun of it it's like yeah you're supposed to like get into like look I'm Christ and I'm on
the cross is what it would look like yes you're there all right probably won't uh play that game
would you marry a Russian girl very curious who asked this are you Russia are you from Russia yeah
huh oh hello Steve but are you okay with this question but are you from actual Russia oh okay
but you you live here you're married to Steve I was seeing if you traveled it okay
I see you got Steve a green cone okay uh I would I well I don't want to marry anybody that's
probably not going to happen but I would marry a Russian girl really I'm taking some time off
between I mean I'm sorry I'm sorry if I support Ukraine and I wouldn't do it all right I would marry
anyone regardless of national let me break it down for you people I'll fuck anything yes I don't
care where you're from earlier I said I was gonna fuck uh uh a lot of on a top or whatever she
was Russian Famke Jansen yeah I wouldn't say I would marry her you know I met her once but look
if a woman can crush you to death between her thighs I think we'll get the marriage pretty quick I
met Famke Jansen once and she was looking around the room for anybody else to speak to yeah
you get that a lot she was uh uh she was a big comedy fan because she was at all the with Trevor
and Zach the kids in the hall show so Trevor Moore who passed away RIP good friend I mean she was
Frick I Trevor with you but she was to come to the whitest kids you know shows when I was in New York
really and I knew Trevor and Zach pretty well Zach who also just directed this movie barbarian which
is supposed to be great I haven't seen it wait that's Zach from whitish man I didn't know that oh that's
very interesting thank you she was nice enough to me she wasn't you know what are you gonna do uh
hey guys other than anything by the gin blossoms what other 90 songs because you die happy if you never
heard again 90s so what 90s song do you never need to hear again also growing up
what were your family's fallback movies when the new release VHS was all out oh like what would
we watch when the new release yeah like your go -to I mean our go -to's were always you know Indiana Jones
and Star Wars I think right yeah we would watch Uncle Buck or fair usually something Johnny sure but
but what 90 songs could you ever go without hearing ever hear I'll be your dream I'll be your wish I'll be
your fantasy miss a girl fucking innocent guy and think that you need hey that's all but that that
doesn't count I'm sorry because there this person is asking like they're talking like the grungee 90s
rock band stuff what I don't know I think I when people say 90s you don't go boy band is that what
you're just singing that was the 90 that was the 90s a song is there what were you just singing boy band
savage garden of savage garden yeah I thought there was backstreet boy no I would love to hear and
there were early 2000s and I'd love to hear I know my number one I've hated it I've hated it from
the day I heard it yeah I'll hate it for the rest of my life I have become cumbersome in this world
what a shit song what a paint by numbers shit song that is I will say I banned the PTA opened for
seven Mary three who performed cumbersome but they're not very good and you have to pretend like
you thought it's good yeah oh you guys like cumbersome here is I have a couple more and they're also
pop songs the one is Hen has said right about breakfast that means she said I think I terrible song
what is this breakfast the Tiffany's oh yeah that song sucks and then the word also how about
that guitar solo barely qualifies as a guitar song then you have the other one that I hate
even more is dishwasher counting blue cars remember that song she works with that song
barely got a chorus what if God what if God no that song sucks what if he was though what if what if
she was one of us make she think come to my window yeah that sucks I'll be your Superman sucks if I go
crazy man where used to that's those two thousand oh it was again a lot of that songs from that
but I'll go I'll go I'll go popular ones I'll go ones that at one time were great I could never hear
spells like teen spirit again for the rest of my life I've heard it too many times I could never oh
fucking I like Pearl Jam Jeremy never play it with an earshot of me ever again for as long as I live
ever sound garden love him spoon man spoon man beat it yeah all right who would you say are your
biggest writing influences asks John W I gotta go John Hughes I mean John Hughes was adamant about
making every line funny but also in character the he made comedies that were funny throughout they
don't make him anymore right for for sure that would be my biggest because it was my earliest and
a continuous influence well for me stand up wise George Carolyn beyond anybody else and then
with script wise I'd have to say Larry David and Woody Allen because those are the two writers I
learned that you could not life influences but I think we're talking about family familial influences
what do you know but now Woody Allen and Larry neighbor with the two writers that I learned that you
could if you make the characters funny that's all that mattered you didn't need gags and things
like that like you mean characters interesting and funny that's true was it scoop was scoop the
turning point I love scoop I will not say a bad word about scoop I love the movie scoop made me
after I'll say a bunch of bad words about scoop this is you by the way what is it what is that you
just did oh pick one of the bad ones and make fun of it man has made classics I know you're gonna
pick one of the bangers he's also made a lot of shit okay well speaking of a lot of shit John
he's my last questions about the sopranos all right which by the way just yesterday a friend of mine said
hey Joe you know you're always bitching about the sopranos I go yeah he goes yeah I didn't agree with
you but I rewatched it recently and it doesn't hold up it's a fucking terrible show it's a terrible
show and one of the things he pointed out was he goes do you know how many times and there's
actually a term for this I don't know what it is he goes do you have many times they go I just went
very Trump sorry it's actually term for this no but he pointed out and I go you're right they do
do that he he's like they constantly do that dumb gag we're the Italian guys they said the wrong
word too much yeah so anyway here's the question Joe why do you not like the sopranos because it's
bad it's a stereotype in fucking full force that's all it is if that show was about any other by
the way I'm not offended you guys know you listen to show I'm not offended like oh my god it's a
stir I'm just telling you that show was about any other race of people it would be fucking discarded
okay by now that is a step -in -fetch it version of Italian people it is up there with fucking my
blue heaven okay with how bad it makes Italian people look well Steve Martin is playing him off
you also in that movie James Gandalfini is playing an Italian guy in the soprano so it makes a little
person is a perfect encapsulation of being an Italian American yes says Chris Longo Chris I'm sorry
that you think so low of Italian Americans I lived it too I I lived it too I what part where'd you
grow up Chris tell me where'd you grow up yeah you know how you know how you know how
it's a real depressing is known for its Italian American population you have a little Italy you guys
have a little Italy that's so interesting and unique who else has a little Italy besides every
city and town in the country Christ even the Statue of Liberty is snoring through that fucking
story cares I can't I can't if Joe's not gonna like the surprise or he's you know he's seen a
couple episodes whatever I don't I don't need to to get involved in this anymore I know I'm not asking
it too sure I'm not asking you too nobody's asking he's asking me to re -explain why I don't like
it so I'm gonna re -explain real quick I'm annoyed because this next one is just gonna wind you up
even more all right but let me just say I grew up I grew up in outside of Philadelphia
fucking Eastern PA South family in South Jersey I had uncles and family members this is just not
how they fucking talk it's not guys it's not it's how people who think Italian people talk right it's
like when they have a 45 year old man right a 12 year old girl character but you know he and you
go wasn't this isn't how this is how he wrote the show is very italic really well all right tell
that to the saints of Newark yeah the the one you've seen for some reason many do it's not your
experience that's fun you've got some weird thing here's what it is folks I'll answer David tell
David it's popular the Beatles the sopranos it's popular David tell say one time David tell say one time
the sopranos would be his favorite show when the red when the red red man and method man red man and
there's a perfect encapsulation what I'm gonna say then I'll shut up red man and method man and a TV
show and it was very bad and I'm a big fan of red man and method man but it's very bad and as
was how high the movie it was terrible and we're talking to David tell one night and David tell a
funny movie which I love it David tell said he goes you know what they do on these shows and it's
true this is what they do he goes a bunch of white guys write it and then they bring in younger black
guys to like black it up because the white guys don't know how to write for black characters because
they know nothing of the black experience so a white guy writes it and then they go to a young guy hey man
how would you say I gotta make a phone call and the black guy goes hey dog it's time to ring a
ding right and he goes and then they write it into the script and they think it sounds authentic and it
doesn't because this is a hodgepodge of whatever that's just how the sopranos feels to me feels like a
guy that doesn't really know the experience talking to other guys are going but how would you say it
and they say and he writes it in and then you have fucking four gabagool references every episode
that's my take on it that's my take on it thank you
and that's what I do I play to the common man the unsung heroes somebody signs of you and you
immediately call him the common man I'm not saying you stupid you're coming though
what while you're wound up what do you really think of Jason Blum a man who to me registers the same
as a glass of milk I have no opinion of him at all he's a producer he's talentless yeah yeah
that sums it up yeah yeah he's talentless so he should get into the background and shut the fuck up
instead of coming out on everything and talking for the movies that he doesn't make well I just
don't get how you come at this man like he fucked your wife can you name outside of don't you dare say
drum drum fill whatever the fuck it was called was the drum oh whiplash don't say whiplash
whiplash whiplash is amazing don't say whiplash and don't say get out can you tell me a good
Jason Blum move I'd have to look at a list but I don't care I'm not defending the man I understand
I don't know I'm gonna seek out this producers work I produce it drives me I get it take more
money than the writers and direct but it and it drives me and that's fine yes and most of the time
the producers are like dust and often and wag the dog where he's in the background and then
and then eventually he goes I'm tired of producing I getting a credit but they're in back in the
in the background Blum is not in the background Blum is out there yeah constantly running his mouth
about how good it is what they're doing how awesome he is da da da da da da da da da and he makes a bad
fucking product I don't know like you know like it's just they don't here's the other thing that bothers me
Blumhouse has become synonymous with modern horror you should call you an extent of special here's
the other thing that bothers me and then I walk I walk from place to place on the stage yeah and he's
another thing that bothers me it's spotlight and then you walk to it I don't like that he's in
the background hiding they put racism and he's another thing that bothers it's like a Billy Crystal show
yeah I'm sorry yeah it bothers me that he's synonymous from horror it bothers me that everybody
every time they talk about fucking modern horror they mention Jason Blum it bothers me he does not
deserve that position as far as I'm concerned his work is bad and it's bullshit it's it's it's it's
it's like how they make Tarantino synonymous with indie film in the 90s but Tarantino deserved it
he redefined a genre Jason Blum didn't redefine shit he puts out bad movie after bad fucking movie
but he's a marketing genius and because he's the richest guy in the room everybody says he's
fucking great that's what bothers me about it thank you common people hey that's it oh oh it's my
another Joe why do you hate I need a breath here Joe your mother dot dot dot I love my mother don't
just say nothing about my mother I'm Italian American I'm a little soprano I love my mother
she makes me more Tony soprano famously despised his mother despised her being funny are you
the uh god dare you uncle Joe yeah you're not gonna but you're gonna it's it's like a fucking Tim
Robinson sketch the soprano should be on I think you should leave you could cut you could cut scenes
from the sopranos into I think you should leave and you wouldn't know it wasn't part of the show
oh it's literally that sketch where he's going motorcycle oh my it's so dumb all right anyway sorry
anyway what's the movie you guys what's the movie you guys have revisited that you'd like to revisit
wait what's the movie you guys have revisited that you'd like to revisit and see
I think I meant to say I haven't revisited that you'd like to revisit and see if it has improved or
diminished in quality asks willy -pie with a very good drawing of the the it is yeah well go there thank
you will thank you so what's the movie you'd like to revisit and see if it's well pot or for making our
artwork this evening pot or shout out to pot or Joe and I for something a little different will
be placing magic markers in our asses and hovering over them to sign them later we thought what can
we give them there's a little more intimate than your average what they made the Metallica groupies
too oh no it was the word the rumor was that Metallica there were so many groupies that wanted to go
backstage to fuck the man that Metallica this was the this was the rumor groupies do better this was
the rumor that they groupie the way you had to get backstage was you had to put a drop stick in your
asshole and if the zilgen symbol wasn't sticking upwards you didn't get it but they wouldn't tell anybody
you just had to put a drop stick in your ass and then we go no no no yeah and it was just a
pie chance you got the zilgen logo facing upward that's the rumor I don't know if it's true man McCarty
told me this joke last night what do you call a Latino with three dicks Metallica you you pimping
this joke you told me it's actually anti -racist that's a good joke it is a good joke yeah shout out to
Matt McCarty great man wait so what movie would you revisit to see if it's gotten worse or
better would I revisit or have I revisited and it did get worse or better would you oh was it your
question oh was you well so that's what you see man yet you haven't revisited sorry I was drinking
oh sorry it was a little drunk nice room to drive down today last time we spoke to will he was
hopping out of the driver seat I said why did you drive you're not going to drink he goes oh space
it out here he is he's kidding remember his own question he's parked right out front
okay we got you well so what would you that's a good the ones I want to revisit I revisit like I
I rewatched Freddie got fingered which I would have considered one of the worst ways I've ever seen
it's not good and when I rewatched I was like bad but I have some respect for parts of it be grudging
respect for parts of it but but in terms of what like you know if I hate something I'm not going
to watch it again unless somebody tells me a million times it's amazing then I might go okay
I'll try it again and I'll usually feel the same way if I hated something when I was a kid if I
didn't get something when I was a kid and I didn't think it was cool when I watch it now it never
gets better almost never unless it was an adult movie I didn't get at the time okay I uh no I
I I've I've I've gone back to many things that uh that I liked to dislike as a child and uh change
my mind one way or the other um but yeah I'm trying to think of one that I this is the problem is
like most movies I loved throughout life I bought them yes and I keep rewatching them I'm trying
to think of something you know what I'll say this it's it's not it's not new it's not old uh
I mean it is new it's not old I would I want to rewatch Elvis in a few years and see if it's still
destroys me emotionally the way that it is I think I might have just been in a weird place with my
family yeah and it hit me in a certain way yeah but that's one where I honestly was like I don't
I think it's as good as I think it was but I'm not sure because it was my not hold up
you know my not hold up I didn't cry at almost nothing I'm proud of it I was on a date
I couldn't cry what if she didn't respect me anymore right
so Joe Joe why did you tell Pat to do what he did I have never and would never I'm moving past
that one uh are we ever gonna get the mid -summer rewatch you both promised to watch it again and
reconsider I lean as fuck no you don't want to watch the three -hour directors come
I it's as you all may or may not have noticed we tend to drink when we do this show
and sometimes things are said that we don't mean and that statement of I will rewatch mid -summer
and re -review it was my equivalent to saying but baby I love you
I will never fucking watch that movie okay I don't think honestly to go back to Will's question
hereditary was a movie that I was like maybe I've often thought because it was only five bucks
for the blue round Amazon maybe I should revisit it maybe I didn't catch something maybe I didn't
get it whatever that's one that I think I should revisit mid -summer's a tall order it's very long
mid -s I love them both no I know would you we talked at length about Florence Pugh last episode yes
we were both pronouncing it wrong I was saying Pugh Joe was saying Pugh which makes no sense
I thought it was Pugh it's Pugh about talk about how to say her name
oh no we did that that was the last episode we talked about that at length and you can
listen to it and it's don't worry darling I also made the mistake of calling it don't worry baby
I am glad though I missed all the don't worry darling drama we did get a statement from Olivia wild
about how she likes to run her set thank god for that yeah Alfred Hitchcock directed the greatest
movies of all time over the course of 50 years never once did we get a statement about how he likes
to run his set yeah wilds one and a half movies in official statement about how she likes to run
her set congrats Olivia between you and Shyla Buff you look like the fucking lunatic right now
that's quite a fucking feat it's true by the way just you see I am dating Olivia why
she the trailer for this new April Ferrara Shyla Buff movie no where he plays the Franciscan
Podropio whatever the fuck it's called what so yeah it plays a priest or something it's it
well it's a historic figure it's yeah it's a Podropio is like the one saint of I think the Baptist
church or something but uh able Ferrara did a movie and LeBuff stars in it so LeBuff if you've
noticed he's doing all these interviews now where he's saying he's converted to Catholicism he's
saying me making this movie made him convert to Catholicism it's probably how he got Coppola on
the right but that's how it I'm getting at yeah the movie itself and Ferrara you know he's he's the
indie king I mean he you know I didn't think it was gonna be high budget but it looks so low budget
yeah like I'm talking about like the audio is off and shit like that it's very hot the last I
heard of LeBuff he was shooting straight dogs at a car window and that was a year ago he was
dating that FKA twigs and she was like yeah we were dating and he would drive around shooting dogs
and then a year later he's arguing and I'm like look I don't think either of these people are
necessarily a a sound source you don't find a person named FKA twigs you're at her I would like
to call FKA twigs all that means is she used to be known as twigs if that's crazy I'm sorry
it means that one point her name was twigs is that weird wait what FKA formerly known as twigs
the audacity the audacity but it begs the question what is your name now FKA twigs
you can't just tell us what you used to be I hope the country sinks into the sea
it's it's coming it's coming what a shit house we live in all right what's your favorite
October fest beer I hate October fest beer so yeah I mean I love enjoying an October fest beer and
then going immediately to bed at 8 .35 pm they're just pumpkin -y and heavy and make me sad and tired
sure enough I don't have a favorite I like like a miller light I'm you know a papse I can't do
anything yeah fest is a word I don't care for sure it's not in my nature yeah awesome I love
them though that's the thing I love you don't want to like taste a leaf in your beer yeah yeah you
don't want to be picking pine cone chunks yeah out of your beer yeah I don't want a drink of beer that
I think like Ike about crane drink he was a cider man if there's anything I know about him it was a
thing are there any tropes and movies that totally turn you off from the film asks for a back
of millions that's a good one yeah any tropes I mean I hate I've started to hate narration
yeah narration often sucks and it's interesting because Corsese talked about how narration like
like people thought it was going to be what killed good fellows and made it not good but he was like
no no you don't get it right there's why and then it works yeah but he's right it's like there's so many
wasn't the narration one of the things in adaptation that they talked about was like with the mark
of a bad movie or whatever my my latest one is anybody I just hate anybody addressing camera yeah well
and sometimes that's narration too yeah I hate it when it's like a guy is walking up to the post office
and then he's like so there I was walking up to my post office and it's like hold on which you know
which at which episode of the sopranos are you referencing I knew the second I had the voice that was
gone but this is what this is one too me and Dan Soder talk about this me and Dan Soder talk about
this one the the freeze frame I bet you wonder how I got here yeah yeah yeah yeah that's one we like
oh god yeah I mean everything when I I've shown the couple friends over the past few years good
fellas for the first time and it doesn't hit like it used to because the movie every single aspect
that would have been ripped off a million times yeah like it's funny good fellas has become the
Dane Cook of movies everybody shit on Dane Cook everybody shit on Dane Cook but it was because so many
people ripped Dane off and did these terrible reinterpretations of him and then they were like I
hate what that guy does is like no no when he did it it was really funny and really good and then
all these people fucking Xerox it and it sucks so like like when he married a child it was cool
oh he didn't marry a child but then when I married oh stop it stop it has a man who's 10 full
years younger than Dane Cook you stop it but but it's like you know like like a lot of people see
good fellas now and they and they think of for instance below yeah which is a shameless fucking ripoff
yeah uh you know and if you watch below it's not it's fine whatever it's passable I guess but it's not good
but if you saw that first it would take good fellas yeah uh because it's got black Betty you know
yes yes also it's got that song folks
listen uh yeah so um do you okay yeah mine mine one now is and again it's why it's one of the things
I said I couldn't believe I loved Elvis so much because he does address camera at one point
it does everything annoying yeah but it's a good movie but it works it works but that fucking
I mean we talked about in the show that god damn basketball show that Will Ferrell and Adam
McCain don't speak to each other anymore that that they that they we the john c Riley basketball it's
like jazz or whatever it was like oh you go fuck your second I tuned out immediately that's when
I dropped out that's the ball so if anything is like jazz I'm out yeah all right did you have a topic
did you have a topic prepped in case no one had questions no absolutely not because they will always
have questions yeah everybody's got questions I am shocked at what you people want to know
I don't understand it I appreciate it thank you for your interest but I don't get it
the people were asking those questions after the first show today I was like what
I know uh but god bless you you asked me how big is my dick on stage and everybody chuckles you asked
me later weird weird uh but go ahead and ask I'm honestly more apt to answer are you out this is the
last one I have one more if you were a movie character how big would your penis who who would
you be so I don't know that means who would you want to be or who are you most like who asked this
question do you mean who would we want to be or who would we be well you got to interpret it
that's good which movie character are you at your core I know it a hundred whether you wanted or not
I know what a hundred percent all right I want to be I want to be Han Solo
I want to be and you know what I'm a little more like Han Solo than you realize
you'd have to be I drive a cool car I lie a lot yeah I have a tendency to call women honey
and sweetheart yeah do women like to be called honey and sweetheart by Harrison Ford just across the
board now but when a waitress calls me honey I I love it it's different that's more like a what's
happening vibe yeah you know that's more like a surely him full all right whenever you need sugar
yeah when a guy does it it's feel sexist and degrading but it ladies I don't mean oh do you have
honey if it was like I mean like oh honey could you hand me that you don't like that either but I'm
just saying if it was if it was if it was Harrison Ford would it bother you if Harrison Ford pulled if
you were waiting for your Uber outside and Harrison Ford pulled up and through the door when he goes
get in sweetheart you'd fucking love it you'd love it you might
oh please 82 year old Harrison Ford is 38 year old regular man
you're in sweetheart get in my cab
I'd get in oh yeah I want to be but who am I actually I'm fucking I'm fucking it's
I said it early I'm Larry David I'm Woody Allen that's that's who I am I think I might be
sometimes who knows but that's who I know that that's who I am my my my core I would say like you
know Pete told me the other day that I he told Jason Alexander he invited Jason Alexander to
dinner with me and this is I told Pete Pete the only time this has ever worked out in the history of
time bringing a surprise guest to dinner is when you and I met when Pete brought us both to dinner yes
otherwise I would rather leave yeah I hate when people bring a surprise guest to dinner so excited
about a Jason Alexander well me and Pete were having dinner and he goes you know I invited Jason
Alexander he had him on his podcast and I was like thank God I wasn't meeting my friend for dinner
and Jason Alexander shows up I have anxiety issue and that's and that's the thing I'm a fan of
Jason Alexander you're not getting George no you want George pretentious I've heard very well you're
not getting George you you want Alexander to come in and be like can you believe this valet right
ask me for a tip or whatever you're not getting that you're gonna get regular Jason Alexander well Pete
said he told Jason Alexander that he is having dinner with his friend is he got to meet this guy
and he raved about me and I want to but he said he really is Jerry Seinfeld meets George
and I was offended at first but then I was like no I love that right that sounds right to me that feels
right to me but characters I've related to Nicholas cage and adaptation for sure whenever I try to
write and I hate myself you know yeah like you have your cool version of yourself like you say I'm
Ryan Gosling and drive or whatever but that's your core you're not you know and if I wore that jacket
you'd be like look at this fucking idiot who does he think it is and I don't mean I'm wearing the
drive jacket in a world where drive exists yeah I mean I'm wearing a drive you walk in you walk in
you look like the divorcee with the you know oh yeah too much hair products oh wow that's
going white jacket divorce interesting hey sup yeah yeah yeah yeah so I actually remember I actually
know the movie character I made identical to yes we like it or not I am especially I want to be
Indiana Jones I am Paul Giamatti an American splendor a thousand in the
America splendor and not sideways both yeah both the only difference is I'd never would have gotten
married and that's what separates me from his character in sideways but him in American splendor
marry her doesn't he was married and he's oh yeah oh yeah oh he's divorced the love him in
American splendor when I saw I had friends that saw American splendor and called me and go have
you seen this movie because I think it's about you and I was like fuck you I was so mad and then I
watched it and within the first 45 seconds when the kid marches away from the house at Halloween
and he goes watch everybody got to be so stupid I was like oh Jesus you know when I relate to
that movie is when he looks in the mirror and he goes there is a reliable disappointment oh yeah
I was like whoa the whole thing yeah the whole fucking thing I've had that experience a few times where
I got hit pretty hard by a movie for sure you know what even though I don't like the man we almost
did for this episode 10 the 10 movies that made you cry we'll probably do that on a future episode
but 127 hours was one where I had to run away from my friends because I was sobbing I don't I still
don't really understand it but he's trapped in the rock and I the point of the movie in the end
is really that if he had told anyone where he was going or communicated with anyone in his life his
girlfriend his mom his anything he'd be fine and then at the end they kind of flash and show you all
those people that he did not talk to as he's dying whenever some reason it just knocked the shit out
he lives isn't he lives yes but I related to that I relate to people who who was James Franco
in this film who wish to connect but cannot okay I guess about Schmidt was a big one for me
well don't ruin it we're gonna do the episode yeah but I just mean like that's another movie
by the guy who wants to connect but can't sure that's something that always see okay I see what
you're saying are we out or you got one more there last one ready yes it better be good if it's
not good we need another question again and this is a good I'll decide it's to it's a question
directed at each of us you know two separate questions Joe did you know you were coming back
for the final season of Better Call Saul post your line about wanting out no I didn't know
I never know season to season I never knew when if they were going to bring me back or not
because that's how not famous or important I am so the story of the show
a lot of people watch and they go look at that you're you're really a part of it look at that I go
uh they they would say good job we'll see you later and then that was it there was no worry on
their part about what if we what if he's working and we can't get him back well like it'll be
we'll get him it'll be fine if you joderosa the character we're not on that show it would have
not changed the trajectory of the show in any way that's not true at all I don't remember you
doing anything I delivered I love I delivered the black book to Bob Oden Kirk you cock sucker
I'm the whole fucking show what is the black book the fucking book that he gives it all through
fucking breaking bad I am the fucking universe you bitch now you've seen how many episodes of
breaking bad don't need to say it I love the passion from man who's never seen the show by the way
that might not have helped my recurrence when I told Peter golden v. school at Gilligan on
in podcasts that I've never watched breaking bad yeah but I appreciated them having me in better
console they might have liked that they actually laughed they were like that's hilarious that's like
I go what's it matter this guy wouldn't know anything happening on that show they were like yeah you're
right well you do the denaro thing you you worked as a vet for about a year right yeah I would yeah
I would come in with dog bites on my hands I think very method the last time I heard of him doing
that was when he he was with an undercover as a knife salesman when he was in the fan for the fan
and that was the end of the rest I'm sure somebody was like Bobby you can't do this for a movie like
the fan you can't work at a knife that's exactly what I was referring to yeah yeah they're like
Wesley said she's playing a baseball player yeah and he's not even practicing baseball no he's
still right yes supporting character he's stoned sword fighting a member of the IRS
high out of his mind you do not need to work for a year as a knife salesman for the fan one of the
dumbest movies ever made RIP Tony Scott RIP Tony Scott it's a bummer that movie sucks that movie should
have been cool it's just not yeah all right last question and then this this one's to you Pat what
band would you do a sparks bro ask doc about these are both from Chris St.
St. Sam Lee saucy good right good night good night Chris St. saucy good night got it okay
which which band would you do a sparks bros as doc about it's a great question
and I yeah I wouldn't be the you know what I am gonna let's close the show with the gym blossom
because they have a fascinating story their guitarist killed himself and the band continued
even though he wrote all their most successful so it's a very dark to smart move yeah well no they
threw him out of the band for his drinking and then he killed himself that's a terrible story yeah
but my point is yeah you got a hitmaker yeah let him drink couldn't agree more he threw him out
of the band then he's gone and then and then you just keep going and then he killed himself yeah this
is like when you know you go to see like a yellow and it's just the drummer yeah and it's like
the Pete Franklin ELO experience you're like oh like the ringo star does a show where he has like
we've got the Glockenspeelist from Jeep trick we've got the mandolinist from you know
yeah it's just a little more collection of people yeah you're gonna see a Jeep trick concert it's just
the fat drummer with the cigarette yeah it's just that guy yeah yeah Bonnie Carlos yes
folks buddy thank you so much for coming out tonight we are heading directly over to the after party
come join us at Joey Roses for all my fun we're gonna go drink thank you for being here everybody
we'll see you next time and we'll see you in hell