It's the bonus episode for our Patryon listeners, folks.
How are you?
It's me, Patrick Walsh, with me pouring an icy cold waters, Joe Derosa, it's your bonus
set.
A little more relaxed.
We're not trying to force our agenda down your throats.
It's just a couple of guys chatting it up.
Now that being said, today's topic is abortion.
I'll be taking the pro, Joe will be taking the con.
Just for fun, just to see how it goes.
No we're doing a Q and A app today, those are always fun, give us a lot to chew on.
You guys have your questions.
We've got our answers.
I'm just going to hop right into it.
Do we have a lot of questions tonight?
We've got a ton already.
All right, then let's just, let's just hit it.
Let's just pat it in.
It's good to see you.
I usually don't like to get right down to business.
I like to wine and dine you a little bit first, but it sounds like we need to get straight
to the fucking tonight.
I mean, there's tons of questions here.
I want people to be happy, you know.
So do I.
God damn it.
Ken Hanley asks, what is the most underrated sequel of all time?
A terrific question to kick things off.
Hello to you, Ken.
Are you Ken?
Well, underrated sequel of all time, I'm going to go with Blade 2 is up there.
I feel like for some reason, Blade 1 always gets way more love than Blade 2.
And I think Blade 2 is far superior film.
Blade 2 is a better film, but Blade 1 is very cool.
We'll talk about them both in the show.
Can I tell you I spent a big part of today pitching jokes because David Allen Greer
we learn has been secretly writing his character on the cool kids, the Fox show I'm working
on.
We learn that he has been writing a book about Blade, but erotic.
It's about an erotic blade.
And then they walk in and I'm composing the theme song to it and they're like, you're writing
the theme song to a book and he's like, it's going to play when you open it like one of those
greeting cards.
We were really laughing.
I don't know how much of it will make it into the final show.
I hope a lot, but that's very funny.
Yeah, Blade blade the erotic journey kind of kind of vibe.
Most underrated sequel, I don't know, I feel like all the ones that are good are not underrated.
I'm not going to say Godfather to I got a perfect one that you will both agree on.
All right.
And it gets dismissed all the time and he'd gone two and a half.
That's my choice.
It's a grand slam movie arc.
It might be funnier than the first movie.
I do think two and a half joke for joke is funnier than the first movie.
People shit on it.
They're like, yeah, two is okay.
I'm like, what are you talking about?
Two and a half is amazing.
And while we're at it, hot shots part doing bad.
I prefer part two to part one.
They are a prefer one to do, but I love them both.
All right.
You know what?
If we're talking a respectable continuation of a comedy, I'm going to shout out Home Alone too.
Lost in New York.
I've always enjoyed Home Alone too.
Traps are bigger and crazier.
It's a different kind of vibe, but I like them.
That's the owner of the poster said that bigger traps bigger city.
It's shut.
Yeah.
You got your bigger trap and get inside.
I had a talk boy when I was a child.
What's a talk boy?
It's the little machine that Kevin carries throughout the movie and it records voices and plays them
back and all that.
The one you got for Christmas, let's say, was much shittier, but you don't remember the
talk boy.
It factors into most scenes of Home Alone too.
It's like what he uses instead of the movie, right?
Yeah.
It's a toy that was invented to sell toys.
Yeah, I forget.
But anyway, it's a great toy.
Next question.
Julie Aguirre asks, what are your thoughts on sleep away camp?
I just watched it for the first time and I need the opinions of those I trust.
This weirdly got a mention a couple weeks back.
It may not have aired yet, but I love sleep away camp.
I watched it with a girl I was trying to get freaky with in the New Jersey area when I lived
out there.
And I got to tell you folks, the movie was a lot more successful than my attempts.
That's a tough date movie.
I mean, you got to cook the train.
You picked it, bang kids in it and stuff.
There's some dark stuff.
I like sleep away camp.
I thought it was fun.
If you don't know the ending to sleep away camp, we're not going to spoil it.
Go watch it now.
It's one of the great endings of horror in my opinion.
Great practical effects in the film.
Yes.
It's a lot of fun in that movie.
What's the next one?
I'm a big fan.
Anthony Minito asks, do you reheat pizza in the oven or stove top?
I'm more of an oven kind of guy, but I hear stove top has its advantages.
Please don't say microwave.
Well, again, these questions are really supposed to pertain to the show itself.
Don't have to.
And to harm.
I never saw that actually.
You've said that in the past many times.
Not on this one.
I left it open.
You left it open.
That's why there's so many questions.
Do you remember to be asking us how to do their damn taxes on this?
I reheat pizza in the oven.
Never the microwave.
I don't think I've ever reheated anything in the oven.
I don't do a lot of cooking of any kind at home, but if I were to reheat pizza, it'd be going
on that microwave.
I'm sorry.
You're a disgrace.
Sorry.
I don't often have pizza.
I usually eat it cold if I do have it.
I do like cold pizza.
Big fan, especially in the morning.
Jake McAlvane asked, are we missing anything during the music cuts?
I didn't even know there were music cuts.
The answer is no.
I don't think so.
Yeah, I don't think so.
I don't think we're being heavily edited.
No.
Will Potorf says, I know you guys aren't huge into animation, but what's your favorite all -time
animated feature, Joseph?
I'm going to go with the Lord of the Rings animated feature.
I really, really enjoy that film.
And I really like the Hobbit one, too.
They're just a lot of fun.
They're dark.
They're creepy.
The second one has that weird, I forget what it's called, but that like animation where they
draw on top of real people, those two are, I think those are the only two animated things
I even own, aside from the entire series of Tales from the Cryptkeeper, which is terrible.
I just have it as a completionist.
I'm going to say Lion King's Pretty Great, Beauty and the Beast, Pretty Great, Pixar, I go
Toy Story 3, Non -Disney, I go Rats and Nim, Secret of Nim.
Oh, I love the Secret of Nim.
Pretty awesome.
And then Adult, I'd go South Park, I mean, that's a pretty awesome comedy and musical.
It's great.
Ken Hanley says, please invite Sean and Hayes as guests for the live show.
Hollywood Handbook, we'll see you in Hell Cross over, needs to happen.
Wow.
Couldn't agree more of those guys are hilarious.
Were you just talking about?
Friends of mine.
I was talking about them.
I did their new podcast, Sean and Ben, Stitcher Premium, a plug, and I were not allowed.
And maybe we'll have half of them on our show as they've had half of us on their show.
No, they are funny guys.
I love them.
Cool.
Will Potter, also, I said it in a limited to one question, but I will be cutting off your questions.
Favorite John Claude Van Dam film?
Why are you getting Will's ass?
You didn't deserve that Will.
I'm just hoping it's not a lot of doubles on here.
I thought you guys would be a little more respectful than that.
You know, you're getting pizza questions.
I told you, you can't, you can't leave it wide open.
I'm kidding.
You're favorite John Claude Van Dam, I mean, I think
the man made no great movies, and he made one, like if Steven Seagull's good movie is
under siege, I guess you got to say Van Dam's is probably time -com.
Well, Van Dam, ever all the true, like, die -hard Van Dam fans always say blood sport.
Yeah.
Blood sport is extremely fun.
What's the second one?
Blood sport, too?
No, no, no.
The second Van Dam movie.
Kickboxer?
Yeah.
People, I think those are the, I, I never liked Van Dam movies.
I'm going to go with expendables, too.
I enjoyed seeing him as a bad guy, and watching him in Stallone go at it, the end was awesome.
Blood sport is genuinely funny, and that J -C -V -D that everybody raved about was very overrated.
Yeah, of course.
What is, oh, this doesn't stir up trouble.
Meredith McWilliams asked, what is Pat's least favorite thing about Joe and vice versa?
I mean, have at it.
I don't have anything on the top of my head, which is good.
That is good.
What do you got?
What do you hate about nature?
The smell is bothers me.
Stop.
Nothing.
I can't think anything.
You make me smile.
I used to not like it when you would scream, do shots in my face, but you stopped doing that.
I used to get mad at you for being really late all the time, and you know, you're much better at that.
We haven't been mad at each other in a long time.
It's true.
The marriage works.
When it works, it works.
Brittney Ferguson says, you guys get enough movie questions, so Joe, how's the dating life going?
I miss you talking about it on emotional hangs, and Pat, how is the married life treating you?
Marry life treating me good, Joe.
Dating life is treating me good.
You know, when you're dating, you can't really get into details, because then it sounds like you're a guy that, you know, I eat the kiss and tell guy or whatever.
But it's going very well.
You've got the feel yet of myself.
Tell me more, tell me more.
Pat and I often do hang out on bleachers in high school baseball fields.
Yeah.
Hey, we're the same age.
John Travolta was in that movie.
And we sing.
Yeah.
When we're on those bleachers.
No, yeah, it's going very well.
Thank you for asking.
I didn't, but I'll pass the message along.
No, not you, her.
I'll pass the message along.
You heard me.
Richard Olmo.
Richard James Olmo asks, what would you guys choose as a profession if you couldn't be comedians or writers?
I sound like a guidance counselor.
Don't I?
I know mine immediately.
What would it be?
I'd work in a, I swear to God, if I, if I, if I even had the chance to do this, I might walk away from everything.
I'd run a, I'd run a video game store, retro gaming store.
You can do that.
Or well, you got the money to open the store.
Sure.
What do I look like, fucking daddy war bucks over here?
Maybe you get a deal.
That's, that's what I would be truly happy doing.
Or a music store.
Yeah, I'd love to work at a music store.
Or not, and I'm not any money in it.
But I would, I would want to work in marketing advertising.
I've often said, I think I could rise to the top of the advertising world in one week.
It's a little disrespectful of anybody that works in the advertising field.
Much like Michael J. Fox and the secret of my success.
Actually, let me change it.
When I see posters, billboards, ads, I'm like, I could, I could run this town.
Let me, I'm choosing not to.
Change my answer.
I would like to do the secret of my success.
Okay.
I'd like to work in a mail room and then double as an anonymous executive.
Yeah.
And live a dual life in the same building.
I'd like to do that.
It's a lot of running back and forth.
There's still time to do that.
Andy Mendez asks, think there's a possibility of a live NYC show.
Also, there's a bar in bed style.
You guys talked about once and I can't remember the name of it, but I want to check it out.
Oh, Andy, I remember the name of it, baby.
Do or dive is the name of that bar.
And the reason we spoke about it was because the bartender, this has never happened to me ever.
He recognized my voice and said, are you Joe from it?
We'll see you in hell.
And I said, yes.
And then I took a video of him saying, let's get on with the Joe and I said it to Pat.
But the man was he was spirited.
Let's put it that way.
But that's a great bar.
Do or dive in bed style.
Go there.
It's so fucking fun.
And drinks are surprisingly affordable because even a dive bar in New York or LA will tend to overcharge.
But that's a great spot.
And yes, there's 100 % chance for a New York live show.
We just have to get the, we have to, we're doing these early ones near us relatively close to where we live.
And then we'll start, the radius will get wider as we see if they're successful or not.
All right.
Jason, why bail if you could live anywhere in the world, where would it be and why?
What are we on the dating game?
You could make whoopee in any city in the world.
When she makes whoopee, she also makes noise.
Like, she's queuing.
No, it's just that's like the thing they would say, you know, they would do those dumb setups.
When she makes whiffies, she also makes noise.
Are you allowed Larry or a silent Sandy?
You know what I mean?
Right.
You ever see the clip in the butt, Bob?
Yeah, on the, on the merit, newlywit.
Where's your favorite place to do it?
And she was in the butt, Bob.
It's a wild wild wild wild.
All right.
And I would answer.
Yeah.
I guess I would live.
He didn't ask for us to talk about the newlywed game.
I don't know that I'd be happier anywhere else.
I mean, even the LA has so many problems, and yet I have to live here to work here.
This is where my work is here in New York, and I can't live in New York anymore.
So not because they chased me out or something.
I just don't like it anymore.
I guess I'll stay in LA.
At some point, I would love to have a house in Kauai.
I think Kauai is very beautiful and Hawaii.
The last place I hope I end up living is LA.
There are many places I would like to live.
Ultimately, though, in a dream world for me, I'd probably want to live in Philadelphia, to be honest with you.
Or I often think of Denver.
I like Denver quite a bit.
But I'd like to live somewhere where you get a little mountain air,
get a little clean air, but you're also not in the middle of nowhere.
You know what I mean?
I do.
But I'm here for now, and this guy next to me makes it an easy task, baby.
Oh, Joe.
Are you glad you didn't move when you wanted to move a few months ago?
Yeah, I don't think...
I finally came to the realization the answer is not going back to New York.
Right.
I love New York, and I miss it, and I love spending time there.
But I know that that's...
You get that t -shirt, that great t -shirt.
I love New York.
Yeah, the heart.
I've never seen one of those before.
I thought that was a pretty unique little shirt to me.
Nick Motley asked, Joe, I was wondering if or when emotional hangs may make a return.
And if it isn't returning, will you be edging out your place as Patrick's future child's godfather?
Pat, could you talk about the chicken?
Ken Hamley says, oh, he'll be edging all right.
The chicken?
I think it means the Pete Holmes chicken.
Oh, well, I mean, I did it on the...
You made a weird podcast.
But the chicken is...
You know, it was a voice that we went into to cope with a rough work situation.
Okay.
And the catchphrase was not feeling it.
Oh, that's right.
I saw the t -shirt to that.
Yeah, Pete made a lot of money off t -shirts.
And since we know he's not a paying Patreon member, I'll tell you folks,
Patty never saw a dime.
I see him up with that catchphrase.
Came up with that chicken.
Pete was certainly there and used to do it with me.
But he goes, hey, can I put this on the website, sell it as a shirt,
and I'll give you half the money.
I said, it sounds great.
And here we sit.
Moths flying out of my pocket.
That is a sore spot for old Patty over here.
Which is why I just set it up to see if he would go into it or not.
I gave him an out.
Happy to.
Happy to do.
Will emotional hangs returned possibly.
Curt and I have talked about potentially doing some update episodes
to kind of tie up some of the story lines that were going on in our lives at the time that we ended.
So it's possible.
I don't know yet.
Bill Burr and I.
Bill Burr and his wife, Nia and I just started relaunched an old podcast.
Bill and I used to do called uninformed.
So between that show and doing this show, I don't know how much time we'll have for podcasting.
But you and Bird on a podcast.
We used to do one and we just relaunched it, but we're only doing two episodes a month.
So and it's only going to be on his Patreon.
So it's like, it's a pretty low pressure thing.
Right.
But but still, you know, cutting you in on the money.
Yes, of course.
What would you do?
Yeah, of course he is.
I'm over it.
I'm a person catching on the money.
Christian Reynolds says favorite David Lynch movie.
If any, for me, it's kind of an even tie between Blue Velvet and Mahal and Drive.
I really love them both.
Drive all the way from me.
Yeah, sure.
Mahal and Drive all the way.
I see that.
But then every time I go back to Blue Velvet, I'm like, fuck.
It's really fucking good.
Do you know this?
There's a little fun movie trivia.
The lady that plays the nun.
Yeah, you see that nun.
Conjuring spin off.
Very scary looking.
You see that nun?
Yeah, I'll see it.
All right.
And we'll do it on the show.
She's the lady that plays the man behind the dumpster.
Really?
Yeah.
Interesting.
Yeah, she's, she's, she's an intense lady, man.
I'm sure.
They dress her up.
She's, because that nun's fucking scary looking too.
I haven't even seen a trailer for the nun.
It looks kind of cool because I think it takes place in like the 1800s.
Oh, that's cool.
Like it a castle somewhere.
I don't understand how time works.
It could be the 1500s.
1800s.
Or it could just be 1930.
Yeah.
It's set in the present day.
But there's, there's a castle with torches.
It looks old.
All right.
Let's go, I think Karen wants to say it.
Let's go see some nun.
You all see it.
I love me some nun.
Jose Gabriel Rodriguez says this question is for Joe.
Did you play God of war yet?
And what are your thoughts?
And are you excited for Nintendo's new streaming service?
Nintendo direct.
I'm very excited for Nintendo's new streaming service.
I think it's supposed to launch in the fall.
I think.
I actually need to read up on that.
I'm, I'm actually surprised.
I don't, I'm not a little more readily knowledgeable about when that's happening.
But yeah, I am excited for that.
And no, I did not play the new God of War.
I didn't, I'm not against playing it.
I wasn't super excited that they turned it into more of an open world kind of thing.
I really like the, the sort of directed levels of the original games.
That being said, the graphics and the new one are amazing.
And I probably shouldn't let something stupid like open world stop me from doing it.
But I've just never been a big open world guy.
I get really distracted.
And then I forget what I'm supposed to be doing.
And I also for some reason get dizzy playing open world games.
That new spider man game looks amazing.
And I'm like, I'm going to get fucking sick playing this.
Swinging all around that damn city.
You know, I don't, I don't follow video games.
Heath Keen asks, what scary movie has had the biggest impact on your life?
Impact on my life.
Mine's nightmare on Elm Street, but I've talked about that a million times out here.
Yeah, I mean, probably Poltergeist.
That was like the only horror movie I watched for many years.
And I still absolutely love it.
And a recent one that had an impact on me socially,
not that it changed me or something,
but I just thought really was very well done and well said was get out.
I love with that movie had to say and I think about it often.
It's a great flick.
Luke Physioc asks, what is the most trouble you got in prior to 25 years old?
I mean, I got arrested for a curfew violation when I was 13 or something like that.
Sneaking out to the quick trip to get snacks took me to the station.
It's the only real trouble I was in for many, many years.
I got caught stealing when I was 13 or 14.
You like Jane's addiction?
No.
Never got into that shit.
But three days, man.
What's three days?
It's that fucking song they have.
Well, I thought Jane says was the song they have.
Well, that's like their, you know, stream hit.
Yeah.
Three days is the one that all the fans are always like, dude, man.
They close with three days went on for three days.
I'm not into them.
I don't like his voice.
I don't like the vibe.
The first acting job I ever did was with Dave Navarro.
He seems nice.
He was really nice.
He was really nice and very funny.
It was, it was an improv thing that we had to do in the scene.
And he was fucking funny.
I was like, yeah, that's nice surprise.
He came to Conan when I was there and he was very nice.
The, uh, he still does Lala Pulusa, Perry Farrell?
I think, dude, I didn't even know that fucking thing was still going.
And then like a week ago, I saw an ad for it.
Yeah.
Not anyway.
Not a fact.
You know, they did the entourage theme song.
Oh, yeah.
Could anything be less Jane's addiction than entourage?
I know.
Oh, my God.
Crazy.
That song.
That show.
Watched every episode.
I wasn't crazy about porno for pyros either.
No.
I liked them better than Jane's addiction.
Not my thing.
I did like that song.
Oh, yeah.
That's a hishin moan.
I like that song.
Edmund Agabbo asks, Joe, have you played Breath of the Wild?
Yes.
Pat, have you ever thought about adapting the video game tuban for the big screen?
Follow up question.
Why not?
Very valid question because I think tuban would be an awesome movie.
But I would now have to give you some sort of credit.
So I probably won't do it.
There you go.
But if you if you made tuban into a movie,
it'd have to be like some government conspiracy story.
Like when they remember when they made battleship and suddenly it was like aliens.
It was like, what the fuck is going on?
Yeah.
All right.
Mike Madrigal.
Do either of you have a particular horror novel, short story,
or comic that you would like to see adapted into a film?
Good question.
I desperately want to see a good adaptation of the man in the black suit by Stephen King.
I don't think it could really stretch into a movie.
But I think it could make a pretty killer, you know, like 45 to 55 -minute episode
of like a master's of horror or something like that.
It would just be so good.
It's such a great story.
It's so creepy.
And the only people that have adapted it were like the people like when King did that thing where he's like,
if you pay me a dollar, you can just make one of my things if you want.
Like those people did and some of them are okay.
But I would really like to see like a really like nice budget,
nicely budgeted version of that.
Okay.
I would say any one of the stories from 13 scary stories to tell in the dark,
which was a young adult scary story collection.
I read when I was a kid and I loved it.
You just mean scary stories to tell in the dark, right?
Maybe it's maybe so.
Well, Guillermo del Toro, they just started shooting last week.
They're making a movie of it.
Awesome.
So you're in luck.
I got what I wanted.
Works out for Pat.
I'm still a shit's creek over here.
Have you seen the show shit's creek?
Yeah, it's pretty funny.
I mean, it's not great, but it's got its moments.
Yeah, I'll watch those two do anything.
I watched the pilot and I liked it.
I'm going to continue out here because it's better.
I think his son really hits a home run at the show.
Yeah, he's funny.
Yeah.
Melissa Jorkowski asks, for both of you,
if you could join any family from a TV sitcom any decade,
which one would you join and why?
I mean, these are just easy questions tonight.
Go for it.
If it has to be literal family, like blood related,
Frazier, 110%.
Okay.
That'd be fun.
If it can just be a figurative family,
Golden Girls all the way.
Wouldn't you kill to live in that damn house?
Yeah, that was going to be my answer.
I mean, there's two family members there.
So maybe that's enough.
Yeah.
Yeah, it would be hard to argue with Golden Girls.
Otherwise, I would say
you know, news radio seems like it would have been a lot of fun.
A lot of fun.
That's not a real family either.
So who knows?
Alves family.
The worst, the worst of all the family.
The creepy dad.
Yeah.
Mom with all that rouge.
And then I guess that was the annoying neighbor who played Jerry's mom,
right?
Jerry's mom was the annoying neighbor.
Jerry Seinfeld's mom.
All right.
I don't even remember.
Dude, even as a kid, I wasn't feeling out.
I absolutely loved Alves.
Heath Keane asks, what was your most awkward sexual experience?
Meredith says the answer is Alves.
Obviously, we were just talking about Alves.
And I did have sex with Alves.
Yeah.
Most awkward sexual experience.
Geez.
A little personal.
You're not going with you fucking the Alves mouth?
Was that a sexual experience?
I don't know what else you would describe.
For me, more than Alves, I guess.
I don't know.
I'll just say Alves.
Why did I dig myself any deeper into this hole?
Nothing I would consider mortifying.
I mean, I got to tell you, they've all been pretty cherry pie for me.
Yeah, I didn't hear any complaints.
I don't know.
Awkward sex.
I have no idea.
You know, the trash you bring back here, you've had some, I'll dare you.
Rough nights.
How dare you?
Just don't lie to them.
Treat them with a little bit of respect.
Come on, stop it.
Don't say, tell them you're joking right now.
I'm joking, right?
People don't know in this day and age what's a joke anymore.
You can bring trash back.
They're not a crime.
You can bring trash.
Do you understand they might be listening?
Jerome Kincaid asks if you could remake any movie or TV show,
what would it be and why?
I think we've had this before,
and I probably didn't have a good answer then,
but I mean, movies, I guess it had to be one that was kind of a mistake.
You know, like one that should have been great and wasn't,
because why would you want to remake a great movie?
Wait, the question was movie or TV show?
Movie or TV show.
I have a great answer.
And we talked about it.
This will actually come out before we talk about it on the podcast,
but on one of the upcoming movie corners,
I talk about a movie called Evil Speak that I just watched with Clint Howard.
And as I was watching it, I was like,
this would be an awesome, awesome movie to remake,
because there's so much great stuff here,
and you could trim so much of the fat,
and you could just punch it up in places,
and this would be what a great premise for a movie.
That would be the one I'd pick this week, I guess.
Okay, there I know.
Yeah.
And I guess I'm going to say this Ryan Reynolds stoner version of Home Alone,
which doesn't sound bad at all.
What?
Ryan Reynolds is making a home alone
reboot where it's a stoner who's home alone.
It sounds bad.
And does he play the stoner?
That's undecided.
I got confused for a second with Ryan Gosling,
and I was like, oh, he almost looks like an old Macaulay Culkin.
That sounds like a sketch to me.
I mean, if Gosling was starring, I would be a lot more intrigued,
but who knows?
Maybe it'll be funny.
Try to be optimistic.
Nick James asked Pat,
would you ever consider writing a horror sci -fi film or TV series?
Absolutely.
I would only do horror.
I hate sci -fi terminology, and I'm bad at it,
so I would not be good at that.
Emily Marvel asks, have you watched many horror musicals?
If so, what's your favorite?
I barely know of any except Geno the...
What does that call?
Rebo the genetic opera.
Although I prefer Geno the pathetic opera.
Horror movie musicals?
The only one...
Well, you know, horror.
I like Rocky Horror.
The original...
I own Fam of the Paradise, I've never seen it.
Fam of the Paradise is awesome.
Never seen it.
That would be my vote.
But the Wicker Man, the original Wicker Man is sort of a musical.
There's some tunes.
Well, a little shot of a horror is a must count.
That's my favorite by far.
Amazing movie.
I put...
I'm going to put Fam of the Paradise over...
Little Shot.
Alright, I'm going to watch that.
Kevin Rogatti says, drink of choice.
Don't say a little ditty about Jack and Diet.
That is my drink of choice.
Don't tell me what to say.
Jump.
These days screwdrivers.
I don't know what it is, but I just enjoy screwdrivers lately.
He went that shitty orange juice.
What shitty orange juice?
They use shitty orange juice in bars.
Tasted a wonderful last night.
Alright.
But that's what I've enjoyed lately.
Can I answer it my way?
Sorry, I don't have a fucking plan words to do with it.
Be Ron.
Have you ever seen a short masterpiece called Boba Curia?
Not horror or just amazing.
I have not.
Me neither.
I'll check it out.
Thank you, Bee.
Me too.
Mike Holinger asks, Bella Legosi or Boris Karloff?
Gotta go Legosi, but that's probably just because of Ed Wood.
Ah, Karloff, 110%.
Okay.
Brendan Jesus.
Which one of you would be the first to die in a zombie apocalypse?
I gotta think I'd live that out longer.
Then me?
I'm tough.
Pain don't hurt.
You ain't gonna worry about pain.
You gotta worry about surviving.
You just said on one of the recent episodes, you don't cook.
You don't have to do shit for yourself.
I can cook.
Could you?
You think you just put a bunch of...
You put a bunch of beans in a backpack and go.
Oh, god.
I don't know.
I think I do pretty well.
There I am with a sack full of beans, eating good.
Meanwhile, you're trying to find a stove.
I would eat...
I feel like I'm gonna do all right.
All right.
I guess we'll find out when it happens in two to three years.
Well, what do you say we put the mics down and walk out that front door
with nothing in our pockets and see how it goes?
All right.
Great.
I do have to be at work at 10.
Excuse me.
I do have to be at work.
I don't mean to create an awkward situation.
I know you wanna eat my brain if you could just get it done by 9 .30.
So I can be traffic.
I know you're undead, but I'll be regular dead.
If my boss finds out, I'm late.
Josh Smallridge says the premise of a new show called Mayberry
is a spin on the Andy Griffith show where Sheriff Andy Taylor
and Deputy Barney Fife are corrupt small town law enforcement
hiding very dark murderous secrets.
That is the longest sentence I've ever seen, Josh.
Wait.
This is his idea.
Who do you cast in those two main roles?
Okay.
He wants casting.
That's a cool idea.
I haven't seen any of the show.
I've never seen the Andy Griffith show.
What's like, it's like apple pie.
I know enough.
You know.
It's like, it can be like, oh dang.
Oh, Bob's cat got loose again.
You know, it's Rockwell played Barney Fife very well
and the Oscar winning three burials of S .K .L.
They build three billboards out of Ebbing, Texas.
I almost blurred into the three burials of alkiades,
Mistratta, directed by Tommy Lee Jones.
Great movie, by the way.
I'm going to put Ben Mendelssohn in the Andy Griffith role.
Okay.
Weird.
I go Gaffigan Griffith,
Sam Rockwell, or Boshemi as Barney Fife.
Was that Boshemi's brother in Black Clansman?
Looked almost exactly like him,
and then I realized it was his brother.
The guy who looked exactly like him,
who was like...
Older cop?
Yeah.
The friend of driver.
I put Mendelssohn in the Griffith role
and I'm going to put...
I'm going to put Leslie Jones in the Fife role.
Okay.
Let's break it up a little bit.
Sure.
Tis the Seas.
And she's good at like flipping out, you know?
Yeah.
That's all he does on the show,
is he panics about everything.
Richard, how...
They both are both subtle performers.
You know?
Yeah.
Richard Howenstein, Pat,
you haven't talked much about your honeymoon.
That's a little private, dude.
Please tell us how it was in Greece.
It was beautiful.
Both the lady and the city.
The islands.
I loved it.
We went to Crete.
So a lot of history.
We went to Santorini,
little touristy, honeymoony, but fun.
We went to Naxos,
one of the most beautiful islands beaches I've ever seen.
Wait a great time.
Three weeks loved it.
Joe, or both.
Talk about a day that you could live over and over again.
One of your favorite days of your life.
You never think of them as they're happening.
That's for sure.
You never like,
this was the best day of my life.
I mean, I haven't said that in 37 years.
Well, I've had nice days.
You know what it would be,
would probably be the...
Go.
Okay, you can go first.
Super Bowl Sunday.
Me and the lady.
Well, I did.
God, high.
She joined me.
We went up to six flags.
No one in the park.
Road rides all day.
Beautiful.
I'm going to go with the Christmas.
Every...
I don't know if I've ever talked about this on the show,
but every Christmas.
When I go home on the night before Christmas Eve,
my friends,
Pinkstone, who we've talked about,
and some other friends of mine that are very close to me
from back home,
we do a thing called Eve Eve,
and we get hammered
and give each other presents.
And it's the most fun.
And we...
It's not like we drink.
Like, oh, let's have some drinks and see where it goes.
It's like, the goal is to get as fucking stupidly hammered
as possible.
Right.
So it's always tons of like,
doubled over laughter.
And then you open presents.
And I'd pick one of those,
because you know,
how can you go wrong?
Notice I wasn't here.
On your special day?
Well, I wasn't at yours either.
In fact, I remember texting you on that special day
and saying,
what are you doing?
Let's say on you said,
I'm at six flags with a lady.
That was fun.
So you...
You shut me out on this special day.
Maybe I saw you at the end of the day.
I don't remember what I did at the end of the day.
And maybe it went horribly wrong
and I don't want to relive it.
Who knows?
James Moynihan says,
I've seen other podcasts do host swaps for an episode.
For example, Generation Y and True Crime Garage
did it for an episode.
I would love to see you guys do a host swap
with my favorite murder.
Would you ever consider it?
I would.
They wouldn't.
There's no way.
Yeah, we would do it in a second there.
Yeah, we'll take their million times bigger than followers.
Who will be traumatized by multiple of what we said.
But I'd love to show.
Happy to do it.
We are trying to get Karen on the show
because she's been so supportive of our show
and we're really grateful for that.
And she's a dear friend.
We wanted to get her on the live shows,
but she's out of town with my favorite murder,
playing 3 ,000 seed theaters.
Yes, we'll be in front of 35 people.
Not that we're not appreciative.
They're just on a different level than us.
Yes.
It's our first show.
AJ Madden.
What's your first impressions of the trailer for Glass?
You know, I think it looks kind of low rent fun like split.
It doesn't have that feeling of like an unbreakable where you're like,
oh, shit, this is going to be incredible.
But it looks cool.
I can't deny it.
I'm sure it's going to be cool.
I'm excited for it.
It looks more like split than unbreakable,
which is not a great thing.
But still, it's going to be fun.
Jacob Heffernin.
Hefferman.
For both of you,
what's your favorite horror movie of the last 20 years?
20 years, huh?
Your favorite horror movie of the last 20 years?
Correct.
Well, I think for you, it would be get out.
Would it not?
Yeah, I think it would be up there for sure.
Last 20.
You know, it gets in just under the wire.
But I might have to,
it might have to be tales from the crypt demon night for me.
It's not 20 years.
It came out like 98, 99, didn't it?
It came out like 95.
Oh, yeah, you're right.
Can't count it.
Sorry.
Then I'll go with the right,
starring Anthony Hopkins.
I'm kidding.
I get, I mean, get out.
It's definitely way up there.
Probably get out.
All right.
Great choice.
But he, but he, but he,
but he, but he,
Devonte Rishan says,
have you seen the adult swim shorts by Alan Resnick
and Alan Tutorial?
And do you have thoughts?
No,
but no,
well, thank you for these recommendations.
They say, I'll check them out.
I know Adam Resnick is a cabin boy
in Chris Elliott's writing part.
It's nothing different from counting crows.
It's Adam Duritz.
Oh, okay.
Brooke Adams asks,
not so much a question,
but I think Joe's hard -bodied pod
insta -post need to be addressed.
I don't disagree.
If you have not seen these things,
it's Joe tell them,
tell them what they're about.
It's a man showing the world
his beautiful body
and not being afraid to be proud
of being femme -furn,
fit -firm, tight -and -tot.
I don't know how else to break it down.
I mean, the videos say it all.
And that man is Joe.
And did you ask the bartender permission
to take your top off in the bar the other day?
When you look like me,
you don't need permission.
You don't need,
nobody's complaining
when that shirt comes off.
Trust me.
All right.
Okay.
She, the bartender's asked me
to take it off again.
Keep it off, she said.
Yeah.
That's another story.
Koi Cook,
favorite horror movie,
rebake, or reboot?
The thing.
The thing,
the thing,
prequel is your favorite remake?
No, the thing,
which was a remake of the thing.
Oh, I see.
Oh, yeah.
The John Carpenter thing.
Yeah, I'd probably vote
for the thing.
I also really like
the Evil Dead remake quite a bit.
Tyler Taylor Parrott asks,
what were your first impressions of each other?
Love it first sight.
Mm -hmm.
All the way.
I saw Pat walking across that
restaurant,
sleeveless,
sleeveless band,
was playing.
Yeah.
And I had the back.
And the world went into slow motion
like in big fish.
Uh, yeah.
Like when they played,
babies got back in big fish.
Luke Physioc says,
Joe, what video game
would you like to see made into a movie?
Well, you guys know I'm a star wars freak.
I would absolutely love to see
the four sun -leashed games made into a movie.
I think they would,
that's a really, really tremendous storyline.
Uh, or the Knights of the Old Republic games
would be very cool.
Even though I don't like
the playing the games
because they're turn -based
and turn -based drives me crazy,
I would,
I would very much like to see them
made into a,
uh,
a film.
My answer is paperboy.
Pat, what is your favorite initial cast?
Not toobin.
No, I was toobin.
No, paperboy.
Favorite initial casting.
Example,
my favorite is bad boys
could have been Dana Carvey
and John Lovitz.
Um, yeah, there's a lot of those stories that fascinate me.
I think the one that I'm most intrigued by
was Bill Murray was going to play Tim Burton's Batman,
which I've always been fascinated by.
I'm most fascinated by the Kingpin casting.
That Kingpin casting really haunts me, yes.
Uh, that is Chris Farley as Randy Quaid,
Michael Keaton,
as Roy Munson,
and Jim Carey as Bigger in McCracken.
So it's -
It's an alternate version I would pay to see.
Top dollar.
Annalise Boyland,
Bowland.
What scary scene from a movie traumatized you the most
as a kid?
Mine would have been, uh,
the dude peeling off his face in the sink
and poltergeist.
Very graphic.
Uh, that's mine too.
Yeah.
Scared the shit out of me.
I had SpaghettiOs
and I got very sick
because they look like SpaghettiOs.
Also, side note, Pat,
one of my favorite episodes of the Gilmore Guys show
was the episode you did about Bunheads
that was four hours long.
I listened to it when I'm down to cheer me up.
Also, Joe, I wish I lived in the US
so I could come to your stand -up sometime.
Thanks.
Thank you, Annalise.
Lindy, excuse me,
Lindsay Stuffaker says,
what's your favorite and least favorite place
you've ever traveled to?
Favorite.
I really loved Kauai,
as I said earlier,
and I loved Amsterdam for different reasons.
Least favorite place I've ever traveled to.
I mean, maybe.
I don't know.
You got one?
Least favorite.
I mean, favorite and least favorite.
Dude, I got.
I got least favorites across the fucking.
Yeah.
Coming out of my ass.
I mean, you know, doing the road is a comic
because like,
dude, I've been to some fucking brutal places.
Yeah.
Brutal.
I actually kind of feel bad.
Like, I don't want to call out one
because, you know,
somebody's got to live everywhere.
You know what I mean?
So it's like,
sure.
I want to shit on somebody's home,
but I will say I've been in some really,
really shit situations on the road.
Yeah.
Like crossing, crossing a highway by foot
to eat like a fucking denny's.
Like just depression, dude.
Like,
sure.
Staying in a hotel that smells like mildew.
And like,
it's fucking awful.
But favorite place.
I'm going to go with,
I don't know,
Italy's pretty up there.
I like.
I also did love Amsterdam.
I really like Amsterdam quite a bit.
Yeah, probably those two.
Okay.
I always say,
you know,
I really like Toronto.
Let me tell you in Toronto.
I'm very happy.
All right.
Luke,
Physioc.
First time getting drunk or high stories.
Is this Luke's fifth question?
Is it?
That's the first time I said it, man.
That's the first one.
Yeah.
Oh, I thought,
wait, are you sure?
Yeah.
Okay.
I'm getting punch drunk.
Sorry, Luke.
First time getting drunk.
I had six my card,
lemonade,
vomited at a college type party.
But I think I was post college.
It was 23.
And first time I got high was probably
five years after that.
Three years after that.
It was when I was about to move from New York to LA.
First drive was after my senior prom.
I was 17,
drank screwdriver,
got shit faced in the woods.
Again,
with pink stone.
Mm -hmm.
I slept in my car.
What kind of vodka?
Or Christ, dude.
It couldn't have been anything better
than like a smear and off.
Or it was probably a Joaquin's or something.
Okay.
It was clear.
And first high was a freshman year in college.
Some are after my freshman year in college.
Got stoned.
Had smoked weed many times.
But it didn't work.
And the time it finally worked.
We were at Denny's.
And I just remember laughing.
I was laughing hysterically.
And then thinking that the manager who was walking around
with a cordless phone was saying that my dad
was on the phone for me.
Which he wasn't clearly.
And then also the French slam tasted better
than anything I'd ever tasted.
Yeah.
It was a hell of a ride.
All right.
I'm a big fan of this day,
to be honest with you.
John Wolf asks,
which score says he film would you want to have a part in?
Bit part, big part.
Would you guys want to share the screen together?
I mean, I think maybe we should be a couple of henchmen
in this, the Irishman picture.
Yeah, maybe a couple of bumbling cops
that they pay off or something, you know.
I think I even bumble my gun to the floor,
like that level of bumbling.
Yeah.
And then I bend over to pick it up,
and my pants rip.
And you're wearing a heart box.
Yeah, heart box.
Kevin Driscoll says,
for both of you,
what was the first rated arm movie you saw?
How old were you?
What impact influenced did it have on me?
The first truly, like,
graphically rated arm, you know,
rated arm movie,
I remember seeing was Kentucky Fried movie.
Yeah.
And it is a lot of boobs.
It's a lot of off -color humor.
I mean, I was, I was a pig and shit.
I mean, I saw it when I was like,
10.
I couldn't...
You see something like that when you're 10.
It's just the most fucking amazing thing you've ever seen.
Yeah.
So that was probably...
That's the one I really remember.
Yeah, that for me was a few years later
with airplane and naked gun and all that stuff.
But I...
The first R -rated movie I think was probably
die hard at my buddy Ryan's house,
which was great, of course.
And then I watched many that my dad rented
with my ear to the speaker and the basement,
like Pulp Fiction, do the right thing.
Saw them all with my eyeball one inch from the screen.
Not ideal.
Good fellow, same way.
Heighten, Davidson,
stories of your first time doing stand -up.
My coworker Laura Kightlinger told me I should do it.
I came, I did 10 minutes.
I absolutely destroyed.
My hands shook the entire time.
I kept making jokes about my hands shaking.
I remember it being a lot of fun.
And it went great.
Joe.
I was in a bar in my hometown.
I'd been doing a two -man sketch thing in there
with a friend of mine named Dan.
Dan quit the night before one of our shows.
So I said, all right, I guess I'm going to try stand -up.
And I went in and the place that had been empty every week
while we did this was now packed.
I had to get up in front of this packed bar
and do stand -up for the first time.
And I was not good.
I got enough laughter that I had the confidence
to want to try it again.
But a lot of it bombed,
because I didn't really know how to write material yet.
And then this kid that I went to grade school with,
who I hadn't seen in forever,
came up to me and chastised me about two of my jokes.
One, he reprimanded me for making fun of the Catholic church.
And then he also reprimanded me for making fun
of vegetarians.
And I was like, oh, I definitely want to do this.
That was all I needed.
Like, oh, people like this getting mad at you.
This is great.
Right.
Yeah.
All right.
It's nice.
Tim Clark, how do you guys feel about those 80s kids' fantasy films
like the never -ending story or dark crystal?
Were they fueled entirely by cocaine?
Something.
I mean, those movies, there's nothing like them when they try
to recreate them.
They're not like them.
They have a very special specific, very dark feel to them.
I'm looping and returning to Oz as well.
Never any story to me is a fucking incredible movie.
It always scared the shit out of me.
And it still does.
And dark crystal, I think, is a very cool movie as well.
But to me, pales in comparison to Lamar.
I am the opposite.
To me, dark crystal is an absolute masterpiece.
I'm eager to watch it again.
It's scared the fucking shit out of me as a kid.
It's so dark.
I don't think it's filled by cocaine.
I don't think Hanson was a big coke guy.
That's probably a weird guy.
But never -ending story is based on a book.
And I love the number -ending story.
But an interesting, interestingly enough,
the guy that wrote the book hates the movie.
I like the both.
Because he's like, you did half of my book.
And you missed the point.
We went to be four fucking hours.
I think he felt they missed the point.
It's like, you know, King hates the shining.
You know what I mean?
But I love that moment.
I'll try you.
That didn't scare me too bad when I was a kid.
Great effects.
It's so depressing, man.
That thing with the fucking turtle.
The horse drowning in quicksand.
That kills me.
That destroys me.
That makes you think of con.
Con, man.
Con.
You think about your dog drowning in quicksand?
Because it's his pet.
It's like drowning in these five words.
I think of the lovable falcor who looks a lot like your dog.
Because I think of how much I love con when I had how heartbreaking that would be
if we were walking through a swamp and you didn't want to go on.
Well, don't take your dog to the swamp next time.
Now, don't send me on a fucking journey to save attorney.
Greg Butler, Magical Girl Anime or Mecha Hentai.
Mecha Hentai.
I don't understand one fucking word of it.
I don't either.
I've never been into anime.
Hentai, I think, is tentacle porn.
I've got no interest in that either.
Sorry.
I can't help you.
Mike Slobodian asks, if you guys could pick a part to play in a pre -established film,
what part would you want to play?
Good.
We've gotten this one too.
But it's a good question.
I wouldn't do it well, but I would love to play the Steve Martin role in
Plants Transcendental Abiles.
I wouldn't play it as well.
But just to spend all that time with John Candy, deliver those great lines and monologues.
Be fun.
I wouldn't be good at it, but I want to be Han Solo.
Be a different picture.
I'll tell you that.
John went.
What are your thoughts on the movie Time Bandits?
Also, why did Joe tell HBO's own Dennis Cathouse off to do what he did?
What did that guy do?
I mean, not a surprise.
I guess he did something with one of the gals, probably.
Yeah, jeez.
I love Time Bandits.
Time Bandits.
I have the criterion.
I've not seen it since I was 10.
I wouldn't be able to make a good estimation until I watch that again.
I love it.
I own it on VHS.
Just to make it extra nostalgic when I watch it.
It's great.
And we'll do it on the show.
That'd be fun.
Leo Lopez, and we are getting close to the end, asks,
is there a way to wear a Bolo tie and make it look endearing, possibly sexy?
Examples?
Also, will you guys ever do an episode on Golden Pond?
No.
I like that movie.
Joe Bob Briggs pulls off the Bolo tie sometimes.
I think Mr. Charlie Day pulled it off in the gas crisis, always sunny episode.
Is that the one where he's like, why don't you just pretty as a peach?
Yeah, he's got the Bolo tie on the hat.
That's really funny when he knows it.
Paul Merchie asked, did you see first reformed?
And if so, any thoughts on it?
Yeah, I talked about it on this very show.
That might not have aired yet.
Might not have aired yet.
Any thoughts on any Paul Schrader movies?
I think the man, when he's hit and makes incredible movies,
and namely, he wrote Taxi Driver and Raging Bull,
but I got to give a lot of love to Affliction, which he wrote and directed.
One of my faves, Nick Nolte, James Coburn.
My favorite is Schrader's autofocus.
Love autofocus.
I love it.
Just to...
Great, great movie.
And to ride that movie.
Love American Jigalow.
I mean, the man makes great shit.
Marcus Megahi asks, which forthcoming horror films are you most anticipating?
I'd also love to hear your thoughts on last year's The Killing of a Sacred Deer.
It's been in my cue for a long time, and I have not yet watched it.
But as far as forthcoming horror, I haven't watched this new Halloween trailer,
but I'd be lying if I said I wasn't pumped to see it.
I watched the new trailer.
It looks fine.
It's not...
It doesn't look bad.
All right.
It's just...
We've been down this road so many times with Halloween at this point.
It's hard to...
Yeah.
It's hard to get, like, super excited, but I will see it, and I do look forward to seeing it.
For me, it's that Mandy movie, that Nicholas Cage thing coming out.
Yeah, I think I can get us into a screening at Tuesday.
So maybe we do it next.
I'm not going to be here.
Oh, then I'll go alone.
I leave town Friday.
All right.
God damn it.
That sucks.
You should see them.
It's on...
It's going to be on demand next week.
Oh, will?
Yeah.
It's a good day and date.
Dozenay Wilford asks, what are your thoughts on sharp objects?
I raved about it on the last live app we did, not live, but, you know, regular app.
Absolutely loved it.
Love the first half.
Love the back half even more.
Richard almost says, please tell me you didn't like it.
My girlfriend loved it.
I wanted to hang myself.
Well, Richard, don't hang yourself.
And I'm sorry, you didn't like the show.
Richard almost says, what is the most embarrassing date story you have?
Back to the damn sex one.
Yeah.
I had a really bad date with a girl who was blacked out drunk in New York, made out with me,
then told me she had hepatitis C after we'd been making out on a park bench.
I don't know enough about diseases, and I spent the night horrified.
I have been tested.
I do not possess hepatitis C, but that was a stressful evening for me, to say the least.
Is that really an embarrassing story, just a horror story?
Well, what's embarrassing on a date?
I mean, you should shut your pants?
Yeah, sure.
I guess that was more of a horror story.
I don't really have one.
I mean, I've certainly had plenty of bad dates, but none that were like where I felt it.
Here's one.
When I was in sixth grade, I started going out with this girl that didn't go to my school,
and she only knew me from over the phone, and from one picture.
Then we were going to have our first date at McDonald's, and we met up at McDonald's,
and she looked at me, and basically ran away, and said, I'm not dating him.
That hurt.
I mean, also, yeah, sixth grade.
Yeah.
That should happen.
Alex Shipley asks, what are your worst experiences on broke girls now that the show's over,
and you're not at CBS?
I mean, look, I had a boss that was tough.
I watch it now.
I'm appalled by some of the more racist jokes, which were put in by that boss.
But by and large, I had a good time.
I met a lot of good people.
I had some bad years.
I had some good years there.
What are you going to do?
I like the money.
Arad.
Typing sums him up, people.
I like the money.
I like the cash.
Just remember that.
Arad.
Typing mishap, preferably involving the opposite sex.
What?
I guess like a texting error, like I want to duck you or something.
Why is everybody on this like embarrassing romantic comedy scenario?
I don't know, but yeah, I don't feel like I've ever sent a text.
I was really embarrassed.
I've sent girls like, you know,
you know, maybe when I was drunk and single, I might text a girl I liked or too early or something,
but nothing embarrassing.
Like, hey, I really like you.
And then you look at the next morning, I'm like, I shouldn't have said that.
But maybe I never liked them when you like them.
I never texted a girl and then was like, I thought you were my proctologist.
Yeah, exactly.
Then that means I said my proctologist flowers.
Although it wouldn't be anything wrong with that.
Yeah, yeah.
If he does a job well done.
I've never been to the proctologist.
Maybe I should check it out.
I haven't either, but my favorite Rodney Dangerfield joke of all time ever is, I know I'm ugly.
I went to the proctologist and he stuck his finger in my mouth.
That's good.
At his airtight baby.
The asshole and the joke.
First big, man, these guys really want, it's like a 17 column out here tonight.
Steve Calpa asks, first big breakup?
Who dumped two?
Who won?
How'd you guys get through it?
Or just any funny breakup or relationship ending stories?
I dumped my girlfriend Melissa Muller in sixth grade.
And she kicked me in the balls in front of the entire class.
Wow.
That was a rough one.
Most breakups I've had as an adult have been ugly, gruesome.
I don't know if it was the people I was attracting.
I know I had a large part to blame in them.
I think everybody feels some sort of regret looking back on relationships.
But again, not like hilarious breakup story for you.
I find them sad generally.
My first big breakup was a girl who's a happily married lesbian right now when I was in the eighth grade.
So she, you know, I see why that didn't work out.
Joshua Taj Bozeman asks, what's it like to work in a creative field and have a body of work that will live long past you?
Is life different when you have creative endeavors that you can leave behind?
It's a very sweet way of looking at this business.
The Joe and I treat with such aggression and disgust.
But you know, it's cool.
Like, even shows I think suck or whatever.
Like, when you see that they're going to be on TV or they still air them or people tell you I love that show, whatever, it's a great feeling.
It's cool to have something that lingers like that.
No, it's very nice.
Yeah.
I'm glad I got to do a couple of records and specials with like the Comedy Central label.
Because I know that that will, that, you know, even though it's under this conglomerative Viacom and whatever else it's like that will live on past when I'm gone.
Yeah.
Whereas the albums I try to put out myself, you know, right.
I don't really know if I'm going to be leaving my estate to anybody.
But you do what you love and you love what you do.
How many more questions are there?
Two.
Oh, really?
It's weird.
They almost always comes to an exact hour.
Thoughts on the child's play reboot asks Daniel Rudd.
Furious.
I'm fear it's just it literally offends me.
Now why they've done 30.
What do you care at this point?
Here's what they're doing.
Okay.
So they're doing a TV series that that Mancini is doing the creator.
Henry Mancini, the composer.
Yes.
Panther theme.
Yeah.
He's the creator of child's play is doing a series with Brad Dorif as Chuck E.
And, you know, it will be the continuing story of Chuck E.
Yeah.
And apparently he's going to bring like the cast members back and all that stuff from all the different movies.
Somehow there are movie rights at a studio and the movie the studio that was rushing now to get a remake of the movie out.
Where it's not a possessed doll.
It's an AI doll gone crazy.
Yeah.
Exactly.
Fucking.
Why do child's play?
Exactly.
No, that is stupid.
Because not angry about it.
And they're trying to beat him to the punch.
It's just fucking annoying.
And is it still look like Chuck E?
I mean, I don't know.
And no, Dorif's not doing it.
No, he's not.
They're not having Dorif.
And it's a fucking AI.
Oh, my God.
Nicholas McCann asks, your hungover is shit.
After slamming some Gatorade and plopping on the couch, you have a choice of three movies to watch in this mindless state.
You have to pick one.
Your choices are twins.
My cousin Vinny, men at work.
Immediately my cousin Vinny.
Same.
I don't remember twins.
I would like to rewatch it.
And if I were hungover, I would watch it.
If it was on Saturday even.
But like I wake up, I could see that scenario.
However, I'm always going to go with cousin Vinny.
It's the best of those movies by far.
Men at work's a terrible film.
My cousin Vinny is a comforting piece.
You're familiar enough with it that you can maybe doze off for a little while.
Yes.
Very well written.
Twins is great too.
But twins is, you know, twins is Ivan right minute.
It gets, it gets pretty.
There's some real fucking sad parts in twins.
How so?
You feel really shocked.
Like there's like a part where they go to the doctor that created them.
Yeah.
And he basically tells Davido like you were everything left over.
Like everything good went to Arnold.
It's fucking brutal dude.
Yeah.
There's some real rough scenes in that movie.
I'll check it out again.
Who's the woman in that Penelope Ann Miller?
She the mom.
I think so.
I can't remember.
She was something and then she left, left for a while.
I just looked her up the other day.
She's got new headshots on IMDB.
Okay.
Why did I look her up?
What was she in that I was watching?
You watching the gun and Betty lose handbag?
No.
That's like what she in that I was watching.
Oh Christ.
My brain is dead.
It's the last question Joe.
That's how you want to go out.
I'm not buttering to yourself about Penelope Ann Miller.
Probably how we're all going to go out.
Let's be honest.
All right.
Folks, we cannot tell you enough how much we treasure your support of us and the Patreon.
We don't do plugs.
We don't do our segments on these special shows.
But we love it.
We love you.
We are cognizant of the fact that we did not
not air one of these.
And even though I have not discussed this with Joe,
we'll throw you a bonus at some point.
What are you talking about?
We'll throw them another.
We didn't air what?
Patreon.
We missed a month on the Patreon.
No.
We're missing a week in October.
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh, on the Patreon.
Are we missed a month?
We missed two months.
Patreon was supposed to be shut down for two months.
And I fucked up.
I don't know what I did wrong.
Well, so we have to we had to acknowledge that at some point we are aware of the error and we are looking to make it up to you,
which will probably be with like a nice long juicy extra bonus.
Yes.
So know that that's where our heads are at.
And it was just it seemed to be more complicated to try to refund those two months and then keep the current pledges.
It's Patreon gets a little, maybe I'm dumb, but it just gets a little complicated.
Yeah.
So anyway, know that we're aware of that.
And yes, we are going to we are going to hit you up.
And just so you know what I was referring to, which I thought Pat was referring to.
The first week of October, the episode will be late.
It'll come out sometime that week.
But it'll be late because we could only stockpile so many of these.
Yeah.
So the first one of October will be come out on Tuesday or Wednesday and set up Monday.
You can't live with that.
It might come out Thursday or Friday because the point is it will come out Thursday.
But you're going to get one.
Thanks, everybody.
We really, really appreciate you.
We mean it.
We really do.
Thanks, y 'all.
See ya.
In hell.