you
welcome to will see you will see you in hell a place i might be one step
closer to Pat. Oh, one step beyond Matt. One step closer to hell. One step close.
I'm just making it up. It sounds like it'd be like a Garth Brooks style, right? One
step closer to hell, baby, but I'm two steps further from heaven from you. I mean no
country song has ever mentioned hell without heaven coming in right around the corner. I will
figure it out. Well, what about one step closer to hell, but I'm, but that means I'm two steps
closer to you. Like she's like she's, she's a bad. Oh, yeah, yeah. But love every minute of it.
Would you know, I love the heat from your little devil keyster. Keysters know when you hear a lot
for, but like if I were to walk up to a sexy babe at a bar and say, hey, it's a slamming keyster,
you're, you're toting back there. Well, I wouldn't go over. And in this song, you rhyme it with Easter
and it's on theme. You got my pants now rising like Easter. Oh, I thought you were just gonna ask
her to like to go out on Easter. No, no, no. I'd like to hide more than an egg.
In your grass, baby. Yeah, and then the grass being the pubes. And then the thing he's hiding is
the earthy penis. Now, Joe, I have to just tell you here. And I know you got a little something to say
as well. But did I ever talk on the show? I know I sent you audio recordings. But did I ever talk
on the show about my neighbors across the street, married couple, one of the most disturbing. Yeah,
things I've ever heard. I, well, I don't know if you've mentioned, I can't remember what's been on
the show and what hasn't. But you've definitely told me that you got these crazy people. Yeah.
I mean, months and months ago, obviously, I woke up, had their middle of the night and I was like,
you got to come outside because I don't know what to do. I'm in a moral quandary here.
And then what was happening was I was going to bed. And when I turned the TV off, I heard from across
the street, this woman going, hey, so many here. And I was like, oh, shit, like who wants to be
involved in something like that? But I was like, look, this lady's something's happened to her. I
want to help. So I go outside and I'm listening for a minute. And her husband is very calmly saying
to her, by the way, I've seen it, these people are my across the street neighbors. He's like
because you're a drunk, because you're a mess, right, fucked up our life. That's why.
So I'm listening. And then finally she's like, I'm calling the police. Somebody help me, somebody
help me. And he goes, go ahead, call the police. I'm very calm. You're fucked up. They're going to
take you away. And she goes, no, I'm going to tell them what I told them the last time you called the
police on me. I'm going to tell them that you're molesting our daughter. She's crazy. I'm like,
so now keep in mind, just me and Heather sitting on my porch listening to this and I'm like,
okay, so is this woman in danger? Did this guy molest their daughter? Is she a psycho? Is she lying?
Then we sat and listened and very quickly it became clear that she was out of her fucking gourd.
And she's hysterically screaming. She throws stuff. She throws herself against walls so that she
gets bruises so that she can report this guy and tells him that's what she's doing for all the
neighborhood to hear. So anyway, like a Batman villain that can't keep the plant, you know, they're
so proud of the plan. They have to, yeah, yeah. So, you know, wound up going to bed. It happened
several more nights after that and really disturbing because she screams like like a ghost or something.
So I haven't seen anyone in the house for at least six months and today I go out, I get the mail,
I hear a massive crash like a glass being shot out of a cannon and exploding and then she goes,
you, nothing. Like honestly, final half hour of the exercise,
voice, you're nothing. She goes, I want you out of my life. And he goes, then you'll be on the streets.
You have no money. And she goes, I'll marry a man. And she goes, actually, I know who I'll marry.
He goes, oh, the guy you were fucking. Now, what would you would have, did you just a quick,
what would you would have, what would you have done? Had she gone, pat,
honestly, I'm a single man, you know, and the crazy ones tend to, tend to bring the heat. But
she's not a bad looking lady, actually. I said, or I'm sitting there listening to them and she goes,
I, ooh, because she's evil. She says like what the devil would say to a man. So she's like,
I know exactly what man I'll go live with. Exactly. And he goes, yeah, the guy you were fucking,
that's that who you're going to see. And she goes, yes. And she goes, because he's nice to me.
And he has way more money. And he has a dick that fucking works and isn't tiny.
I'm like, holy shit. I leaned against my mailbox like to steady myself. Like, where is this going?
This should be, this should all be a compile in a book of called, what might have been said before
he hit her. I mean, she, she is so clearly, look, look, look, look. She's asking for it or something.
I'm not obviously, I think if you've been listening to us for six years, we know you know we're not
those guys. No, no. This woman, I'm going to try to say she's asking for it without saying it.
She is dying for him to hit her because she clearly wants some sort of settlement or she wants to go to
jail. But she wants him to go to jail. The whole time I'm sitting there listening to these two,
they have a 16 year old daughter who hopefully is at school today. But they're going at it so hard.
And I'm sitting there just like, this is miserable. And finally, as I, as I decided, I didn't want to
listen to it anymore. I actually had recorded a chunk of it and deleted it because I felt guilty.
But I was walking in and I thought to myself, how did these two make it longer marriage -wise than I did?
How is this marriage going the distance? I guess they're staying together for the kid, but my guess is
that kid would be thrilled if this ended. She's drunk off her ass and it's 1245 here. My take on that is
and I've actually floated this theory past a few people that have usually agreed with me.
I think when you're in something that turbulent and that crazy, yeah. Excuse me, it's tough for either
part of you to get out of it because one of them is an abuser who's going to, you know, and then the
other one keeps thinking, if I, I've put so much into this, if I could just fix it. If I walk away
now, it's just a waste. It's like, it's like you're spool -unking, deeper and deeper into a treacherous cave.
And you just go, well, what am I going to do now? Turn around. Like I got this far. All this was for
nothing. And it's not a good way to do it, but that's I think the mentality you get into.
Yeah, I mean, look, even in even in movies and stuff about, like even like marriage story
for God's sake, they weren't talking like this to each other. I mean, this is beyond the pale.
This is death threats and shit. And then this is like a cast of Eddie's movie or something.
Exactly. My neighbor on the other side, nicest guy in the world, he and I were kind of talking and
laughing about it last time. But then at the same time, we both are like, boy, I really don't want
them to be taking her body out of there in a stretcher in two weeks. And I could have called the police,
you know, because even though I'm hearing both sides of the story and this woman is obviously some sort
of having a psychotic break, I think today's issue was she started drinking again because they missed
rent. So she was screaming, everything's my fault. And he goes, not everything, but not paying
the rent is because I make the money. You sign the check. You didn't do it for months. You told me
you did. So now we could lose our house. That is your fault. Renting a house of the, what are you doing?
What, what, what are they doing times a thousand? What are they doing in every aspect of their lives? I
will say having listened to these people like they were a sitcom for hours at a time or a radio play.
She's the problem. However, did he make her crazy? Was it like some old Betty Davis movie where he
gas littered until she went insane? I don't know. My money's on this. You finally go over there. You
see the silhouettes in the window. Yeah. You hear the fight. You see the violence. But each of
their silhouettes is in a different window. You go over to stop it. The man answers the door turns and
half of him is the woman. Not a bad twist. I thought you were going to go home alone where it's her
with like Michael Jordan cutouts and she's making them dance to fool the neighbors. That too,
that's a good one too. Could be either a really realistic haunted house this year. Just a couple on
the on the cusp of divorce was our theme for the neighborhood haunted house. That's rough style,
man. And you know what? It's a cliche thing to say at this point. But I, especially when I lived in
New York and then my early days here in LA have lived in some of these shittiest most dangerous
places this country has to offer. I worked in Newark for a while for God's sake. I never heard anything
like this until I moved to this nice little suburban neighborhood in the hills. It's it was the point
of blue velvet and many other such movies. Things are more fucked up in the sub. And of don't worry
darling, which we discussed last week. You scrape beyond that surface. You find a bunch of fucked up
shit. Yeah, it's dark. It's dark. It's I believe it's along the lines of what the chili peppers
referred to as californication. Pretty on the outside ugly in the middle. Isn't there an alderon
shout out in that song? Alderon. Isn't Alderon a Star Wars planet? It's where princess
lays from. Yes. Look at the lyrics because he gives it gives a shout out to your plant, your home
planet Alderon. In the song california, I'll look it up. I want you to talk to us Joe about your
health while I look up in lyrics to californication. No, I don't want the decovne show. I want the song
go. Mr. Bungle, their best album is called california. And it's my favorite record of all time. And
they were interviewing them about if because it's sort of a concept record. And they they said,
what's the theme here? And Mike Patton goes, what do you mean? And the guy's like, well,
california, like, what are you trying to say? And he goes, well, we're not trying to say it's all
pretty looking but ugly underneath. Are we the fucking chili peppers?
That's pretty fun. Yeah. Anyway, um, and then before we get off it, and then I want you to take
the reins completely. Yeah. The lyric is, boy, when you really read the lyrics, that's that
chili peppers are worse lyricists than I thought. Yeah, that's not a good scene. This is not a bad
little verse here, though. I like it. Space may be the final frontier, but it's made in a Hollywood
basement deep. And Cobain, can you hear the spheres singing songs off station to station,
which is a David Bowie album. And I guess Cobain did cover David Bowie.
Don't know what that means, though. And Alderan's not far away. It's californication.
Meaning, well, they blow up Alderan in the first Star Wars. We're going to blow up soon.
Maybe. Also, I thought it was first born intercourse hard core soft porn. And I was like,
that is a really disturbing lyric. First born intercourse. It's actually first born unicorn.
First born unicorn, which is much less disturbing and actually kind of sweet. All right, Joe, tell
us. Take it away. No, I've never gotten to say this in my life, but I get to say it today. I went
through a battery of tests today. Yeah, not for anything major. My cholesterol was high. I got a
blood panel done right around my 45th birthday. My cholesterol, everything was fine, but my cholesterol
came back high. My doctor was like, look, let's be safe. Go get a plaque check, which means you
got to get a CAT scan of your heart. And I said, Hey, while we're there, let's look at all of it.
You know, ultrasound, the liver. Look at the thyroid. We're always scared about that liver.
When you lived out here, it'd be like me and Joe, go to lunch and at least three minutes of
lunch would be devoted to liver. Well, when I lived out there, I had, I was diagnosed twice with
fatty liver, but both times my numbers were off. My liver numbers were off in my blood work. They
haven't been lately. And my doctor also was like the chlamydia spike the liver numbers. Oh, yeah,
yeah, and the herbs. Got to read. Yeah, I don't know which is called the clap anymore. I got all
of it. It's called a clap. Yeah, like a kind of a scatter gories die situation where it's just like
you know, one for every letter on the die. Exotic ones, you know, ones I couldn't pronounce.
The, uh, that's one of, uh, man, one of the great Richard prior jokes we talked about going to
Vietnam. He's like, they got a VD over there. Scared of shit out of penicillin.
Recoiled. Yeah, well, I remember, I remember, Joe, you had something that the doctor called
Audrey, too, which is where the head of your penis sings Feed Me Seymour. It sang show tunes.
Feed Me Seymour was one of them. To me, kind of a fun treat. But as you said, you couldn't
shut it off, which I imagine got annoying after a while. Couldn't shut it off had to feed at human
blood. Sure. It got old. Yeah. So yeah, I just said, look, let's, let's look at everything while
we're there. My doctor was even like two. He was like, your liver numbers are fine. You're going
to have fatty liver like every American in the, you know, he's like, who cares? Don't worry about it.
So, you know, at least that was, I was, because that's kind of how I always looked at it. After a while,
I was like, I feel like everybody must have this. Like, this is like a, look at the, look at Americans.
Like there's no way that the people I see in the street every day don't have this. They're not dropping
dead left him, right? Anyway, so we took a look at everything today. I get the results. They're
concerned as they're getting a little too much liver in the fat. Hey, we got to isolate this fat here.
Do you take coffee with your sugar? Yeah, that's one of those. I told you right that doctors aren't
supposed to mention weight anymore, right? We discussed that on here. We don't have it in my act.
Oh, okay. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. I already had a joke about it. And then you telling me that allowed
me to say, I have a friend. Y 'all good. I'm good. And, and really validate the joke. But, um,
yeah, I mean, so, you know, that's, that's where we're at. Like, you know, I mean, hopefully,
everything's okay. It's a little nerve -wracking, but, um, but, you know, they won't tell you anything
there, which is the thing. But, and which sucks because they know what's, they see the results
right then and there, but they're not allowed to tell you. Oh, yeah. Well, you having a little
elevated cholesterol and, and fatty liver or whatever, these, these tests are just as random as,
testing for anything else, aren't they? I mean, you don't have any reason to suspect you have this
stuff. The heart scan was the main one because he was like, with elevated cholesterol, I need to make
sure you don't have plaque building up. And you don't have blockages forming. Yeah. We're already
formed, God forbid, because that's going to gauge if I'm at risk for heart attack, which is,
behind cancer, my greatest fear of just getting a massive hearted, or strobe dropping dead.
Every male in my dad's side of the family has dropped dead suddenly and pretty young of a massive
heart attack. So I started looking into it very early and got on a stettin, the smallest dose of a
when I didn't need to for cholesterol. It was like, no, you're fine. But the guy, he was like,
you know, I tell a lot of young guys, he goes, you just get on this and you don't get the plaque.
I mean, we're turning into men's health podcast at this point. But I'm telling you how I'm telling you,
ask the guy, can I get a, I'll tell you more off air, but maybe he's maybe somebody listening to
benefit say you want a 10 milligrams stettin. It's the smallest pill I've ever seen. I take one
each day. I have the cholesterol of like a 12 year old Swedish girl. My health is immaculate
considering how I, you know, drink and live. I really recommend doing something like that if
it's a concern of yours. There's no reason not to. The pill does nothing else. It has no side effects.
My doctor said we could do that. And I said, great. Let's talk about it. Yeah. And that was two
weeks ago. I called his assistant today. And I literally said, Hey, why don't you tell the doc if
he ever feels like it, getting back to me about this cholesterol pill. It's only been two weeks. Let's
see how, how through the roof we can get this number before we discuss the medicine. Yeah. But that's
why I changed my diet two weeks ago. That's why now that it's nice or weather, I mean, I'm just
never going to be an exercise guy. But like today, I try to, I'm trying to put in the 10 ,000 steps
every day when I can. Yeah. Well, you got it easy there. I think for the most part, for the most part,
when it starts, go to the far Dwayne Reed, you get 4 ,000 steps. Yeah. So, tell me anyway,
that's why I made the joke at the top of the show everybody that I'm one step closer to hell.
I got to tell you with everybody getting worse and worse and worse and worse at their job.
Doctors are no different. No different. Oh, no. Not at all.
They, so basically my doctor who was as cold, this is the writer's guild health center I go to,
like, you know, I don't know. I don't know why I expected to be like a community or something. But
this guy was as cold and indifferent to me. He was in and out of that office in 25 seconds.
But I had to go, I had to say to him, hey, man, can I just ask you a couple of questions? You know,
like, it's like, well, for starters, I'd like to update you that I'm not married anymore. And I'm
single and I'm going to be having sex. And so like, I was just kind of like, aren't these questions
we should ask? And he's like, yeah, okay, I'll write that down. But like annoyed. So I'm like, all right.
And I was, I was let down by the appointment. But the big thing was I said, I'd like to do just the
full panel before I get back out there in those streets. And it'd be nice, you know, as I get back
out and have to deal with all kinds of shit condoms and everything else to just be able to take that
off my mind and know my status is completely free and clear. And he goes, you're married. Why would
you, why would you need to do that? Are you worried you were just married? I go, because I want to
do it for peace of mind because we don't really like, we don't really like people to do that. I go,
well, I'd like to do it. Then he goes, all right, and you've got no symptoms. I said, sir,
I have no symptoms. I'll pay. But I, yeah, I'd like to do this, please. He goes, okay, you know,
why, by the way, do you know why they have to do that? No, my doctor really don't. My doctor told me
to get that. He wanted to know if I'm clean. My doctor explained it to me. They have to get
things approved so you don't get charged. Okay. If your insurance doesn't approve it,
you're going to get charged. So my doctor told me flat out. He was like, he was like, I can't just
send you for a long scan that you're asking for. I have to put down a reason. Okay, yeah, that makes
sense. Luckily, you were a smoker and you're not anymore. But we can say that we have a concern because
you weren't exposed. He was like, if I don't have that, they will charge you for the test. So I never
knew. You'd think they'd just explain this to you. You would think it would take less time than
the stupid who's on first were playing for me to get my blood drawn after having not been to the doctor
in three years as a 40 year old man. It seems like a pretty reasonable request. I'm like, I'd like to
look at my cholesterol, my blood sugar, but because the guy, the guy who gave me the statin recently
died of a massive heart attack. So I was kind of like, no, okay, well, that's troubling. My heart
specialist. Anyway, the guy was no help. He runs the tests. I get the call that, well, actually,
I had to call, of course, after two weeks and say, hey, what are my results? Let me look, Mr.
Wallace, you're completely clean. That's why the doctor didn't call you. Your cholesterol numbers
are perfect. This is perfect. Everything's good. Your sexual health is perfect. You're good. I say,
okay, great. You know, I feel control revealing this. We're all close. Then I have sex
and we don't wrap it up. You know, I'm like, here we go. Let's roll the dice. I know my status.
And I get a call a week later, Mr. Walsh, this is doctor, whatever the fuck, we realized we did not
give you the results of your, your analysis when we talk. They had just said the only reason we
call is when there's a problem. So my heart just stops. And I'm like, oh, fuck, now whatever I have,
now my first time out, I got to call somebody. You know, you know, all this shit, I'm just like,
God damn it. This is horrible. And it's nothing. They just said, we just forgot to give you one of
these results. It's clean. So I go, it's my pH or what? Yeah, your pH is good. So you're clean
for this. You're clean for this. I'm like, okay, so you guys just forgot and then give me a heart
attack. But now let's say flip side, she called and said, you have genital herpes. Then I've had sex
with someone and infected them because the doctor made a mistake and didn't read me my full report.
Yeah. It's like that, you know, look, this is a crazy dark place to go. I apologize for the podcast.
But I was just sitting there like, how are you as a doctor also going to slack off to the
extent that my and someone else's health are at risk? It's really fucked up. And I know I'm paranoid
about all that shit more than most. Don't get me wrong. But man, it really, it shook me up when I
thought about it. I was like, well, who knows what else they miss. No, we're living like in a Michael
Moore documentary at this point. It's bad. Yeah, really. He really, he, when I made him go past
the 25 second mark during which he tapped my neck, had me breathe once with his hand on my back
and then left and even feel my dick and balls. That used to be a reliable at the doctor's office.
Especially like you hear when you, when you turn 40, you think they're going to be checking for
the shit that you get when you're 40 along for some. This guy had no interest in me,
sexually, no interest in me. As a patient, really, it was just like he came in. He saw that I looked,
you know, reasonably healthy and upright. And he said, I'll give this guy 30 seconds of my time.
And I don't, I don't, I don't think that's good for people. They're going to miss major,
major issues that people have. Let me think about like language barriers like, you know,
they're, I don't know. It's, it's crazy. It's crazy. Yeah. A lot of that happened to me today
where the nurse or doctor's aid or whatever, she was like your heart rates too high
to do the test. So we got to give you this pill to slow it down. And I was like, okay. Yeah,
she goes, but your blood pressure is too low. And the pill is going to lower your blood pressure.
And they go, would he have made my blood pressure is too low? My doctor said,
elaborate. Yeah, my doctor said it was fine. And she's like, yeah, it's fine. It's just too low.
And again, who's on first? You get into this cyclical conversation and you're going,
the circle, like, oh, listen, miss. No, the doctor's name is low. Dr. John low.
Oh, no. No, no, is the nurse. Dr. Henrietta, no, it's so crazy. And I was just like, so wait,
so you're going to give me this IV now to, to raise my blood pressure. Right. So when you give me the
pill to lower my heart rate, which by the way, my heart rate was 75. But it has to be to get this
test in the 60s. I was like, who the hell's heartbeat is that low dead people? Yeah. So I'm just like,
this is insane. Like they didn't tell me any of this might be a thing. I don't know what you're
talking about. And then finally, you get to the, and she's like, can you ask your doctor? I go, you
want me to try to get my doctor on the phone? I could barely get the guy in the room when I have
an appointment. Yeah. Yeah. Do you think I'm just going to call him right now? I mean, it was insane.
And then finally, I like, I was so annoyingly, like, pestering with questions. She brought me
into the room to talk to the lady that run that, I guess was a doctor that she didn't tell me.
That's the other thing. Nobody gives you a title. I don't know what the hell anybody could have been
the damn janitor for all I know. You know, I got to tell you, sometimes whoever's taken my blood,
I'm like, do you work here? Because that, that's always like some person who has no credentials.
Sometimes they're in sweats, just like, yeah, hey, and they'll take 10 pints of blood. It's like,
you're not going to go feed that to a vampire somewhere. Are you? Yeah. Yeah. It's like, yeah, you're waiting
for like John Aston to come in and start checking your, yeah, somebody comes in like how did,
yeah, how did the super get in here? But they go, she takes me to the lady who does the test.
And then that lady was like, here's what's going on. And she explained all of it to me. And I was like,
okay, then fine, like, let's do it. But the lady, the other lady was like, she was like so cryptic.
And she just kept going like, I do whatever the doctor tells me. And I'm like, okay,
then I need to talk to the doctor like I don't understand what's happening here right now. Yeah.
It was fucking bad shit. In the end, they were all very sweet. We got it done. But it doesn't exactly make
you feel okay about when they go, like when it, like if I get the results and they go, you're fine.
You want to be like, did you definitely check everything? Are you sure it's my file you're looking at?
Right, right. Does this did not seem like a well -organized? Yeah.
You know, rack it when I was in there. Yeah.
Anyway, I went last night to see Roxy Music 50th anniversary tour.
I love this fucking band. And they there really are a true cult band. I mean, their big success was in
the 80s when I in my opinion, their way past their prime and making really pretty like elevator
music and stuff more than this. It's beautiful song. Don't get me wrong. But I love their early,
like, stuff with Brian Eno and their more punk shit and crazy shit and all sorts of weird influences
and everything. So they're all in pretty good health. They all sounded amazing. And like these are
old fucking men just jamming. And they did the really smart thing of bringing in a younger band behind
them who just fills out the sound because they're, they're going to do their thing. But it made it feel like
an orchestra or something was there. It was awesome show. St Vincent opened up. But
okay. Cool. I love St Vincent too. Yeah. The appeal really was I, and I recommend this to any other
lonely folks out there. Or if you, if you like a band who nobody else likes, nobody I know likes
rocks and music. Couple people maybe, but they couldn't go to the show. So day of the show I wake up
and if you type in you want one ticket, no matter how big the show, you will get, you can get the best
seat in the house for a very low price because it's usually rich people buy tickets for like eight
other friends. Four of them drop out. They don't care about the money. So they just start selling them
off as singles. Like, oh, for a hundred bucks, whatever. I had in my opinion, the best seat in the house
for rocks and music because the forum. I hate that the floor is not, there's no stadium seating.
So if you're in the back of the floor, you might as well just go home. I like to be elevated. I'm in
the perfect seat. There's two open seats next to me. And who climbs in? But
these Australian girls, one who I actually thought was Kate Beckinsale, the other who was discussing being a porn star.
And these girls were just like dancing. They were blowing bubbles at one point. Who was bubbles you
at? No, folks. They're blowing bubbles in the air. They're having a great time. Look, this doesn't
lead to me having a threesome with these people or something, but they could not have been sweeter.
And I think they sort of sense that I was just like a kind of sad guy there alone to watch this band
and just involved me, but also like new wind to leave me alone. And you know, just I had a great night.
And then in front of us, there is a point to this. There was a man look sort of like how Jack Black
starting to look now with the long gray flowing kind of wizard vibe, but age an extra 25 years.
You feel like maybe he was at the first Roxy music show. He was standing at the front of my section
had clearly done acid for the first time in a long time and was shooting like imaginary bolts of
lightning out of his hand and dancing and taking your shirt off and everything. And somehow I was not
high. I did not have a single drink. I just I found this to be a beautiful site. Normally,
that kind of thing would annoy me, but this was just a man having a great time. It made me feel like
I can still have fun as an old man, you know, this dude was there alone too. I almost went up to dance
with him at one point, but as I said, I wasn't drinking. Good for you to stick though to the regimen.
I see something like that when I'm not drinking. And I'm like, what am I doing?
Fucking yeah. No, I would start drinking. Yeah. No, I held it. And I, you know, I wish I had a
video to show you. I don't, but the thing is me and these girls all kind of instinctively get
our phones out because this guy was acting particularly crazy. And then all three of us were sort of like,
no, the man's having a free evening. We're going to sit here and film him without his permission.
And we put our phones away. There was a good sense of community. So all I'm saying is,
you know, I really didn't want to go to this show last night, even though I bought the tickets.
Sometimes you just buy a ticket. Yeah. I don't want to go to this fucking thing. Right here. But
you're always good to go for the most part to get out of your house, go interact with human beings.
It was good for the soul. I mean, a much better mood today than I was yesterday because of the
experience. So there you go. And I am too. I've been gotten my prodding and poking behind me.
Let's, uh, did you have to do the, uh, the curb thing or the easy money thing with the,
with the suction cups all over you? Yeah. Yeah. I had to do that. That's not a great look. No,
not the stress test, but I had to have those things on me. You didn't do the running on the treadmill
or whatever. No, that's the stress test. I didn't have to do that. Um, let's move to the movie corner.
Yeah. Geez. We're really, uh, burning a midnight time here today. All right. My movie corner
starts with, come on, baby. Bring it up. Bring it up. Show you, you got to start.
I only have two for this week. Um, okay. I'll do two too. The first is,
by the way, the Oscars are now talking about going to New Psycho or talking about going to streaming
because of their poor viewership. Uh, so they're talking now about doing a streaming only version
of the Oscars because nobody gives a shit. I mean, take it, take a hint, guys. Leave the party already.
Nobody cares anymore about this bullshit. End it. Um, anyway, that's, that's a quick new,
and there's nothing really more to talk about there. But, um, I got, uh, I did a rewatch of collateral.
Ooh, I love collateral. I loved it. The first time I saw it, I enjoyed the rewatch.
Doesn't age quite as well as some of the other Michael man stuff. I mean, look, it's, it's
crews at his best. It's Jamie Foxx at his best. It's, uh, Jada Pinkett at her best, like every,
it's roofalow at his bed. Everybody's at the top of their game in this thing. You got, you got,
I forgot having our bar dam is in it. Playing like that gangster. They go in the middle of the movie.
The best scene in the movie when, when that, that part, I get, it gives me chills when Jamie Foxx has
to go in and pretend he's Tom Cruz. Yeah. And he's like, I can't do this. And then he goes in and
gets his shit together and realizes like, it's all on the line. Right. And then he go, and then like,
there's that moment where he goes from being timid to where he turns it on and goes, he goes,
for the guys behind him with his, like, about to pull a gun out and he goes, tell your man to take
his hand off his gun before I take it and beat his bitch ass to death with it. And you're like,
it's such an awesome turn of the character. And then he starts regurgitating the Tom Cruz speech.
Right. Like you pivot, you adapt to whatever. It's awesome. It's, it's, that movie is awesome in many,
many ways. It's got a couple aspects to it where you're kind of like, all right, that's a little
corny. But I think all Michael man stuff does like he's, he's, he's always going to have that Miami
vice in him. But you know, it's a fun watch. And it does a really good job still of which is the
most important part of the movie. In somehow forging this, I'm very unlikely bond between these two
characters as much as Jamie Foxx hates Tom Cruz, as much as Tom Cruz or Jamie Foxx would kill the other guy
at the drop of a hat. If they got the chance, they're still like this weird bond there. And at the end,
when Tom Cruz is dying, Jamie Foxx makes sure he doesn't die alone. Like in a kind of sweet
interior. Tom Cruz is a monster. But it's a fun, it's a fun flick. It's worth a watch. And then,
and then, you know, noticeably shitty. Now I remember it being one of the first to actually just go
full, you know, iPhone almost look. Yeah. It looks, it's very, very obviously shot on video. Yeah.
Yeah. So, but it's worth the rewatch. I would, I've said many times, there should be a box set
for Michael man. And it should be thief, heat, and collateral. It should be a three, those are his three,
like straight up, like neo new war crime thriller movies. And there should be a box set of the three of
them. But there, there isn't. So black hat has its fans. I bought it real cheap. And I've never watched it.
Just, it's a, like a two and a half hour Chris Hemsworth movie. It's hard for me to get that excited.
But it has its fans. I, heavy did you, uh, did you finish heat too, by the way?
No, I'm still reading it because like an idiot, I started reading that. I started reading Stephen
King on writing. I started, I was still reading Legion in the middle of like four books. And then I started
two graphic novels. I started Batman 89 and, uh, and the Punisher first, um, but I'm like, I'm a mess.
I'm a mess. I'm a mess. And then I go to the store today and I buy the new creep show comic. I just,
it's, it's the intake is absurd. But no, heat too is still great. I just haven't finished it. Plus
the erotic western that you're writing. Yeah, that doesn't help. Which you've been writing for a long time, Joe.
Yeah. I, uh, my only note when I read the last draft was, where's the erotic question mark?
And I hope this next draft reflects more eroticism. Well, I've added a character who goes by the name
Six Shooter. Okay. Because he come. He's like Peter North. Like, like spurts a lot. Yeah, he has
multiple orgasms. And that, that seems to have spiced things up a bit. You know, Peter North never really
had a, he came up in a day before, uh, Viagra B. Oh, yeah. He, he came like that every fucking time.
That's why he was famous. But we've never seen his equal. We've never seen his air.
Even the guy who's catchphrase is dropping loads. He doesn't drop loads. Like Peter North did. No.
There's only one Sinatra. That's it. Like, you know, yeah, others can satellite around it. But you
don't, you don't get a second one. And Peter North has to be retired. I mean, he was old, he was old
for porn when I first encountered him when I was like nine. Yeah, he or if my mom's listening 24,
I've looked him up in recent years or months like, he doesn't act anymore. But he's, he seems
active. Like, he's got business. I, he seemed like he did all right for himself and he just doesn't
do porn anymore. Okay. That was my takeaway. He owns a Jersey Mike's franchise. Something like that.
Fastest growing franchise in the US. I've heard that. I think from you. You see, I keep waiting
for you to make me a cash offer, but you haven't done it yet. I, a friend of mine came over the other
night and just this malaise that we're talking about. It's like he comes over and immediately we were
both like we didn't really want to hang out. We could just tell. So he's like, let's watch a short
funny movie and then call it a night. We're just cranky. We, so we sit down and I go, let's watch
Lost in America. Now Lost in America, an all -time class. When I did my very short -lived sitcom,
when, which Joe was even more short -lived on, living good. Yes. There was a poster in the lead character,
Chip's apartment, of Lost in America. That's how much I love this movie. And I thought it was
thematically appropriate and it was free to use because it was in the Warner Brothers archives.
But Lost in America, I always thought it was just like this perfect comedy. I've seen it 10 times.
It makes me laugh so hard, but I forget every time that it completely falls apart after Vegas.
He doesn't, he doesn't not bother to write a third act. The third act is a quick joke of they go
back and suck up and after this big easy writer trip, they realize they prefer the corporate
line. Great little final joke, great little tag, final twist. It's not the third act of a movie.
So I guess I'm annoyed as I grow up and become more focused on structure of scripts,
which makes movies less enjoyable to watch. I hate that because I look at them technically.
I really do hate it. I lost something when I started getting into all the, you know,
the highest structure of screenplay and everything. But where was I, Joe?
What the fuck was I talking about? The third act falls apart. The third act falls apart.
I disagree. I don't, I think it, the Vegas stuff is so funny, but it's like the start of the adventure
it seems like and then it's just over. It's the Vegas, I think the problem is the Vegas thing plays
too big of a set piece. There's, there, there in Vegas for too long, like half the movie. Yeah,
it's a lot of Vegas, but, but after Vegas is when you get the whole movie, you get the, the scene
that defines the movie, which is the lecture and the RV about the, you've got a lot to say,
Death's Day ever again and all that stuff. Sure. But it's very rarely, and I, you know,
it reminded me a bit of, certainly of, you know, my father, maybe myself at times, but you'd rarely see
that portrayal of how mean spouses can be to each other. And this movie, it's just Albert Brooks.
He's just writing himself as the asshole. She did a very stupid thing, but he is so mean to her
and for such a long period of time that it goes past the point of funny almost to where it starts
to seem abusive in a, but that's what's kind of great about it. Sure. He's just like, he can't let it go,
he won't let it go. She knows he'll never let it go. That scene was added, which I think I mentioned
when I talked about it. Yes. Because people were like, he just forgives her. What?
Right. They wanted him to, to let her have it. Yeah. To me, Julie Haggerty is so sweet. And I have,
I love her so much that I think you sympathize with her regardless. And just because I love to gamble,
I know how you can get carried away. But it's a really great comedy. Don't get me wrong. And the stuff
when he is getting transferred to New York is like, I hate your suit, your song sucks. And I could
fight you. Or what was it? I could, I could hurt you. I could hurt you. Yeah. Yeah. That's
seems amazing. So many great laughs. That seems amazing. Yeah. Fuck you. And what I'm going to pretend
you didn't say that because I know you didn't mean it. Fuck you. What you might forget, Joe. And I
certainly had forgotten who I knew I remembered that it started with this bit, but not who it was.
The movie starts with almost five full minutes of none other than Rex Reed. Yep. Talking. And then
it goes over and he's being an idiot in the thing. He's talking about, I think it's really making fun
of Rex Reed. And he probably had an axe to grind with him. So he put his stupid interview in his
movie, very self indulgent and weird way to start loss in America. But that's the charm of the
movie. Like he makes movies that are unlike anybody else. Whereas it's not, to me, it's not even like
he's influenced by Woody Allen, you know, which I guess they were kind of peers more than anything else.
Albert Brooks was always doing his own thing. And he's just a total hero of mine. I was really
bummed out. I'm still bummed out that that's all Larry David came up with for him for that last
season of current. No, what a waste. I hope he comes back and lets them interact more. But anyway,
and Kightlinger, you know, I'd love to see. Yeah, it might have been you. Albert Brooks might have been
like, I don't want to, that's all I'll give you. Maybe I don't know. But like he does that with his
movies. He, well, I think modern romance is the masterpiece. And like, I agree and Stanley Kubrick
agrees. Yeah. And like he'll, but like he'll hang in something for what? That scene in modern
romance is like the Vega sequence. The, the, the, the, the, the, the Kuelude sequence. Yeah. Is like
the, and it's funny, but it goes on and on. Like of him, like walking back and forth on the Kuelude,
it's so much of the movie. And it's, you know, it, it serves its purpose, but it is a strange choice.
I'm trying to think of what the equivalent would be in, um, in, you know, he kind of does it in
the muzzle movie. Like such a huge part of the movie. And it's the funniest part is him bombing
at the show. Right. Like when he first gets overseas. And like it's such a huge part of the movie.
And then here's the crazy part with that. The routine he's doing is so absurd.
But then I looked it up and it was his routine. It was like what he used to do with standup.
But like when he did it back in the day, it was I, he was doing it. I wrote, he was like making fun of
this, this concept. But then in looking for comedy in the Muslim world, it's played like he doesn't
understand what funny is. Like, like, it's, it's a bit confusing. But I, I hope that we get, you know,
Woody Allen just announced his retirement and he's going out with a thriller, which is a bummer.
Uh, you're going to do one more, give us like a classic fucking whatever, but we're not getting it.
I hope Woody Allen, I mean, I hope Albert Brooks does another, I hope he does one more movie. Like,
I don't see it. I don't see it. I think that's it. But, you know, especially once he started kicking out
the novels, I was like, oh, no, he's found this other outlet. And by the way, I own the novel. I've,
I've owned it for 12 years. I never cracked the thing once critically acclaimed, never cracked the
thing once. It's my unfold. That was the end of, uh, of, uh, Gene Wilder. He started writing novels.
And that was, yeah, never made another movie ever again. Yeah. Uh, you know what? I got nothing else
for the corner. I was, I'm going to save my other one because it kind of goes with some other stuff
I've been watching. I like to be thematic. Okay. In the corner. Um, yeah, all, all I got to check
off was the Indian runner, which I had always wanted to see Sean Penn's directorial debut.
And it's a song, it's a movie based on the song Highway Patrolman, the Bruce Springsteen song,
which is like a 220 length song. And the movie is of course 127 minutes.
It is very actory because of course it's Sean Penn directing. So it's like a young David Morse,
a young Vigo Mortensen, a young Patti Arquette. You got Chuck Branson in the mix playing like a rare
dramatic role where he's not beating anybody's ass. I had to be right at the, toward the end, right?
It was towards the end, yes. Um, so basically, you know, it's that's the cane enabled story. One
brother is good. One brother is bad. Uh, I thought the movie was pretty painfully boring. It might
have been a nice little actor showcase at the time. It's got a real good reputation for some reason,
but I think for a while there, everybody thought Sean Penn was Danero. And now I think everybody
thinks of him as a clown, but it was a great actor for a while. I think he's a pretty solid director.
But he's done better stuff than this, the Indian runner. Now let's talk about our movie at hand,
which is Joseph Walker's crimes of the future. As I was writing the description for today's episode,
I mean, how to even write a description of this movie? I, well, description for our episode today,
I said, the only crime of the future would be if somebody made us watch this movie again. I,
I just hope I never have to watch this movie again. I was so excited to see it. I really was. I was
like, wow, David Kronenberg, because I, you know, I know he was doing those sort of crime dramas for a
while, whatever you want to call him. And those are fine, but it doesn't excite me when I hear David
Kronenberg is going to make like a gangster movie with Vego Mordz. I don't care. I get excited when
David Kronenberg does Kronenberg shit when he does horror. And the fly is in my top horror movies ever,
ever of all time. So I would argue, I always say that exorcist is the scariest movie of all time. I
actually think I'm changing my mind and saying, I actually think it's the fly because it's so
scary to think of going through that. But yeah, it sticks with you that move. Yeah. But you know,
it's like Kronenberg going back to body horror, sci -fi horror, naming the movie after one of his
early short films, like a pretty shitty short film I must say. Yeah, I just, I was excited for
this. And you know, the trailer, I was like, yeah, it's like kind of bad CGI, but they'll probably fix
it, which they didn't know. Somebody ran out of money somewhere. It says here online that the budget
was $27 million. No way in hell. Right. No way in hell. And then it made 4 .5. So a massive loss.
They're not going to let him make a movie again if that's the case. It doesn't look, that money
wasn't on the screen, that 27 mil. No. I mean, it's shot in like, you don't got to pay the guy from
Felicity, 27 mil. Who's the guy from Felicity? Scott Speedman, the guy who plays like the
the organ hacker or whatever the guy with the son. Okay. Good looking guy. I think the man of the
streets. I mean, it's like, yeah, this thing is shot the way a student film is shot when you want to
make a student film about the future. You're like, excuse me, you're like, okay, we'll shoot it in
warehouses. Yeah. With no furniture. And we'll have everybody wear like thermals. So you can't tell
what year it is. They also, they do some of it on sets that look worse than multicam sets. Honestly,
there are some of these like organ harvesting rooms or whatever. The sets are so cheap looking.
Now the devices and shit, I guess that's where a lot of the money went. They're all pretty cool looking
and weird. But I thought the world that was in was so drab and boring and shitty looking,
that it was hard to even look at. The entire movie to me looked like he went back to the set of naked
lunch and cobbled together things from naked lunch to make these new things and then just shot it
there. Like, and that was it. Like, it felt way more akin to naked lunch to me than it did to like
any of his horror movies. Right. The plot of this is that it's the future. We don't know how far
into the future. People are, I get people have for people have lost the ability to feel pain.
And people are also also growing organs that they shouldn't have. So some people are embracing
that others aren't. But because of this inability to feel pain anymore, surgery has become art.
And they're doing like body and it has also become the new sex, which they say 5 ,000 times in the movie
that surgery is the new sex. They say surgery is the new sex 5 ,000 times. They equate art to pain
5 ,000 times. They hammer down your throat that Vigo Mortensen is an artist and the thing his art
grows inside of him literally as tumors and organs that he is body is rejecting that he has to
birth and give to the world because his pain is the art. It's like it's so fucking heavy handed.
It's like and Cronenberg his whole thing used to be letting you sort of figure shit out even in his
most commercial movies like the fly you or even scanners or something a lot is left to you the viewer.
And you know, they're very kind of cerebral you work with him kind of you're figuring it out
it you know video drums the same way. But this is really like spoon feeding to a point where it does
get obnoxious coming from a guy who didn't used to have to do that. I don't know why he thinks he
does have to do that. I don't get it. It also then becomes this thing. It also becomes this thing where
where the people that have get in this of this
reveal happens later in the film. But you find out that the people that are embracing this evolution
of the human body the only thing they can eat without suffering pain because that's the one way they
can feel pain still is is by eating like normal food. I guess so then they eat this like version of
food that still like has to be like when they eat it all has to be calibrated with like vibrations
in a special chair because that's the only way you can digest things. Right which as as Joe very
had a very funny tweet about with I mean a lot of the movie is watching Vigo Mortensen try to swallow
clop and that's a lot of the movie and gagging and choking on it. He's doing this terrible I mean
it literally sounds like an impression of dark man. It sounds like Liam Neeson's voice and dark man
and he's dressed like Liam Neeson and dark man through the entire movie because he's so sick he has
to cover everything when he goes outside. So he's got the thing over it only his eyes are exposed. He's
really pale. It looks like it sounds like dark man. Yeah. And then he so then you learn that the
people that are embracing this evolution of the body can only digest plastic and then somebody wrote to
me on Twitter like as I was getting into that part of the movie like fuck that movie like oh there's
plastic in our food it's fucking obvious. I was like oh yeah I guess it is really that's another
just like terribly heavy -handed thing. Right um I outside of of a very tight commentary about
our food becoming plastic and art hurts the artist. I don't see what any fucking point of this movie
is. I think it was so dumb. It was just terrible man. I hated this fucking movie. I hated it. And then
it's and it's the kind of disturbing at times where it made me mad where I'm like I don't need to see
like a guy dancing with ears 20 ears all over his body. I don't need to see like this French I
freight the French actors actresses name but I need to see her. Yeah. Licking Vigo Mortensen's
like wound. This is like when Kronenberg did like crash and you're like buddy relax take a
week off. I like crash quite a bit but this felt that felt new and this felt exactly like what you're
saying him rehashing crash or recrashing if you will but I thought this felt like a lot of
warmed up left over Kronenberg. If it I liked it more when I thought that it cost $2 million
which is how it looks. If it actually cost $27 million I hate this movie because what a waste.
I thought he did some cool little low budget fun jaunt. Yeah regardless it's not super entertaining
there are though a lot of Kronenberg visuals. It had been a while since he had made a movie
and on that level and as a completist I've seen all the guys movies. I was like all right check that
one off but it felt very much like to compare somebody we were just talking about seeing a new
Woody Allen to make kind of like a guy trying to pull the same old tricks they're just not working
as well anymore. Mortensen must just be visuals. Vigo must just be like if you're doing it I'm in.
Clearly because what who would want to play a part where the whole time you're gagging exactly
it's just like why would that yet ever be a part you would want to do? I thought it was cool
that like I like the evolution of Kristen Stewart I like that she's you know she's in she's she and
Robert Pattinson are very similar in the sense that like they kind of keep evolving farther and farther
away from the twilight thing that launched them like getting away from being these like teeny
bopper heartthrob stars whatever. I thought it was came with Taylor Lautner. What became? I like
that she was in this. I was like well that's cool and I just feel bad for her that it's fucking shit
movie yeah um it ends with oh it ends with so Vigo Mortensen is against eating the plastic
because he's like fuck you I'm not going to give into this evolution I will not embrace it I will
keep taking these things that are growing in me outside of my body and then finally in the end he
eats the plastic and it's happy it and it smiles and that's how it ends and it's an ending you see
from a mile away um yeah you sucks it sucks it sucks it sucks it had a vibe to me of like going to see
a David Kronenberg Broadway play where it was just like yeah all right you know
it felt very stagy and theatrical both in its acting and in its sets uh I don't know I I will say hearing
that it costs 30 million dollars changed my whole perception of it if it was just a cheap riff with
some friends because he's you know he's done movies with Kristen Stewart and Vigo then I get it
but if he really got that much money together to make this script then he then he should stop making
movies and give some money to your son who made a much better movie than this called possessor I
still haven't seen that it was good and he still to my knowledge hasn't made a second movie I hope he
I hope he hasn't I'm wrong but possessor is amazing I think done one or two things Kronenberg's got
another movie in the works I believe uh I'm just looking it up right now all right filmography yeah
the shrouds okay who knows I mean he's you wrote that one Dean Arcoons
and there's no Wikipedia link but it was a computer shroud he's a little off his game maps to the stars
was kind of yeah not for me that one although maybe a revisit that's interesting he worked with
Robert Pattinson I forgot that movie saw Cosmopolus and that has its fans too all right actually on a
revisit um existence kind of sucks too he's been off it was spider good spiders I didn't care for him
now so he he had three bangers with history of violence eastern promises and a dangerous method like
those were all pretty well received if I'm not mistaken correct the first two way better than
dangerous method that movie was just about spanking care nightly yeah but he's been off his
and it should have been called spanking care nightly um I look I hope he I hope he comes back to
whatever you know I don't know uh hope he comes period so he can finally make a movie about something
else yeah just for once let him come into an aliens vagina shape wound
so that he can heal whatever's damaged in him and move on to another topic because it's getting a
little old I'm really over this is about sex as a fill in the blank right I don't give a shit anymore
I don't care anymore we all like fucking go make a porn oh movie and shoot people fucking if that's
what you want to talk about like you know this this thing where it's like no I'm making a higher version
no you're not like right you're talking about sex like that's that's what it is and nobody
like there's nothing like hot or erotic about seeing sex shoved into like blood and guts like
it's just fucking weird and gross like I don't enjoy it I know I'm done I don't want to see it anymore
all right anyway hogged down majorly down uh yeah yeah hogged down here too although I think
a little higher up than Joe um I will say we are going we're definitely going to do the new hell
razor oh yeah and I think that's dropping in the next week or so um how are you sure I'm gonna see
bros Joe if you're gonna see bros my new bros the return of the comedy you know I don't not want to see
bros I just got so much on the palette right now for October I don't know if I'll be able to
and we're seeing some stuff because you guys sometimes want to know I mean we're at some point
going to do pearl watch it pearl we're at some point going to do speak no evil which is a terrible
title for a film um but it's on shutter and then what else do we discuss I would say look I would
say without question October will contain pearl it will contain hell razor and it will contain
barbarian and barbarian yes I would say those are a safe three and then the fourth slot could
go to anything I mean I mean I'm I I'm not gonna ask you to sit through the monsters uh but
god no I'll do the monsters I'll do the monsters it's because I want to we also talked about pearl or
would it not pearl uh blonde right what's it called blonde blonde people won't shut the fuck up
about this movie I mean I'm like my god guys and see 17 always gets them in a tizzy that's why
they rate movies and see 17 for the city he said it took two and a half hours to transform her into
Marilyn Monroe what what did you transfer you put a wig on her I don't understand what you had to do
what did you have to do personally anyway we'll be back next time folks thank you so much we'll see you
next time and we'll see you and hell
you