Folks, it's we'll see you in hell.
It's time to get down.
It's time to talk about movies.
Joe DeRosa here and Patrick Walsh here.
Welcome folks.
We're going to be talking to you about Christopher Nolan's depressed stage.
Uh, that's my Michael Caine.
Chris Nolan's got Oppenheimer coming out this summer.
Yes.
I know everyone's real excited to me.
The trailer looks about as boring as shit, but, uh, I'll be there.
I love Christopher Nolan movies.
Yeah, I'm surprised.
They're putting a $300 million picture on the back of, uh, what's his face.
What do they call that guy?
Red eye.
Peaky blinders.
It's Billy and Killian Murphy.
Billy and Murphy.
Yeah.
I never know how to pronounce it.
Killian, they call it Killian, like Killian's red beer.
Wait, he's the star of Oppenheimer.
He's playing Oppenheimer.
Yeah.
Like I know that Peaky blinder show is big, even though I've never seen it, but
he's, he's an odd choice to lead your huge budget movie, I think.
Well, he's a Nolan alumni.
Um, but also to, I feel like Nolan's at that point where he's like a Spielberg.
It's like, it almost doesn't matter who's leading the movie anymore.
Like, yeah, he's the star.
Same with Tarantino, which is weird though, that Tarantino is doing the
same thing as Scorsese getting DiCaprio for every movie he does now.
Yes, man.
DiCaprio.
He's supposed, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Just, um, jackpot.
That kid hit the jackpot.
Yeah.
He gets to work with whoever he wants and, and rightfully so, rightfully so.
Uh, he opens the pictures.
He's talented.
He's attractive.
Killers of the flower moon, which I assume we'll be doing, uh, getting rave reviews, man.
Yeah, I'm excited.
I'm going to attempt to read the book, uh, before the picture comes out for hours.
I'm excited about that.
I wonder why, I guess, because Scorsese is Mr.
Film, but like, I wonder if it wouldn't have been more appealing to let him
direct 10 episodes of this thing.
Uh, give us a 10 hour picture from Scorsese at the end of his career.
You know, I don't need 10 hours.
I don't need four, but we're going to have it.
Yeah.
Then you like the three and a half of, uh, the Irishman Joe.
I love the Irishman.
Uh, that's a special, special case for me.
I mean, the deck was pretty stacked on that one, but, uh, you know, people, I
was in a recording session the other day and some of the other actors were, were
saying, uh, they were like, you know, this, this last season of succession, it
just hasn't been that good.
And I don't know.
It's okay.
It's been okay, but like, it's not as good as I had hoped.
And they're kind of tying things up too quickly and they've
got too much to get through.
And I was thinking like, yeah, cause that's what happened.
These, these shows with this, we're going to do 13 episode seasons and we're going
to do each episode is an hour and nine minutes.
You're like, it's too much cutting down.
It's just too much.
I mean, succession is your standard 10.
And I feel like people keep, people who keep saying they have so much to wrap
up, it's that's not that kind of a show.
Each week they, they argue about finances.
They backstab each other.
You know, there's big personal things happening, uh, in this final season,
some deaths and so forth.
But what do you, what do you think they have left to tie up?
I never understand people's criticisms.
I'm like, just enjoy the show and shut up.
They weren't mad about it.
They just were saying the air in the room was, was one guy said it.
And then everybody else was like, thank you.
I feel like I haven't been allowed to say this to anybody.
Look, I, I enjoy succession every week.
This final season has not, not involved me at all.
You know, people keep talking about how, oh, that last night's episode destroyed
me to my core or whatever.
I haven't had that experience, but I think it's a entertaining program for a
peep show as far as that guy's work goes.
But who doesn't?
Yeah.
Can we get a, can we get a new, or we are getting a new, who's in it?
Who's in the new peep show?
Oh, that's how we feel or something.
Mini driver, you know, who you'd expect to be in it.
Wait, no, is it really, are you joking?
Thousand percent.
Wait, you're serious or a thousand percent.
You're joking.
Is leading the American version of peep show.
When I reached out to you to tell you about it, that's what we talked about.
Mini driver.
It's for FX.
It stars mini driver and someone named a mom blood Jehovah.
I mean, there's your confusing lead today.
Not that Killian Murphy is leading.
That's look, I couldn't agree.
Could not agree more.
Um, let's see here.
It's from Stephanie Robinson who writes for Atlanta and what we do in
the shadows to quality shows.
Great.
Love it.
Um, and okay.
The leads in this version are both female.
Secondly, they are workplace peers, not fighting flatmates.
Jehovah plays a long suffering assistant to drivers, emotionally
unstable tech entrepreneur.
It's already not the same show.
Yeah.
It's just a completely different show.
I imagine the only thing they're using is the four, the format of
talking to the camera, basically.
Why not get, if you're going to do this, right?
Maybe they tried.
You get, you get the broad city girls, you get Garfunkel and oats.
How good would Garfunkel and oats be at peep show?
It'd be amazing.
Like get, get a comedy duo.
That's what made the original so good.
Mitchell and Webb were a comedy dude.
There was like a chemistry there.
Yeah.
You know, get two of the women from the black lady sketch show.
You know what I mean?
Like get, like get two women who are in comedy that have worked together,
that have a vibe and a chemistry.
Maybe, maybe these two are dynamite together.
I don't know.
I don't even know who one of them is.
Um, as for many driver, I find her delightful in a gross point blank
and goodwill hunting.
I don't know that I've seen her in much else circle of friends back in the day.
I loved many driver 22 years ago when I last saw her in a crippling drama about
child rape called sleepers.
I've never seen her do anything sort of funny.
Well, uh, gross point blank, gross point blank.
She's fine.
I like, I do remember people walking out of gross point blank at the weekend.
It premiered in my hometown, slapping their knees saying that many driver.
Boy.
He's a good romantic foil in that film and she's laughs of her own.
She's great.
I'm not, I'm not discrediting her talent.
I just don't understand when you get, they did this, they made this mistake
already with our dear friend, Johnny Galecki.
They tried to redo the American peep show and like it didn't work.
And it's like, I just don't get what it's like.
You have a formula in front of you that works.
You, you watch it.
Perfectly works.
Yeah.
For nine seasons, you say we want to do that again, except in America.
Okay.
Maybe you take the it's like going, man, do I love that chicken parmesan over in
Rome, let's make it in America, except with ham and American cheese and no
sun, you're like, make it with the same ingredients sort of.
I think every remake attempt of this has gone for making it an office
sitcom, which is odd because as you're saying, why veer from while it works,
but they do it all the time.
Um, it doesn't really matter now because we are still on strike.
And I heard yesterday that the prediction is December that it will be over,
which would be seven, eight months.
Now I don't know if that's true, but it's certainly looking pretty
bleak at this moment in time.
Does it affect you in New York?
Is there picketing going on in New York, Joe?
I see it on, on the, the news, I guess.
I hear, I hear pray tell of picketing.
I haven't seen any, a friend of mine went over to the picket site
yesterday and said, nobody was there.
I feel like, I feel like you're in the WGA.
Why aren't you walking the line?
Drag on.
I'm sorry.
I'm just, I'm dealing with other issues like, uh, needing a rat
in the city.
I live in and, uh, being recently burglarized.
Yeah, sure.
Sure.
Uh, you know, I'm being burglarized too by the studios.
I support the WGA a thousand percent.
I don't think that with, I say this very respectfully to my own industry.
I do not think that picketing will do a goddamn thing.
Uh, but I think it's a nice demonstration and I, I support the
cause and I think the industry itself is despicable.
And I hope that they get fucked in every way possible, but unfortunately
I don't think that will be the case.
And I don't think that in any case ever really does much.
It's just kind of a thing for press.
They'll have to give up something at some point, but yeah, it sucks.
I have been picketing and the other day I sort of realized how antiquated
and sort of ridiculous it is, even though I have enjoyed doing it.
And it gives you a good feeling of solidarity and connecting with other
writers and talking about your issues and stuff, but, um, this guy comes running
over because I learned three days into picketing, we're supposed to be
blocking cars from entering the lot.
However, we're all just told to move when the cars get there, like you keep
them from entering the lot for about five seconds, maybe, and then they just go.
So this, this guy comes running over and he's like, everybody put your signs down.
These are allies that are trying to get on the lot.
So all of us in the picket line had to put our signs down so that they were
touching the sidewalk and then the teamsters could enter the lot because
that meant they were no longer crossing a picket line, but we had to do the
symbolic dropping of the signs.
And it's like, guys, this stuff is from like the Jimmy Hoffa days, you know,
like we don't at least explain to us what all this shit means.
Yeah.
One of the, one of the license plates driving by you says net prez.
These are allies.
Get out of the way.
Hulu boss with like, yeah, sunglasses on the, Oh, um, it's, it sucks.
It, uh, you know, we're out there, everybody kind of knows, yeah, this
might not be, uh, making a difference per se picketing, but at least it shows
that we care and we're out there.
What I hate that the guild has been doing is theme picket days and costume
days, and I am actually going to send a letter to somebody and tell them
that I don't think that's right.
We're entering a negotiation with people who wear suits to work and have a
billion dollars and you got somebody dressed as Wonder Woman and somebody
dressed as a witch out on the picket line.
I think it's ridiculous.
It is nothing would turn me away.
I said this in the room when we, in the same room where we were discussing
succession, we were also discussing the strike and I said, nothing would turn
me away from a cause faster than a chant.
They were talking about some of the chants that were happening.
Here's the thing.
I'm glad you brought up Jimmy Hoffa.
That's when picketing, that's what picketing was.
That's when it worked.
When picketing meant we will literally obstruct your thing
from working and functioning.
Right.
Yeah.
You don't get out of the way for anybody.
And if the cops show up, we're going to fight them.
Like that's like what, that's what picketing, that's when picketing was
something, this thing of like organized, uh, uh, diplomatic picketing.
It's pointless.
It's, it's, I guess it's again, it's good for some press, but there's no
difference between doing that and everybody just sitting home and not going
to work.
What's the difference?
You don't go to work.
They also, they, we go to, we go to gates that are pre -approved by the studio.
So like, let's say we're going to CBS Radford where they did Seinfeld, uh, and
NBC's outsourced, which I worked on equal, equal, um, quality and popularity
shows and they'll say like, Hey, Radford will only let us pick it at this one
gate.
And I'm like, Radford will only let us pick it.
Like what, what is this?
Well, um, not shitting on the cause.
And I've been out there three days a week since it started.
I get, I get it.
I like it.
I enjoy doing it.
I'm just saying, um, I wish we could bring back a little of that sort of fire
Joe's talking about where at least you, you know, you had to, you could stand for
maybe five minutes before letting somebody go through or something, make
some impact, but we just really, a car pulls up and it's like right this way,
sir.
And I'm not sure what we're doing.
Here's your other problem.
Yes.
And this happened with Occupy Wall Street.
You go down and you try to pick it for real and really block the doors.
And what happens is you start fucking overworking people that have nothing to
do with it.
So like, like you're saying, you try to get out of the way for the teamsters or
whatever.
It's like, you know, what happened in New York was there was like small shop
owners, like the guy that owns the deli at the bot, you know, on the ground floor
of the wall street building that they're protesting can't open his deli business
cause there's all these people in the way.
And then the attitude in New York during that was, Hey, sorry, man, it's
casualties of war.
And then that's fucked up too.
So my point is, is everybody agree on a cause and stay home, enjoy yourself.
Why are you suffering twice during a strike?
You should be, the strike should be like on King of Queens where they're like,
they're like running around town, having a great time together because they can't
go to work, you know, like enjoy your strike, put your feet up.
Um, I hear you.
I hear you.
I, I think when we'll finally start to make a difference and start, uh, rocking
the boat is right now the AM it's called the AMPTP.
That's the studios.
They are currently negotiating with the DGA.
They never finished negotiating.
That's the director's guild of America.
They never finished negotiating with the writer's guild because they gave us a
shitty offer after they're done with the director's guild, they start negotiating
with sag, the screen.
Yeah, it's, it's pretty fucked at this point.
Like if all three of these guilds say, I'm sorry, guys, the offer you're giving
us sucks and we can't accept it.
And the three guilds strike, that's never happened in the history of Hollywood,
the a hundred plus year history of Hollywood, where all three
guilds go on strike together.
If we unite and that happens, they're done.
They can't just air, you know, dating, dating with no face or whatever
Netflix reality show they got.
Um, they're going to be fucked at a certain point.
If we pull actors, writers and directors, but we need everybody to do it.
So we'll see.
Yeah, they're, uh, they're, yeah, it's what a mess.
I mean, look, everything is, you know, let's not go down that road, but
have you seen dating with no face on Netflix?
Dating with no face.
Yeah.
It's just people that don't have any facial features, uh, hooking up.
Is that what it really is?
I wouldn't be surprised.
You believed it.
Do we, you know, no, what does dating with no face mean?
I just made it up.
I was, I was, I was picturing two people without faces, like kissing, and it
was creeping me out and I had to share the thought the blank, remember the
blank in the Dick Tracy movie Madonna at the end.
Yeah, exactly.
I do remember that.
Um, Joe, I thought of a joke that you might like while I was, uh, at the
grocery store the other day.
Okay.
Uh, um, George Clooney's got his brand of tequila Casamigos.
Brian Cranston and Aaron Paul have their brand of tequila dos hermanos.
When is Liam Neeson going to give us Qui -Gon gin?
I like the joke.
I think you should do a different liquor for the second one.
I think the first one should be tequila.
So absolutely.
Danny DeVito has, but I don't know, Dan DeVito has limoncello.
Okay, sure.
I can call it whatever I thought of it as I was logging on this morning.
And I was like, nobody has a vodka.
Nobody has a whiskey to my knowledge.
So I just went with two tequilas, but you're right.
Could have gone limoncello.
I have actually tried a batch of, uh, DeVito gave us all
bottles of limoncello.
It's delicious.
Yeah.
Limoncello is always great.
Um, I thought of a bit for a script maybe you could use.
This is true.
Mike, my friend Brian was telling me yesterday, he gave his uncle an
edible and his uncle hit his uncle so hard his uncle had to lay down on
the wood floor during dinner.
Okay.
And I said, uh, you're, you, the scene should be your wife is standing
over your uncle as he stares up at the ceiling and he goes, Jesus Christ,
the ceiling won't stop moving.
And she goes, the ceiling's not moving.
And he says, don't tell me I'm the one laying on it.
There you go.
Yeah, that's good.
That's good.
It's okay.
We're working it.
It's a good little sitcom bit, right?
Oh, I like it.
We'll get it there.
More innocent, more of an innocent kind of sitcom, but you know, I don't
think you put that on the Miss Pat show.
You'd have to be like, you smoked crack or something.
No, this would be like a free form.
Yeah.
Family sitcom for sure.
I was, um, talking with Joe.
So there is no show called dating without a face.
However, there's a show, uh, milf manor.
Yep.
Which everyone said, you know, comes right from 30 rocks, milf Island, which
used to be like a wildly satirical joke 10 years ago, but milf manner is, uh,
you know, moms who are, it's, it's a bunch of sons and their moms and there's
like fucking going on and moms feeling abs and trying to decide whose abs
belong to their son and all sorts of bizarre challenges and things are getting,
things are seeming more and more fake basically.
And I texted Joe the other day, one of my new favorites, which is what is, or
what am I eating with Zoe Deschanel?
What am I eating with Zoe Deschanel?
And it's a picture of Zoe like thinking like, what am I eating?
That's a new show on HBO max, which of course is now called just max.
Um, we're doing that by the way, that was, that was made when we still had writers.
That wasn't something that was thrown together over the strike.
So who knows what disaster shows are coming our way?
Um, Zoe Deschanel eating a sandwich and going like, it's a sandwich.
That's a show now.
That's a show.
Um, one of the stars Joe can't get his sitcom about a guy with edibles laying
on a hardwood floor on the air.
It's not fair.
Hard.
Well, the title might be the problem.
It's called hardwood and, uh, they suggest that I change it.
And I've said, I'll walk, uh, one of the stars of milf manner.
I'm learning just now is, uh, Lisa Wilcox of nightmare and Elm street fame.
She plays Alice in parts four and five.
She's one of the milfs.
Yeah.
I guess later in the game, she's one of the milfs, but anyway, she, uh, I met
Lisa at, uh, when I first started in comedy 20 odd years ago, one of the
first road gigs I ever did was in Jersey at a Hilton where there was a comedy
club and she was there because the hotel was also hosting a horror convention.
Uh, I met a lot of my horror heroes at that.
I met Robert England.
I hung out with Michael Berryman from the Hills have eyes.
I hung out a little bit with Sid Hague.
I met Doug Bradley, actually made Doug Bradley laugh, which was cool.
Uh, um, but anyway, I met Lisa Wilcox.
I think she came to my show.
No, no, no, uh, he, he laughed almost as if he resented laughing.
It was one of those guys where it's like, he's not going to give it to you easy.
Um, anyway, I met Lisa, I think she came to my show.
I remember the evil dead, the women, the women that started in the original evil
dead movie came to my show and they were very sweet.
Um, but then Lisa Wilcox, I met, I think she came to my show too.
She was very nice, but I remember being like, holy shit, she is smoking hot,
which was weird because I never thought that Alice was hot in the movies.
And I guess that's kind of the point of the character.
She starts like sort of homely and then becomes like this, like female,
like beautiful warrior, like that's kind of the transition of part of the,
the physical transition of the character.
Right.
But, so I'm not surprised as my point that she's on MILF
manner, uh, cause she was a MILF then.
Well, it says here, uh, in the pilot alone on the guys, the sons show
off how much they really know about what mature women want between the sheets.
And in front of their mothers, uh, her son, Ryan gets the moms all worked up as
he demonstrates his oral sex skills on an orange placed between a female
dummy's thighs, Wilcox says she's dated men 27 years her junior and explains
that she believes younger men are better in the bedroom because older men
have an insecurity about them.
It's kind of annoying.
Well, she's 59 lease.
I'm 45, babe.
Let's get it going here.
I'm, uh, I'm entering my sexual peak, Lisa.
So come on by, I have a different sort of, uh, yeah, go ahead.
What is a guy's sexual peak?
Isn't it like 18 and a woman's is like 40.
Mine has never, mine's never ended since I was about 14.
I can't turn it off.
I don't know what's going on.
I'd like to be released from this prison at this point.
I have a similar drive.
My friends were always like, yeah, you know, I just don't have any drive anymore.
It's actually kind of a relief.
And I'm like, yeah, I'd love some relief.
I still, they also say weed's supposed to dampen it.
I still wake up hard as fuck every day.
Sorry.
Sorry to say, um, Joe, let's go to that movie corn.
Why not?
Yeah.
Just a quick new psycho though.
And I don't want to get into spoilers.
I haven't read any, but God damn it, man.
Indiana Jones is not getting great reviews and I'm really, I'm like
legitimately depressed about it.
I mean, all I saw was one of those ridiculous 10 minute con film festival
standing ovations and Harrison Ford was in tears and I found it very moving.
So I thought everyone liked it, but maybe everything out of con was like,
it's better than crystal skull.
It's great.
It's a fitting ending, dah, dah, dah, dah.
But now all the American, not the American, but like the, the, the top
critic reviews right now and rotten tomatoes have it at a 50%, which is
the lowest score ever for an Indiana Jones movie that is 27 % lower than.
Here's the weird part.
Crystal skull is at 77 % critic score.
It's at a much lower audience score.
So I'm like, okay, maybe this is the opposite now.
Maybe this will be a lower critic score, higher audience score, and it'll
actually be a cooler movie than it's being represented as being.
I don't know.
I feel like, I feel like, I feel like Ford's an easy tar.
I feel like this franchise and Harrison Ford are an easy target
for critics to kind of now try to get back.
Yeah, look, critics for a while now have been, and I want to be careful how I
say this, they've, they've clearly given passes to a lot of things that aren't
that good because they're too afraid.
They're going to get called like sexist or something like that.
Uh, and I think they want to kind of talk about, and I'm not saying all of it.
I'm just saying there are things where that's happened.
And I feel like this is finally the white, straight, male enough thing
coming out of Disney in the last few years that they can really shit on to
get all the stuff they didn't say about these other movies out of their system.
Uh, I might be wrong about like, about like Shang -Chi or, or whatever it was,
whatever, yeah, and I might be wrong.
And then also too, it's not all critics.
Uh, uh, Hollywood reporter gave it a glowing review.
Variety kind of said it sucked.
The worst I've read though, is that people are saying it's just, it's fine.
It just doesn't live up to Indiana.
Nobody is coming out and saying, this is bad because they're just saying like,
it's just like, you don't care.
Like, and I'm like, well, I'll care.
Right.
I might try to watch all four this weekend.
I haven't seen Crystal Skull since the theater, but I do think American
film criticism is at its all time lowest point.
If they're paying the people who write movies and television shows in a very
fucked up way, uh, critics are getting critics never got anything.
I used to go to see a midnight show on a Thursday night of the new movie.
I remember driving the reason I quit reviewing movies was I had to drive to
see a midnight showing of mad money starring Diane Keaton, Queen Latifah,
and somebody else, a terrible film.
And you would go at midnight to see the movie, write your review at like 2 a .m.
to get it printed Friday morning and you would make $50.
And I think that that money has gone even lower.
You know, talk about AI being a problem.
AI is definitely going to start entering the critic world because they'd rather
control the reviews that are being written anyway.
So it's, um, it's a bad time.
Like there's no critic right now that I go to.
I used to go, what, what did Ebert say and read Ebert's review?
Um, I've had, I've had various, there used to be people at the onion AV club
that I would read everything they wrote.
There's no one there anymore.
Most of these people have realized they can't sustain a life being a critic of
film or television.
So that's why, you know, when my buddy was like, Hey, is air any good?
I was like, I thought it sucked.
And he sends me a picture of the a hundred percent rotten tomatoes score.
I'm like, yeah, that doesn't mean anything anymore.
So to me, that doesn't mean it doesn't as a matter of fact, one of the movies
I'm going to review in the movie corner, the whale, which, but if you just looked
at the press clips and the footage, meaning the video footage, um, and the
Oscar and all that stuff, you would go, Oh my God, this movie swept the world
and everybody loved it rotten.
It's got like a 67 % or something.
Yeah.
Like so multiple Oscar nominations.
So I don't know what's going on anymore.
I also think in the end, it's interesting to me that this new Indiana Jones has
exactly a 50 right now it's at a 51 % because I do think this is right up the
middle where half the people that watch it are going to say Hollywood, ain't
what it used to be.
This harkens back.
This reminds me of a time when movies were X, Y, and Z.
I love this.
Yeah.
And the other half are going to go, I'm tired of praising these old things.
This is bullshit.
I'm over it.
Do something new.
Fuck your D aging, all this stuff and blah, blah, blah.
Um, one of the new reviews says, and again, I'm trying to stay away from.
Spoilers, but it just says it hits Vokes or Vox, whatever the, I'm not
going to read the review, but the review headline says Indiana Jones on the
dial destiny reminds you how much Hollywood has changed the new Indiana
Jones movie hits different in the IP age.
I'd be curious to read that review after the fact, but I think that's
speaking to what I'm talking about.
Yeah.
Where it's like, look, we live in a different time and you're either going
to like, this is either going to stir something up in you that you don't see
anymore in a movie and you're going to enjoy that or you're going to go.
I mean, honestly, I think it's why Spielberg moved away from doing action
and is now into doing these dramas of all kinds, because I think he was like,
I'm not going to make the negotiator, you know, or fast five or 10 where the
fuck it is now.
So anyway, yeah, I mean, I got it.
I got a date Sunday night classic dinner in a movie and I looked at the
list of movies and we were like, maybe we won't see one.
It's the little mermaid reboot fast and the furious 10 guardians of the galaxy
three about my father, Sebastian Maniscalco, which apparently is not.
It looks bad.
It does, but it's getting decent reviews.
It's it's apparently it is kind of funny.
Little mermaids, the machine with Chrysler, they were, they were released
two movies starring comedians at like the same level on the same weekend.
Makes no sense.
I, but you're not going to take a date to see the machine.
I like Bert, but you're not going to take a date to the machine.
I think the machine actually looks like a funny action comedy.
It might be.
Yeah.
So anyway, it's just like, there's nothing to see, you know, the Mario
brothers, John Wick, four hanging in there.
I'm just like, go see, I guess we don't see anything.
See, he's already done.
Oh shit.
I want to see that.
We're going to see the Julia Louis Dreyfus movie.
We finally found a spot showing that, but still a 24 is new
masterpiece as everybody keeps saying.
Cause a 24 apparently isn't allowed to put a fucking dud out.
Uh, everything they do is a mass.
They do it all the time.
They just don't report on it.
24 also buys projects for the most part.
It's like they're, they're, they're, they don't develop most of the stuff they do.
They're just putting it out.
It's very strange how much people log onto that logo.
I like most of their stuff too.
I just, I feel like they have good taste, but it doesn't mean
they're making all this stuff.
I didn't make this Julia, this Julia Louis Dreyfus movie.
They bought it.
I'm a big Julia Louis Dreyfus fan.
Yeah.
But let's call spades spades here.
You know, I I'm a little over it.
It's like, Julia, you're like a fucking billionaire at this point.
Let somebody else get out of the fucking way.
Let somebody else work.
You need a podcast now.
It's I didn't know she had a podcast.
I don't, I don't mind making an indie movie.
I didn't know she had a podcast.
Uh, it's, it's, it's she's got it.
I'm being a little harsh.
Yes.
Yeah.
Not only she has a podcast, but she's got to act.
She doesn't have to act.
Nobody has to act.
Uh, she's got a, she's got a number one podcast.
The podcast thing is really sticking in my crawl.
It really is at her with celebs again.
It's it's whatever it is.
You don't need a podcast, Julia.
You're in the fucking Marvel franchise.
You have done three successive, massively successful TV shows.
You can do any movie you want.
You're doing, you're doing at least two movies a year at this point.
Take a fucking breath.
You don't need to make every dime on the table available to you.
And for an industry that loves calling out capitalism and, and, you
know, greed and all this stuff.
It's like, call out some of your own folks.
Like give me a break with this already.
Tom Cruise doesn't hear you.
Julia, Louis Dreyfus does.
Who did you say?
Tom Cruise, even Tom Cruise has the decency to be like, I'll
do one every few years.
Jay, well, what JLD is doing here that Tom never does is doing an indie movie.
And I'm sure she did not get rich off of you hurt my feelings.
I also am excited about it because it is Nicole Holliff center who did enough
said and many other great, great films.
And I'm excited to see them reunited.
What's enough said the one with her and Gandolfini.
Yeah, that's actually one of my favorite romantic comedies ever.
I love that movie.
And I'm a big fan of the drive.
I really am, but it's like, it gets to a point where, you know, somebody pointed
out the other day to me that Barry and I don't, I don't say this to disparage
anybody, but he's like, I'm watching the show.
Yeah.
He goes, I'm watching Barry and I suddenly realized, I suddenly realized
the voice of the preacher or whatever on the radio is Bill Burr.
And my friend goes, yeah, my friend goes, yeah, cause, cause an actor
didn't need that part, you know, give it to this is my point.
Like we're supposed to be getting past this whole look at the strike.
The all of these things that we're saying we support and these causes are,
they're supposed to be a means of spreading the wealth and making a
fair playing field for this whole diversity push this whole gender push.
It's to spread the wealth, make an even playing field.
And yet there are people who will just not stop working.
Oscar Isaac, take a day off.
Tom Hanks, take a Tom Hanks now has to be in the fucking Wes Anderson movie.
Jesus Christ, man.
You know, it's like, it's like, look, I think it's cool that you'll
leave where you drive is in a indie film on one hand.
On the other hand, that could have went to, to, uh, uh, what's your name from,
um, uh, the mob, uh, what's her name?
And mom and affairs.
Not as Jenny.
Yeah.
And Alison Jenny's won an Oscar.
It's like, it could have went to an Alison Janney.
It could have went to a Laura Linney even like just, and then these are known
actresses, but it's like for the love of God, Laura Linney and Alison
Janney work all the time too.
I'm not, I'm not, they're not the best examples, but my, what I'm saying is,
is even if you stepped down to the next tier, you're dealing with people who have
won awards and act consistently, let alone where's the breakout, where's the
breakout lady that, that gets to be in the indie comedy now that, that,
that made her life.
They talk about how TV used to make stars, like everyone on taxi was not a
big actor at that point and they became big stars, TV used to break them.
The last time that kind of happened was like Beth bears became a TV star
off broke girls and it happens occasionally with these Netflix shows
or maybe Wednesday or something.
But really the problem is TV, much like Broadway has become who's in it.
You need big stars and even TV shows, even in Broadway shows who's in it.
Well, then I'm not going to see it.
Um, it sucks.
There is no real system for like breaking new people.
Um, it does suck.
Oh God.
Oh no, go ahead.
I was going to say, well, let's take that into.
The movie corner with the first movie I will review, which is the whale,
which is exactly what we're talking about.
Everybody's going, Oh my God, the black sheep story of the whale.
You've pointed this out to me.
This man was an international movie star.
A massive star with, with a beyond chiseled body for about 10 years.
Well, you know, it's like, we're not talking about some unknown.
We're not talking about if the whale starred, Henry Winkler.
Okay.
Yeah.
Which it wouldn't obviously, but I'm just grasping at an example.
You'll get what I mean.
If the whale, Henry Winkler, you'd have a story on your hands.
Oh shit.
This guy was supposed to be big and he couldn't get out of the shadow of the
Robert Forster and Jackie Brown was who I was going to say, Pam Greer and Jackie
Brown was a story, even Travolta was a story.
Uh, and I guess Brendan Fraser and Troll, it's similar.
The point is, is it, do I think Brendan Fraser is a great actor?
I think he's fucking tremendous in this movie.
I really do.
His Oscar speech was one of the pukiest things I've ever seen in my life.
Um, I enjoyed the whale.
Let me talk about the movie itself.
I liked it.
Uh, I've it stuck with me.
It was haunting.
Uh, I'll tell you what was particularly haunting.
Most of his meals through this movie are part of my regular repertoire.
Bucket of chicken.
Absolutely.
Couple of pizzas.
I'm not above it.
Uh, it wasn't until the big binge eating scene, uh, when he's like putting the
two slices together, like a sandwich, he's pouring like ranch and like he's
sitting at the fridge where that was a very, very disturbing scene.
Then he starts throwing up.
Um, clutching his heart as he's shoving a sandwich in his mouth.
Yeah.
I liked the whale.
Uh, I thought it was a very touching movie.
I thought, uh, I don't know that, you know, it's a movie I'll add to my
joke list of like, you know, I used to have a copy of.
I used to have, I used to own precious on DVD and one time Amy Schumer.
You gave it to me.
Yeah.
Amy Schumer saw it in my apartment and she was like, you own precious.
I was like, well, we watch it on the holidays.
I think it's funny.
Like that's a funny joke.
I like to make about like nine and a half weeks or like last
tango in Paris, these disturbing movies.
You want to watch, but, uh, I would, I would use the whale in that same way.
It's nothing I would ever want to throw on, right?
But it's something I'm very happy.
I watched and you know, uh, unfortunately it's a, it's a bit tainted for me by
everything I'm saying and everything around it, uh, you know, the stuff with
short round where it's like, Oh God, isn't it so touching how this guy was just in
the middle of nowhere and now all of us guys, there's a campaign that happens.
And it costs money and either you are spending that money or your reps are
putting the money into the story for you.
This is it's all crafted.
It's no coincidence that with these rigged fucking award shows that in the
same, that if you'll notice people, the awards given away every year sort of
follow a theme, they sort of, what a coincidence this year was the underdog
year at the Oscars, everybody that was winning with somebody that made some
miraculous comeback or whatever, it's all bullshit.
It's all crafted.
It's all story.
Um, I mean, actors and directors always wind up winning for like their
latest weakest project, you know, like it's like, you know, I love the
departed, don't get me wrong, but like for Scorsese to win his first Oscar for
the departed is kind of madness.
Like they, they do this shit all the time, Pacino winning his first Oscar
for scent of a woman or whatever, you know, like they, it's all show.
It's all the dance.
These people buy awards.
The reason people don't get nominated is because they're, they did a movie
with a small studio that couldn't afford to buy it for them.
You're not paying people off, but you're, you're advertising their
performance to the point where you almost feel like you're cheating.
If you don't vote for them, that's what goes on these for your consideration
campaigns sometimes cost more than the movie itself.
Yeah.
So anyway, uh, I like Brendan Fraser.
I like Julia, Louie Dreyfus.
I'm a fan of their work.
I just wish we could stop and start crying a little bit of foul on, come on
guys, like enough with this enough.
Let's stop pretending.
It's not what it is.
It's not the rich get richer.
Let's not stop pretending.
It's not some exclusivity club.
It is.
And let's not.
So, yeah.
Kay Huy Kwan will be in one more movie and then you'll never see him again.
They will forget about him.
They'll forget about him just like they did the first time you ever see the guy
who said, I'm the captain now and captain Phillips again, he was bankrupt.
He, that was a big story that he was absolutely broke.
Yeah.
You know, tease them with it.
And then it's like, all right, now back to the basement with you.
The will was good.
Sadie sink is, is, is, is, is good.
Um, the, the, the lady that places friend, his assistant is a little
irritating through the whole thing, but she is good.
Um, you know, the cast is good.
Aronofsky does a nice job with the material.
The ending is a little bit trite, a little corny, but I did, I did like the movie.
And also very similar to the ending of the wrestler also by Darren Aronofsky.
And of my life, similar to the ending of my life with Michael Keaton.
That's a good movie.
I did not care for the whale.
Um, but it's, you know, it is what it is.
I said, I wind up saying it is what it is all the time now.
Um, speaking of rotten tomatoes, I, my, my buddy Ian was like, what is this now?
Rose burn is in a show on Apple TV called platonic.
And I said, oh no, that show is called physical.
And he goes, oh, okay.
Then I, I go into Apple TV.
Rose burn is in two shows.
Both start with a P, both titles are eight letters long.
Both shows have come out within one year of each other.
One is called platonic and one is called physical on the same channel.
Starring Rose burn.
This is what I'm talking about, man.
It's that's, that's too much.
That's too much.
It's that's what I'm saying.
It's crazy.
Uh, Rose burn, and maybe she got the idea, uh, because her husband is
working 24 hours a day, 365 days, Bobby Cannavale.
I'm a big kind of Ali fan, but it's like, baby, go on a fucking vacation.
My guess is that these two people are not in a happy marriage with the
amount that they work, but what I'm just guessing, what do I know?
Um, Rose burn and Seth Rogan are the stars of platonic.
Seth Rogan is also in three television shows a year, but here is the premise
of this show and this thing really bothers me that this show got made.
Okay.
They even acknowledge when Harry met Sally, when Harry met Sally is a
great relatable plot and obviously done about as well as it could have been done.
Can a man and a woman fuck and remain friends?
The age old question, perfect concept for romantic comedy.
The plot of platonic is this.
Rose burn is happily married with three kids to the guy from bros, the
guy who's not Billy Eichner from bros, the gay guy, um, the opening
scene is about seven minutes.
By the way, is guy Brandon making a fucking stink about that, that a
gay actor is playing a straight guy.
Where, where are you now, guy?
Yeah, guy.
Yeah, you're awfully quiet on this one.
Asshole.
All right.
Sorry.
I I've never met guy brought them.
I don't, I don't shadow Joe's views here.
Um, here's what happens.
It, the opening scene is seven minutes of her three kids and her and her husband
trying to decide what to watch on movie night, the one kid's going like emoji
movie, emoji movie, they're all arguing about what movie to watch and it goes
on and on and on, no jokes, no laughs.
Um, and suddenly I go, wait a minute.
What am I watching here?
I go out because I don't even know the premise of the show I'm
watching in the first seven minutes.
Sure enough, at the end of this discussion, Rose burn sees on Facebook
that Seth Rogan, her old platonic friend, they never fucked.
They've been friends for a long time.
She hasn't talked to him in years and she learns that he just got a divorce.
So she's like, oh no, my old friend got divorced.
Her husband goes, you should reach out to him.
She reaches out and I'm like, all right, here we go.
She reaches out to her old platonic friend and she starts fucking
around on her happy family.
Nope.
The premise of the show.
And I watched three episodes is Rose burn and her old friend, Seth Rogan,
get together and hang out.
There is no story twist.
There is no dramatic tension.
There is no story to speak of.
It is Seth Rogan and Rose burn hanging out in the first episode.
Rogan goes, can I offer you a weed gummy?
For Christ's sake, man, how many times are you going to do this, buddy?
He gives her the weed gummy.
She has one, they go to a diner and there's a 10 minute scene where she
talks with her mouth full of food.
Oh my God.
10 minutes.
She just keeps talking with her mouth full and he's like, I forgot how high
you get and how many, how many times does this happen?
Yeah.
How many times does this happen?
Ready?
Yeah, that's what he's doing.
I can't believe how high you get.
Oh, guys, this is not a television show.
Okay.
Then Seth Rogan's like, man, I gotta get a second opinion and talk to my boys.
So he goes to the bar he works at and he's working with like a Hispanic guy,
an Indian guy, and a Egyptian guy who are his three best friends.
They're in one short scene together.
And then it's right back to him and Rose burn there.
I don't, I don't know how this even got pitched.
I get it.
They go in there.
If they have those two stars attached, that's how it got pitched.
But I mean, how do you go in and say, we're going to do a show about two
people who used to be friends and they start hanging out again.
I just, what are we doing guys?
What are we doing?
And then my ultimate kind of mic drop here
is that after watching those three episodes and by the way, not hating them,
they pass the time, you know, they're they're pleasant enough, but.
I go, I look it up, I'm like, man,
I wonder if critics agree with me.
Hundred percent.
Hundred percent, meaning everyone just thinks it's great.
Oh, it's got a hundred percent rating, you mean on Rotten Tomatoes.
Yeah.
It's enough already, I'm just sick of it.
It's it's I've been saying the same thing
about the Marvel Universe, Cinematic Universe for the last three years ad
mausoleum.
People just take and take and take and take.
It's never enough.
They have to, you know, biggest movie stars in the world out there on TV hocking
fucking Snickers bars and T -Mobile and whatever other fucking
lukewarm product they can put their disgusting greasy pig fucking fingerprints
all over. It's just enough Davidson.
Pete Davidson's doing Carl's Jr. now.
It's tough and literally like biting into a burger and he's like, oh, yeah,
I love these bacon ranch, no cheeseburgers from Carl's Jr.
It's like Pete, you have three television shows telling the same story.
I'm for your life.
I'm friends with some of these people.
I'm friendly with some of these people and I'm just fans of some of these people.
Every person I've mentioned, I have no ill will towards whatsoever.
Yeah, it's just terribly disappointing
to me, which will bring me to my second and last because I know we're deep and
I only do two, but this one's on topic because it's another indie film that I
enjoyed that was also kind of trite.
But I watched Stan and Ollie.
I like Stan and Ollie. I liked it.
It was fine. It was charming.
I cried a bit at times.
But here's another thing.
This goddamn movie was made, aside from the prosthetics,
was made like the 200 grand or something like it's a cheap little fucking movie to
make, it was not an indie, it's a true indie, it seemed like.
And it stars.
The great Steve Coogan and the great John C.
Riley, two guys I'm a huge fan of again, guys, can somebody else work?
This thing bothers me, this thing of,
oh, I do I do popcorn, big studio movies all the time.
And then when I when I'm in the mood,
I graze over to the to the field of indie films and I do some of those.
I enjoy those.
It's a nice breath of fresh air.
And then I glide.
It's like.
These are roles that two unknown actors or two lesser known actors or two poorer
actors.
Would have murdered to get their hands on to sink their teeth into these two guys
are great in the movie, I'm sure Julia is great in this new movie.
Brandon was great in The Whale, but for the love of God, let other people have a
fucking chance, man, Jesus Christ, it's insane.
It's insane.
And by the way, everything I'm saying is true and you know it's true when you look
at the supporting cast of these movies,
the supporting, the drop off of notoriety from the two main people in these movies
to the supporting, you're like it goes from a list celebrity to what's it?
What's his name? I don't who's that guy.
Yeah, immediately
you know, Kugin's not an A -lister.
I thought they were both good in that movie.
John C.
Riley apparently has not had an acting offer in like five years is what he claims.
And if you really think about it, we have not seen him in much.
OK, I might be wrong.
People different than Riley and Kugin in terms of taking all the work.
I'm not picking on anybody.
Kugin works a lot.
And I love I'm not picking on anybody.
I'm just saying this thing of like to Kugin in, by the way, overseas is a massive
celebrity, like you can't judge Kugin on American celebrity.
He oversees this fucking guy is like, you know.
It's got data matter how many love breaking in.
Yeah, he had a lot of attempts at breaking in that just didn't land
night at the museum, the other guys, he just never quite made it.
But he is big overseas. Here's my point.
Here's my point. Is Kugin great?
Absolutely. Is he great in this movie?
Absolutely.
Is Riley the same for everything the same about Riley?
Could maybe I don't know, Matt Berry get to play Ali and give this guy a chance to
be like, let me show my fucking chops.
There are other notable people out there that just aren't at that level.
It's like I just feel like it's the same
people get a shot over and over and over and over and over again.
And that's part.
And look, and you're right, it's not their fault all the time.
I'm sorry, I'm not going to
cry poorhouse for some of these people.
If Riley hasn't gotten an offer in five years, that sucks.
And and I get it.
You get in and you want to you want to keep working and all that.
I'm very, very aware of that.
Rogan and Riley are two different people, absolutely.
But.
Look, I admire we were laughing at it earlier.
I admire that Nolan's got Killian at the front of his thing going, I think you're
the guy that can do it. Fuck them.
I don't care.
You're you're not he got it.
We gave Krumholz a sizable role.
Yeah, I'm not putting love it.
It's a perfect example of what I mean.
Krumholz, an exceptional actor, a known actor, a working actor,
but a guy that like that role in Oppenheimer means a certain thing to him
that it does not mean to that Steve Coogan or whatever that is.
So that's that's all I'm saying.
And as much as I am scratching my head
about the mini driver casting, God bless. Yeah.
It's a good thing.
I'm not happy no matter what you do.
I'll do a second and do it quick and then we'll get on to our film of the week.
But speaking of Pete Davidson, who I actually just learned,
I can do a pretty good impression of when I did that Carl's Jr. spot.
I am not friends with him, so I can speak freely.
I do like him as an actor.
I think he's overexposed to the point of making me sick.
I don't understand how he wrecked his car into a mansion in Beverly Hills
with a woman in the passenger seat, and we all just moved on to the next bank.
But he crashed into a house.
Him and his girlfriend crashed into a house in Beverly Hills, right?
Yeah, exactly.
And it just kind of came and went in the news cycle.
I didn't know that. Anyway,
his new show, Bupkis, I watched.
I am friendly with Judah Miller, the kind of co -creator, showrunner of the show.
And I checked it out on the Peacock Channel.
At first, I really liked the show.
I think they kind of ran out of things to do.
The first four episodes of the show are
telling the exact same story as Judd Apatow's King of Staten Island,
which came out three years ago.
I don't get it, but it's telling the same story.
He lives in his mom's basement, blah, blah, blah, yada, yada.
We just saw this.
And it's, by the way, not that interesting a story.
You know, a stoner's dad dies in 9 -11 and he lives in his mom's basement.
We didn't need a couple of retellings of this origin story of Pete Davidson.
But it's charming, it's entertaining.
I've gotten so sick of Bobby Cannaval,
I can't stand the sight of him, but he's really good in this as like his uncle,
his older uncle, he plays him when they're kids and he's like the cool uncle
who's like doing blow and shows him how to take a piss and all this other stuff.
And then he's kind of the older, sadder,
unhappy uncle when Pete grows up and he's great in it.
Edie Falco plays his mom.
The opening scene of this is Pete Davidson
jacking off with a Oculus Rift, one of those VR machines.
And as he comes, he's just going to come into thin air.
He's standing up with the thing on and he's just going to blast his load.
His mom comes downstairs, Edie Falco,
the greatest television actress of her generation, with a
basket of laundry and Pete Davidson, her son, comes all over her.
He goes, oh, comes, it splashes all over Edie Falco's shirt.
She leaves the shirt on in the next scene, which I admit was kind of a funny choice.
She was like, I didn't want to wash over.
But I guess that's funny.
It's really disturbing and gross, but whatever it is.
I mean, to make that the opening scene
of the show is wild.
And then in the back half of this series, they just lose the thread in a big way.
There is an episode that's all like a speed racer style car chase with extreme
special effects that look awful, which is Pete Davidson and Machine Gun Kelly
racing around the streets of New York or whatever.
It's an awful episode.
Then the ending is this black and white
artistic attempt with Pete Davidson.
You know, it goes off the rails.
It's not worth watching.
I don't think we're going to be seeing more bupkis, but the first few are
entertaining enough in the same way that King of Staten Island was entertaining
enough. If you like the guy, you'll probably like the show to some extent.
OK.
Let's talk the prestige.
Our movie today.
We've got the trick.
And again, very, I think, very on theme with what we're talking about.
In the right way, the prestige movie comes out to pretty high budget,
high profile affair.
Nolan has made a name for himself at the time this is dropping.
And I don't think this is pre -Batman, correct?
Yeah, he had done Memento, he had done
Insomnia, and I believe, yes, it's pre -Batman Begins, but let me check.
I think and he and he filled it with actors that were on the come up, right?
Yeah, I mean, now it looks like a who's who,
but everybody was on the come up at that time.
Yeah, we got Scarlett Johansson in a small role, you know,
it's a very consistent cast as far as notoriety of that time.
And then Peppers in an old veteran in a supporting role with Michael Caine.
That begins was was the year before the Prestige.
Prestige was between Batman Begins and Dark Knight.
So and even with Batman coming out, that's still before Bale is Bale,
because I remember when they announced that Bale was like, who?
Oh, the American Psycho.
That's interesting.
This is if you look at the way that this
movie is cast from lead to support.
There is an appropriate graph of notoriety
that mildly declines as you get from top role, top billing to smaller role.
That's how things used to be.
Anyway, enough about that.
Let's talk about the movie itself.
I believe that I've seen the Prestige so many times.
I learned something new about it every time I watch it.
I discover something new.
I've always said about the Prestige that it functions to me like an amazing
two plus hour episode of The Twilight Zone, my favorite TV show of all time.
And I.
Think that this movie personally is is Nolan's masterpiece.
I think this is everything that he does.
And just at its best, we're going to keep you guessing,
we're going to hop all around what's real, what's not.
It's a little supernatural.
It's a little grounded.
The characters are amazing.
Everybody is on a quest to to to to a personal journey of some kind
that they are extremely passionate about and dedicated to the that each person's
journey affects the other person's goals and wants and what they're after.
It's it's it's very, very much.
Characters all pitted sort of against
one another, but in a weird way, working together.
It's very much what Nolan does.
You know, Nolan is.
He I feel like Nolan is in Dark Knight is a great example of this.
He's always kind of doing heat in one way or another.
I just think this is his best take on that.
I think it's an amazing, amazing movie,
and I think it's got stellar performances in it.
I love it.
If you've not seen it, it's about two competing.
Well, not initially, two magician, two aspiring magicians initially
that eventually become competing magicians.
And what drives their competition is that Christian Bale's character.
Unknowingly, or you're not quite sure, causes the death.
Of Hugh Jackman, Hugh Jackman's character's wife.
I prepare a bow of ugly fame, who we don't see much anymore either.
But and that sort of starts the rival.
He doesn't know if he tied a good knot or the right knot or the wrong knot.
So he's either responsible for his wife's death or he's not.
But Jackman is obsessed with it because the wrong that leads to her laugh out loud.
Funny. Yeah, she drowns.
Yeah.
The big laugh out loud moment of the movie is when Jackman goes, how could he not?
Oh, while alone in his bedroom, a hilarious moment of the movie.
But it's not camp.
You know, the movie has a couple of funny camp moments, mostly from Hugh Jackman.
But
it is a really great film.
I remember when it came out, I thought Shyamalan.
I mean, I thought Nolan was going to be the next Shyamalan.
Comes out with memento, you know, amazing twists and turns, amazing script.
I'm like, oh, man, this guy is great.
Follows it up with insomnia, goes big budget.
That's kind of maybe his unbreakable, you might say.
I guess prestige is really his unbreakable.
But
I just thought that this guy was going to make these little puzzle box movies.
Inception, he still does.
But I never thought he would reach the heights he's at now where he's getting
five hundred million dollars to do literally anything he wants.
But he deserves it.
He is one of our best and most distinctive filmmakers.
He's kind of like a Shyamalan meets a
Michael Mann or Ridley Scott.
He is experimental, you know, he's always wants to surprise you and trick you
with his narrative, but he really is a classic epic filmmaker like a Ridley Scott.
Like he makes beautiful looking movies about giant subjects.
So
I love the prestige because it's small for him.
It's a small potatoes movie for Christian Bale.
Or Nolan or Christian Bale.
You say Christian Bale, Christopher Nolan.
Yeah, it's it's entirely based on its story.
You know, this is not a movie that relies
on big sweeping epic camera moves and things like that.
It looks great.
I love I love the movie.
I love the way it feels. I love the way it looks.
This movie came out three months after
The Illusionist of Memory serves with Paul Giamatti and Edward Norton,
another Dueling Magician movie.
And that one has long since been forgotten to the sands of time.
And the prestige you don't hear discussed
near as much as Nolan's other stuff, but it is a really, really, really strong
screenplay in particular.
They talked about how difficult it was to make into a movie.
They adapted a book, but eventually they
landed on basically making the movie into the same three acts that Michael Caine
describes as being the three acts of a trick.
Well, that's that's one of the great things is the movie's got you all over the place.
You're constantly watching every scene
to see what you're missing, what you're what you're not catching, what you're
and it jumps timelines with no help.
It doesn't help you out. Right.
What you're supposed to be looking at or focused on versus what else is happening.
The movie in and of itself is a magic trick.
And then like you just had the three acts
break down the three act, the pledge, the turn and the prestige.
One of the hardest I've ever laughed.
It's the hardest I ever laughed ever on the Opie and Anthony show.
It was right around the time that two girls, one cup was going around.
There was this other video was right at the time the prestige came out.
There was this other viral video that was equally as disgusting where a guy puts a
metal glass, sorry, glass jar up his own ass and then it shatters.
Yeah, and he has to pull the pieces out.
And we watched it at that time.
Yeah, we watched it on air on Opie and
Anthony and the prestige trailers that were playing on TV, the TV spots.
As soon as it breaks,
Anthony goes, every magic trick has three parts.
It's the turn and I laughed so hard.
It was it was very funny.
Anyway, it's it's it's an awesome, awesome movie.
And the fact that.
It when it begins, you're convinced that it's all based around this trick.
Called the the transporting the
transported man where Christian Bale walks into a doorway on one side of the stage,
bouncing a ball as he bounces a ball across the stage and then in in real time
instantly comes out on the opposite side of the stage from another doorway and
catches the ball physically impossible to do.
Yeah.
And that the entire movie is based on Hugh Jackman's obsession with this trick
and figuring out how he does it and the.
Him manipulating Christian Bale and their game of cat and mouse and
and blah, blah, blah, in in in in his pursuit of this trick, figuring it out,
Bale not telling him, then giving him clues because his back is against the wall
and blah, blah, blah, blah, blah,
and you're you go back and forth through the entire movie.
You're like, this is something supernatural is happening.
And then you go, no, no, it's not.
And then by the end of it,
Bale, having gone to meet Tesla, the scientists, which I love that they do
that in this, too, with all the weird.
Unproven kind of into real life, you mean?
Yeah, around Tesla and then like making him and Tesla played by David Bowie.
Yeah, one of one of my favorite Bowie roles.
Yeah.
And and then Tesla builds him this machine
that actually can duplicate a human being, so it does become literally
supernatural and science fiction at one point.
And then I generally hate good.
I generally hate when when the explanation is supernatural and there has
been no supernatural element in the movie to that point, it always feels like a cop
out to me, except in this movie, because they go to Tesla and he's a scientist
and he was working with this kind of stuff.
It's really a perfect development for the story.
And usually I hate that kind of thing.
Well, heightened by the fact that in the end you learn
that Christian Bale was not doing anything supernatural.
He has a twin.
Yes, which they call out immediately.
In like the first 30 minutes of the movie,
Michael Caine is going, he's got a double.
It's the only way.
They tell you what the trick is.
And you're like, yeah.
And then Hugh Jackman's like, it's not a double.
It's impossible.
And they they red herring it just enough that you're like, well, I guess it could
be a double. And even if you figure it out in that moment, it is a double.
Doesn't matter. You're still going on this whole other journey where you're going
to learn.
You're going to see Hugh Jackman's way of doing it, which is this science fiction
way where he starts cloning himself and having to murder the clone every night so
he can do this trick.
It's so awesome.
It's such an awesome movie.
It's it's a real beautiful ending to it because not only does the supernatural
thing work in Jackman's case, you've got the real believable explanation
with Bale that makes it work better for you and makes it work better for me
because you have you find out how they both did it.
And it's also so dark.
That I didn't mind, you know,
like it's like, yes, we are adding a supernatural element.
And yes, that's a little stretching of belief, whatever you want to call it.
In a movie that's had no supernatural prior, even though it is about magic.
But the fact that it is so dark that he is literally killing clone after clone
after clone just makes it awesome to me.
Love it. And he gives that chilling speech at the end, never knowing each night which
one I would be the one drowning or the one appearing in the back of the theater
for the right. I was like, that's that's like a bone chilling speech.
One of the great themes, too, you know,
the whole the whole reason that this all happens is that Jackman figures out a
great way to do the trick, but he has to sit under the stage.
He doesn't get the applause.
It's all about needing that
love from the audience or whatever.
So it really is hubris that winds up killing a great, great thematically, too.
Yeah. Yeah.
Because he because Jackman halfway through
the film figures out a way to do the trick where he finds a guy that looks
enough like him played also by Jack, which is all right.
And they refer to him as being fat, which I was like, why not give him a fat suit?
Yeah.
So Hugh Jackman, who's in amazing shape.
But because of the way the trick has to work, Hugh Jackman ends up having to take
the applause under the stage and the fake Hugh Jackman is up on stage getting the
and then that guy starts blackmailing him and it doesn't work out.
But the point is, is it is hubris.
Jackman complains about that.
And it's it's hubris that drives him through this thing.
There's a there's a thing they establish
at the beginning of the movie about a real magician lives.
Twenty four hour lives in the illusion.
Yeah. And they go see this ain't this this
Asian magician who's like he was ancient, he's like 90.
And they realize he's actually not this doddling old man.
He's actually doddling.
Is that a word? That's a word, right?
Dot doddering doddering old man.
Then they then they realize he's not it's
impossible for him to do these tricks that he's able to do if he's the age and
at the fragility that he's at and he's living every day in public as this.
Fake version of himself and Hugh Jackman denounces that and says that's a living
hell and bail is like, that's what it takes.
And then the beauty of the ending where you bail reveals my my twin brother
and I have been living this illusion, we we had to take turns with with
the same woman each day. I actually loved her.
He didn't. She killed herself over this.
Yeah.
He had to cut his fingers off when I lost my thing.
You see all he sacrificed, but you also
realize that the entire movie Hugh Jackman has not been this American whatever.
He's this rich lord who's been pretending
to be this poor American magician the whole time.
And he's also been living a complete illusion to throw everybody out.
It is wild.
The climax of this movie.
Has one of the greatest climactic moments I've ever seen.
One of the Christian Bale twins is being
hung for the apparent murder of one of the Hugh Jackman clones.
Because the cops don't know there are clones.
They think they just that he murdered Hugh Jackman.
And he didn't, you find out it was an accident, but it was a misunderstanding.
But anyway, he's in jail and he's going to get he's going to hang for this.
And Hugh Jackman at this point has bested Christian Bale.
He has revealed I've actually been this rich lord all along.
I've now acquired your daughter.
I've beaten you, I've beaten you and Christian Bale is left.
You don't know he's a twin yet.
He's in jail. He's screaming like that's the man that I'm in here.
Supposedly have been killed and all.
It's it's horrible.
And then he's led to the gallows.
And as he's about to drop, they say any last words.
And he Christian Bale's witness whispers Abra cadabra.
And I remember sitting in the theater going, what the fuck is about to happen?
Like, what is the trick?
And then, sure enough.
Hugh Jackman, having won.
Is with Michael Cain throwing getting getting rid of this machine
that Tesla built for him once and for all, and Michael Cain brings up his wife
drowning and says, which is so awesome when he goes,
I remember telling you at your wife's funeral
that I had a friend who almost drowned and he said it was like going home.
I lied. He said it was agony.
And then he just walks away like, fuck you, I'm done with you.
And Jackman is sitting there and then all of a sudden somebody comes out
of the shadows, the shadowy figure shoots Jackman.
It's a fatal wound.
And as Jackman is dying, the person comes out of the shadows
and reveals it's Christian Bale.
And you're like, what is fucking happening?
And then he reveals we were twins the whole time.
You know, it's fucking awesome, man, that the movie is just fucking awesome.
Yeah, it's like, you know, when Michael Cain says, like, it's not enough.
He's got to come back in the end.
The trick's got to come back.
You're like, OK, so some even though you kind of know that something
will happen, that's how well written the movie is, is that there are ten
instances where you're like, I'm ahead of this.
I know where this is going.
And you kind of do.
But it's still told in such a fresh and crazy and original way
that you're fooled every time I'd already seen this movie.
And I fell for every trick that it had up its sleeve.
Even though the first time I saw it,
I was pissed at myself for missing the obvious hints.
I still fell for it.
And it's a really good movie.
And again, even if you guess certain things.
There are still other surprises.
Take, for instance, the final shot.
Like where Jackman says with his dying
breath, like, you know, something about like the horror that surrounds you down
here right now, and then the final shot is the reveal that there is glass tank
after glass tank after glass tank of his drowned clones.
Right. And and even that you're like, fuck, I didn't think of that.
Oh, my God. It just keeps coming, man.
It's it's it's an awesome.
And then also that he goes in the opening
shot is a bunch of magician hats, you know, rolling around on the floor,
like 50 magician hats, the opening shot of the movie.
And like you should be thinking, why is this happening?
But you kind of don't. It just sort of seems symbolic.
But then all that adds up in the end, too.
And then and then the fact that he goes to Tesla.
Who
Kane refers to as a wizard.
Yeah, and Tesla is in the heated battle at the time with Einstein, like the two
literal.
Wizards that walked amongst us that were
changing society, that were changing the future as we would know it forever.
We're in the same heated competition
that these two magicians are in, destroying each other's lives.
You know, like it was what an awesome movie, man.
My hog is way up for the prestige.
Do yourself a favor if you haven't seen it.
Well, we've ruined it if you have haven't seen it, but it's still worth a watch.
And even when you it unlike Shyamalan,
even when you know the twists of this movie, you can keep watching it over
and over again, like you'll discover a new detail every time.
It's great. It's worth a watch.
Certainly worth a blue 4K purchase if you don't own it already.
I have it on Blu Ray.
I will probably upgrade.
And it's cheap on 4K now, right?
It's like 1799 on Amazon at the moment.
So and
there's a theory that you can also read about online.
There's all kinds of theories.
It's one of those movies, too, so you can kind of keep exploring it.
But there's a theory that Tesla's machine doesn't actually do anything.
It's I'm reading this here off letterbox, but it's all part of a magic trick.
Nolan pulls off by making us think the machine works when, in fact,
Hugh Jackman uses the same double he had ever every night and he never dies
until the night bail breaks in.
This is this guy, Andrew Bowley, writing about it on letterbox.
You can read his thoughts, but there's a bunch of this online.
Fascinating stuff, just people's different takes on the film.
And what's great about it is that like a great puzzle or magic trick,
a lot of these different ways in kind of work or make sense.
People can explain their take on it pretty well.
Hog way up for the prestige.
Check it out if you've never seen it.
We are going to be back with another
story about magic and magicians called Dragon Slayer, 1981's Dragon Slayer.
That'll be our next one.
I am on only Instagram at the Patrick Walsh
and the Miss Pat show is currently airing on BT plus.
Jota Rose, a comedy
on Instagram and Twitter.
Taste Buds Livestream.
May 31st, that's coming right up
9 p .m. Eastern Standard Time.
Get your tickets at moment .co slash taste buds.
And please tune in to or visit Joey Rose's.
If you're in town, come check us out.
I guess I can announce this officially.
The release date is coming soon, but my new album.
The Penthouse Papers Collected Readings,
which is a collection of readings
that I did in a studio of all the op ed pieces I wrote over the course of two
years for Penthouse magazine, is coming out via a special thing.
Records in June.
Please check that out.
The specific date is coming very soon.
Keep an eye out.
I believe it will be June 9th, but that might change.
Also,
I got a massive tour.
I'll get to that later.
Anyway, we'll see you soon, folks.
We'll see you next time.
And we'll see you in hell.