I will see you in a little, I'll see you in a little.
And my name is Patrick Walsh, and without further ado, I'd love to get on with the show.
And at the same time, on with the Joe.
Cut out.
Did it.
Cut out completely.
On Mayan.
Maybe it's in the recording, but I think it's in the recording.
And if not, that'll be the lost on with the Joe.
I'll have heard of it.
No one else will.
It seemed like the frequency went so high that it like, I don't know, it's weird.
It's weird.
I've kind of had it with Zoom.
It keeps crashing every week on us.
And we always lose some shit, you know.
Anyway, today we're talking about memory, which is a documentary about the alien, the first
alien.
Yes.
That was the, so it's only about alien.
It's not about the alien franchise.
It's just about alien, and we'll get to that later.
But you know, alien, a pretty graphic film, classic, obviously.
And in line with that, I have an interesting screaming in where I don't have it in front
of me, but Marvel, Disney got called out for apparently editing some of the fight scenes
in Marvel movies.
Like when they were hitting Disney, you know, the fans called it out that they were kind
of, I guess maybe I, my assumption was tampering down some of the violent areas a bit more.
So the screenshot I saw was something from Captain America, and there was a bloody aftermath
of a shot and, and the shot instead removed a lot of the blood.
Yeah.
So stuff like that, right?
So this is, this is the world we're living in now.
They get called out on it.
There's a big fan outrage, of course, right?
Because God forbid any of these people just go by these movies.
They are so precious about, and they want to protect so much.
And you know, God forbid they spend money to own these things that they're so concerned
about being censored and taken away from them.
But anyway, that's besides the point.
There's a big fan backlash over this editing.
And then Disney comes out and says, these were accidentally edited.
Now, even if you've never come on, never come on.
Yeah, even if you've never, it's crazy.
That's insane.
It's crazy.
Even if you've never edited anything or worked in TV production as we both have,
you know that that is impossible.
You can't accidentally edit something.
It doesn't happen.
No, you can't do that form like Disney plus.
So here's the entity, the biggest, let's be honest, evil entity and all of entertainment
of all the monopolizations that's happening that are happening in Hollywood right now.
Hypocrits beyond their wildest dreams in the organization.
Disney is the worst of the worst, right?
Yeah.
This is what they think of their audience.
This is what they think of the consumer.
They think of all of us as being so stupid that we would actually accept the idea that these
things were accidentally edited.
This speaks to a huge problem between the provider and the consumer.
It speaks to a huge problem in my, by the way, if you think your consumer is that stupid,
then what do you think kind of product will be given?
You know, like when you watch Wonder Woman 2, let's say, that's what they think of you.
That's what they think of you.
They know you'll watch it regardless of how good it is.
Well, that wasn't a Disney one, but I get what you mean.
Sure.
They're all the same.
Yeah.
Well, yeah, it's a shame.
It really is a shame.
But well, you know, it's inevitable, it was inevitable, it was going to happen sooner or
later.
But yeah, here we are.
That's just incredible to me.
That was like when Netflix said with the train wreck footage they used from the Canadian
train wreck in bird box, and then the people in Canada said, could you take that out?
It was actually a horrific event in our country's history.
And it was very traumatic for a lot of people.
And they said, you know, we would, we would, but once it's streaming, we can't pull it down
and edit it.
It's insane.
It's a complete line.
It's just they're all lying.
I was just reading about friends working for all of them.
Of course.
And I intend to hopefully work for them again.
But Netflix this week also our last week, whatever, they canceled the babysitters club, obviously
not a show I ever watched, but beloved by its fans and well reviewed.
And then they revealed that it was also a very, very, very big hit.
So they interviewed the creator and they were like, so what happened here?
Like you must have thought you were getting another season and she said, it was explained
to me like this, it is no longer enough to be a huge hit in America.
That doesn't even factor into Netflix's decision.
They are looking for something through their algorithm, which is how they decide everything
now, through an algorithm that appeals not only to all the quadrants, but all meaning four
quadrants means different ages, men, women, whatever.
And also they need it to be a four quadrant hit internationally, which is what they look at
way more than just America, because Netflix is now a global corporation, just like Google
or anything else.
So they said, yeah, you do have really actually incredible ratings, especially for a show
about teenage girls, but you're not making the algorithm dance.
You're not hitting in Japan, you're not hitting here, wherever it is, we're doomed.
I think everybody knows we're doomed.
They keep the one good thing about I used to hate Twitter because of writers giving advice,
which is one of the most sickening parts of Twitter.
Oh, writers who have never watched comedians giving advice.
No, I see that's a lot of writers give advice and then you look them up and they've never
had a produced credit.
I saw some girl the other day doing that, 20, a 20 tweet thread and she's never worked, but
well, those who can't, you know, it's one of those things.
Yeah, for sure.
But it's just there's a lot of writers now banding together and starting groups and stuff
about how nobody can sell anything and nobody can get anything off the ground and people
are wasting two to three years of their life on projects that they never even get to pitch.
And it's a terrifying time to be in my business is all I can say because all this stuff,
everything is just reached an ugly head and everybody knows too much and everybody knows
that their secrets are out and they, I don't know, it's all bad.
I wanted to bring up in the screaming and Joe and I have discussed on this show Ezra Miller
who portrays the flash in the DC averse.
And there's a video that I have seen multiple times of him choking out a young female fan.
She approaches him at a thing and he chokes a young female fan out on camera and this was
a long time ago we discussed this on the show but I was like, Joe, how is this man still
working?
What's going on here?
What's happening?
And you and I think a lot of people said clearly this is some sort of fake thing and he
knows the girl and it's a doctored thing or whatever because otherwise we shut him down.
Couple days ago, two Hawaii residents filed a restraining order against Ezra Miller.
They were singing shallow the song from Star is born at karaoke.
He screamed at them until they left the bar saying shut the fuck up, shut the fuck up.
You're at a karaoke night, you know, you're in Hawaii.
Maybe hit a bar that doesn't have karaoke.
Sure, you hate them.
And you know an actor like Ezra Miller probably performed a couple times up there at the mic too, you know.
So he followed them to their hotel room, this couple first into their bedroom, stole their wallet
including social security card, credit cards, etc and threatened them repeatedly saying, I will bury
you. So now we got to say that other video is real and this man is a menist to society.
I don't think he's a menist to society.
I want to know what they were saying.
You know, this is, I'm sorry.
I'm at a jaded point where I hear a story like this and I say, if they were saying,
fuck you, we hate you, fuck you.
And then he breaks into their rooms, he knows their shit and says, I'll bury you.
I'm not saying, I'm not saying he should have done that.
I'm saying, I want to know, first of all, what was going on in the bar.
I find it hard to believe that Ezra's sitting there, they're singing and for no reason he's
screaming, fuck you, fuck you, shut the fuck up and then follows them home.
Unless he's mentally imbalanced and if he's mentally imbalanced,
then we need to help him and not crazy shame him as they were the man's mentally imbalanced.
Well, clearly, I'm not saying, well, I'm not saying the guy isn't,
that doesn't, let me put it to you this way.
I'll phrase it in another way.
That does not sound to me like a man who is a guy and I'm, I'm sorry,
obviously you're not attending anything by this and neither was I,
but he's a, he's a, is it they then?
Oh, sorry, sorry, they, they were sorry to say, I'm sorry, sorry.
Obviously they, in my opinion, you break that story down.
They were not doing something that to me reeks of menace to society.
They were doing something to me that reeks of unhinged famous person.
Yeah.
And just like with Will Smith, as I don't condone the slap, I think the man is in terrible pain and needs
help. Yes.
So, you know, I just, so I don't know, you know, however, at some point,
it's on you to get that help and see help, absolutely, absolutely.
I'm not saying it.
But I mean, these stories, man, you hear these stories and you go, oh my god,
wouldn't ask for what a piece of shit.
And then like a year later, they'll be like, turns out,
the people karaoke and kept flashing a gun at him.
You know what I mean?
Like, that's how the news goes anymore.
Yeah, true.
And that something like that may, may not have happened.
I don't know, but I can't even believe anything.
I'm reading anymore.
It's crazy.
Like, so it's a bummer.
I'm a fan of Ezra Miller.
But and I'm excited for this flash movie.
Thank God it's in the can before this happens.
Well, he better, I'm guarantee the people behind that movie are like,
lock him up until this movie comes out.
By the way, we got Morbius in theaters now and there's about 250
reports of Jared Leto targeting underage girls,
fucking them, raping them.
So it doesn't matter all these reports.
I've never heard of any of these.
Google them after.
I mean, there's endless reports going back years and years and years
and they all know details about his giant dick and et cetera, et cetera.
So yeah, as Ezra Miller, you know,
I think we all watched.
We need to talk about.
Yeah, first thing comes up.
Yeah, holy shit.
Are you seeing all the photos of completely empty theaters for Morbius?
No, that's a goddamn it.
Jared Leto now.
I thought actually thought Morbius was the first Marvel movie in a while
that I actually thought looked pretty good.
That's supposed to be terrible.
I saw and seek it out.
So I tweet again, I'm spending too much time on Twitter.
I'm lonely folks.
But this guy, I left so hard at this.
He goes, I'm here.
He goes, I thought I was the only person in this screening of Morbius.
So I was going to take a picture of the auditorium and didn't realize my flash was on.
And the picture is of one scared nerd looking directly into the flash
getting his picture taken because the guy didn't realize.
So like imagine you're alone there in a theater and somebody just immediately takes a flash photo.
You got to see it to get the bit.
It's very funny.
Yeah, okay.
So I guess we won't be doing Morbius on the show.
I haven't, I'm not going to see Morbius.
But it was one of the only things in theaters that I thought we're probably going to do X.
I loved X.
I hope you see it because I think of all these goddamn fucking movies that are streaming.
And this thing's only in the theater for Christy.
They got the new Matrix streaming day one.
I got to pay to see X.
Well, they, they always release things immediately now.
I mean, it's going to be on HBO Max in a week.
Every time I put, I turn on HBO Max.
I'm like, didn't this just come out?
And the answer is always yes.
Like there's no turnaround anymore.
My hesitation with X, I love going to a theater.
And I don't mind paying and all that.
I really don't.
But the only reason I'm hesitant with X is because it's an A24.
An A24 is quickly in my life becoming my second only to James Blumhouse
in atrocities attributed to the, contributed to the screen.
So I'm just, you know, but you're saying it's not the typical A24.
You're not saying you get in there and no, there's a difference between what they produce
and what they acquire.
So they acquired X.
They acquired X.
Yes.
So that was a finished film presented to them, I believe.
Yeah, I was going to say, this Thai West has kind of been out of the.
Yeah, big distribution game for, well, he was never really in it.
But you know what I mean, like he was, well, it's that good.
It's a really, in my opinion, a really excellent movie.
And they, I'm so excited to see the prequel for it.
If they do it, big, I think they maybe are already shooting it.
But I loved it.
So, all right, good.
And also all practical effects.
Okay, all right.
Well, look, I'm a sucker anytime like an old lady is being creepy,
which seems to be featured quite a bit in the trailer.
I, you know, it's very, very good.
I have some scary stuff over here.
We're still here.
Well, two things.
Would you say we're still here?
Yeah, two things.
So we said, one of the last episodes, we said,
Brain Candy was coming out on Blu -ray.
It's out.
I went and looked.
It was already out.
It had just been released.
So I bought a copy.
It's like 12 or 15 bucks.
I'm happy to have it.
I don't think that the Blu -ray experience is changing much
in the Brain Candy viewing.
No.
And in fact, I don't know that anything has been,
no, it says 1080p high definition.
The cover of this thing looks like it was photocopied inside Dave Foley's basement.
It always had a terrible buster.
Let me see it.
Hold it up.
It's not the poster itself.
It's the quality of the print.
It's like it's that's what's happening
because the DVD and Blu -ray business is going under.
So things get cheaper and cheaper.
Even though it's been proven,
the only way to move these things
is by making them cool covers, special editions.
That's the only way people buy stuff anymore.
But that said,
I'm very happy to have it.
I'm excited to get it and excited to play.
And then I've been playing if you're a video game person.
Ratchet and Clank, the 2016 version,
which was a remake, part remake of the original game
and part a new adaptation of the movie that had come out that year.
I bring this up for multiple reasons.
Number one, the game is really fun.
And it's a free download on PlayStation Plus.
So if you have a PlayStation 4 or 5,
you can download this game.
It's beautiful and it's super fun.
And it's genuinely funny.
It's really, really funny.
And I never said that about video games.
I hate when video games try to be funny,
because that's always out there.
This is genuinely really funny.
I really enjoy the experience of playing it.
But the bigger reason I bring it up
is because it made me go up and look up the Ratchet and Clank movie
that came out that same year.
And the poster has all these big names on it.
And Stallone was one.
I forget who else.
I think Paul Giamatti was one.
And then I went and looked,
because there's been like 17 Ratchet and Clank games
starting with PS2.
And it's been the same three guys doing the lead role voices
that whole time.
So I looked at the cast of the movie
and I was like, oh, here we go.
They finally make a movie and they recast the original voice actors
with like Stallone and whoever.
That sucks.
Right.
And it was like, no,
every major actor building the posters
playing a supporting role in the movie,
the original cast that made these games popular,
made these characters popular, I should say,
are doing the voices in the movie,
which is how it should be
fucking Nintendo,
you fucking assholes
with your Super Mario Brothers movie,
where you kicked Mario to the curb
the guy
after how much work has this man put in for you
and you replace him with Chris Pratt,
your garbage.
There's there's proof,
there's there's previous proof
that you don't have to do that now.
And I didn't know that.
So I think it sucks.
Anyway, I would I would almost guarantee
it has no effect on box office
to have big stars voicing characters.
I just don't think it's amazing.
I would disagree.
Go back and look at the response
to the announcing of the Mario Brother
with Super Mario casting.
They're going to have a big back.
They have they already have a big back.
Oh, no, no, no, no,
backlash I get.
I just mean that they think they need
to spend $5 million to get Chris Pratt
to voice something when they don't.
Oh, yes, I agree, I agree.
It's it's a classic.
It's one of my favorite John Mulaney bits,
which I know I probably have done on the show before,
but he talks about how,
you know, no kid goes up,
looks at a movie poster and goes
dank shepherds in this.
One, please.
You know, it's very, very fun.
But yeah, it's it's
you know, I don't know.
It's I liked like, for example,
I just watched Mitchell's versus the machines
and I thought Danny McBride gave a really good vocal performance
and wasn't doing his usual stick.
And I appreciated that.
I thought that was a movie
that really went out of its way
to cast the right people for it.
In that case, I don't mind it being big star.
But clearly folks.
And I'm not talking about Italian representation
or anything like that.
Chris Pratt should not be playing Mario.
It's fucking stupid.
It makes no sense.
No, he doesn't have an interesting voice even.
It's like just a guy's voice.
Yeah, and I guess unless they're going, you know,
it's like this Buzz Lightyear thing that's out now
and they're like, well, it's not Tim Allen
because it's the movie about who Buzz Lightyear was based on
or whatever the fuck there's.
You're like, guys, yeah.
It's just confusing.
Just make it Tim Allen.
Like, yeah.
And meanwhile, you start to go.
Well, I wonder if it's because Tim Allen's a Republican
or I wonder if it's because they think Tim Allen
has no marketability.
And then in the same breath, they're like,
we're doing a Santa Claus TV series on Disney Plus
starring Tim Allen.
Yeah.
So clearly, what a work with the guy.
Why aren't you cowards casting David Crumholz
to replace his role as Bernard the Elf?
That's a good question.
That is my question.
And but my, well, my question is, do you think they're not
or do you think it's a secret thing where they said to David,
keep your mouth shut?
Well, he would have told me, but they, I don't know.
I should ask him if he got asked or not.
But I think it's been pretty public about not getting asked.
Oh, okay.
You know, David, in his case, you know,
he used to be really outspoken on Twitter to a to a degree.
I mean, these things can come back to bite you.
Now, Chris Pratt is surely going to have a problem on his hands
in the coming years because he's a very, very active member
of the Hillsong Church.
And they've started on Discovery Plus,
a new exposé documentary of how fucked up
that Hollywood Church is.
So we'll see what happens with him.
But I mean, it's becoming worse, clearly,
than the vetting they do for political office,
the amount of scrutiny into the private lives of actors.
It's completely nuts.
Let's go to the movie corner.
Um, I would like to start by showcasing a great new standup special.
I watched this morning.
The worst standup special I've seen in a long, long time
is the new Foxworthy special, which I watched with friends.
I mean, good Lord.
He's doing jokes about how women pack soup cases differently than men.
He's doing like the most stuff you would,
stuff you would have seen on ABC in 1982.
Like the exact same jokes with no spin on them.
But what do you expect from Jeff Foxworth?
I never expected anything.
And we watched it with the expectation of it being bad.
And I'm saying it went way below those expectations.
He seems like such a sweet guy.
Yeah, I almost feel bad.
I haven't seen it yet, but I almost feel bad.
Like it is shocking.
Yeah, anyway, um, it's it's the kind of stuff you would see,
like the warm up comedian at like some holiday in, uh,
you know, retreat for an insurance company kind of vibe.
Like you go there and they're like, oh, we got a comedian, everybody.
And he comes out and does five minutes.
Anyway, no, I watched
Gerard Carmichael colon rofaniel, which
it's strange because it is revealed that that is his actual name,
rofaniel and the special.
And they just tell you what it is.
And the other is real first name.
Yes, his middle name drive.
That's interesting.
Yes, that comes out at the end.
And then also coming out is Gerard himself who tells you that he's gay
about half through the special.
It is treated as a reveal and yet every single piece of press about it,
every single tweet about it, it talks about how he's coming out in the special.
So it wasn't surprising to me in those ways.
And I also, you know, just from hanging out with people,
have known Gerard was gay, but I didn't know until I read the thing.
Oh, really? Okay.
Yeah, I had just, you know, you hear rumblings, whatever.
But, um, what really surprised me about this the most is that it was good.
I walked in, eyes, nine tenths of the way rolled.
I do not like this sort of sort of comedy special,
you know, like the Drew Michael thing where it's deathly serious.
I never, I got two minutes into that.
Nanette, I watched and it's entirety, uh, and really, really didn't like it.
Mostly because I think you should say this is a performance art piece or
a one woman show or one man show or whatever.
I agree that there's a difference between stand -up and one person show.
I do, you know, um, it's a very begosian kind of thing.
But also too, this is, and you can tell me because you've seen it, I have it.
This is my one issue that I take immediately when I hear that there's like a big
reveal, like a big vulnerable reveal.
I'm like, well, it's still a show that you had to rehearse in some way.
So like with Nanette, she was doing that.
I was at the Sydney, I think I've told this to her.
I was at the comedy festival in Melbourne, excuse me, when she was workshopping that show.
And she was winning all the awards.
And I was like, oh my god, she's, who's this lady that's winning all these awards?
And they were like, she's a local comic.
She's doing a show about how she's quitting comedy and she cries every night in the show.
And I was like, oh, and then you see it two years later become this global phenomenon.
You're like, what seems a little disingenuous to me that you're running this thing over and over
where you cry and say you're going to quit that you keep doing.
I hear you.
That's a controversial stance.
And people have been talking about that special for years.
So mission accomplished, Hannah Gatsby, you, you got what you wanted.
But, right, um, I, I hate that stuff more than anything.
I find things disingenuous even when everyone in the world is telling me it's genuine.
I'm just like, I don't buy it.
I don't, I am very skeptical of everyone and everything for whatever reason.
I watched this special this morning and it really hit me.
I think, uh, I have to be honest, I've never liked Gerard standup.
He's never made me smile.
It's a nice man.
I met him.
I did standup with him once.
Very nice.
Very nice guy.
I like Gerard a lot.
Is it, uh, I haven't seen him do a ton of standup.
But yeah, uh, he's a Greek guy.
It wasn't for me.
Uh, I love to show.
Carmichael show.
I thought it was one of the great multi -cams of recent years.
Maybe one of the only great multi -cams of recent years.
It was a good show.
Um, and I've known him to be a guy.
He's, he's almost legendary in TV circles for just saying,
fuck you, I'm going to do what I want to executives,
which is really, really, really, really hard to do.
And I admire him for that.
Yes.
But I do not like his standup generally.
And I think this crystallized for me why I don't like it,
which is I never knew who he was.
He does not tell you anything about himself or who he is.
And also sometimes it didn't really feel necessarily like a prepared set.
So you watch these specials and you're like,
this feels like night two or something.
I've tried to workshop a new set.
Um, this I also has the same sort of lack of preparation.
You know, he goes up a lot of it just feels like a man talking from his heart.
And at the end, there's actually the audience starts shouting out questions,
which I've never seen in a standup show.
So it seems like that was probably something that was planned.
But I don't know that.
Mm -hmm.
Um, even with all these things that I had my guard up so much,
I found the special very, very moving and very, very funny.
And it's because he's telling real true stories about,
at first, the first half of the special is about secrets and families,
particularly in black families he's talking about,
but in all families have secrets.
I, you know, Irish Catholic families have a tremendous amount of secrets.
The amount of shit in my family I could go on for days.
You came from a cult of cannibals, was that correct?
That's correct.
Yeah.
And still, you know, once in a while I need to feed to keep my, my blood up.
But yeah, I remember when you got that airbrush t -shirt on the boardwalk,
I got the need to feed.
Yeah, exactly.
You wore that whole summer.
Sleepers.
Tank, tank, tank, tank, tank.
Because it's sleep connected at the bottom.
Tank belly top.
Yeah.
But, uh, I, for the first time felt like I get this guy,
I get why he has seemed so close off because he has been hiding a very large
part of himself for a very long time.
Mm -hmm.
And he talks about the guilt he feels of doing that,
the guilt of his family.
But mostly his family is, if they're not shutting him out or calling him names,
they are that thing of, look, I accept you.
I never want to hear a single thing about you being gay.
Don't ever talk to me about being gay again.
Talks about his male friends who are like, I feel like I've been tricked into having a gay
best friend now, because they've been friends for 20 years and didn't know.
Um, that is a side of the coming out story I haven't heard before.
Are you friends with a guy for 20 years and you don't, come on.
You know, you know, that's, I'm not saying he's full of shit.
I'm saying his friend.
It's like, what, yeah, your friends are never like, hey, dude, um, just curious.
He talks about even being closeted in his gay relationship where it'd be like,
I'm going to suck your dick, bro.
And they'd both be like very aggro about it because he wasn't comfortable with being
traditionally gay.
Now, all of that stuff I have never heard before from anyone.
It felt like very fresh new standup.
He does it in a sitting in a chair conversational style that I also usually hate.
But for whatever reason it worked on me and I'm telling you if I like this going in with this
many grievances about it, I think it's pretty special and I think it's one that will
stand the test of time, not because of the gimmick of him coming out but because of him
talking about the very real stories and the pain that he has gone through and forced himself
to go through. He's done it to himself.
I just really was impressed by it.
I will say that and I, it changed my opinion of the man.
I urge you to check it out if you like standup and who does.
Are you about to come out right now?
Yes, I am.
That brings me to my next point.
No, I just, I dug it.
I dug it.
I will check it out.
It's not really typically my thing but you've convinced me that it's something that I should watch
and that it's more than just the hook of he's coming out of the closet.
I have a friend, my friend Willie Hunter worked a lot on the sitcom.
Yes.
I think he co -created it or something.
But Willie's a good friend of mine.
I know Gerard mainly through Willie and I like those guys quite a bit.
And I'm curious, I'm curious to see what it is.
I'm glad to hear that it's more than just,
because HBO's been doing this thing where it's like,
and look, nothing against these guys.
I've met Drew Michael a million times.
He's always very nice.
His two specials just were not for me.
It's just not for me.
But that said, it's like everybody has the right to do what they want to do.
But this one sounds like it might be something I enjoy.
And I didn't know that his real name was worth it.
I was like, why is he called worth it?
Because when I saw that,
I was like, is he just calling it a name so he can be like Hannah Gatsby?
But that's very interesting that it's his real first name
and the whole thing is about him becoming his real self.
And that's interesting.
It sounds like there's a lot of, you know,
different differentiating elements of this
from what the typical version of this is.
It's a very, very effective special.
I think another big part of it for me is that I have,
and I don't even comment on most of them,
just because I know a lot of comedians.
But I have watched easily 50 comedy specials in the last year
and I have never laughed.
And I just keep going,
well, I guess comedy's getting shitty.
I don't know what to tell you or, you know, am I not,
am I, I turned a lot of them off halfway through.
But this just caught me.
I don't know what it is.
Now at the end, it does develop into Q and A
and that that part is a little weird.
But like having just watched that as he's special,
which is him sitting in a chair telling jokes
where the punchline to most of them is quoting a 90s hip hop lyric,
including, you can do it, put your back into it,
like that, like these songs like from when I was 21,
he, it's just the laziest shit.
And as I have said, it's a 28 minute special padded,
where you see footage of his opener,
you see footage of a Z's waiting to go on stage,
and you see a clip package of him throughout the years,
as if we all want to see a Z's grow.
And like look, look at where he is now doing shit comedy,
just pathetic shit comedy.
And what is a Z's rewarded with,
after turning in this incredibly lazy,
stand -up special that probably netted him a million dollars,
he's now directing a movie with Bill Murray, starring in it.
This is, I mean, this is where we're at.
Well, you're right.
I don't like them.
I don't even know where I was going with it.
I hate a Z's special so much, but no, it's fine.
I get it. Look, he's not, he's, again,
a guy that's always been nice to me,
but I look, I have a much greater distance
between myself and a Z's than I do between myself and Gerrata Drew.
And I have a different opinion of him than I have either of them,
but I can say a lot more openly here, or casually.
Yeah, I could see why you wouldn't like a Z's.
I get it.
I never, I always did like a Z's,
and I like, at least the first season, a master of none, a lot.
I like that too.
For me, this special was just like a true fuck you, you know,
just a true fuck you.
And, well, here's what bothers me about it.
Yes, this is what bothers me about it.
This is kind of what bothers me, I gotta be honest.
This bothers me a bit about all these specials.
And I said this years ago,
about when Sarah Silverman did the special in front of like,
you know, 50 people in the room.
Yeah, it had jokes.
No, it did. It wasn't a knock on her.
It was just the, I made a joke and I was like, you know,
can you leave the 50 person special to me?
The guy that can probably only bring the 50 people into the room.
Right.
Like I'm getting a little, you know, like there's a wave of DIY
specials happening now, which are really great.
And even if they're not DIY, they're like, even if they're done by a bigger outlet,
they're presented in a very DIY fashion.
So like I saw Joe list last night.
Joe listed his camera or his, sorry, his special, very small level
at the, I think he did it at the fat black lounge or the village on the ground.
One of those two.
Anyway, Comedy Central has produced it.
It's great.
It's, it's raw.
It's real.
It's simple.
It's got six and a half million views on YouTube.
I'm so happy for him.
Shane Gillis did it on the art, did it himself.
Got three million views and I think a month or two.
Mark Norman DIY, do these things monetize in any way?
Or do you just get your money on the, how they monetize on YouTube?
Yeah.
Okay.
And then also, you know, obviously it leads to other money and stuff.
But like my point is is like, Mark Norman did one like that.
Sam Rell has done a couple now that are like, I think in the millions of views.
I think it's brilliant.
You know, Sam is now headlining the beacon in New York City.
And I might have already sold out.
But this is a guy that I've known since literally since he was an open -micro
and who I do spots with it on shows at clubs all the time.
And who I know one of, he was a friend.
He's my friend.
It's so exciting to see that happen.
It's so exciting to see Shane get the shaft from SNL and then put out his own thing
and then that thing leading him now to literally a theater tour that's going as far as Australia.
That's so exciting to me.
And it bothers me a little bit when the guys that are given the HBO and Netflix keys
also do those types of specials.
Because it's like guys, Aziz, you can sell out of theater already.
So why don't you let us do the thing that we need to do to build ourselves,
which is the low -down and dirty special at the club.
And you go do the thing at the theater because that's who you are.
And even with, I'm not saying Gerard and Drew Michael are theater,
I don't know if they are, to be honest, maybe they are.
But that's the only criticism I would have about this.
It's like you can do whatever you want.
But my point is it's like if mega death or Metallica is going to do an HBO special,
it's going to be most likely the stadium show.
That's what they do.
You know what I mean?
Like leave the acoustic unplugged thing to.
You know, unplugged was a show for a reason.
Because I was like, here's a setting you will never, ever see these bands in.
Right.
Boom.
It was a weird hook gimmicky thing to do.
I'm not crazy about it when these celebrity comics are like,
I'm also going to do the thing where I sit at the comedy seller.
It's like, come on, man.
Yeah.
Come on.
Like because it takes it away.
Don't get me wrong.
As he's his last big theater special was absolutely terrible as well.
No, I'm not saying it wasn't.
Yeah, I'm just saying, you get what I'm playing.
Yeah, that's my primary criticism with these types of things.
From, and then it has to be a case to case after that of whether it's good or not.
Right.
No, but anyway, I, I got a short movie quarter this week.
I saw, I'll just hit this in one stride.
Like, because I mentioned it last episode, I watched equalizer one and two,
started Denzel Washington.
I bought these.
I had seen equalizer one in the theater.
I loved it.
Never hadn't seen it since.
Never saw equalizer two had seen a few clips of it on YouTube.
Love the clips.
I was like, I, you know, so I just went ahead and bought both.
It was like $12 to get the double blu -ray.
Which I only regret buying now because now that if they make,
when equalizer three comes up, there'll be a three pack.
And I'll be, and I won't be able to, my OCD and ANO alternatives will not let me have the single
d blu -ray of equalizer three.
And then the pack of the two, I have to have all my area.
I hear you.
So it's just that it's no way to live.
You know what I would probably do in that situation is sell the one and two pack and buy the three pack.
I, I will do even worse.
I will buy the three pack and throw or give away the two pack.
So at this, at some point, you've spent like $100 on the equalizer franchise.
And you never saw it in the theater.
Anyway, they're, what can I say?
They're great movies.
If you like that sort of thing, it's definitely a little bit of the older guy,
the older actor in the revenge mode thing.
But it's not like taken or whatever.
It's not like they came after his family.
And then he went after them.
It's not, it's, it's, it's a little more of a John Wick vibe where he's like sort of a guy that
stepped away from this life as this secret agent assassin, whatever the fuck he was.
And then it's pulled back in.
And in that sense, it's John Wickish.
But it's not as comic bookie and over the top is John Wickish.
It's got a little, it's a little more grounded.
And then also too in the scenes where he's not destroying a room full of people.
He's Denzel.
Right.
So he's awesome.
So like the, so the, the kill scenes are secondary to the scenes where like he goes
and meets the bad guy he's playing the cat and mouse game with in a restaurant and sits down
and they have the face to face.
It's those are the best scenes.
Yeah.
And then everything else after that is, is, is just gravy.
But probably that movie was written for a Keanu Reeves or somebody like that.
And when they got Denzel, they were like, we got to actually write him some stuff to act.
You know, I don't know for certain, but what's his name directed it?
The guy that, um, Antoine Pouple.
Yeah, I feel like he, well, I feel like he wanted to do it and wanted to do it with Denzel
because they had a history.
Oh, yeah, training day.
You're right.
No, you're right.
But, um, they're just great movies.
They're a lot of fun.
They're, they're really graphics, surprisingly at times.
They're very violent, but, uh, but they're awesome.
And there's a scene in both movies where he has to go confront, like I said, the bad guy
and the one -on -one.
And it's awesome.
Like he's, yeah.
So in those movies, though, the, the, that scene in both movies serve as the turning,
serves as a turning point where you're like everything really heats up after that.
Um, there's always somebody younger in his life that he cares about,
that, that gets threatened because of what he's doing to avenge some other thing.
Um, and he doesn't take credit for any of the good deeds he does.
He just, it's just an awesome, it's awesome.
It's awesome.
He, oh, he's got OCD.
I don't know if that was part of the show.
But the character in the movie has OCD.
So he's like counting things all the time.
He time himself.
Yeah, they do that baseball stuff where they're writing stuff on the screen.
And that kind of thing, yeah, I remember them.
He like, no, well, they don't do the writing on the screen,
but they do show the, like, don't they?
No, no.
Well, it's him like kind of laser eye figuring out the scenario of the room.
Yeah, they do that where it's like it zooms in on like,
right, he'll be in a room and he zooms it on like the shot glass and then a, uh,
paperweight and then whatever.
And then when he kills everybody, you see how he uses those things, like, yeah.
And he always times himself on his watch.
Um, but like the big, the big, his first big scene in the first movie,
he goes to the door and you think he's going to leave because he's outnumbered
and these guys are like, get the fuck out of here.
We're going to kill you.
And he goes to the door and he opens and closes at three times, which I think is great
because he's got an OCD and then he locks it and he locks himself in with them,
which is so, it's so exciting.
You're just like, yeah, it's all, they're, they're just really cool movies.
I really like, I highly recommend Equalizer One and Two.
I enjoyed them both as well.
I last night watched The Bubble, the new film from Judd Apatow.
Judd Apatow tweeted the night of the Oscars.
He could have killed him there about the slap and then the entire world turned against Judd Apatow.
Um, I mean, it was a real pussy thing to say.
But Judd Apatow, um, who I, me and Joe had both worked with,
was the name and comedy throughout the last decade, the biggest.
And he still has a pretty impeccable producer track record.
His track record has a writer director, a little spotter.
And I think in recent years, obviously, we're not getting the, the high, high bar of a knocked
up or a 40 -year -old virgin, but I still think that he still makes a good comedy film.
You know, they're, they're more even, even this is 40 or a, or a funny people or a
Staten Island or train record. These movies that people talk shit on to me in a world where we are
not getting comedy movies anymore, they're still pretty good comedies.
Um, The Bubble, I started seeing really rough reviews, really rough reviews and
yeah, it's, uh, it's a complete mass.
It is, as you can imagine, a two -hour, 10 -minute comedy because he won't do a short comedy,
he just doesn't know how to do it.
But let me guess, his wife and kids are in it.
Wife and kids are in it.
Uh -huh.
Um, I still think Leslie Mann is a pretty good comedic actress.
I tend to like her things, but I, I think so too.
And nothing against his kids, I just don't understand why they only work in his movies.
Well, no, the one is, is a big and euphoria now.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, you know, they're getting work.
Oh, that's good.
That's good.
He's, he's, this one is bad.
And it's, it's clearly like he went in and was like, I want to go to an isolated place with actors.
We all actually quarantine ourselves and shoot a movie about being quarantined together.
Not a, not a bad idea, even.
It's more of a Soderberg idea than an appetite idea.
But yes, so he goes and I don't know if they had a script.
It was written with Pam Brady, who was the collaborator that Parker and Stone turned to for their movies.
She co -wrote, you know, all the, the team of America and South Park and all the shit.
And Hamlet 2, she wrote, which is a very underrated comedy with Steve Cougan.
And I thought, boy, these two together, this is going to, at the very least, have a bunch of great jokes in it.
It kind of doesn't.
The cast is all over the place.
It's Karen Gillan, who I think is pretty bad in this.
Keegan Michael Key, who's in one out of three movies.
Pedro Pascal, who I do not get the appeal of at all.
He's not funny in this.
Armason, who I'm tired of looking at at this point.
And I don't know what to tell you.
It's not, it's not as bad as people make it out to be.
And I think for the first half hour, it's a fun, funny satire of Hollywood.
It's got Peter Sarah Finowitz, who I like a lot, that British actor.
Rob Delaney as an agent.
And when it's, when it's satirizing how self -absorbed and obnoxious actors and actresses are,
it's good.
I mean, who's going to know that better than Judd Appetel?
But
past that point, it's about the making of a movie called Cliff Beasts,
yeah, which is like a Jurassic World type movie.
And we see so much footage of Cliff Beasts
and they think this shit is real funny and it dies embarrassing death.
All this Cliff Beasts stuff.
There's a scene in this.
Beck is one of my favorite musical artists of all time.
And I know everybody gets old and it's sad.
But there's a scene where to cheer up all the actors who are stranded and in quarantine,
they have Beck come on over a video screen and perform ladies night.
Oh, yes, it's late.
He's night.
And he changes the lyrics to be about Cliff Beasts.
And as he does this, and I mean, he's singing it while like mugging into the camera and stuff like that,
they cut to this big group of actors dancing to it.
And they do the full song, ladies night, in the middle of this movie.
This thing, I started wondering at some point if I was ever going to get an erection again
watching this scene.
It is as soft as a scene as I have ever seen.
And I guarantee you Netflix was like, I know Beck is cool, but you have to cut this.
This has really been in a two hour 10 movie.
There are seven lengthy musical montages where you see the entire song perform.
You see the apt -out daughter record a full song parody on TikTok for four minutes.
Like he's got to learn the art of editing.
And especially, I think knocked up is one of the great modern comedies.
And I think Forty -O Virgin is the same.
They all could have benefited from some trims.
But in this movie, he's got a pretty rough movie that he lets go on that long.
And boy, do you feel it?
I don't know.
I don't think it's completely without worth because some of the Hollywood's entire stuff is funny,
but it's tough stuff.
All right.
And then are you done, Josh?
You have no more?
No, I have one more.
Okay.
I was just thinking of...
I was just thinking of, you know, what I wanted to say versus what I didn't want to say
about the apt -out thing.
Look, I think the biggest issue with the thing like this is, and I haven't seen it.
But to me, just from your description, it reeks of,
look at the celebrity cool kids having a good time together.
Yeah.
And it sounds annoying.
It sounds privileged.
It sounds.
It sounds like here's what we did with our quarantine because we could, because we're rich and famous.
And I'm sorry, Judd apt -out, again, always been very nice to me.
But Judd apt -out is not the guy I want to hear Hollywood commentary from.
Exactly.
He embraces it like no other.
And for him to be like, isn't it funny that some people act like this in Hollywood?
Judd, it's not for you to say.
That's, you know, exactly.
Well, and the cast, you know, when you watch, and I used to, he was a,
an idol of mine, a Freaks and Geek.
When he was doing Forty -O -Virgin, knocked up, whatever I was like, this is the kind of movie
I want to be doing.
And then immediately Hollywood stopped making those kinds of moves.
But even the ones he produces, I'd watch the special features.
And the cast hanging out would be as funny as the movie.
These people are not all comedic actors.
David DeCovney has a sizable role in the thing.
And I think DeCovney is also playing Apertile in the movie, basically, which is a little tough,
because he's Leslie Mann's ex -husband, and all.
But the cast doesn't seem to get along or like each other.
There's no sense of play or fun to it.
The improvs aren't fun.
Yeah, it's just, it's a kind of comedy that even though I used to love it,
just now feels dated, I think, because we don't have comedy anymore.
It's a ragtag cast in that thing, man.
It's super ragtag.
Like people must have passed on the thing.
Yeah, I was reading the cast list.
I was like, I was like, David DeCovney.
What?
Yeah, I know.
On here, like, I think maybe it could have worked.
This is a thing that could have worked, it sounds like I didn't see it.
But it sounds like it could have worked if it was like Seth Rogen leading the charge.
Like this is the end, where you actually believe the camaraderie amongst all these people.
Right.
And you want to see them together.
But nobody's asking to see DeCovney, the Mandalorian and Leslie Mann trapped in a room together.
Nobody gives a shit.
It really is like throwing darts at a board that has actors pictures on it.
I mean, they got the funny blonde girl from Borat,
who they don't give anything to do.
And it's a real mixed bag.
And they seem like they don't have much to say to each other in the movie and in real life.
So the fun does not translate to the screen.
All right.
Oh, by the way, then at the end,
the last line of the movie, Joe, and this would infuriate you.
It's Keegan, Armason, and I think the Borat lady.
And they're looking up at this helicopter as it flies away.
And they're, I don't remember exactly, but it's like,
man, like what a disaster this turned out to be.
And they're like, at the end of the day, we came together to give people a good time
during a very stressful time in the world.
And then the credits, I wonder if he didn't go back after realizing the movie didn't work
and shoot that bit as like even we didn't mean this seriously.
But like, no, Judd, you got to own it.
You made this movie at a rate of probably $25 to $50 million.
You have to own it.
You can't at the end say, yeah, we tried something that didn't work out.
It's not a sketch.
And also the joke, I mean, my god, this is like, it takes two seconds.
The funnier version of that joke is, yes, we did.
And we failed.
We failed.
Yeah.
Like the characters admitting like this sucked.
Like that's, yeah.
Anyway, my last movie corner before we get to our movie is very quick, very simple.
I bought the, because I only had it on DVD, but I bought the four pack to replace it.
Blu -rays of the Batman quadrilogy, the original, the Tim Burton,
through Joel Schumacher ones.
Because I wanted to rewatch, I never wanted to just want to have one, Blu -ray.
Number two, I wanted to rewatch Batman Returns because I'd been seeing some things on the
internet that were saying, you know, it's not as bad as it was.
As people say, it was in sort of a lost masterpiece.
A plus film, it might have been.
Yeah, so I remember liking the theater and then subsequent viewings.
I remember not liking it at all.
Mainly because of Jim Carrey's approach to the riddler,
like playing it like the Joker.
And also, Tommy Lee Jones playing two -face, like the Joker,
like everybody was the Joker.
But anyway, he sucked in that time.
Yeah, I hated him.
And although I also hated Eckhart, so I don't know why they keep going back to two -face.
I love two -face.
But yeah, I don't think he's got his true shining moment yet on the silver screen.
But, and then also Kilmer kind of a step down from Keaton.
Who cares, doesn't matter?
Kind of.
I went back and watched it.
This is all I'll say.
Loved every minute of it, and it's a thousand times better than the Batman.
Yeah.
That's all I'll say.
And then I might dip into it.
Keith on the call sheet, you got Chris Walken.
I mean, the movie is just an endless...
That's returns, that's returns, babe.
Walken's returns.
For some reason, I thought you started this talking about returns.
No, forever.
I know you texted me about forever, but I thought you started this talking about returns.
Oh, if I don't, I miss what?
I'm sorry.
I don't think Batman ever ever is an A -plus movie.
I need to correct that on the record now.
I was shocked that you said it was an A -plus movie.
No, no, no, I got it because I wanted to rewatch Batman forever.
I'm sorry.
There it is, okay.
Uh, because I was seeing all this stuff, like it's not as bad as people say,
blah, blah, blah.
And I rewatched it, and I enjoyed it very much.
And even despite my gripes that I just said about Carrie being whatever and Tommy Lee and whatever,
it's still a thousand times better than the Batman, than the new movie, the Batman.
It's a better, more fun movie to watch.
And I'll leave it at the end.
Fair enough.
I remember what, like, is there like a...
There's three letters and they're like,
wait, those letters correspond with...
Are those numbers correspond with these letters of the alphabet?
M -R -E.
Mr. E.
Mr. Edward Nigma.
The Riddler.
Isn't that in there?
Uh, well, his name...
I don't, it might be.
And his name in the comic and that one are just in four.
She comes in in four.
But that's the thing.
His name...
The problem with some of these Batman villains is they were created in the like 30s or whatever.
So, like, the Riddler, when he first came out, like, it was actually kind of cool
that his name was Edward Nigma.
And if you want to stay true to the comics,
you're kind of stuck with that, you know, so you're better off just not mentioning it,
you know, in the new movie.
Yeah, I mean, I don't, I don't even remember forever.
I remember being not thrilled by it at the time.
And then Batman and Robin was...
Oof, oof.
But my third one today is California Split.
A movie that I had seen and really enjoyed.
A Robert Altman picture with Elliott Gould as a degenerate gambler.
And George Siegel, the late great George Siegel,
as a guy who kind of is visiting the gambling world but doesn't have a problem.
And it's about how Gould sort of sucks him into the degenerate world
and what happens there.
It's, you know, it's, it's classic Altman.
It is people talking over each other.
Every scene has 10 people talking at once.
I had heard that this was one that you need to watch before it leaves Amazon Prime,
which it may have already done because they were like,
we've got the uncut version, which to me felt zero different than the other version I had seen.
But I don't even think it's one of Altman's best.
And I am a man who really loves to gamble.
But it's a great movie.
And the chemistry between Gould and Siegel is phenomenal.
The movie is, to me, everybody talks about Kubrick's influence on Paul Thomas Anderson,
but I feel a lot more Altman in his stuff.
And it has some similar faults to like a licorice pizza.
It's too shaggy.
There's not a real plot to it at all.
It's just kind of a character study, but it's a great one.
And I think if you're going Gould Altman,
I prefer the long goodbye because it's got a great story to it.
But definitely worth checking out if you never saw California split.
So it's a good gambling movie for sure.
And it was remade unofficially as Mississippi Grind with Ryan Reynolds and Sam Mendelssohn.
Another good gambling movie.
Was that good?
Mississippi Grind?
Yes, I loved it.
Yeah, all right.
Cool.
All right.
Our movie today, sometimes we cover these documentaries because for some reason
in the horror genre, a lot of feature -length documentaries are made about classic films.
And they're usually pretty goddamn good.
Today is memory, which is, I forget the full title.
I don't think it's called just memory.
Or the origin of the origins of alien.
That's what it is, yeah.
And it just focuses on alien, the first one.
Which let's not get into the old arguments.
But I like that it just focuses on the original one.
I think that's very cool.
And you get a little bit of Prometheus in there too
because of its connections to the first film.
But I mean, man, they don't even discuss the sequel.
I thought there was going to be a sequence where they at least where they went like
and then aliens is great because it's like an action version.
And then alien three, well, I think they at least could discuss that the series went on.
They don't.
This is it. They like end it.
This is it.
Well, I just talked about alien.
You know, it's one I remember getting it for Christmas, the alien quadrilogy,
which now of course there's many, many more movies.
But it was the four alien movies in a big box.
And it had like 600 hours of extras.
You know, now you can get an Amazon for 10 bucks.
But it was a huge thing.
I was so excited when I got a Christmas.
And I watched all the shit.
I watched all the documentaries and all the special features.
But I was going into this like, what don't I know about alien?
I've seen all this stuff.
There's been full length documentaries made about all the alien movies.
And they don't do that shit anymore.
But I thought what could this have to offer me?
And what it does offer is that it is a very sort of academic look at the alien movies,
I would say.
There are some personal stories.
They spend a lot of time with Dan O 'Bannon's wife Dan O 'Bannon
wrote the movie and is now dead.
And they talk about, you know, at least 20 minutes,
the movie feels like a Dan O 'Bannon biography.
But it's very sort of academic and looking at specific shots in the movie
and making things down.
The director of this also did a movie breaking down the psycho shower scene.
That is a pretty interesting documentary.
But that focused on one scene.
So, you know, I'm on letterboxed and when I looked at what my friends
had said about the movie, nobody rated it higher than three stars.
Nobody seemed to like it much.
And I get that.
There's something kind of cold about it.
Ridley Scott's not in it.
Sigourney's not in it.
They do have Tom Scarrett and a few of the other actors.
Patricia Clarkson, is it?
No.
Not that's not our name.
Not Patricia Clarkson, sorry.
Isn't it Cynthia?
No, but the lady from Witches of Eastwick that puked up all this.
Let's bring her up.
Let's not cherry pits.
Yeah, but it's.
I don't know.
It clearly left a lot of people cold.
Her name is Veronica Cartwright.
Oh, yeah, close.
But, um, but my name's not Cartwright.
Called right.
For me, it left me a little cold as well.
I thought, okay, I love this movie.
I didn't really come away learning anything about it.
What I liked the most was the Dan O 'Bannon segment
because he seemed like a really interesting guy.
And his wife seemed to love him very, very much, which I love this.
It's very focused on O 'Bannon.
And the whole thing, I think, is much more
that this is O 'Bannon's picture than it's, and they praise Ridley Scott
through this thing.
Don't get me wrong.
But it's very much taken, which I'm sure you appreciated, Pat.
It's very much taken in praise of the writer.
Because this started as Dan O 'Bannon's idea, his script that he shopped around,
like this, you know, which I thought was pretty cool.
They talk about from the earliest days that everybody knew,
including Roger Corman, who almost produced it,
which would have been a much lower budget, worse movie.
But everybody knew that the Chess Berster scene was going to be huge.
Everybody knew from the jump.
Like, whatever we do, we got to make sure this Chess Berster scene works out.
Including Ridley Scott was like, we got to make this perfect.
They knew they had something amazing.
I still remember, and this is one of my earliest memories.
Like, we're talking five or something.
My next door neighbors had rented Alien.
My parents went next door to watch it.
We were not allowed to even be in the house while they watched it.
Because it had this reputation as being so scary and terrifying.
And my parents were both so shaken up by it.
Neither of them likes horror, but they were just like,
really shaken up by it.
And I remember this like mystical thing around the movie.
And this Chess Berster scene.
And there's a reason.
It is the modern equivalent of the psycho shower scene.
It's one of the great horror scenes of all time.
So they go into that.
But that made me wonder, what does this have to do with the origins of Alien?
Like, I thought it was going to be about getting Alien made or something.
And it is, but that's where the movie lost me a bit.
I didn't mean the origins of the Alien franchise.
Is what the documentary is about?
I thought it didn't really thematically add up as a documentary.
Because if it's about the origins of Alien,
then the Dan O 'Bannon writing it stuff makes a lot of sense.
But then why are we analyzing scenes from the film?
That's not the origin of Alien.
The title is maybe a little,
you know, a dissection of Alien would have been a better or more appropriate title.
I mean, first of all, kind of a fun punny title.
Alien dissection is a thing.
I'm a big Dan O 'Bannon fan.
He wrote Dark Star.
He wrote Alien.
He wrote Dead and Buried, which we reviewed on here.
Prevented the Living Dead.
Return of the Living Dead, which is way up the ladder for me.
He wrote Life Force, which is my second favorite, Toby Hooper movie.
He wrote The Invaders from Mars remake, which is awesome.
He wrote Total Recall, which is awesome.
So I'm a big Dan O 'Bannon fan.
He died much too soon, unfortunately.
So I really, first of all, the movie, this movie is very well done.
They really captured an atmosphere for a documentary,
because a documentary often is a lot of talking heads, obviously.
And I liked what they did with this from a director standpoint,
where it was all, every person they were interviewing was drenched in blackness.
Very cool.
They put this really cool opening on it.
I forget what they're called, but it's like a plan.
What was that?
When that started, I said, oh, fuck.
I didn't think that was cool at all.
I was like, what is this?
We're doing re -enact.
Who were they?
What was that?
The witches or whatever that was.
They talk about it in the, they talk about it.
It's from Greek mythology or something in the movie.
It's three.
It's the three, it's not the sirens,
but it's three women that lure men who do evil deeds
in or something like that.
What did it have to do with Alien?
They said, for me it's the same.
Yeah, they say it's like a big theme in the movie, Alien.
So they just shot a version of it as a cool opening for this thing.
Which I thought was really cool.
I liked it.
I really got my attention.
And I liked that, again, that this focused on the writer
and getting the script into the right hands.
I liked that they talked about how much of a struggle that was
and the people that didn't get it and all that stuff.
And I did enjoy that there was some outsider commentary
from critics on the movie.
It got a little heavy at one point.
I'm never a big fan of when they start to get into
too deeply what a movie means metaphorically,
especially when it's being talked about by people who were, you know,
not even born or like were three or four or five years old
when this movie came out.
They hit a little too hard on the this whole movie
as a metaphor for mass toxic masculinity and misogyny.
I agree with that to an extent.
But I gotta say I'd agree with it more if anyone was misogynistic
to the women on board.
That's not a part of the movie at all.
Wouldn't that have been part of it if that was a theme
they were trying to do?
I guess, I guess, which is why I started to think they were
putting a little too fine a point on it.
I agreed that it was groundbreaking
and it shouldn't have been.
It shouldn't be now groundbreaking that a female was the lead
in the hero.
But it was and a female with a very large visible bush.
Let's not forget it.
But it was and it is and that's what it is.
And so I got why there was talk of gender
about the film and about what it meant and all that stuff and what.
But I thought the most insightful thing was the one critic
when she said, I'm not sure they quite knew
that they were doing that.
I think it just ended up sort of being potentially
of the time versus the lady with the glasses
who was like, if you unpack that the misogyny was programmed
into the road and you're like, oh, Christ lady enough.
Whenever somebody doesn't just say like my theory
about what it means or whatever and somebody comes in with
the movie is about toxic masculinity.
I'm always like, shut up.
Like I just don't think that now when they go into class
I do think the movie is very much about class.
Yeah.
And they show you they dissect that one scene beautifully.
I thought where they got all the characters in the frame
and they talk about how the power positions suddenly change
and everything and yes, I agree.
And by the way, the most powerful position in the scene
is a woman.
It's it's it's Veronica Cartwright giving all the scientific data
to Tom Scarrett, which is what she is the epitome
of the high tier in that scene.
Yeah.
If anything, I think alien all the aliens are very pro woman.
And they to me, to me, if really Scott set out to it's like,
it's like being in TV.
Okay, you write a show where like a friend helps a friend out.
And then they come in and they're like, there's no heart to this
because what they mean is they want you to come in and spell it out
and have the violin's play.
And you're like, it does have heart.
It's a friend helping a friend out of it.
But they want you to to go overboard with it.
I think if this movie had been Tom Scarrett being like,
what do you know?
You're nothing but a woman or whatever than yes.
But Ridley Scott knew it could be a pro feminist movie
by simply making the woman who survives until the end a woman.
And that is why it is a movie about female empowerment.
Not that not this other stuff you're reading into it
or that the alien represents the penis, you know, they go into how it
it feel, you know, raping the guy is what that
chess buster scene supposed to be.
And I was like, no, I don't think so.
Now what I did find interesting was his wife.
Well, the writer does Crohn's disease.
And then it felt like it was eating him from within.
Right. And that's might be where he came up with this idea
of the alien bursting out of his chest.
The co -writer does say Ronald Ron Shushit
who wrote the story with Dan O 'Batton.
He does say that the facehugger, when they came with the idea,
he said literally, the alien fucks him.
And he's right, right, yes.
So there is a rape element to it.
There's a pregnancy element because it's
planning on eggs inside of your, whatever.
But I thought it went, I thought it went too far
when the lady with the glasses was saying like,
the robot's last act is an act of misogyny
to put this woman in her place.
It's like, no, it's not.
It's an act of him trying to kill the human
that's in his way in that moment.
Right. Those are two different things.
Now if you want to think that that's a metaphor for something,
then fine, but a robot would not care if it was a woman or a man.
A robot is not sexist.
And the robot even explains at the end,
I'm stronger than you because I have no conscience
or whatever he says.
Played by the great Ian home, by the way.
But I'll go to that moment.
But what's funny to me when they get to the talking of this sort of thing
and the themes on this, you know, he don't hear from anybody
that was involved with the production of the movie.
Not one of them in this segment comes in and goes,
oh yeah, that was, you know, we tried to do that.
Not one of the, which is always a little suspect to me.
It gets a little shining where it's like, guys,
I'm not hearing peep from anybody that was actually working on the movie.
Yeah. I mean, that room 237.
Yeah, yeah.
So because I guarantee they asked them
because they definitely wanted to have people say stuff
to back up these opinions in their documentary.
And I bet all the cast members were like,
no, really, definitely never said anything like that to me.
And it didn't support their argument, probably.
Tom Scarrett, in fact, at one point is like,
talks very candidly is like, they said it was a two million dollar budget.
I said, that sounds like an Edward movie.
I'm not doing it.
Right. They called me back a week later.
We got the budget to 10 million.
And I said, okay, I'll do it.
Like it was so just like, which yeah, I gotta admit hurt.
It hurt my opinion on Tom Scarrett a little bit because I was like,
so you didn't see how cool this like, there's no investment on your part.
You're just literally like, give me the money.
Show me the money and I'll do it.
It's a lot of accuracy.
But I get it too.
I don't know, I took to me, this was better than room 237,
which I just thought was just, I agree.
Talking to morons, the documentary.
But I get why I left people cold too because it left me a little cold.
I think the reason it would bother most people is because you go
and expecting a comprehensive documentary of Alien.
Maybe even as you said, the Alien franchise.
It ain't that.
If you want that by the Alien quadrilogy for 10 bucks on Amazon and watch
literally days of special features about all of the movies,
including the best of all those documentaries is the one about Alien 3,
where they go into Fincher's just battles with the studio,
that almost wrecked his career before it started.
I'm listening to the audio play of that now,
on Audible starring Lance Hendrickson.
And it's the original story what it was supposed to be.
And it's so much cooler, it just makes so much more sense.
I have that on Audible and have a listen to it.
And then once you get to Resurrection,
I mean, we're off the reservation at that point.
That movie is when she actually does fuck the Alien in Resurrection.
Yeah, I don't know.
To me, I enjoyed the documentary.
Anytime you dig deep into a great, great film like that,
I can watch that shit for days.
This is short, it's 90 minutes, which is to its credit.
And yet I wish going in, they knew what they were doing.
I feel like I don't know that the director
knew what story he wanted to tell here.
And I think calling it the origin of Alien is a big mistake
because while it does that, it also does other stuff.
So I don't know, it felt like half of a great Alien documentary to me.
I loved it the whole way through.
I really enjoyed it.
It's something I'd probably even watch again.
And one thing we failed to mention was the highlights on Spotlight on HR Geeger.
They did this, which I thought was fast.
It's a Geega.
So I liked it.
My hog is up for Alien.
My hog is slightly up as well.
To me, this would have worked better as a DVD special feature.
But it's on shutter, check it out.
Fair enough.
Folks, we'll be back mid -month with some more flicks.
Like I said, probably X and whatever else.
In the meantime, I'll be Joe DeRosa, comedy on Twitter and Instagram.
If you want to follow the official account of my band now,
given the story on the last episode,
it's also underscore WinFall on Twitter.
I will also be, if you're living in the Texas area,
I'm doing Houston, the Come and Take at Festival in mid -May,
and going right to Austin to do the creaking cave for four shows.
Go to my website, joderosainfo .com for your tickets and all that crap.
And come to Joey Roses if you're in New York City.
Open Tuesday through Sunday.
Joey Roses NYC .com for information.
I'm at the Patrick Walsh on Twitter and Instagram.
Miss Pat Show is season one, which I was not a part of,
although it's very, very funny.
Just started airing on traditional BET.
I would recommend not watching it there.
And getting the BET Plus app, which is very cheap.
It's like $23 or free on Amazon if you want to trial.
But I would not watch it on traditional TV,
because they're cutting five minutes out of every episode.
And they're also cutting all the profanity.
We get a list each week of all the profanity that's cut
and it's like 12 pages long.
You don't want to, I mean, why would you watch the show edited?
The beauty of the show is that everyone's talking real and authentic.
But that's it.
We will be back as Joe said with X and whatever else is coming down the pike.
Thank you to Emily.
Thank you to all of you.
We are trying to put together some sort of live show in the near future.
Hopefully around Labor Day.
We'll let you know as soon as we do.
Yes.
Thank you all.
We will see you next time and we will see you in hell.