Hello, everybody, and welcome to another scintillating episode
of We'll See You in Hell. We should really find out how many of these we've done at this point,
hundreds, just hundreds. Today's episode is about Sick, a movie that, you know, at a time when the
business is just making foolhardy decision after foolhardy decision. They have decided to release
this movie Sick, a, in my opinion, above average slasher picture about COVID at a time when horror
movies are making bank just like, you know, 10 times in their budget. And we just dumped this
on Peacock. I never understand the actions of people, but that's where you can find it, is on
Peacock. Foolhardy, I don't know that I've ever heard that term. I decided to use some big words
in my intro, scintillating foolhardy. Foolhardy is dumb. Yeah, no, I was able to put that together.
Yeah, it's like a Dickens word, recklessly bold or rash. Dickensian. Yes. But yeah, it's a pretty
generic, I guess, slasher. But what makes it interesting is that it's about our current times
or more specifically the beginning of the COVID -19 virus. We'll get to that. Yes, Jim.
I was going to say, speaking of foolhardy decisions, what's your take on this
Golden Razzies thing with the fire start? They nominated the girl that started in the fire
as worst actress. Did Efron get nominated? Because he was worse than she was. No, Efron didn't get
nominated. Well, then I'm upset about that. He gave one of the worst performances of that year.
But if you don't know the story, they nominated her as worst actress. There was a lot of blowback.
You're picking on a 12 -year -old kid. I love the hypocrisy of all this shit. These are the same
people that all fucking went after Jake Lloyd in Phantom Menace for being a bad eight -year -old
actor or whatever. It wasn't George Lucas's fault that he wrote a dreadful script and then is not
a good director of actors. Not his fault. I shouldn't say all the same people. Who knows?
It might be different people. But my point is whatever. That's an unfair point for me to make
or parallel for me to make. I realize that. I retract. People went after the Razzies
because all of a sudden the Razzies are in bad taste as if they were always in good taste.
The Razzies immediately apologized and said, we have missed the mark and sometimes you do that.
My whole response to this is that's horseshit. You knew exactly what you were doing.
You didn't give a shit. You thought it was funny and you got called out on it and now all of a
sudden you're going to act like you've had this awakening or epiphany that, oh God, we just never
realized that we could have hurt somebody's feelings. Oh, shut up.
It's the point of the Razzies is to hurt people's feelings. It's the purpose of it.
I think the Razzies have always been shitty and mean in the same way that top 10 worst lists are
shitty and mean doesn't mean I don't enjoy them. Joe and I were watching some Siskel and Ebert
10 worst lists very recently. They're funny. But yeah, the people made this stuff and I'm
sure they get their feelings hurt. We're in a society now where somebody getting their
feelings hurt is the worst thing that can happen. So we have to do away with the Razzies.
You can't say, oh, I don't want to insult a 12 year old. We'll go back to just insulting people
15 and up. You have to be done with this stupid thing or say, fuck you. We're the Razzies, baby.
Those are your two options. You can't go, wow, here's the quote. Sometimes you do things without
thinking. Then you are called out for it. Then you get it. It's why the Razzies were created in
the first place. Shut the fuck up. What? Shut the fuck up. Like you've got some motive behind it
that's pure and good, picking out the shittiest things of the year. The recent valid criticism
of the choice of 11 year old Armstrong as a nominee for one of our awards brought our attention,
brought to our attention. How insensitive we've been in this instance. As a result,
we've removed her name from the final ballot. We also believe a public apology is owed Ms.
Armstrong and wish to say we regret any hurt she experienced as a result of our choices.
There's more. Worse. We have never intended to bury anyone's career.
It is why our Redeemer Award was created. What? There's a Redeemer Award?
We all make mistakes, very much us included. Since our motto is own your own bad. What?
We realize that we ourselves must also live up to it. I mean, you got Drew Barrymore from the
Firestarters saying this is bullying and this will not stand. As usual, everything just goes
completely out of proportion very, very quickly. The Razzies are a stupid, nonsensical, mean thing
and if we want them to keep going, they have to keep being that. And by the way, you can't
do a nice version of calling out the shittiest shit that ever shat. We never intended to bury
anybody's career. Okay, you went after Alicia Silverstone this year. Like she needs to be
picked on as she does one movie every year, you know, in a business where it's impossible
to grow old as a woman. You should get nominated for it. She was in a movie. That's what I mean.
It's like you're going to go after Alicia Silverstone. Pete, you're going to go after
Pete Davidson after he just had a mental break on the set of his TV show and they had to halt
filming. Give me a fucking break that you guys are kid gloving everything. Sylvester Stallone,
by the way, got nominated for Samaritan. It's like Samaritan wasn't a great movie, but it's like
he wasn't bad in it. Yeah, he's just one of those guys they love to go after. I do look,
I love seeing Machine Gun Kelly on this list. I do too. I do too. I don't care what you say about
Leto. You can hate him all you want. He's not a bad actor. You might have thought Morbius sucked,
but he's not a bad actor. Blonde, this is incredible. Blonde is nominated for Razzies and Oscars.
What the fuck is going on, dude? Blonde is a perfect movie for dumb film bros to be like,
it's amazing. It's not a good movie. It's like torture porn without the torture. It's like
for a dream without the point. And this is the problem now. Now that they've apologized
for this little girl, now they're going to have to apologize for, not have to, but it could very
well may come to this. Lorraine Bracco, you're going to pick on an aging woman in Hollywood?
That's fucked up. Pete Davidson, you're going to pick on a kid that's got mental things going on?
That's fucked up. What they should have said was, yeah, guys, you're right. Only people 18
or older from now on, sorry about that, and kept it moving. But they act like now they're human
beings behind this whole thing. They've fucked themselves. It's over. Now, I've never looked at
the Razzie nominations before. I'm doing it for the first time. But what I'm seeing here is they
do jokes in the nominations. I didn't know this either. So we got worst screen couple,
Andrew Dominic and his issues with women for blonde. That's a screen cut. The one that made
me laugh was Tom Hanks and his accent and fat suit and Elvis. I was like, that's funny. Andrew
Dominic is a, how was that worst screen? He directed blonde. He directed it. It doesn't make sense.
I love this too. Andrew Dominic and his issues with women. Okay. So then does the girl that starred
in blonde, I'm blanking on her name. Does she have issues with women? Because she happily did the
movie and by the way touted it and is very proud of it. Like fuck off with all this anymore, man.
I'm so tired of this shit. Also in worst screen couple, both real life characters in the fallacious
White House bedroom scene in blonde. So there's a scene where John F. Kennedy forces Marilyn Monroe
to blow him. Very disturbing. And then that's like a joke in the same thing as Andrew Dominic
and his issues with women. I don't get the whole organization why we're giving them press or why
we're talking about them right now, frankly. Andrew Dominic being, I haven't seen blonde,
so I don't know, but Andrew Dominic being one of the only people that's ever in a Hollywood film
called out the shittiness of John F. Kennedy and he's got issues with women because -
Well, the main issue is that's a made up scene. It's very strange in a documentary style movie
to make up a scene of Kennedy forcing Marilyn Monroe to blow him. Well, is it a made up scene
or is it based on hearsay? Who knows? I don't know. I mean, from everything I've read about it,
it didn't happen. I'm sure Kennedy was a scumbag, but to be inventing bad things that happened to
Marilyn Monroe, she had more than enough on her own. Maybe I'm wrong. The Razzies, fuck you.
You're stupid. The reason I enjoy Siskel and Ebert tearing down the 10 worst movies of the year
and not the Razzies is because Siskel and Ebert devoted their entire life to singing the praises
of film. They're men who wrote one Pulitzer Prize, as in Ebert's case, for film criticism.
The Razzies is assholes who have never made anything, throwing darts at a dartboard,
and then once they're called out on it acting like we all look to the Razzies every year
to be like some voice of reason. I mean, fuck off. Yeah, it's all stupid. I hate everything,
including you, Pat. What? I'm all right. I've had it with you. No, I get that. I get it. I'm there
too, but that's fine. What else is happening, Joe? How's the restaurant?
It's good. As I've said in the past, New York makes it so easy. Yeah. They keep small business
open. Yeah. Everything's good. I'm enjoying doing my new hour very much. It's getting tighter and
tighter, better and better. I want to thank everybody that's coming out to the shows.
We've had a lot of sold out shows, including at the residency I've been doing, and it's just been
a really amazing run. I'm looking forward to doing it more and in more places. It's a surprising
turn of events for me. I thought even as recently as a year ago that going on the road and stand up
as a primary thing in my life were not going to be a thing anymore. I was wrong, and it's been
better than ever, so I can't thank everybody enough. There you go. It's a rare positive.
All right. I was on an award show here all of a sudden. Well, you asked me how things were
going. I asked how the restaurant's going. Next thing you know, we got Joe thanking the little
people who supported him on the way up the ladder. Look, I'm like anybody else. You ask how things
are going, I'm going to give you something that equates to money and my career versus some sort
of human achievement. That I have none of. It's Friday. Tomorrow's Saturday. I am not going to
drink this weekend, which means I have no idea what I'm going to do. I'll probably be sitting
in the house both nights. Maybe a museum. Yeah, sure. Maybe the New York Public Library. You look
the microfiche. Museum will knock out a good 90 minutes, and then it's on to cake.
It's tricky. I was going to not drink for a while. Like we've said, I mess up here and there,
but for the most part, it hasn't even been that difficult. But I was thinking about maybe putting
on my dating profiles that I'm sober, or at least I'm sober for a few months or something.
Because all anyone wants to do is grab a drink. You don't want to go straight to dinner and get
stranded with somebody. Made that mistake the other night. So it's like, can you go get coffee?
I don't necessarily need to be hotter and more anxious on a date. I don't love a coffee date.
My buddy put it on his profiles that he's sober, and he said most of the time, the girls that he
talks to and is flirting with or whatever, they're like, so how sober are you? Oh, I don't drink. I
just don't drink at all. Oh, sorry. That's going to be a problem. He says more often than not,
women don't want to be with a guy who's sober, which is really interesting to me.
I mean, look, even if I didn't drink, I wouldn't want somebody that was sober.
I hear that. But how is anyone supposed to improve themselves?
You don't live in an improve -yourself world. We all see the grim end in front of us. We all
realize that it's just a matter of, you know. Yeah, I don't know. That's a tough one. I'll
tell you what I like in the stretches where I don't drink, and it's all based on Seinfeld
and rules of engagement. I love a diner meeting where you sit, you get coffees,
you get a couple desserts. I love it. This is a meeting of friends, or are you talking business?
Either. Business, friends, date, any one of the three. That's a nice alternative to
a bar. There's action, there's people moving around, there's stuff to talk about. A diner
meeting is a good place to meet. Much better than a coffee shop.
I could attempt a diner. I mean, a lot of times, I always hear the girl's voice in my head,
and I hear her in that instance saying, he's taking me to a fucking diner.
Maybe she's not saying that. I don't know. If she's saying that, maybe I don't want to be with her.
But also, too, I'm not saying you say, hey, honey, how about a great Friday night at the diner?
Saying you want to meet instead of a drink. Hey, let's go meet at this place. We'll get a
coffee and some pie and some cake. It'll be fun. I'll give it a shot. I know when Christian Slater
did that in True Romance, it seemed nice, and it worked out. He got Patricia Arquette out of the
deal. Wait, say that again? Christian Slater takes Patricia Arquette out for pie in True Romance,
and it leads to them being lovers. It worked for him. That's a classic Tarantino thing, a
absolutely gorgeous babe going to see three karate movies by herself and then wanting afterwards
to go get some pie and discuss it. That's not something you find in real life. It's like how
in movies, whenever our hero walks into a bar, there's always an incredibly beautiful woman
sitting alone at the bar with no one speaking to her, which I have never seen in my entire life
once. The movie, they lie to us. They give us false expectations and false hope. The
Tarantino was just at the comedy store. Saw a bunch of pictures with some of my friends with
him talking to him outside. Annie Letterman had a really funny caption on her Instagram. She had a
picture of her talking to Tarantino, and she wrote, she wrote, how cool is this place? A chance
meeting of Quentin Tarantino and Brett Butler. I miss old Brett. Yeah, it was a very, very, very
funny book. And in the picture, Annie's wearing a leopard print coat. She does kind of look
like Brett Butler. It was very funny. I just finished his book, Cinema Speculation,
Speculation. Really enjoyed it. He's a great writer, obviously, but it was the most
egoless writing I've ever seen him do. He never once slips into that. All right, obviously I'm
the master of this, the kind of stuff that he can't keep himself from saying in interviews. He doesn't
say it in the book. He's just a great film writer. There's, there's, hold on. There's a moment of
that though, because I listened to the audio book and it is, but then the first chapter where he's
like, he's like, picture that little cue watching. Oh yeah. All right, quit and take it easy.
But the first chapter is about, uh, hello, Papa, whatever the fuck that movie's called that you've
talked about. Where's Papa? Yeah. Yeah. I had seen most of the movies he discussed. I have yet to
listen to his podcast, which I hear is great. And I'm excited to check those movies out too.
He's doing it with Roger Avery, who he wrote Pulp Fiction with, and then Roger Avery killed someone
with his car while drinking, I believe. And now they're, they're friends again. But, um. Hey dude,
how great if his 10th movie was him and Avery writing together again? It would be great. I
think they did Dogs together too, I think. No, that was just Pulp Fiction, but, um. Oh, well, okay.
He should do. He's got too big an ego. He'll never write with somebody again, but he should.
As his final thing, it should be a sequel to Pulp Fiction, just meaning same universe,
four intertwining pulpy stories. Yes. Close it out. That's the one that really puts you on the map.
Full circle. You got Avery back in the house. Maybe you have a Marcellus Wallace dip in or
whatever, and you do your fucking picture. I'm with you. I'd obviously be there regardless.
I love what the man does, and I really enjoyed both of his books. Um, yeah, I was very pleased
with Cinema Speculation, and I finally finished Made Men, the book about the making of Goodfellas,
which I started literally three years ago. How was it? And was loving it, but didn't finish.
It's great. It's just, it's, um, it goes through the movie kind of minute by minute
while telling you stories about how it all came to be. I mean, it's, it's got all kinds of great
information, great tales. Uh, the movie was going that the only way the studio was going to greenlight
this movie for a long time was if the two leads were Tom Cruise and Madonna. And Scorsese was like,
I think Tom Cruise is an excellent actor. He's completely wrong for this. And I'm not going to
entertain Madonna. Don't bring her name up to me again, basically. Um, and you know, it's a good
thing he's stuck by it. I think now it's so much, can we get a star in this role? And that's what
De Niro was. De Niro was like, if you're going to cast Ray Liotta and Lorraine Bracco, we need a
Nero at the top. And that all worked out for the best. But now it's all so star -based that you just
wind up with people who are just not right for parts. Like that movie would totally be Tom Cruise
and Madonna today. And nobody would think twice. Um, and that's why it wouldn't be the classic. I
mean, then the movie would not be the classic it is with that cast. It just, some movies you look
back and everything fits perfectly. It brings us to our upcoming episode that had Joe had a great
idea about movies that would have been better with a different, not better, but just you could have,
I don't mean better, but just, you know, a recasting. I, I, the idea is, what are we going to do?
We're going to say, you know, who would have been worse? No, no, no, no. Don Knotts would have been
worse. It's quite the opposite of either thing. You said it's saying it's taking a role where we've
said, I can't imagine anybody else in this role. And then going, you know what? Actually this guy
is the one person I think that also could have done it. Okay. Okay. You know, that's all not
better. Not worse. Just, just, you know, Oh, that actually would be interesting. That could work,
you know? Yes. Sure. Yeah. Um, let me take us down to the movie corn. If I
play may, um, I watched last tango in Paris.
So the only time what's, what's your take on the film? That's, that's, that's upsetting.
I feel like there's no reason for it to exist other than to laugh at how upsetting it is.
Yeah. I mean, I saw it when I was real young. It was one of my sneak out of the videos for
store in the Tucker, the man and his dream case movies. And I just remember being like, boy,
this is not as fun as show girls. This is not really arousing me at all. This is making me
feel horrible. But, uh, the premise of the movie is Marlon Brando right as he's settling into
middle age. He's not like, uh, in that weird Dr. Moreau phase where he was losing his mind.
Um, and he's not obese yet. He's just getting older. He's very, very depressed. The movie opens
with him screaming like, that's really had the first scene of the movie is him screaming. Yeah.
Um, his lady friend has just committed suicide. And so he throws himself into a sexual relationship
with a young woman, half his age. He says, no, there's going to be no names. I don't want any
backstory, just straight fucking. And that's basically what they do. And, uh, of course,
there are some feelings caught as often happen in these explicitly sexual relationships, but
the movie when I was growing up was always, always, always on top 10 of all time lists,
always. When I watched it, I was obviously too young for it. Hadn't even had sex at that point,
but I was like, this does not seem like one of the all time great movies.
Then a few years back controversy struck and the story was reported that Bernardo Bertolucci,
the director and Marlon Brando sprung a rape scene on the young actress who plays the
quote love interest. And I remember that day on Twitter, Jessica Chastain and all these people,
like this was, I thought this was a classic film. I'm disgusted. I'm nauseous and everybody getting
us. And I myself thought at that time, Oh my God, how incredibly fucked up that because the story
was reported as Marlon Brando had sex with this woman against her will. That's not what happened.
There was a rape scene in the script and they added the element, which is now the most famous
scene of the movie of Marlon Brando going, go and get the butter where she gets butter.
He shoves the butter into her ass and has sex with her, which is not graphically done. I mean,
it's, it's implied, but it's, it's certainly gets your attention. And it's the strangest thing.
I put it up on letterbox. A buddy of mine wrote me, you rewatched last tango in Paris. Really?
Cause it's supposed to be this document that's like burned and never seen again
because it contains this assault. I think it's beyond fucked up to spring anything in a scene
on an actress, but that's what what the hell was, what the hell was being sprung that he riffs,
go get the butter. That's what's being, what is being sprung from what I can gather. That's
what happened. I wasn't there. The ad libs a crazy line and now that's, that's a, she's like,
don't want, you know, a man shoving butter in my ass. I don't want to be on film doing that.
But did he shove the butter in her ass? No, no. So that's what's really interesting to me. And
like, I feel weird talking about it, but I know that many, many people are under the impression
that this woman was legitimately sexually assaulted on set, but there was a rape scene
in the script. Maybe I'm mistaken, but I read a lot about this the other night on Wikipedia and
IMDb and all the things to try to figure out how this got so convoluted. And it seems like Bertolucci
was kind of a perv. There's a whole subplot in this movie of the girl's boyfriend is a French
director who's trying to make her do stuff against her will. That's a subplot of the movie,
which is kind of fucked up. What is an actress herself said? She came forward before her death
and said, she felt raped by it. She said, it felt like this little like boys club where they were
spring and, and Bertolucci claims I would, I didn't want her reacting as an actress. I wanted her
reacting as a woman. Okay. All right. Well then that's, yeah, there's your fucked up. And when
you see this scene of Marlon Brando sort of pushing her face down into the ground and he's behind her
as far as I can gather from my detective work, that was all in the script, but the direction
that the scene went within the scene was not discussed. Nowadays that would be beyond the
pale because you have intimacy coordinators. Anytime two people even kiss, you have to do that
in the seventies. This was a time when Dustin Hoffman would slap Meryl Streep to get a genuine
reaction out of her. The lines were very blurry. Whatever went on on this set seems to have made
a lot of people uncomfortable, including Marlon Brando, by the way, who said, who like parted ways
with Bertolucci and said he didn't like the way he got performances and so on. The movie has become
deeply controversial and is another one that I think in five years time is going to be just
impossible to find, but it's because people think it contains footage of an actual sexual
assault. What I am saying is that it's grayer than that from what I gathered, but was certainly a
fucked up situation. The movie itself, look, as an older guy who has kind of tried to throw myself
into relationships that weren't working and, you know, tried to do the sex with no feelings thing
etc. A lot of it hits home because both parties are just trying to feel better and they're both
doing something that makes you feel better, which is sex, but it's also self -destructive. I think
the themes of the movie are pretty interesting and Brando is great in it, but it's always going to
be tainted now by the methods of how they got the movie, and I don't think the movie was ever this
masterpiece that it's made out to be. Certainly an interesting and controversial film. Joe?
I re -watched The Color of Money. Oh, love it. Which I hadn't seen. Scorsese and Cruz.
Yeah, I haven't seen it in years. I saw it, well actually I only saw it once,
I think when I was in college or something. Watched it on an airplane. God damn, it's a good movie.
This is when a movie was a movie, baby. The Color of Money. That was Scorsese saying, by the way,
because I just read about this, that was Scorsese being like, oh fuck, after hours bombed and
everything he's doing is not working, and it was like, I need a studio hit. That was a studio hit
back then. Yeah, that's wild. I'm going to do a sequel to The Hustler, which is an awesome movie.
Yeah. It's fucking great. It's a sequel to The Hustler. It's based on the book,
but very loosely, that was written by the same author that wrote the book of The Hustler.
It really only shares the title. This movie takes place, I don't know, 25 or 30 years later,
whatever the hell it is, 20 years later. Paul Newman, star of the original film, is now out
of the pool game, and he is selling, he's a liquor rep that sells booze to bars. It opens with him
kind of sweet talking a woman that you find out eventually he has an actual romantic relationship
with to buy some whiskey, and it's a great scene because he is in fact in his own way hustling her
to buy this whiskey that isn't as good as he's saying it is. And what happens? He hears from
across the room the breaking of pool balls and realizes something special is happening
at the pool table, and there he finds Tom Cruise, who becomes his protege. It's in that moment
I immediately realized, oh my god, Kingpin is an exact parody of The Hustler. I was waiting to say
it. I was waiting to say it because when he hears the ball hit the pin in Kingpin,
when I watch Kingpin after having seen Color of Money, it's got added laughs because it's
a true spoof. It's like a true almost scene for scene parody. Yeah, and it's wild because
they're like, they could have been like, the logical thing would have, not logical, but you
know, the immediate idea would be let's do a spoof of The Hustler, and then somebody clearly
was like, no, no, no, let's do a spoof of the sequel. But it's just an awesome movie. He takes
Tom Cruise and Mary Elizabeth Mastrantonio, who plays Tom Cruise's girlfriend in the movie,
on the road. She understands what all this is about. Tom Cruise doesn't. He's just an amazing
pool player, and Paul Newman is trying to get him to do one simple thing, play to the best of his
ability and to stop showing his ass. And Tom Cruise can't, I mean, Tom Cruise, every, the whole
fucking movie is amazing. Every person in it is awesome, is so awesome. Turturro, right? Turturro's
in it. He plays Newman's original protege, who's like a cokehead, who he drops for Tom Cruise.
Cruise is just a smacked ass in this thing, but he's great. And him and Newman are doing the
shot, the trick shots for real. This is pre -CGI and whatever. You're actually seeing them do
these shots. It's incredible. Forest Whitaker pops up as a hustler that hustles Paul Newman,
and it's like this devastating scene where Paul Newman starts feeling himself again,
and getting back into actually playing pool, and then he gets hustled, and it's devastating.
And the movie culminates with the two of them having to go head to head at this pool championship.
Newman beats Cruise, and then finds out that Cruise threw the match,
and is proud of himself. I threw this in the way that you taught me to throw matches,
because I knew the odds were on me, and I could make all this money if I threw the match,
and I finally listened to you and threw a match instead of having to win by all means necessary.
And Paul Newman is devastated. And then the final scene is Paul Newman goes to Tom Cruise and goes,
I want a game with you one -on -one. No money, nothing, whatever. I want your best game.
Paul Newman breaks the balls, and he does this whole speech about if you beat me tonight,
I'm going to come back and whoop you at this competition down in Florida. And if you beat
me in Florida, I'm going to come back and whoop you in Dallas. And then he does the break,
and he goes, I'm back. And you realize that's what the whole movie was. In the final 10 seconds,
you realize the whole movie was about Paul Newman becoming the fucking pool shark again,
and the redemption of this character. It does break my heart that there was originally a scene
in the movie that was going to bring Gleason back as Minnesota Fats, and him and Newman were
going to have a scene together. And you want to talk about a different time in cinema. Gleason
and Newman decided this doesn't fit well enough into the story. It doesn't need to be in the movie.
And they said no. And I wish it would have happened because it probably would have been
Gleason's literal final film role, and Gleason's best role outside of Ralph Cramden is Minnesota
Fats. But if you've not seen The Color of Money, first watch The Hustler, and then watch The Color
of Money. You could watch both out of order. It doesn't matter. But do yourself a favor and watch
these two pictures. I'm going to watch both this weekend. It's been too long on both, and I thank
you for bringing it back to my attention. I own them. I'm going to buy the both. As I'm talking,
I'm like, why do I not own these? I'm buying these both. Yes. I would like to shout out
a holiday movie that I feel like is just starting to get little glimmers of respect,
The Family Stone. Recommended it to Joe. He did not watch it. I hope he does at some point. I think
he'll like it quite a bit. But Family Stone. Let me read you this cast. Dermot Mulroney, Sarah
Jessica Parker, Diane Keaton, Luke Wilson, Claire Danes, Rachel McAdams, Craig T. Nelson.
It's a who's who. The premise of the movie is Mulroney is bringing home Sarah Jessica Parker
to meet his very close -knit family. The sort of secret they're hiding, because these movies always
need a family secret, is that Diane Keaton has cancer. There is a shocking scene in this movie
where Craig T. lays down with her. It's a PG -13 movie, but she shows him. She wants to fuck,
and she reveals this missing breast, and he puts his hand on the scar. It's just a movie. It's a
holiday family movie that goes way darker and way more real than you'd expect at every turn. It's
perfect. I think it's an amazing movie. I really do. It reminds me of Once Around, which is the
great Richard Dreyfuss, Holly Hunter, Danny Aiello movie that is pretty much impossible to find for
some reason, but they're good sort of pioneers of this awkward comedy. There's a scene in this that
is rough, because Sarah Jessica Parker plays a woman that the family doesn't like at all,
but it's not really her fault. She's just different than they are, and they're so tight.
It's like when you're dating somebody and you realize you're never going to get away into this
family. They're too close. Whereas when I bring a woman into my family, they're so excited to have a
new energy around that can make our gatherings less tense and uncomfortable. But some of these
families that really are successful and really love each other, they don't let newcomers in,
and that's what Sarah Jessica Parker is experiencing. I've felt like her character
before where you just can't win, but it all builds to this scene that plays even more shocking now
than it did at the time because of how much attitudes have changed in 20 years. But there's
in the family, it is the brother who is deaf, and then he is engaged to this guy, and they want to
have kids. And Sarah Jessica Parker, who's always trying to just connect with people in the family,
and she is genuinely interested and cares, but she's like, you wouldn't want the kid to be gay,
would you? And they're like, what are you talking about? And she's like, well, I mean, why would
want their kid to be gay? And what she's trying to say, you understand her point, is why would
anyone want their kid to be gay in a world that is so harsh to gay people? But the only way it is
coming out of her mouth is why would anyone hope for their kid to be gay? And then she starts
talking about nature versus nurture, and aren't you worried with two dads that the kid will just
automatically be gay, whether it wants to be gay or not? This is like a holiday dinner.
Diane Keaton starts going, she's slamming on the table like, shut her up, shut her up, and Craig
T's like, all right, calm down. Craig T's perfect in this movie, he's amazing. He's trying to keep
everybody civil, and then she keeps going, and then Craig T goes, all right, shut up. Like,
he turns on Sarah Jessica Parker. The scene is so painful and uncomfortable, and the movie is funny
on top of everything else, that I watched it again as like, it's the perfect way to do awkward
comedy where you understand everyone's point of view. It's the only way that it really works.
If it's just somebody being a fucking asshole, it doesn't work. It works when everybody is trying
to do their best and failing miserably. I think the movie understands dysfunctional families more
than way more praised movies on the subject. I think it's great as a Christmas movie,
great as a romantic comedy, great as a awkward comedy, and eventually very, very moving and
touching. Luke Wilson is awesome in it. The first word, it understands character. The first thing
she says to Luke Wilson as he walks in is Diane Keaton goes, I'm only going to say this once,
you are not to smoke pot in this house. While you're home for Christmas, you are not to smoke
pot in this house, and every character gets that moment where you understand who that character is
from one line of dialogue. Rachel McAdams is playing a total bitch in the movie. She hates Sarah
Jessica Parker. Never seen that side of her. She's great in it. Obviously, I love the film.
Check it out if you haven't seen it. People either hate it or love it. I strongly love it. I recommend.
All right. Excuse me. I'm only going to do one more because I get hung up on the themes
of my movie corners, but my second one is also a sequel.
It's a rewatch and it has a new psycho tied to it too. I rewatched for the second time Ghost
Busters Afterlife. My mom had not seen it when I was home at Christmas. We watched it together.
She loved it. Second watch, I got to say, I liked it even more the second time.
The Ghost Busters coming in at the end did not feel tacked on or anything. It seemed to be much
more organic and appropriate. The similarities between the original film and this one were far
less glaring. This felt like its own piece of work and a very good sequel and a very good,
I don't want to say attempt. It just felt like a good, well executed reboot
or equal, whatever the fuck the term is. I loved it. I laughed a lot with my folks.
You know, Paul Rudd, the character podcast, everybody in it is great.
It's awesome when they do show up at the end. I just loved it. I just thought it was great.
I am very, very excited that they have confirmed that the sequel is definitely happening.
They announced it a while back, but they just confirmed the sequel is going to take place in
London, which I think is very cool. And Murray, Ackroyd, and Hudson are all signed on officially
to come back. And not just how they came back last time? I'm assuming now they'll be way more
in a featured role like their mentors to the new group. Oh, and Sigourney Weaver is signed on to
So I'm excited. I think it's going to be a really cool sequel. And yeah, I'm there for it, man.
I bought the box set on Amazon of the real Ghostbusters cartoon, which I also really like.
And I've been thoroughly enjoying that. I even went back and rewatched Ghostbusters 2 and I was
like, all right, now that I got some distance, it's a lot more enjoyable than I thought it was.
Never hated Ghostbusters 2. Never had an issue with it.
The end is, I really hate the end. I hate the Statue of Liberty thing. I don't like it.
I like that it's a parallel where it's like, look, the big thing isn't attacking the city,
it's helping it and inspiring hope. That's like a nice, interesting parallel.
But you know, man, I don't know.
Bill Murray in these movies for me, it's like a Tom Hanks thing. I've rewatched The Burbs twice
this week just because I just put it on when I was doing stuff. And Bill Murray and Tom Hanks
are in that same category where I'm like, please just do a thing where you're the guy again.
I'm excited to see more Bill Murray where he's just Bill Murray again and not doing some
fucking accent and whatever. And same with Tom Hanks. How bad. Dude, you rewatched The Burbs.
You want to see Tom Hanks so bad again just being Tom Hanks.
Yeah. You're not going to get it.
Yeah. And it's just like -
You're not going to get it from Murray either.
Well, you get it in Ghostbusters. That's where I'm excited that he's coming back.
Hopefully. Yeah. I didn't feel it in the last one. But I mean, that to me was the one real bad
element of that first Ghostbusters after life. What's that?
The CGI, them coming up at the end.
It didn't look - when I rewatched it, I was like, I don't think they're on screen. I think this was
shot on a set because the entire thing now, I'm like, this makes more sense to me. I don't know.
It didn't look as - it just looked - I don't know. The whole thing just made sense more to me,
visually, story -wise, everything. I just enjoyed it. But my point is I'm happy that
we might get to see Venkman be Venkman again. And I hope that Tom Hanks at some point does
some sort of - I was hoping for it with a man called Otto. I was like, oh, cool. This might
be like Hanks being Hanks again. And it's not. No, it sure wasn't.
I did not like that movie. My parents loved it. Not for me. I would love to shout out a little
something that's on Amazon Prime. Also, apparently a fuller version is on YouTube. It is called -
let me locate it so I get the exact title - The Making of Rocky versus Drago by Sylvester Stallone.
It is a black and white shot on iPhone look at Sylvester Stallone in the editing room
re -editing Rocky IV. Over the pandemic, there are masks lying around. It is no frills at all.
It feels like the kind of thing that would have been a special feature back in the day,
and I'm sure it's on the Rocky IV Blu -ray, whatever. But you can watch about an hour -long
version on Amazon Prime. This thing just started up when I finished 13 Lives and I wound up
watching it. Stallone is so charming. He looks fantastic. He's got to be 70 plus.
And he's just talking - he reminded me of, you know, that no matter how legendary this guy is,
people always think they could have done things better. Think if they had another chance,
they'd fix it. You know, that's what truly kills people about working in the arts.
And you can see it just eats him up. He watches a scene from Rocky IV. It looks great,
and he's just like, who would shoot it that way? I didn't know what I was - I was so stupid. Why
would I do that? And then he'll tweak the scene in a very minor way that maybe your average viewer
wouldn't even notice. And he's just like, oh my god, it feels so good to correct that after all
these years. It's kind of a beautiful thing. It's a man talking about his whole career kind of
through the filter of this one movie. He talks about how he's been too vain at different points
in his life, and he wishes he had known then what he knows now and all that. It's a legend of cinema.
You got to be real. Stallone is a legend of cinema, reflecting on his career. And it's just
really, really special and nice. I really had a great time watching it. And apparently there's
a 90 -minute version of it on YouTube. For me, the hour -long version was more than enough.
If you're a die -hard Rocky IV fan, probably check out that 90 -minute version. But well worth
watching. Really interesting. And a look into the editing room that you just rarely get with people,
especially nowadays when they won't put forth the money for special features. Which is hilarious
because you see that Stallone had a friend shoot him on his iPhone and made a really compelling
90 -minute special feature. It's not hard to do. They just don't care about the consumer anymore.
So did you see that new version of it? No, I wanted to watch this first and I'm excited to see it.
I'm excited to see it too. I think Rocky IV sucks and I think it's the worst of the
the series. Yeah, it's just like a big long montage pretty much. And he's like obviously
the robots coming out, you know. But when he's talking about all these cuts that he's making,
I'm like Stallone, you're talking about a movie that's already like 84 minutes. I don't know
how much you're going to get out of it. But I do want to see the new cut. For me, it's all about
Rocky I, II, and Balboa in terms of the greats. I loved Creed also. Stallone talking about Rocky
I and II is some of my favorite stuff in the cinema speculation book. He prefers II,
which is a classic Tarantino thing, but I really love II as well. So I really liked how much
he got out of that movie. Creed I is excellent. Creed II sucks. You know, I love Rocky Balboa.
I love Rocky I. I love Rocky III and I like Rocky V. I think II is the second worst of the group
and III is, to me, or I mean IV is absurd. And IV is when they turn him into like a superhero
and it's just so stupid. So I was excited to hear about this recut. I just haven't seen it yet.
He's just, you know, you feel like sitting down with
who are some of his compatriots of the day. You know, you feel like the same thing with like a
Van Damme or something or Seagal would be miserable. You forget how truly intelligent
and fun to listen to Stallone is. He's the best. And he's just really gets what people want
out of movies. And he's been, you know, I wish we got another Copland. I don't think that's going
to happen, but we got that one and it's a masterpiece. I'm going to watch Tulsa King
just because I love it. Even though I haven't heard tons of great stuff, some people love it.
Some people are like, eh, but I'm going to watch it just because I'm like, you know, what am I
going to do? Walk away mad that I watched charming Stallone? Yeah, I've heard it sucks, but he's
charming and, you know, I might give it a look too. But anyway, sick, sick, sick, sick, sick,
sick. Queens of Stonehenge. Sick is a movie co -written by Kevin Williamson, the writer
of Scream and many lesser products such as I know what you did last summer. And the faculty and,
you know, he wrote a lot of shitty horror too, but the blueprint seems to kind of be Scream.
It starts with a sort of seemingly unrelated killing of, I guess, a gay dude who's at the
grocery store and everything is cleaned out. He's not gay. He's not? No, in fact.
Oh, okay. Yeah. Well, I just thought he's getting like look at your ass grinder messages and so
forth. No, he's not getting grinder message. No, I know who it is and who it becomes. Sometimes I
wonder what it is you're doing as you watch these movies. I was sober as a judge and could very
clearly tell you the plot of this. I don't mean substances. I mean, I just picture you're like
under the couch looking for a golf ball that ran out and rolled under there. You're like, wait,
what happened? Anyway, no, he's in the grocery store and he gets attacked. It starts with a guy
in a grocery store. It's the pandemic. He's wearing his mask. Everybody's wearing their mask.
Everything's bought up. He grabs for something. The lady grabs the last one. Which, by the way,
that lady that he goes to grab the last thing of toilet paper or something and the lady just
grabs it and she's holding a kid. She goes, seriously, dude? I would have been like,
yeah, seriously, lady, get the fuck out of my face. Like, oh my God. But anyway. Yeah,
you handle things differently than most. They do a good job of
of immediately showing you like like when he walks out of the I'm getting a little ahead of
myself, but let me just I'll come back around to it. When he walks out of the grocery store with
his mask off, that guy goes, where's your mask, dude? They do a good job of immediately capturing
like the tension and attitude of everybody when an exceptional job, an exceptional job
of recapturing that time to a point where I was like, do I even want to watch this?
But he's in the one thing that's off is
immediately he's in the line, right? And it's he gets the text and it says, do you want to hang
out? And he says, who is this? And they say, are you safe? Are you tested and clean or whatever?
That's the one thing that's off. Those tests were not available yet. This is very much portrayed as
the very beginning of the initial lockdown and whatever. Those fucking tests were not available
for months and months and months. So maybe it's not. No, it is the initial because they're
leaving school over it. And I think they put up on there like March 2020 on the. Yeah. So that's
the one thing where that's not accurate. But who cares? He gets the text when he's staying in line
and then the guy and then the tech starts saying like, nice ass, what are you doing? And then he
immediately starts being like, who the fuck is this? Lose my number. Not because he's mad about
the ass comment. He's but he's like, stop fucking around because people do do that. He turns around
and he's like, oh, there must be somebody behind me. Flicks off the line, blah, blah, blah. Yeah.
Goes back to his I guess it's his college, whatever. And a person breaks in all masked up,
not like scream, but like covid style, messed up, but with a hood and stuff.
And and and it's a brutal murder scene. It's but it's it's it's it's exactly the opening of scream.
It's it is a phone thing that's creepy and then the person gets brutally murdered. It's its own
little standalone movie. I don't know if Kevin Williamson wrote this and then the young woman
who co -wrote it with him was added later. My guess is she had a really clever premise for a
horror movie and Williamson was brought in to rewrite it as my guess. But from there we follow
these two girls who are going to their parents like getaway cabin for the weekend. The one daughter
is Pamela Adlon's other daughter. The other the first one was an ill raiser. Nepo baby much.
And it's there and they're leaving college and they established like they're going to do
a quarantine hang like this is like what we were all doing at this time like they're going to
quarantine together. They start getting weird texts as well. Some I see you I'm watching you
that kind of stuff. She thinks it's a guy she's dating. Yes. Who does show up. Correct. At some
point and this is it's not really revealed in the trailer. The trailer has the funniest gag in the
movie which is the girl runs up to a car and is like there's a guy trying to count me let me in
let me in. The driver goes do you have a mask. Are you fucking kidding me. They they edited it
together in the trailer to actually be a much funnier bit. In the movie it's not it's played
more real but I thought that was a great bit. Yes. The whole movie is a commentary on COVID
hysteria from from all angles. It's people not taking it seriously enough. It's people taking
it way too seriously as you find out eventually. But the point is is these women are being stalked
or hunted by the same killer as the guy you saw at the beginning or at least he's in the same costume
or get up. The boy that comes to see her that she's dating who says the texts were not me. I
swear he gets murdered and then and then the the killer who we find out later is killers. There's
a few of them. Much like in Scream. Yeah. And it's a mother figure much like in Scream 2 or
Friday the 13th. Yeah it's yeah you find out it's a family and it's a mother husband and son.
And this this is where that that reveal comes later but this is where the movie started to
become problematic for me because it was like okay we're like not even halfway through and we're
down to two characters. We've seen two deaths. We've got two characters left.
True it's when now we're just like I'm not that like checked like I'm just like what are we I gotta
watch I'm just gonna watch these two like clearly they're not both gonna die like so like I've just
felt like where do we go from here now you know. And when the boyfriend comes in you're immediately
like it's obviously not going to be this possessive boyfriend character who walks in
seconds after the first creepy thing happens. That would be too obvious and too easy.
So once you know it's not him it takes the real who done it out of it. I mean you're basically
waiting for some character you haven't met to come in and say I'm the killer. So it's not a
murder mystery in that regard. It's not like Scream where it's which one of these 30 people
is the killer. To me the motive when it comes and obviously we're getting into spoilers here
but it's Jane Addams who I love from Happiness and many many many many indie movies. Don't forget
Frazier. Frazier of course yes. A big fan of hers. She is funny in this but she basically plays the
mom the dad is there as well. They have a video showing that in their mind this girl who they are
trying to kill and the guy from the beginning played a role in getting their son or daughter
Joe sorry. Their son. Their son passed away from COVID. Yeah they overpower the one son that's there
to kill them and they actually do kill him. Then it's revealed from the parents they had a second
son who's dead. He died on a ventilator because of COVID. Why did he get COVID? Well he contracted
it because the main character Adlon's daughter threw a COVID party. Like she was one of those
people that was like ooh fuck COVID hashtag fuck COVID and threw a party. She made out with the
guy in the cold open. He's who gave it to her. She then spread it to people at that party. One
of those people eventually gave it to her son outside of the party. This reveal of the motive
to me was I was like okay I get what we're watching here. We're watching a COVID horror movie.
I understand how this ties in and all that. I didn't really have a big problem with that.
So they're there now to kill her because she killed their son. I didn't have a problem with
the connective tissue there. I just thought from here on out every part of it was executed so
poorly. It was so corny. It was just poorly acted. The dialogue got really bad here because up until
this point every scene between one of the girls and the killer it was so well directed and so
well done. Every time they outsmarted the killer or overpowered the killer or whatever it was I
was like everything made perfect fucking sense. I was like this is really good. I really believe
this guy is going at them full force and they are actually getting away from him by the skin
of their teeth. All of it made sense and now in this part they just drive the theme home so hard
and it's just dumb. It's just dumb like the mom. The girl tied up on the couch crying
I don't have COVID and the mom going you are asymptomatic. It's not played for laughs. It's
doesn't work. It's corny. It's stupid. It's really stupid. I disagree. I think the action stuff was
directed well. This guy is John Hyams who is the son of Peter Hyams who was a great kind of
journeyman director of the 80s. Peter Hyams directed what's what? We are nepo -ing all over
the place. I know. Peter Hyams did Timecop with Van Damme, the relic 2010, the year we made
Contact. He was a pretty big director and his son does like universal soldier directed cable sequels
but this film reviewer I love always writes about him as being this great director of action
and I think so. I mean the slasher stuff to me we had complete opposite reactions to this movie.
I thought the opening was very effective as a little standalone mini slasher movie.
From there I thought it was a competent well -directed slasher and I didn't give a
shit about it at all. When they brought in the COVID stuff I said oh now this is very interesting.
I do have a soft spot for Jane Addams. I did think there was some intentional comedy her running down
the street on fire at the end. Hold on, don't skip. Let's get to it. I don't want you to skip
ahead. I'm sorry I'm not trying to tell you what to say but I felt like you were on a good course
but then you skipped to the end. That's how I felt. I thought all of the discussion about
COVID and the parents being really angry and looking for anyone to blame
really tied into to this paranoia and the feeling people were having about COVID. Now
there haven't been to my knowledge any real movies dealing with COVID so this all felt sort
of fresh new maybe not the perfect COVID horror movie but a really good sort of BB plus attempt
at doing a horror movie about this thing that affected us all and I thought that it was really
a good time. It was effective. It was short and I thought the twists when they came were really
cool and worked. I like the the mask with um what do you call it? What do you call it? Chloroform.
Yeah I mean that scene she gives her a mask that has chloroform on it. Some of the stuff you're
kind of like well wait but what happens though she gives her just for the people that haven't
seen it. I mean she who gives who a mask with chloroform on it?
Is there something you want to say Joe? No no I'm saying just talk elaborate on what you're
saying. I'm saying you you just said she gives her a mask with Chloroform. Jane Addams gives
Adlon's daughter. There's only three characters in the movie. Right but but but and then she passes
out or something like I'm asking. I don't remember that part. Oh well she yeah she gives it to her
and then that's she's running away. She runs up to this woman for help but she winds up running
up to the woman who's trying to kill her. Okay okay. She puts she gives her a mask. If you're
going to get in my car you have to wear this mask and then the mask has chloroform on it. That's
right that's right. Now that's that's cool however it's a bit dumb that this woman is driving around
with a chloroform soaked mask and knows that this girl is going to run up to her car. There's
elements of this movie that's that's strained credibility. Don't get me wrong. Look he's a
great action director. All these critics are right. He doesn't direct performance as well.
I'm sorry. You as a director you have to know that when Jane Addams yells you are asymptomatic
and the way that she does it's a bad take and you need to do it a different way. It's a bad take.
Uh there there is and I stand by this. There is zero intentional humor in this film. The part
Pat was referring to earlier is in the final moments of this movie Jane Addams who's the
last surviving member of this murderous family they manage to light her on fire and that's how
she finally dies which is stupid in my opinion because every part of this movie was so tied into
Covid. You should kill her in a way that's Covid related that you don't give her Covid but
or maybe you do. I don't fucking know but I just thought it was dumb to just light her on. I was
like it's a it's a visual and it's stupid and it's got nothing to do with anything and who cares.
Right. But aside from that I can live with that. Jane Addams then runs down the street on fire
Daffy Duck style going oh oh oh oh oh and it's absurd. It's absurd and I don't give a shit if
that moment is supposed to be funny or not. In a movie that took itself this seriously and had
no humor up until that point it doesn't work. It doesn't work. It's a goofy fucking Looney Tunes
ending on a movie that's trying to say something. This movie is desperately trying to say something
and much to my surprise it seems like it's trying to say more so than not that people that took
Covid too seriously are fucking crazy. That's a surprise swing coming out of a Hollywood studio.
It certainly has you sympathizing far more with the people that violated Covid rules than the ones
that took it seriously. Yeah. You know for instance the lady in the supermarket at the beginning
she's an asshole to the kid just because he merely tries to grab a package of toilet paper.
He submits to her. When he walks outside without his mask on and the guy yells at him
it's like dude he's outside fucking relax you know or whatever. The guy that yells at him
seems like an asshole. He gets murdered for going to a fucking party. These two girls get tortured
for going to for having a party. You know and especially with the movie coming out now with
hindsight we have it seems certainly to to point it's to target far more the people that took it
all too seriously than the people that didn't which is sort of confusing again because it's
a Hollywood movie but that's driven home by the fact that Jane Addams is her character has shown
zero sympathy in the last moments of this movie and in fact set on fire
and left to comically run down the street. I just kind of I mean what did you want like the
like her to get like stabbed in the nose or something like stabbed through the nostril
or something like that? I think like yeah maybe if it was like they took a this is a terrible
that's not terrible it's just not good enough but like you take a long q -tip and you you jam it up
her nostril and it stabs her in the brain and she dies. Like for every part of this to be so
COVID connected and then just have it does it does start with like the crawl of like by April
2020 this many people had died or been infected and it doesn't you know it's not that serious a
I think what you're what you're explaining as like
they they don't or we don't know who we're siding with I think that is a fault of the
screenplay for sure I think if they had decided something they wanted to say about COVID
then this would have been a more effective movie they really don't and maybe that's because it's
political discussion and it's still ongoing but there it is pretty wishy -washy about its themes
and what it wants you to believe you're right the people who are punished are the people who were
taking COVID seriously that is a very strange thing to do in a movie like this if that's your
I don't know that they they gave it enough thought in terms of thematically what they
were trying to say and maybe I just looked at it as more of a straight slasher and therefore it
didn't bother me I think I did think it wasn't slapping my knee but I definitely think there
were humor attempts throughout in his not as as as scream was but they are doing the same shit
more half -assed versions of it but they're talking about famous horror movies from the past
the girls are saying funny things amongst themselves etc I think there's a difference
between but but here's here's where I'll just disagree with you again scream has very intentional
humor throughout the entire thing right now let's just say this did and I missed it what scream
doesn't have is skeet ulrich dying in a funny way yeah that just doesn't work it just doesn't
fucking work and you know look I don't care if the filmmaker maybe Kevin Williamson is like
fuck covid they they they locked us down and we didn't deserve it and it was that he could be one
of the I don't care and if that's his take then great that then make a movie about your take I
don't give a shit I'll watch it or whatever I just didn't I didn't get that from this what I got from
this was let's wouldn't it be interesting if we did a movie where we challenged the viewer by making
the seemingly good guy the bad guy and making the seemingly bad guy the victim
I think that's what they tried to do and I just didn't get that out of it I just I just was like
yeah yeah these people are fucking lunatics and like and and and I don't know all right you know
it misses it misses the bullseye it has several chances to really hit a bullseye with what it's
trying to do and say and it doesn't I I grant you that completely I don't think this is a great
movie by any means but I'll take it over let's say Hellraiser another horror movie with another
adlon yeah because it's it's got a pulse it's uh it's it was fun to me it was short it ended
around the time I felt that it should have ended and the the character of making the the mom and
again it might just be my soft spot for Jane Addams but seeing the mom as this crazed villain
when what she's doing is just what Jason's mom was trying to do in Friday the 13th and we know
that Williamson is obsessed with these old horror movies but she's in her mind 110 right so I thought
that even though she wasn't handled realistically certainly I thought that there are real people
like that that scare the shit out of me and they are in the world and making one of them a villain
is so much more interesting than it being just some faceless dude I liked that aspect of it for
sure I agree okay that that that that adds a few points given what you said in my for me
but I'll also say this another major major timeline flub is the contact tracing it's that
that was not a thing yeah I didn't even really think about that but yeah it's true yeah they're
they're like and and these are things that are so easily fixable yeah it's strange everyone
everyone remembers this this is this is very recent history that we all went through and
were scared to death by so they might have just been hoping nobody noticed and it worked on me
but it didn't work on you because there were well there was also a second lockdown there was a
at that point yeah you know it's like these are these are two sentence rewrites where it's like
guys it just makes it make so much more fucking sense man yeah you know I don't know uh it's not
a bad movie I I've softened my take a bit after this discussion and you've convinced me of a few
things it's not a bad movie it's worth a watch I guess I would say my hog is medium out it's not
down but yeah my my hog is sort of I would describe my hog as having uh recently come
oh Jesus so it's kind of just like it's drifting downward but it's got a heaviness to it um
that's it for me folks we don't know what we're doing next time but we know that we will be
doing an episode about uh recasting some of the great roles or if not the great roles then
just roles where we think wouldn't this guy or gal have been great in this role I think that'll
be a fun episode when's the oscars oh geez they just announced the nomination so they'll be in
march probably oh okay so not yet all right uh yeah we'll do that uh well the what pat just said
I mean and um I think Megan will probably I just watched Megan that's that's one of the biggest
recent horror titles so if Joe sees that we'll do that I tried to go I swear to you I tried to go
I had plans we met up me and my buddies to go see Avatar and we were just like we can't do it we
just can't do it we don't have it I completely understand um and my review of that is based
solely on being blisteringly high so I don't you know I did see in our little our patreon I
guess it was when I discussed it on the movie corner or something there was uh this guy
who was like I was out the minute that the aliens said bro which is always a big uh Joe DeRosa
grievance as well people not talking about this both but I'm like are are they even aliens like
that's why you're going in to me arms folded I'm just waiting for one of these avatars to
say the word bro you're not going to enjoy Avatar that's a big complaint online is that like the
the just it's written I think look I think Cameron's strength has never been dialogue
you ain't got to tell me but yeah I think that's the big grievance is that look to me Avatar and
what turns me off from it is in this current climate where everybody's bitching about nepo
babies and everybody's bitching about capitalism and greed and all these things the movie to me
looks like an embarrassment of riches it looks grossly huge in budget it looks like a spectacle
for spectacle's sake and it looks like if you took away that element of it there would be nothing
left now I know I haven't seen it I'm just saying that's what it seems to be to me
uh I don't know though it's not that I mean there I I thought that some of the the worlds they go
into in this thing were just absolutely beautiful I wanted to hang out there you know I'm not the
kind of freak that's like the regular world is too depressing because I'm not an avatar world like
these morons online but man I enjoyed the hell out of my my three hours watching this thing
but I also think it's a movie that was helped immeasurably by a very strong edible
b imax c3d I mean they go to they go to other worlds yeah there's underwater worlds and
I mean it really makes me want to see it more because I hate the fucking
the avatar world like yeah you're not you're not that far well this this person on on the
patreon had said they walked out after this bro thing or whatever they walked out of the two hour
mark the final hour 20 minutes of this movie is a giant classic James Cameron non -stop action battle
if you want to leave right before that starts and complain about it again yeah I'm not gonna
break my back trying to convince you to watch avatar 2 they made plenty of money off it
but I I sure had a blast on it I understand why you wouldn't see it I get it
all right folks we'll see you next time and we'll see you in hell