Huff, Puff, and spin the house down at Golden Nugget Online Casino!
Right now, new players can deposit just 5 bucks and get 500 total spins on Huff and
More Puff, the slot that's blowing players away.
Download the Golden Nugget Online Casino app and use promo code Nugget1.
That's code Nugget1 to enjoy 50 spins a day for your first 10 days.
All on our players' favorite game of the summer.
Now's the time to score daily bonuses and spin for all the bacon on the game everyone's
hoffat about!
At Golden Nugget Online Casino!
Gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamberler.
Please play responsibly.
21 and over, physically present in Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania, and West Virginia
only.
Void in Ontario.
New customers only.
Non -withdrawable casino spins issued as 50 spins per day for 10 days valid for featured
game only and expire each day after 24 hours.
See terms at GoldenNuggetCasino .com slash promos ends at 11 .59 p .m. Eastern on August 31st, 2025
Your burger is served and this is our finest Pepsi zero sugar. It's sweet profile. Perfectly balanced is the savory notes of your burger
That is one perfect combination
Burgers deserve Pepsi
Hey, everybody. Welcome to We'll see you and how the podcast brought to you by Fangoria,
podcast network for more information about the network, including other programs how to
follow the show and find past episodes of we'll see you and how please visit
Fangoria .com. Good to be here. My buddy Patty Walsh. Look, let's just address it
right off the bat. Pat say hi first of all. Hi, I feel like you're kind of
dominating this so far. I haven't really had a chance to make my voice heard.
There's Pat Walsh in one year. I'm in the other. We keep getting people
saying why are you split? Why is one guy in one year? Why is one guy in the
It's so if you want to watch the movie, you can have us balanced on either side of it with the movie audio up the middle. And I know for effect our dear friend Karen Toguerreff.
Very funny comedian and writer of Mr. Show fame, she listened to every one of our episodes on her drive home from I forget the state Sacramento, California.
Yeah, she texted me a great great compliment about it. Yeah, it's me too. There were no more me focused than the podcast
But there were no audio complaints. No, she had no audio complaints. So I think we're fine. Okay, this week
We're doing the shining so if you want to watch along with us now's the time to queue up your DVD or get ready on Netflix
I feel like everybody owns the shining in one way or another. Yeah, we should just get into it because two two hours and a half
Yeah, so this is a long one. We're just going to go if you need time pause if not we'll count it off and hit
We'll do a one two three play right patty. Sure
All right, one two three play
And we're in you got your Warner Brothers logo there the movies rolling
me. We have never gotten into a movie so quickly. No, it feels good. I also like seeing the Warner
Brothers logo because usually that means I'm getting paid. I usually associate it with them
about to watch a Batman movie. Yeah, sure. And usually that's not good. I disagree. I like a lot of
well, I'm talking about the old ones. Okay, I like the first one and the other three are
You know, Joe, it's good to see you.
This is a fitting movie to watch because a lot of people are snowed in on these coast.
Yeah, it's the big blizzard of O6 snow pockleps, they call it.
Yeah, O6 sounds better than 15, doesn't it?
It does.
I had one blizzard when I, oh boy.
One blizzard when I was in New York, and I loved it.
I wish there was more of it.
You might want to tighten your stand because you're getting a little slide down see that see that one in the middle there
Yeah, no, no, no down that one. That's the one you tighten
Pat Walsh just not a work of Mike stands guys have been working on television all right for
32 years
I've got my start on the jury Louis telephone
As a boom mic operator as a boom mic you should know how to work that stand boom man the movie here comes the boom is based on my
exploits. I said, look, I put on a few pounds. Kevin James was playing me, fellas. I was very
angry about that. I consider myself more of a Brad Pitt, John Ham type, but that's fine.
As far as sitcoms go, I always thought of you more of a sort of a Cynthia Nixon type.
Uh -huh. Okay. Then a Kevin James. I think out of the sex in the city
I look the most like sent the index and I'll take that. Yeah. Well, you're both tall red headed gals. Yeah, both love the ladies. Am I right?
This is just an endless opening to a movie. I love it. It's disturbing. It is a little loud. I think it's gonna be a little loud for us, Joe. I can turn it down a bit. Okay, because I mean, no one's even talking yet, and I'm having a little trouble. Well, it's music is playing. Yeah, you can't hear me and you though. I hear us fight. I can but I
I'm gonna have to struggle. I feel like this kid is just have you read the book the shining?
No, I was too busy adjusting the levels
Hold on talk while I do that all right. I will
Stanley Kubrick and Diane Johnson. I wonder if she ever wrote anything else. I'm gonna look that up
I love the movie of course. I feel like everyone loves the movie
the book
is
phenomenal as well and as I said I have not seen the remake we've talked about it
before with Stephen Weber who is acting out my words this week on the show I
write for I wrote him he's in prison on the show and he's doing a musical in
prison I wrote all these songs for him to sing and I want to ask him tomorrow
because I'm gonna spend the whole day with him about the remake of the shining now
what I like feels at once what I'd like to see now is somebody come do a remake of
that episode, but cast Jack Nicholson in the Steven Weber part. Sure. Sure. See, see
out Weber likes it. That really blow people's minds, I feel like. Well, yeah. Can you do
with Nicholson impressions? I feel like that would be the perfect time to do it like. Here's
my take on Jack Nicholson in two broke girls. I think everyone can do an okay. Wait, now we
actually have subtitles. Yeah, put them on Pat. Oh, okay. Do you think this, when
When you walk in and all this equipment setup, do you think it just pops up by
itself? Well, you at any time I said you should put on subtitles, you act like
I'm asking you to like because now we're going through the Apple or the Mac
mini, which is an actual computer, which means putting on the subtitles is as
easy as getting the progress bar to appear and clicking the subtitle button. On the
Apple TV, you got to fucking flip the thing up and then I found out a whole
Downpods are real pain in the ass. It's just told them that's the old Apple TV the new one is a whole another thing
I have the new one. I haven't hooked it up. I've heard don't hook it up. It's more difficult than the other one
It's true. It's a much better product
It just takes a little more there's a learning curve because it's
You've had that other one for four years and now this is a different device. Don't love learning
folks I do love the curves okay I still want to do Nicholson my impression of
Nicholson and two broke girls do it girls we got to make some fucking money
around here what do you think of that yeah this diner cash ain't cutting it man go
ask the gentleman that used to be on Saturday night live if he can give us a
a couple of bucks. I forget his name. I think I must have snorted it up. My god damn knows
circa 1978. There you go. That's fun. It's not a bad show. That's still fun to do. We've added
two impressions to the show. Yeah. We have Sam Elliott, which Sam Elliott ordering food. Karen said
to the Sam Elliott impressions were stellar. Okay, good. And now we have Jack Nicholson in two
brokerals. Yeah. I think of another one. Oh, and then I did that half ass Sam Rockwell
impression one time. Quarter ass, I would say at best. I put my all into it. So the
effort was full ass. The accuracy is not is not spot on there enough. Yeah. Now look
at these beautiful subtitles if I just may. Now is that a is that a product of
Kubrick's hand, more than just how all the subtitles I guess that's probably how the subtitles are if you're trying to get a compliment on your Mac many I'll be happy to give it to you
The subtitles look nice. They look beautiful. They do better than most watched a couple foreign films this weekend. The subtitles were shitty actually ruined the movie almost because they looked so like
that I was losing emotion for the movie.
Yeah, bad subtitle.
Bad subtitle, bad lighting is another thing
that will take me right out of the experience.
Watched a movie called Phoenix.
It's on Netflix Instant.
It's on a lot of top ten of the year list.
It was fantastic.
Who's in it?
Nobody.
I mean, German people.
So, as far as we're concerned, nothing.
It's about Phoenix Arizona.
Yeah, German people moved to Phoenix.
Thanks. No, of course, it's about the whole cause. Yeah. It is so hot. That's the whole
movie. Can we go to the breaking bad house after lunch? That's in New Mexico, I think.
God, damn it, Joe. Sorry, buddy. Sorry. Joe's big, a lot of people like, yes, and with
their improv, Joe's big on the no but. It's just tough when you're part, when you're an
official part of the big, of the better call, solve breaking bad universe, when you're an
Official part of the canon the soul of us. Yeah, it's hard to hear you know
It's kind of like you just said like remember in Star Wars when the Enterprise is a no -no -no pet
It's not that star Trek. Right, so I'm just saying I didn't criticize you and I'm a key key part of the two -bro girls universe
I didn't say anything wrong about it
Nicholson's referring to Earl the cashier as that guy from Saturday Night Live because he was on Saturday Night Live
It's Gary the cashier or maybe the actor who portrayed that's what I mean
I meant my the joke was that Nicholson was so coked up. He doesn't realize that he's got the character
I think I introduced coke to the improv, but that's fun
Anyway, Phoenix is it's right after World War two and there's this woman who's had pretty it was had a lot in common with good night mommy
she had pretty severe facial reconstruction surgery and
and she I guess that's that's where the similarities end but she bumps into her
husband and he doesn't recognize her because the reconstruction wasn't
perfect and it's a whole is he a monster is he a nice guy kind of thing was
really good and the final scene was off the charts folks I urge you to watch
it's on Netflix since it's a new film yeah about a year old I don't know why
I guess rising from the ashes now I it took me one second to think about it now I completely understand
Sorry, I said yeah, yeah, sometimes I don't spend that one second to think about that I don't either and it's and it's also
So it's not a movie about Phoenix there's an also not a movie about the Marvel comic book character the Phoenix
No, it's a movie about a German lady with a busted face. Yeah, really good. All right
Six degrees of separation here. There's also a movie called Phoenix from the 90s that started in jellic
Houston who Nicholson dated. Okay, what's that about? Uh, I think it's her and I believe
Ray Liotta. It's one of those like desert steamy crime thriller kind of things. She's banging
Liotta. I don't think so. I tell you she's a wild looking woman these days. I saw her and transparent
and I was like, Hachi Machi. Why? She's just, she's just a wild looking lady, man. What do you mean?
It's either a lot done, or maybe the sad state of affairs that just nothing done looks
like that now, but her face was crazy.
And in Joggy Houston has always been a very severe looking woman, kind of an intense
looking woman.
Yeah.
And I found her delightful on the show, but I was just like this lady.
I've never seen a face like this in all my life, and I'm not trying to be a dick, it's
just a wild face.
and you could sure she would understand if you said this after on the last
podcast I talked about how I hate people shooting on Kathleen Turner's face
yeah but you know that's what you call Hollywood folks yeah he only sticks up
for his ethics when it's in style I I kiss your lips while I'm stabbing in the
back this is a filthy town I hear you it's a terrible town I've been very
depressed for weeks me too I don't like almost everyone that I come in
contact. Exactly the same thing me too. Yeah, I look at I look at Facebook. Oh, I mean I'm sorry
I look at Instagram and Twitter in the morning and the entire time I curse out loud at my phone. I
know and I see people's pictures and I go I'm literally in that blue chair where they're going,
oh you fucking idiot. You fucking idiot. I have a bit about it in my act now. I do the same thing.
It's me in that chair on the toilet being like, why do I follow this person? Yeah, find more on. Here's
my impression of me scrolling through Facebook, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck
you, fuck you, that's all I'd done.
And I found myself some, because I do what you're definitely not supposed to do, which
is I look at Twitter like right before bed, because it whips me into a frenzy.
And I look down the other night reading these tweets and I'm digging my fingernails into
my palm on my hand making me so quietly angry. You know, I'm not happy. I'm not happy
that you're depressed. You know, I'm not happy. I'm not happy that you're sad. I am happy
though hearing that you're depressed only because it makes me realize I'm not crazy. No,
it's this city gets to you after a while. It does. And I'm glad we're watching something
cheerful like gallons of blood pouring off. And as we were saying that the shot of the blood
River came into the hallway, which is like what is in my mind right now.
Remember when we were at that heart convention and we were in a cab with those two twins?
Yeah, they were grown up now.
We, Joe and I were in a, like a escalade to the airport with the twins from the shiny,
and they could not have been sweeter.
And I so desperately wanted to take a picture of them, but I was like, I don't want to bug these ladies.
They're sweet old ladies.
They were, you know, they're probably 55. They looked pretty.
Yeah, they looked great.
I kept whispering in each other's ears like they shared that weird twin secret thing. Oh, that's
sexist by the way what I just did. Sorry. What? I've learned on Twitter that if you know because I
said yeah they looked great and it's a woman that's that's me being a misogynistic pig. What?
Because apparently I've never said that about a man before which I have all the time. Yeah, I do too.
I'm reading a lot of that stuff online about how like I totally agree like you shouldn't say it's
wrong to say to a woman like, hey, nice tits, you know, or be like harassing or whatever
like, but it's starting to bleed now into like this thing about all compliments where
it's like, you wouldn't tell a man he looks nice. And it's like, no, I constantly do.
I went to a barbecue yesterday. Three of my male friends told me I looked great. I told
three of my male friends how good I thought they looked. I complimented their bodies.
I wasn't trying to have sex with them. I was saying, you look really good.
You know, just you didn't tell me I look great when I came in pat
I'm always happy to see you and you're like the wife at this point. I get it
I don't got to do anything to bed you at this point
You know when I saw on Twitter the other day and almost sent it to you because it infuriated me so and I knew it would get your
Goat so I didn't send
was someone being like hey
Don't
If you if a woman tells you her age and you think that she looks younger than her age
Don't tell her she looks younger than her age because that's not appropriate
Maybe she doesn't want to hear that now folks. I don't know the this is what compliments are
This is what compliments are someone tells you I'm 50 years old new oh my god
I wouldn't have thought you were older than than 35 and also why would you make that into a bad thing and why are you also
We're saying that about women if it's bad then say it's bad for men and women yeah people often tell me
I look quite a bit older than I am, doesn't make me feel great, but I would never think
to take to the internet about this, I shouldn't go antics, people are going to figure out who
this person is, but why?
I want to know.
I'll tell you after.
I was kind of like, well, then what do you want to hear?
I guess you can't really say anything.
It's not going to happen, so I'm not going to be the guy that's like, we're barreling
towards a society where, but there are certain, it'll never happen, but there are certain people
out there that really truly wish we lived in an environment where there was no real interaction.
Yeah. Unless it was somehow 100 % gainful for them as individuals. Like it's insane. It's
insane. You can't, it's crazy. I don't even understand that age one is blowing my mind.
Like someone tells you you look great or are any compliment of that nature that doesn't bleed
into your ass is incredible whenever I get why that's weird. Of course, I guess of course
I've never said anything like that in my life. Hello, you look great. Like the guys in the
sopranos said that to each other every day. It's like, it's just a nice little thing. But yeah,
this was, unless you know that somebody wants to be complimented on their age, don't ever offer
that information. And I'm like, I'm not even going to take that and start using that in my life.
How would you know that? That's a terrible thing. How would you know that?
How would you know that? So we have to design a system where when I meet you, I go, hello, Pat,
I like to be complimented on the following my age, my looks, my rear end. Yeah. Like so then here's
I find offensive. My breasts, my career. What? I also, here's the alternative. You meet a woman,
she says, you know, look, I'm 45 years old and you nod your head. Isn't that like a little weird
I always look, yeah, that seems about right, you're 45, yeah, I've been saying for years
For years I've been having this debate with people
It's sexist
It's sexist towards women when people when women say you never ask a lady her age. That's sexist
That's the second that means I'm treating you different than I treat a man. That's true
But I do follow that rule. I never ask somebody hold that. Oh, I ask away. I don't care. Okay, because I'm a feminist
I'm going to I'm I'm I'm I'm for quality. Sure
That's a quality. I'm exhausted. Kat Steven said it best. It's a wild world. Yeah
Did Kat Steven sing cats in the cradle. That was Harry Chapin. Okay. Uh, he's saying it about his friend Kat Stevens who was in a cradle at the time
They had a weird sort of baby fetish role play thing going on between a lot of people don't know about that backstory
right right I have a good shining story from that convention yeah that we were
at you told it on the already told it on this you did told on the live one
because we were there that morning at eight o 'clock oh that's right but it was a
nice little areas by eight fifteen I think I had had three screwdrivers on that
podcast yeah we we kind of pounded that weekend into the ground we drank all day
that day yeah all day it was a strangely depressing festival you know we're
very alone in the world. Yeah, that day was fun though. It was fun. We went from literally
drinking from quarter to eight a .m. until one a .m. That's true. It was an amazing feat. That's true.
It was an amazing feat. It was very proud of us. Folks, I should also mention in case I die during
this podcast, which is a stronger and stronger possibility, that I... Last time we did this podcast,
which was Nurse 3D. I'm walking back to my car and I was like oh I'm feeling
extremely dizzy and light -headed. And the next morning I woke up 5am mid -passing
out which I've never I've never passed out in my life. I was like I'm gonna pass
out. I'm like oh no every time I would turn my head I would almost black out and
pass out. So finally I stand up to walk the bathroom splash water my face. I fall
over and wake my girlfriend up. I'm like, I need some help here. She sits with me. We're like,
I don't know what's going on. Every time I move my head, I would almost pass out. I let it go.
It kind of went away throughout the day and it came back real hardcore the other night at dinner. I'm
sitting at dinner, break out into a cold sweat. I'm like, oh, I'm gonna pass out again. This is not
good. I go running out of the restaurant. Where are you eating? It's called birch. It's a nice restaurant
here in Los Angeles. You made a big scene in the middle of it. Not a scene. Not a scene.
I kept it to myself.
It was concerning, I go to urgent care
and the doctor is like, ask a bunch of questions.
He's like, you seem really healthy.
I'm gonna do drunk history again.
I just had a physical while my blood work was perfect.
He's like, I don't know what it is.
I don't really have an idea,
but usually in this case, it's an inner ear thing.
You have an infection you're not aware of.
I just lost the whole story
because I'm furious that I've not been invited
to do drunk history again.
Well, I don't make the choices Joe
Could you just be happy for someone else I'm tired to be it happy for everybody else. What could you do it once I do it all the time
Why the hell is it cast already fully? I believe so
Do you tell your manager you're interested though they'll call and get you know
I'm getting irritated all right
So I'm going to do it. Joe's making this about him, but it's really about me folks.
And the doctor's like in her ear, he's like, I think it's just simple vertigo. I think you're
fine. I'm like, boy, that's a relief to hear, doc. This has been a really stressful week or two.
He goes, take this medicine, which is just drammamine, which makes me extremely drowsy, but it does
help the offness because I was feeling pretty dizzy. And then as I'm walking out the door, he goes,
Yeah, you know, if it's if it's not gone by Monday, you go get an MRI the only other thing I could think of is it could be like a
brain mass
As I'm walking out the door
Right, so of course that's kind of nagging at me
But taking the drama did make it go away. I'm not gonna get the MRI. I'm thinking. It's not a brain mass, but I
Could be dead at any point and then you guys will all treat this podcast like it's a legendary thing because I'll be dead
Well, I'm glad you're getting one more drunk history appearance in before you're demise
And it's nice to know you'll be sitting at home going son of a bitch that should have been me
I just I just want to be part of certain things
So you just you have representation you say you know what I'd like to do. I'd like to be on drunk history
You didn't have to do that
Did you no, I didn't did you I didn't don't you dare don't you dare I'm sorry. I'm kidding
well good luck with that and I really hope it doesn't cause a brain
hemorrhage oh it's it's definitely nothing alcohol related I am I do know
that much sounds like denial to me folks well no I sure it's not the booze no yeah
I'm kidding I'm joking why are you getting this I haven't seen you a little while
breaking your balls a little bit right where you get a fucking fresh. Oh boy. What movie?
It feels like a score says. Yeah. Good fellas. Come on. I haven't seen you in a while. I'm breaking
your balls. You're getting fresh. Yeah, it's from good fellows. I haven't seen you in a little while.
Billy Bats says it to Pesci before Pesci kills him. Pesci. Yeah, I remember.
Now, after we did Nurse 3D coincidentally, now I believe out of all the podcasts we've done,
Then we've had a handful where it's been movies that we didn't really respect or
sort of weren't that great or whatever.
Nurse 3D was one of those few and out of those few Nurse 3D was the worst, I would
say.
We were an agreement that it was a terrible, terrible movie.
The girl that started it, the two days after we did the podcast, the girl that there
I knew thing came out that the girl that started is trying to now so the makers of the film
That was an old that was an old news story, but yeah, that was fascinating blaming her for ruining her career
Yeah, she thought it ruined her career and they dubbed in like a bad expressionless voice
She's expressionless through the whole movie right exactly, but she was blaming all source
She's and she was blaming them for like she wanted $50 million or something for running her career. You should look it up
It's a fascinating story and just a classic case of somebody who's you know out of control
suing anyone who'll listen
It made me mad. It was one of those things that made me mad in the morning when I read it. Yeah, I got aggravated. Yeah
I get it. I got real aggravated. I get it. She didn't win. She's not going to this won't go out of trial. It's just the nerve
Yeah, the nerve
Yeah, this movie ruined my career. Well, then why did you do it? Hey? Hey, sister, you think maybe a light bulb would have went off when you were walking across a kitchen
Sans pants and your clam was swaying across the paprika shakers
You think maybe then it would have popped in your head that this wasn't a great idea. Yeah, well look
Oh, no, it's because they dubbed a voice in it ruined my performance her starring in anything
would not have been a smash hit she wasn't the kind of name that's gonna open a
movie she didn't realize that either it's just passing the buck point in the
finger she got a big opportunity didn't connect because I'll tell you she
wouldn't have been suing if the movie had made any money at all of course not of
course not have you have you been to the overlook hotel I know people who have I
haven't but look at that the gold room is the bar in my neighborhood the gold
named after the gold room in this movie. I think it's possible. And it's a gold room in the movie.
I've never been there. Where's it? Connecticut? I wanted to look up that. And also if this woman
has ever written anything else, I'm going to do both now. You're going to look up where it is. Yeah.
Yeah, I've never the hotel from the innkeepers is actually not far from where I grew up.
Okay, I like the idea. My buddy Pat Healy was on that acquaintance. I should say we're not close, but I like him and I see him sometimes. I'm a fan of Pat Healy. Yeah, I'm not a huge fan of that movie, but I like Pat Healy quite a bit. Yeah, and I like, who's the girl that's in it? I like her too. I forget her name. I forgot both their names until you said Pat Healy and then I remember. Oh, yeah, that's the guy from. What's that David Kekner movie called. Take the money for
of finger cut off your nose for money cheap thrills. Yeah yeah that's a good
movie. She was a novelist essayist satirist who was the Diane Johnson who
co -wrote this movie. I didn't even hear that you were looking that up. They were
looking up the overbroker overlook hotel. One thing led to another. It's in the
Colorado Rockies. Oh it's in Colorado? That's right. Really? That's right. Oh yeah
They're driving up those huge mountains. I'm an idiot. You know, I don't deserve to be on drunk history
But damn full. I can't even tell where the location of a fucking famous mountain range. Oh God
All right, that's all right. I'm sure the answer is somewhere in the bottom of this bottle of wine as I pour in
I was a brother. No, I've never seen you drink wine ever
What what caused us it feels less
It's alcoholicgy. That's why I think many, many parents enjoy several glasses of wine at night.
It's just the other night I drank a couple wines. I smoked some light reef.
A bottle of red.
Then I put on my headphones and listened to the new Megadeth album as I played a space video game and it was one of the greatest nights I've ever had in my life.
Honestly, that's all I ever want to do except not Megadeth and not video games.
Oh man, it was awesome. The mega -death, the like, anthemic metal went so well with like,
you know, fast, frantic space action. It was, it was a lot of fun man. It's strange
you should say that because I just watched the decline of Western civilization part two.
What am I featuring mega -death? What are my favorite movies ever? It's just the best. I bought
the box that the punk one should be more in my wheelhouse because I really love X, you know, and all
that. And I did love it. The second one is something real
special. Well, the first one is like more of I think a
celebration of punk music, whereas the second one is kind of
like, look at half of these bands. Yeah, because you got
good bands in there, like Iro Smith and Megan, and whatever.
And then you have those hair metal bands that one of the
saddest things ever is that guy that just is drunken as mom's
pool the whole time. I watched the full which they have on
on the, on the Blu -ray, they have the full interview with him. It's fantastic. He's drinking
like just pouring bottle after bottle of vodka into his throat with his mom looking on,
talking about how he's a piece of shit. It's incredibly depressing.
Brutal. And wonderful. Brutal. My favorite line in the movie, though, is when Steven Tyler goes,
you can really fuck to a good arousment song. There's a million great lines like that.
And Steven Tyler's hilarious in the movie. If you haven't seen it, you gotta check it out.
It was unavailable for decades now. It's out directed by Penelope Spheras, who directed Wayne's world and
Clueless, no, no, I know me heckling. That's related directed fast times. Yes. Okay. Speaking of Clueless, Stacey Dash all over Fox news. Oh, yeah,
saying outlandish things. I think that's kind of her bag now, which is crazy. That's everybody's bag when the acting gigs run out. What was she saying?
She was saying, well, she said, she said we shouldn't have a BET, we shouldn't have Black History Month, we should either integrate or not, and you know, you know, it's hilarious.
The probably read this weekend, BET showed like 40 music videos starring Stacy Dash.
She also started an TV show that was on BET.
Yeah, yeah.
And she's also been on the cover of like a zillion, like Black centric magazines, like Shabani and stuff like that.
They called her out on it on the view.
Pretty good.
It's one of the only times on the view I ever saw somebody get called out where I totally
agreed.
You're watching the view with your morning coffee here, I assume?
Look, man, I got, what do I got to do?
I don't need to prep it for anything, like drunk history.
You know what I mean?
You know what I'm saying?
I'm just sitting here.
I did a nice job on drunk history and they asked me back.
Can you just be supportive?
I can't.
And I won't.
I could, but I refuse.
our buddy Pete home just got an HBO show with Judd App, happy for him, congrats Pete.
That'll be interesting.
I remember when he told us the idea, yeah, and now it's being made, isn't it weird?
It is weird.
That's how it works in this business.
Go on.
Stacy Dash.
I got nothing else.
I don't remember why I watched the view clip, somehow I linked to it.
Now since we tend to get a little like oddly political on here lately, what do you think
about this whole boycott of the Oscars for they're not being African -American nominees.
I agree with it, but I agree with it 100%. The problem though is I do think that the people that
are boycotting should have been boycotting other things a lot longer ago. Sure, you know, I think
the Grammys deserved a lot more shit than they got for letting you know, Macklemore and Iggy Azalea
sweep the hip hop award. You know, so that's that's absurd. I'm a little disappointed that that
that some people that are boycotting didn't get involved until it seemingly directly affected them.
But I agree with you and Viv's response to Jay to Pinkett. No. Because Jay to Pinkett's like,
I'm gonna, I'm not going to. So and Viv wants this video. The first one she hates Will Smith.
She despises Will Smith. Yeah. But the video is off the charts funny. It's supposed to be fun.
But she makes some real great points and she's like, she's clearly just so angry with Will Smith, but she's like, you know, back in the day when I wanted to have the cast unite and get a little money for the rest of the black actors on staff.
You know what your husband told me Jayden. He said your deals your deal and my deals my deal so fuck off
Wow, so now maybe you could do a little work helping other people get jobs
Then your billionaire husband and your billionaire children. It's it's incredible. Wow all right
Take look that's that's those are fair points, man
Sure, and then she's like well Smith didn't deserve it. She's like that accent what what accent is he doing on that movie because it was different in every
So now I didn't see concussion.
I may have a concussion.
I may be dead by the end of this podcast.
So I will check it out if I live to see it.
But yeah, I don't know that Will Smith
has been nominated.
I don't think he, I'm not saying he just necessarily
deserve to be nominated.
I'm saying, this is what I was going to say
before you cut me off with your own agenda.
I love it by watching you.
What I was going to say was the problem doesn't lie with,
well, the problem does lie with the Oscar,
with the award shows or whatever.
However, the real problem needs to be fixed is projects, enough projects aren't being green
lit.
Yes.
That allow any diversity of actors to be acting.
True.
So, that's the real problem.
You know, there's this focus on like, well, what are we supposed, the people that are opposed
to the boycott, there's a focus on like, well, what are you supposed to do, just nominate
people just because?
And it's like, no, that's not the solution either.
The solution is Hollywood should be making more diverse programs and I'm getting really really tired of people saying like
The diversity issue isn't an issue. It is a fucking issue flip through your TV shows and your stations and everything. It is
uncanny
The amount of white faces sure and you can make the majority argument all you want
But in real life, we are all far more integrated with people of different nationalities than we ever see on these TV shows and quite frankly, I'm kind of getting tired of like the fucking Steven Avery Clans of the world determining what I get to watch on my TV.
Well, it's middle America. So is the Avery family.
This is true. Okay. So we're the ball. Have you watched all that?
It annoys me. Here's what people are getting behind. That's what people are getting behind. Yes.
And when the fact is, no one has any idea if he did it or not because it's the most biased document.
And let me say this. Let me say this. I loved it. It's insanely biased.
Let me say this publicly. Please. Please. Let me say this publicly.
He was sent to jail wrongfully in that first 14 year term, whatever it was, that seemed
to be the truth.
It seemed to me that he was sent to jail incorrectly, absolutely.
It does seem that things were conducted during the trial and the second trial that were
possibly designated that it was a mistrial, possibly he was framed.
I'm not disagreeing with any of that.
My only problem with the whole thing is every single person that is the loudest mouthpiece
for this guy to be freed, is the exact same person who had they known Stephen Avery before
this big mishap happened, they would have tried to run him out of town with fucking torches.
Yeah.
Like the guy did so much creepy shit before any of this.
And for some reason, that's just, that's just like ignored now.
It's like, it's like all the sexual assault behaviors and everything.
It's just ignored.
I'm not saying, so he should be in prison for life because of that, or he deserves a
Because of that I'm just saying everybody I know that supports this guy is like you're the exact person that would like be tweeting against this person
Yeah, like it's I mean people take to Facebook about this shit, and it has like overtaken their life, and it's just like
You know how many millions of times this has happened and the fact that he is wide is sort of more irksome because this happens to black people
I think infinitely more than it happens to white people
I love the it's one of my favorite Eminemil Erics when he talks about Columbine and he goes well now
it's a tragedy. Yeah, that's the only part I remember. Yeah, it's like that kind of shit has
been happening in other communities for so long and they just don't demon as a mass killing.
They demon as like an unfortunate economic problem in this in that neighborhood or whatever. Yeah,
it's like it's it's so fucking ridiculous man. I'm really really really getting tired of one of
the greatest things I ever heard somebody say in regards to this sort of thing. I saw Mark Marin
at comics once in New York and some like sort of right wing guy said something like
criticism, heckled him or criticized him about something he was saying and like the heckle was
something along the lines of like, well, I don't hear those people complaining, you know, speaking
about like, yeah, people in economic straights and stuff. And Mark Marin goes, you know why? Because
anybody that really should be complaining is too busy working three jobs to feed themselves. That's
It's like I'm really kind of getting tired.
Nor do they have a mouthpiece to go complain about it on the.
Right.
Every person I hear, tree stumping about it, about any sort of real issue, it always seems
to be a very privileged white person.
Yeah.
That's always who gives the most of the stuff.
And they just get tired of it, man.
And they also do nothing about it.
So like, hey, I posted 800 Facebook things about it.
Have you done anything?
This is doing anything.
Yeah.
Have you talked to any of your city councilmen?
Right.
Have you gone to any town hall meetings, right? Have you tried didn't you get behind certain legislation?
Of course not and that probably wouldn't do shit either, but like it certainly does nothing you posting on Facebook about
It's just the whole thing makes me sick. I hate everybody on the right and the left. Yeah. You all make me sick
Yeah, you're pieces of shit
Well, I'm watching the thing to talk about you know, because this is a movie podcast
the staircase is like an eight -part
genius documentary about did this guy or did he not kill his wife one of my
favorite things I've ever seen you can rent it you should look for it it's on
Sundance originally but at the end of every episode you're a hundred percent
convinced like the end of episode one you're like oh fuck this guy definitely killed
his wife the end of episode two you're like the system is fucked clearly this
man didn't kill his wife and because they're just they're toying with you that's
all these, that's what a documentary does. Right. So for making a murder for 10 parts to
never give you a single bit of conflicting information when there is ample shady conflicting
information is really very fucked up. And if I watch the thing too, I mean my girlfriend
were pacing around the house like this, the system is fucking, we got into it too. But
then at the end of the day, you're like, wait a minute, and then you start reading all
the shit. So he answered the door when this girl came in a towel. So he had called her
several times from a block's number. You know, like there's a lot of weird shit that
goes on. I'm not going down this rabbit hole. But there's tons of stuff that is very
important to this story that is not in the documentary. And then the people keep posting
about it are ignoring that stuff still because they're choosing to believe what they want
and not believe what they don't want.
It's a classic argument that is always posed and put forward
when you're dealing with people of faith.
Whether the faith is God or Stephen Avery's innocence
or Woody Allen's guilt or whatever it is,
people draw their own conclusion.
They have faith in what they believe to be true
without any real hardcore proof to support it either way either way and then you and then you
argue them and say but what about this and this and this and it's like arguing with a Jesus
freak yeah they can't answer your questions right well that's just because you know that's a it's not
just beat no I just presented you with a fact yeah so now what what's the counterpoint to the fact
What's the argument? So then the girlfriend goes on Nancy Grace. Yeah, she's like
Which I also that's the old con dog bark like he used to beat the shit out of me all the time
And he was insanely violent and he's very fucked up and he told me don't ever say anything about it
Or it'll ruin my case and on and on and then you tell this to people and they're like, yeah, but it's Nancy Grace
Well, okay, you hear and maybe they did pay her off her story
but you hear it's Nancy Gray she hear well that girlfriend's clearly not you
know a reliable source I've heard that from a different couple of people. Oh she
was she had a DUI so she's an unreliable source of whether or not she was
abused. Now here's the thing here's the thing if that girl now when that girl was
telling that story I was I wasn't sure if I believed or not I was like well this
could just be a convenient thing to be saying right now I don't know but it
doesn't mean that I'm just gonna completely discount it it means to me that the
jury is still out on that. Sure. And again, once again, had this been a situation
where Steven Avery was not wrongfully imprisoned and a woman had come out against him with
the record that he has already and said this guy beats me. She would be given a hell of
a lot more credibility. And if anyone, any one of these people, many of whom are like are
my friends would hear this from her. And she said, well, you know, he used to be the
shit I'm in, they're like, yeah, I don't know if I believe her because she was an alcoholic.
Folks, that's insane and that's what you would scream in somebody's face about doing
in a bar if it wasn't tied to this documentary that manipulated your emotion, right?
You know, this stuff's going on all the time now, don't doubt the victim.
You have to believe the victim and I completely agree with that, but they're choosing to not
believe this victim and I realize that beating a woman doesn't make him a murderer, but
but it does certainly factor into a trial
for a man accused of murdering a woman.
I don't necessarily think he did it.
I don't necessarily think he didn't do it.
I don't know, I love talking about it.
But it's the people who are 1 ,000 % sure
you just want to shake and be like,
what the fuck's the matter with you?
The jury's out, that's my point.
Yeah, that's my point.
Of course.
And people are latching on to anything.
The new thing now, which I've seen 800 people posed,
is that there's a really obese serial killer
uh who was in the area around this time and there's a picture of a guy who looks very vaguely
like this obi serial killer in the background of one of the trials. Now I don't think it looks
anywhere near enough like him to make this case but everybody's like, well that proves
it. It was a serial killer. You're lashing onto things that prove the point you've already
decided in your mind are true. Uh it's again it's it's faith arguments. Well then why is it in the
Bible. Right. Exactly. Well, okay, that was written a hundred years or 60 years or whatever after it was passed on word about. Yeah, but it but then but that's similar stories after a hundred years like for Christ. Yeah, you know, it does honestly does a better job week in a week out of presenting this stuff is date line.
date line every every commercial break, you know, you're like, okay, but I didn't expect
to hear about that.
They're not bias in any way, reporting this shit.
And I don't know how a documentary that is a billion percent biased is being hailed
by everyone at this mass as this masterpiece as much as I enjoyed it.
It's obviously extremely entertaining.
Well, here's the other here's the other point I would like to make about this documentary.
Obviously the go -to defense for Avery's innocence is always is always he was
going to sue them for a money they didn't have right money they didn't want
to pay this was clearly a set up you never hear the flip side of that
argument you never hear the flip side of that argument which is okay so if we're
just going to believe that he was framed because of this coincidental instance of
him theoretically getting them into a position
where they owed him this money.
Yeah. Okay.
Why don't you flip that around and go,
well, couldn't you just say it the other way?
Couldn't you say, you're just saying he's innocent
because they were gonna have to pay him this money?
Do you see what I'm saying?
Of course.
You could just flip it the other way
and it never gets flipped the other way.
Yeah.
I completely agree.
The reason I saw it.
By the way, I almost lost that completely.
No, I found it.
Halfway through it, I kind of forgot what I was trying
and to say, I found out that the terror that came into me, when I finished episode 10 of
Mega Murder, my whole reason, which I have not heard anybody really discuss, we talked
about it a lot at work, is my whole reason for thinking he couldn't have done this is because
I'm like, it takes a sociopath to be this convincing, and this man is very close to mentally
handicapped, you know, so when he's like presenting his case, you believe that he didn't do it
just from watching him talk. I agree. And an idiot, which no offense is what Stephen Avery
legally is technically classified as, uh, or a moron or so. There's actually IQ determinations
and he is like a moron or a mental measure. There's all these different terms. Right. Uh,
and he's like 10 points above Brandon, the brother who everybody's like, you know, this, this, this,
that kid was obviously taken advantage of. I don't necessarily think he had anything to do with him.
But this guy to put a pro in his column I don't think he's smart or savvy enough to be sticking to the story for this long and not have some I think the most fallout if he's not guilty I think the most likely in my opinion the most likely explanation of or the most likely of turn of events was probably the nephew all the stuff the nephew said was true but it was at the hands of the neighbor.
yeah and the neighbor said we're putting this on your uncle and if you say any
different we'll fucking kill you sure that's you know and I know that I'm not
the first person to say that but that to me alright I could buy that but I've
heard a bunch of theories I think they're all pretty plausible it's very fun to
talk about I just people really scare me people don't realize that they are
exactly the same as Fox news but for the other side that's what bothers me Bill
Mar is Bill O 'Reilly, but for the other side.
Yeah, it's of course, but nobody on the other side of anything,
and neither are right. Anybody on team Bill Mar,
anybody on team Bill O 'Reilly will never understand they're just as bad as the
other person. No, they won't ever see them. I tweeted, as we talk about this,
it's funny, before we did the Parkinson's, I tweeted my favorite thing that I've
ever tweeted. Okay, it has to do with this. All right. I try to live my life somewhere
and we're between Sid and Nancy and Ron and Nancy.
That's my favorite thing I've ever tweeted.
That's where you wanna be.
Somewhere between crazy anarchist and ultra conservative.
I thought you were at first saying
between Sid and Nancy, which is a very small.
No, I try to live somewhere between Sid and Nancy
and Ron and Nancy.
Okay, all right.
I think that's a good philosophy.
Yeah, I agree, John.
you know potentially murderous heroin addicted couple yeah and two of the most
elitist pricks that ever lived yeah somewhere in between there right yeah I
would agree all right I wanted a little more this is my favorite shot of the
shining and I I believe completely ripped off by my favorite shot of boogie nights
when marquee market sitting on the couch yes staring vacantly into space
because he's like, that's enough of this for me.
They're both thinking different things in these moments,
but two of my favorite shots.
I don't think it's all coincidental, either,
that as we talked about Steven Avery and we spiraled down
into that whole thing, it was parallel
to Jack Nicholson losing his mind in this movie.
Yeah.
I love that Stephen King wrote this as he was
like a coaxed up alcoholic who like presumably was kind of hating his family for keeping
him from getting work done. Like there's a lot of layers of this movie. Have you seen
room 237? Yeah, I can't stand it. I hated it. Just a bunch of fucking idiots. Yeah. I
hated it. So they can't have tomatoes represented the American Indian. And then I loved when the
people that worked on the shiny came out and they were like, no. Yeah. It was just what we
had to put there. Yeah, because we worked in a kitchen. Well, they're like, but Kubrick was
such a perfectionist that he obviously chose each thing to represent something. Or he chose it
because visually he liked it. You idiot. I liked it as a everyone can take different things from a
movie exercise. Yes. But I found it boring and I found everyone in it to be criminally insane.
This movie I will say is the most perfectly framed film, unbelievably shot movie for sure. I've ever
seen every shot is perfectly framed yeah it's like it's like a comic book panel yeah it's really
really beautifully shot you could I think you could watch this sound less for sure oh yeah this
is a good background at the party movie I know true Kubrick heads find this to be lesser Kubrick it's
far in a way my favorite of Kubrick's movie who finds it to be lesser Kubrick I think you're real
coober heads your real film heads do for sure because it's you know it's a horror
movie and it's not trying to say something but it is actually saying a lot of
things i mean to me it's just as valid as clockwork orange and i i would almost
consider clockwork orange or her movie yeah i agree almost the first half full
metal jacket is a horror movie the second half is not great in my opinion i hate
the second half yeah but that first half is i mean every every second up
until Vincent Napier blows his brains out on that toilet is,
I mean, it's masterful.
Yeah.
I think I was 10 years old
when I saw Full Metal Jacket.
My dad rented it with me.
Mm -hmm.
And that's that opening scene
with Arley, Irmery, whatever his name is.
Yeah.
Like, you know, you're 11, 10 or 11 years old.
It blew me.
Oh, it was like when I saw Dice Clay for the first time.
Right.
I just was like, this is the greatest thing I've ever seen.
Or like when I saw Alph for the first time well not really, but when I saw my first episode of Alph
Which kind of changed my life
Did you think Arlee army was more effective in full metal jacket or saving Silverman?
I gotta tell you I love him in saving Silverman and I love that he makes out with the guy at the end of it saving Silverman folks
No one would call it a good movie, but laugh for laugh
It is fucking hilarious
Who's in that against Steve's on Steve's on and Jack back like at their funniest before they cared about anything
They both seem like they're high in every scene and silverman and no not silverman
Jason Biggs who is adequate Jason. That's why I met Jason Biggs
And Amanda Pete who played the girlfriend and every one of those movies back in that there was nobody better to me than Amanda Pete
It is such a funny movie and I watched it very recently and was howling
laughing. There's so much funny shit in it. A lot of it seems improvised by Steve Zonajek Black,
who are gods at that time for me. I just watched that guy Dick Miller documentary about the
Dick Miller, about Dick Miller, the character actor. And when they got to the Burbs, which is one of
my favorite films of all time, they interviewed Corey Feldman and Corey Feldman goes, I was pretty
wild back then. I remember I was smoking weed on the set a lot in my trailer with Sam
Kinnison. Sam Kinnison's on the set of the burbs. Yeah, smoking weed with a 17 -year -old kid
or whatever. That's really bizarre. And then it cuts to Dick Miller now and he goes, he
was a quarry. It was a bit of a smart ass. And he starts laughing. And then it cuts to pre -seen
footage before the director yells action and Corey Feldman is dancing around in
the scene uh -huh and Dick Miller goes shut the fuck up kid we're trying to get
some acting done that you're action is I'm Dick Miller on Netflix or where to
say it I want to watch that I watched it on Hulu okay I don't get Hulu it was
great he was in Gremlins which reviewed on the show he's in Gremlins he's in
Roger Korman movies. He's in every Joe Dante movie. Now I worked with a comedy writer whose name is Mark Torgrove
He's half of the writing partnership and
Me and Pete work with them on outsourced
He tremendous show
Better than the rapid guy
Honestly, you ever say it? No, I never thought it was better than the rapid guy
Put the mic in front of your face. Maybe this is why nobody can hear you in the park.
I am tasting it. It's not directly in front of your face. I can tell from here,
but I feel it on my mouth. What do you say after that we do the podcast tonight? We go up to a bar
and have a few. We talk about this every time. I'm fine to do that. You'll do that definitely tonight.
Yeah, I think that's a good idea since I'm on drama main and it might be dying, but yeah, I'll do it
for sure. All right, because Pat, I got to tell you, there's a void here that can't be filled.
Surely alcohol will feel and you'll wake up feeling even better tomorrow. I keep thinking tomorrow
Be the day I wake up and I go now's the day. It does it. It's not coming
You got to have a kid. I think that's what I'm realizing more and more. I think I got to have a kid. No, no
That would be the most depressing thing. So look at I think a way to illustrate this dog out of my life. I'm kidding
I love you, Con. I'm joking. So if the dog dies within a year, this will be used in the dog trial in the truck
Yeah, in the in the frame Joderosa was framed 10 part net series about that'll be called the death of calm. Yeah, by the way, by the way
If I was the center of a documentary docu -series see that wasn't
impeccably shot. Yeah, let's see how many people
Routley behind it. I can tell you right now people are gonna come out of the woodwork against Joderosa, and I'm leading the pack folks
Mark Dorgrow was auditioned and was cast, I believe, he'd have to clarify, but I think
he was cast as Danny, the kid in the shining.
And Kubrick saw this other kid like to more game the part, but he basically had the part.
And to tell you how much Kubrick must have a vision in his mind is that this guy I worked
with looks identical to this kid.
Really?
and Kubrick must have just like envisioned a kid like forget talent not
that this either of them are talented that they're fine but like he wanted a
kid who looked exactly like this apparently because they're old are
identical how old are who they are talented you mean you said that wrong I'm
sure that I'm sure this guy was a talented child actor I don't know I worked
with him as a 50 -year -old comedy writer 40 -year -old
okay whatever but a Danny I think he's fine I think he didn't like you know
to come to drugs or anything but you know what I love about this always odd to
me in a movie by the way if I may don't they're doing this father -son scene
Jack Nicholson is is in his like underwear in a bathrobe and he's holding his
son on his lap yeah now in a true father -son relationship this is fine but this
isn't this is a set where an actor sure has to take this child on to his
a little awkward. It's kind of a little awkward. Yeah, I would think. Yeah, I was
sure you know who you're dealing with. If when you do a sex scene in a movie, do you
get a boner? I did do a sex scene once in a movie. I, everyone, everything I've heard is that
you do not because there's so much. I did not. It was the most, it was the most awkward
thing I've ever had to do in my life. Right. What movie was this? So I cannot watch it.
It was a comedy that I
Directed and wrote with Bill Burr and Robert Kelly called cheat. Oh, you wrote yourself a little sexy, and did you?
Well, my character had a sex scene and I played my character so I had to do the sexy, but
It was a it was a almost fully nude sexy. Yeah, it was comedic, but it was awkward
And I took my the film went to the Tribeca Film Festival pet. Oh, I don't want to brag
but first ever directorial effort goes to try back a film festival.
The Traback of Film Festival, which is spearheaded, I believe, by Dirty Grandpa.
Bobby De Niro.
Oh, I only know him as Dirty Grandpa.
Okay.
Okay, fair enough. I only call him Ronin.
Anyway, but you know, I took my parents to see it.
Right.
And it was kind of weird watching the sex scene with my mom next to me.
What I want to say here is look at Nicholson's head, folks.
there is not one, not one star above like fifth down on the call sheet working
today, who's rocking that level of balding.
They don't allow it unless you go bald like Bruce Willis or whatever else.
And I respect it so much that he was headlining his movies back in the day.
And we just he also is not a he's also not an impeccably good looking man.
No, he looks like he looks like every one of your buddies dads from the suburbs.
and that is what plan and simple makes people like when people talk about this
heyday of 70s movies that it was a better time of movies there's no other way
to look at it your actors your biggest actors at that time were Dustin
Hoffman Al Pacino Robert De Niro Jack Nicholson Jean Hackman these aren't good
looking men they're five feet tall and most of them and the women of that
period too, we're not to me like these like these like bony -assed fake -titted, you know, Angelica
Houston was uniquely beautiful. Sure. Meryl Streep was uniquely beautiful. Sure. Glenn Close was
uniquely beautiful. Sure. You know, it wasn't this like... And you bought them. Like there really aren't
any of those people working today who don't fit into that exact mold. And those people are never
great actors really they might have presence but they're never great actors and
that's why less and less I'm excited to go to a movie because I'm always like
oh what are we doing here who's in this they're all kind of the same yeah it's
a bummer it's a shame this kid's got great sweaters through the whole movie by
the way well this was one of the theories because he had an Apollo sweatshirt that
they thought it was some sort of thing about the faking of the moon launch
for Chris. What was the theory about his Mickey Mouse sweatshirt earlier? There was one
I think it was about the disney vacation of America or stupid garbage. John I'm going
to step up for one second cover for two minutes. Alright, that's about to spill beer on
himself. Empty and I am not. It's a first beer, but we're watching a movie. When you say
somebody that paints a picture of me, pantsless. You're not talking into the money. Jumping
which doesn't help the picture get up to get your beer you're gonna miss the
best part of the movie which is now the witch scene I believe oh no it's not
because he doesn't see the witch Nicholson sees the witch as Pat proclaims his
sobriety he just walked across the room you're not on the mic pat they can't hear
you and you're still talking it's it's it was yeah he almost did it my big fat
Greek wedding. He got up and walked out with the headphones still on and almost did that jerk back fall down thing, that
Nea, Nea Varvat, what's her name? Nea Varvat, John Varvatos, I believe, was the star of my big -fack Greek wedding.
And my big -fack Greek wedding part two is coming out where somebody else gets married or they're renewing their
Val's or something. I don't know. Here's my review of my big fat Greek wedding part two. Seems
like somebody renewed their bowels. That's gonna be my review of that movie when it comes out.
Seems like somebody renewed their bowels because it's a piece of shit. Get it. But I am a John
Corbett fan from back in the section of the city day. So I support anything that guy does. And Nia
She does a good job. I like her. She seems like a sweet lady.
Neavard Dallos, something like that.
Anyway, Shelley DuVall is just running on Jack Nicholson.
And I believe this is the scene where she's going to tell him that Danny Solo
witch up in the room. And this is, this is to me one of the scariest things
that's ever been committed to film.
Once he gets into the room with the witch, Nicholson, I mean, if you ever read Dr. Sleep,
the opening chapter is about Danny as a child still after the events of the shining,
being revisited by the witch in his apartment with his mom, and the witch smearing her shit
on the wall in the bathroom, and it's one of the scariest fucking things I've ever read
my life.
Is Dr. Sleep the shining sequel written by Stephen King?
Yeah, I didn't read it. That's crazy. I own all his books and it's mostly about a grown -up, Danny
dealing with this like sleep cold or something, but the opening takes place right after the events of the
Shining. Oh, okay. I didn't hear anything about it being good. I never looked at it. It got very good reviews. Okay, this
witch lady comes back at the beginning, though, and it's scary as fuck. I watched this weekend,
because I had my own little blizzard at the doctor told me to not leave the house, which was great. I watched so many movies
Watch this documentary that's on Netflix called The Nightmare
Yeah, it's about sleep paralysis. It was scary. I think I should make a horror movie, but
That's the kind of thing that like once I hear about it
I will find a way to work that into my life having sleep paralysis. There's another documentary called The Nightmare
That is also about sleep paralysis, which I don't understand how two movies about the same topic with the same title were made
No, and you can't find anything about the other one online, but it's on Amazon. I've watched it. Okay
And anyway, when I saw that, they say in that documentary,
it happens to people that tend to open themselves up
to a pipe worrying about it and be concerned.
And I had a bit on stage where I said,
I will get this sleep paralysis
because they say it'll worry about it.
Yeah, if you worry about it, you'll get it.
And I'm like, oh, so it's definitely gonna happen
to me then, okay, great.
It's pretty scary shit.
When I was Googling this constant dizziness or whatever,
they were all saying like as soon as you find a way to stop thinking about it you
won't be dizzy and it's very very true like I haven't really engaged with
anyone coming over here and like talking and stuff I I'm not feeling dizzy at
all but when I'm sitting in bed like I wonder if I have a brain mass I get real
dizzy real fast I mean it just sounds to me like you're being a little pussy well
I've really never had any illnesses of any kind of my entire life
So I don't think I am being a pussy was very serious. I can't speak to that because I haven't been with you your whole life
But the time that I have I've found you to be
Nicholson is hilarious in this movie these faces are faces I make when and ever anyone speaks to me
Which I'm sure they don't appreciate they are I would imagine like I would bet
And that buggy night scene, and I'm imagining Mark Walberg is a pretty dumb man.
I bet Paul Thomas Anderson showed him a still of Nicholson making that face in the shining.
Cause you know, oh, Paul Thomas Anderson is obsessed with the show.
I should just make this just do a check.
Nicholson does.
Okay, boss.
You want me to make this face?
I can make this face.
That movie, uh, I, it's one of my favorites, but originally de caprio was cast and dropped
out of the last second.
to do Titanic. And as much as I enjoyed a capriot, I think he would have been too good
for the role. And Walberg being dumb helps that movie immeasurably in my opinion.
The fantasies I'm having right now that Walberg hears you saying this somehow and beat you
up in public are so vivid in my mind. I pray that Walberg beats me up in public so that
I can get five million dollars from it. That was a tweet. That was another tweet. You
Jesus Christ, John. Yes. When will the whole be filled for you, John? Never. Just don't
on me. All of the Wahlberg brothers have to pretend the other ones are cool.
I don't follow that one. How do you not follow that? I will. Oh, like Mark has to pretend
that Donnie is cool. And Donnie has to pretend that Mark is cool. They all have tool bag brothers.
You don't get it. But they're all actors. Oh, for God's sakes. And they are kind of cool, aren't
forget it man. Why does your Mac many keep going in and out of focus because it's
underneath that because there's a there's a there's a piece of a single piece of
plywood between this and the fucking shit time Warner Router. Oh okay. So this is
the guy that you met him the elevator. By the way folks I kept saying earlier the
witch scene we were nowhere near it apparently. I thought that was happening but we
are in the bar scene now with the bartender. And in this scene, he does talk glad you asked me that
boy. Yeah, he talks in a very proper accent in the scene with an expectation almost English sounding
and then in real life, he's like, there were no cups in my room. He said, literally,
something like a jerky boy's character in real life. And I'm like, this guy's the greatest actor
of all time that he can switch from this voice to what he did in the shining.
Well, you can tell them briefly again about meeting the man in the elevator, maybe they didn't hear it.
I was in it, if you didn't hear the episode, I was in an elevator.
Pat and I went to a horror con in Denver called Mile High Horror to do a live broadcast of,
we'll see you in hell where we did maniac cop two in a theater with some very lovely loyal people that came out.
fans of that show of that movie and some of them fans of this podcast.
Anyway, if they weren't when they came in, they sure were when they left, you know?
I always say, if we can reach one person pet, we did our job.
And I think that's roughly what we do.
Anyway, the first night we were there, we arrived at like 10 o 'clock, it was kind of late.
and we were going up to our rooms to drop our bags off before we went to go
drink because even though we had to wake up at 7 a .m. we still felt the need
to go drink because there's missing pieces inside of us emotionally.
Anyway, I'm at the front desk and they're giving us all of our things to check in
and whatever and this 80 -year -old man walks up and they say, Mr. So -and -So, this
was given this was left for you from the festival people and they hand him a
minimal of all but he goes well what's in it and the guy at the desk who was
clearly high real high that kid was who was so high folks and although you're
working the front desk at a hotel you better be a little hot in Denver and high
baby yeah so he goes well what's in it he goes I don't I don't know man and he goes
he goes well what what what was it given to me for and the guy goes I don't know
And I'm thinking, who is this crazy old man?
And then he goes, there are no cups in my room, by the way.
Zero cups.
There was not one cup.
And the kid goes, we will send some up immediately.
And then I got on the elevator with this old man
and this other guy.
And the whole ride up, he just kept telling me,
there are no cups in my room.
Can you believe it?
Wall to wall, not one cup.
How do you have a glass of water?
There's not one cup that he gets off the elevator
and the other kid goes, that's the bar
tender for the shine yeah I was like I don't understand that how does a guy like
that never win an award he is clearly so far out of his own personality in this
film sure but like is that a guy who ever acted again you know it doesn't
matter look at him in this movie he's great but you're not gonna nominate this man
for an academy he was in real life he's time daily and in this movie he's like
time daily star of cagnon listen yeah who was the star of Kate Nallie remember
Kate Nallie well it was it was you know it was Jane curtain Jane Curtain from
from SNL and the other end of mine made love to her daughter once I bet she's
beautiful I found Jane current to be striking I agree completely she reminded me of
my aunt Sammy who has passed. Not that I had the crush on my aunt, but they were pretty
women.
Aunt Sammy.
Yeah.
That sounds like a Christian wig character. She was a lot of fun. She was a lot of fun.
All right.
You drink Amaretto straight up. Never saw anything like it in my life.
What is Amaretto?
Well, the cure. It's an almond liqueur that most people mix with milk or coke or something.
right. She would just take it straight. Love to Amoretto. Alright, downed by the bottle.
I admired that about her. Um, it does sound more and more like a Christian wig character
as I continued to describe her. Yeah. Oh, Sammy loves her Amoretto. Yeah. Anyway, um, Jane
Curtain. Who was the other lady in K now? Crystal Mike lives in my neighborhood. I just saw
her the other time. Oh, I also look who lives in the rich neighborhood everybody. Can you have
a little tacked. I also have now seen and my girlfriends these are all the time. Andy
McDowell who walks like apparently 20 hours a day around my neighborhood. I love Andy
McDowell. She's great. My father once told my mother he would leave her if Andy McDowell
expressed the slightest interest in which might have contributed to their divorce. I don't
that I would pay lots of money to sleep with are Andy McDowell and Mary
Steenberg is my number one. Steenberg is the best. I never did much for me. I
find Steenberg and to be with every passing year just hotter. Yeah.
Steenberg I'm for sure. Oh my lord. She deserves dancing. Now let me share my
He deserves her that's a great that is a power looks I love I love them together
Let me share my tweet with you about Andy McDowell. I think I tweeted this once to the lovely Karen
I'll try to give it more support that you gave my two tweets anytime
I've ever mentioned a tweet in the show you've spread your cheeks and shout on it, but here we go
What do Andy McDowell and my uncle Gary have in common what they both ruined four weddings in a funeral?
Yeah, so you've said that tweet on this show. I think I have this is one on other of my favorite shots is
This guy with a portrait of a naked woman with an apple. Yeah, it's scabbing cruders
Just like sort of the angelic character in the film. Yeah, and then they finally show you him in his home quarters
And he's got tits all over his room. I love it. Which is great. I love it
Which is great and it's I feel that it's a statement to say sex is not evil sex is beautiful
Oh, violence is evil, which is how this man will meet his end unfortunately, you know, do you love the Simpsons parody of the Shining the Shining never saw it. Oh, you don't watch the Simpsons. Not really.
I bet you'd love it. I've seen many episodes. I like it.
I just want it's parody of the shining is is perfect really to the point where you almost mix up the two play scamming brothers.
Well, it's actually the Scottish janitor is him.
Is this character filling that role and who's Danny Bart.
Yeah, but you know, Homer's, you know, it'll send.
Yeah, you should just watch it's 10 minutes.
It's it's going to be in Marge's Shelley Duval.
Right.
Do you find Shelley Duval attractive? There's somebody who also could not exist in today's climate.
Um, I sometimes, sometimes, you know who I found quite attractive in her, in her formative years was Lily Tomlin.
Never in my thing.
Have you ever, a young Lily Tomlin has got, has got Williamsburg Brooklyn written all over.
She was a doll. That's not my thing either. She was never my cup of mustard nor was Shelley
DeVell. I like a young lily tongue. Shelley long. Shelley long is kind of boringly hot, though.
There's, I like Shelley long. I mean, I always was, I was a cursedy alley guy over Shelley long.
Yeah, yeah. I always liked Rebecca. Look at this. Is this the witch you're referring to?
Yeah, this is the which okay now we're in the scene that bathroom is amazing
Could you imagine having that bathroom in your house? Just all green?
Lennonium and ceramic now they made that for the movie right
Yeah, of course that that's just not the way that this bathroom looks right now
This is kind of the way that the the in an upstate, California looks which
Is where a couple of friends of ours are having their wedding don't mention the names
But Madonna in is I got a room there for the wedding I did too and they all have like really creative cool looking rooms like this
I got a weird discount on my room where I got like that it was called like the like trail hike package
Oh gosh, it's something about two can teens or something. Okay, but it was cheaper for some reason. I don't know why
Can I tell you and I'm not proud of this?
This is one of those scenes, like Beverly D 'Angelo in the shower
and vacation where when it starts happening,
I can't help but think of the thousands of times.
I paused a VHS tape and masturbated to this.
Thousands of times.
I mean, look, your business is your business pet.
That's all I had, and I can't stress enough folks.
That's all we had was pausing a VHS tape.
It was tough back then to get your nut off.
It really was.
What year are you talking? This for me would have been you know, I guess I was 1990. I was you know 10 years old
pausing VHS tapes and they were they had to be VHS tapes that were PG like 16 candles had PG breasts
Candles is rated or though. It's PG. It has 16 candles is not a PG movie
All that you want about a thousand dollars on it. No, I don't want a bit of a thousand dollars on it. How about ten thousand dollars. Okay
It has it has the f -word it has smoking of reefer and it has tits and it's rated PG
Why do you think I've seen it more than perhaps any other moon?
Just looking this up. I know he's not he's on Twitter folks. I'm not that's just what open when I open is the devotion to the craft
That's just what open brings
16 candles yeah, I or like I was allowed to watch vacation because it is PG my parents for
got about. How was that movie PG? It was because it was just prior to the PG 13 rating,
but nowadays it would have been an art. You can't show tits, f word, and joint, and not
have it not be rated art. Yeah, they say f in it, don't they? They do. They fucking
forgot my birth. Yeah, this part's pretty good. So gross. Now, what is wrong with her skin?
is it riding off? Yeah. God bless this old lady. She's like, yeah, I'll do a full frontal.
I wouldn't have pegged her as a witch. Well, that's how he describes her in the sequel book.
Right. That's why I say that.
That is really rough stuff, man. Yeah.
Yeah, and in the in the doctor's sleep he talks about how her flesh like sticks to the wall because it's like rotting off. It's pretty gross.
Now Stephen King's famous quote about this movie is that he hated it, of course, and he said Stanley Kubrick apparently wants to make a movie that will hurt people.
The hell does that mean I don't know it's his notorious quote about the movie where it's like, but shouldn't horror kind of want to
I don't know either. I think he just thought it went too far, which I don't really see. It's not like criminally disturbing movie. It also doesn't go as far as the book goes. Yeah. I never understood Stephen King's issues with the movie.
That thing in the in the movie where you see like the guy like with the bear. Yeah.
costume on or whatever yeah that's like a bit apparently I think a big thing in the book where it's
like these orgies where they would dress up as like bears and stuff right so it's probably just
he cut stuff out of the Stephen King didn't want to cut out but like it's so insane to me that Stephen
King will like endorse silver bullet which you and I watched oh well I watched and then you fell asleep
but you can't love silver bullet not to shine it was a 1 a .m. screening and I know
But I loved it. I had a great time watching it who is entertained, but obviously the shining is a better move.
We should at some point, not for this podcast, because who would listen to us for four hours, but we should watch that Steven Webber version.
I don't really want to. Yeah. I'd be curious. I'd be curious to see it. Yeah. I mean, who else is in it? Hold on, I'm going to look it up.
Probably like Nancy Travis.
she was in everything in those days I miss Nancy Travis where is she bid I think she's around she's
probably got her money and happy let's see here she was the long -suffering wife in that shelly
Duvall was looking good right there yeah okay that's good stuff she's on whatever one of the one of
those sitcoms that lasted for like 45 years. This is I'm sure she made her money.
Uh, let me see here. Okay, the shining. Oh, she's still on it. Last man standing with Tim Allen.
Yeah, that's what it is. But before that, she was on a different one called with Michael
Malay or something. Well, she's still on last man standing. This is the one before. I
know she's still on last man. Let's see here. Nicholson ever get plugs or anything? He
still pretty balding by the Joker. I feel like he wasn't that balding though. Yeah he must have
gotten a little something done. I'm trying to find the... Dervolta is full plugs at this point.
It's easily spotted I guess when you see some but like Jeremy Piven was obviously bold in the 90s
then came back with full hair. Nobody seems to care. You know who plays the wife in the TV miniseries?
Rebecca Demorne. Oh, I love Demorne.
What's she been up to? Melvin Van Peoples in the Scam and Crothers' Room.
Okay. I love Hannah Rocks the Cradle.
That's a genre of movie I wish they'd make a lot more out.
Demorne is 56 these days.
Check's out.
Now, there's the cover of the miniseries, which always looks like Anthony Michael Hall to me.
That is a terrible cover.
Well, you said you wanted to see the God damn thing directed by Mick Harris. Now Mick
Harris also directed writing walkers. Well, I don't know. He directed a bunch of the
hell razor sequels that weren't good, but he also directed the writing the bullet
adaptation which I bought today based on the fact of that it got such good reviews. What's
right in the book. It's another Stephen King adaptation. Okay. He did sleep walkers. Good
It was, it was well received.
Okay, yeah, I'll watch it.
Got accolades, two prime time Emmy Awards, okay.
Fair enough.
I love Nicholson on this scene.
Now what do you love about it?
I just, there's some element of a,
husband really discussed it with his wife
that always just makes me chuckle,
probably because it reminds me of my childhood.
Sadly. Just a man yelling at a woman. I got to tell you I'm looking up pictures of Rebecca
DeMorne. Current pictures. And I think I want to marry her. Folks, I mean it's this is what it's
come to. Joe's googling pictures that you can't see of Rebecca DeMorne and showing them to me. I mean
Are you disagreeing? She looks very attractive. She always did phenomenal. She was in the in keepers. Wasn't she?
We are now that was the lady from top gun
Okay, well, she was in something like that
Who was that?
Kelly McGillis Kelly McGillis. Yeah, lesbian. Uh -oh. The morning is single
I'm sure you I think I think I could have a shot with a lady like this
get in there she's heading towards 60 well make sure if she tells you that she's
60 you don't say that she looks younger she's married to Patrick O 'Neil
sportscaster and Bruce Wagner novelist so I mean it seems like she's open
minded to an artist type are you an artist time I would say so all right I'm
gonna make a play for the morning get in there hey that's not make it sound
crash pad. All right. I want to miss
the morning. I have a Joe
Derosa on the phone for you. Oh,
my put him right through. What an
artist type. What does he want? He
says you're holding up really well.
Okay. He said you're pushing 60
and he thinks he's got a chance at
that. Well, he's not wrong by
all means.
All right, scat me and
there's just now calling the hotel and they're closing in. Now, crank me if I'm wrong.
We have roughly an hour remaining. Oh, Christ. Normally, we'd be out at this point.
We have an hour remaining. We're at 122. Usually, we end at 130. So we better whip this
in the shape, Joe. Well, I mean, we were doing great. I knew we shouldn't do this goddamn
movie. We promised the people you did. I had nothing to do with them. Well, you said
we should start saying what we're going to do. No, no, I never said that. So now we need
to pick what we're doing next next. No, we're not doing that because we're going to end up
in this fucking jam again. We get another hour, another hour. Maybe we should smoke some
brief. What do you think? I think you're going to be
measurably slurring your speech. Am I slurring? No.
No. Well, I need you to ramp it up. Have another beer or something because you're
getting slow over here. Oh, people. I think, though, I think you'll find
they're loving me out there. This goes out live, right?
Right. Folks, tweet in your thoughts. Time to take some calls.
Hey, folks, I would really help if we could take some fucking calls you want me to I can't tweet
For people said yeah questions about the shining right? Yeah, do that. All right, but you got to talk while I do it
Pack because I can't do two things at once. I'm not a god googling Rebecca de Mourne photos. Can you blame me?
It was worth it the juice was worth the squeeze
You not agree
Okay, well, let me let me think about what I watched this weekend. I watched
Some curb enthusiasm. I'm rewatching that with my girlfriend. I think you and I have a Larry Richard Lewis rapport about us. Who's who you think you're definitely Richard Lewis?
You're out of your fucking mind. You're very the sky. I'm very David. Well, okay.
All right, I'll be Richard Lewis. Fine. You get to be the star.
There's a shot of Richard Lewis when he had to help a blind man move where that ridiculous Harry has is drenched in sweat
That me and my girlfriend pause and laughed out for like an hour and a half. It's one of the funniest things
I've ever seen and I love Richard Lewis. Why would you take a personal?
Because I want to be Larry David. I relate to him. Okay. All right. I relate to him. You can be them both
You know if I had said Larry David you would have said I'm Richard Lewis. That's not true
I watched Phoenix as I mentioned I watched Western civilization which I mentioned this is this is death
I can't think of what I watched well. This is riveting well. You're also not you did tweet all right. I
Watch a lot of dark. I want you can carry this. What are some new documentaries that I watched pets stop, please
This is sad at this the nightmare which I already mentioned right. I watched a documentary called deli man
What's Deli about the New York Jewish Delicatescence?
It was wonderful
Save the day. So what it was wonderful. It's just people talking about it how thinly sliced their corned beef is
It's they interview owners of the most famous Delicates contestants that are still in operation. It was wonderful
Okay, it was wonderful a lot of Jerry Stiller interviews
about how much he enjoyed this. Yeah, we used to go to Carnegie Deli and Sid Cesar would get behind the
counter. You know stories like that. That's not a real story from it, but you know what I mean. Well, I just
put it on my must -see pile. No, I love it. See, I love a deli, though, because I have class. I like Deli's, Joe. Doesn't
mean I want to watch a documentary about them. It was wonderful. It brought me great, great joy. All right.
Uh, can't you just was in there that Delhi like 45th and 8th or something by letterman 45th and 7th maybe and I ate there with friends when I first moved to New York and they came with a check and the sandwich was going to be like $24 and I left.
You walked out now I'd like to go back and give them that money, but I was like, I, yeah, I couldn't have afforded if I wanted to.
Well, who I was like fuck this and I walked out who paid for it?
Probably does the waiter pay in that situation? You were alone.
Now I was with people that we got split checks.
So you walked out, I said I can't do this and I left.
And what'd your friends say?
Afterwards, they were like, it was pretty expensive and I was like, I'm sorry,
I can't even afford that if I if I wanted to afford it.
I was gonna have to wash dishes like I was in the muppets take fucking men at.
back with the rats he paid his dues folks everything in New York I was like
this can't be the price everywhere I went coming straight from Missouri I'm I'll
say to all of you almost through a full bottle of wine yeah yeah which I don't
know if that's a lot or not it's that should be your intake for the evening
usually. Really? But I've done it. I've done it. I watched a movie called Uncle John. Yeah, I
keep seeing the starting John Ashton at midnight run fan. What year was this movie? It brought out
this year. It was kind of interesting. It was like half of it was a like a romantic comedy
and the other half was like did Uncle John kill this guy or not? And they keep going back and forth
and you're like, how are these connected? And they kind of sync up at the end. How's John Ashton
it. He's great. It wasn't an amazing movie. I'm a big fan of John. It's worth a view. I love John
Ashton myself. Is he funny at all in it? Price divorced. I learned because I looked him up.
He's not funny at all in it. No. Because he is a funny guy. Yeah. We got a couple questions here.
You want to answer him? Let's do it. Did you get a real boner or a fear boner when the sexy lady
in the tub became a rotting corpse? Real turning into fear. I'll say real straight through.
Real and then I got harder and then the other one just says I can't think of any questions. Okay. That's help there. Well that unequalized was the boner question. I did have to sort of when before the woman turned into a rotting hagg. I did have to sort of mentally stunt my potential boner.
because I was feeling it a little bit which I always kind of feel sitting next to a
hunk of a man sure like Pat Walsh. Now even out of this day just simply a naked
woman walking on the screen can just pop up a bone zone. Sometimes. I that
definitely when I was a kid it was relentless but nowadays I can usually keep it
in check because of the amount of disgraceful porn that we've been subjected to
Yeah, well yeah, yeah, but I I've reduced my masturbation intake to I don't know maybe once a week
Twice a week I barely do it anymore. So nowadays I get that sort of young kid flare again when I see an attractive woman in a movie
And I'm like oh, I'm gonna get your boobs like it's kind of exciting. No, I still have that. I just might not spring to attention immediately
Well, because you're a degenerate pervert, that's Trump, whose mind has been just destroyed by
Phil also true. Everyone in this scene has used the N word and we're watching it with subtitles,
which makes it extra uncomfortable. Yeah, yeah, it makes me a little uncomfortable. I'll tell you
what else didn't help the Oscar cause and I loved hateful eight. You know, I loved hateful eight.
What else didn't help the cause was the fact that one of the white actors to get nominated was
Jennifer Jason Lee playing the most racist character in history. Yeah. Yeah, and Samuel Jackson
I never saw mentioned or discussed as a potential nominee
Which I think people just take him for granted at this I agree just a thousand percent because he was incredible
She was very good in the movie, but I don't think she deserved a nomination for it necessarily. I got to tell you my money would have been on
What's his face the sheriff guy?
Kurt Russell. No. The guy that plays the race of sheriff that becomes
Walton Goggins. Yes. Yeah. Yeah, I don't ruin anything. Look at a snuck in there
If this was Samuel Jackson's first movie, he would have won best actor. That's what's kind of fucked up
Probably was he nominated for Pope fiction? He was he famously lost to Martin Landau for Ed Wood and
And in the little box they put the actress faces in the five little boxes. You see Sam Lijax and go
SHIT! Mother fuck in the box on screen. I don't believe that.
Joe, what do I gain from making that?
I have seen this. I don't believe that. Here's why I don't believe it.
Google it. It's a widely publicized claim.
Don't get anything, but you also believed last week that I had seen
Get hard with you, which I didn't see and then I remembered who I saw well, my friend Jaron
But Jared
But you can see this it's one of the most famous moments in Oscar history
He's got the box on him and he said he starts cussing in the box. He's really genuinely angry
He did probably deserve to win. Why are you telling me this because now I want to look it up
Just watch it later. I already told you what happens. I'm gonna forget later
Somebody tell me all you like Samo Jackson said shit when he was faces in the box. I don't need to see it
I believe it happen. I don't need to watch. I don't believe it. I don't believe you. Oh, I don't believe any of your bull shit
I
Don't fucking believe a thing you're saying right now, man
Okay, thank you're full of shit and I thought it for a long time and it feels good to finally say it to you
How much longer do we have in this movie?
Joe Holy God.
10 minutes has passed since we last checked.
I've got to stop doing this.
I have a right to entertain these people now.
I truly thought.
We've pledged to entertain them.
I truly thought about 20 minutes had passed.
No.
9 minutes.
You know why?
Because you're finishing off that one.
Is that what it is?
Yeah.
Why don't you have another drink?
Because I'm trying to keep myself in control.
I'm enjoying a beer.
Sippin' up like a gentleman.
Fair enough. You're doing wine shots over in the corner. I'm not doing wine shots. I've just had a few glasses of wine
Well, what's in the what's in the news? What's going on in the news?
The hell is the matter with you
You excited about suicide squad. I am actually are you no because that guy has only made terrible fucking movies and this will be terrible to me
training day
No, he didn't he wrote training day
Wait, isn't suicide squad the guy who made, oh no, that guy's doing batland and Superman David Avery wrote
training or air, or air, excuse me, wrote training day. He directed end of watch. He did
uh, first time watch. Yeah. So the guy who is doing batland and Superman Zack Snyder. He's the
one of the next all the time. Except the only terrible movies. Why are they interesting? David
like a sort of crime thriller -y kind of thing,
and they were like, this guy's good at that.
All right.
No, I like, then I like the evening.
Zach Snyder, you know, I enjoyed the dawn of the dead remake.
I said, that is amazing, and then everything else.
Hot trash.
I don't like Watchmen, but I think it's a good movie.
I just didn't particularly care for it.
It was terrible, but at least it was long.
What else did he make?
He made sucker punch which is one of the worst movies ever made in my opinion. I like to man of steel. Oh
Why didn't you like man of steel? I hated it. Why?
Just joyless
I he made 300 I like 300. All right. You didn't like 300. I didn't like 300
Oh boy, he just makes like soulless
Yes, you know, movies with nothing to relate to in them.
And I hate them all except on of the day.
We've gotten zero other questions.
Why don't you retweet this and see if it helps.
Joe, what are they going to ask?
Questions about the shining.
What do they mean?
What are they going to ask?
But we can answer our own questions.
It'd be fun to hear people from the audience say, hey, you have more followers than us.
an idea. Well, I know we don't need to bring that up. I mean, I don't think they enjoy
you as much, but you have more followers. I do. I do. But look, you have all those followers
on Vine. So what do you want to send a vine out? Somebody just, I'm kidding. No, I was making
fun of Vine. Somebody just asked, do you like ice cream Joe? That's their question. Do you
have an answer for that? They asked you. I mean, I like ice cream. But do you have an answer
about me for that I would say you like ice cream yeah wrong how little you know
me you don't like ice cream I have a most of the time I will have an allergic
reaction to it because many milk but you like it I like the flavor of it pet but
I can't eat it all right folks I rest my guess all right what do you take with
all these colors like they're a lot of use of reds like hard orangey reds in
this. Blood's coming. Blood's coming. What do you take of the blues?
Somebody's going to blow it. You get that from blue. Well, we discuss blue in
regards to night bar and home stream. Yes, blue, well, that was sleep in
night bar and home street, correct? Yeah. What are you taking this movie? I'd have to
start watching now looking for blue. I have a look at the framing of that shot.
Is it it's what if this was your house? It's insane that it looks like the grand Buddha pached hotel
Yeah, it's insane how perfectly framed the shot is every shot is perfectly framed like that
That's look at it
Did you enjoy eyes wide shut?
Yeah
Yeah, that's fine. I
I hate it AI and then I watched it recently and loved it I like to AI better and I hated eyes wide shut
Because I was expecting a lot more fucking watch again recently and loved it
What is the I don't even remember what the plot of eyes wide shut is there's not much
I mean, it's just a marriage collapsing Tom Cruise goes to a sex party
That's it. It's kind of caught up in a
Underground world of sexuality. Okay, wife's like every guy I see I want to fuck. Let's try to get a rise out of them
Just about a marriage falling apart
Okay, and just kidmen ever get banged outside of the marriage. No
She talks about wanting to she walks around in a
Negligé
Okay
So it's it's it's Tom Hanks banging Tom Cruise
I know I'm kidding. Tom Hanks banging. It'd be funny. That alone would be, you know, in all the movies, the Tom Hacks has been and I've seen them all, baby. I don't think we've ever seen Tom Hanks have sex.
Unless you can prove me wrong. Maybe big when he feels that woman's up.
I don't want to see Tom Hanks have sex. No, you don't. It's going to ruin Tom Hanks for me.
It's going to ruin. I have a Tom Hanks impression, but it's only visual. So I can't really do it on the podcast. Okay, but I have a great Tom Hanks visual impression. Can I say it?
Yeah, but I don't think we should do it right now is my point. Right. Because nobody can see it. You know what I mean? Yeah. I could do it for you. I mean, I don't care. I'll see it after.
see it after. She's got very hungry. I'm hungry. Let's say 15. It's that time. Yeah, I'm jealous of the people in this movie that they have this big industrial kitchen where all this can't food in it. I would like to eat some of that right now.
What do you think about I think I might like might benefit me to have a pantry like a house with like like that like a kitchen.
And I am told this is your food for the entire year, right?
And if you eat it, you know, at a reasonable rate, you gain no weight, you lose no weight
by the end of the year.
This is good for you.
I think I would kind of love that.
Why don't you ration it out?
Why don't you and Annie McDow and Kristen Wigg have some sort of rich people neighborhood
meeting.
Yeah.
Where you have a system where this happens.
All right.
I will.
know, we all share a communal thing. Yeah. Okay. You know, sorry, the rest of us are
out here living real life. I think it's a great idea because you know, Wig and
McDowell ain't eaten much and that leaves more for Papa.
Wig to me looks like she could put it away. She's a thin woman, but she looks like she might
like to get down with like some pizza or strumboly. Strumboly. I just get that vibe from
All right, I get a strumboly vibe any McDowell. I picture eating seeds
Maybe leaves she's finding on the ground now from the amount that she's walking. I worry about her health
But wig I think you could pull up and you know have a beer and some ribs with her probably you know
Maybe not strumboly, which I don't think people really actually I eat it
What is stromboli? It's like a personal pan pizza. It's the better version of the calzone. A stromboli is a
large
Doe baked dough product from your pizza places, okay
And it's you know, it's the full dough thing like the dough cover like a calzone is there dough in it
But it's large and it's filled with stuff. Okay, so you get a cheese steak one or an Italian meets one or a pepperoni and cheese or a meatball
Sure, and they're delectable. They're delicious the calzone will have the calzone always has regottachis plus mozzarella and
And whatever and it's a personal size thing
Stremoli is for multiple people and it doesn't ever got to cheese. It's always mozzarella and
meat and it is
Delicious folks. I am sorry. I'm sorry
Well, what was wrong with that? Oh, it's fine. It's fine
What was you asked what a Stromboli was? It was fine. Well then why did you say that?
Crystal Wig this year also not mentioned in the acting races was amazing in a
movie that is also now in Netflix called Welcome to Me which I loved. She plays a
very mentally disturbed woman who wins the lottery and decides she's gonna make
a talk show starring herself to bring herself fame and I fucking loved it I saw
and theaters, not one person has mentioned it to me,
not one person mentioned it for Oscars.
That's what, that's why this business is so fucked.
People like racism obviously is a major problem.
But they send you, they send people who are in the academy,
screeners of the movies that are coming out.
And if a movie does not get sent to people's houses,
it has zero chance of being nominated.
it. Sure. Never once has a movie or a performance or a screenplay
been nominated for an Oscar that I wasn't sent at my home as a member of the
writer's guild and the actor's guild of America. And you will get movies that
don't get nominated. For instance, Pat and I both received this year, Furious
Seven. I received two copies of Furious and not Mad Max. And I got to say, yeah, I
loved Mad Max. It was the most fun movie I saw all year next to Star Wars. I
nation. In this year, I do think it does. I don't know what I, what else I would put above it.
This year was a terrible year for movies. When I'm looking at this giant stack of movies that I
was sent for my consideration, I'm like, most of these fucking suck. Oh, the other ones are okay.
There are other movies that could have been nominated. Yeah, for sure. Argo. That was three years
of an award. And at one best picture. National treasure, I was disappointed to see it didn't make
That was 12 years ago and was not nominated the break up which people write off is just a comedy
But I think it's a lot of emotional value. You think these movies all come out this year
I believe all movies come out every year. Okay, every year again and again
Movies are never finished. They're just abandoned
Here's a movie. I love that that should have gotten a little love
Sleeping with other people starring Jason Sudakus and Allison Brie
I thought that movie looked terrible. I did too. And yet it was great. And I bet you'd love it. And folks, I heard that's my if you take away one thing this week, watch that movie. It's great.
Pat Walsh if you haven't noticed is a big fan of he wants to see a lot of the SNL movies get nominated. I remember when ladies man came out and looked was looked over. He was very angry.
I'm doing a guy that thinks all SNL characters or actors do SNL movies based on sketches.
That's fine.
Well, who's not, yes, ending now?
I said, that's fine.
No, that's not a yes and that's what's called a dead end. Yes, and my favorite of those S &L movies was probably
Dreamgirls
My favorite S &L movie is wired
Did you see wired I tried watching it. I'm sorry Michael Chicolus as John Bolush. It's terrible. Did you read wire?
You mean the movie where John Bolushie's corpse wakes up and goes and relives his life at the big it's terrible
Oh, they do it like Scrooge style he wakes up in the morgan leaves and it's like what am I doing here?
It escapes. I want to watch him and goes in like
Witnesses his life or whatever. I want to see like who plays Acroid who plays all these people
Dan Acroid was played by we talked about earlier Glenn close
Very odd joys. I always thought Glenn close should play George Washington
That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it
I was in a video study today that was going out of business and selling off all their
inputs.
Of course it was.
Selling off their complete inventory.
Where was it?
Santa Monica Boulevard.
It's called Video Hut.
Santa Monica and what?
And why on earth would you not tell me?
Because I asked you to hang out all weekend and all weekend you kept talking about, like,
I'm too dizzy to hang.
I have vertigo. I can't try again. I went over. I bought five. They were doing five for 20s. Oh, that's actually not that good deal. I got some movies for going on a birthday one movie one movie. One movie. I almost bought because I only went in to get horror movies. Right. One movie. I almost bought that I did not buy what a movie called Mothman written by Pat Walsh. They had a DVD copy. They have a DVD copy of it. That might not have been the R's. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It
was your name is on the back of the box. I looked at it. Oh, well, thanks for picking
it up, Joe. You didn't think I'd want it. They didn't even send me a cup. I figured
I could just buy it off of Amazon if I ever really wanted it. It's terrible. Well, that's
what you've told me. And I was like, I don't know if this is worth owning just because my
friend co -wrote it. Well, I would like to go. I bought a lot in the great Hollywood video
close out of about three, four years ago. Maybe more. Something tells me Mothman will still
be there. How dare you. I didn't know they did a release of it because contractually, I am supposed to
get a DVD copy of it and I did not receive it. Well, it's on DVD and I looked it up on the internet
to make sure I could buy it elsewhere if I ever wanted to because I didn't want to waste one of my
fives on it. Thanks Joe. Well, because you tell me it's terrible. Truth be told, watch it to be like,
this is ironically funny. Truth be told, I wrote a terrific horror comedy version of it that was not
shot. The version that was shot is perfectly fine by sci -fi channel movie
standards. It just doesn't take into account any of the cool shit that was
written for it. Yeah, well that's part of why I didn't buy it. I was like this isn't
Pat's work. No. This is the work of some suits. Yeah.
Liked of my life. I just jumped in on the line to let people know we're still
watching the movie. Yeah you're not I'm gonna announce that you've killed this bottle. I haven't
killed it. The remainder of the bottle. The remainder of the bottle is in the glass. Okay.
Why are you being so judgy? I'm not being whenever you drink, you accuse me of being judgy.
I'm not being judgy. I drink myself and I'm not being judgy. Okay, it feels a little judgy right now.
Yes, if we have this conversation every time every time I drink. Yeah, that seems judgy you saying that all right
Why don't you get another beer buddy? I'm drinking a beer. It's you're nursing it. Come on man. You're making me feel bad folks. I have worked
Tomorrow. Yeah, you said you wanted to go to a bar after this
And you said you would do it
This is the alcoholic mentality folks Joe says we should go to a bar after this then
an hour later it's you said you wanted to go to a bar because I said we should do
that and you said yeah let's do it folks I kind of don't want to anymore anyway
it doesn't matter when we get it by tea I'm getting tired from the we can say all the
things we want to say that we can't sound there's a great taco truck at the end of my street
we have walked down to that sounds great I also have left over KFC in the fridge
I'm assuming it's fine. I'm in decent weight.
What do you get up? You get a ten piece?
Today I got the eight piece bucket plus two large sides.
Match potatoes and gravy and coleslaw, of course.
And I ate four pieces and some sides for lunch.
And I thought, even if I eat the other half,
for dinner that's meals for the whole day. I actually have done the calorie calculations
of a bucket of KFC. Yeah. It's way less than you think. It's like fifteen hundred calories
or so. At the end of the day, you're eating chicken and then you got some fried bread
shit on it. It'll be about two thousand calories when all said and done, which is what you're
supposed to eat. I just kind of didn't care. When I lived in New York, I would get Popeyes
on a Saturday for a hangover but I haven't had fried chicken. Like, I love it. I haven't
had it in a very long time.
KFC is the best fried chicken on planet earth in my opinion. The, uh, the, uh, what do you
make of that? I'm not using chicken. They use like gelatinous orbs that they farm. Insane.
It's retardedly wrong. It's not a thing. You're not supposed to say that word wrong. I'm
sorry, it's retardedly incorrect. It's no, it's, it's come on, it's crazy. It's like, it's
chicken. It's fucking chicken. All right. gelatinous orbs. That's what they say. They farm out
like things that aren't a lot of like they're, I don't know, there was apparently a 60 minutes
about it. I didn't see it. And what did 60 minutes say that it's true? That that's where this
report came to be. What do you think is Chinese food? Like, when you get orange chicken, here we
go at the racism now. That's nothing. Here we go at the racism. I asked you to keep it off
this podcast. I'm saying when you bite into a piece of orange chicken, it's not chicken.
Texts it is. It's a piece of chicken. Then why does it not look or taste anything like any other
piece of chicken? It's it's a chunk of chicken that they roll in a batter and fry. What the hell do you
think it is? I don't know. That's why I'm asking. But any sort of Chinese food does
does not look or taste anything like chicken.
It's delicious.
Here's what I can't wait for.
When I, tomorrow when I say I'm posting the podcast
and you say, please send it to me.
I'm worried about the Chinese chicken remarks I made.
But I'm not at all worried about it.
You're never are during the podcast.
You didn't hear me say, is it dog or cat?
That's kind of what you're insinuating.
Which is like the oldest of racist thing.
I'm saying what is it?
Because it's not chicken and I've always wondered.
There is chicken pet, but chicken deep fried in so much batter that you can't tell it's
chicken anymore.
All right.
It doesn't have the texture or taste or appearance of chicken.
General sourced chicken to me always tastes like chicken except fried.
Sounds a little different.
An orange chicken is more like a bread.
It's heavy breading on very little meat.
I'll give you that.
All right.
But it still tastes like chicken to me.
anything else? Any other races you want to dissect in one fell swoop? I stand
probably by this is not being even remotely racist. Anything that I've said is
not even remotely racist. Talk about Indian food now. What is that gravy? I like
Indian food and I like Chinese. I don't like Indian food. I love Chinese food. I hate
Indian food other say they're saying that Indian food now is like the official cuisine of London because London has no
Aside from like bangers and mash seems like the worst food on the fuckin fish chips when I went to London. I was like
I definitely lost weight
I was walking a ton and I was like I'm not excited to eat any of this and then tell my ass anybody to recommend a restaurant
They would recommend Indian food
It's not like going to Italy. I don't like it. It's all in that it's all in that thick gravy
I don't care for it, and there's a lot of like, is it ginger flavor?
Well, Indian food is like your curry, a tikka masala.
A tikka masala, that sounds Italian.
Does?
Folks, I think we might be getting a little preview of Joe and drunk history right now.
It's not that sounds Italian.
Yeah, no, it does.
A tikka masala.
Yeah, it does.
Say another Indian cuisine. I'll do it Italian.
This is not questionable in any way for you racially, but me suggesting
That orange chicken might be something other than chicken is race. Well, what else do you think it is Pat?
I don't know. I'm just curious
What no you you have an idea in your head clearly. You're going somewhere. I have no idea and I order it
So obviously I don't think it's dog or cat. Well, what do you think? I'm just wondering what is happening pork maybe?
Why would it be pork if it wouldn't it chicken cheaper than pork? I have no idea. I really don't
All I know is like you get a grilled chicken it looks and taste one way you get a fried chicken
It looks and tastes like grilled chicken. That's fried. This gentleman for the Chinese food. I don't know what that is
For the critics of my wine intake on this podcast
Pat Walsh just pulled a beer out of the pocket of his army jacket
So I didn't have to get up so he didn't have to get up again
John Rambo style. This is my third of the evening. This is my third glass of wine. You only get three out of a bottle.
Folks, get four out of a bottle. That's why you get a bottle of wine for a couple when you go out on a nice 10.
So I'm on my fourth. I find barely a glass ahead of you. You've been demanding that I drink faster than I get a beer out.
I'd like you to criticize me faster
Please drink faster. Is it so much that I want to drag you down to what I am to what there is no end Pat
It goes on and on. It's a cycle of pain
More questions from the fans on Twitter. I'll tell you what I love is some of those nila wafers the best cookie of all time
This guy just said give me a shout out on the podcast. That's fine shout -outs to Jack O his handle is what underscore is underscore Rizzo
And I don't know what resource I would not have given them that China contribute something ask a question
Then we'll give you your shout out our friend barn wood b -a -r -n -w -o -u -l -d barren wood
Said you belong on the east coast Joe. Oh
These are very me centric tweets, which I don't mind
Are you getting anything over there? No check
Here neighbors here neighbors walking by I have the thinnest windows in my new apartment
the thinnest windows. And as Pat has heard, apparently my upstairs neighbors are rolling
around back and forth on the floor or something. What have they been doing up there?
He might be a noise that he can hear us giving a full podcast, you know, a full commentary
on the shiny. So this girl Samantha Shambley. She's all excited. Oh my God. Oh my God. Why
can't I remember all my questions? Yeah, I read that one already. Samantha, we want to
hear your questions. Well, I love that you have Garfield. You got anything
else? Or is that it on your Twitter page? I'm a big fan of Garfield. I used to
laugh so fucking hard at Garfield. What was it that you liked? The lasagna? It was
just the high jinx between him and the dog. It was generally his disgust with
John and John's loneliness. The lasagna, the naps, the hating of Mondays, is a
smile at best. But when he'd really lay into somebody I would laugh out loud. I used to
love Garfield and friends and then the spin -off Hampton and friends. Who's Hampton?
It was a pig on a barn. They used it to pat out an episode of Garfield because Garfield
didn't go in any adventures really. Well one thing I did, oh yeah, Hampton
and friends, I remember that now. One thing I did enjoy about Garfield, it really was the
personality of a fat man that loathed the world. Yeah. You know. And just really demeaning
towards the intelligence of that dog. Yeah. Well, dog was talk. Yeah. It was almost like
he was, it was almost like he was prejudice towards mentally handicapped people or something.
Pretty hard core stuff when you think about it. There was also Heathcliff, which was just
worthless. I hated Heathcliff. Terrible. Heathcliff would always do the thing, which is one of my
favorite comedy trips, which is put a whole fish in your mouth and come out with just the skill.
Another question over here. Is it a true Kubrick? Is it true that Kubrick insisted on real blood
coming out of the elevator? No. I don't know, is it true? That can't be true, right? That is from
Dave 5545. I mean maybe are they talking about like animal blood? I think I
have heard that rumor before. All right. I think there is supposed to be an
amazing shining documentary. I've seen the documentary that comes with the
Kubrick box set. I've seen that one too. That goes into the shining. They don't
mention anything about that. The one where it's like him playing the music.
Yeah. He's yelling at Shelley Duval the whole time. Yeah. Yeah.
Well, she'll I did all despised about that. That's pretty intense. Well, there's the argument of he hated her
Or that's what he needed to do to get the performance
Yeah, I mean he he brought her to like the brink of sanity, which she hated about him
This is like that error of filmmaking where they're like he couldn't get the take
So he went up and kicked him in the balls. Yeah, and then he got it baby, you know like this now
You couldn't do anything like that at all. No because everybody's a pussy. I just read it article about vinyl the
Martin Scorsese show and they talked about how Olivia Wilde and one takes spat water and Bobby
can of all his face and they talked about this in the article like 25 times like it just brought
this rawness out of the performance they were so blown away by it would be a very minor thing
and I also tell you this can of all it spats some water in wild space and it was discussed can of
would be thrown out of Hollywood, thrown out of Hollywood. You can't, you can't
spit in a woman's face in a film set or in life. Or should you? I'm just saying it was
odd that it was discussed so often. Now this is a topic. Rarely do we get
political in this podcast, but Pat has been lobbying for this for years. They'll
the right for to spit water in a woman's face. I've never sped anything in
anybody's face. I'm just saying they talked about it like it was a return to the roots
of cinema and I was like, I wonder if Bobby can't have all had spat in Olivia Wilde's
face. How that would have gone down. Old BC. Did you go out for the Ray Romano role
in vinyl? I have no idea. I auditioned for it and get it. I think you probably went out
for the Ray Romano role. I went out for a role of a really arrogant record executive
that insults a lot of people.
It's probably a remnant.
They talked about,
of course, as you're seeing as addition to him being like,
who is this guy? He's fantastic.
They're like, you don't know who Ray Romano is?
He's like, no clue, who is it?
And that's how he got that.
Wow.
Another question here.
This one comes from Mitch Oliver 14,
MITCHOLIVER 14.
Who would you rather take to the prom Betty or Veronica
or Jughead?
Mr. Willoughby
We got here from Rob Larrick at our L .a. U. R. I. C. H. Rob writes in right free is a big fan of the show
Yeah, is it me or do the twins look like the byproduct of an incestuous Oompa Loompo relationship?
There is a bit of a I could say a range look to them. I will say this when when we saw them in person
They looked like completely normal people
Although identical. They do look a little otter in this movie as kids
So I wonder if it was a makeup thing or not. What do you think? I think it was just them
They they were intriguing looking women. I thought
Another one for Mitch Oliver 14 when the hell is the Jeepers creepers episode coming. I mean Jesus Christ
Yeah, get on my level
I hate the movie. I think me loving it and you hating it would lead to a great show
It's not on Netflix currently and we're
unfortunately locked to Netflix because of this TV setup situation I have in my new apartment.
So we will get to it eventually.
Recorded one over at my place.
Because then I would have to bring all the equipment over to your place.
Do you understand how this works, Pat?
You really don't do it.
You just throw things in the sand.
Yeah, you think you just come in and you just sit down and talk and it's just a...
You have no idea the work that goes into this, do you?
I know the work Joe. Do you know the work? I know the work, but do you appreciate the work appreciate the work?
Where's your pocket be? I saw Danny Collins. I loved it so much. Yeah, it was a very good film all speaking of Bobby canoval
I loved it speaking of a man who has fake hair, by the way, Bobby canoval
I truly truly love the film. Yeah, it was a good film. I liked it quite a bit. Yeah, it was completely slept on
I think he was nominated, not an Oscar, but I think he was nominated for a best actor and a comedy at the Golden Globes, which he lost.
He lost to Matt Damon in the Martian.
Yeah, exactly.
That hilarious picture of the Martian.
Danny Collins isn't funny either, but it's a technical comedy as opposed to the Martian.
It's got funny parts.
It's a dramedy, but it's really good.
but I think Pacino just can't bring in any audiences anymore,
but it's kind of amazing it wasn't a hit
because it's just a straight up the middle,
very likable movie.
Yeah, no, he's great at it.
He's great at it.
Correll Steve Correll was originally cast
in the Bobby Canavale role,
and then the movie would have done better.
But he had to drop out,
Pacino said that you got it.
I wouldn't have bought it with Steve Correll.
Yeah, you don't buy Karell as Puccino canna Valley you guys Puccino so Puccino insisted on canna Valley once Karell dropped down
I love canna Valley. I was once in a bar with him my good friend Seth Herzog was talking to him
Because I guess they're pals and I remember looking across the room and thinking oh, that's the guy from the station agent
There's before he was kind of famous. Yeah
He was in a
I think in a place all called take me out. I may have told the story before but I take me out
Was it based on that song?
This is based on the France Ferdinand.
Yeah, OK.
No, I used to, I didn't have a cell phone
I first moved to New York, and if I had a date,
I would have to be like, meet me at this intersection.
And you have to just meet me there at this time,
or we won't hang out.
So I used to go in and try to get student tickets
to Broadway shows to take a date.
So I would get in there two hours ahead of time.
Right.
This is your, this is your inside the actor's studio.
Right, talk.
So I was like if I don't find tickets here for 20 bucks, I can't bring this girl to anything
So I don't know what I'm gonna do. So I finally get tickets of the Pulitzer prize winning play take me out
So I meet her and I'm like, hey, I got us tickets. It's Pulitzer prize winning play. It's supposed to be amazing
And she's like, oh great. We sit in the front row. I keep talking it up like because I can tell she's not excited
I'm like it's supposed to be so good. I'm so excited to share
The first thing that happens the curtain opens and there's a
a bar at the top of the stage with water coming out of it.
Then I realized it's a locker room scene.
Take me out.
It's about a gay baseball player who has to come out like to his teammates.
I get to take me out of the ball game, but also take me out of the closet.
It starts by some penis and cracker, jacks.
Yeah.
Exactly.
Exactly. Outcomes 12 full -frontally nude men. They stand above me because we're in the
front row with these $20 tickets off. And he thought all my dreams have come true.
Looking up into the taint balls and dicks of 12 men with this girl, and I've been telling
her again and again, this show is going to be so great. You're going to love this show.
And she looked so red face and mortified. It was a really pretty traumatic event. And who
does Bobby can of alley play?
but I'm pretty sure he was in it.
He was one of the guys in it.
I might even be wrong about that.
I know Daniel Soon Jata was in it,
who was in rescue me.
But just looking up at a lot of Dix,
and it was very uncomfortable.
And we did not take the relationship past that point.
I mean, I don't understand what the problem is.
It's like taxi driver and taking Silver Shepherd
to a porn theater.
I'm like,
Hey, it's nice to meet you.
Now let's go sit in the front row,
Looking up at a bunch of guys that bad. I think it didn't go well. I think she's a square man. She was a square definitely
But she didn't like it. Hey Jack. I think she's a square. I think a girl that I would like to continue hanging out with would have been like this is a hilarious
Right thing to happen and would have understood that you wanted to crop on that stage and put those dicks in your mouth
Yeah, one after the other right right one after the next like you were sampling frozen yogurt
Yeah, yeah, exactly. Yeah, I mean she just doesn't get you, dude. No. All right fair enough. It happens
Scatman crudders is about to die by the way
I mean
Again, this is really the only big jump scare in this movie perfectly frame shot. He's walking between these pillars
It's perfectly framed
Nicholson is about to come out and hit him in the stomach with an axe and
Also like okay, so this is a perfect like jump scare in this movie
This has really never been replicated in horror movies either like they're not ripping off this
They're ripping off in
City's or whatever the fuck, you know in cities is great. I know you love insidious jump. It's fine
But ripping off what you mean like a guy jumping out with an X like we're just a long steady shot
You actually see the guy walk into frame and stuff. You don't see that really in horror movies sure
You see a quick jump cut jump cut jump cut
sure somebody opens the window and there's somebody stand up behind them
sure flash a lightning now here's my question to you obviously this movie is
about this character that Nicholson plays going mad and wanted to murder his
family because of the spirits in the hotel do you think that this would happen
to any old guy do you think in a different situation this guy wouldn't have
try to eventually murder his family or do you think it was this was all meant to be. I see
the movie a little bit more as a metaphor for alcoholism and people doing things they would
never ordinarily do. I don't even necessarily buy the whole spirit element of it. So I think they're
telling you that this guy left his own devices drinking career not going how he wants it to go
So, is turning against everyone in his path.
I think he didn't want this family, didn't want a wife, didn't want a family.
That bear suit is so disturbing.
It is.
I see that a lot online now, it's like a meme, the bear blowing the old man.
Blowing the old man who doesn't have his pants down by the way.
He should have his pants down.
Doesn't have his pants down and the bear couldn't be blowing him because there's a bear
mask. True. So what was he doing? Nozzling is nuts. I think it was maybe maybe it was a time
before you could show man blowing another man. I don't know. But it's I think cruising,
starring a young Al Pacino came out around this time. And was there a blowjob scene? There's
fisting in cruising. Fisting? I think it might have been in between two. Cruising is Al Pacino
from William Freak and who did the exercise. Yeah. Al Pacino goes undercover in the gay scene and
and then becomes, it's up to the viewer whether or not he becomes gay himself, but there's
so much gay sex club action, fisting and all that.
Well, who gets fisting?
Extras in the background.
Does Pacino do any hardcore sex?
No, but he's around it, and he's clearly very conflicted by it.
Okay.
Couple years back, James Franco did like recreations of scenes from cruising as like a movie
because he's into those art pieces not as a joke to like yeah like as a
statement you mean yeah I don't know what the hell that was all about okay my
favorite thing James Frank over did it was the thing where he did the acting
lessons on funny or die and he tries to get his younger brother to day
Dayfringer to play a scene from Rebel without a cause as having a crush on him, which I always thought was very funny on his brother on his brother, yeah, yeah, yeah, we're in the tail stretch of the film here Jack Nicholson is now chasing young Danny around in the snow. I'm honestly so angry that I'm not in New York to experience this blizzard and I think it's so fucking sick of the weather being the same.
Here no one wants to hear you can plan about that. I'm telling you something man. You I missed the snow
Ten minutes into that blizzard. You'd be like fuck this. No, I love it
And every where I go home for Christmas and I want snow and it's you love it when the snow is falling tomorrow
Well, you still can't get anywhere and it's all great sludge
I always loved the snow and when I was in New York and they canceled the subways and I had to walk to work
I fucking love the snow. I love it. It's something different
I just think I'm saying what I'm saying is is is a light snowfall is very nice. This kind of snowfall where you're trapped. I don't think you'd want that. No. I was essentially trapped all weekend. I enjoyed it. I watched a lot of movies.
see now she sees the ghost so there is a thing to the spirits sure or is she
seeing the true nature of her husband oh god we don't know I think it's
obviously a fucked up hotel I think they put drove them over the edge fair enough
to haunted hotel but I think really it's supposed to be seen as a metaphor for now
is this this sequence here where they're running through the snow the maze
whatever yeah is are they truly outside in the snow or is that a set I
would imagine everything in this movie is a set I feel like they're really
out I feel like in a documentary you see that they're really outside in the snow
okay I think like I know all of the Vietnam shit and
Fulmau Jacket is in London.
Like I think he so liked controlling his environment
that he made sense.
Anything you want, remember that part?
I assume that's Asian prostitute.
That's the hooker where they sampled Miso horny.
No, yeah.
She was all Miso horny.
Anything you want.
10 dollars.
10 dollars time.
Yeah, and then they sampled it in Miso horny.
Oh, Miso horny.
You're too live crew fan.
Yeah I find some of this stuff outrageously funny. Do you think there'll be a
two -life crew straight out of Compton? Yeah I think that's the follow -up.
Bring Matt TV back is the yeah there you go. That's a Matt TV sketch you're
absolutely right. I think easy you should have been nominated this year. The guy
that played easy? Yeah, of course. I agree, too. He was fantastic. I agree. I thought
F. Gary Gray should have been nominated. F. Gary Gray will never get the respect he deserves.
How frequently is a best picture nominated where there's not the director also nominated? It's
never happens. Almost never. Well, when you're nominating only five directors, but up to ten movies,
that's stupid. They also, that's what's weird too, is they could have had two more slots. They could have
had one for shredder to come. But it didn't get the votes apparently. So what are you
going to do? So it's, it's not the same number every year? No. Maybe not even five
years ago. They decided instead of five best picture nominees, it could be up to 10. Right.
Which I think is kind of weird. But it was done after the dark night because they thought
like maybe if we start letting in some more commercial movies, it's up to 10. But not people will
watch it. But not 10. Right. No, it can be 10. But I think it doesn't have to be 10. No.
I think they have to get a set number of votes that apparently straight out of Compton didn't get.
Patty, here you go. Here's a question for you. Another one from Rob Larek.
I recall a shining reference on its always sunny
seven or eight years ago. Did you write that?
There was a very heavy one flow over the Kuku's Nest episode when I was there.
Yes, I don't remember that, but I don't remember what he's talking about with the shining. It's possible. I don't think I wrote it
He was empty left. Yeah, maybe I remember when I was there
They did that very heavy kook was nice episode with debita. I love that episode. Yeah, that's a really great
I think I'm in that I am in that episode. What are you playing it? I play the comedy club MC. Oh, that's the same episode pretty sure. Yeah
now
The comedy club episode isn't that the episode where Dennis goes into the
Insane asylum. That's why I'm thinking it's the same one. No, the other one is the other one the Cougars
That's one is DeVito ends up somewhere at the end and it's suddenly Cougars nest. It's not the same episode
Okay, all right
I just watched season 10 on Netflix. I think each episode of this podcast you have said I just watched season 10 of always sunny on that
That's not true
it's can't be true because I just did it okay maybe the last episode I said it
you know you're real you're real prick tonight I'm not a real I don't mind
saying it because I'll let these people know what the real real relationship
between us is I think I think they know when is this movie going to add but I have to
Peace so bad right now. I'm going to pee between your legs. Oh, baby. Do we have one bathroom in this place? Yeah, okay, that's fine
I'm just wondering because I also really have to pay
Well, we can cross streams. I don't care
I'm gonna borrow last night buddy Brooks, and I said let's cross streams and you got kind of weird about it
Weird like let's do it or weird like weird like why don't want to and then I was a little tipsy
I was like, why not? Who cares? And that makes me look more suspiciously trying to get
him into the bathroom. Well, you did once try to pee on a tree in front of my girlfriend,
a lot of her female friends, and I thought that was odd. When was this? We walked away.
When did this happen? You might have an exhibitionous streak. When did this happen? About a year
ago. Where? Georgia Vince, the whole gang. Where, where were we? It wasn't assaultive.
We all just took a step away. I know it wasn't assaultive. Where did it happen, though?
On a on a public tree on a street. I think it was outside of Kumail's party, perhaps.
It was just kind of like, well, this is happening. We all have to
walk away.
You were trying to perhaps
Holler at one of Heather's friends and then I said, this may be why she's not
Enchanted with you
Because you peed on a tree. I was not trying to holler it in 30 minutes after meeting. I just come on, man. Sometimes you got a pee. I know
I know wouldn't you like to pee there are some night especially when I'm taking the trash out at home
I'm like I would love to just pee on the side of my house and mark the fucking territory back when I had a front
I love peeing outside. I'd go outside. I'd be like I could just pee right here. You can you really can
Yeah, I mean, you know I don't find it offensive
But that's just me that's in certain states. It's it's it's a sex crime and I think in all states
It's a sex no not in all states. That's not true
But if you pee in public and get arrested for it in like Texas
You have to like you have to register as a sex offender. Mm -hmm. Is that nuts? Mm -hmm
Actually, I think that's truly insane. It's it's crazy. Stephen Avery by the way has a lot of like
Shaking his dick at people crimes on his repertoire. Who Stephen Avery? Who's Stephen Avery?
Shall we discuss Stephen Avery for the middle hour of this podcast? Roger Avery, I thought. Roger Avery
co -wrote Pulp Fiction. Oh, Stephen Avery, the director of Suicide Squad. Oh wow, that's David
but I hear it. Roger Avery directed killing Zoe and he co -wrote. Stephen Avery is the
man who was on trial for murder. Oh, yes, yes, making a murderer. Sorry. I got a
little. We are wrapping this up just in time. I got a little confused. Sorry. I got
a little photo. I think you'll see my face in this photo. If you look closely enough.
So yeah, he does have a lot of sex crimes that aren't pissed involved but they're they're also not like rape
They're just like it's I jerked off on my cousin's car. He ran
Yeah, he ran in his cousin with his dick out and jacked him on her car. Yeah, nuts
What do you take of this closing shot where you see Nicholson and me?
I love the whole I celebrate the entire film
But I'm not saying I don't pat.
I'm asking what you take of this shot where he's finally
in this picture.
Do you think that this hotel absorbs people?
And then makes them a part of their history.
Do you think that a ghost from the past spoke to him?
I'm asking your interpretation of it.
Because he wasn't in the picture at the beginning.
Correct.
Well, yeah, I would assume so.
Yeah, I take it that the hotel just
It's like makes you a part of it, I guess, you know?
Yeah, right.
Yeah.
I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you,
a comedy on Twitter. You can follow. That's my Twitter. That's not Pat's. Don't get confused.
Mine is Joe to write to comedy. Mine is the Patrick Walsh. Twitter violence to Graham.
Yes. And for those of you in San Diego, as they say it in the Anchorman films,
I will be at the American Comedy Club. The first week in February. I think it's the fourth
in 5th right for four shows come out come out to show let's hang out you can
also hear me on Ali and Georgia Ali Ward and Georgia Hardstarks podcast which
just came out and you can also hear me twice on the best of you made it weird
Pete home podcast telling two different stories. Now you're just all over
everything these days aren't you? And soon my second appearance on Drug History and
well. I also will be doing the Kim I kick a show with Al Jackson and tone bell as we do at the
Riot LA Comedy Festival this Saturday January 30th at 3 p .m. Special guest Mosha Casher. So anyway
we'll see you soon folks you've been listening to we'll see you in hell a presentation of the
Fangoria podcast network produced by Thomas DeFail and executive producer Ken Hanley of
of Fangoria Entertainment for press opportunities,
advertising inquiries and information about
we'll see when he'll contact Ken at Fangoria .com.
Thank you.
Thanks, folks.