I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, and when the sound of your screams becomes
a thing of my dreams, you know I'll say, I'll see you in hell, you know I will.
I'll see you in hell, you know I will.
Folks, it's we'll see you in hell, back for the second episode of November and we are here to
talk about the second installment in Russell Crowe's exorcism trilogy. I can only assume
a third is on its way, the exorcism. Well it's true, yeah, this is the exorcism,
there's the Pope's exorcist and Russell Crowe is currently shooting the Pope's exorcist too.
The one we're talking about today is its own entity, it is also, I don't know if you realize
this Joe, written and directed by the son of the actor who portrayed Father Charis in the exorcist.
So it's - Who died of alcoholism, so it's sort of an inspired by true events kind of vibe.
So Jason Miller's son - Correct.
Did this? Correct.
Okay, but not, obviously not, well his famous son is the kid from -
Jason Patrick. Yeah, that's the famous son, this is another son.
This is Joshua John Miller, that is correct. As my buddy, well I don't really know him,
but a guy I like, Drew McQueenie said, I did not realize that this is a film about the relationship
between the alcoholic star of a movie about exorcists and his adult child made by the adult
child of an alcoholic movie star who became famous for a movie about exorcists.
Now, I'm on Wikipedia. Yes.
He died from a heart attack, it says here, but he was an alcoholic? I didn't know that.
Yes. Okay.
Big time. I love Jason Miller.
Yeah. He's got a great scene.
Have you seen this ninth configuration William Peter Blatty movie?
Is it worth the purchase? I've never seen it. I watched the Jason Miller scene where he comes in
and he's talking to the dog like the dog's an actor. I was like, this is hilarious. I want to
see this movie, but - I should give it another go. I was completely baffled by it when I watched it,
but I kind of write off anything I watched during the pandemic. I obviously did not give it a fair
shake. It was weird. It was weird as hell. I know that much. It's considered the unofficial
part two, because Blatty wrote The Exorcist, then he wrote Legion, which Legion became Exorcist 3,
and this book existed in between the two, and he made this movie in between the two.
People say that this is the unofficial second installment of the Exorcist storyline.
I don't know why, because I don't know anything about it, but I know it deals with religion and
supernatural to some extent. Exorcist 3, or Legion, is also very funny and very goofy,
and then gets terrifying. That's what people kind of said about this, was that it's like -
You might like it. It was not at all what I was expecting when I saw it. In a good way,
I just couldn't get on its wavelength. I've been re -listening to Friedkin interviews.
He sounds so much like Donald Trump. It is crazy.
Yeah, he does.
It's crazy.
He does. They made two movies that consisted of interviews with William Friedkin in a one year
period. I think we talked about both of them on the show. And he had it at Biography,
which is great too, his autobiography.
I want to give a quick shout out to Puddle's Pity Party. If you've not seen the Puddle show,
it's a great show. It's a clown that sings with a beautiful voice, and it's very funny, surreal,
somber in its own weird way. But anyway, he's a good buddy of mine, and he just did a big show
at the Colonial Theater in Phoenixville, PA, and I opened for him, and we got to hang out afterwards
and stuff. It was just a nice time. If you can catch him on tour, go check him out. It was fun.
He just sings songs?
He - there's like video bits. It's, you know, it's a multimedia show. But yeah, it's good. But yeah,
he doesn't - yeah, it's not like he gets up and does like stand up or something. It's music.
But people are laughing or not?
They're laughing, but then at times it's very pretty. It's an interesting - it's interesting.
It's all done with a humorous tone, but yeah, at times it's - but it's also quite sincere. It's
a nice show. It's fun. Have you seen anything lately? Any live stuff?
Well, I went and saw LCD Sound System twice last week.
How was it?
Thursday and Friday. I always enjoy them. I had accidentally told two different people I would
go with them, and then I was like, ah, what the hell? Fun to get out and shake my ass.
I wish them and Pulp and other bands that play like several nights in a city
would vary the fucking set list.
Yeah.
I don't think it's too much to ask. You know, you have people going out to multiple dates.
I saw Pulp three times. I saw LCD twice and every time it was the exact same set. A bit of a drag.
But they're great. He's on Ozempic or has worked out or something. He looked like a different human
being. And I had a good time. Went and had a great dinner with some friends beforehand.
I'm trying to just always be social because I was breaking out. I really was and am breaking out of
my depression and, you know, probably maybe not permanently, hopefully permanently, but
seemed like right as I was sticking my head out
along comes this darkness at 4 15 p .m.
Yep.
Just like, God damn it. You know, like I'm doing Zoom meetings as part of my workday and it's so
black outside. Like I feel like L .A. gets darker than anywhere else. It's like I feel like I'm in
Alaska driving around. Nobody leaves the house. It's just like, you know, I don't know if part of
it's the election or holidays or what, but it's the vibes here are apocalyptic.
So I just keep setting up dates and hangs and dinners and it helps, you know,
getting out chatting with folks.
It doesn't help that with the L .A. with the light issue, you know, a lot of people,
including yourself, live sort of up these windy roads that go through the hills and things like
that. And those streets like that that are built that way just can't, there's not going to be any
life on the street after dark, you know what I mean? And you're so far removed from anything.
And then L .A. too also is not a great city for like concentrated areas. It's all very spread
out. So I'd imagine, I mean, I lived there and for whatever reason can't recall what it was like
these times this time of year. But, you know, I'd imagine it's just it does feel darker
because it's not like, you know, oh, well, yeah, it's dark out,
but there's Times Square or whatever, you know?
Yeah. Well, yeah, I mean, that's that was my Halloween. There's never been a single
trick or treater because it's pitch black and up a winding hill and into oncoming traffic. Like
these parents don't have a death wish for their kids, but it's hard to kind of get into any sort
of positive feeling. I'm definitely the first day they're available, putting up a Christmas
tree, decorating it, just trying to be more proactive about not slipping into these
seasonal chaos of depression. Yeah. And it's good. It's good to stay on top of it.
I got two dates this week that I hope become future episodes if you're going to see them,
but you're not going to see Smile 2, right? I actually hear from multiple people that it
has nothing to do with part one at all and that it's excellent.
I've heard Pinkstone said it was really good. Yeah, I keep hearing that.
All right. So I'm not against seeing it. I would like to see Heretic first.
I'm seeing Heretic tonight on a date. So if you want to do that for the next two folks,
you heard it here first. I think those are two on the docket for sure. It'd be nice if
Heretic or Smile 2 would theoretically be our third episode this month. It'd be nice to do.
I was thinking, I hate to say it on air because it doesn't commit us to anything,
but I was thinking for Thanksgiving, maybe we do like When Harry Met Sally or something. We do
like a true fall, you know, autumn in New York kind of movie, you know? That might be nice.
I've talked about Harry and Sally on this, but we've never reviewed it. I'd be up for
discussion on that film. The film rocks me. It's a great one. Apparently the Crystal sweater in
that one is coming back in a big way. The white Billy Crystal sweater when he's crouching in the
jeans. No need for that. That is, you know, I'm not saying I had it exactly, but my wardrobe was
pretty similar. Like my parents dressed me like a little Jerry Seinfeld, like a little Bill Crystal.
I just always, you know, a turtleneck and a sweater and corduroys, you know, too much,
doing too much. My parents dressed me after Carrie Fisher in that film.
Which film? When Harry Met Sally.
Anything Carrie Fisher, they would dress me in. Any one of her roles. Lover Boy.
Sure. That was the pizza kid that fucked everybody? Yeah. Yeah. Dempsey. Dempsey's
best in my opinion. Probably not a lot of passionate late night bar arguments about
Patrick Dempsey's best film. I think that usually everyone maybe says one title each and then we
just move on with the night. Not anybody's standing really firmly by their pick there.
Well, there's always the one guy that insists it's can't buy me love and then I'll start
making sheep noises at him. Yeah, follower. What was he? Oh, Thanksgiving he was in. Yeah.
He's good. Maid of honor. M -A -D -E. Yeah. Of honor. Terrible film. I did a thing, Pat, that you were
one of - I did a thing. You're one of the folks, one of my dear friends that will appreciate this.
I went to a record store yesterday in Pennsylvania that I hadn't been to
and I traded some records and I was snooping around trying to find stuff to spend my credit on
and I saw on the wall an original pressing of Queen, A Day at the Races, which is their follow
up to Night at the Opera, and I said, you know, I own Night at the Opera on vinyl. I own a lot of
the Queen records on vinyl. I don't own Day at the Races. Why don't I own this record? This is
one of their big records. And look at this, it's an original pressing, oh my God, and it's 20 bucks
for an original pressing of a great classic - I'm getting it. Yeah. I get it, I get home,
I go to put it on my shelf, what's sitting there, Queen, Day at the Races, already. I'm like,
son of a bitch. So then I go, well, I own a reissue, this is an original pressing,
that's how I'm going to justify this. I go to pull my reissue off the shelf,
no, that's also an original pressing of the same album. Yeah. And then I look further and I don't
own a Night at the Opera. So the one I was sure I had, I don't have. And now I have two of the one
I thought I didn't have. And I got to drive back to the store now and return it and find something
else. Because I can't even think of - if you lived closer, I would have just drove into your house and
said, Merry early Christmas, Pat. Here you go. And I would have taken it, although I also own
Queen, Day at the Races. I own all Queen albums and love them, especially lately, very heavily into
all their albums. I loved the album Jazz, I listen to all the time. Oh, that's a great one. Jazz is awesome.
But what you're saying, my mother, and for some reason I never, I always associate like my love
of movies and music to my father. My dad and I would rent six movies on a Friday, watch three and
Friday and Saturday night, blah, blah, blah for years, years and years. But really, my dad never
collected anything. He didn't have a single collection to his name. But my mom had thousands
and thousands of books. And I remember her being probably the age I am now. She was probably in her
40s. I was a teenager. And I asked her, like, how do you never buy the same book? She would go to a
book sale or book fair, come back with like eight giant shopping bags of books and never double up
and had really anal weird alphabetizing systems for them too, like I do. So then one day, age 45
or something, she comes home and she's getting ready to put a book back. Let's say it was
Misery, Stephen King. And she sees that there's already a copy of Misery there. And it was like
in a horror movie when you like drop the book in slow motion and it shatters on the floor. But
it was like her, I'm old revelation. She was like, I can't believe I didn't realize I already own
that. And it is a feeling. I've only had it once or twice with my massive record collection,
my massive DVD collection. I've only doubled up once or twice. I'm good about knowing what I have.
But when you do double, it's a dark feeling for some reason. You'll feel like you're losing
control, slipping away. Yeah. Yeah. It's tough. I did it, well today, again, I took the 4K copy
of Night of the Hunter that I got on Amazon. I brought it up to my bookshelf to put with
my other Kino Lorbo films. Yeah.
And I said, well, while I'm up here, let me see what criterions I might want to grab
because they keep putting criterions on sale every other week. And what do I see there?
Night of the Hunter. Right. I'm like, son of a bitch. So drove directly back to the UPS store,
sent the 4K back because I gotta say, even though it was a 4K and the criterion's only Blu -ray,
the criterion packaging and everything is so beautiful. I was like, I'm not getting
rid of this. I'll send the 4K back. So, yi yi yi. It's rough stuff.
Uh, is anything going on in the world of TV and film?
For me personally? Anything at all?
I'm just trying to think of what's happening. Have you and I been passing any links back?
Um, I always got something to shit on.
I surprisingly don't have any news psychos at the moment because I've just been avoiding
the news so much over the last week or two because of all the noise. I feel like I'm missing,
you know, announcements of entertainment related things, as well as any news that's being announced.
Well, Martin Lawrence is doing a sequel to Blue Streak.
Oh, that is right. We did discuss that, uh, which is wild to me that that's happened.
You did not seem surprised by that.
I don't know that it'll ever see the light of day, but I didn't hate Blue Streak when I saw it in
the theater. It definitely doesn't demand a sequel. I wonder if they'll bring back Luke Wilson.
I kind of doubt it, but he could do it.
I want to direct people to a TikTok or an Instagram reel that I have sent to some friends.
Girl's name is Nyissa N -Y -I -S -S -A dot L -I -Y -A -H and in the video she is ranking
horror icons, who she thinks she could take in a fight.
And it's just a real, real funny video, especially for fans, I think of this podcast.
So first up is like Chucky. She's like, easy, I'll kick, I'll kick the shit out of Chuck.
But, um, interestingly enough, the horror villain who scares her the most shakes her to the core
is the Jeepers Creepers villain, who she keeps referring to as Jeeper, which is very, very funny
to me. And then she'll like try to move on and be like, I'm still thinking about Jeeper.
And the video made me laugh really, really hard. I don't know why this girl is so traumatized by
Jeepers Creeper, who was never scary to me at all. He's like an eagle man. But, um, that was a funny
video. Other than that, yeah, there's not a whole, oh, Simon Kinberg doing a new Star Wars
trilogy we discussed. I was going to bring that up. Now we have very different takes on this. Now
I'm not a big Simon Kinberg fan, but my take to Pat on this was, I said, look, the guy's got
experience in doing blockbuster, popcorn -y movies that feature action and some of them decent
characters. And that's kind of always been the thing that worked with Star Wars in the past.
If you look back to the original trilogy, you know, like, Lawrence Kasdan wasn't a guy that
tons and tons of stuff. He had written some movies and he had written some movies that kind
of locked in with the style of thing that Star Wars is. So I have hopes. Kinberg is not directing
them. He's just writing them. I'm sure there will be a gaggle of ghost writers as well.
But I am happy at least that Disney seems to be sort of course correcting. And this is not
anything against anybody they've used regarding gender or anything like that. I'm just happy to
see they're plucking somebody that has some experience in the popcorn genre to work on these
things because they just haven't done that, you know, really. I guess even, well, I mean, you know,
it can go terribly wrong as we saw with who's the guy that did The Last Jedi, the guy that did
Luke Jumper. Yeah. You know, it can go wrong. It can go wrong with J .J. Abrams. It went right
with J .J. Abrams once, then it went wrong with J .J. Abrams. So I'm not saying -
Take The Last Jedi over a third Star Wars. I can't between the two anymore. I don't even know.
But my point is, you know, hopefully it works. But, you know, I don't know. I don't know.
It's also, it's nice to see somebody just with experience being brought in. So I don't know.
We'll see what happens. But by the way, it's episodes 10, 11 and 12. It is the official like
trilogy to the sequel trilogy to the sequel trilogy. But it's not revolving around the
Skywalker story. So I guess it's just going to pick up -
New people?
I think. Like it might be a Rey, who's Daisy Ridley's character trilogy, but that's
ominous and smoke. Like nobody knows. Like they're being very vague. So I don't know.
Star Wars to me is my broke back mountain. I just can't quit Star Wars. So, you know,
I'll always be there. And hopefully it gets good again. We'll see.
We'll see. It's years and years away.
Eight million. I have, speaking of Star stuff, I have lost any semblance of Trek
with Star Trek. Jesus Christ. There's like eight Star Trek things happening. Like I'm like,
what, wait, what?
New with the, with the new people or whole new people or what?
There's like a -
Tarantino was going to do one. That fell apart.
That didn't happen. But the Abrams one might still continue. And then like there's three
new TV shows or something. And then they're going to do a movie. That's a spin -off of Discovery. And
I've lost all track of any of it, man. There's so much Star Trek shit happening. And I don't know,
I don't know what's like, not that I was a huge Star Trek fan, but I was able to at least follow
it. Yeah. You know, uh, yeah, I sorta like the initial six movies. I saw, I didn't like the
Patrick Stewart ones. Didn't care. I thought the first Chris Pine Star Trek was great. And the
first one, um, yes, I liked the first two with Pine. Um, the third one was pretty, pretty shitty.
So, well, here's, this is interesting. Uh, Frasier,
which relates to today.
Frasier, by the way, relates, yes, to today's episode.
Um, Frasier has had this, this second season of the reboot or sequel series, whatever it is,
it, it has had one or two episodes that actually I was like, okay, this is starting to feel like
Frasier again. Yeah. They did one where BB, his agent comes back and it was awesome. She, that,
that lady who plays BB, she was, it was a tour de force. It was old Frasier. And I was like,
I don't think the problem is the writing. I think the problem is, is you need
people with that theatrical background who can elevate this material to the farcical heights
it needs to go to. If you - Not a skill everybody can do.
No. And if you watch, and by the way, Star Wars issue, Star Wars is elevated when a Liam Neeson
steps into it and goes, no, this is how you do this, you know? Right. You can, you could read
an old Frasier script and you go, yeah, it's funny, but I don't think you'd be like, oh my God,
this is poetry. But then David Hyde Pierce and, uh, and Kelsey Grammer and BB Newworth and, and
you know, these people step into it and it's like, oh my God, it goes to this, it ascends.
But anyway, uh, there are reviews of the latest episode. I have not seen it yet, but crack .com
is saying the new Frasier finally made an episode that feels like old Frasier.
Um, so I'm very excited to see it. It's, it's, it says all the reviews, episode nine fixes a big
problem with the reboot. Um, fans are wrong about the Frasier revival. Uh, uh, what else here?
Whatever. It doesn't matter. Um, I, uh, I'm excited to see this episode now. I, I'm, that's,
that's exciting. I don't know what the plot of it is, but the screenshot I'm seeing is him dressed
like Benjamin Franklin basically. So I'm, I'm already excited. Uh, all right. I'll check her
out. I mean, I'm, I'm surprised Paramount Plus is even hanging in, but I'll check her out.
Well, yeah, there's like stories coming out that CBS is going to go belly up finally.
It's been, it's been happening. As you know, I worked for BET and about three months ago,
they almost sold the entirety of BET to puff daddy, Sean puff daddy comb. So very relieved
they didn't, but it gives you an idea of where they're at in terms of their business at the
moment. I saw a news story where I guess they interviewed him and they said, what's the hardest
part about being in prison as a mogul? And he said the food. Good one, puff.
Yeah. Yeah. It should be a reality show. He's likable. He's very likable.
Well, do you remember when he had the reality show? I've been saying this guy's an asshole
for decades. Yeah. When he would order the interns to run across the Manhattan for him. That's all
I remember to get like cheesecake and you better be back in 18 minutes. And I look, I get it. I get
that a lot of it was just, we're going to do crazy stuff because it's a little more of that
getting your cheesecake and 18 minutes spirit and the workforce, in my opinion.
What do you, what do you got for the old movie corner today?
Well, I'd love to start with, I guess I'm in a TV state of mind today, but
the title is so generic, unfortunately, that I always forget it. It's called anatomy of lies.
And this is a three -part Peacock documentary that is steadily making the waves in the television
writer community because it's just sort of the greatest schadenfreude type
true crimes pushing it. I guess it is a crime, but it's a real, with all the different characters
and types of people you have to put up in the TV business, put up with as a show runner, as a TV
writer, there's always a problem person or problem people in a writer's room. There's always egos to
contend with, giant personalities to contend with, I guess in every job. But in TV, you've got to
assume everyone in the room doubled down on themselves and thought that they were in this
difficult business. So you're dealing with some difficult characters and people with personality
problems, anxiety, et cetera, social issues. This movie, this documentary is about a woman.
There was a news story about it, maybe a year and a half ago. And that story is great, but the
documentary, I would just sit back and watch. It's a great hate watch. It's about a truly terrible
person. It is a woman who, to get a job on her favorite show, Grey's Anatomy, and she was already
an established writer. She had been writing for years on the vampire diaries and other shows.
She said, I'm sick of working in vampire shows, but couldn't break into another medium. Now,
I was a multicam guy for many years. I also struggled from this. It's hard to jump,
you know, from one comfort zone to another. She found it was taking a little too long,
so decided to pretend that she had cancer. She not only pretended this to her co -workers,
but she made a video bringing on several celebrities to sort of sing her praises.
The video got watched by Shonda Rhimes, who gave her a job at Grey's Anatomy, where she quickly
overtook the writing staff. She started just ordering people around. She started saying,
I'm going to write this episode, as opposed to being assigned an episode by the showrunner,
which is what the job is. So she very quickly is such a teacher's pet that she winds up like
second in command. She's barking orders at everyone, including people that have been there
forever. Anytime anyone questions her, she says, but I have cancer, so I would know.
Then stories come up about rape. She says, oh, well, I've been raped. She makes it's just story
after story. She says, oh, I was actually in a bombing situation like this in Philadelphia.
She does it over and over and over, and eventually people start going,
something's weird. Why is this person like Forrest Gump? Why is she involved in every major?
Eventually, the wheels come off. It is revealed that she's been lying about everything.
She's also been lying. She's lesbian. She's been lying to the women in her life as well,
preying on emotionally unstable women, sometimes with children in the most heartbreaking case,
and she takes over their family and destroys their mind from inside the relationship.
It's a great, great study of a sociopath. I am pumped to watch Joe's zodiac recommendation,
and this is kind of the same thing. I watched three episodes in a row.
I've worked with numerous people like this where I'm like, something is off.
This person is a liar. The business has become such that it rewards you saying,
this pitch is personal to me because even if you go in and pitch your take on the penguin,
they'll go, but why is it personal and meaningful to you? You have to find some reason for that
and that causes TV writers to become liars. They know that if they say this happened to me when
they pitch a story, it's going to have more clout because it feels real, but they're lying so often
and you can't call them out, so you start to feel crazy. This documentary captured that beautifully.
After discussions from people that were in that room with her who silently hated her for years and
get their comeuppance, that's the sweetest part of that. There's a lot of really funny writers
who are throwing out whips and one -liners about this maniac that they worked with.
Great documentary and not too heavy. It's true crime, but it's not like people were dying or
anything, so it's a lot more fun to watch than the norm. I recommend it highly. Anatomy of lies. Joe?
Um, my theme today is comedy television, but I'll start with something relating to what you just
said. I watched a few more episodes of the dark side of comedy, The Vice Show. And the two I watched,
let's start with the Ellen one. Now, this is the Ellen thing we've all wanted to see.
Yeah. Is it new?
I think this season is newer. I didn't remember seeing these episodes the last time I tuned into
that show. But there's an Ellen one and it starts with, you know, all the bubbly stuff you'd expect
about Ellen. They're talking about when she did the sitcom, the coming out episode, the sacrifice
that she made, all of this stuff. And I'm going, here we go. They're going to ball wash Ellen
and make it sound like she was a victim or targeted unfairly or whatever. And by the way,
she deserves all the praise for what she did with the sitcom. She deserves all of it. I'm not taking
any of that away from her. But I thought they're not going to turn this on her. They're going to
turn it on her. Yeah. To the point where, and I say this carefully, I really do.
There are some executives that criticize her at the time she loses the sitcom and say
she did not lose this sitcom because of her coming out. That did cause some damage
for people that weren't ready. But they say that's not why she lost this. She lost it because the
show wasn't good anymore and nobody wanted to watch it. And she got too greedy with the integrity
and the virtue of what she had done. And I was like, so when you're watching this in real time,
you're like, that's a really harsh criticism and a thing a shitty male executive would say.
But then when they start to get into the talk show and all that stuff and how absolutely
irresponsible she was in accountability for what her producers were allegedly doing and her
behavior, whatever. And then you start to see the writers from the sitcom start to be like,
yeah, you know, man. And these people that were saying glowing things starting to be like,
yeah. And I think it's terrible that she did that. And you're like,
holy shit, man. This woman might be sociopath from way, way sooner than we thought.
But who knows? But anyway, the quote of the entire thing is there was some little kid
who at the time was like 10 years old. He was a singer. She found this kid on the internet.
She brought him on the show. It was one of these classic Ellen things. Like I'm gonna make you a
star. You're a shining soul that the world needs to know. This kid starts telling his story about
his experience with her and I'm paraphrasing, but he goes, you know, it's like an apple.
An apple is shiny and beautiful and sweet. And then you get to that core.
I was like, holy shit. And he tells this crazy story where he's like,
you know, she came into my family. She was like, I'm going to change your lives.
She said to my mother, you will never have to work another day in your life. He's like,
it was the most beautiful thing ever. She had this interest in getting into music. She was
starting a record label imprint with a major label. I was going to be the first artist released.
And he goes, and she had sent me this Justin Bieber documentary that was playing in theaters
and she had gotten advanced copy and she wanted me to watch it because she thought it'd be a good
lesson for me or whatever. And he goes, but I was on the road doing shows when she had sent it.
And I'm a kid and my mom's like, you know, honey, you're really overwhelmed right now,
traveling, doing show. Well, let's watch it when we get home next week.
Yeah. And he goes, so the first day I'm home, I'm getting breakfast with my mom
and the phone rings and she goes outside and I can see on my mom's face, she's being like
basically berated. And my mom comes back in and she's like, Ellen wants to talk to you.
And he's like, okay, this kid gets on the phone with Ellen and she's like, I'm really disappointed
in you that you didn't watch that documentary yet. Do you know what I had to go through to get you
copy of this thing, whatever. And he goes, and after that, it was never the same.
She never spoke to us again. And she abandoned the entire record label project. And I was like,
there we go. That's right. So it's an amazing episode topped only by the episode I watched just
after it, because I couldn't believe that a title in season two of the dark side of comedy
was family matters. I was like, oh my God, what happened on this show?
Yeah. And I knew Urkel was supposed to be a tyrant is all I know.
They get into that. Yeah. And in his defense, they interviewed the son, the kid that played
the older son. And he's like, yeah. And he's like, let's be real. Jaleel carried that goddamn show.
He's like, everybody can be mad. Jaleel carried that goddamn show. We were there because of him.
That show doesn't make eight seasons without Steve Urkel.
No. And it doesn't make it without Steve Urkel.
Did you know the youngest daughter eventually did porn?
I did not know. I know McCrary was doing
transsexual porn and I believe now maybe has married his co -star.
Wait, the son was? Darius McCrary, yes.
Are you sure about that? Because they didn't talk about that at all.
Eddie Winslow, yeah. Well, yeah, this is recent developments.
Oh, okay. Yeah, the youngest daughter, the one that went upstairs and never came back
down again. Yeah.
Very briefly, but she stepped into the porn arena and she's actually doing very well now.
She's like sober. She's got a kid, you know, and you feel really bad for her because she's like,
you know, she's a child and they treat her the way Hollywood treats everybody, like horrifically,
which is why children should not be in that business. But they get into the absurdity
of where the show goes in the ninth season where he has the machine that like turns him into
Einstein and all this stuff and like leading to my favorite Key and Peele sketch ever with
The Little White. Yeah, they show that when he comes in as the dad.
That is the funniest Key and Peele sketch. They go through actual episodes of the show.
It's a wild, wild thing. But the biggest takeaway is,
and it's great that they get this out there. They just talk about how unfair
the mistreatment of a black show versus a white show and the double standard and they talk about
Full House. They don't shit on Full House. They just talk about how like, no, these shows were
in the same universe. They're on the same night. Right.
They talk about the day they went to the Full House set and they were like, wait a minute.
This is what your set looks like and your dressing rooms and your
craft services. They were like, it's just insane how differently shows are handled
and people are treated due to race. So they get into all that.
By the way, that still goes on. That has not changed at all.
Yeah. They interview most of the cast. The only one they don't have any interviews with is the dad.
I forget the actor's name. Carl.
Reginald Phil Johnson.
Yeah. But everybody else is interviewed and it does sound like Jaleel White is a little bit of
a bratty whatever, but it also sounds like he's got an incredible amount of pressure put on him to
carry the show. The kid's delivering, man. Anything they throw at him, he does it and he knocks it
to the park. It is truly incredible and it looks like they're all on good terms now,
like everybody's made their amends and everything, but my God Almighty, dude, they got switched.
I don't know if I've ever seen this happen. It's switched networks in the final season
and the mom left and they just recast the mom. I never used to go on a lot more than it does now.
I never knew that happened, but Dark Side of Comedy, some of it's a little tabloidist,
tabloid -esque, some of it's riveting, some of it's good, some of it's bad,
but those two episodes I did thoroughly enjoy. Jaleel White did a Miss Pat show. He was great.
He was nice. He also has his own line of weed, purple oracle, if you're at the dispensary and
you see it. I saw our new to Shudder, Doc of Chucky, a five -hour documentary about the Chucky
franchise that to me was not boring for a second and I don't even really consider myself a huge
Chucky fan. I hope Shudder continues to do this kind of stuff. I wish we had gotten more volumes
of that six -hour horror movie thing they put out, whatever that was called that we did on the show.
The In Search of Darkness.
In Search of Darkness, yes. But I love it. I love when you have everybody back,
I love it when it's awards and all documentary. I quickly lose interest when it's people saying,
there was no genius like Don Mancini. He was the greatest. He did everything right.
It just gets very boring if people are protecting their jobs. The best documentaries are the ones
on the Scream Factory Blu -rays where they're two hours long about Return of the Living Dead
and everybody is just gossiping and telling stories about who fucked who and who had the
rights and who screwed each other over and so forth.
Well, I told you the one on the Halloween III documentary where you're expecting the guy,
everybody to be like, it was brilliant and nobody got it at the time. First
talking head pre -credits of the documentary is one of the producers going,
it was idiotic not to have Michael Myers. It was a dumb decision. I wasn't asked,
they sent me a fat check so I shut up and I walked. I'm like, oh my God.
Yeah, that's what you want. Or like RoboDoc, the RoboCop documentary is just people with old
gripes and grievances. Those are the ones that are fun to watch.
Yeah. And that's what this is. If you're a diehard Chucky fan, this is obviously your
number one must see. I've seen all the movies. I enjoyed them to varying degrees. I liked all
of them for the most part. But this is just great. The first hour or so, maybe even more,
is about the inception of the first child's play leading up to its production. So you got Don
Cini writing this script. You got a producer bringing on Tom Holland to direct and then do
a draft. And then this thing goes into the endless rights disputes over the character of Chucky.
I always, cause I liked Tom Holland, just sort of sided with him and assumed that he was in the
right. You watch this documentary, he does not seem in the right. They talk to Tom Holland a lot.
You get to even read the letter that he wrote to the writer's guild. And you know,
it's very well researched and investigated. But these things happen all the time. People think
they have different ownership of the script. Where it becomes really important to decipher
who did have the idea is when it winds up being a franchise that lasts for 40 years over multiple
movies and multiple franchises and multiple TV shows on multiple networks. Then you really do
to nail down who came up with the fucking character. So this is a great documentary
because it explores all that. You've got both men arguing their points on camera.
Don Mancini is great. He's a charming guy, as is Tom Holland, as is who carries this documentary,
Brad Dorif. His interview segments are the highlights of the thing. He's really funny
and really cool and just great to listen to. Eventually his daughter enters the franchise,
they start talking to her as well. She was in Cult of Chucky. But anyone who you want to see,
Jennifer Tilly, Chris Sarandon, everybody who's ever played a role in this thing gets talked to.
You do that original trilogy, then you go to kind of the rebirth and when it became sort of more
Chucky and all that. And really you're left with kind of a fascinating five -hour, not boring
portrait of this little idea, a doll that comes to life to kill people, not even the most original
idea, that became this multi -decade beloved thing. Speaking of beloved, they talked to
Oprah Winfrey, who is so furious that her big Oscar movie, Beloved, was beaten by,
as she calls it, something called Chucky. And she talks about it with such disgust.
She's like, this was an adaptation of Toni Morrison's Beloved Enough. Very, very funny
little clip. But the documentary is loaded with laughs. As always, behind the scenes on a low
budget horror feature is always going to have a lot of great stories. And they talk to Nicotero
and they talk to everybody under the sun. For a horror fan, you really couldn't do much better
than Doc of Chucky. Make a day out of it or fall asleep to it for seven nights in a week.
It's just great. Can't recommend it highly enough. Joe?
Um, more comedy. I watched, finally, Review with Andy Daly. I'd never seen it.
Oh, there's some great episodes of that. Yeah, a friend recommended it. If you
don't know the show, it's a fake, it's a fake news show where he plays a fictional reporter
who's going to review life. And he gets these mail -in videos from the public that say,
I never did X, Y, and Z. What do you think that's like? And then he has to go do it. And of course,
every suggestion is something horrific, like divorce. So he has to divorce his wife even
though he doesn't want to. Racism. He has to just become a racist even though he doesn't want to.
Um, it's very, very, very funny. But the thing that made me laugh the hardest
was a guy just goes, what do you think it's like to eat 10 pancakes? And he's like, that's it?
That's, I don't, that's dumb. That's not heavy enough. But well, I made a pact. I said I would
do it if they suggested it. So I'm going to go do it. And that sequence of him going to a diner,
ordering 10 pancakes, the setup of him being like, normally when one eats two pancakes,
he feels full. I will now eat 10. Uh, he gets through three. He goes, I've now eaten three
pancakes and already feels if I've made a horrible mistake. And then just him at the table going into
depression. It can't do it. The producer coming in and pep talking him and he's just going,
please go away. Please leave me alone. I was laughing so hard. It's so funny. He's a great,
great comedic actor. Yeah. There's not much I can say about it. That'll do it justice.
Just watch it. It's very funny. I think it's on
Paramount Comedy Central. So it's probably Paramount Plus. Yeah. So, but check that out. It's
one I finally saw, even though I think Joe, that you and I did it as a commentary,
but of course I didn't actually hear it. The Paul Lynn Halloween special. Oh yeah. Um,
this thing's just wild. I mean, we did a drunken commentary over it when Joe lived here in LA
years and years ago, but a friend of mine brought over the DVD. Do you have it on DVD Joe?
I can't believe it's available on DVD. I will purchase it.
It is. And the craziest thing about it is they don't really have a lot of extras and it's only
a 50 minute thing. So the extras are a little desperate. There was an extra that is a collection
of Paul Lynn quotes that is done like a PowerPoint where each quote flies in
like the world's cheapest PowerPoint. And these quotes, like it starts like, it'll go like Paul
Lind on dot dot dot cooking. And it's just some generic quote of his. Like I have a spatula that
I always use when I'm cooking in the kitchen. This thing goes on and it becomes funnier and
funnier almost as if it was a sketch, like prepared to be this way. But at some point,
quotes take such a turn where I guess he falls into depression later in life. And the quotes
with this like zany music playing each quote flies into screen and they start being like,
I guess the only thing that I think about every single day is probably my death.
And then it'll like fly out of school. I'm just making them up, but they get so
and depressing. Paul Lynn is a fascinating character. This special is fascinating.
They're not addressing the gayness he's making out with women,
but it's Florence Henderson. So there's also kind of a weird vibe to it.
Kiss performs six full musical numbers in the thing. Paul Lynn is singing and dancing throughout.
It is Halloweeny. Good to see Betty White. Good to see Margaret Hamilton who played the Wicked
Witch of the West. I can't say I laughed. It almost seems surreal. It's like this collective
hallucination of the seventies where, I don't know, did people know that he was a gay man?
Yeah, I've learned in later years like you think everybody didn't know about like
famous guys that were gay. And it's like now everybody knew you just didn't talk about it,
you know? Which is why he makes like on like Hollywood squares, they'll be like,
Paul, what's the worst kind of car accident? And he's like, well, I've never been one to be
being rear -ended. Okay. You know how to do like stuff like that.
Yeah, that's a double entente, I'll say. Yeah.
There was none of that in this, but maybe because it was like a family -friendly thing.
I just looked it up on Amazon. You can buy the DVD for $55.
Wow. Okay. I wouldn't do that for this extra. Well, if you don't like that, you can buy the
two -pack with this and the Chris Angel Mindfreak Halloween special for $399.
Oh my God.
I particularly enjoyed the bits where he is like playing a truck driver.
Yeah. And he doesn't realize that like you already look kind of like a truck driver,
you're an old man. Like you just need to put on the gear, but he's wearing like a big red wig.
Yeah.
To play a truck driver. Like he just, his portrayals of masculinity were making me laugh.
You got Tim Conway, who must've just been waiting in the wings at all these 70s specials.
Like he's in every single one of them. It's entertaining. Definitely from another time.
I definitely think too, in hindsight, like Paul Lind is being like, let's really
make me do the most butch stuff possible. It'll be funny. Like, you know, that's part of the joke,
I guess. Yeah, I guess you're right. Him playing like the Latin lover and all that. You're probably
right. My last one is a comedy series I had never seen by two men that I'm a big fan of,
but it just hit Netflix and I watched it start to finish. I couldn't stop Detroiters. My God,
this show is so funny. It's incredible. Oh, that's a funny show. Yeah. I've already started
re -watching it. I'm already like re -watching it again. I love it. Yeah. It's really, really,
really, really funny. It's about, if you haven't seen it, it's Sam Roberts and -
Robinson.
Robinson. No, Tim Robinson and Sam -
Sam, I want to say Worthington. What is his name?
Roberts. Robertson? Who are we, Joe? Who am I here? These guys have two of the most - Sam
Richardson, Tim Robinson. Yeah. They have two of the most generic names any human beings have ever
had. And they're interchangeable. Tim Robinson, Sam Richardson. And it sounds like you ask these
characters what their names are in a scene of this show, that these are the fake names they would come
up with. They play two guys running a small commercial production company where they make
commercials for local businesses. That's the premise. It is scripted. It is much more grounded
than like, I think you should leave, but it has a lot of that absurdity injected into it. It is
very much their style of humor. It's so funny. Just watch it, enjoy it. My favorite episode by far
is the George Wallace episode where he plays the soul singer.
Yeah. That scene, he plays a soul singer where his big hit was called Ocean of Tears. Yeah.
And they go to his house and they're starstruck to be in this guy's house. And that scene where
George Wallace is like, would you like to hear the story behind Ocean of Tears? And they're like,
oh, please, please, can we? And he goes, well, I went through a bad breakup and I thought to myself,
what if a man cried so much, he cried an ocean of tears. And they're like, uh -huh.
And he's like, that's the story. And they're like, no, no, no, that's not a story though.
And he goes, I don't think you guys get it. He cries so much, it creates an ocean of tears.
He takes a beat. This made me laugh so hard. And he just goes, start to think about the ocean.
There'd be whales in it. Shrimp.
Yeah. Yeah. It's a very funny show. My, the hardest I laughed ever in that show was when
he was trying to sing the jingle himself. Tim Robinson.
That destroyed me.
And he's going, sing. That made me die laughing.
That destroyed me. It absolutely destroyed me.
Over and over and over and over. They're very funny. And it's like,
you know, there, there's always going to be people who will like fold their arms and say,
that's dumb. If something can make me make a noise with my mouth and throat,
I give it the highest of praise. It is so rare these days.
I said to Pinkstone about the thing when he's trying to sing the jingle.
Yeah.
I go, of course there have been Tim Robinson sketches that overall made me laugh more
because it's a sketch. I go, but this moment in Detroiters is the hardest he ever made me laugh.
Like in, with one thing, like it, it made me laugh. He looks so insane.
There's also like a hundred little laughs around the fringes, like naked gun style as well.
It's a very funny program.
Yeah. How many central did really funny programs for a long time,
and then they just stopped completely and now there is nowhere for them to go.
Nope. With that said, speaking of people with their back against the wall,
we come to The Exorcism, a movie about an alcoholic actor who is estranged from his
father and trying to rebuild the relationship, getting cast in a remake of The Exorcist
in the father, not Marin, no Marin. Yeah. Marin, right? Yeah. Harris.
Harris, sorry. The father, Harris role. It's a different name in this. They clearly couldn't
say we're remaking The Exorcist outwardly, but they are. That's, they allude to it a million times.
And during the production, things start to go haywire and lo and behold, Russell Crowe himself
becomes possessed and a real exorcism has to take place. David Hyde Pierce plays the priest,
who is the consultant on the film. Sam Worthington, I never thought I'd see this day,
folks. I never thought I'd see Adam Greenberg plays the director. Sam Worthington plays the
co -star of the movie. I never thought I'd see the day where Sam Worthington had less lines than Adam
Greenberg in a movie. Worthington is barely in the film. Then you have Chloe Bailey, who portrayed
The Little Mermaid and is kind of a big star in like the eighth lead of the movie. She's in a,
you know, just what you would imagine that a movie about an exorcism would have a
interracial teen lesbian romance. Which is odd for one reason. Chloe Bailey's character is portrayed
as an adult in the film and she is actively pursuing a 16 -year -old girl. And it's very strange.
And it's never... Yeah, it is. It is. Yeah. I don't really get what that was. It was just confusing.
Well, it reminded me a bit of Beetlejuice Beetlejuice, where it's like, I think they
tell these directors, like, you have to add some diversity in two categories or something. And
like, oh, let me do this interracial lesbian thing. That sounds kind of hot. Like it is so
not part of this movie, just like it was not a part of... Was it Beetlejuice or what am I
thinking of, Joe? Whether you're thinking of Ghostbusters. Ghostbusters afterlife. I mean,
it's just so... It throws the entire balance of the movie off because it's not a B story
because it doesn't factor into the A story. It's just its own weird thing that's kind of hanging
off the side of the movie. And it's a strange... And just to clarify what you're saying,
it's out of place because it's a romance story that shouldn't be there. And then because of
diversity stuff, they make it like a lesbian romance or whatever. Right. Until you're just
wondering why you're watching this, not because why do I have to look at a lesbian? It's because
why is there a romance in this story at all? Exactly. Exactly. If Russell Crowe's daughter
in this movie was dating a guy, you'd be like, what is going on? Who cares? This has nothing
to do with anything. I guess it's supposed to be in this to show that the daughter takes
an investment in the production itself, but what they don't do, which is what they should have done
is... Well, what they do do is Russell Crowe gets her a job on the movie and you're like,
okay, now his daughter will be present. Okay, that's smart writing. And then you think what
you need to do for emotional weight is just show, which they do, how Russell Crowe is being mistreated
by the director and insulted left and right and whatever, and then allow the daughter just to
respond to that. Allow the daughter's emotional journey to be in response to this father who let
her down, who now she kind of wants to see redeemed, but also still kind of lets her down.
There's so much there that speaks to what this movie is about and they don't really pursue it
at all. They also abandon the movie in a movie thing by the time the third act comes along. It's
can't quite commit to anything. It just winds up not really feeling satisfying in any area.
I will say this, I am shocked at how committed Russell Crowe is to this role. He does not mail
it in. Still trying, yes. I thought he was going to be sleepwalking through this thing for a paycheck.
No, he's in it. He's into it. I found his character in this versus his character in
The Pope's Exorcist to be leagues more interesting. I did care about his relationship with his
daughter. I did feel sorry for this guy. I wanted to see him get it together. All of that I thought
was interesting. As the production starts and you see that he's having a hard time and then you start
to realize, oh my God, he's possessed or he's becoming possessed. That was interesting and then
there's a critical moment where he's fully possessed and he attacks the daughter and attacks
her girlfriend and everything and then he jumps out the window, a jump that would make any person
die and they never explain it, how he lived or anything. They just never explain any of that
and then all of a sudden he's on the set of the movie and David Hyde Pierce goes in to do an
actual exorcism with the girls and the way all this gets resolved is this terrible wink to camera
as a nod to The Exorcist where David Hyde Pierce sacrifices himself to free Russell Crowe the demon.
Now, here's why that works in The Exorcist. Because Father Harris is having a crisis of
faith through the movie and is plagued with guilt about abandoning his mother and losing his faith
and then when he sacrifices himself to save Reagan, it is the ultimate gesture of his
regaining of faith and self -sacrifice to redeem himself. In this movie, David Hyde Pierce plays
a wonderful, beautiful man who shouldn't have to die. What should happen is Russell Crowe
should have to sacrifice himself to save his own daughter but his daughter never gets possessed.
For some reason, it's just the priest and Russell Crowe and then the priest sacrifices himself
and by the way, they fix the exorcism by stabbing David Hyde Pierce with a cross through his chin
like he's a vampire and he burns up into flame and dies. The epilogue of this film
then shows Russell Crowe and a confessional talking to a priest about how he is slowly
rebuilding his relationship with his daughter but not attending to the fact that he's murdered
multiple people as a possessed man and none of it's addressed. There's a scene in this thing
where he bends over fully backwards and clearly something is very wrong on the set and the reaction
to that is Adam Greenberg as the director, it cuts to a scene of Adam Greenberg or Goldberg,
sorry, it cuts to a scene with him talking to Sam Worthington going, this guy's a bum,
we got to get him out of the picture, you got to take over his role and I'm like,
did you not see what just happened? What is going on? It's crazy.
Yeah, there's kind of a lot of that and I thought the story was going to be,
which I think is a more interesting story than what we got, Russell Crowe's not good in the role,
they don't like him in the part, so when he starts getting infiltrated by the devil,
why not make him be a much better actor when the devil's in him? That's a good movie,
then I'm interested in that story. It just kind of never clicks into the right gear,
so it's never scary, it's not like it's a satire of, it's not like Scream or New Nightmare or
something, it's not that smart, it's not that witty, it's not that funny and there's certainly
not a lot of scares here. The only moment of the devil being the devil really is exactly the same
moment as Glenn Close in The Deliverance, Russell Crowe's like, can I taste your pussy, dear?
To his daughter and it's like, Jesus, but it's just like the devil says,
pussy to his daughter, that's about as rough as it gets, there's no real crazy devil action
and we're in this glut of possession movies, we've reviewed on this show alone in the last year,
at least 10 possession movies and none of them are standing out to me, they're just getting
repetitive and dull, particularly exorcism movies are at like, they're where zombies were when we
decided we needed fast zombies, something's got to give. I'm shocked they keep making these things,
but I will tell you this, for as lackluster as this movie was, its redeeming quality are the
performances, everybody really gets into their role and sticks to it and goes for it and the
performances are good. Again, Russell Crowe's performance was good enough that I held interest
up until it got stupid, but it got stupid towards the end anyway, so I was like, alright,
I guess I should just sit through the exorcism part now, but I'll say this, and it really hit
me like a ton of bricks last night, I'm sitting there going, they've made a million of these
possession movies and exorcism movies over the last couple years, and it is testament to the
hacks that Blumhouse are that exorcist believer is the worst of them. It is incredible when you
step back and think about that, that it is worse than these two Russell Crowe exorcism movies.
Yeah, it just makes more, they make more sense, you know, like at least they told a somewhat
gettable story, but I don't know what Crowe's doing, you know, we got Gladiator 2 about to hit
theaters and Russell Crowe's doing like direct to DVD, you know, exorcism movies, it's kind of a
between the cheapos and the big budgeters, but he's still got it, he's still doing it,
it's not a Bruce Willis thing where he's, you know, vacant either for health reasons or for
just being checked out reasons, he's still there, he still gives you a performance every time,
and I don't know, I guess he's just not super bankable at the box office, but maybe people
will watch him in this stuff, and so be it, he's kind of gone the way of like
the great British actors of yore, like you know how like when Albert Finney or some of these guys
would start appearing in horror, like he's just kind of going that way, and maybe that's fine.
I think my take is he's made his money, he clearly likes his food, clearly likes his booze,
I think he's just a guy going, I made my money, get me easy gigs, I'll give it my all, but I don't
want to go to Australia for nine months, you know, or you know, go down to the jungles of
wherever and live in squalor because the piece is so important and needs to be told, I think he's
like, I want to go across the street, I want to do the thing, I want to go home, and which, hey,
I don't blame him for that, you know, whatever, great, you know, have a good time.
Yeah, the movie is, I would say, a little less than solid, it's solidly made, but it's not like
it's any particularly great movie. As is my hog. Yes. Less than solid. Mine is down,
less than solid, the exorcism is on shutter, the substance is on movie and Amazon Prime,
we are hoping to do Smile 2 and Heretic later in the month,
we are at See You in Hellpot at Instagram, I am at the Patrick Walsh at Instagram, Joseph.
JotaRosaComedy Instagram, JotaRosaComedian TikTok. Folks, we'll be back with more Thanksgiving
month treats, we'll see you next time, and we'll see you in hell. Thanks, everybody.