I'll see you Wes Hale, I'll see you Wes Hale, say when the sound of your screams becomes a thing on my dreams
The atmosphere will change again, I will see you Wes Hale, say when the sound's out
Hey, hey!
What's going on? Hey, welcome to, we'll see you in hell! The podcast with the movie
talk and the movie walk! Joe, you have to try, these people have paid. You have to at
least look at them. And how do we get the worst chairs in the room? These are the chairs
from my RV, the one. Is there an igloo cooler I could put my feet up on perhaps to really
complete the picture? Hello everybody, how are you folks? I'm Joe DeRosa and I'm Patrick
Walsh. Welcome to the coffee shop, we managed to get where at the black cat here in New
York City, we managed to get 50 chairs in and I think they're almost all full. I know I
hope everybody can you see, can everybody see, ideally almost? Yes. Is anyone uncomfortable?
You aren't, you get the best seat in the goddamn house, animals. This is why I don't
like to be close to them Joe. I like to do it over Zoom. I don't like to be close to you,
either frankly. I don't care for it, I don't care for it. Would you like a beer before we
get started? I do, I have one here. Why would you get that already? I grabbed it and I will
put it on my tab. That's why you were late for the entrance, grabbing your fucking medicine
egg. Please buy beers from these nice people who have given us this beautiful venue, the
black cat lowery side. Yes. Spend some money in here. Please, the black cat here in New
York, one of the best coffee shops around. And they're wonderful neighbors, they're right
next door to my bar and they're just wonderful people, Justin and the whole crew over here
are great. And that said, I would like a modelo, please, if somebody could pass it to me,
I will pay for it. I promise. Shouldn't modelo be a twist off? Who are you kidding? I just
about broke my hand on this modella. Who are you kidding? You're the same price as a bud light,
you shouldn't be a pop off. No, no, it's modelo's, no, you shouldn't be a pop off. You shouldn't
be charging me Greygoose prices. I took it even further there. Pop off to a cheap brand
modelo adds a foil to the top that I think is very nice. Golded foil. Thank you so much. Oh, look
that that's open already. That's probably safe to drink. Folks, I got to tell you, I get too nervous
to do this, I think. I've been over there doing breathing exercises and shit. Okay, so let me tell you
what happened. I woke up this morning, like like Kevin's mom and home alone. I woke up like
four a .m. like in a hot, sweaty panic. It wasn't all about this. Some of it was the shambles of my
life, but a lot of it was this. We're in the neighborhood. The shambles of my life. I do. It's all that
gets me out of bed in the morning. God damn it. We're in a go on. So my friends have a bar in the
neighborhood that we're using as our like sort of green room. It's an undisclosed location, right?
Oh, please. Yeah, because we want to have our privacy. Like we're the Beatles. Anyway, we're not in this
dive bar. We're in another street. Blackcrest is a great bar. Give them your business. I'm sure they
don't want the business. They are. I like them immediately. I don't like most. I don't need the
no, I'm kidding, but we're over at Blackcrest and they were nice. Reynolds who owns the place
dear friend of mine. And again, wonderful neighbors. And they were nice enough to open their bar
and hour early to let pet and I hang out over there before the show. And this kid is in the corner
like Mary Lou retten. Okay, doing all kinds of shit. I go, what are you doing? He goes, I just
got to be over here for a second. Don't make fun of me. And I go, I won't make fun of you. Why
I want to make fun of you. I get it. You got to like deal with your shit. And then I walk over
and he's going, and all I wanted to do was make fun of him. And then I felt bad. And I was, I
didn't do it except for now in front of me. Thanks for. Thanks for making it in front of 50 people. Yes.
But I, yeah, I have, I, you know, I have issues sound like they're getting worse as I get older.
And they're not supposed to. They're supposed to get better as you learn. But I'm not. And they're
just better as you get older. No, it really does. It's nothing. Yeah, you sound like that old
Cosby routine. Remember we go. Why don't the old breathing, the Lamas thing he should do? It's a
Lamas thing. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. But he goes, he goes, you know how a dog pants, the guy who
helps me with my breathing. And he's like a dog is panting to release like stress and stuff. So I,
I do that. And it helps. But I get scared. I don't know why. I don't know. I don't have to explain
myself to you. It's a nerve -wracking thing. We talked about it a little bit, a little bit. But
we've been drinking. We talked about it a little bit. You know, you were like, well, you do this
every day. Well, I do stand up every day. Stand up is very different. There's a different energy
that comes along with podcasting. Then comes along with stand up. Stand up the audience is a more
electric energy with podcasting. Right. It's electric. Two men and lawn chairs.
What would stand up? There's an agreement between the comic and the audience where it's like, okay,
we're going to laugh this much, this frequently. With podcasting, it's usually not live. So people
are listening in their own way. And then all of a sudden you make it live. And then all these things
you thought were funny when there was no live audience, actually, aren't. Yeah. And then the
audience is there and they're like, well, we're going to react how we react at home. Well, and hopefully
vice versa things you don't think are funny might get a laugh. That is true. That is true. That is true.
That is true. Of justice. Laugh, justice, folks. I like that when I look out, it's into avoid.
There's people on all sides. But when I look to the audience for my big splashy numb, look how my hand
is shaking by the way. Oh, okay. No, I'm just going to say I look at Mike and also be honest,
which is fine. You know, you're honest because there's nothing we can do to rep or mandio at this point.
Who is how many people at this show are coming to the next show? None? Oh no, no, you're not allowed.
That was the point. So we truly do have a new batch of people for the next show, which will be the good
show. We save the sauce for later. I'm kidding. We have a great show plan for you. We are
going to be reviewing. Jimmy Fallon is here. We're going to be playing Frisbee golf with the corpse of
Betty White. Remember when they said, no, when they were like, there were like those rumors that
were, they were like, uh, from the center of the gold mirrors, apparently, be Arthur called Betty
White a cunt once. Yeah. And it was like, well, and then all this stuff came out. They were like,
that didn't happen. Jesus Christ. These are, and then right before Betty White died, it was like,
no, no, it definitely happened. Yeah. And it was all confirmed that it actually happened.
I heard it happened. And honestly, this is going to sound like a joke, but it's not. I heard
that Betty White put, did an upper Decker in B Arthur's bathroom. She took a shit in the tank
of B Arthur's trailer toilet, which I would love to be true. And I think is true.
I would call you a cunt if you did that to me. But it would be like, yes, I'd be like,
you fuck again. Respect. Yeah, it'd be a funny cunt. Yeah. By the way, that's a non -binary cunt
that I'm saying. There's no gender attached to it. Ladies and gentlemen, I don't say that hateful
word, but you do what you want, Joe. That's the least of my hateful words. I got a bunch.
I got to be honest, a big source of my anxiety this morning. And I'm sure that goes for everyone
here in the room is the death of our queen. America's queen too, by the way. Rupal died.
We were just taught like how yesterday, I'm looking at Twitter. People I know and respect
all kept screaming about the queen. Go to bed. Unplug your computer device and go to bed.
You're yelling about the queen. And I'm Irish, so I'm told I have some racial reason to hate
the queen. So I actually have valid reason to hate it. Wasn't she, she was a colonizer, correct?
Trash. I don't need that in my life. And she threw the Irish out because she was
having up the original pilgrims this late. Well, she was 192. I'm going to say this about the queen and
it's thank you for shutting the door because this stays in here.
She coasted on her looks for too long. The woman coasted on her looks for too long. You know what's
interesting is every live show we've had, I say something mean about somebody's looks and everybody
gets quiet. And that's not mean. Well, I mean, the queen, she was a handsome woman.
But I remember, I don't know, I literally don't know what she looks like before the wrinkles.
My entire life, which is 45 years, she has been a wrinkly old woman. Well, in the name of
God, she was a wrinkly old man. And that was not her. No, I know. But it was 80. That's simile.
But you're like, in that, in that case, in the whole sketch, she looked, that was goddamn.
I'm like, you call, you call me an idiot. And I busted out fast simile to prove you're wrong.
In the same breath. Oh, really? How about me using the word facsimile, which I don't know if I'm
possible. Ah, facsimile this. All right, fair enough. You make a valid welcome to New York.
By the way, it is great to be back in New York the night before September 11th and flying out.
Who's flying out tomorrow? September 11th? Anybody have a moment of panic? Booking that on kayak .com?
Think about maybe a Monday departure, 912. Yeah. But you got a nice discount on those flights.
Well, isn't it? Oh, it's five. Is it the 20th anniversary, too? That'd be a good time to strike.
It is the 21st anniversary. Oh, okay, then you're fine. If nothing happened last year, then you're fine.
They told you they never forget. I did. I love how I got Rudy Giuliani like on today's show now.
Like, remember 9 -11, I saw him on a clip this morning where he goes, you know, in a lot of ways,
it was the worst day of my life. Uh, and in a lot of ways, it was the best.
That's his. That's his eyeball. He's like he's a Giuliani on a talk show. Yeah. Talking about how well
he handled 9 -11, that is like Danny Bonda Ducci showing up and doing a partridge family song. Like,
remember? Yeah. We remember. It's not enough. Yeah. We remember, but you didn't put your teeth in
this morning, Rudy. Little more pressing. Him with him. I'll never forget him with the hair
sliding down his face. It doesn't get any better than that. Oh, it's best. By the way, before I forget,
before I forget, shout outs. Shout outs. Can't handly over here. Uh, for helping us with so much stuff.
Shout outs to Mike Harrington. Hey! Doing all the sound. And shout outs to Emily Florent, Simpson.
We miss her. She's sick. She's not here. Got the COVID. Everybody say hi, Emily. One, two, three.
Thank you. It's very nice. I think about the people. Yes. Um, I got a scary stuff here. I'd love to
do. Go for it. Uh, so I was on, uh, is anybody just curious? And be honest, is anybody in this room
is your favorite movie, Apocalypse Now? Really? Okay. It's your favorite movie? Okay. It's a great movie.
So I hadn't owned it. Uh, I, years ago, I had a VHS copy of it. But, uh, I had, in recent years,
I didn't own a copy. So I went on, um, Amazon to try to find a copy of it to put into the collection,
support kind of an obscure indie. Yeah. Well, I was, I was hesitant because it's not a movie you
just pop on. It's, you know, you got to be ready to, yeah, you got to be ready to take it in.
Certainly not a date movie. You know, let's put on Apocalypse Now. Anyway, so I order the 4K
off of Amazon. Um, and this is what arrives. This is what arrives. I'm expecting one disc to show up.
Instead, uh, this is what I get. It's a six disc. It's been talking about this all day. Only person
mad that he got too much stuff. It's a six disc. Yeah. Set for Apocalypse Now. It's got Apocalypse Now,
the final cut in 4K. Apocalypse Now, redo in 4K. Apocalypse Now, the original in 4K. Also,
all three of those on Blu -ray. Also, the hearts of darkness, great documentary, uh, in 4K and on Blu -ray.
And then an additional, I don't know, four discs of special features. Four, are you ready for this?
1399. Which is one of the greatest deals ever. I agree. I was so amazed at how good this deal is.
But I asked the question for a reason. Whose favorite movie is Apocalypse Now? Sir, you raised your hand.
I am giving you this because I don't know. I don't know what kind of fucking psychopath I think I am.
That I would ever watch this much of this goddamn movie. This is sick.
So enjoy it. Get it out of my sight. There you go. It's great deal. You already own it?
Yeah, that one? All right. There you go. Maybe, uh, yes. Wouldn't it be more effective if you had asked
everyone their favorite movie? And then he had set Apocalypse Now? But I've been more effective if you
went and go fuck your self outside. How about that? That'd be a very effective. Yeah, I'll sign it.
But you got to take the wrapper off for them. Yeah, just pull the cellophane off. Be careful, a child put
hard work into that. Respect the art. And then someone urinating into a Gatorade bottle, uh,
sent it to Joe from Amazon.
Cuts it on the online. I'm trying to sell this at a Comic Con or something.
Who signed it? Copola? No, Joe. Erosen. Oh, who? What? You can keep it.
Folks on my, uh, $22 1 .2 mile Uber ride over here today.
I thought of a great one that I have never done. And I hope this pleases the fans. Oh, yeah,
let's do it. Hell Joe. Is it me you're looking for? I can see it in your eyes. That's all I know
about the song. I can see it in your smile. Lionel Richie. Lionel Richie. Father of Nicole Richie.
Father of Nicole Richie. RIP. She died? Oh, she's alive. I don't know anything about it. Wait, did Lionel
Richie died? Lionel's alive. Okay. So it would stand to reason that Nicole was alive.
I think maybe you're doing like a career is dead bit or something like that. Folks,
how are we dealing with the Don't worry baby. Press tornado. Are we stressed about it? Is Chris
pronounced Pug or Pogue as Joe says Florence Pogue even though there's no Oh, I don't know where he got
that from. I got to tell you when the wild thing and old shoulders get together. To me. Florence
Pug is, you call her shoulder? Oh, I see her this shoulder. Is she broad shoulder? Is she broad
shoulder? She's broad city shoulder, my friend. She can't wide shoulders, that girl. God bless her.
Nothing against her. You've been critiqued for your shoulders. I have. I have no shoulders.
You're saying maybe she shave off a little bit of it to you. I think me and Pug do a body swap
comedy together about shoulders. She learns what it's like to not have shoulders. I learn what it's
like to have shoulders. Too much shoulder. Yeah. Well, it sounds terrible. Miss Flow as Olivia Wilde
thinks calls her in the video that she is now saying was taken out of context where she
constantly on video says in private to shine above. Well, I guess we'll have to see what Miss Flow
thinks, but I hope you can come back to the movie. She's now saying that was taken out of context.
Well, you know in that moment that you talk shit about everybody to everybody else. Yeah.
I'm not saying I like anyone in this God for second time. That God for second time.
Sudakes is trash too, by the way. He is. I got no I got no allegiance to today. No, no. And
you'll know why he's trash in about a year when the show ends and the truth about Jason Sudakes is
revealed when it doesn't pay to have him be Mr. Nice anymore. Folks, serve the divorce paper or
custody papers to or at Comic Con. I like the man style. Regardless of what's coming out, I like the
man style. That's fucking amazing. This is your stage going. I think this about Ant -Man. There they go.
You're giving up your kids lady. That's fucking incredible. Anyway, sorry. That's fun. This morning,
I woke up hot jittery panic, home alone mom, Catherine O 'Hara, bowl cut, Kevin. And then I went and
got a bacon egg and cheese. I came back. I tried to go to sleep again. Could not go to sleep.
Jittery weird. And I decided to read. I got so bored of looking at Twitter. A profile of Olivia Wilde.
A lengthy vanity fair profile of Olivia Wilde in which I learned that her last name is actually
Cockburn. And she decided to go by Olivia Wilde as a tip of the hat. Her words tip of the hat
to to Oscar Wilde. Son of a bitch. The defense rests. It was that the thing that you told me over
there that you were going to drop out. That was that. And then there was she goes she goes we read this
original script for Don't Worry Baby. Darling. Darling. Sorry. Much better title. The original title was
Cool It Tuts. They changed it. Shut your trap witch. Nobody wanted to see it. But the hey,
Han, can you give me a minute in theaters this August. There there was a script called called Don't
Worry Darling. Set in the 50s with the exact same premise that Olivia Wilde adapted. She says she
said it became like this great piece of IP, meaning like they call IP and Hollywood like a book that
you adapt or whatever. And that's the only thing they'll make anymore. So she's like it was this great
piece of IP. Now they came up with the title of the premise and the story you threw them off the movie
that only happens when a star throws their weight around and like has somebody stamped out.
Right. She doesn't even mention their names and the article. She's like someone wrote this script.
And this happens more than you'd like. She sucks. I didn't care for her. So she's she's
fucking her understudy Harry style understudy or whatever it is in terms of employee. Yeah.
She's fucking her employee Harry style. She's under him now baby. Harry style. By the way,
though, Harry Styles. He's fucking her Harry style. He's playing a game in a new movie which I believe he
will probably get some pushback about because he's well now he says he's you know he says he's
whatever fits the interview. Oh, he's one of those guys. Okay. Okay. You know, I just feel like
we're all fluid mate. I sucked off a bloke on the way over mate. But then I'll also go down on
some pussy and I won't think twice. Me boss. How's your uncle? What is it Bob? Bob's your uncle.
Uh, Mark Ruffalo. I think it's Ruffalo. Ruffalo Ruffalo. Whatever the fuckers name is.
Ruffalo. That's what it is. That's as the entire room. It's what I'm what I'm feeling that it's
pew. Florence, pew. Why do you all know that? Pew. By the way, you were talking about Pearl Jam earlier.
Who in this room looks the most like Eddie Vetter? You'll spot him immediately. I thought it was because
you put him in my head. That guy with the hat on back work. You're on the wrong side of the room.
Oh, that guy. Look at that guy. He looks like Eddie Vetter. And look at him looking around like he
doesn't know. Yeah. How well he does. Right here. You sir. What the stash? Yes. You got a
Vetter vibe. Are you a surfer? Are you a surfer? Oh yeah. So there we go. All right. Okay. So
who came the farthest to be here? Oh, that's wow. Literally cross the country.
Los Angeles. Okay. Wow. Wow. I'm so sorry for the three of you.
I hope you have other. Are you seeing Lady Liberty? That's a lot of pressure. All right.
Sanchez and Comedy is it is what the at least, you know, go up in the torch or something.
The balls on this kid. You ready for this? I'm ready. Yes. This is what Ruffalo says.
But the thing that Marvel has done well is that inside the MCU, just as they do with the comic books,
they let a director or an actor sort of recreate each piece of their own style, their likeness. Marvel
generally lets them bring it bring that to the material. If you watch Star Wars, you're pretty much
going to get the same version of Star Wars each time. Then the sack on this fucking kid that he's
saying Marvel movies are more diverse than what Star Wars brings to the table. Now I'm not saying
Star Wars is incredibly diverse, but this fucking idiot. This dumb fucking this guy was supposed to be
when Mark, for those of you that don't know, when Ruffalo debuted,
when he debuted and you can count on me, he was supposed to be the next Brando. That's what they
were saying about him. And he truly was incredible in that film. I love that. He's amazing as an actor.
And this guy now walks around in green fucking makeup on a TV show where Megan the stallion
twerks with the lead character. And he has the sack to fucking say, well, we're original here at
Marvel. What the fuck up? Well, have we seen Luke Skywalker twerk with Megan the stallion?
Have we discussed this on the show yet? The twerks scene? No, I didn't see she Hulk. I was in it as I
discussed on the... You said you ever listened to one of my solo corners? Why would I?
Why would I? Wow. 24Ws at the end of the wow. Why would I? I get enough of you.
All right. Regularly. I get your criticisms via text 24 hours a day. That's true.
Girl, he's telling me I'm dumb. You're telling me what you think about my... Why would I ask for more of that?
Could not ask for more than the love you gave him. You think I want to listen to you talk for 90 minutes
about the entire Ron Howard catalog or whatever the hell it is you do on this Godforsaken solo thing
you put up once a month. That's not a bad idea. There's also a lot of ranting about the sad state of my life.
Don't forget that. Folks, Joe was texting me last night. You got to watch this Pinocchio movie.
Thank Christ I did not do it. But Joe's over there watching Pinocchio. I watched it. I watched it.
I got to say this movie recorded good. In fact, I'm excited to see both Pinocchio movies coming out this
year. That's my nose growing for the home listeners. My friend Brian made the funniest dumbest
joke about the movie. I said I'm going to watch Pinocchio tonight and he goes who's playing Pinocchio the
members of Congress? I thought that was very funny. Your friend Dennis Miller? It was it was a dumb
funny Pinocchio. No, that's a funny joke. So, take us to the movie corner baby. Let's get into it.
Let's do it. Let's go down to that movie corner. Yeah, what I say. Yeah. All right. Now,
you usually go, Joe, I could take us on over. Yeah, if I may. There's not a lot of corners. There's
poo corner. That's where Winnie the Poo lived, the worst character in the history of literature. It
truly is sad. Even as a child. Yeah. Like, who can we get who's more depressed than Winnie the Poo? We
get an overweight donkey who like seems to be living in mud and sticks. It's a shit cartoon. Even
as a child, I hated it. I didn't give a rat's ass about Winnie. Like, in real life, that
dog can really or would be like. Like, just it would be screaming. Piglet, I hate piglets trash.
Tipper. Isn't there a rabbit named rabbit? Am I wrong? Seems right. Great job. AA millen.
And then the kid that's hanging around with Chris Robin. Yeah. With these child -like animals.
Yeah. Problematic. It's a little weird. He was a kid too. They weren't fucking. He was old
enough to know better. Oh, the word to take his pants off. Let me Winnie that Poo.
Let me Winnie that Poo. What is her name? Florence. Patterson. Who's flour? Oh, that flour.
Jesus Christ. I forgot already. Yeah. All right. So we're in the movie corner. We're in the movie
corner. Pinocchio. I have an napkin, so I didn't have to get my phone out. That's hard. Yeah.
I mean, you were over there. You're right on a napkin like you're planning a heist or something.
I don't think hell is this kid doing it? Well, that's after. I'm not making enough money off this.
I'm holding up. What's this tie restaurant called? Detitful?
Tylicia. Tylicia. Detitful makes sense. No, it does it. It's at least works.
Tylicious. Detitful is not a tie sound like D to you. You addlicious to anything.
Bootylicious. How about give it a tie? Chocolicious. Listen, if you're going to go that
route, tylicious. Not a lot of support for give us a tie. But wait, let's talk about the
but I think I met Pat. Pat came to my standup shows last night and I know my way there. I know
what that was. Why are you being me? Don't be me. I thought it was a wake.
We were right. I was riding over and I met him at the club and I said I saw something just now
almost maybe pull over. He said, what? And I said, there's an off Broadway theater around the
corner. They did that magic show. I actually saw it. That really incredible magic show that was
on Netflix. That guy. Where the guy like guesses what everybody's life is at the end. And we just
trust that he didn't know any of them. I saw it live. I swear to God I was like, he has magic in him.
There's something. I don't understand how he did any of this. It was crazy. Derek Del Guardio.
Yes. I flew into Del Guardio. Anybody else?
So it's a cool little like off Broadway. I did it. It's a cool little off Broadway theater.
They do good shows there. But the show playing there now. I said, Pat, I almost had to pull over
and breathe for a minute. Ready for this? It's called hip -prab.
Hip -no -sis meets improv. Starring. A hypnotist who I guess is famous. That's one of the
only jobs where you could say, I'm a famous hypnotist. You'd have no way of proving it.
All right. It's like saying, I'm a famous fireman. Like, okay, I guess so. I'll take your word for it.
They're really famous. You can be like, you're not famous and then go, oh, aren't I?
Like that. And then Colin. I made the sound to cheapen it for the home viewer.
But I didn't need to make the sound. And then the guy from whose line is that anyway,
with the white here, Colin, mockery, mockery. He's making a mockery. A comedy is what he's doing.
They're in the show together off Broadway right now where they blend hip -no -sis and improv.
I don't understand. So they're all doing pretty well then. I did just see Ryan Styles
doing out like a full lengthy advertisement for knockoff Viagra on my Instagram.
Ryan Styles, who's dating Olivia Wilde. That's Harry Styles.
Oh, I thought Harry Styles wasn't on the Drew carriage.
Anyone seen this on Instagram? Maybe I'm, I don't know why I'm getting targeted at this,
but they're like, hey, divorce? Let's get him the Viagra. But he's like eating a sandwich and then
he looks up and he's like, I'm Ryan Styles. You ever not be able to get your penis hard?
Like, it's that blunt. And I'm like, why would he do this?
It's not the joke. It's not a joke. There's no joke in it. He's just advertising Viagra.
He's like, are you, are if you can get him, you ever wish it could be thicker and bloodier?
More engorged?
That's not what he says.
Wait, now you didn't talk to us about Pinocchio.
Oh, tell us about the show. Go ahead.
No, no, that's it.
How, hip -rof, but how was Pinocchio?
All right. Yeah, they were here, right?
We're in the movie.
Pinocchio, um, okay, so the funniest, so it's getting batched. The reviews are very bad.
The funniest review I read said, and I don't agree with it, but it's very funny line.
It said, this is only the second worst movie this year that features Tom Hanks as a puppeteer
with a ridiculous accent, which is very, very funny.
I titled my review, Pinocchio.
Pinocchio.
Oh, both quality.
I didn't understand what was happening as I was watching it.
It takes, I'm not exaggerating.
Is anyone animated except Tom?
I'm getting to it.
Oprah, uh, uh,
no, it's it's, or would you let her walk her mat and ask her questions?
It takes.
I'm not exaggerating.
The first full 30 minutes of the movie take place in Jepetto shop,
where Tom Hanks is running around with a wig on.
In one of those pajama gowns, where it looks like you have to have a lantern.
Yeah, right.
to have buttons on the back that you can undo and shit out?
Now, because it's the gown, it's the pull -up gown.
But it looks like he would have to walk up a spiraling staircase
to get to his back.
One of those things.
So it's, yes, it is absurd that this is being referred to
as a live -action film because everything in this movie,
except for Tom Hanks, is animated.
Every single thing down to the landscapes, down
to the fishbowl, down to the cuckoo crocks that he has in his shop
as a woodmaker, toymaker, whatever the fuck he is.
It is the most pointless thing I have ever seen ever in cinema.
And is in Pinocchio the exact same design as in the animated one?
And it is animated.
And is Figaro and all of them the same designs, too?
Yes, it was Figaro.
Yes.
And you might be surprised, Pat.
Yeah.
But unlike you see in most mainstream movies,
unlike you see in most mainstream movies,
Keegan Michael Key is in this.
Oh, good.
I was worried he might have a quiet evening at home.
He's in it.
He plays some damn wolf pedophile wolf or something.
I don't know.
I don't understand what's going on.
But he plays it.
So he's in it, too, then.
He's not animated.
Oh, he plays it.
Oh, he voices the wolf.
That's what I was saying.
So instead of just like if they're like,
silly said, we want to make a live action adaptation.
Instead of going, so we're going to get Keegan Michael Key.
And we're going to put him in these prosthetics
and make it look really interesting and cool
because we could do that.
No, it's a full CG wolf that he's just the voice of.
This is Bob Zamekis.
My Bob Zamekis.
Zamek's.
Bob Zamek.
He's giving up.
That witches thing.
Anyone to watch the witches?
Oh my god.
Ready for this?
Yeah.
Guess who voices the seagull?
Glory of the seagull.
Who's a main character?
Yeah, they say a wild guess.
Wanda Scythe.
Lorraine Brocco.
What?
Because in Italy of days past, they said,
let's drop in an Italian that clearly just walked off
the BQE.
Yeah.
So she swoops in.
Who is she playing the seal of the seagull?
So everybody's going, everybody's going,
I got my dick again.
Let me jump in the bot.
The Italians in this, it's over the top is Lido
and in the group.
Hank's doing it too?
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's that.
That's every person in the movie.
And then Brocco drops it.
And she's like, I'm sorry.
I just take Pinocchio.
Jav, do you want to get a strawberry?
What the fuck is going on in this thing?
It's a terrible, terrible, terrible movie.
It's just pointless.
I don't understand the point of it.
And then he doesn't turn into a real boy yet.
Well, no, this just came out, Joe.
Isn't that weird that he doesn't become real?
He decides he'd rather be would.
Oh, oh, and I forgot.
Joseph Gordon -Levin.
Yes.
As Jiminy Cricket.
Oh no.
By the way, by the way, how did this not get brought up
and scary stuff?
They are making a move.
It's been made.
Disney Plus is making an origin story for the star
from when you wish upon a star.
Oh, that's not a joke, either.
That's happening.
I will.
Starring Ariana DeBose.
Who?
I don't know.
But she's in it.
I'll kill you right now.
No, they're doing it.
It's called, when you wish upon a star,
it's called wish upon a star.
And it's an origin story for the star.
That's how it's promoted.
Go fuck yourself.
What are you talking about?
I didn't make it.
This is insane, and I will keep bringing it up.
And I am sorry, but I will keep bringing it up.
The spin -off of Ferris Bueller that is being made
by my dear friends, by my dear friends.
Well, your dear friends, God bless them.
They're making a spin -off of Ferris Bueller
about the two guys that steal the Ferrari for the day.
It's the only way to get anything made.
Called, what is it called?
Garcia and Henry's Day Off.
It's literally called something that absurd.
What is happening?
I don't know.
I really don't know.
Anyway, Pinocchio sucks, but you can see it right on Disney+.
You don't spend any money.
And it's a confusing way you got to spend money for dough.
Yeah, but it's pointless.
I just don't understand what they're doing.
I don't get why they think anybody
wants to see a fully CG, whatever I animated,
version of Pinocchio that has a live -action Tom Hanks in it.
That is no different than the original film.
I mean, you know, I got to be honest.
I usually like Tom Hanks.
By the end of this thing, I was praying
for the film at L .F .E .E. ending to kick in.
Couldn't you pick a movie where he died of something else?
It's only a movie I know where he dies.
That's true.
I was telling Joe earlier, do you see the video where Tom Hanks was yelling
at the paparazzi who like tripped his wife?
Where's that Hanks?
Where's his Taken?
His like elevated Taken.
It can't be too low -brow or else he'll be cumbly amnesia.
It was that great one.
We talked about that video's awesome because he goes,
back the fuck up, my wife.
And it's the same Hanks you get with.
There's no crying in baseball.
And you know, I miss that Hanks.
I miss like loud, unravelled Hanks.
God damn it, hooch.
What's your favorite?
What I used to do with Tom Hanks' impression in my act.
OK, I do it.
It was, I would set it up and I would say
this is Tom Hanks angrily disagreeing with somebody.
So I would get an audience member to do it with me.
Have I done this at the show?
No.
You go, I see you got WrestleMania six on your shirt,
but I prefer WrestleMania.
No, no, I'll give you a line.
Oh, you give me the line?
Yeah, that's how the bit would go, yes.
Trying to do it with a hip -rope over here, I mean.
So you go, you go, I go, this is Tom Hanks angrily agreeing
with somebody, this is what he always
just do with movies, doesn't know anymore.
So you go, what do you tell me?
She's a mermaid.
Right, so what do you tell me?
She's a mermaid?
I missed that Tom Hanks.
That was awesome Tom Hanks.
I agree.
Yeah.
His last real comedy attempt was Lady Killers, which,
wow, on a recent rewatch, all shut the fuck up at underrated.
I won't call great.
You're right.
It's got a lot to say, saves the movie.
JK Simmons, yes, who's whole bit as he shits a lot.
Yeah, simplest thing in the world, that's a very funny catch
race.
He's funny.
And I think Hanks's character is funny, even though I don't know what is happening in the
movie, right?
It's if Hanks would have just played that without the dumb accent that he has to do, I like
the Colonel Sanders, but I think he should have done that as Colonel Tom Parker, actually.
By the way, have you watched interviews with Colonel Tom Parker?
He sounds nothing like that's weird to do in the movie.
It's wild.
It is.
Yeah, it makes no sense.
Anyway, anyway.
I'm not sure, what do you got?
The new Lena Dunham picture, sharp stick.
I don't even know if this movie exists.
Okay.
Well, it was written and directed by Lena Dunham.
It is available to buy on Amazon or whatever, but it's her.
She has cast herself as a woman who is nine months pregnant, and she didn't do anything
to herself, which shows such a weird self esteem, I think.
You know what I mean?
I've never heard of an actress doing this ever.
Right.
She's playing a woman who's nine months pregnant with no acting on it.
Maybe that was the character that she goes, oh, I actually could play this.
I guess.
It was just like, you know, there was a mean in a mean way.
No, the movie was everything about it was super uncomfortable, and that is ultimately what
I really liked about it, actually, believe it or not.
But she was married to John Bernfall, one of the most attractive men on earth.
She loves doing that, and he immediately starts cheating on her with their much more attractive
younger nanny.
So she barely tries.
He starts fucking her well as wife's nine months pregnant.
She's autistic, even though that isn't said.
Dynamiz or the other one?
The girl who's fucking Bernfall, but she's clearly got something going on, and she's a virgin
at 26.
Now that that's a huge problem, if you're a virgin at 26, mazel's off, I was 23, but they,
they, it's weird.
The whole movie is super uncomfortable and weird.
Lena Dunham is barely in it.
It's this girl's erotic journey from Melanta, Minsk, and by the end of the movie she's like
tired of fucking John Bernthal and has moved on until like the end of the movie is her trying
everything.
So it's like she's got this checklist, and it's like, I did Bukkaki today, and like literally
that kind, like I had double penetration today.
And she's not, she's mentally something, so the whole movie you're like deeply unsettled
and uncomfortable, but that's what Lena Dunham does.
There aren't that many people doing it.
I thought girls was awesome for a while, and then it lost me, but I like this movie quite
a bit.
All right.
I don't know why it's called sharp stick.
I don't know either, but it was erotic.
Okay.
There you go.
That's how erotic it was erotic erotic erotic, I watched I own this Blu -ray in my collection
and it's actually worth some money now, I've got ladies out of here, out of print.
Out of print apparently, but I read I had watched it a little very long time.
I rewatched because the new Lord of the Rings show is out, which I haven't seen yet, but
I rewatched the Ralph Baskey Lord of the Rings animated film, My God, what a fucking work of
art this thing is, it is so good, it is so good, and it is such a shame they never got to
make the sequel to finish.
And he understood, he understood, the Peter Jackson, I know, Ralph Baskey got it, he's
like, guys, we're getting in out in 90 minutes, and then we'll do a second one for 90 minutes.
You don't have to see every fucking bit of information, he gets right to the meat of it, but the
thing called Cinnusco where they put like the drawing on top of, is that what I think I was
caught on top of it, rotoscope, sorry, they shot the entire, thank you apocalypse now, yeah.
I watched, I watched the making of and they shot the entire movie, they shot the movie,
they shot the entire goddamn movie just with real people, and then they did the animation on top of
it, but it's just one of those fantastic, like when you watch the docu making up thing, they're
just like, and then this will speak to the next thing I'm going to review, but they're just like,
we didn't know what the fuck we were doing, it was a disaster, Baskey, I love that old Hollywood
shit where it's like, they'll be interviewing Baskey in this documentary, and he's like, he's like,
yeah, I went into the office and I told him I had six backers for the film, I didn't have any
backers, but anyway, they bought it, and you're like, they just got it done man, like they just took
these crazy chances, but the movie is just so amazing and so beautiful to look at, especially on Blu -ray,
and it's awesome, I like the Peter Jackson Lord of the Rings, but I was a little disappointed because
they didn't capture, I had seen this when I was a kid first, this feels like the more mystical
sort of fairy tale version of it, and it's so, so worth a watch, it's so worth a watch, and I also
rewatched the animated Hobbit and the animated Return of the King cartoons, starring Orson Bean
and brother Theodore as Gollum, and those are fucking great too, they're just a, it's a really,
really fun trilogy of animated stuff to watch, but the highlight is the the Basky Return
Lord of the Rings, it's just incredible, never seen it, never seen it, and you did see Cool World,
not good, no, but as a, as a reefer head as you are, you would love this Lord of the Rings,
all right, get nice and fucking tuted up, and to have a day dude, you're gonna love this, my jazz
cigarettes, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, roll some great devils lettuce, yeah, I'm telling you
would love it, I'll watch it, I don't think I'll love it, I've never liked anything to do with
Lord of the Rings or the Hobbit, but only, but as I'm saying, all you know is the Peter Jack, actually
I like Smog, Smog, Smog was cool, yeah, yeah, he's cool, desolation of Smog, yeah, that's a cool title,
yeah, I remember when it came out that you said the only reason, yeah, that's why you wanted to see it,
it's like, yeah, I think because I thought it was desecration, I thought it was defecation,
what's, what's desolation is your alone, right, no idea, desecration is something to do with like sex and
nuns, yeah, or you just, you're fucking, you're fucking up somebody's body when they're dead,
no, that's not what I'm gonna feel you, does anyone know what it is,
a state of complete emptiness or destruction, oh, I have that,
I'm desecrated, you're smog, I'm gonna call you smog for the rest of the night,
thank you, aren't there like three, four tool songs called desecration,
there's, tool has some of four subjects they cycle through, desecration,
sex with eating shit in a prison, yeah, fucking a person that you don't know what the person
is, it's a disturbing, and then weirdly falling in love for the first time,
which are some of my favorite of their songs, I saw tool live, I saw tool live right before
the pandemic hit, and I'm not a big tool fan, but my buddies all wanted to go and say,
all right, I'll go, we had really good seats, and it was a great show, they were solid band,
I put them in the band, I put them in the category of bands for guys that think they get it,
rage against the machine, sublime, is there bands of guys that think they get it,
yeah, not to say they're not fun bands listening, even though they're good, I would include radio
head, yeah, I agree, anyone who's coked up at a bar talking about what really is,
they've got kiddie at home, but tools funny, yeah, tools funny, it's because because
Maynard, the main guy, he's the one guy that starts out there being a rock star all the time,
he makes wine, and he does all this stuff, the other three guys, what's more rocking than wine,
but the other, the other three guys are just in tool, that's their gig, so you go to the show,
and it's Maynard in like, plaid pants, purple, mohawk, wild, and then three guys that look like your uncle,
they're just like lit, like they're like, let's go out again, I got a, I got a kid during college,
that's why I went to that summer fest at, which at the Greek, which was gin blossoms,
and sugar ray, and ever clear, and RC playground, yeah, here, god, how many suicides backstage at that
fucking festival, and on the shit, each of the bands would be the lead singer, whether it'd be ever
clear sugar ray, whatever, with like frosted tips, like it was 99, and a wife beat her out doing it,
and then three guys who were like, thank god this happened, yeah, and thank god state farm gave me
the week off, to come to summer fest, I met sugar ray, mark, what's his name, his brother now,
mark my graph, I met mark my graph, I did a radio show at LA, he was coming off as I was going on,
he was the first guest, I was the second guest, he was the nicest man ever,
and I felt so bad that I made in front of him, so I was just, but I will do it again right now,
his face, I was like, is this the killer clowns around our space, Halloween nights,
and really, oh yeah, that's some work, and yeah, you're going to lose these people,
they don't like this talk, some work done, some work done, put down the yellow construction tape
around this man's face, some work done, there was a teamster eating a sandwich on a bucket,
next to his ear, there you go, that's what I'm saying, you got it, you got where I was going,
good stuff, you saved it, they were offended for us, thank you, thank you, I saw hard core,
because Paul Schrader was ailing, and I thought that he was going to die, and I love Paul Schrader,
what's hard core, hard core is George C Scott, I always want to see this, so much like Tim Robinson,
it blows my mind, from I think you should leave, they're identical twins,
and he should have played his dad or grandpa or something, he was in Angus, he would have done it,
George C Scott was in Angus, ladies and gentlemen, as was Kathy Bates, great movie action, but,
can I just give you, I was rewatching, I think you should leave, when he goes, it just destroyed me,
it was the line I never caught, when he goes, I used to eat the chicken spaghetti at checker renos,
thank you, I love that, I'm sorry, I love that, I love that, and then when he used to be a piece of shit,
the baby, he's like, I think the baby knows, I used to be a piece of shit, the baby things people can't
change, I've changed, I used to be a piece of shit, I used to be a piece of shit, chicken spaghetti at checker renos,
okay, very funny, all right, sorry, I'm sorry, I got it,
has anyone seen hard core, the film, so crazy man, it's about a man who learns that his daughter,
who appears to be 16 has gotten into the hard core world, and Peter Boyle, the sleazy
detective, is like, hey, his daughter goes missing and he's like, I found this thawary years,
and George who's got his like, where is she, typically subtle performance,
and then Peter Boyle's like, how show you, he doesn't just tell him, he brings him to a peep show,
the whole scene seemed insane to me on this viewing, and this is a comedy point out,
hardcore is supposed to be a comedy, no, it's not, it is, it is, if you read up on hardcore,
it is, it is referred to as a dark comedy, it's really worth it in a different movie,
no, this is a very serious movie, which there with Catholic overtones, the auditions,
the auditions sequence with George, he's got his plate for comic effect, a thousand auditions,
where he pretends to be the porn producer, and he's like, bringing people into the game,
wearing a disguise, yeah, so nobody would even know who he is, he's wearing like a bad to pay,
and he's bringing in actresses to audition for him, yeah, but I don't think anything is intended
as a comedy, Paul Schraders would never make a comedy, I don't know, the autofocus pretty
goddamn funny movie, that's true, anyway, sorry, I'm sorry, go ahead, in my crazy, this movie is not a
comedy, okay, but, did you say that it could be? Well, there are moments that make you laugh,
it's funny, he just said, yeah, no, there, there are laughs in it, so like George D Scott
goes in to watch this porno, and Peter was like, hey, I think your daughter's in here,
it's like, why would you present this information in this way to her father,
so he goes in and watches it, and he's sitting there and you hear like the flickering of the old
projector, whatever, and then see Scott, definitely the scene that made him do the movie,
he starts going, charred it off, turned it off, like Charlton Heston standing in the wings like,
whoa, George, you don't need to give that much, baby, let's, let's rain it in, and the scene, yes,
the scene where he's wearing a Donald Trump wig and interviewing porn actresses is hilarious,
there's laughs, but it's definitely not intended to be funny, all right, and it's real Catholic,
like a lot of polish raiders shit, it's a good movie, it's like eight millimeter, you're like,
hey cool, a movie about porno, and then you've never been softer, all right, I'll keep the third one
brief, it's what she said, all right, I said I would speak to, because she was sore from the first
two, you know, I lied, I was gonna actually talk about something else that related to what I was
saying, well, no, actually, I will, this makes sense, because it'll tie into jaws too,
the revenge or the review, no, that's part four, no, we're doing jaws today, we're at the
final one, I hinted at this in the last, my last movie corner, there's a docu series on Disney
Plus right now, it's called Light and Magic, it's about industrial, light magic, and I turned it on
because I'm a sucker for anything that's about like the making of Star Wars, blah, blah, blah,
I always find it a fascinating story, but this is obviously about much more than that, it's about how
George Lucas built this company called industrial light magic, because they didn't have a company
that could do what they needed to be done for the original Star Wars, but then the docu series takes
you far beyond that, it ends up with Jurassic Park and how they're the first house that is able to
provide CGI effects and all that stuff, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, it's just an awesome,
awesome docu series, because again, it speaks to this thing, this rogue thing that doesn't exist
anymore where guys and women, it's men and women, they just, they got it more guys, more men,
and women that acted like men quite frankly, no, well if there were women they knew their place,
and that's what I appreciate it about that one. They just got it done, they got the job done,
everybody's going, we didn't know what the fuck we were doing, we were terrified, it was hard,
it was kind of like what they explored a little bit in the TV series, the offer, which was obviously
greatly exaggerated, but I like things where it's like, shut the fuck up, stop whining,
everything is on the line, we got it the fuck done, and it somehow worked out, it's just such a
cool, awesome rogue approach to filmmaking to art to whatever, and you don't see it anymore,
especially in the studio world, I mean you just forget it, it's done. So I found it to be a very
inspiring series, I thought it was great, and it's very funny, it's very entertaining, and then
also you learn a little, you know, a little bit here and there about why a certain shot works,
I was telling you earlier, like they say, they're talking about the initial shot and star works,
that was the whole movie, how like that star destroyer flying through frame, they were like if people
don't buy this, nobody's going to buy the movie, and they talk about that, and they say the reason
that shot works is because every aspect of the star destroyer is in focus, and if any of it wasn't
in focus, it wouldn't have the impact visually that it has, it's just fascinating, and my favorite
thing was when they're asking George Lucas, like what was your initial idea for Star Wars, and he
goes well, the first, he goes the last real sci -fi movie that had come out was 2001, and it was beautiful,
but it was so slow, every shot was slow, and he goes I wanted to do what they didn't 2001, except fast,
I wanted to see dog fights in space, but fast, and I wanted it to be like an old fantasy movie,
that's all I had, it's just cool, it's fucking awesome, and then it turns into this legacy, or whatever,
I just found it so fascinating, I can't believe they never did the Star Wars, because we're going to
talk about George, I saw George two days ago in real D in the theater, can you believe they never
put out Star Wars, and have they, have they done Star Wars in 3D, I guess they did the crowd would know,
they're going to do them all, but the only thing in the first one is nobody showed up, really,
was it pre -3D being a big or something, meaning Phantom Menace, meaning Phantom Menace,
yeah you can't start with Phantom Menace, my dad was just out in LA and they had the trailer for
the re -release of Avatar, like they're like it's back on the big screen, for the first time, like
a three -minute trailer, and then my Dalien's over and goes, what the fuck is this,
this completely unfamiliar with Avatar, it's interesting to go, I don't know the time to go into the
dad's, you got that to look forward to, I got a hour of dad tales, speaking of Star Wars,
I remember taking my dad to see the prequels, just before prequels were a thing, like the Star Wars
prequels were the first prequels, like in a mainstream scope at least, trying to explain that
to my dad was, you know, we're halfway through the movie, so that's Luke Skywalker's son,
like no, that's his dad, Darth Vader's boy, why did he have a mask on, because he's a boy,
dad, yeah, boy's gonna wear masks, dad, why do you have a mega -
I have a lady's princess layer, right, no dad forget it, boy I'd like to take a crack at her, dad,
you're screaming, yeah, yeah, I see him going over to Olive Garden after this, get some of those,
that Ginzo food, all right,
Joe's dad is Ginzo, it's fine, I saw blue collar also by Paul Schrader, I would say the man's masterpiece,
he wrote taxidriver, but he didn't direct it, the best movie he's directed might be blue collar,
and super diverse at a time when didn't need to be, the stars Yafat Kato, who was amazing,
he's awesome, Richard Pryor, Dickie Pryor, fantastic, and the great Harvey Kai tell,
they have amazing chemistry together, they're three best friends who work at a plant, they're in
the union, Richard Pryor, the whole movie just wants to get his locker fixed, he has like a very
easy goal, and the union will not do it for him, the whole movie is about race, intention,
and capitalism seems like it was made like two days ago, incredible moving, incredible moving,
and I read Paul Schrader had a heart attack during the filming, as did Francis Ford Copeland
in Apocalypse Now, people used to care about their movies, as my point, they would have heart attacks,
they cared so much, but apparently the three leads hated each other, Kato, Pryor, and Kai tell,
and while Pryor was improving at some point, he kept improving and improving, and Kai tell through
something into the camera and broke it, and he goes, might as well, we're not going to be using any
of this, no need for the camera to be on, he's like, we got a great script here, what are you doing?
This is a terrible Harvey Kai tell impression, but Pryor and his bodyguard then tackled Kai tell
to the ground and beat the shit out of him, it's all on the Wikipedia, the IMDb page is like a
well documented movie with disaster, Paul Schrader was going to become a priest, he was like, I don't want
to work with these maniacs anymore, but the movie is awesome, it was well worth the struggle,
it's a great movie, and it's hard to find, I think it was not criterion for a bit, you can get
the blue right, but it's a really really really good movie. All right, let's get to the picture at hand,
let's do it, Jowls, 40th anniversary, I saw it in IMAX, Joe saw it in 3D, they were both available
for one week, but they might have extended it because my show was completely sold out.
I got to tell you something, I was excited to see it again, I was excited to watch it again,
and I had just ordered the 4K blue ray, which I didn't give away, because the makers of that blue ray,
were sane and didn't put six discs of Jaws into the package, they said one's enough, and then
here are a couple interviews with drivers, I think okay, great, we've got a sharkless cut of the film,
I mean it's just, no shark, rest easy, by the way, I was telling you about that criterion,
yeah, I mean the bonus features on these criterion are fucking embarrassing, it's embarrassing,
I love them, I just got fuck you, no you don't, no you don't, I just got something I'll never
exaggerate it, I'm not exaggerating, I text you about this, I'm not exaggerating,
the screen factory, a subsidiary of shout factory, you get a blue ray from them, they're like
we have the unearthed directors cut that we thought was lost in a fire, we have reconstructed it,
here you go, I got the Bruce Lee criterion, the special feature was here's some interviews with his
wife from YouTube, I'm like are you fucking kidding me, what is this, sometimes that come up a
little short, I'll branch, I'll branch, but usually they have good stuff, so I was excited to get
the 4k Jaws in the mail from ordering it, and then you said let's do it for the show and I said
oh that's perfect, you was a great idea, you had to end the summer and it was a great idea,
it was, it really was a great idea, I thought let me just see if it's playing in theaters because you
said it was, you saw the climax and it was playing in real D at the regal cinemas which I was disappointed
about, I said I would rather just see it regular, I took a friend of mine to see with me and she said
the same, she's like I'd rather just see it, and we were sitting there for all of 30 seconds,
I'm not exaggerating, before I was like oh my god, this is the most amazing real D experience I've
ever had, just the shots, you were on black tarher one, yes, yes, and she wasn't there, she was
someone I can't imagine, and you were alone at home Joe, not watching television,
yes, it was, it was, because Ken you saw, I saw you tweeted about it, it was
the immediate shot of, and we'll get into the movie and all that, but let me just says the immediate
shot of the camp party, and here's the thing, nowadays when a movie is made in real D, it's made with
real D in mind, that's on the table, so basically what the director and the writers do is they go we're
going to create this diorama on the screen, it looks like you can reach into it and grab it and
always not meet, look at it, when they take a director like Spielberg who is at the peak of his
fucking game with a movie like this, and they apply real D to it when it was never intended,
you start to see the brilliance of the shot in ways you never saw it, so I'm sitting there
watching the fucking camp fire sequence, and I'm like look at now everybody in the foreground
is shadowed, and then the fire is behind them, and then there's people behind them, and then
oh my god, look at the tent back there, you're seeing the depth and the framing of everything,
and then that leads into the initial hill sequence with the woman in the water,
and the water is spilling out and what looks like into your chest, and you're seeing
why the movement of how she's moving in the shot and in the frame makes sense and why it's
constructed that way, I was like this is, it blew my mind, it only got better from there, it just
kept getting better and better and better. Yeah I mean I think the reason that it's like
considered one of the best movies ever is because it just is, any format you look at and in,
it's kind of amazing, so I max really longer than the trailers, I listened to my deck and
playing about how close we were sitting until I explained for the 40th time, and there are 50
rows in front of us, please shut up, you monster, but once it started being close was like the water
scenes, it was like being in the water, and then these scenes like the town hall meeting where he
scrapes his quince scrapes his nails in the chopper, which I still can't, can we just talk about, can we
just talk, has there ever been a better introduction of a character, obviously the best,
what this shock, we should have started the show with that, really, there is a chalkboard behind me,
a cookie or a cracker, eating a cookie, for no reason, because what's the actor's name, I'm
like Robert Shaw, because clearly Robert Shaw was like he's going to be eating a cracker in the scene,
he's a cracker bully, it's got a shack shed but I just picture it that way, I see him as a cracker bully,
yeah, he's like that's what's happening, cracker boy Robert, we got it, you can eat the crack,
get it each up alive, and he's like taking the bites out of it, I mean what a fucking, oh my god,
well that, I mean, so that, an iMacs to go off Joe's point, you're looking like in the town hall scene,
Spielberg has like a hundred people in focus, which is impossible to do really, so you're looking at
like the, because we were sitting close, dad, but you look over here and you see like in the upper left
corner like these people doing something, and then you look like a mile over in iMacs, and there's
interesting stuff going on over here, then there was a scene where like Roy Shiders getting in his
truck early on, and it's framed so perfectly by this white picket fence of his house, that I was
like that's one of the coolest shots I've ever seen, and it was Roy Shiders getting in a truck, and
and in the 3d one, I think I believe I'm right here, the truck pulls up and there's a fence in the
foreground with a hole in it, and then the hole in the fence frames the truck, and you're like this
is goddamn brilliant, and it's the simplest shots, I mean there's a reason he became the biggest
filmmaker in the world, so, oh sorry, no go ahead, so let me speak to a point,
jaws, why is it a great story, well for many reasons, let me point out my favorite reason,
any story where a man's man is coming unglued throughout the film, I love it, Shider is falling apart
through the first half of this movie, because he can't deal with the grief and the guilt of the deaths,
and they're right, and when the woman comes up to him and she's like my son would be alive if not
for you, and the guy's like ah she didn't meet me, and he's like no she's right, and she is right,
that's what you're missing for movies now, is Shider has the whole conscience of a dead child,
and you don't hate him because of it, and now when you pitch anything like that they would go
we'll hate him, no he didn't drown a kid in the bed, when you see that kid go down you're like
holy shit, this is fucking serious, Spielberg's throwing like bloody uh overalls on the beach,
by the way, just dead kids left and right, that's the first time you see blood in the film is when
the kid dies, you don't see any blood when the woman dies initially, you see a little bit, a little
bit, a little, do you, you see some blood, okay, well, when that kid dies, you see God yeah, I don't have
shark, but you do see blood, but I was saying you're going I'm surprised I didn't show any blood when
the woman, did you feel like the shark maybe looked a little fake in 3D, because in iMacs there was
some moments where I was like okay, there are moments, you don't see blood the first one, you don't
yes, thank you Mike, I don't have backup either when we record at home, you don't, you don't see blood
till the kid dies, and it's so much blood and you're like and it makes it worse because you're like a
child, just die, watch them draw us over there, how do you know, you knew that quick,
IMDb has a violence and war gun,
Aris, fair enough, oh, I feel so good, I'm going to double check, because I can't go off that guy,
there we go, I can't go off that guy, but my point is is you see so much blood when that kid dies,
and it's so disturbing and you're like oh my god, they're going to see it, and then that scene,
because then drapes his character comes in and they're going to try to figure all this out, right?
you mean Richard Dreyfus, coming in like a freight train into this picture?
so I want to talk about that, I want to talk about that, but I want to just speak to the point
of Shider coming on glued, when drapes shows up at his house with the two bottles of wine,
love it, and Shider, how much did you want to give it to Shider's wife?
not at all, I don't find her attractive, I was really attracted to Shider's wife, I don't find her
never found her way, and it never affected me before, I've never, I get to be honest,
I was a little upset about the way it was feeling about Shider throughout the film, yeah, it gave me a
lot to deal with, well you think he's doing plugs a wig or just old man hair and in jaws, oh man he's
like 32 in that movie, he's got hair, something's in law that hey, you know, but here's the thing when
drapes his shows up, with those bottles of wine, and he, I'm a court beard ever, can I make the point?
yes, he's got two bottles of wine, he opens that red wine, and he pours it directly into his
glass of water with ice, and drapes makes that face like, Jesus Christ man, and he's just staring
forward, I'm like, this is what I'm talking about, here we go, and then when he goes, let's have one
more drink and then go cut that shark open, you're like, I can love it, I love it, it's really like,
it's kind of perfect, so the book, which I wrote when I was a kid is okay, but then they got
Carl Gottlieb who wrote like the jerk, like he wrote it with Steve Martin and Carl Ryan, but he's like
a comedy writer, he wrote, I think, oh god, you know, like he wrote all these, but he wrote one of the
greatest screenplays of all time with jaws, and it's very funny, but he also knows not to be hammering
on jokes, it's all character jokes, it's very funny, it's very, very funny, and the three of them play
off each other beautifully, yeah, now dryfish, you want to talk about a performance? Yeah, he's
incredible, dryfish doing that thing, the fact that he was bold enough to put on that wetsuit and be
seen on camera, yeah, that thing where he's looking at the body, when he's looking at the bodies and he's
going, the body of the girl does the thing and he's going, yeah, because you know it is so horrifying,
George C. Scott does that same thing in the actresses part three, and he does it a little bigger,
actually he does it smaller, George he, in exorcist three, George C. Scott does something very similar because
he's a homicide cop and he lifts up the sheet of his priest friend that's been killed and he just
goes like this, he looks at it and he goes, and like looks away and you're like, that's so good,
because you're like, that's what you, it's not, it doesn't end being disturbing, it's disturbing,
so dryfish pulling that sheet up and going, can I have a glass of water please,
and he's breathing so, it's, he's just so fucking good in it, man, he's also, shiders awesome,
shaw's awesome, shiders wife's hot. When they talk about the shape of the mouth of the shark at the
heart when, when he's there and he's like, it's the bite radius, yeah, he's all it's not this, it's
not this, and I'm like, we got it, we got it, and they're like, we've got this shark, and we've got this
going on, and then he's like, now, no, you don't understand where to drive us, just really bring it in,
I agree, I agree, I agree, they don't want, they don't want it to be true, but it's like, yeah,
it's probably not, it's probably not the shark that you want to speak to now, right? I was going to
say the whole movie, I thought about school shootings, which is not a, look, I'm not in a,
I'm not in a great place, but, I thought about COVID, honestly, I thought, I was like, oh, it's
like COVID, you can apply it to anything, there weren't school shootings happening when jaws came out,
but you can apply it to COVID, it's like, you know, Fauci had these moments where he's going up to
Trump, meaning the governor of the town, and being like, hey, I don't think we've, we've got this,
Fauci turned out to be awful. Yeah, you know, yeah, it wouldn't be nice if we had one decent person
to say it, and the whole thing, yeah, no, we've got nothing, Trump everybody, they're all fucking
awful, but, but not comparing Fauci to Trump, I didn't, we don't need to go, relax, I'm just saying
everybody sucks, we have no shyener is my point, where's our, there's no, we don't even have a
because of what it means for the economy, right, but it has, it's true, that's it, they know it's
true, and then it's like, hey, we seem to be having a problem where there's a school shooting every day,
but they're like, let's just keep sending them kids to school, that seems like a pretty good solution
for it, that's what I kept thinking of, it's just, I think because kids were dying in the movie,
but it's like, where you cut, smash cut, it's just pat alone in here, hours from now in the dark
going, I mean, but that's a thing, because the kids, you know, the kids die at a,
that's not far off from what I'll be doing back at my hotel tonight, but it's a brilliant movie,
it works amazingly well as a character study of these three dudes, it works as a thriller,
it works as a horror movie, it's scary, it's funny, it works as an allegory for what pretty much whatever
you want to throw at it, it's brilliantly directed, every shot is perfect, I don't know what more
I started crying, because I cry all the time now, we're both doing very well, you want to hear
you want to hear a real cry? I'll tell you a real cry, I was walking here today, I was imagining
what it would be like to do the show tonight, and I was imagining going, I'm Joe Deroza and people
in my head clap, and then this isn't about me, now I'm going to cry, this isn't about me, I've ever heard,
this isn't about me, and then, and then I imagine you going, and I'm Patrick Walsh, and everybody
going so excited and crazy for that, and I was laughing, I was walking and I started laughing,
and I started crying, and how happy that made me, about people like cheering for you,
but it didn't happen, not if it happened, thank god, I would have been a mess, but I cried, I teared
up a little bit in this movie, at the scene, what a beautiful, god damn it, you want to talk about
a scene that a movie builds, when they're on that fucking boat finally together, and Shaw has been
riding drivers the entire movie, a fucking college boy, and all that shit, and they start comparing
the scars, and you realize in that moment, you see that that flint understands, quint, sorry,
that quint understands that not every college kid is a pampered whoops, and that
drivers understands that not every one of these blue collar guys is a blowhard or whatever,
when Clint, he's been just as precious the whole time, when he tells that story about them in the
water, the best, yeah, and you see the bond, and they drive us in the frame, listening
intently, it's amazing, yeah, so it's the greatest story he's ever heard, and they bond, and they
start singing, and then it's broken by the fucking shark attacking the boat, but before they,
when they're comparing scars, what I really noticed this time is that they keep touching each other,
so like, drivers are, and then quint, like the big bully guy, has his leg draped over
drivers, and they're like holding hands essentially comparing scars, and their legs are on each other,
at a time where that would have been strange, well I thought that was awesome,
it is awesome, and they're comfortable with each other, it's the beauty of the bond, it's that moment
you have in a bar where you put, we've all had this moment, well maybe not, I've had it many times,
it's that moment you have in a bar where you put your armor on a guy, and you're drunk, and you go,
you know what, when I first met you, I didn't fucking like you at all, but you know what, I was wrong,
you're fucking awesome, yeah, I do that in the next morning, I'm like, I wish I didn't tell that guy,
I liked him, I still hate that, next morning you realized it was a coat wreck,
yeah, you're a good man, I'm pregnant for some reason, with the coat wreck, but that scene,
and that leads me to my only criticism of the entire movie, my only criticism,
my only criticism is an interesting thing what this movie is, it's a it's a it's a bridge movie,
it's a movie that sort of bridges two sort of generations of cinema, because there are several
moments in this film where they're playing very sort of optimistic sort of flighty, whatever,
where do you want to call it, music, and you go, oh, that's like old cinema, that's like we're on the
high seas, you know, like that's elements of old cinema that are in there, that in this day and age,
I don't think you would do, the music is much too, it's sugary, the movie never be made,
right, yeah, but my one criticism is, because hits of all time would never be made, when that shark hits
the boat, when it breaks up their bonding session, there are too many stop starts until we get to
the end, they, I didn't need to see them hook one barrel, whole sequence, hook another barrel,
whole sequence, hook a third, but I think they could have condensed that a little bit, that's my opinion,
that's my opinion. Look, I'm a big barrel hook and head, I love, I love watching a barrel get
up, I guess, because it didn't bother me at all, I felt like, I feel like that, it's not,
doesn't hurt the film, that's my only criticism is that, that it is so intense, when the shark hits
the boat in that bonding scene, and water is rushing in, and I'm like, I don't want it to stop,
I, or stall from here, I don't like that it stalls, and they kind of solve the water problem,
and then the water problem happens again, and they stall it again, and it happens again,
I was like, this is the moment, like in this moment where they finally realize they respect one another,
let's see them now all fucking go down together, you know what I mean, like, so that, that,
literally my only criticism, and it is brutal when Robert Shaw gets killed, I mean that is,
you feel like that's real, like it is, it's weird to give a shit about a death in a movie,
because it's been a very long time, but you do, when he breaks that CB radio, and he's like,
it's, it's man versus beast, how fucking dare you, try to take something away from our glory out
here, wow, for me, the only thing I found to repetitive is at the beginning, when they're about
to get on the boat, Roy Scheider goes, you're going to need a big boat, and then later he says,
you're going to need a bigger boat, I thought in the home stretch, when he comes in, I'm like, don't
do it again, and when he looked into camera and said, you're going to need the biggest boat,
I was like, Steve, you're better than this baby, you're going to need like the biggest boat,
and we didn't need him smoking the cigarette around his head, dice clay style, did not need that,
especially in a pre -dice clay world, we didn't even know who he was referring to,
but I mean, and that's the other thing before, before we wrap it up, that's the other thing too,
is like, just talk about, and I don't mean to, I swear, I swear, I don't mean to put a gender
thing on it, by saying, oh man, I wonder, I mean it was for edit, we'll just end with the jaw stuff,
all right, it's, it's, but it's everybody in the movie, I love, I love that the wife goes,
want to get drunk and fool around, I love that they're all fucking smoking, I love that they're all
smoking, I love that everybody's being candid, I love that like they're, they're calling each other
out on the bullshit, it's just a different era of human beings and society, five years later
of Cregty and Joe Beth and Poltergeist, yes, they're a real married couple, they, they,
kids go to bed, they smoke a joint, the dad's worried he's putting on a gut, she's like
cracking up at his body, whatever, like these things make you care about the people in the movie,
and they do not do them anymore, they don't give you five minutes to hang out with people,
so that you care when they're in jeopardy, they won't do it, that's the problem.
I agree, I agree, I agree, it is just a magnificent film, it's, it's, yeah,
jaws, my hog is, for jaws all the way up, I, I feel like I've been taking Ryan Stiles
as my agra, my hog is so hard, I love the film, I love jaws, smile you son of a bitch,
this is a, I was just talking to you, not quoting the moon, but I think you should check out this
little slaper, now have you seen two, I haven't seen any of the sequels to jaws, I saw three and four
in the theater, okay, as a kid, which one's Michael Cainan, four, this you get to prestige,
then you get to bloody shock, keeps calling the shark master Bruce, mocked through the entire film,
the, this the prestige, four is so bad, here's what the plot of four is, these shark has followed the
wife down to the tropics because it's personal, yeah, that's the third one, and you know how
much you'd like to see Roy Shiders' wife fight the shark, honestly, I'm gonna rent it tonight,
Lorraine Gray, I looked her up, I was like, what else she got going on, big fan,
uh, it's so much, wait wait wait, hold on, no, let me tell you the lineup of jaws,
that's what I say when I'm done with the date today, so thank you so much for the lineup of jaws
for, and if you didn't, you know, not my, yeah, I'm a sensitive lover, jaws one, Robert
Shaw, Michael Dreyfus, Richard Dreyfus, sorry, Michael Douglas, Michael Jackson, Douglas Adams,
yeah, now Richard Dreyfus, John Adams, Robert Shaw, uh, Roy Shider, jaws four, ready, yeah,
yeah, Lorraine Gray, I'm in, Michael Cade, yeah, and Mario Van Peebles, okay, all right,
look, I'm gonna watch them, I'll watch them all, they get worse as they go, jaws three, Dennis Quaid,
fuck Mary Kill, Drifus Shaw, Shider, well I'm gonna fuck the female, they're three men,
I'm a little tipsy at this point, we got another show to do, what, wait what's going on,
this is a show, I would marry Drifus, fuck Shider, and kill Shaw, no you fuck Shaw, that guy's gonna bang
your brains out, what do you know, all right, now I killed Drifus, you want to listen to that all day?
I think we'd get a lot, yeah, I think we'd get a lot, shut up, you little fucking worm,
get out of my face, you know who does a crazy, great, Drifus is Darryl Hammond, you ever see
that SNL thing, you mean the master of impressions, yeah, yeah, that's so weird, rich little, rich,
little, yeah, that's our show, thanks for coming out, thanks everybody, we'll see you now,
go hang out next door, we'll see you after the next show, go hang out and drink, thank you everybody,
oh, we'll see you next time, we'll see you in hell