Howdy folks, welcome to we'll see you in hell.
Joe DeRosa, Pat Walsh back at you with that movie talk. How you doing, Patty?
I'm doing well. Hello, everybody. I got all mixed up. I thought that we didn't get you your last two
in January, but we did. So, you know, the schedule is going to be changing. It's not I was going to
be first in the 15th, but you'll always get your four episodes a month plus my bonus.
Has anybody complained? I haven't seen any complaints. Nobody's complained. I'm just
always on the defensive. You know, speaking of which, yeah, what I'm always on the offensive.
What is what did you have on your face? What is that? I knew there was just a matter of time.
I look like American psycho if he didn't work out for 10 years. It's their their bag under eye
things. So like, I never thought I would be using them. But I have had bags under my eyes
since I got to Atlanta. I'm not sleeping well. And I'm sick of going into work and looking like a
damn bum. So I'm hoping they remove the bags from under my eyes. Oh, boy. Listen, those, you know,
these Joan Crawford, like, yeah, I things under myself. Yeah, I was gonna say, it's not a hot
look. I'll be taking sunset, Sunset Drive, or Sunset Boulevard Boulevard over here. What was
Gosling? And yeah, exactly. Cool movie, actually. Um, folks, it's a q &a episode today. So we're just
going to answer questions, both episodes this round are special episodes, meaning we're not
going to do segments, we're just going to focus on the theme. So this one's q &a. Next one is top
our top five favorite TV shows and movies of 2021. And we got a lot of questions to answer. So we
can get right to it. But before we do, I will say Pat is in Atlanta. Yes. And I am stuck in a hotel
in Rutherford, New Jersey, where I was snowed in last night. How much snow you get? Iced in it,
ice rained and then the temperature dropped. And I was like, it didn't seem like a good idea to drive
home. So I instead stayed in the hotel where the club is and drank a lot. What were you drinking?
Whiskey just by the it was absurd. People were sending drinks up while I was on stage. It was,
you know, some kids sent me two whiskies. Yeah, together. And I took a sip of one and I was like,
what is this scotch? And he's like, Yeah, I was like, he's like, I upgraded you from Jack. I'm
like, I didn't want the upgrade. I hate scotch. So I gave it away. He got real upset with me.
I understand you could have at least pretended I bought him a drink back. Okay. All right.
That kid did to get so drunk that he wouldn't leave me alone for the entire night. Oh, boy. And
kept coming up to me afterwards in the bar and putting his phone in my face and saying,
say, Krista Stefano is a pig into my phone, please. And I was like, I don't want to please leave me
alone. Yeah. Well, I hope he doesn't hear this and kill himself. But you stay in the hotel,
right? You literally hear it through the wall. What hotel you stand at? It looks sort of nice
for a for a road comic hotel. I mean, it's not. Yeah. So a place called the Renaissance Hotel.
It's not a bad little spot. You want a club called bananas. Okay. exclamation point.
No, no. Unlike a club called bonkers. I used to do that did have an exclamation point. Yeah.
Can it really be considered a real comedy club if it doesn't have an exclamation point?
Or is, is it if it's not spelled with a Z on the end? Yeah, exactly. I said this on stage last night,
and I was talking to Bobby Kelly, yesterday, who's a very funny comic and a good friend and
familiar, of course. Yeah, I said, Where are you at tomorrow? And he said, or he said, Where are
you at tonight? And I said, I'm at bananas. And I said, Where are you at tonight? And he said,
I'm at Uncle Vinny's. And I said, What are we doing? Yeah, yep. What are we doing? And then he
said, if you want to feel bad, tomorrow night, meaning tonight, Krista Stefano is headlining
the Beacon Theater in New York, while we're doing clubs. And I said, I'll make you feel worse.
I'm catering his after party.
Which is the truth. I can't fit into my tux. Yeah, which is the truth. I we he bought sandwiches
from us for I'm finished, Pat. It's over. Oh, I thought you were kidding. But no, no, no. You're
kidding. Okay, though. He bought sandwiches from us for his after party. Yeah. Well, that's nice of
him. It's very nice. He's one of my good friends. And I'm thrilled that he bought the sandwiches. But
it does mean you're officially out of show business. When you're providing hoagies for
party of the comedian who just headline theater. But you know, you're still you're still playing,
you're still out on the road. Yeah, it's, it's, I know, I'm kidding. It's we had a sold out show
last night. The crowd was great. Our friend David Krumholtz is coming tonight. Love it. Tell him
early show. I will tell him hello. So I make jokes. I like to self deprecate. Yeah, I mean,
I've been in Atlanta here about three weeks for and I just don't understand how you do it. It's
when I'm working, I worked a minimum 12 hour days, hence the bags under my eyes. But I'm great,
you know, it's it's what I needed. I keep my mind super occupied. I'm actually doing what I've never
done at work before where I'm like approaching people like what can I do for you? Usually I'm
hiding in a corner. Right. But I'm just, you know, I'm not having a great period of my life. I'm
trying to keep my mind focused. And it's helping tremendously. Right. But then when that Saturday,
Sunday hits that loneliness hits, it's like woof. And I'm also doing no carb because I can't keep
doing my Peloton every day. I was like, I'm just going to get fat out here. So fat her. So I
am doing no carb, which is great. I have no problem doing that. I always enjoy that diet pretty much.
But then when you drink, there's nothing to absorb it. And I woke up this morning just feeling like
my head's killing me. I'm pretty good at doing the no carb. I go off the rails with the booze
because I'll start. You start the night going, well, I'm on a no carb thing. I better drink,
you know, tequila. That's what I drank or whatever. And then by that, like six tequila or fifth tequila,
you're like, I got to have a beer, man. This is crazy right now. Like it's too much. The
it's bad. I actually, this is a gross little story. Then we got to get to these questions. But
I woke up this morning, walked over, you know, 20 degrees over to the Whole Foods
across the street. And I was like, I'm going to get some vegetables in my system and just kind of
shit this horrible feeling out of me. So I eat a big thing of kale to kick off my day, cup of coffee,
chug two giant things of water. And then I'm sitting there and I was like, am I going to throw
up right now? And then a quick explosion of kale came right back up into my mouth.
My cheeks puffed out and I caught it, walked over to the sink and spat it out. But I was like,
Jesus Christ, Pat, what are you doing? Permanent midnight over here. Yeah, not good. Not good.
I'm over here rubbing, rubbing eye things on my forehead. Now we're both lost and that's fine.
Joe hit me with that first question. And thank you. I mean, my God, you guys turned out. Thank
you to Emily for collecting them. It was great to see some of you on the Thursday night chat the
other night. All right. And thanks for sending in so many questions. Let's do it. I haven't even
looked at them yet. Sorry, I missed the Thursday night chat. I was so hungover on Thursday that I
didn't leave my bed for the entire day. Yeah, we're thriving, Joe. Well, a quick, quick anecdote. I
was with my buddy. We went to meet his fiance for dinner already in a state of things. Yeah, she was
too pleased that we showed up in that condition. And as we were trying to leave, she was he was
standing in front of her and she was clearly not thrilled after dinner with with us. And yeah, he
was saying, I'm fine. I'm fine. And she's going, sweetie, just go. You're drunk. It's okay. We'll
talk about it later. Just please just go with Joe and go have fun or whatever. Right as he was saying,
I'm fine. He went to sit down on a chair that wasn't there, fell over, hit a table, six glasses
broke. And it was one of the funny, I mean, it was, it was like, fucking Dudley Moore, Arthur style
shit. I was like, that that was in a movie, you'd be like, there's your scene. No, that that that to
me, that's the thing, I don't lose my balance, I don't scream in people's faces. So I never have
that bottoming out moment that I need. You know, I just kind of keep going. But if that happened to
me, if I missed a chair in front of my fiance and all that, I would probably quit drinking.
Bless his heart. He was like, that's not wasn't my fault. But there was a chair there. So owned it.
Owned it as six waiters are cleaning up glass shards around him. Anyway. Oh, boy. All right.
First question is for Rocky Harjo or Haro. Okay, Patrick, what is your favorite sound or noise?
My favorite sound or noise? You know, it's the answer they always gave on that James Lipton thing.
And I hate to say it, I like that baby laughing. I'm a sucker when I see an Instagram video of a
baby laughing really hard. There is no better sound. It's delightful to me. I know how their
dreams are going to be crushed from that moment on. But just it's just a pure unfiltered joy. And
you can make a baby laugh by doing literally anything. Yes. That's nice. Gosh tree asks,
what did you guys dream of doing when you were kids? What about in retirement?
My dream as a kid was to be honestly was to be a rapper. I thought that that's
and I rapped from a very young age through college. And I thought that's what I was going to do.
But did you have a name picked out for yourself? I had many names through the years.
Joey delicious. Joey delicious.
Delish. Sure. And then you're pissed when delight took your thunder. Yeah.
But I thought that's what I was going to do. Retirement I never, I still don't think about
because I'm convinced that I will drop dead while working. Since I have no real plan for
retirement. But that's where I'm at. Yeah. You know, it's a very positive thing. I need to put
on my stop this from popping mask. I wanted from a very young age to work in movies. I thought I
but then when I got to film school, I hated the technical aspect of it and apertures and all that
shit. So I, I just knew I at least knew in general, I'm not one of these people who like
keeps trying to figure their shit out. I always knew what I wanted to do. Didn't think it would be
easy. And it wasn't, but I never really changed the course. As for retirement, you know, I'd love
to be one of these guys who can still sell a movie at age 65, 70. I hope that happens, but who knows?
Yeah, my dream retirement, I guess is and I guess I do think about this, it's to be able to write
short horror fiction. Yeah. And somehow be able to monetize it. Well, be real, because you know,
it's easy to be hard on yourself. Lord, I know that. But at some point in your life, you must
have wanted to let you want must want to own a bar. Aren't you kind of living that dream?
Or did you never have that desire? No, no, I that's a dream of mine. Yeah, but not since
kid. That was okay. No, that was like, that'd be a little weird, I guess.
Mommy, I want to own a ball. Yeah, what do you want? You go out on Halloween with a towel over
your shoulder. What do you need, sweetheart? Yeah, a little one of those visors.
I'll get you another one. All right, you get the lemonade stand, but you're polishing the
red solo cups with the towel. What do you need, honey? You know,
Matthew Toddy asks, if you had to watch the same movie every day for a year, what would it be?
Pat can't answer zodiac.
Matthew Toddy, I hope that you go by hot toddy in your personal life. If I could watch one movie
for the rest of my life. Interesting. You know, I think I'd go with Goodfellas to be honest. It's
just it's I've never once been bored by a minute of it. And I feel like I could watch it three times
in a row and be happy to do so. So I'll say Goodfellas. That's a good question. I mean,
I always say my favorite movie of all time is Hannah and Her Sisters. And I could watch it
repeatedly, but I don't think that's the one I'd watch every day for the rest of my life.
I probably have to say Glengarry Glen Ross. OK, I've never quoted a movie more. Pete Holmes and
I have quoted that movie for years, like exhaustively. Like, I don't mean like we just
quoted here and there. I mean, like, we go through we have different themes of quoting it. We're
do like Glengarry Glen Corona. And it's like every you have to take the lines from the movie
and change them to be coronavirus references. And like we did Glengarry Glen Hoagie, where
it was like it all had to be deli references. Like, it's crazy. But we laugh endlessly when
I do it with him. So I guess it would be that movie, I guess. It means you'll never see a
woman again. Yeah, that's it. You know, I've never met a because there's no women in the movie and
no one would want to hang out with you. I try not to just do blanket statements. But the this girl
I worked with yesterday was like, we're taking out some pitch that's supposed to be like Glengarry
Glen Ross. So I keep pretending I've heard of it. But of course, I haven't. And I'm like,
I don't know that I've ever met a woman who loved Glengarry Glen Ross, or who even brought it up.
I tried to show Heather early on in our relationship, and she was asleep in 10
minutes. It's just like it doesn't work for women in some way. I don't know why.
It's real old school guy shit. You know, it's the plight of the you know, a man makes his bones,
you know, it's that whole thing. But anyway, it's the males steel magnolias. Sure, but I like steel
magnolias. You know, it just it's weird. It doesn't go the other way. They don't like that.
All right, Matt Elliott asks, What's a good Pat's dad story? We haven't heard yet,
because it always makes me laugh and feel normal about the relationship I have with my own dad.
I mean, shit, I feel like I've shared a lot of the bigs. I told the April Fool's Day story, right?
I don't honestly, I don't remember that's not ringing a bell, though.
That's one that's popping in just because I've been writing it. I've been kind of,
you know, not we're not writing my own story, but using some of my own stuff to write this kind of
more personal script I'm doing now. But yeah, I'll do that when I it was April, it was when
you're a kid, when you first hear about April Fool's Day, it's like so exciting. And you're like,
Oh, man. And weirdly, now I don't care at all. And if somebody were to prank me, I would punch them
in the face. But I unscrewed the lid of the salt shaker, the classic prank, and I sit down to dinner
and me and my sister are kind of giggling at each other. We're like, Oh, can't wait. And my dad
shakes the salt on his food, as he always did. Salt comes out. And he just closed his eyes so
tight, which always indicated the pain was coming. And he was like, who did this? Who did this?
And I was like, I did it's, you know, it's for April Fool's Day. Do you think it's funny?
You think it's funny that my meal is ruined now? And like, just the very quiet tension and then
eventually into him yelling, grabbing my arm. And then like a two hour lecture on the danger of
pranks. They can go wrong and hurt people and on and on and on about it because he had a little
extra salt on his plate. And my mom just sitting at the end of the table going like, Kevin, just
just scrape it off. Just scrape the salt and just him plowing ahead and going and going and going
Not a funny story. But there's one for you. All right. Yeah.
Not sure I understand this question. Jeremy Griffin asks, you often talk about comedies being
punk rock like Ace Ventura. Do we? All right. Well, what I learned from talking to the
fans the other night, the Hellions is that they remember shit away better than you and I do.
All right. It says, What does this mean? What makes comedy punk rock in your view? Well, I mean,
I you know, as a stand up, I would say what made comedy punk rock was, you know, was the
brash expression on apologetic expression of ideas and thoughts and whatever and sometimes
those things crossed lines. And, you know, sadly, it's it's kind of going away as it is in punk
rock. I mean, you know, I just watched a documentary called Can We Take a Joke? And,
you know, they talked in that thing about, you know, how we have like punk musicians apologizing
now. Yeah, for being too punk. You know, and it's happening in comedy too. And I'm kind of confused
by it. But but also, too, you don't know the person's shoes that, you know, until you're in
them yourself. So I can't speak for anybody and why they do what they do. But that's what I always
meant by it, that it was a rogue thing. And that when people were trying to, you know, shove it
into the mainstream, it was, you know, never made sense, you know, to me. Yeah. Yeah, I mean,
Ace Ventura really is the perfect example. I feel like I probably said that, but it's been a while.
I mean, Jim Carrey, you know, that Dumb and Dumber to a lesser extent, and then it's just such a
shame when you see what he's doing now, the exact opposite. But it's like, yeah, I had never seen
anything like it. It was somebody completely unhinged. And it was also trusting that people
would enjoy that, you know, like every day on set, if I was directing that, I'd be like, is this
gonna, I mean, this could be the worst movie of all time, or the best, you don't know. That's the
and him just doing something that had never been done, unless you look back to like Jerry Lewis,
who you also got to kind of consider punk rock, you know, just trying something that had truly
never been seen. Nicolas Cage used to do it too. And succeeding with it. I mean, when they stick
the landing, there's nothing more exciting, because especially now, movies are at a constant
flat line. They look the same, they sound the same, they feel the same. And yeah, we need something
like that. We need some big comedian to come out. And if somebody did it, he'd be a huge star,
you know, but or comedy or sort of not scream for him to be canceled. For sure. Yeah. Yeah. Okay.
What are Suzy? Mariano says or asks, what are your desert island discs? But in movie form top 10.
I actually have my top 10 movies in my phone. I wrote this down years ago. I think we should do
it. We should do an episode of that now. All right. Yeah. Well, we'll come back to that, Suzy. I agree
that that'd be a good special episode. So modify your questions. Well, actually, we're doing
more than what you asked, we're going to do a whole episode of our 10 favorite movies. That's
a perfect special edition for us. But I'll do a desert island discs, you know, a couple albums
that I would I would want. What's yours, Joe? You know, Mr. Bungle, California, Raising Hell, Run DMC,
Frank Sinatra and Joe Beam.
Fumanshu, definitely, probably the action is go. Motorhead,
Ace of Spades or Iron Fist.
You know, there's probably more, but I'm just kind of spoon. Give me fiction, for sure. Yeah, I would
go Elvis Costello this year's model. His new record is pretty good, by the way. His new one is very
good. Yeah, especially because his last one's kind of left me cold. I'd go Fleetwood Mac Tusk. Lately,
I've been listening to nothing but Metal Lands by the Wrens. And that's something you know, you very
rarely meet people who know the Wrens. But that is an amazing album start to finish. It's very
depressing, but it's very good. And who I'm seeing tonight, one of my all time favorite bands, Old
97 is too far to care. I realize over time is perhaps my favorite album. It's just incredible.
And those first two Strokes albums, you know, Weezer Blue and Pinkerton, you know, I got a lot.
Queens of the Stone Age, for sure. Rated R and then Songs for the Deaf. There's a lot.
Yeah. All right. All right. Let's see here.
Who would win in a fight? Judge Judy or Macy Gray? This is asked by Drew Tiberius -Pole.
Uh, I think Macy Gray on Sheer, uh, unhinged, unhinged.
Yeah. I mean, 20 years ago, Judy, maybe, but Macy Gray has got it for sure. Do you remember
that in that Spider -Man movie where there was just a full Macy Gray performance? Like, I mean,
if anything could ever date a movie, I mean, it's a full performance. And I think the song
is called My Nutmeg Fantasy. I will say her big hit, I Try to Walk Away and I Choke is
one of the great pop singles of our time. You know, I think it's an amazing song with an amazing,
powerful key change and her voice is awesome, but she didn't really hang onto her fame.
Yeah, it's a, it's a shame. I think she was, I don't know, was she into drug? I mean, it seems
like it, but I don't, you know, I don't know if that was ever done. Why did it seem like it,
she seems to be on drugs. I saw her live once and I was like, what the fuck is going on, man?
Like, anyway, Aaron Schwartz asked if you could grant a second season to any TV show that only
got one, excluding any you had a hand in, what would it be? Correct answer is Terriers. I know
right off the bat, High Fidelity. I was so sad it got canceled. Yeah, I really wanted to see where
it was going. I loved that show so much in terms of recent shows. Absolutely. And the shit they let
go on for years and years. High Fidelity was a really great example. For me, I got to go
off the top of my head with Freaks and Geeks or Undeclared. I thought, you know, those were
basically so far ahead of their time and so far ahead of, you know, they're what streaming and
cable is now, but they were just too weird for network. I never saw Terriers. I hear it's great.
Scott John asks, with the cult following that's been garnered, do either of you find this podcast
more fulfilling than other projects you've done? And are there any kinds of potential career
opportunities that would lead to this ending? Well, I mean, it will end, of course. I mean,
either with one or both of our deaths, perhaps a murder -suicide situation, or,
you know, just we'll get tired. I can't go on forever. But I find this way more fulfilling,
of course. I mean, we can do whatever we want and talk about whatever we want to, you know,
it's not like you have to answer to 800 people and compromise your vision and everything else. So it's
very fulfilling, of course, and that you guys love it so much as fulfilling. The only reason I don't
go out, you know, broadcasting and advertising it is because I worry about killing the career that
brings me in money. You know, I worry they'll go back and hear something, whether it be an actor I
insulted or whether it be us ranting about, you know, Louis CK, whatever it is, I just worry.
So that's the only thing that I don't like about doing this. I also love that I get to see my old
Joe for a few hours a month, which, you know, we're in different places. So it's nice.
I agree. I agree with everything you just said. I mean, look, the thing I enjoy most about doing
this is it's very nice to be able to see a friend and talk about a subject you love
and somehow help pay a couple of bills with it. You know, that's a true gift. I feel that
with both of my podcasts in the same way that I feel the blast, excuse me, in the same way
that I feel blessed with the with the bar that I got to open. And, you know, for some reason,
I appreciate stand up, but it's very different. It's a very different thing.
There's something about podcasting that makes it a little more private, a little more special,
probably because you get to do it as Pat said, with a friend. So yeah, I mean, you know, but
who knows, you know, as long as I'm in Rutherford, New Jersey, I'll do this podcast. Yeah.
Dave Dewitt asks favorite TV theme song. Easy Night Court. I've been watching Night Court.
Yeah, Seinfeld sort of sort of ran with that baton with the funky bass opening theme. But
the the Hellions chat the other night and my immediate answer was Perfect Strangers. But
it could change. It could change. I mean, there's very the latest. One of my favorite
opening credit sequences in at least a decade is the new one for the Peacemaker, the new John
Seamish show on HBO Max. It is so funny. And to have Steve Agee doing choreography and Robert
Patrick doing choreography. I mean, it's it's really, really funny. And it's one I'll never skip.
For sure. Yeah, that that intro is is great. It's really great.
John Wolf asks, What are some podcasts you like to listen to? Zero. I don't ever listen to podcasts
ever. I got asked that as well. On the other on the other show, but I listened to my favorite of
all time that I've been listening to for 15 years is the best show with Tom Sharpling. He is a hero
of mine. It is a difficult show to recommend to people because, you know, it's got such a
long history and it's hard to just kind of come into. But I love it. I also love his new podcast
with Julie Klausner called Double Threat, which is equally funny. And that's about it. I mean,
I have my my big obsession was 80s all over, which my buddy Scott Weinberg did with Drew McQueenie.
And they went through every movie released in the 80s. But unfortunately, they stopped at about 85.
I still hold out hope they'll bring it back because I really love that show.
Will Potter, our friend, what's the nerdiest activity you've ever wanted to try out
without the judgment of your friends or family being a factor?
Well, it would never be a factor. If I wanted to do it, I would just do it.
But I guess there's a part of me that always thought I might enjoy a role playing game,
a Dungeons and Dragons or something like that. But, you know, I'm not I wouldn't be ashamed to
try it. I've just never done it. But it is very nerdy. I know Will's working on some some of that
stuff now. I would like very much to dress up in a Boba Fett outfit, carry a lightsaber around the
convention, swinging it about, and cosplaying. But I will never do that.
By cosplaying, you mean putting on a colorful sweater and drugging a woman, right?
That's an outtake, by the way, from the Between Two Ferns movie. The whole credit seek closing
credits is outtakes. Yeah. And they're really funny. But he's talking to Jon Hamm. And he's like,
So they put Don Draper's like, you know, sports coat or whatever in the Smithsonian.
And okay. And he's Jon Hamm's like, Yeah, that's really an honor. It's amazing that it's in there.
And Zach Alphaness goes, Yep, right next to the Cosby sweaters.
That's funny. That's weird, too, because Don Draper didn't have like a signature sport
coat that I recall, but might not be the spork is something.
Maybe a tumbler for whiskey or something. Mason's I'm watching, by the way, this new W Kamau Bell
documentary about Bill Cosby. And I've never never once smiled at anything Mr. Bell has said.
But he's a good documentarian. And it's very interesting. It's
believe it or not, it's not painting a good picture of Mr. Cosby.
It's on Showtime, four hours, I would check it out. It's cool. And that's not cool. You know,
it's interesting. Mason scan asks, Have you ever seen a ghost or a UFO? No.
No, here as well. Nothing, nothing even close to it, to be honest.
Jared Smallridge asks, I lived in I live in Portland, Maine. Oh, the better Portland.
I think I always wanted to live there. I live in Portland, Maine, where we've recently been
blessed with snow, which leads to lots of time to sit around and watch movies begs the question,
what are your favorite snowy movies? Mine are the thing ravenous and Fargo. Also,
Pat, can we please get an on with the Joe, my cold dead heart, which are appreciated.
I'm going to I'm going to combine and go and do this and on with the snow.
Oh, right. There you go. You pick mine. The thing in Fargo are the perfect answers,
but I will say, I always like a movie, a full 50 % more if it's set in the snow always because I miss
it. And I thought when I came to Atlanta, I'd get some but it somehow doesn't make its way down here.
So love the snow movies. If you're asking about a literal snow movie that were snow as a factor,
I would say the thing is definitely one Empire Strikes Back, undoubtedly. But if you're asking
them movies that I like to watch when it's snowy outside, nothing to me tops for some reason a
hammer horror movie when it's snowy. It takes me back to being a kid when you were watching like
the local, you know, whatever affiliate before we had Fox and UPN and all these other stations.
And you know, it'd be Sunday and like the horror matinee would come on every week and
I really enjoy when it's cold and gloomy out a hammer horror film.
Yeah, I would say for both both a movie set in the snow and one I like to watch when it snows,
I would say Misery is another great choice. Oh, yeah, it's a good one. I forgot about Misery.
Marco Van Wassenhove. Will Joe ever release that hour of comedy he didn't want to release
because of PC culture? Well, I did not want to release it. It's the hour I shot or recorded.
I didn't. It wasn't a video hour. It was a, you know, it was an album, but I recorded it in Chicago
right before the pandemic lockdown. I did not release it because of PC culture. I didn't release
it because well, maybe I said that in the past because I said I didn't know if I wanted to do
comedy anymore because things were becoming so policed. That doesn't worry me quite as
bit as much as it used to, but it just was dated. And after a year and a half being locked inside,
just didn't seem to make much sense. I certainly wasn't going to try to release it
at the beginning of a lockdown when none of us knew what was going to happen or what we
do with our money. But some of that material has made it into my new hour. It might get released.
I don't know. I'm not going to release anything until I feel really strongly about it. And the
problem is in this culture, there's something new to be aggravated about every single day.
So it's kind of hard to keep a shelf life on anything anymore, but we'll see.
Nigel Faulkner asks, growing up some of my favorite movie memories
came from going to the drive -in. Yes. Have either of you been to a drive -in cinema?
Any fun memories or horrific stories to share? For sure. I went when I was a kid twice. There
was one about an hour from my home in St. Louis. And I remember I saw a double feature of Batman
Beetlejuice, which was awesome. And I turned around and was able to see bare breasts on the adult
screen, which was very cool as well. The other time I went, it was UHF. And I think a UHF and
problem child, I think. And then in recent years, I used to go a lot. I discovered there was one
45 to an hour away from LA. It's still there. It thrived during the pandemic. They had all
the movie premieres there and everything. But I used to love to go. You could see three.
I would get very, very high so that it would wear off at the end of the six hours. But I saw all
kinds of shit. I remember getting, I was clearly high because I got very into the movie Noah with
Russell Crowe. I was like, this is fucking awesome. But I bet if I watched it now, I would not enjoy it
much. Yeah, we had a drive -in right near me where I grew up. So we went all summer long
for many years. But my two favorite memories were seeing Rambo 3 there with my dad and us both
becoming elated when he says, I'm your worst nightmare.
It's a nightmare. Yeah, that really lit us up. And then that was the one where the heroes are
Taliban. No, he's helping that he's protecting Taliban. Yeah. Okay. And then shouldn't have done
that Rambo. And then the other is seeing Masters of the Universe, the Dove Lundgren
Canon film there with my parents and my best friend from childhood, Billy Morgan. Yeah. I mean,
you know, you can't beat it. You're at a drive -in, you're like 10 and you're seeing a He -Man live
action movie. It was fucking crazy exciting. They're bringing out a new Masters of the
Universe just announced live action. Starring one of the Jets from the new West Side Story.
What's that? The asshole that you said is a douchebag. Who's the guy West Side that you said
is the worst? Oh, Ansel Elgort. No, it's not him. It's the guy who stole the show and West Side
Story for sure. But he's built like Julian Casablancas. He's not He -Man. I guess they're
going to beef him up. But I also told Joe, Steven Spielberg just cast David Lynch in this movie
about his childhood, which I'm really excited about it. Well, what people are speculating is
that Spielberg for years talks about when he met his hero, John Ford, the great director as a kid.
And his impression, Spielberg's impression of John Ford sounds a lot like David Lynch.
So there's a lot of people speculating that he's going to be playing John Ford, which is really
cool. Okay, very cool. Yeah. Austin Taylor, Hitchcock, Deep Cuts. Have either of you seen
Blackmail or Hitchcock Presents Breakdown? The episode starring Joseph Cotton. Blackmail is
impressively suspenseful for nearly a hundred year old movie, especially the knife scene.
And the concept of breakdown scares the living shit out of me. If neither of you
have seen these, just give me a Hitchcock deep cut of your own, but please consider these.
I never saw either of those. My deep cut. I mean, I don't know that it's a deep cut,
but you know, well, I guess, you know, I don't know the trouble with Harry's really funny.
Um, stage fright is also a really cool Hitchcock movie that, that,
that people don't seem to talk about quite a bit. So I picked those two.
Yeah. I, I've not seen any episode of Albert Hitchcock Presents, which is a big gap in my
resume. And I, I think I've seen Blackmail, but the Hitchcock ones I haven't seen are the,
are those hundred year old black and white ones. Uh, a lesser known one I'd recommend is the man who
knew too much with Jimmy Stewart. I actually prefer the Jimmy Stewart version to the original.
And, uh, saboteur is a great black and white one from the early forties with Joseph Cotton.
Uh, really, really good. That's, that's due for a remake for sure. I would check that one out.
Also his later period is often neglected like his R rated movies with tits and blood and stuff like,
uh, uh, frenzy family plot, you know, that there's some good stuff in there.
Steve Murdoch, what movie have you guys completely changed your mind about
an old favorite you have grown to hate or a movie you've come to appreciate?
Um,
well, I mean, I know I've got a million of these, but I just can't remember any of them at the moment.
The, uh, you know, yeah, it's hard to think on the spot of that, but like my,
um, definitely one that I always sort of forced myself to like as a kid. And then when I watched
it as an adult was like, this isn't good. Is the Goonies. Um, I don't think Goonies is bad. I just
don't, I don't think it's, it's deserving of all the lavish praise people throw upon it. The truth
is everything I liked when I was a kid, I, I essentially still like when I grow up, um,
when I grew up the, uh, when I was a kid, the shit I didn't like, I still don't like,
I kind of had pretty strong taste even then, but there's definitely been movies that I,
on a second viewing, I was like, Oh, the biggest one for me is Phantom Thread, which I enjoyed.
Um, but sort of left me cold on a first viewing. And then on the second one,
I was like, Oh shit, that's, I see what this is about. I see what he's doing and I got it.
Uh, PTA works that way for me a lot, except on licorice pizza. A second viewing did not help
that one. It hurt it. So there's some answers.
I loved when I was young, I loved the movie Willow.
Yeah. I can't stand to watch it now. It's so boring. And it plays in the bar all the time.
I don't know why the bartenders are always putting Willow on.
Well, Ron Howard is, uh, is not the man to be directed in that kind of material for sure.
He's a great director, but not for that stuff. And, uh, I remember loving it, but I haven't seen it
30 years. They're going to do that Disney plus series. I'm curious to see it. I'm always
down to watch a Warwick Davis thing. Yeah. But, uh, yeah, that's mine. Uh, Emily asks or says,
Joe, you for, wait a minute. Did we miss? No. Uh, Joe, you forgot my birthday.
Did I? Sorry. I'm not really a question, Emily, but okay. How can I leverage this enough that you
had to a commentary episode on Nightmare on Elm Street three, winter beast, evil dead 81 near dark
or night breed? Um, you know, I'm not against doing a commentary episode. It's easy enough
for us to do. Um, is it, how would we do that? We would just, you just, we would just stream it
simultaneously, you know, I'll just be watching it in the room while we do that. Yeah. Yeah.
My concern would be wifi bandwidth really. I mean, but it might work out.
Um, evil dead, we've already reviewed, so I don't think we should do a commentary on that.
And I believe we've already, we, we definitely reviewed Nightmare on Elm Street three because
we did the whole series, um, near dark I would consider. And I mean, if you want to hear me
shit all over a movie for two hours, I'll do night breed. It might be a good one because I've
seen that horror film. Uh, Emily likes it, which is stupid.
And tell her happy birthday, Joe. I did. Happy birthday. Okay. All right. I thought I did.
Rocky har harrow Harjo fellas. What is your favorite controversy in tinsel town?
Um, I think we already had a question from Rocky Harjo because I almost said
Rocky Harjo picture show, but, um, okay. Favorite. I mean, the, to me, the darkest, uh,
is that fatty Arbuckle one where he was, you know, putting a bottle in a woman and it broke
or whatever. You know what though? I just watched a documentary about him. Apparently he was cleared
of all that. He didn't do it. Okay. Eventually was able to make a moderate comeback, but like
the damage was done. Like, yeah, like he wasn't a part of that situation. Apparently, you know,
who knows? It was, you know, but, but yeah, that's a, that's a dark one. I mean, look,
the one that shook me to my core was the Cosby scan. I mean, I just, I still can't wrap my head
around it. There was the one that Rod Stewart had to have his stomach pumped, you know, to get all
the come out of it. He had so much come in his stomach. They had to pump it, which is absurd.
Yeah. Like tall tales in the eighties, you know, Richard year with the gerbil. Yeah. Yeah. That
was a big one. They, they threw that a couple guys, Jerry Petticolli, uh, who was, uh, like
he was on like entertainment tonight. He was a guy from Philly. It was a local Philly guy. Then he
went to, uh, national, but, um, anyway, they said Danny K used to love, uh, lying underneath the
glass table and having a woman shit on it. No harm in that. No, not hurting anybody.
Steve Harrison, Joe, what is your favorite horror horror video game moment? Uh, hands down a
resident evil four, uh, which is one of my favorite video games of all time. Um, and it was the first
horror video, like real horror video game. I think that I had played, I played the first one when I
was in college a bit, but I didn't really play it, play it. I just sat and watched my friends play
the resident evil four. When you're in the cabin and you have, and the zombies are descending on
cabin and you have to block the windows and they start breaking through like thriller style,
that level blew me away. And that was before I had ever seen anything like that in a video game
where it was simulating like a literal scene I'd seen in horror movies. So that's, that's my answer
hands down. Uh, John Wolf, Pat and Joe, what's a good day of writing normally look like for you?
Um, it's always completely different. Um, I, I wish I was one of these guys who did like,
I wake up at six and I do 10 pages and then I run and then I do another 10, but for me, uh,
it is always a, oh shit, I'm really inspired to write something. It comes over me quickly.
I'll cancel plans. If that happens, I'll, you know, I'll, you know, because it's rare to be
by that kind of inspiration. When I do write like that, uh, it's all day. I can't stop.
As I have said repeatedly on the show, weed helps me get into that state where I can write
for like 12 hours. And, uh, that's it. I have no schedule. It's, it's just, um, I catch it,
I catch it as it comes, unless you're writing on a show where you have to force yourself
gun to head to do it. Um, yeah, without a deadline or something in place, I'm kind of a mess. I'm
my least favorite hands down with staff writing. I did not enjoy that, um, at all. Uh, I, you know,
I had some good experiences and I'm glad I did it, but I did not enjoy the clock ticking while
you wrote, um, you know, my favorite day is, is when I bang out, uh, a short story and really get
either all of it down or, or a lot of it down. That's, that's, I don't know. That's very
rewarding to me. Yeah. Uh, Ben Lee asks, Pat, you mentioned that you saw an early cut of
Ingrid Goes West a few years ago, and we're at the Q and A with Matt Spicer, who was discussing
changes the studio wanted. Do you remember any of those changes? Did you end up seeing the final
cut? We're into three questions now, Ben. And then he adds Joe, any good heckler stories.
Uh, yeah, I saw the original cut, which was roughly 20 minutes longer when they asked for
feedback. I said, do not change this. This is the best movie I've seen in a year. Do not change a
thing. And then they cut 20 minutes and I told my buddy who produced it. I said, you made a mistake
and, and I couldn't really point to what was missing. I just know that it, it made a more
complete full vision to me. So it was kind of scenes going on longer, you know, cut jokes,
stuff like that. And there was a slightly different ending. It's a very dark ending.
Anyway, you slice it, but, um, I just preferred it. And I saw the new version too, which is
excellent. And I probably would have loved it more if I hadn't seen that uncut version.
A heckler story. Just last night, my two biggest fans at the show who told me before the show,
how much they loved me were so disruptive throughout the entire show. They were warned
they would be thrown out repeatedly. It's always nice when the people who love you
are also destroying the show. Were they just drunk? Drunk ain't the word for it.
Yeah. You know, uh, just wild, like just full loud conversations with other people at their table,
like screaming things out. It was just insane. And then so drunk that when I was trying to address
them and be like, dude, just talk to me, like, what is it that you want to communicate? They
couldn't make sense out of what I was saying to them. So yeah, there you go. Okay. It's always
fun. Uh, Umar, not Uber says, yo, Joey and Patty, can you both each give me an underrated film
for a double feature? My only criteria is one film needs to make me sad and the other needs
to make me laugh. Any genre? Well, we don't, we don't know what you've seen and what you haven't.
Um, I mean, for me, if I'm recommending somebody, a lesser known comedy that really cracks me up,
I go, I go Saving Silverman. You know, it's not classy. It's not, uh, it's not Wes Anderson,
but it just makes me belly laugh every time I see it. And, um, a movie that no one on earth has seen
that I saw at some all night horror on one Halloween in New York is called King of the
Ants, directed by Stuart Gordon, the great Stuart Gordon, and, uh, starring a horrifying George
Wendt. And there are visuals in this movie that I have not been able to shake. And I saw it 20 years
ago and you can rent it, you know, King of the Ants is an exceptional movie. It's, it's sort of
a crime thriller, but with Stuart Gordon, it's, there's major horror elements to it as well.
Uh, underrated comedy, ready to rumble all day long, Oliver flat, um, Martin Landau
playing, he was in BAPS black American princesses. Yeah. And of course, David Arquette and the great,
uh, um, Scotty con Scott con, uh, I think I'm going to Scott con this year. Actually
you dress up as your favorite Scott con characters. Okay. I thought it was just
a bunch of Scots meetup. Um, and then I should have said Scott con con the, uh, yeah. So, um,
but that's my comedy movie that'll make you cry. Um, Jimmy cons a great follow on Twitter, by the
way. I don't know if you're very funny. He's very funny. I feel like he gets some help on it, but
he's funny. Um, I'll tell you a movie, a great movie that can, that'll make you cry from recent
years that blew me away is, um, sing street. Excellent Irish movie. Check it out. I could give
a shit. No, you'd like sing street job. I swear you'd, you definitely would control is a movie
that'll sit with you about, about the guy from joy division. Yeah. That's a dark ride. Uh, so there
we go. Uh, and, and, and very underrated, uh, Mark, Dan Bison says, Hey fellas, hi Mark, Pat.
Oh no. Then he has questions. Sorry, Pat. Have you, sorry, Pat, you once alluded to having sex in a
theater. Uh, what movie was, where were you at? I, I don't know if I know. I don't think I had
penetration of theater. I definitely got jerked off in a theater more than once. And the movie
was a midsummer night's dream, which of course she can change to cream if, if you'd need to.
But, uh, the one with like Kevin Klein and Michelle Pfeiffer, it was so unbelievably boring.
And, uh, yeah, my girlfriend jacked me off. I got a blow job in
another bad one. Oh, blast from the past with Brendan Fraser. Again, you can make a joke out
of that blast from the past. Yeah. But, um, yeah, those are, those are two I remember.
And I found a used condom and can hardly wait when I was an usher, which is again,
a joke you can use. Guess they couldn't hardly wait. But, um, yeah, that might,
you might be mixing up stories a little bit, unless I just lied and said I had sex. I don't
think he does say if the, if this is true, he did say, yeah, found a used condom that wasn't mine,
got a handy and a blow job. Joe, what's your favorite Halloween special TV show episode?
Meaning like, I guess he means like an episode of a TV show about,
you know, like the, like a special Halloween episode. Yeah. Um,
Roseanne always does great. Roseanne did great. One of those, the Roseanne ones were really fun.
They were like, you know, they were like special, but those aren't my favorite. Um,
there's no Seinfeld one. I know there's a Frazier one, but I'm blanking on it now. Um,
is it that horrible perfect strangers episode where they're flying for some reason?
I'll give it to the perfect strangers. I mean, that was bad. It was, you almost gotta respect it.
It went like supernatural in that last season. That's crazy. Uh, I'll give it to the perfect
strange. Okay. Uh, Chris Marsh says, Pat, did you have a tough adjustment to marriage and cohabitating?
Is it claustrophobic? And then he has a question for me, Joe,
what would quickly be the biggest obstacle if the love of your life moved in with you tomorrow?
I definitely had, had an issue with the cohabitation part, but that was pre -marriage.
We lived together for quite a while, but I definitely felt a little, I'm a lone wolf,
you know, at my core and, uh, having somebody in your shit at all times. And you know,
they're never going anywhere to some people, myself included can be a little overwhelming,
but, uh, you know, you get over it and then it's nice to have somebody there.
Uh, for me, cohabitation, aside from her leaving giant shits in the toilet on flush,
which I can't think of anything worse, it's messiness. I can't deal with it. I can't deal
with the messiness. Uh, and I, I literally wouldn't be able to, to marry somebody if it
came down to it. If, if we had to live together, unless she said we can live in separate apartments
so I can stay messy, then I could do that. But I can't, I can't deal with it. People that are
always losing things. You're trying to get out the door. Where did I put my keys? I, I, it drives me
call her phone twice a day. I'm like, put it in your fucking pocket. I've never once lost my phone.
Yeah. Can you call my phone? Well, it's either in your bedroom or it's in the living room, you know,
like Zach Henderson, uh, you get to choose the genre or even plot. If you want to take it that
far of Tarantino's last film, what'll it be? I know already, and it's because I fantasize about
it. I desperately want him to go back to the crime universe of the first two movies. Yeah. I want him
to go back and, and close it out with something pulp fiction, reservoir dogs related. Yeah. As
much as I've loved his, uh, his forays into the past, your Django's, your and glorious bastards,
et cetera, to me, that's his best stuff is, is when he's dealing with LA crime, uh, and just
LA in general. I mean, once upon a time in Hollywood exceptional, he'd be, he'd be proud
to go out on that, but I hope we get at least two, three more. And I hope as Joe says, he brings
it back to that crime world. It's like he's Scorsese. It's like Scorsese is always great,
but when he does the gangster shit, it's impeccable. You know, for sure, for sure.
Barb Allen, are you tired of Alf stuff? I, I haven't encountered any out to have recently.
As far as I know, it's been done for a while, but yes, I hate Alf. I can't fucking stand it.
I love Alf. I think he should host the Academy Awards this year, but, um, if you mean, am I
tired of Alf jokes? Uh, you know, they always make me smile, but I also am sort of like,
you know, that's not really it. It's insane to think a story should be private when you
tell it on a podcast, but it's definitely one. I don't look forward to like my mom going,
what is this Alf story? You know, but, uh, I could never be tired of Alf. He's a very
comedic influence on me. If I'm being real is Judd, Sal, Sal amanders. Oh, sound. That's
right. Okay. Uh, is Judd Apatow a bad man? Geez. Um, you know, what, what's the bar?
If you look, if you look at the bar in Hollywood of what people do, absolutely not. He's,
he's just, um, and I work with him and he was incredibly nice to me. So I wouldn't say so.
Um, yeah, I mean, he's, he's, I don't know. He's always been pretty nice to me. Uh,
I worked with him for two weeks. Yeah. Uh, then quit because I didn't want to work in television
anymore. Um, but, but you know, he, Judd seems like a nice enough guy. He gets a little, especially
for having his, his level of power. I mean, he's, he's fine. Yeah. So
folks we are at, and what a question to end it on is Judd Apatow a bad man. I'm going to end my
shows with that tonight. Yeah. Pose it to the audience. You've got cards and little golf
pencils. I'd like everybody's answers. Folks, we're only halfway through these questions and
we've hit a solid hour here. So, um, we're going to actually break this into a two parter. Uh,
we'll bring you the best movies and TV shows of 2021 in the second half of this month,
but for now we're going to stop reset and get to answering the rest of your questions as the second
episode of February continues. And we will, no matter how long it takes, finish this list in
part two. Um, I also think this is good because there's several 2021 movies I need to watch. I
had a hard time coming up with five good movies from 2021. So I want to make sure I see some more
I picked, I did, I did TV and movies and I picked the things I really, that just took me out of the
shit existence we're living. Yeah. TV. I had a list of, of 15, 20 and movies. I was like,
I guess I'll say that's good. I don't know. It's been a bad year for movies.
Joe DeRosa comedy on Instagram and Twitter, joeyrosesnyc .com. If you want to come see us
when you're in town, go there for all your Joey roses bar and sub shop information needs. And
also I'm touring at the moment, not consistently, but about once a month I'm going out. I will see
you next in February, March, uh, in Philadelphia at the punchline comedy club. I will then be
going down to South by Southwest directly from there. Um, April, I think I have something coming
up on the West coast in May. I will be back in Austin, headlining the Creek and cave. And in
DeRosa info for tickets and information about shows, the Patrick Walsh Twitter and Instagram.
I have nothing to plug. Um, but we will see you next time and we will see you in hell.