All right folks we are back we'll see you in hell episode two for the month of July
we're talking 28 years later the first in a new trilogy because there's not enough zombie stuff
out there we need more zombie stuff uh -huh I hear in the second movie they're going to bring some
vampires in and then the third movie is going to be a Marvel crossover so we're getting plenty
of what we need here uh but we'll get to it Pat how have you been since the last episode
well I peed uh felt good felt relieving um I'm pretty good I
been listening I just finished last night the Michael Richards autobiography
I know you I had you downloaded as well I don't know if you've been listening
I I listened to I have an interesting story about this I listened to the the first you know
the forward I was happy to hear Seinfeld who amazingly somehow made the forward to somebody else's
autobiography about himself yes which was incredible but I I listened to the first chapter where
Michael Richards I think was talking about something Seinfeld oh was the his hair yeah
uh Kramer's hair being too crazy or whatever the hell it was um and then I fell asleep not because
I was bored but I was just kind of lay in there in that mode and I started to have one of those dreams
where the thing that was happening in reality was happening was affecting the dream and the two things
were integrating okay so I started having a dream where a guy was talking to me at a party and
what he was saying was the Michael Richards audiobook that was playing in my horrible experience
and in the dream I got up and said shut the fuck up man and I remember the part it's when he said
the thing about Marilyn like like something about Marilyn lived there once and I used to just put notes
in her mailbox or I don't know what the hell he was talking about me he might have been quote in somebody
else but but I spent I spent the entire audiobook saying shut the fuck up yelling it at my at my uh
car radio he is insane as we all knew uh he's got that comedians in cars with Jerry where he sits on
the floor and Jerry's clearly embarrassed in a public restaurant and there are so many stories in this
book where he like he's like I went to Billy Crystal's party I walked in and even though nobody
else was in the pool I hopped in with my shoes and clothes on and I got out of the pool thinking
everyone would be laughing and everyone was very mad there are so many times where he does something
completely insane and then is shocked 20 years later that people didn't like it and I came away
from this book loathing Michael Richards I wish I had never listened to it you might be saying oh
the the N word incident wasn't enough I guess not I didn't realize how unwell he is it's a 15 plus
hour audiobook and he doesn't get to his acting career till about hour 10 you are listening to literal
hours of army stories did you know he was in the army I didn't he has nothing funny or interesting
to say about his time in the army and you slowly start to realize he's only telling you these stories
because they all involve black soldiers and I think he wants you to know that he was friends with
black people at one point whenever he talks and whenever a black person speaks he uses a black voice
it's not extreme but it's there and you wonder how that possibly could have gotten past the producers
of the book he refers to another black soldier as quote a street wise Shakespeare who always had a
jive rhyme to share jive and street wise using the description um he's always talking to them like
I wondered where my my friend Lee Roy was and I said Lee Roy where are you and he yelled out I'm
smoking retha motherfucker like that's what he's doing oh boy throughout these stories are so boring
an endless that I started listening to it on double speed which is the fastest you can listen to it
and he was kind of sounding like a human being if you listen to it at regular speed it's like
that's when I realized it's like the the guy in uh Ferris Bueller in what way like that's how he talks it's
impossible to listen to he is so self -absorbed then I'm like okay he's getting to his acting career
finally can't wait to hear about UHF can't wait to hear about you know Transylvania 6 5 ,000 and
problem child these movies I really enjoyed when I was a kid he has one sentence about Transylvania he
has one sentence about UHF and he has one sentence about problem child there's no mention of his
only starring feature role in trial and error a really good movie that Cisco and Ebert gave two
thumbs up to he doesn't mention acting in it he only talks about Seinfeld and the Seinfeld stories
are ones you've heard before you know of course it's good to hear an inside take on one of the great
shows but he doesn't have a lot of insight into it he spends a whole lot of time bitching about the
Michael Richards show uh I thought well how could they be bad the scripts bad I called Jerry he goes
no these guys are great writers you can trust them but I gotta say I started to feel like maybe
only Jerry and Larry were the funny writers because these scripts were absolutely horrible at some
point I blew up on set they were arguing about what color the countertop should be and I started
screaming at them for several minutes I'm dying out here my career is dying and you're arguing about
countertops and he is telling this story as if he is the hero yeah he says the very next day the show
was canceled well no shit you fucking monster you know what the parentheses is to that 120 people were
out of work yeah you fucking asshole I oh god I hate him now yeah and then you're like okay he's
getting to the n -word incident we're gonna hear the humility the accountability the apology instead
he says 50 times now no comedian had a problem with what I did every comedian understood that's
just what happens when you're on stage and it's like no if that's what happened then we'd be hearing
about every other comedian who did it he's more upset that people were filming his set then what he
did he says and by the way we all make mistakes I'm not saying we still got to hold this guy over the
coals but he tells the story and here's how he tells it I'll keep it brief because he because he kept
it brief I'm up there doing my stand up and I start hearing these very loud gentlemen in the back
being very rude I yell up at them shut the fuck up they yell back at me you're not funny we go back
and forth comedy club stuff you know school yard insults and taunts I go home the next day I come
back to the comedy store and there's a reporter who wants my side of the story I say what do you mean
she says well we want to hear about the racism I say racism what then I search my brain and I remember oh
yes I did use a few choice words you're like what is fucking wrong with you this is how he explains this
Joe that is almost verbatim I mean I I I rewound it I was like you know he says I had to do the work
but to him the work is like walking across Peru by himself sleeping on the floor meditating all this
hippie -dippy shit guess what guess what guess what guess what no for him I had to do the work man I
couldn't get fucking hired exactly they had he been hired again the next day he would have kept
fucking working and whatever yes he couldn't get hired again until and by the way he did keep working
he was on a sitcom on on on TV land and he talks more about that and how much he appreciates
Christie Ali for looking past what he did and bringing him on her TV land show then he does about his
film career it's fucking ridiculous um he seems wholly unlikeable monster he's another he's
another and I know I keep bringing up the guy's name over and over but I just can't get over it
he's another Will Smith who is now spinning his Oscar slap into like you know my my truth and
growth moment and all this shit because the guy is incapable of just saying I'm a psycho when I
fucked up yeah we by the way Will we know what your wife was doing cheating on you with your son's
friend we'd understand you losing your shit they just can't do it I mean you know what well I'll
go as far as to say this seems like you slapped the wrong person in that train call
the hell you slept in Chris floor he's on the one that fucked your son's friend yeah it's if
you're a fan of uh of Seinfeld you've probably seen the incredible bloopers that there are there are
such an immediate mood lifter these Seinfeld bloopers but what you see time and time again
is Jerry Jason and Julia dying laughing and Kramer going knock it off focus focus he looks at
sometimes like he's gonna hit Julia Louis Dreyfus he gets a little you know not I won't say violent
but he gets mean with her in the bloopers and you're like wow that got uncomfortable at the end there
his temper is clearly unhinged and you know obviously Jason Alexander's a little full of himself
they kind of mocked him on the curb thing the curb reunion but the way Kramer talks about him he tells
this story where they don't have his suit ready for an event and the Seinfeld gang was like flown to
a nice hotel for this big up front event and they don't have his suit ready so he comes down wearing
his robe to go to this big event and he's like Jerry was laughing Jason as usual looked at me like he
thought I was insane that's always how Jason looked at me yeah no shit you are so he's like I came
down in my robe and for 10 minutes I screamed at the staff for not having my suit ready
and could you believe it Jason that night didn't want to talk to me he thought I had gone too far
he still can't say like I I was nuts I did leave this story out we'd never know but he tells you it
like he thinks he's the hero of it yeah it's like Ellen he's like an Ellen exactly exactly people are
these people are sick they're just sick it's it's it's a shame now on the flip side a guy who's
less famous but you know similar a character act a tall gangly goofy character actor Daniel Stern
his autobiography is 30 minutes on his childhood whittled down to only the interesting and funny
aspects and then it's a movie by movie discussion of his entire career project by project hilarious
stories about other actors actors he didn't get along with actors he did and it's a great super
entertaining listen and then you just hear what this business can do oh well it was probably
already in him let's be real but it's like how do you how do you think that we bought this book
to hear eight solid hours of army stories you you maniac mm -hmm anyway that's the end of my wrath
well there you go look you just did the segment yeah I did that's the new segment you did it
uh I I'm gonna listen to more of that Michael Richards book just because I'm curious or maybe I'll
just return it audible started letting you return titles then get your credit back really yeah they
were doing it for a while I don't know if they still are but that that was the thing when they
have to they have to prove that you didn't listen to a certain amount or something no no sometimes it
was just like you could just be like I just didn't like this like this is not formidable you
should not do that you're already struggling I'm sure there was a limit to it there was a you
couldn't like do it all the time but they were pretty accommodating the one uh anecdote in the book I
enjoyed he's close friends with Ed Begley junior who was one of the nicest men I ever met so I don't
know how how Ed Begley junior and Michael Richards are good friends but they're at a party
I believe Carrie Fisher's house and Albert Brooks is there and then my ears perked up because I
always wonder what he's like as a man you never hear any details about it really yeah and that was
the one good story and and Michael Richards again is made out to be a fucking monster and he doesn't get
how uh they're at this party Albert Brooks comes up to him starts talking to him and he's like how are
you know you enjoying your success have you bought a great house yet and uh he goes I did and Albert
Brooks is like I live 10 minutes away I got a new house I love it so much would you and Ed
want to come see it I really just want to show it off so he goes so we we left the party we drive up
to Albert Brooks's house this is this is what I'm waiting for some sort of fun story yeah he goes we get
there Albert shows me around as he pushes the doorbell a fake dog starts barking and I say to him
why do you have the fake dog thing immediately Albert's face falls he said I spent so much money
on this I thought this was going to keep my house safe um and he just started spiraling about it the
money he'd wasted and everything else and he goes this is when I knew I liked Albert Brooks he was real
in a in a city of people who are fake and I was like here's one moment I like you I like Michael I like
Albert I'm having a good time then they go inside Albert Brooks shows him his new treadmill is really
expensive little workout room Michael Richards immediately hops on the treadmill and he goes you know
looking for a laugh I thung myself off it well I crashed into his wall and put a giant hole in it
he asked me to leave shortly thereafter but I heard that he put a sign next to it that said Michael
Richards did this and left it up in his house forever and you're like you're going into people's new
homes and destroying them and pretending you're funny what a just a what a jerk off asshole seriously
like and and he thinks that because Albert Brooks put that sign up that he's like I love that guy he
was a lot of fun no I would be I have really I think Alexander's the last one in the cast that I like
like I I would be excited to meet Seinfeld because I have tremendous respect for him as a comedian yeah
I do not I have met him it was not it was not unpleasant but he was not very friendly
um I don't think there would be any reason for him to be friendly if I were to meet him again I've
met him twice the one time he was a little more receptive but my point is is I don't think he's a
very warm guy and I would be shocked if I had met him and and found him to be again Michael Richards
is an idiot fuck Julia Louise Dreyfus I'm sorry but lady go the fuck home let other people make
a little bit of the money all right you got to do a podcast now I've bitched about this at length
enough Julia go home you're doing Marvel movies now go home yeah yeah poor Jason Alexander's out there
like still like you know fucking well he's also doing a podcast but he probably needs the money yeah
well because I need the money I can KFC for fucking three years after Seinfeld yeah um
but you know even he went on stern and did the thing where he was like well they killed off my
feet everybody hated her whatever it's like what is wrong with all of you I know what is wrong with
all of you well one one more moment he because he clearly doesn't like Jason Alexander but he never
quite says it so he talks about he goes when uh Julia on our first table read had nothing in the script
and she immediately marched over to Larry and Jerry and said I'm not gonna be like the eye candy
or I'm not gonna be the chick or whatever like I need storylines and jokes he goes uh later on I didn't
have something in an episode but I kept it to myself I knew Larry would take care of me later on
Jason was cut out of an episode once boy uh he was certainly an example of a different way to
handle the situation he clearly had a temper and you're like he had a temper we've we've seen your
temper you fucking monster oh my god this is also though where this is maybe it was a different time
in the business but this is what I'm talking about it's like Julia marches over I'm not gonna be
a set piece I want storyline who the fuck are you at this point lady the ego the Larry Charles has
the story about the gun episode the the one of the two scripts they didn't do in season two because
Julia was like this isn't funny guns aren't funny it's like lady you're not famous like yeah just
do your job but it's like oh yeah you come you you you have billionaire money you know I think
the karma oh yeah everyone forgets that I forget that she was wealthy before she even started acting
oh so I'm saying yeah um I I will never write the tell all book because a nobody would buy it and
be it feels like bad karma and you're just asking people to come out of the woodwork and say the
most unflattering things about you however you learn real quick in this business if you have even a
modicum of fame you almost always become nuts that the things people say the the the the writing uh
the critiques that they will throw in your face you're like holy shit like now I'm not doing this
well we worked on it for a week so can we talk about it you know like they they are so entitled
and it's almost like the the the lower your star is on the wrong the more entitled jar uh and
this michael riches book christ is a good example of that the uh it's just it's it's what it you know
I don't know I guess this is why you know everything we're criticizing these people for it's also why
you become successful yeah not you just think this way um but yeah it's just fucking wild I mean I'm
I'm you know I'm on a god damn set I'm I'm apologizing from the minute I step on to the fucking
thing uh I'm so scared I'm gonna lose work yeah this is this is tough work to come by this is not
this is not easy work to come this is getting acting work we're getting your show on the air
we're getting the job writing whatever it is it is it's like being a gold miner
and finding if if the the behaviors were condemning it would be like being a gold miner
and finding gold and then just be like I just throw it over there yeah no we found the thing
that we've been looking for like protect this let's get it back up to the surface
it's it's just wild man it's wild to me the the actor who gave me five years of PTSD and I don't feel
I'm exaggerating uh was making $80 ,000 a week and he was working roughly 25 to 30 hours a week
so there you go yeah uh Joe did you get do you get down and dirty with amazon prime day
did you celebrate do you celebrate i celebrated uh i said i sent b i said the b's as i call them
i sent him a nice flower floral arrangement and an edible one of the edible arrangements yeah it was
uh it was it was uh made up of the uh body parts of the children of his employees
i enjoyed that quite a bit uh no i went on you bitched about it to me i went on you said it sucked
and i went on and i didn't see anything i mean i only looked in my two sections which was um um
you know i went into movies and i went into video games and i just saw nothing
even sort of uh of note i mean it's like years ago it would have been like
ps5 amazon prime day 250 bucks you know like that would have been the deal
they were amazing deals you know they were so reminiscent about a website but yeah it was great yeah
they were selling like third rate Nintendo switch games
barely discounted the movie section had a few things a few but i mean christ almighty the one actually
it's what we're talking about this is the one i found most important the sign fell box set the dvd
it is available on 4k and blue right now the dvd version of it was $55 i paid 64 it
10 years ago yeah that's pathetic that's pathetic yeah it really bugged me especially at a time when
america could really use a break could really use some discounts you know everybody's struggling
and we all just saw you have a 10 million dollar wedding on a yacht with your clown wife
and by the way have you seen the reports of like what a hero bezos is for marrying an age
appropriate woman and she's a mother can you believe it she's a mother and she's 55 yeah well
she may be 55 her face is two years old her tits are five like give me a fucking break uh he also
you know looks like a mole you know he should be thrilled he should be happy
i i hated looking through i look at amazon every day it's something that helps my OCD i take
stuff to the post office every morning and it kind of starts me out in like oh i started my day
making money you know and doing something productive it helps me stupid but it is i know what the
prices are of things and what they do now for prime day is they lie about what the retail
price is so let's say you have a blue rate let's say it's this lethal weapon 4k
and it's 20 let's say it's 20 bucks and and yesterday it was 20 markdown from 25 let's say today
they say it's 19 dollars but that the retail price is 50 they just make shit up so they're lying about
how much the discount is and people fall for it you see oh my god this thing 60 % off i better buy it
but then when the sale ends the price might actually go down you're getting completely hoodwink
so if the only time you go to amazon is prime day like a lot of people you're like wow these deals are
amazing but they're not if you knew what the price was five days before the sale you would not think
this was some amazing deal to try to doop the american public while you're one of the most rich
and successful corporations on earth is stomach churning as is everything amazon does and i would love
to be able to break away from them i try more and more lately to sell stuff on ebay my vinyl i try
to sell on discoggs whenever possible discoggs is just a great side and they take a lot less money from
you but yeah amazon should be ashamed of themselves it's it's it's emblematic of everything that's
wrong with america and could they have one good show could amazon prime make one good show and could
they stop passing on my shows you know the reason they give every time they pass on one of my shows
not global enough that's a that's a nice note that you can really take to hard as a creative person
and work on it's like oh you thought my script was not global enough how do i even take that note
they're bad at everything they do they're the most successful company on earth that is america did
did i ever did i ever talk about the um the justine bateman thing that i saw on here no although i
i believe she's like oddly right wing now and bateman is super liberal so i don't know how that works
out at thanksgiving but i i don't know about her politics at all but she she was really insightful
she talked about um she's like the these companies are not making content to make content
they're making content to sell product yeah and she was like so in other words she's like apple
is not making movies and tv shows because apple is interested in making movies and tv shows they're
making movies and tv shows to direct you back to their product which is the the iphone and the
computers and the whatever amazon is doing it to keep you going to the amazon website to buy things
and i just was like wow i'd never thought of it that way and i thought it was a really really
insightful uh take on that like it's it's sad it's very sad it's it's all a means
to to keep the store open i mean that's always anymore yeah for sure yeah bummer anyway um let's go to
the movie corn yeah i'm gonna do three shows in the corner and i'm gonna start by tipping my cap
to our very own Joseph de rosa if i may the high point of tires season two oh thank you
he's only in a couple scenes here and there but it was always a delight and by the way
not just because it was cool to see a friend uh just because i thought your timing was hilarious
that scene with you and Shane where he's like do you think people would have a lawsuit about my weight
or whatever i was really laughing at that you're you played that perfectly thank you uh that's the
that's i posted that the other day that's the hardest i've ever laughed ever on the set of something
and it was the longest it ever took to get through a thing on like we we did that so many times
instead it's so many different ways and laughed so much it's truly was a good joyous moment to have
with him yeah it was a really funny bit and and tires is this like kind of shaggy dog very very
likeable thing you know it's uh it it goes down smooth as they say it's like not jamming it's
it's got a tone all its own you know and it's not really Shane's tone either it's yeah it's a it's
almost a gentle comedy where the comedy is edgy uh which creates this kind of interesting vibe
it's like uh it feels as if you're watching people who work at a tire store it's not like joke heavy
it's more how people actually interact and i thought the second season was a step up from the first
and i'm glad it got picked up and eager to see where it goes well that's great i'm glad you liked it
i i love working with all those boys um and you know it was fun for me to see on screen uh at the
premiere and i've told the guys this but it was i felt like we i felt like it was nice to be a part
of something that i felt like captured philly yeah in pennsylvania so accurately and it was just
it brought a tear to my eye to be like this is this is where i'm from man and here's a show that's
it's always sunny takes place in philly but it's not a very philly centric show you know what i mean
this show to me feels like pennsylvania like it feels like you know uh the attitude the the mentality
and whatever um by the way i watched the two new episodes of always sunny last night and i'm always
you know careful because i know those guys and everything but the them at abbot elementary like i get
i get that we used to have the flinstones meet the jetsons and all that stuff but i was just like
this show is so far from how it started out you know it's nuts there's one big laugh where
quinta brunson calls katlyn ulson of uh she's like i you know i'm sorry i i need i'm not
because she's a very like on on abbot which i've seen a few episodes abbot it's it's cute
but she's like you know i i try to be ladylike and i try to be sweet but there's just
something about this d that gets under my skin i have to say it i just think she's uh
and then the guy next was like go ahead you can say it you can say it because i just think she's a
fucking cunt unbleaped wow it's like whoa whoa and he's like i really thought you're gonna say
bitch there she's like it didn't cover what i wanted to say like that was a good laugh and you know
it's kind of neat to see them infiltrate a show that's on network but like i was just like what has
this show become the second one i thought was funnier and it builds to a reveal that was hilarious
classic story all right don't spoil anything because i want to say in a word i'm not saying a word
the second one i want to see i don't care about the abbot crossover but does the second one at least
feel like hey we're back it's sunny to an extent yeah to an extent but the to me the reveal made it
worthwhile it's a funny show um it's still you know it's still easily one of the funnier shows
on television and and in season 18 or season 17 mausletoff i mean to even keep coming up with
plots is impressive at this point are we getting any are we getting any good uh how we're
10 classic Dennis in these first two episodes look i love the guy but he didn't have a classic moment
weirdly it felt like the three of them reacting both episodes and usually it's people reacting
to them yeah um so i don't know i i enjoyed them both it's it's still you know it what other show in
season 18 would be even remotely quality it so i always tip my hat um well speaking to tv shows
i rewatched i'm just about done uh Larry Sanders
masterpiece from the jump i was really you know as i've been talking about on the episodes you know
just just a tough time in uh personal life and uh my friend chip was like you know i just
rewatched all of Larry Sanders man and uh you know he was like i was i was really down and it man it was
just it really was enjoyable and i was like you know what i'm gonna do that and sure enough it brought
me great comfort and great joy uh the the show is just outstanding um and every time i watch it i
learn a little bit more about what it is they're doing i never quite fully and it's with change the
changing of times in our culture and whatever also that add to this but this latest watch was a real
like wow like i'm man these characters are very selfish yeah you know i think the first few times i'd
seen it we played a little more funny absurd you know show business insecurity with a little bit of
vanity and whatever you know this this watch around was was it hit on a deeper emotional level about
like where your life ends up when you only think about yourself and and and and that sort of thing um
it's it's just an amazing amazing amazing show and just toward the force performances
by everybody in this cast you know Gary Shanling Jeffrey Tambour rip torn Jeanine Garafalo Jeremy
Piven Wallace Langham uh Mary Lynn Rice Cobb um she's great um friend of mine she yeah Mary's awesome
she's great um and so is Jeanine they're the only two i know from the show but uh the uh
with uh uh uh uh uh uh Linda Dorsett like everybody on the show it's fucking great man it's just so
funny um already is my favorite character but Tambour remains the untouch untouchable goat in the
comedy department on that show i mean the guy it's it's like it could be the funniest character i've
ever seen in a tv show tambour is one of the funniest characters of all time yes uh and then he just
brought the same energy to arrest it and and made it work even even more not even more but continued
to work you know he's he's he's great he's always funny i haven't seen him in ages i guess he got
lightly cancelled but well he's 80 and i think like he got hit kind of hard at the end there and then
was just like you know what fuck it i'm done it says on his Wikipedia he's retired um but it's people
should retire in the acting game it's sad man it's sad to think like Gary Shanling's gone rip torn it's
a little easier to stomach because he was the elder of everybody yeah but you know
it's just this this is a tv show that was made at a time where where everybody wasn't needling
and nitpicking to see that every single character was redeemable and heroic at all times these people
are flawed Scott Thompson oh my god i must forgot he's amazing on the show um he plays that little
lyrical period theater down here all the time as buddy Cole he does monologues i go every time he's
so funny he's awesome man i've i've i kind of know him a little bit we still have the same manager he's
a really good guy and uh yeah i would i wish i could go see that i wish i was able to go go down
and watch that but he um but you know they make you know they make homophobic jokes they make racist
jokes they make not it's not the crux of the show they make sexist jokes why to illuminate the flaws
of these characters yeah uh there's purpose when somebody says something off base or out of line um
and there's not this thing of well then the audience will never like them again it's like no we're
we're we're we're gonna steer into the absurdity of a person's ignorance uh it's just an amazing
amazing show and depicts the industry fucking perfectly i mean it and it nails it man it nails it uh
you know in the last season when the ship starts going down like truly going down like
you really see the ship oh Odin Kirk's in it christ almighty play steve these killer on that as the
agent yeah yeah like god almighty and then not to mention the the weekly biggest stars on earth are
guest stars on the show um i would highly recommend Judd Apatow's book about Gary Shandling which of course
focuses a lot on his time on Larry Sanders and Gary was his mentor of course um the books great i
just bought it which i'm gonna rewatch the show soon as well i have the the blue rays of Larry Sanders
which are out of print and kind of worth a lot of money but they're all on max aren't they yeah
that's that's surprising actually they would keep that hanging in with everything they've cut
but um yeah if you're a fan of Shandling his book is awesome i recommend
i watched uh a rare Netflix show that i actually sat down and watched uh too much
Lena Dunham's new show i mean i'm on uh i finished seven out of ten now i know i know
Lena Dunham makes people mad i do think that is because of her weight a lot of the time it's because
of her in her black soul and her hard personality and her disgusting demeanor
well i think a lot of its weight uh i really do maybe not for you but for a lot of people that's
really where they go they criticize it i'll cite her latest post uh but i'll go ahead finish please
go ahead look do i agree with everything she said absolutely not um they they do love taking her
words at a context and shit too um i just think she's a genius writer when i rewatched girls over
the pandemic i got it i always liked the first couple of years and not the second but i realized
she's judging these characters too just like on Larry Sanders and i think and i'm not i'm not saying
this at all to you Joe i'm saying that i think we go oh we love these Larry Sanders guys and their blind
spots and their racism and their sexism and on all this because it's real and when she posts
it when she writes about real young women and how self -absorbed and vapid and and awful they can be
we think why are she celebrating these characters and i think that there is a lot of sexism and a lot
of weird shit that goes against her and all the comments like didn't she molest her sister
it's like well she was trying to open up and share a personal story i didn't read that story i don't
know but it's like people just get an idea of you and they never let it go um i think girls is one
of the best written shows there is i think it's a and i don't i don't need people to explode i think
it's a better written show than sex in the city certainly or and just like that where they're killing
off characters and bringing them back because there's no quality control um her new show where they
killing off and bringing back what do you mean it's a very it's a very big thing on the internet that
where the in the first season this the only black character on the show um was crying because her
dad died then in season two her dad comes to dinner and he's played by billy d Williams and then in
season three she's there's a whole storyline where she starts sobbing because her dad died and it's like
they don't they don't even remember what they're doing with the characters season to season that
also means the executives are checked out the writers assistants checked out everybody's checked out it's
not good but um i will i loved her movie sharp stick or i certainly found it interesting nobody saw
that movie but it was basically about a borderline autistic mentally handicapped very young girl
who is seduced by the man whose children she's babysitting and uh it's disturbing but it feels real
and and really interesting you know i think her work is interesting so too much stars mega stalter
who's a funny internet personality she's funny on hacks but she's got three lines a week on hacks
i'm watching the first few episodes and i'm like this girl is not a star this show is not involving me
i'm not into it it was trying to be like uh nobody wants this like a romantic a modern romantic comedy
oh yeah pet oh my god i hate everything about this this girl fucking blows
all right all right i watched so try watching some of her stand up it is a fucking oh yeah yeah i
could not see in her stand up i've seen a few of her uh like vine type videos and i don't really
know much about her she's funny on hacks but she's below a supporting character on hacks true all right so
she is as the star i was like no she's not a star this doesn't work for four episodes i'm watching her
she you know she moves to London she falls in love with a guy there and it felt very kind of
generic rom -com a little bit of Lena Dunham's wit you know popping in um it's got her her mom is
played by Lena Dunham who does look very different now wait she's playing the girl you just
mentions mom correct they're fucking ten years apart of age i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm wrong sister
older sister who's like super depressed and bedridden okay it's pretty ballsy for
Lena Dunham to be like yeah i'll just be a bedridden slob on my own show uh Rita Wilson is the mother
i'm sorry i did mix that up and reaperlman as the grandmother now obviously i know what reaperlman
looks like i saw three episodes of this show google the actress and realized it was reaperlman she's got
a new face um no judgment just saying i didn't know it was her but for the most part it's a it's a
London set Bridget Jones style rom -com and it might have been pitched this way where Bridget Jones is
actually fat you know it's not it's not Renee Zellweger with an extra 10 pounds who plays the male
love interest what's his name he hang on he's an actor will sharp will sharp yeah from white lotus
and he's very likable so this is believable oh no yeah i mean sure and and it's you know there's a lot of
uh yeah there's a lot of that where you're kind of like well now wait a minute but
episode five so i'm at the point where i'm like why am i even finishing this i'm doing other things
i'm hardly paying attention to the show i i have a i have ocd and i like to complete things which is why
i don't like starting shows uh if i know i'm gonna bail i feel like i've given this thing so much time i
gotta finish it whatever then episode five hits the show every episode of the show has been a half
hour suddenly episode five is an hour i'm like god damn it this this episode of the show
shows how it should have been a movie because it it leveled me it show it goes back and forth between
her old relationship with a very subtly and realistically abusive toxic ex -boyfriend very subtle
it's not like you know the classic oh my asshole ex but like it's something that a lot of women deal
with this type of guy in a relationship and she meets this new guy he's exciting he's hot he's into
her she's having fun but the ghosts of her past relationship keep fucking up the new one
and they go back and forth between the old and the new the new the new boyfriends like i feel like
you're having an argument with somebody who isn't here and she is she's arguing with her previous
boyfriend i've been there baby i have been there too i have been in a relationship where the woman
is doing it to me i'm like you're screaming at me now and i've done nothing like what is this and
once you talk about it it's like sorry i thought you were gonna react like my ex did or whatever
it goes into how that fucks with you i'm living that now i am every day with my girlfriend trying to
be like pat you're scared you're wanting to run away you're afraid of getting left again you're
afraid of getting i talk myself through this every day uh it i look you you can judge away
i was a mess by the end of this i i had set my laptop down i'm sobbing freely sobbing we go into
episode six i'm crying the whole time episode seven i'm like is this the best show in years you know
i think episode five of that show which is called pink valentine uh obviously a comparison to blue
valentine um i think it's the best episode of tv i've seen in ages i freely admit and i hate when people
say it takes a while to get good i don't even know if you need to watch the first four episodes of the show
just watch episode five if you've ever struggled with this in your life where your past relationship
traumas are fucking up your good new relationship i can't imagine a scenario where this episode would not
absolutely blow you away um so i of course i i recommend it very highly i don't know how the show ends
i don't know if it ends well i've got three more to go but yeah it it's something and i i wish
Lena Dunham would kind of cut away some of her more annoying things although nobody's ever going to
love her who hates her now you know you can't really turn people's opinion on something i'm going
to go in on Lena Dunham she deserves to be hated she's a fucking rich girl that has zero
fucking concept of anything uh nobody she does have extreme talent though which is what i don't
fucking care she she's i'm not saying that to dismiss you i'm but it's like who gives a shit
so does Michael Richards he's a fucking idiot she's a fucking idiot she's a rich girl that grew up
that was handed everything she hit throws her weight around no pun intended she you know she
think done and done demanded to get the guns removed from the Jason born posters i mean she's
she does unlikable fucking thing after unlikable thing what's that yeah that she demanded that the studios
remove the guns from the Jason born subway posters because it was jar it was triggering and jarring
that's a big thing you can look it up that actually happened i mean i i believe you i i've never
heard of that well also like it doesn't even seem like she was a known entity when the born movies were
out she was there was past girls she was like i won't fucking work for this studio if you don't
fucking she sucks she absolutely fucking sucks it's one thing after the next but i'm going to just
point at her latest stupid fucking thing that she did to show yet another out of touch white woman
on this fucking planet because there seems to be an endless supply of them uh here's her quote
from variety i've been in hollywood at every size i've been a sample size whatever the fuck that
means uh i had my body change because of life illness aging menopause menopause sounds the same
as early but i don't know why maybe maybe she has early menopause from from illness i was like okay
well i don't know i don't know what she's been through i'm not going to certainly mock her for weight
i'm it's not my style if anybody has anything to say about any of my actors meaning on this show
try a bitch i'm going to be taking my hoops out ready to fight this stupid white bleeding heart
fucking liberal who's so on a mission to protect everybody doesn't even understand when she's being
racist when she's appropriating there's a comment under this from a black woman that says
sigh when is cause playing a black woman going to finally go out of style i'm gonna fight a bitch i'm
going to take my every white woman in america it's not everywhere they all appropriate black dialect
yes they do it's not ever it but it's not every and gay dialect you know it's it's it's it's a lot
it's a lot of people it's not every it's a lot but i'm just saying she's she's just this is just
this is what she does every fucking time she opens her mouth she said something stupid she's not
likable she's just not likable like and i would argue she doesn't have to be and she she's in
she's in one scene per episode of the show and i know you're not going to watch it and you don't have
to i'm just telling you this episode was extremely effective and well written and i think she's
very talented and if we were to not endorse the work of people in hollywood for being annoying
we would never watch a movie or a tv show ever again but but but my question i guess where i'm
getting a little confused with you is we just went in on Michael Richards for 30 minutes about
what a dislikeable awful asshole he is why does she why does she get this he's brilliantly
talented too like why does she get it well and i and i'm going to keep watching sign falls
until the day i die just like i'm going to watch her shows when they come out because she's a gifted
writer okay but i'm saying she sucks and you're allowed to say that i and i feel like you're holding
back on saying she sucks that's what i'm saying i feel like for some reason you don't want to say
she sucks because there might it might bite in the ass at some point not at all i have no chance
of ever working with lean to dunham she writes everything herself i just uh i think the vitriol
towards her is insane and i think a lot of it and i'm not saying you at all but i'm saying a lot of it
from a lot of people in the world is shut your fat mouth i really believe that and you can see that
in the comments because often the comments say shut your fat mouth um i don't know i i just i think
she's a gifted writer i think michael riches is a gifted actor i think roman polanski is a gifted
director you know like it's it's it's what it is i'm just telling you the shows good and as i said
i wish lean to dunham would cut away some of the more annoying aspects of her personality which led
to this discussion but it's not going to make me boycott her work or something because that episode
deeply affected me and i thank her for making it i don't think you should boycott her work i just
think you should join me on piling on and she said oh i can join you in saying she's annoying and
says some stupid fucking shit absolutely that's awesome now now her saying i'm going to defend my actors
doesn't bother me at all no the whole my hoops thing the hold my hoops whatever is like
if you know i i thought that about people i've dated i thought that about friends of mine where it's
like could you stop this i'm a middle -aged black woman thing that you're doing because it's not a
good look on you or could you stop that yes honey or yes queen or whatever else it's like
i don't think all gay people love that you're doing that either you know i get i think we just you know
i've got maybe a bigger threshold of pain with her actions but the only time you ever hear what she
has to think is when she has a project out so you know it doesn't bug me the uh the uh what was
going to say that doesn't matter all right uh what i was going to say doesn't matter not what you
said doesn't matter um i i will do well let's do one more and then get to the movie but uh uh this
is connected to Larry Sanders i watched uh rewatched modern romance which i do think is the greatest it
is romantic comedy ever made uh i think you're gonna say best out at Brooks but yeah it's it is the best
Aber Brooks as well uh but it stars Catherine Harold who also starred as one of Larry's ex -wives
on uh uh Larry Sanders um simple story movies begins with a breakup scene a very funny breakup scene
and then it follows the trajectory of a guy who goes through all the emotions post breakup
which lead to the get back together which lead to him being way too insecure once they are back
together leading to him acting in greater extremes to try to save the relationship thinking
that they're that's what's gonna make them turn the corner uh at his own expense Aber Brooks comes
off a bit like look i don't want to say crazy but obsessive in this uh not in a funny way even he
he's really he's relatable and recognizable but he's uh he's crazy in that movie he's having a hard
time and uh yeah and then that's and that's kind of where the comedy comes from um the uh i would say
her Catherine's character is it's i wouldn't i would say it's pretty not very full what are you
now there's not really any flaws it's this is really from the perspective of like this one person
spiraling out after a breakup that he wanted and i can relate a hundred percent to it i can relate
to being in that place where you're like this isn't working i don't feel good we're causing each other
a lot of pain uh just emotionally because we we're not in sync we need to end this and then you feel
terrible and you go what did i do and did i just send the only person that will ever love me out of my
life and so on and so forth um you know it's there's there's there's a there's a very quick scene in
Annie Hall where uh he when he says the dead you know the famous dead shark line and he breaks up with
her on the airplane and then it cuts immediately and he's in the street in New York and he walks up
to a stranger and he goes i feel really bad i think i made a big mistake it is that extreme it's
you're you're in one moment feeling like this is the most sound and healthy thing for both of us to
do for one another and then in the next moment you're just like what have i done it's the regret
is so immediate it's it's incredible to me it's incredible to me i had a joke in my act about it
about like it's it's like it's like going into it's like going into a Chinese buffet when you're really
hungry like like that's the breakup it this seems like a great idea right now this is what we need to
do and an hour later you're like this was a mistake i feel terrible uh i have i'm sleepy i feel
fucking awful so uh and it could be any buffet people all right it doesn't have to be shiny uh but
Chinese is the funniest because of all the sugar yet anyway um i just love the movie so much uh
i actually watched it with my ex -girlfriend right before we broke up uh and we both found it very
relatable um i'm surprised you even referred to it as a romantic comedy i would say it's an unromantic
comedy really it's it's about the opposite of romance but yeah it's a masterpiece well i mean
they're together through most of the movie and it's you know oh that's true and they end up together
in the end i mean it's you know but i don't think it's a happy ending to me anyway the um they're showing
this week i'm i'm going with my girlfriend to see uh lost in america mod and romance double feature
which i'm just very very pumped about at the numerally um all right 28 years later uh
let's let's get into it uh let's get into it joe and i have already fought about this um it got
out of control on the 4th of july we passed it up you wouldn't have wanted to listen to it it wasn't
funny but we got through it and and we always get through it because we have grown and if somebody could
point out to me what win our official 10 -year anniversary of this podcast is i know it's this year
isn't it or was it last year i think it's this year uh let me know because we we should do something
although i have this sinking feeling it's probably already passed but um yeah the way joe and i handle
our conflict now is really a lesson in growth we're better about things we misunderstood each other
we were quick to apologize and patch things up but um we i don't think have been this
diametrically opposed on an issue maybe since the r aster pictures um 28 years later
is you know i've had several people ask me oh if i haven't what if i haven't seen the other ones
or what if i didn't haven't seen them in 20 years you don't need to see them the only thing you need to
know is that uh it's a rage virus although it's clearly just zombies they transfer their virus
by bleeding into one of your orifice as a mouth i knows getting their blood on you etc um and that's
about it because this is kicking off a new trilogy it's got nods i guess to the other two movies but
to me i went in expecting a lesser sequel to a couple of really strong b plus zombie movies that i
enjoyed 20 years ago i recently rewatched them i found them to be uh maybe not as at not as great as i
remembered but being solid entertainments they look like shit um especially the original is like
a really bad looking movie um this one to me was a spectacular looking movie it's the return of
Danny Boyle who i forgot could even be a good director and it is the best of the 28 movies to me and
i think this is where i said joe off it is the best movie of the year um just it is just an insane state
basically i and i don't know what else would be number two i mean i mean they're not far off on
letter box i haven't given out a single five star all year i gave this four and a half and i
gave ugly four i did think it was bad i mean it's it's big epic action filmmaking and horror film
making with a pulse and with a soul and i found myself tearing up at it and getting emotionally
invested in it in a way i didn't expect um basically it's three small movies the first is what's
that guy's name the guy who's married to the old woman Andrew Taylor Johnson right oh
something like that kick kickass yeah kickass yeah Aaron Taylor Johnson uh who's very likeable and
i don't know how his star never really took off he's great in bullet train which is a good move we've
absolutely shit on him many times but this bullet bullet train change me up on him i was like oh this guy
is good he's never been given a good role but i like him this is one of the first movies i've seen him
it well i like to be kickass but this is one of the first movies i've seen him in as a grown man that
where i was like oh okay he's doing a good job i mean i was rolling my eyes when he came on screen
because he was terrible and not faradu and i was like oh forgot he was even in that you know
god we got to do this with this guy but anyway yeah it's it's him and his son uh going off to
hunt zombies in the beginning well there's basically they're they're they're they're in the quarantine
camp there's an area that's been that's important there's a camp there's a area in England or whatever
that was quarantined when all this happened uh there's the mainland surrounding it that's
essentially the wild west and then there's this camp where they all live and are rebuilding a small
society and part of that rebuild is when you become a man of a certain age you have to learn how to go
hunt zombies not to hunt them for fun but because they still have to go into the mainland to scavenge for
supplies so you have to know how to defend yourself so he's gonna bring his kid two years too early
the kids only 12 you're not supposed to do it till you're 14 uh just a pointless detail
the like to but there's no point in being younger in fact it hurts the story but anyway you have to
you have to go into the mainland the only way to get to the mainland is to walk across this very long
natural bridge whatever you would call it remember it's like a stretch of whatever
and you have to do it at low tide because at high tide the bridge gets covered in water a rule that
they defy not once but twice in the movie after telling you that once the water comes up you can't get
back in your trapped and then it happens and they just run through the water um but anyway he's
taking the kid right to the mainland and then so so but keep keep going I didn't mean to cut you off
I just the that's fine I'm just basically laying out the basics of the plot it's it's it's essentially
three acts and it almost feels like three different stories because it's the dad and the son there
are gonna be spoilers here the son which I thought was a great piece of screenwriting the son breaks away
from his dad and then takes their mentally unstable mom out into the wilderness now I
have heard criticism of why would why would this kid do this because he's 12 and he's stupid but
they give him an even stronger reason because the mom is unwell the father cheats and goes down
on a woman and the son sees it and he's like well fuck this guy I'm taking my mom and getting away
from him to me that completely explains it kids are stupid and emotional and irrational and everyone
saying well no kid would ever go out and do that I'm like well this kid did you know they're telling a
story that that helps propel the reason but that's not the reason the reason is is because he believes
there's a doctorer on them in in the danger in the mainland that he can put his money to that's he
no longer trusts his father after that you know the father's like he's not he's not even a doctor he's
nuts don't worry and he's like I think my dad is lying so that he can go get some strange to me that
it's completely explained like to me I had no issues with anything story wise certainly compared to
other horror movies and action movies I've seen I thought it was a model of you know clarity really
but the mom and the son then go out on their own and then they have adventures and then eventually they
meet this doctor who was described as odd up you know also insane and it winds up being a pretty
normal guy a doctor a jack's doctor played by Ray finds who you know diagnosis the mother and helps
them out and there you go there's basically three acts to the movie and then there's sort of a
post thing where that's setting up the the next entries in the trilogy the second one will be directed
by the woman who did candy man remake and I'm not sure about the third to be honest with you but
I know that I'm pumped to see them I know I wish Danny Boyle was directing all of them because I think
he's got his groove back with this movie and basically I just found it scary and exciting and
suspenseful and visually cool and I love the soundtrack and I love the acting and I loved everything
about it and though this argument never works I you know I get on letter box and see all my friends
feel the same and I'm talking to them about it and I was honestly thrown by Joe's not just dislike
but extreme hatred of this film because we're we're rarely this opposed it's not a good movie
it's just not a good movie it is a movie that is fully derivative of a million other things
that makes it not good the the the counter argument that anybody would make to that is well I don't
know those things so I don't know what your time it's like no bullshit for the same argument I made
we haven't I don't play the last of us so I don't care and I didn't like the show but but even my
girlfriend is a bit of a game but it doesn't mean it's not true it doesn't mean it's not true it's
people it's the same thing as people going on to the going on to YouTube and saying the take this
chair joke in the naked gun trailer is brilliant and then people like us go no it's not it's a
fucking joke from 1934 that you did worse than the original which was in a three stoogeous short
there it's not a valid thing to say well I don't know the thing you're talking about
therefore it doesn't apply it does apply the last of us was derivative of 28 days later the walking
dead was derivative of 28 days later great 28 days later started a new thing it was original whether
I liked it or not is is irrelevant it was not bad it was original it is now spawned all this other
stuff and just like Stephen King's it the the 2015 where whenever the hell that came out was
took all this stuff and we heavily criticized it for this took all this stuff that was derivative
of it like stranger things and whatever else and then just mimicked the stuff that copied the original
IP this did the same exact thing why is there a 12 year old kid well because there's a 12 year old
kid in the last of us that has to go and what and what is the journey of the kid well they've got to
get the kid from point A to point B and the only way to do it is by going through this super dangerous
terrain that that whatever and it's got to be and somehow the kid is magically able to navigate it
whenever it's the same fucking story it's just the same story it's not interesting there were
two or three genuinely like like horror moments in this I would say I thought the thing in the
in the woods was interesting where the zombies were kind of crawling up to them I thought that part
was cool the part where there's the guy hanging upside down in the with the blood bag on his head
or whatever I thought that was kind of cool I love the pregnant zombie and deciding whether we're
not we have to kill the baby and all that I love that right pregnant zombie was done in army of the
dead they just did it in army of the dead the Zack Snyder movie yes it's yes that's in literally
in army of the dead the out movie was fucking awful yeah but I don't but I think I think our
disagreement is really that to me a movie can be derivative on original most movies are all movies
are influenced and inspired by something and it can still be good no I don't think you know a movie
that is influenced by something else has to be bad it's not influence it's taking scraps of other
movies and using them and not having an original story those are two different things influence is
the ugly step sister looking like a giallo film that's influence this is not influence this is we
took things that were already done because we didn't have a better idea for a script and I'll give
you another one the alpha zombie that's from land of the dead and it was stupid in land of the dead
and it was stupid in this it's stupid I fucking loved it I I love that he had a giant dick I love
that he is this this giant weird thing and everybody in the theater was laughing I mean to me the movie
was crazy it was nuts at a time when no movies are crazy and nuts so it felt new and exciting
and bracing to me admittedly I haven't seen this stuff now my girl probably the last of us she's
like yeah I guess I could see how there's similarities to it she loves the last of us the show and
the game she's like I guess I could see that but to me zombie is a a a specific sub genre of horror
that will always have elements of other zombie movies because zombies have rules and there's
not that much you can do with them except I thought this movie did a ton with them maybe they've
been done before I guess I would say this did it better you know land of the dead is a movie I don't
remember watching I thought it was awful let me let me army of the dead was worse but so like
let me explain why zombies evolving especially in this movie makes zero fucking sense zombies are
based on lizard brain animals they're they're fully lizard brain they're not mammalian zombies are
not mammalian they're lizard brain they're snakes they're crocodiles they're alligators they only know attack
attack attack attack that's all they do the fact that you're going to try to make a version of it
where a where theoretically an alligator starts to become more aware and what it is is absurd
and in this and in this movie especially it's counteract productive because the whole point is
is this virus deteriorates your brain completely so so then you're going to evolve re -evolve it's
just it doesn't make any sense whatever we could that's that's a besides the point argument there
is other issues I had with the movie his dad being the the kids dad being a priest at the beginning
in the cold open who so so there's a kid at the beginning of the movie in the cold open
it's and it's it's the cold open takes place in the 28 days later time period it's as the outbreak
is starting which I thought was kind of cool a little kid runs his his house gets rated and
and everybody's getting killed by the zombies whatever and his mom says run and you know get to your
father he runs to his dad who's a priest which just like all right guys I guess the symbolism I don't
fucking know this is just confusing this kid is calling a priest his dad this is confusing whatever
the priest then does this whole thing where he welcomes the zombies to kill him because he
thinks it's the rapture and the great day of judgment and he will now be ascending into heaven and
this is God's plan and whatever as he does all this he also desperately makes sure that his kid can
hide and be safe so so that part makes no sense if that's what you think this happening have your
kid get eaten too and you will all ascend and this is it doesn't make sense the the kid it
then jumps forward 28 years later uh this is just a writing device I don't I can't say this is a
flaw of the movie it is very confusing though you don't know who that kid is you're like is that
Alan is Alan Taylor Johnson the kid or like wait wait wait a minute what's wait a minute okay you're
trying to figure that doesn't matter turns out at the very end the kid is this guy Jimmy who runs this
uh you know this band of pirates or whatever the fuck you want to call it out in the wasteland
who end up scooping up and and and and and bringing in the the the main kid from the movie that we've
been talking about but but let's go back just to when it jumps to 28 years later when you meet the
kid and the dad and the mom who's sick you find out later she has cancer the mom being sick to me
was confusing because I'm like wait does she have the rage thing because she's acting crazy but she's
well I think that was you know supposed to be what you think and then when you realize it's cancer when
Ray finds diagnosis her look I heard a lot of sniffling in the theater and there was some coming out of
my own nose I did not expect to have an emotional connection but I thought that stuff was really moving
and I think you're just talking about them trying to to make you think maybe she was or you
or I think you are supposed to think who is this little boy in the movie and then when you find out
who he is at the end I was like oh cool I love this new character and I assume he'll be in part two
and they're all based on Jimmy Savile which is weird their their gang is based on Jimmy Savile the
now disposed pedophile of the BBC I guess that's going to be some kind of symbolism later or whatever
but like they were supposed to look like him I I didn't catch it when I saw it but then when I was
reading about the movie online it was like yeah he he leads this like little cult that's based
on Jimmy Savile that's odd I wonder if there are molesters them but maybe it means they're going
maybe it's because they represent the church and there's yeah I don't know maybe that maybe
the priest thing will be justified later I don't know my biggest issue with this movie was and I will
say it one last time and then I will shut up I felt like it told a very unoriginal story the and
and I will be specific the idea of the child and the adult having to get through the wasteland
in order to achieve a goal whether it's to get medicine or because one of them has the antidote in
their body or whatever we've just seen it so many times its children of men it's I am legend it's the
last of us it is a story that has been told ad nauseam at this point in within a genre that is
fully exhausted of anything new or interesting or whatever and then I won't recite all the other
things that were completely derivative is the movie well constructed sure is it a well told story
sure it it serves zero purpose in my opinion I just I just was like you've got to be kidding me we're
just doing all of this all over again I guess okay cool and a new trilogy because we need more
bloat from Hollywood to you know god forbid they just make one and say we're just finishing up or
no it's got to be this you know it is it is pretty balzy to call your shot in this day and age because
this movie very well could not have done well and then they would have been fucked I am surprised they
did it that way for me you know I've seen all those movies you mentioned I've seen half a season of
Garland who wrote this and Alex Garland is a writer who can be brilliant ex Mahina he can also be
really really bad like you know men the 824 horror movie men one of the worst movies I've ever seen
you know he never know what you're gonna get he also did civil war and then warfare which I didn't see
and he you know a lot of his movies are like we're going from A to Z you know the 28 franchise does feel
a lot like civil war and they're an entirely different genres I think he rips himself off to some
degree he also publicly said the gold standard for this kind of thing is the last of us any zombie movie
going forward that I'm talking about the game not the show any zombie anything going forward is gonna
owe a massive debt to last of us because that's the gold standard so to me you know in a world with
you know Tarantino being the best example of it but everything being derivative there are no new
stories in Hollywood at a certain point it didn't bug me in the slightest I mean to me going to see
my 50th superhero movie of the year where every story is exactly the same and it ends with giant
people who can't be killed punching each other and you can't tell who's hitting who I was delighted to
have a movie that was for two hours suspenseful exciting gave me characters I cared about gave me
characters that when they died I got emotional which hasn't happened in about 10 years for me and I
got to just give it props you know freely admitting I have not played the last of us I've seen all these
other zombie things we're talking about some more memorable than others but a story of a father and
son who need to get from A to Z and there's a lot of danger along the way that's a story as old as
time and to me they you know they say there are only six stories in Hollywood and it's the way you tell
it I thought this movie told it fantastically I loved the super imposing of like old war footage and
stuff I didn't quite know it was going on at first but then I really got into just the vibe of it
and I remembered for the first time in 20 plus years that Danny Boyle can be a fucking kickass
filmmaker when he wants to be so you know it's not the end of the world pun intended when two people
disagree on things but there is something odd about how intensely we disagreed and that might just be
that it exactly mimics the last of us to a point that you couldn't deal with and I haven't seen it
so no no no it's not it's not that it exactly mimics the last of us to a point I couldn't deal with
it's that every element of the movie mimics something else that's already been done like this the
argument you're making is an argument you have contradicted yourself it's it's it's a I don't say
this offensively into you Joe by the way but but but there's so many times you've looked past something
being highly derivative but you know okay give me give me an example well Joe I could go through
the 10 years of things I mean this movie you said I I will never see this fucking movie never
then you had to get an oil change so you go see it yeah you're not gonna like that movie yeah I
was enjoying it for the first 15 to 20 minutes when they're walking across the thing and it's
doing the war footage and I did understand what it was I thought that that was fucking awesome and
I was like this movie is gonna be awesome and then they do the whole thing where the zombies are
sneaking up on them in the forest and the kid gets the headshot I was like I'm into this yeah I'm into
this and then the second they have to get back because the shit hits the fan and the bridge gets
covered in water they break immediately the rule that they set up before they leave which is
you can't get back once the tide comes in so but they did I mean sometimes somebody says something
can't be done and then you do it that that's that's storytelling I just I don't get it you know like
if they said that it's completely impossible and there's now you know like but they did it because
there are heroes and and every action movie in the dawn of time nobody can survive the gauntlet
and then they serve the gauntlet but that's not but that's very mad about that I'm not mad Pat
it's I'm not mad why are you bothered by that because it's bad writing would you mean why my bothered
what why are you curious about the Michael Richards book you did an hour fucking rant on it but show
just listen to the one thing I'm saying here every movie nobody every Clint Eastwood movie every
look at the gauntlet nobody can get through the gauntlet but that's Clint Eastwood can and that's the
excitement but Pat I get that but that's not the purpose that that serves it's not your climactic
task or challenge that's not what that is it's it's a moment that happens within the first act of
the movie and you're like wait a minute they just said that they can't get back if the water
company they could just run through the water like and I guess maybe the point was it's not fully
up and they're barely gonna make it back whatever it's fine but my point is this to that was
the first part where I was like okay we might have a we might have a problem here this is a little
all right I don't know and I said they're awesome they made it what's coming next like that it's
just a different way to watch a movie like I went in like I like the other two and I'm excited
to see where this goes and I had a blast I don't it's just certain things bother different people
I guess but like I was completely invested I never questioned anything in it that's all I can
say it just worked for me I've never seen a giant tower of skulls but maybe it's been in something
before I didn't say that that was incredible visual I didn't say I didn't again I didn't say you
did say that was in there Joe I'm saying I've never seen that before and you're saying everything
in the movie is derivative I've never seen a tower of skull don't be a shit you know what I mean
when I say everything in the movie is derivative obviously there's things in the movie so then why
can't I point out some things that weren't and I'm saying I'm pointing out everything that was I'm
pointing out things that weren't and I'm saying I never saw that either I'm but it but it doesn't
make it a good movie it's it's a set piece it's like I thought it was a great movie and I thought
that every set piece felt exciting and new and you thought it all felt derivative right that's okay
and I'm sure and I'm sure that because this but this is what I love about your personal don't make
I see you go in there don't make it personal because it's not you see me go in there what the hell
are you talking about that's making it personal no you just said to me I went in with a chip on my
shoulder so there's no way I could have liked it so I will say back to you it couldn't have been that
you were in a great mood on July 4th on the date with a woman that you very much care about and maybe
that let you have a little more enjoyment out of the movie and think it was a little better than it
actually was can't that be a two -way street that's not sure sure all right what's always going to say
that's it I think the movie sucks I think it's a quality film in and of itself but I think the reason
it sucks is because it's just taken everything from from everything else and I will stand by that argument
and it will be the same argument that people make about the naked gun being really good when somebody
like you or me who actually knows comedy knows film knows jokes will watch that and say this sucks
because every single part of it or I shouldn't say every single excuse me that's hyperbole but a lot
of it most of it I've seen it before it's just taken from other things and I don't care that's my
argument I think that's a very fair argument it is and that's it you know that's where I stand on
movie my hog is my hog is is a zombie and not an evolving one my hog is diamond hard as though
I took a double blue chew before going into the film I just to me it's one of the best horror action
movies in the past couple years I had a great time with it and I thought it was exciting and fun and
gory and crazy and insane in a really great way that felt fresh and new to me we will what are
we doing Joe we're doing bloodlines yeah final destination bloodlines and then we picked the fourth
no it could be Superman it could be bring her back it could be I would say it's most likely going
to be either Superman or bring her back but but who knows it could be it could be anything I've
I've been gently avoiding bring her back it's just the the subject matter is a little grim for for sure
the way I've been feeling and I'm like I don't know that I want to see a movie about a dead
daughter being brought back to life right now but but it's supposed to be great and I do want to see
it yeah I love that one and it did just hit streaming we may do it we may not we may do mission
possible we may not but we'll definitely do final destination bloodlines um I am at the
Patrick Walsh on Instagram we are at CU and Helpod on Instagram September 24th the airplane to the
sequel 4k will be released and I do a commentary track on that 4k which is my first and hopefully not
my last uh you can pre -order that I believe starting today and uh that's it for me Joseph
that's it same plugs as last time please check out the special July 21st on my youtube at Joe
Derosa Comedy uh if you want to see it early go to disruptor comedy .com you can pay I think it's
eight bucks seven bucks uh if you want to watch it uncensored uh and commercial free I say uncensored
and commercial free we we're probably gonna have to do some bleeping when it hits youtube because
they're really just what hitting hard with the monetization stuff lately so yeah I know what does
that mean you can't like well nobody under 17 could watch it then or buy it no it's just like on
YouTube though like you know if there's curse words within the first X amount of minutes you get
demonetized it's it's a lot of shit man that's weird but anyway I I'm hoping we can get it on to
youtube with zero bleeps uh I think that we will be able to because most people do but my point is if
you want to see it early and you want to see it without fail and add interruption or something go see
it now on disruptor .com tour dates at Joe Derosa Comedy as I said in August I'll be in Rhode Island
and Denver and then so on and so forth uh we appreciate you all listening we'll see you all next time
and we'll see you in hell