I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, and when the sound of your screams becomes
a thing of my dreams, you know I'll say, I'll see you in hell, you know I will, I'll see
you in hell, you know I will.
Folks, welcome to We'll See You In Hell.
You can hear the boominess in the room.
I got a little natural reverb going.
Why?
Because it's the start of the big boomy month of October.
Halloween, horror, fun, candy, a boom.
Just a weird way to kick things off.
Why is it boomy?
You have a new mic?
We haven't worked out the kinks?
No, it is a new mic.
It's not the mic.
I'm in my condo in Austin, Texas, and it's a very concrete type of place, and you know,
it's just a big old room, so it's a little echoey.
High ceilings, no rugs, you know, how bad is the boom?
It's fine, it's fine.
Have you seen the Costco guys on Instagram reels, TikTok?
They do a song called Here Comes the Boom.
Well, undoubtedly, the masterwork of Kevin James.
Well, it's different.
Somehow they either act like they never heard of Here Comes the Boom, or they're doing their
own thing, but it's like, it's actually We Bring the Boom, probably to avoid copyright
infringement.
Yeah, because that movie was based on a song called Here Comes the Boom.
Remember?
Here comes the boom, here comes the boom.
Oh, yeah.
Ready or not, that was saliva, right?
Something like that, yeah.
Here comes the boom.
Terrible song.
And then the new one, so these Costco guys, I don't know how they came into my radar,
but now if I get on the internet, I see them.
It's a dad and his 10 -year -old or so boy, and they walk around Costco and give things
either a boom or a doom.
And it's really bad content.
It's not funny.
You get a strong impression the dad is abusing the son.
The kid eats something called a chicken bake.
That's his go -to.
And then the dad, they cut to him four or five times a video going, double chocolate
chip cookie.
And then he takes a bite out of a double chocolate chip cookie.
I know this sounds like the stupidest shit you've ever heard of.
It's worse.
They have their own original music.
It's really bad.
They do collaborations with other Costco celebrities.
It's really rough stuff.
It's enough.
Well, hold on.
First of all, I want to respond to exactly what you were just talking about.
But just to backpedal for a moment.
I would like to apologize for my terrible intro.
And I also would like to come to expect it.
I'd also like to make clear.
That I do not seriously think here comes the boom is Kevin James's masterwork.
I was trying to be a smart ass.
As far as Kevin James movies go, I guess it's one of the better ones.
But did you see it?
I watched most of it.
OK, you know, it's like an MMA fighter.
Yeah, and it's not what you want.
If they if you if I told you during the King of Queens years.
Yeah. Hey, dude, there's a movie for Joe.
Better years, better years, but they were.
But if I said to you, hey, dude,
Kevin James has a movie coming out where you place an MMA fighter.
You're laughing immediately.
Yeah, I would have gone.
I didn't go at the time, but King of Queens years, I would have gone.
And you're like, the joke was more open minded then.
These were just better years.
But also, too, you'd assume the joke is, oh, he's out of shape.
Yeah. And that's the gag.
And it's like, no, no, that movie, like he does get into shape.
Yeah. And he they actually had to write it into the into the show.
Like in season six, all of a sudden, carries like, look at my new man,
because he's like, he's not really fat anymore.
And then he gets fat again. Thank God.
Yeah, I saw that's another clip
that for some reason always comes upon my my feet is Kevin James
talking to Joe Rogan, just a couple couple brain trusts.
And Joe Rogan's like, how?
Do you lose weight?
You know, Kevin James is probably 350 pounds in the video.
Seen that clip.
And he goes, you know, the crazy thing is he goes in 40 days.
I could be down to 200.
I like to do like a 40 day fast.
That's why is he telling the truth?
I don't know, but he seems to be serious and like believing that he does this.
And it's like, Kevin, James, I've never seen you look like
you haven't eaten in 40 days.
Let's give me a break.
I I believe it because he does.
If you can see in movies and again on the show,
he fluctuates hard, like he goes way up.
And way down.
And I think he's an all or nothing guy.
Yeah. Kind of the worst guy to be.
That was a great I listened that whole episode as a stand up comic.
I might have appreciated more than the average listener
because they talk so much about stand up.
But it was a great episode because they really got into like
the road and like starting out and all that.
I thought I thought I found it very interesting.
I mean, he had how long was he a stand up before King of Queens came along?
It seems like I saw the one special and then he was a big star.
That special is after King of Queens came out already.
It's like after the first or second season, I think a while.
You know, back then you would do stand up for like.
You know, around the five to eight year mark or maybe ten year mark,
you'd get the Montreal gig and you would get a development deal if you were good.
And, you know, people were getting shows 10 years in at that point.
You know, that's not the case anymore.
But, yeah, you didn't have to be, you know, they used to take a guy
like a Kevin James who nobody knew, and they would be like, you're funny
and we think you might have a show in you.
And they develop a show around the guy.
And if it hit great, like he wasn't famous before King of Queens.
You know, like that's what they would never do do that now.
They would never be like, let's take this no name
and build a show around them.
They'd be like, let's take this no name who only has 800000 Instagram followers.
Yeah. And then they want the no name to make the full name for themselves
and then leech off the 10 years of work that went into it.
Yeah, exactly. So.
But back to you, which leads me right back perfectly to your Instagram thing
or your tick tock people, the daddy and son.
Yeah. Go bros. Call them by their name.
It's it's.
It's so disturbing.
It's like this is what content is now.
It's like you see these pages.
I mean, I'm not saying anything nobody doesn't know.
But it's like, you know, these pages, these accounts where it's like,
you know, my loud mom, four billion followers.
And it's just clips of somebody's mom being like,
did you get the groceries again? Yeah.
Mom, why are you so loud?
Why are you so loud?
Are you taping me?
And you're like, and then they'll book them at the stress
factory in New Jersey for eight sold out shows.
Beetlemania outside in the parking lot.
She's going to be a bitch.
Yeah, it's a it's a dark time.
It's a dark time.
I I have a fun, brief little activity for us to do here.
So I had been off the apps, the dating apps.
Basically, in the words of Tyler Perry said,
you know what? I can do bad all by myself.
All right. And I was off.
I just it just came to me.
Sometimes I make myself laugh, you know?
Yeah, I laugh. And that's and that's nice.
But yeah, I was like, I'm going to give it another shot.
Just just walking up to ladies saying hello, whatever.
And I was doing that kind of my heart wasn't in it.
I just finally realized, like, I don't even want to be in a relationship.
I have no interest.
And the other day, I'm pulling the apps off my phone.
So I'm not ever tempted at a lonely moment or something.
And I realized that I had paused my hinge membership, but not canceled it.
So I still had like three months of juice on it. Yep. Yep.
And I'm like, well, I can't let her go to waste, you know.
But I'm like, Pat, unless you see like something amazing
or there's some great connection that pops up, don't go out on these
like killing time, but also dropping two hundred dollar dates.
You know, it's fucking stupid. Yeah.
And sure enough, there's a
very attractive young woman on here, lives in my neighborhood.
She's talking about the American
Cinematheque and like the local movie theaters.
That's her bread and butter.
That's what she likes to do.
And honestly, the amount of like old movies I go to see alone
at like 10 p .m. or something, I'm like, yeah, that'd be real nice
to have, you know, a partner to go to some movies with.
Maybe we hook up and whatever else.
I'm going to hit this girl up.
I do. We start talking, starts talking about how much she loves multicam sitcoms.
She's like, I know that's not really in fashion or whatever.
I'm like, that's what I do.
I don't put that shit in my profile because I don't want actresses
trying to date me to get a part.
I don't even mention it. So.
We're talking and just hitting it off and about the format.
And she does this really cool program.
I won't get into specifics, but like, you know, a pro bono type program
with people here in L .A. and just, you know, great sparkling banter going to town.
And she goes, well, let's go to a movie.
She goes, I think it'd be fun to go to like a late night movie.
It's spooky season. We get a drink beforehand.
I'm like, I love it. It sounds great.
So I send her the schedule for the Cinematheque.
I'm like, see, see what tickles your fancy in the next few weeks.
She comes back. Oh, my God.
I really want to see drag me to hell.
My friend said that's a lot of fun.
It was like a 10 p .m.
Drag me to hell with a couple of drinks.
This sounds like a dream.
We plan it. The date is happening in about 48 hours.
And this morning, right before I got on here with you, Joe,
I'm looking back through a profile because sometimes you don't read every word.
Want to make sure, you know, it's not like they have four kids or something.
And you're like, oh, oh, OK.
That's a different scenario that I was ready for.
I'm looking, everything's looking good.
No problems.
She's looking for a long term relationship.
Liberal, you know, I'm going through.
I'm like, all right, I like this.
Don't have children, want children, blah, blah, blah.
And then I hit.
What type of relationship she's in and looking for.
She's that she's into non monogamy. OK.
And I know this is becoming more and more commonplace, but.
She's she's not non monogamy, so I'm like, OK.
So that means if I get into a relationship with this girl,
we probably have are going to have to have some sort of conversation
about like dating other people.
Look, maybe that'd be good for me at this time in my life.
I've always felt like I couldn't handle that, but who knows?
I'm like, all right.
Then below it, it says.
Kitchen table slash semi nested.
What's that mean?
Joe, it's exactly what my question was.
And together on the podcast, we are going to find out
what I have gotten myself at.
I guess table E &M, so maybe some guesses first.
My thinking at first, I misread it as kitchen sink.
Like, I thought like that means like, I'll fuck animals.
I'll fuck fucking everybody.
But it says kitchen table.
When you said kitchen table,
I thought it was going to be like kitchen table, wherever you're able.
Like meaning like, I like to fuck all over the place.
Sure, great.
But I don't I have a feeling that's not what this is.
No, because the next words were semi nested.
Semi nest.
So semi nested is the is the part that's sort of clear to me.
That seems to me like, OK, she lives with a boyfriend or girlfriend.
But then why semi? Aren't you nested?
Aren't you nested?
Yeah, I don't I don't
I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know.
I don't know what any of it means anymore.
I've been liked by multiple women on a dating app
who all identify as queer in their profile.
I don't understand some of that as well, Joe.
And I'm like, am I just do I look feminine?
You know, I guess queer can also mean.
No, queer just means queer, right?
That's what I thought.
I asked my friend Caitlin, she said, no, queer, queer
can mean you're still under the opposite sex.
I was like, what the hell are we talking about?
Hi, I'm straight. Now, I will suck a cock.
It is weirdly like becoming this thing where it's anything but straight.
Like because they like letters keep getting added to LBGTQ.
You know, they keep there is like more letters now, which is fine.
There's plus A plus.
Yeah, but it is starting to feel a little bit like anything but straight.
And I'm like, well, I guess I should just stop saying straight.
I'll start saying demis.
Demisexual. Yeah, is demisexual.
They like you for your brain only.
That's sapiosexual.
That's one a woman told me a woman told she she matched me.
I was like, wow, that's a good looking lady.
And I look at her profile and says she's sapiosexual.
And I look it up and it's like they're only attracted to intellect.
And then I was kind of like, well, shit, now I'm offended that you liked me.
And by the way, a hats off to a hats off to Sir Mix a lot,
breaking down the gender identity walls,
never getting any credit with baby got back.
He was laying out his it was laying out his identity right there.
Yeah, I have long said that.
And and and I don't want to get off this because I really do want to look up and
what this stuff means.
But when I would that song came out in 91, you know, I would have been a little boy.
And I remember me and my friends kind of laughing about it, giggling about it.
A, the video had giant butts in it, you know, the big fake butt,
and as well as real ones.
But the thinking amongst me and everyone in my nine year old peer group
at the playground was, can you believe this guy likes a fat ass?
Can you believe this guy would be into like two shapely buttocks
fighting under a tight skirt?
Yeah, because just the norm at the time was like anything resembling
a little weight on a woman was just considered the worst.
So the ideal and you see this in, you know, if you're watching Married with Children
and they bring in an extra to have everybody hoot and holler,
that's going to be a playboy centerfold more than likely.
But outside of Playboy centerfolds, the ideal was like a woman
that was built like a plank.
Yeah. And he shits.
He shits on all that through the whole song.
And the video was banned from MTV.
And I promise you, it was not banned because it was too salacious of a video.
It was banned because they were like, yeah, how dare this?
It was racist. I think it was racism, frankly.
But how dare this guy on MTV?
Yeah, no, it's I'm completely with you.
That song is there's something kind of beautiful about it.
And I'm sure that women appreciated the song as well, for Christ's sake.
Like, oh, finally, someone who likes me for me with my giant ass.
By the way, now.
There's nothing I love more than a giant ass, really matured in that way.
So I have looked up kitchen sink, I'm sorry, kitchen table polyamory.
It means a style of polyamory in which all partners and metas.
So now I need to look up what metas are.
That's the problem. You don't even understand the definition half the time.
Style of polyamory in which all partners and metas both know each other
and would be comfortable sharing a meal around the kitchen table together.
No secrets and no weirdness.
No weirdness.
Excuse me, contrast this with some other styles like don't ask, don't tell
in which one or more partners do not want to be reminded of the fact
that another partner is seeing someone on the side.
I would call that don't enter this lifestyle polyamory.
It's not for you. Yeah.
This thing was posted six years ago to Reddit.
So this isn't even new.
So kitchen table, I want to make sure I'm following.
Kitchen table means we're going to have multiple partners
and we're able to eat dinner together and it's not weird.
Yeah, so here's a new one from field, which I think is like the threesome app.
No, field is the one I tried and it's not.
So what is field?
No, I'm saying I tried field. It's not, I thought it was, that's why I tried it.
Oh, this will be an easy way to freeze them.
But I'm saying, what is it if it's not?
It's just, it's just a normal data gap.
They're all normal.
Every one of these things is like, we're the one that does this.
And it's like, no, no, no, you're not.
It's just like every other app.
It's like, they're all, they're all the same.
All right.
KTP kitchen table polyamory is customizable.
But the general idea is this.
Everyone in the group, lovers, metamours.
It's a metamour.
I guess a paramour you're in love.
So a metamour is like, you're in love with maybe multiple people, just using context clues.
I guess everyone in the group could sit down at a kitchen table and share a meal.
That doesn't mean that each person is sexually or romantically involved,
but there is a baseline of friendship, communication and mutual respect.
What are we talking?
So it means friendship?
It just means that everyone your girlfriend is fucking is a good friend of yours and vice versa.
And you all enjoy a meal.
I used to live with this guy.
And he would, I would say, I would, I would say he was beyond square.
You know, like he was like a nerd.
And he was obsessed with Apple computers.
I'm tipping off to some of my friends listening who this guy probably was,
but he had a whole, he came into a lot of money
and he enabled me and a few friends to live with him during college.
I commuted to college and got to live like in a nice suburban house for pretty cheap.
And at some point during the college years, early twenties,
this guy who I had never seen with a girlfriend,
has a girlfriend and now they're going to be polyamorous.
And even at the time, at the time, this sounded even crazier.
I'm 20 years old in Missouri,
but I figured it's not my place to tell the guy how to live his life.
I just saw some potential danger here from a guy who's barely had a girlfriend
falling in love with someone and then trying to jump into polyamory.
It would be like Cameron Fry from Ferris Bueller attempting polyamory, you know.
And sure enough, they have people over from Craigslist,
one of them a sheriff of a neighboring town, like twice his age,
and his wife, they come over to the house
and after like 30 minutes of talking and polite conversation,
the sheriff grabs my friend's girlfriend that he's in love with by the hand
and just walks her upstairs.
And now my friend's sitting there with the sheriff's wife who he's not attracted to
and this other couple who are like not really feeling it either.
And they're trying to have like polite dinner conversation
while my friend is listening to his first serious girlfriend
getting railed by a neighboring town sheriff.
And he's like, you know, obviously shooken up by this.
And it's like, what did you, that's always my question with these people.
Where did you, what did you think was going to happen?
Yeah.
And maybe, maybe there are these unicorns or whatever you want to call them
that can truly do it.
But like the odds that you and your partner are going to be
on the exact same wavelength at all times.
And they're like, well, communication's key.
Yeah, I mean, sure.
I just don't know what you're doing.
I don't, I don't get what you're doing.
And it seems to be a first date conversation now.
Like, are you into it? Are you open to it? Would you be open to it?
And my answer is always just no, and maybe that's boring
and maybe I should look at it, but I think it would destroy me.
I don't know.
I've been in some open relationships.
You know, I was able to, I was able to more or less handle it.
Yeah.
The problem is, you know, there was, you know, the, well, I shouldn't say always,
but one of the times the woman like broke one of the rules.
Yeah.
And like that really hurt.
You know, we had a rule of like, you couldn't,
it was when I was in college and we were neighbors
and the rule was you weren't allowed to bring anybody back to your apartment
because we live so close together and she did.
And it ruined the relationship.
I had a therapist tell me once, he was like, and I think he's wrong,
but his take was, he was like, it never works.
Never works.
One of the people always falls in love with another person.
And I was like, I don't think it never works.
I think it's complicated.
Yeah.
But my take on everything now is it's all become so,
it gets to this point where there's so many definitions of things
that none of it means anything anymore.
Like, there's too much information now and it's like,
it makes it so complicated.
And then to me it creates this illusion that there's a mathematical equation
that works for you that's out there.
You just have to figure out which one it is.
But it's kind of stupid because it's like, no,
what you have to do is you have to, I mean, it's not stupid.
This is what happens.
But my point is you have to figure out what works for you and what doesn't.
And a lot of the time that is not something that you can define on a first date.
A lot of relationships open up 10 years in because they need to spice it up
or whatever.
I know married couples that did that.
They were like, look, we've been married for 15 years.
I get it.
You're allowed to have sex with another woman.
Just don't tell me about it.
That's not something they're discussing pre,
they're not discussing that along with the prenups.
Well, you can go the middle ditch route of telling your wife
like day five of the marriage that you want to open it up.
That's always an option.
Yeah, yeah.
I wouldn't recommend that.
No.
But yeah, I don't know.
I just feel like it's so much information.
That's what I was saying before about like the the the with the with the letter
identity stuff like it's like it's just becoming anything but straight.
Yeah.
And now queer can mean I also am.
If queer means I can also like the opposite sex,
then what then what the hell does bi mean?
That's what bi was there for.
Yeah.
So like, you know, it's.
If you're queer and you're hitting me up on an app,
I'm sorry, but you are bi.
Like maybe if I if I looked like Hannah Gadsby or something,
or if I if I looked more like there'd be some some confusion or gray area.
But like you're a woman approaching a man on a site designed for sex and dating.
At the very least, you got to change your thing.
Maybe you're straight questioning.
I bet there's somebody.
There's multiple people listening right now that are probably like,
oh, they know exactly what the term is.
Yeah. No, guys. Queer means this.
We just don't know.
But well, I am sitting in front of Google.
We're definition.
Oh, it says, you know what the first response that came up with?
And this is probably why our nation is at war.
The first thing that came up was queer definition for children.
For children.
Strange.
Anyway.
Oh, by the way, the definition of weird is strange.
That's the first definition.
Strange, odd, denoting to or relating to a sexual or gender identity
that does not correspond to established ideas of sexuality and gender,
especially heterosexual norms.
I guess that does leave things pretty wide open.
This kid, I saw this kid.
I can't remember his name.
He's a younger comic.
Yeah.
But I saw him last night at the at the mothership.
Excuse me.
And man, he had this joke.
It was so fucking funny because it was about the dating apps.
And he goes, he goes, I was on a dating app.
And did you know one of the hobbies listed is Black Lives Matter?
Yeah.
He's like, yeah, I support it, but it's not a hobby.
And he's like, what do you do in your spare time?
You consider the value of people's lives.
He's like, you know, he's like a hobby is something you're supposed to squeeze in
in the off hours when you get home from a long day.
Right. Exactly.
Yeah.
It distracts you from the drudgery of your life.
And he goes, why don't you believe Black Lives Matter?
He goes, look, man, I've been swamped at work.
That's funny.
Yeah, it's a very funny joke.
Yeah, I feel like I have an hour of standup from the apps.
I'm considering just picking it back up.
I know standups hate that popping in and out of the lifestyle, but I've been
shaving and editing and pruning some material.
Walsh, in a world of Costco bros, there's a lot worse you could do.
Sure.
I can also do the Lyric Hyperion one man show is something I've been considering,
but it would be sort of a light spoof of that material as well.
Nesting partners, by the way, I can't leave an open -ended thought here.
Nesting partners are two or more people who agree to own a house or rent an
apartment together.
So it's as simple as that.
Semi -nested?
I don't know.
Does that mean that you guys are roommates, but sometimes he sleeps at his
other girlfriend's house?
It's also like, does this mean that we're going to go see Drag Me to Hell and
then I'm going to have to go meet her boyfriend at home?
That's my number one question.
Sounds like you're going to have to go fuck upstairs while the others eat dessert
around a kitchen table and then you're going to have to go down and they're
going to chant, we will make you one of us and then you're in.
They all have like pieces of twigs and sticks and twine in their mouth to build
us a nest that we have to sleep.
We have to have sex in the nest that's built by the other partners that we're
not sleeping with.
They're all like, they've taken on bird qualities.
I got to say too, I'm a hundred percent for an open relationship.
Yeah.
I've been the other man in an open relationship.
I'm a hundred percent into it, but whenever I read about this stuff, I always
get a real, what's it called?
Oh, God damn it.
I can't believe I just blew this fucking, because I can't remember the name.
The name of the movie.
No, I always get a real wicker man vibe.
I always picture them all in gowns with wreaths on their heads.
That's the end of hereditary.
Yeah.
Which is obviously very influenced by the wicker man.
I'm sorry.
Midsummer, not hereditary.
Yes.
But it's very, there's something very Fulcar about all this.
Then it would have been easier.
I mean, like if I'm on a little like weird, uh, commune and everybody's like in,
in white sheets and you can kind of see their nipples and stuff when the sun's
out, I think then I could get very quickly into the polyamorous lifestyle.
Maybe it'd be easier for me now that I've lost the ability to care for people or
to trust people.
Um, maybe, maybe now is the time since I'm just sort of completely broken with
regards to relationships that maybe, maybe that's when people turn to
polyamory.
I don't know if nothing else has worked for them.
Maybe that's the move.
Uh, either that or just get yourself some escorts.
I mean, that's an easy, it's probably cheaper than dating in Los Angeles.
Honestly, I took Joe Christ.
I took, I w and here's how, this is how stupid I am.
I took this girl out Sunday night.
We have a nice time.
The, I start talking about how I'm going to the bowl the next night with my
friend.
This was last night and I was going to see the war on drugs, Lucius and the
national three good bands, a good, good lineup and the Hollywood bowl,
beautiful night, foggy night.
So like the lights of the bowl and the fog, it was like awesome, beautiful,
whatever.
But anyway, my buddy Tim that I always go to concerts with canceled on me at
about 4 PM.
He had just gotten back from Germany and he's like, sorry, I just can't do
this.
I'm going to crash.
And I had told this girl on the date that I was going to this show.
She said, I've never been to the bowl.
I list the band.
She loves each band more than the one before it.
And when Tim cancels, I'm like, all right, now it's a little awkward because I
went out with this girl for the first time last night.
Can I really ask her to go out two nights in a row?
We had a good time.
We didn't have like a two night date in a row kind of vibe.
But I'm like, you know what?
This would be really fun.
I'm just going to hit her up.
I do.
Joe, here's, here's where the problems begin.
The beginning of any dating thing.
You get, you get one date now before the person's real.
Werewolf comes out.
Oh yeah.
And it comes out hard, comes out hard.
She goes, I almost, I almost can't.
It's going to rattle me up to even go through this.
And maybe it's minor.
Maybe I blew it out of proportion, but I asked her to the concert.
She's like, OMG.
Oh, I'm so excited.
I would love to go.
I've never been to the bowl.
Yes, I'm in.
Let's go.
She lives very close to me.
I go, all right, great.
Should we, should we meet there or should I pick you up?
Because nowadays you say, should I pick you up?
They're like, no, I'm not going to give a strange man my home address.
Thank you.
It's like, oh, okay.
I was trying to be nice.
Anyway, yells that as he's folding his knife back up.
But I go, I'll, I'll, I'll pick you up.
She goes, what time does the show start?
I said six 30 and the bowl's kind of annoying because you think no rock
concert could start at six 30 sharp, but they do.
There's a curfew.
And she's like, okay, great.
I'm going to go to my five 30 yoga class.
Oh boy.
Now I just, I just said the show starts at six 30.
It's a half hour drive to the bowl.
Plus parking plus that mile walk up to the bowl.
Once you have parked.
And I'm, I'm like, I'm already angry.
You know, I'm already regretting doing this nice thing and being like, oh, this
girl would actually really love to go to the show.
I should ask her.
I go, well, that's just not going to work.
I'm sorry.
You'd have to skip the five 30 yoga class to make the six 30 concert a half hour
away.
And I'm trying to say that without being an asshole, you know, without being
condescending and it was hard.
Yeah.
She goes, you're going to think I'm making this up.
I can show you the texts.
She goes, my body really needs the class today.
Okay.
This girl teaches yoga.
So she's, she's taking two to three yoga classes a day.
You know, granted, you might think your body needs this one, but you can
probably skip it.
And also we're going to be walking straight up hills.
So you'll get some exercise anyway.
I go, yeah, look, let's just pretend I didn't ask you to the concert.
Like I'm backing out of it.
I go, there's really no way to make this work.
If I, if I'm going to pick you up and try to make it across town and you're
going to do this clout, let's just skip it.
Let's go out.
Let's go see another show before the end of the year.
No big deal.
She goes, I really, really want to go though.
Yeah, I can't even.
This is, I know.
And you're sick.
I want to be like, if you really wanted to go, you'd skip the fucking yoga
clout, like, you know, but I don't know her well enough to talk to her like
this.
Not that you should talk to anyone like this, but I'm going nuts.
I'm just like, what, what?
Just never, never talk to this person ever again.
I'm already there, except wait, Joe.
So I go, yeah, look, let's just skip, let's skip the night.
And she goes, can you give me 10 minutes to think about it?
Holy God.
How old is this human?
She's 35 years old, Joe.
I said, I said, sorry, but, but like, no, this was, this was kind of like a,
Hey, I'm sorry.
This is last minute, but do you want to go do this really fun thing?
And now it's become this giant chore.
You know, like I'm being nicer than that, but I'm like, it's really not a
big deal.
I'll find somebody else to go and we can just skip it.
About five minutes pass.
She writes back.
I'm just, I almost can't believe saying it.
She goes, I'm just going to go to the first half of the class for the love of
God.
So she's going to go from five 30 to six.
She goes, then, cause she doesn't have a car, Joe, can you pick me up at the
yoga studio and drive me to my apartment so that I can get a shower and change
at 6 p .m.
To make a six 30 concert a half hour away.
I said, no, I'm sorry.
I thought I was being clear, but that, that won't work.
There's the only way that can work really is if you're like, yeah, come pick
me up and we go to the show.
And if not, let's please hang out another night.
She goes, all right, I'm skipping the class.
I guess my outfit is cute enough, but can you please bring me a jacket?
85 degrees outside.
I go, yeah, yeah, I'll, I'll bring you a jacket.
She goes, preferably something denim because that would match with, and then
starts describing what she's wearing and what kind of men's jacket she'd like me
to bring to the concert.
I throw a jacket in the car.
I go pick her up.
We have a pretty nice time at the concert, but I'm like, this is over.
You know, I, I've not, I don't even know why I went.
I should have just blocked her and moved on with my life.
We get home this morning.
I wake up.
I have a text.
She goes, something happened to me last night.
I woke up at 4 a .m.
violently ill.
Like, okay.
We had one drink a piece, you know, so I'm like, all right, I'm not sure what that would
be or why that's my fault or responsibility, but okay.
Then she goes, there's no mention of like, thanks for last night or had a good time
or anything.
By the way, we parked at your Elks Lodge hole where you and I used to drink.
They charged $60 to park.
Oh, no, the, the, the American Legion, American Legion.
Yeah.
The place that where the veterans go, it's not an Elks Lodge hall.
I pull in there, pull in there and they're like, it'll be 60 bucks.
Yeah.
I'm like, what's the alternative?
You know, I go look for street parking and then we're walking up in the heat or I was
just like, fine, take it.
You're out so much money on this, on this night.
I didn't even want to go on.
And then exactly like you're saying, I'm like, I'm just never going to speak to this person
again.
She said, I left two phones in your car because when she got into my car, she was holding
two phones together because they were doing a data swap.
Okay.
So she's like, in your console, I have two cell phones.
Can you bring them to me?
Because she doesn't have a car.
Like why, this is why people are not dating.
This is why people aren't dating.
Suddenly, like I'm rerouting my life for this woman that we've been out once.
You got to learn how to just say no, dude.
You got to, this should have been cut off.
Yeah.
This should have been cut off.
You shouldn't have even made it to the concert.
You just put your foot down.
You go, listen, it's no big deal.
I'll hit you up another time.
We'll go to a concert.
End of discussion.
It's like, I know, but she's going, oh no.
Yeah.
I really wanted to go.
Yeah, I know.
Yeah.
And then you go to that.
It's a bummer, but we'll hit it up next time.
Don't worry about it.
Like, you know, I left two phones in your car.
That's a bummer.
Can you bring them?
No, I can't.
I'll put them in an Uber for you.
Oh, but that won't work.
Well, that's cool.
Well, then you can come over here later, but I can't bring them over there, right?
Like, you got to just start, you know, putting up some walls here.
Anyway, this has been a nice therapy session that we've had here with Pat today.
And you want to hear the crazy thing, folks, Pat goes into therapy and talks about movies.
That's true.
Mike, did you catch that new joker?
Foley, I don't.
I honestly don't have.
That's how I kicked off therapy this week.
I don't have any movie corner because I've been traveling and I was at Skankfest and
I'm happy to move directly into the Salem's Lot review unless you very much want to tackle
your own movie corner picks.
But I don't really have anything for it this week.
I kind of want to save the one thing for next time that I want to talk about, because I
like when we have episodes like this where we just kind of talk about life for a while
and the fans seem to like it too.
Yeah.
And I think that's OK in lieu of me talking about the latest multicam sitcom I watched
or something.
Yeah.
I will say, you know, oh, you like multicam sitcoms, Joe?
You should be a part of my new Thrupple with me and the girl who likes multicams.
We can all get dinner together and then you can watch me fuck her on the kitchen table.
Yeah.
I'm a multicam amory.
It means we like only multicam sitcoms.
We only fuck while watching multicams.
We fuck with a laugh track, basically.
I will do a quick scary stuff because I think this is interesting.
R .L. Stein has a new comic book series.
I mean, I don't know how new it is.
It's new to me, but I think it's pretty new.
It's called Stuff of Nightmares and it's an adult horror comic.
He writes the stories and each issue is a pretty substantial size.
Like each, what they've done is compiled basically the four comic installments for each story
into like one compendium.
So each book you buy is the four different parts.
I don't know if you can actually buy single issues.
Excuse me.
So they're like 15 bucks and it's this pretty solid length of a read, but it's all right.
It's not great, but he's got this character called the Nightmare Man or something that hosts it.
It's very tales from the crypt.
And he kind of guides you through the story like a crypt keeper would.
And the one I read was like a take on Frankenstein.
It was a zombie story, but they're pretty fucking gory and there's sexual stuff in it and there's cursing.
It's a hard R, which is weird for R .L. Stein, but it's worth checking out if you like comics.
The artwork's good if you like horror comics.
And if you like R .L. Stein, I would say especially.
It's definitely more intriguing than like Goosebumps or something.
Yeah, I used to love R .L. Stein.
For a while I was reading them all and Christopher Pike as well, who gets less props.
I don't think I know him.
I know the name. What'd he write?
Christopher Pike's big one was he did two big ones.
Monster, which was very similar to the Buffy thing of like dating a guy.
And then once he takes your virginity, he becomes a monster.
Real hot teenage sex scene in a hot tub that I remember being an awakening for me.
And then Chain Letter was his other big one, which I'm surprised.
I'm shocked they never made it to a movie, but that's about one of those chain letters.
If you don't send this to this many people, you'll die.
And that was a whole series of books that was very good.
Chris Pike.
All right. I'll check out Pike.
Oh, you know what I'm thinking of Chris Pike? I'm thinking of Pine.
I'm thinking of it. Yes, this is wild.
I was thinking of Pike, the original captain of the Enterprise.
And I was like, why am I thinking Chris Pike?
It's because Chris Pine played the Kirk.
And I was combining the two names. And here we are.
There you go, folks. That's how my brain is working today.
Makes sense.
OK. Oh, yeah. I'm looking him up now.
I remember these books.
Yeah, I mean, he was definitely for an older crew than R .L. Stein.
He was trying to basically bridge the gap between Stein and a Steve King.
Yeah, these are like, yeah, like if if Stephen King novels were for like sort of kids.
Great artwork, super like 90s.
These fonts and colors are great.
I would buy these just to have them on the shelf. They would just be decorative.
They were great.
Wait a minute. His novels, The Midnight Club and The Season of Passage have both been optioned by Mike Flanagan for Netflix.
So I guess they already did The Midnight Club. Cool.
So he is still adapting his stuff. That's cool.
I was confused by The Midnight Club because.
Are you afraid of the dark? The Nickelodeon show was The Midnight Society.
Yeah. And I always wondered if there was any connection between the two and who thought of it first.
But I guess it's just using the word midnight. It's not that big of a deal.
But yeah, how are you feeling?
Do you want to talk about this?
Let's let's get to Salem's Lot.
I mean, yeah, take the people through the through the through the brief.
Go ahead. Lead us in.
Well, Salem's Lot is, of course, one of Stephen King's most beloved horror novels came out in nineteen seventy five.
So we're talking about something that is literally shockingly fifty plus years old,
which is nuts.
You know, the original Salem's Lot miniseries came out in nineteen seventy nine.
That was a two parter directed by the great Tobey Hooper.
I recall enjoying it very much, finding it spooky, having a good vibe, being, you know,
I feel like a lot of these made for TV movies were much scarier back in the day, I guess, because they had to be.
But it was good and scary. And the book is good and scary.
And they did a sequel, which I didn't see. Have you seen that, Joe?
Return to Salem's Lot.
Oh, Joe's gone. He's long gone.
But, yeah, return to Salem's Lot.
I didn't see they've done Salem's Lot before with Rob Lowe, I want to say that came out in.
Oh, so twenty eighteen did a Salem's Lot bit.
We all remember that if we watched that show, three hour, two part miniseries starring Rob Lowe came out in 04.
There was an epics television series called Chapel Wait, which was a prequel to Salem's Lot.
This is pretty well -worn territory.
And I guess my issue with this new adaptation is that they chose to do nothing with the excellent material.
They chose to not take it in a new direction.
They chose to not shoot it in an interesting way, tell the story in an interesting way.
They whittled it down to two hours when all other versions of this have been like a miniseries.
And yet it still feels like there's not enough stories somehow.
It's a mess, the new one, and it's a shame.
It was written and directed by Gary Doberman, who did it.
He direct, wait, no, he produced it.
He did. He wrote Annabelle Comes Home, The Nun, The Nun 2.
He wrote it also.
The new it, of course, but a lot of horror chops, none of these movies I would consider great.
But here's what I just read last night and which kind of opened my eyes a little bit.
The initial cut of Gary Doberman's Salem's Lot was three hours long.
It included the Marston house opening, which I think people are upset is not in the new movie.
He says his first draft of the script is one hundred and eighty pages.
Something happened here because this is a big title.
Pet Sematary and all and it and all these other recent Stephen King things have done gangbusters box office on low budgets.
Even it only costs like thirty million dollars or something.
So for Salem's Lot to get dumped on Max, you knew it was going to be bad and it is.
But to hear that it was originally three hours nowadays, that that generally makes the fans go, well, it must have been amazing.
I guess we just will never know until we see this classic version.
But sometimes the three hour version sucks as well.
And my guess in watching this is that another hour would not have helped in any way.
It's a very boring on the nose retread of the Salem's Lot story.
The cat Lewis Pullman.
Well, he does not have his dad's charisma.
This man is not a leading man.
I never thought Bill Pullman was was awesome.
I think I agree.
He's a good character actor and he's good, like in Lost Highway or While You Were Sleeping, where he's kind of a cuck.
He was always a good cuck like Kinnear.
But yeah, this kid's got half Bill Pullman's charisma.
It was good to see Alfre Woodard just because she's a great actress.
But like to see her have to deliver this shit is tough.
The movie seems really influenced by Mike Flanagan's stuff.
Like the priest has a monologue that feels right out of Midnight Mass.
Midnight Mass is considered by many to be sort of a very, very loose, uncredited adaptation of Salem's Lot.
There are a lot of similarities.
But this story.
If you're going to be the sixth person up to the plate, like I don't understand not doing anything fun, new, interesting with the source material,
not trying to mix it up, not trying to have any fun, put a spin on it.
The movie just lies there for two hours.
I was bored out of my skull by Salem's Lot.
I don't necessarily agree.
I thought it was all right.
I thought it felt to me like a solid TV movie.
I wasn't mad at it.
I certainly liked it better than the Rob Lowe version.
I haven't seen it.
I own it.
I mean, it's fine.
The Rob Lowe one is fine.
But the Rob Lowe one, they take all the scariness out of the vampires, basically.
What's the main vampire's name?
Bartlett? Bartlow?
I don't recall.
Whatever.
But in the Rob Lowe one, that head vampire doesn't look scary.
If I'm remembering correctly, he looks more human than not.
This one, I thought, drifted things back to the Tobe Hooper vibes.
I liked that they actually said it in the time that the book was written
and didn't make it a modern version.
I liked it aesthetically.
I thought it looked cool.
It looked, from a cinematography standpoint to me,
it looked a lot like scary stories to tell in the dark.
It had that sepia tone, fall, October, middle of America vibe.
And I enjoyed that visually.
I thought the acting was good.
I liked Pullman.
I really enjoyed the female lead.
I thought the guy that played Striker or whatever,
the vampire's familiar, whatever that character's name is.
I didn't think he was bad,
but he certainly was no Donald Sutherland or James Mason,
but he was fine, he was good.
Excuse me.
I very much enjoyed the guy that played the teacher.
He's that character actor that's in everything.
So there was stuff I liked.
I thought the lady that played the nun who plays the vampire in this,
she looked awesome.
She was scary looking.
I was like, the vampire's scary.
Stephen King said that about Salem's lot.
He wanted to make vampires scary again.
He was like, they should be like the idea of rot and it's gross.
And I thought that they took the ball with that and ran with it in this.
The vampires seemed very unpleasant to be around.
They seemed animalistic.
But with that all said, the construction of the movie itself,
again, it just to me played like a TV movie.
Had this been a mini -series, a three -hour mini -series that they split in half,
I would have been pretty satisfied back in the day.
That's not really a thing anymore.
But they did a lot of made -for -TV stuff in this,
or just even movie adaptation stuff.
They combined characters and they sort of streamlined everything.
And at times I thought that worked,
but there were times where glaringly it didn't work.
I mean, they come to terms with vampires being real in 10 seconds,
which is just not believable.
And then once they get their hands on this book about vampires,
they have the answer to every conundrum they're facing
with this problem in the town immediately.
And it was a little too convenient for me.
I did like the change of the ending.
Some people are mad that it doesn't end at the house,
the way the story does.
I thought that drive -in thing was cool.
I thought that was a really cool, savvy thing.
We're going to show how the whole town goes, the drive -in at the beginning,
when they're normal, and then at the end they're all there
because it can sort of house all of them.
And then they can be out in the daytime
because the giant screen is blocking the direct sunlight.
And then the way they kill them is tearing down the screen
and burning up the entire town all at once.
I found all that very clever and very cool.
I mean, it didn't make for much of a big ultimate showdown with the main vampire,
and it wasn't quite as scary because it was out of the house,
but it was still cool.
I like that last, you know, when she gets stabbed through the mouth
and the steak comes out of her mouth when she's trying to eat the kid.
Like, you know, I don't know.
I thought it had it in enough places.
If they put out a three -hour cut, I would watch it.
I would be curious to see.
Yeah, it looks like, so this was delayed quite a bit,
but it was announced in April 2019.
Filming began in 2021.
Film was originally scheduled to be released September 9, 2022,
so two years ago, was pushed back to April 2023
before Warner Brothers pulled it off their release schedule indefinitely.
Stephen King said at this point,
which is especially for a guy who lies about everything,
they're like, when's it coming out?
He's like, I don't know. I'm confused why they pulled it.
It's not like it's embarrassing or anything,
which that's basically Stephen King saying your movie fucking sucks
because he'll rave about anything.
But yeah, it had obviously some problems.
I don't know in a world where this movie's not really tearing up the,
I guess it's number one on HBO Max, but they also don't have anything else.
I don't think we'll get that three -hour cut,
and I don't think I would watch it.
I felt the cinematography of this, just look at,
they put a 1975 Instagram filter over it.
The plotting was off. There was no build of tension.
I didn't like the characters. I didn't like the cast,
and I didn't like the telling of the story.
Just a complete washout for me.
So we're coming from different spots.
My hog is very down for Salem's Lot,
and we're racking up an array of Stephen King adaptations
that is somehow worse than the first time around.
Yeah, that I agree with.
I just feel like with Pet Sematary, with other stuff,
why are we getting after all this time, and these books,
when Pet Sematary first comes out,
the movie came out three years after the book,
and somehow they get it right.
Now with 40 years to really understand
what people love about this material,
we're doing cheap, shitty, TV -style knockoff versions of them,
and it's very frustrating.
I pray that when they finally get to Misery,
and I'm shocked, as always,
that we have not seen Melissa McCarthy do Misery yet,
I just pray they give it a little more care,
because these adaptations to me are junk,
and if we're going to live in a world
where we can only see movies that are based on books,
take the necessary time and effort
with the books that are great.
And in my opinion, they really missed the boat on this one.
I do agree with your overall take on Stephen King adaptations.
Look, I'm at a point where I'm blaming the studio more than anything.
Sure.
I think studio interference has become absurd.
Oh, yeah.
And it was always bad, but I think it's become absurd.
So God only knows why something ends up the way it does at this point.
I mean, even if a director is not capable,
they will send somebody in who is to do the job silently
to make sure they don't lose their money.
Like they're plugging the holes in the dam as this moves.
So at this point, to me, if something is great or if something is terrible,
it's because of the studio in some way or another.
But it's just, you know, you watch the opening credits of this thing.
I mean, they're playing like some kind of stock licensed spooky music track.
Yeah.
You know, over this After Effects sequence that just looks like
yet another rip off of the seven opening credits of seven.
And then they're using the John Carpenter font, the classic Carpenter font.
And I'm like, we might be in trouble here.
But my point is, I don't think that that was the director's choice.
I really don't.
I think the director probably wanted to do a cold open.
And and really start things off like, you know, in a cool way.
And I feel like the studio was like, no, you have to do a credit sequence.
Why do you have to do a credit?
Well, because baked into the deals of all these fucking actors.
Right. It says they have to get billing in this way.
It's all this bullshit now that doesn't let anything breathe.
Like nothing can be good anymore. Nothing.
Yeah. Well, they don't trust the person that they hire ever.
And it's like if you're if you're going to entrust somebody with, say,
forty million dollars, which I would imagine this movie cost,
vet them, interview them, check your references, whatever you got to do.
But you got to support that horse.
You know, you're putting forty million dollars behind a person's vision.
Then what are you doing shitting on the vision every step of the way?
And that's mostly what's happening now is they hire people.
They like to hire people who don't put up much of a fight, especially Marvel.
You know, people who are just who will just do what they tell them to do.
And that's what movies are starting to feel like is just sort of committee run.
And the problem with a committee decision on a movie
when every decision is committee based is you're getting no personality.
You're the goal is for everyone to enjoy everything equally.
And what you wind up with is a movie that doesn't touch anyone,
because who wants that?
A movie made without passion just to, like, check off a bunch of boxes.
And that's what movies feel like now, almost across the board.
Like, let's try to.
And the reason comedy is gone and all that,
because they make all these decisions about what works in Japan.
Right.
The Warner Brothers is building their film slate
about what will connect with Japanese audiences.
And that's not going to always work on us, you know,
something that works in Japan, in America and everywhere.
Yeah, that might be what you want bank account wise.
But what you're left with is a movie that has no, like, personal flavor,
no regional flavor.
You know, you're just like watching a thing.
It's like watching a blender.
You know, you can you can maybe admire how it was put together or something,
but it's not touching your soul in any way.
Sucks. Yeah.
And we were talking about this last night at the show I was doing,
but it was like these fucking studios, man.
It's like, you know, they're they could spend, you know, the reason they're
they're pulling these movies and and and and, you know,
cutting things short and and not allowing things to breathe is all based in money,
obviously.
But half of the problem is, is these fucking dumb adults
think a low budget movie is ten million dollars.
And it's like, maybe if you fucking idiots
didn't spend five grand a day on fucking craft services,
why don't we start there with the amount of shit you're throwing in the trash
every day that nobody wants to eat?
Like, why don't we start there?
Why don't you not have 18 fucking key grips on this thing?
You know, I mean, these studios could be making one million dollar movies.
They would they would be fucking tax write offs.
And if the movie hits, lucky fucking day, free money.
And and they learn the lesson every fucking 10 years.
Another goddamn Blair Witch or whatever comes out some thirty thousand dollar thing.
And it blows up and makes 100 million at the box office
and then becomes a viral sensation and a franchise and whatever.
And they still don't take fucking notes from it.
They still don't take notes.
Even when these idiots started to make found footage movies
because they were like, well, these are cheap and whatever.
The found footage movies looked like 30 million dollar movies
that they were trying to make look cheap.
Just guys make it cheap.
Yeah, totally.
You can you can ensure it.
You can take care of everybody.
But but this is the but the but the other big problem is is is these these these fucking agents
and these reps that that demand all this shit for their clients and whatever.
And then and then the talent is a problem, too.
Everybody's a fucking problem, man.
And everybody acts like they're in it to make art.
Nobody's in it to make art. They're all in it to make money.
They're all ego fucking maniacs.
And that's kind of why, to be honest, I was rooting for this movie
was because the cast really did seem to care.
They really did seem to give a shit.
And they really did seem to be behind this thing.
And together, you know, funny enough, like the characters in the movie fighting this thing.
And they did really seem like thrilled when it was finally going to get released.
And like and I looked up a lot of the actors like they're they're not big influencers.
They don't the lead woman has like twelve thousand followers on Instagram.
Like these are not well known people.
It wasn't like they were doing the thing of of, you know, let's let's get this let's get this pop star
and throw her into the movie because people watch for her.
So, you know, man, it's a rare occurrence.
This guy seems to give a shit.
I don't love a lot of what he's done.
I wasn't a fan of it. I wasn't a fan of the nun.
But I respect the fact that he's got his horror chops.
And it seems like everybody did give a shit.
It just didn't come together.
But I'm going to blame studio on this one.
So my hog is my hog is out. It's not down.
It's out. It's hopeful.
A hopeful hog, a hopeful hog.
And my hog is saying, hey, you put that three hour cut in front of me.
I'm going to get in there.
So we'll see what happens.
Folks, obviously, it's going to be all horror all month for the month of October.
I'm not sure exactly what we're covering yet.
We're talking about potentially doing the substance.
We're talking about, I guess that is the only thing in theaters that's horror, right?
Because Joker.
I have seen the substance and Joker, which is horrifying, but not horror.
And I don't know what's coming out this month.
There's a few big horror movies.
There's Smile 2.
Oh, God.
You like Smile 1.
I love Smile 1. Smile 2 looks terrible.
Yeah, it doesn't.
It looks terrible.
Yeah.
Hey guys, what if we did the first movie except it was about Lady Gaga?
I don't care.
There's a lot of that going around.
There's also Terrifier 3.
Okay.
I think I'm so far past my old pussy days.
I feel like there's almost nothing you could put in front of me that I wouldn't be able to watch these days.
But I got to tell you that the way I felt after watching both Terrifiers, I don't know if I'm doing three.
Well, I get it and I respect the craft and I get the gore hounds love their gore and etc.
But it just makes me feel hopeless in a way that's almost not good for me mentally.
You know, like I don't I don't and I love dark shit too, but there's just something about it.
There's something about that clown, folks.
They said this.
They said this third one is even crazier than the second one.
But it's a Christmas movie.
If we were to do it, we should do it at Christmas.
Great.
That would be that would be good.
But wait, the substance is horror, right?
You were saying Joker is not horror.
Substance is absolutely horror.
Joker 2 is not.
No.
I had a long conversation about Joker 2.
I haven't seen it yet and it did not make me my buddy saw it.
I was like, this sounds unbearable.
I'm going to be real honest with you.
I did walk out of Joker 2.
All right.
So I you know, I walked out with not much left, but I looked at the Wikipedia.
I was like, I know where this is going.
And it was for a movie that everyone seems so embarrassed by, like including Todd Phillips.
They're like asking him like what went wrong here or whatever.
He's like, talk to Joaquin Phoenix.
He wanted to, you know, improvise every scene five minutes before we shot it.
And my question with them is just like, then why did you make it two and a half hours?
It clearly doesn't work from the first frame.
So why not just make it a tight 90 and leave with your hat in your hand and a little respect?
It's an endless movie.
It goes on and on and on.
And it's wild.
They don't hear.
This is the exact opposite of Salem's lot.
Yeah.
They're like, we'll go shoot the editor run free Joker.
Or whatever the fuck it's called.
You know, and then this poor bastard making Salem's lot is like, can a bitch get a two hour cut?
They're like, no, no, in fairness, you can't walk into Warner Brothers and say, can a bitch get a two hour cut?
Yeah.
And you never could.
You never could.
I mean, I've just about had it with Joaquin Phoenix.
I think I'm done.
Oh, no, I don't think you're the only one.
I think with this, the back to back of him walking away from that movie days before shooting and then Joker two,
I think he is done. I don't think any,
any studio is going to commit $10 million to him anymore. He'll be,
he'll be back in the indie world, which is probably where he's better off.
Yeah. But it's like Joaquin, you got away with that. I'm not here,
whatever the fuck it was called. That weirdo, you know,
whatever you were trying to do, you got away with that, dude.
You got away with that. Not only did you get away with that,
you got away with a couple of accusations that were connected to that project.
You skated through that. Yeah. They more went to Casey Affleck, but yes.
And that was, I'm, that was not, I'm not there. That's the Bob Dylan one,
but I actually love that one. Let me look it up. Joaquin documentary.
I was just thinking of pretentious. I'm still here. You're right.
I'm still here. So what's the Dylan one? I'm not there. I'm not there.
That Dylan one can go fuck itself too.
Totally agree. You mean the Chamele one or that one?
No, the one where it's like Kate Blanchett playing Dylan and John Goodman
playing Dylan. And I'm like, go fuck off.
Well now you're bringing in Mast and Anonymous,
which is another bad Bob Dylan movie. You're mixing them up, but I'll let it,
I'll let it go. Folks, we will be back.
I'm on Instagram at the Patrick Walsh.
We are at CU and Hellpod for like little best of clips and show dates and things
like that. And that's all we got. Joe, any plugs before we go?
Yeah. Summerville, Massachusetts, December 7th, I'm doing a big,
big old Christmas show. Uh,
stand up going to bring the new hour of material to you, Massachusetts.
And there is a big surprise happening on that show that I'll be announcing very,
very soon. Um, but it's going to be a holiday extravaganza.
It's going to be very fun. Um, and then the new tour starts in 2025.
Uh, dates are all available on joderosa .com.
There's a shitload of dates, uh, in the, in the winter into spring.
So come on out folks.
All right, we will see you next time and we will see you in hell.