I'll see you in hell.
Folks, it's we'll see you in hell.
Well, we're back, we're back, we're back marching into the month of March with a hot review
of Conan one and two Barbarian and destroyer.
I'm here with Patty Walsh.
My name is Joe DeRosa.
How are you?
Well, I'm sick.
So I'm going to sound a little sick.
I'm on a little cold medicine, but other than that, I think I'm going to be fine, you know.
I'm doing all right.
What are you sick with?
It's not COVID or anything like that.
It's been a sore throat for a couple of days.
You know, who knows who knows, things going around.
I do see more and more people with masks and I'm like, what news are you watching is, you
know, what's going on, who, who to trust.
I'm not, I'm not doing it again.
Take me.
Take me out.
Oh, well, you know, parts of England are locked down again.
No, no way.
Yeah, yeah.
What parts?
I forget the name of the city, but wherever they're shooting, the new Superman movie, the city
is like on, on like level three lockdown, like the, the set images that leaked, everybody has
a mask on and they, they set in the stories, they're like, yeah, this part of England is
locked down again.
And it's, it's being met with, with great protest.
But I got to tell you, I'd welcome with open arms and other lockdown.
We didn't know how good we had it.
I don't welcome it.
Now, is it possible that maybe they just saw Spider -Man and thought that everybody was masking
again?
Well, that would only be one person, but you see, he wears a mask.
Yeah.
Joe.
I'm with you.
That's what I saw on Hinge the other day.
I want somebody who will riff my bit.
I can't even get a podcast co -host to riff my bit.
I, you look, you give me a good bit, I'll riff it.
You give me some good Coke, I'll sniff it.
You give me some good, sorry, I guess.
I'm not, uh, passionately screaming about whether roast beef or corned beef is better.
There it is.
I don't know.
I was wondering when it would happen.
Yeah.
Rick.
Uh, uh, the important issues, I didn't, I didn't say I enjoyed that either, Pat.
Uh, no, but I would, here's why I would welcome another lockdown because now I'm not scared
of COVID.
So now I would just, I would freely hang out with other friends who weren't scared of it.
There would be no, like we have to isolate for two weeks.
I'd have friends come over and I'd go see them and I would trust that they wouldn't
willy -nilly go around old people or anything like that as I wouldn't and, uh, we'd have
no responsibilities and we could fucking party and have a great time together.
Like, I don't know, it sounds good to me.
Yeah.
I'm, I'm certainly not living in any further fear about it, uh, whether it comes back or
not, whether it is back or not, but as far as staying inside, I mean, I, I've been disciplined
lately.
I've been writing, been staying in anyway, been doing my, you ever do morning pages?
You ever do the artist's way, Joe?
I have been trying to get myself back into the swing of getting up and writing and it has
not happened yet.
Yeah.
I think I've been a little creatively overwhelmed with, uh, perfecting this, this hour that
I'm doing on the road and then also just getting the house ready, like moving stuff from
the apartment down to here and, you know, it's been a, been a six month process of that.
So, um, when I say getting it ready, you mean to have a kid in play style house party, right?
Yeah.
A real roof razor.
Exactly.
I've got the folding table downstairs, uh, for the DJ, uh, DJ, yeah, um, I just, you know,
I'm just not, uh, I'm finally, I finally made the last shipment of stuff down here.
Uh -huh.
And now I'm just like, okay, now I can kind of like, all right, like I can start to look
at my place in New York as my place in New York.
I can look at this place as my place here and, and there, you know, you've moved a lot swirls
around until you're kind of settled and trying to figure it all out, you know?
How much with the, with the movers where you micromanaging, how much were you, we like, uh,
that's my, my Flintstones bubble heads actually, so if you could just sort of maybe straighten
the box out.
Thanks.
Uh -huh.
So that kind of stuff.
Surprisingly very little.
There were a couple things where I was like, guys, this is really just, please be very careful
with this one thing.
Most of it, I was like, just get it down there.
I don't care.
Just get it there.
I packed most of them myself.
There were, the only stuff I didn't pack myself was glassware because I was like, okay, I
want to make sure I do that right or whatever, but everything else I packed myself.
And, uh, you know, I still have my, you're candy dishes.
Yeah.
Candy dishes.
Uh -huh.
Now I did have them over separate the candies.
A little, uh, plastic strawberry wrapped candies with the juice centers.
Oh.
Is there a worst?
Those are good though.
Oh, boy.
Here we go.
Here's our first taste buds.
Joe.
I'm going to drink some coffee.
No, uh, I love them.
I love them to this day.
I was given one after dinner recently and enjoyed the hell out of it.
I, here's how I remembered them.
I remembered that my parents had a gift basket business that they ran out of our house at
one point.
That wasn't their only gig.
Believe it or not.
24 years into this podcast of the first time I mentioned that.
Well, I got to be honest, I forgot about it until you just mentioned those candies because
it wasn't their soul.
Kind of a money loser for the family.
Yeah.
Dark period.
This is the dark years.
They still their day.
You want the boy?
You want the bully.
He can get in the basket for a price.
They, um, but they had dedicated this whole room in the house to gift baskets like all the
supplies and, um, and just general, just in general.
And I had one of those, uh, I had one of those houses growing up where there was never any
fun snacks in the house, like ever, like there was something or anything.
But what my mom would let me have when I was like dying for some fun snack was, uh, during
that phase was those strawberry candies because they had a ton of them because they would
like pepper the basket with those in the, in the little fake grass that you put some
color.
Just the maddened pops up.
Yeah.
And I just grew to, to despise them, uh, just, just, just, it just felt like such a cheap poor
fucking excuse for like skittles or something, you know, and I'm a big fan.
The only time I would ever object to them is on Halloween, I've actually seen them out
there on Halloween night.
And I think that's a disturbing, nobody wants to see a strawberry on Halloween.
I'd personally rather see the old black and orange brown peanut butter taffies that many
think are the worst Halloween candy that maybe don't even make them anymore.
But in my day, there were these little nougat balls.
You remember those, Joe?
Yeah.
There's, that's just that whole, uh, yeah, no, no, I'm saying, yeah, like not at you, I'm
that, that, that tone is directed at the candy.
It's shit.
Yeah.
It's fucking, I actually kind of like it.
I, listen, none of these are offensive to the, to the, to the, to the taste, but these are
all, you're like a saltwater taffy.
I hate it with all my hate all of it.
I hate salt.
I hate saltwater taffy.
So we used to go to the lake of the Ozarks.
This is before Jason Bateman shot it up and it was like, all there was to do it.
Night was fudge or saltwater taffy.
And this was, uh, these were terms for the asshole and the pussy in Pat's family.
Uh, yeah, yeah.
You can guess which was which now I, I, I, I, I hated, here's why I hated fudge and saltwater
taffy.
I can tell you exactly why because we would go to the shore every summer.
And at the end of the, the Jersey shore and at the end of the trip, yeah, every year.
My mom, her last stop was to buy saltwater taffy and, uh, fudge, uh, to bring home.
And it was, it was with moms on these two things.
It was indicative of the fun as ended school is coming.
You know, when you went into the saltwater taffy store, this was it.
That was a wrap.
You know, no more arcade, no more, your dad's buying a t -shirt.
Like, this vacation's over.
We're going home now.
It's not as fun at home.
Dark memories connected to a lot of these candies for me.
Jotaroza, colon, fudge and saltwater taffy coming to the temple weed -filled halls of comedy
central suit.
Is that even a place anymore?
What do they do?
It's a guy in a shack just like putting in tapes as a gala web series.
Then then like, you finished production on the web series and the guy with the check vanishes
into thin air.
A lot of that stuff goes on.
Dear God, I can't even believe they still have a logo.
I'm like, what is going on?
Look, even when they had fucking South Park Broad City and all this shit, they always acted
like it was a clown show over there.
We don't know what money is.
Yeah, you do.
And now, come back to bite them.
They don't know how to treat talent.
They got too late.
Unless you'd like me to make you a pilot, Comedy Central, in which case I love your product
and I have for you.
I would make a pilot for them and they could put it out over the soup cans connected by
strings that they broadcast.
Like, I'm like, I don't even know.
They're putting everything fully on YouTube now for free.
I watch the whole John Stewart thing for free on YouTube.
It was crazy.
Yeah.
They got into the internet game too late.
Man, Viacom was kicking and fucking screaming with the internet.
I remember when it was happening and they were just like, they didn't know what to do.
Viacom, if you're listening to us, entity of Viacom, you owe me and my fellow mispat writers
so much money and residuals, get off your ass, hire a residual person and pay us what we're
out.
Plus interest or you will be sued by the writer's guild of America.
You've been warned rice and now over the airwaves, this is your fourth warning.
Okay.
That sucks.
They're not going to pay you.
Sure.
This is the one that will push them over.
Yeah.
Now, I'd like to do a little screaming in.
No, not screaming in.
What do you call it?
You got a product.
Scary stuff.
I haven't done one of these in a while, huh?
No, we haven't.
But the reason I even bring it up is that I got it in the mail as I was walking in for
Joe today to join for the podcast.
But you got it for me.
Kujo.
No, I got it in the mail for me.
Oh, you said, I think you said for Joe when I was going to meet you for the podcast.
Okay.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
On Zoom.
Okay.
No, it's okay.
But I got this Kujo 4K.
Okay.
I love the old classic poster.
I love the poster.
It contains dog days, the making of Kujo.
Just call it the making of Kujo.
I mean, you know, they title these stupid feature at just call it the making of.
Nobody is anyone in the country going, have you seen dog days?
What's that?
The making of Kujo.
And the nominee is for the best documentary short subject.
Oh, dog days, the making of Kujo.
It also has Kujo revisited around table with stars, D Wallace, Danny Pintaro, Daniel Hugh
Kelly, and director Lewis Teague.
Okay.
A bunch of interviews, audio commentary.
All right.
I can't wait.
Audio commentary by Lee Gambin, author of Nope, nothing wrong here, Colin, the making of Kujo.
Here.
Lord.
Uh, 2013 audio commentary by director Lewis Teague and a 2007 audio commentary by director
Lewis Teague.
Wow.
How low is your life if you listen to both of these Kujo commentaries by director Lewis
Teague?
Well, not even a decade apart.
And he's calling the studio.
You guys ready for another commentary?
No, Lewis.
It's been three years.
Just recorded it.
What format you needed?
And I recorded it.
Um, I'm embarrassed to admit, I've never seen Kujo.
I've only ever seen like the highlights that that's everybody's seen.
What?
I know we talked about Kujo.
No.
I don't think so.
I've seen shit.
Let's do it on the pot.
I'm watching it tonight.
All right.
I don't have it.
I don't know.
You heard it here first.
You heard it here first, folks.
Um, I've seen, you know, that scene.
Where they're stuck in the car.
Or isn't that the whole movie?
They're in the car.
There's a lot of car.
You have you read the book?
No.
It's just never.
Uh, I'll watch it.
It just never interested me greatly.
The dog going crazy or whatever.
Looks pretty great too.
Gotta be honest with you.
One of his best.
Um, I have a second gap in your, uh, your.
Demography.
Joe.
Yeah.
Now, is it now, now nostalgia aside?
Is it a, yeah.
Is it an actual good Stephen King adaptation?
Because children of the corn was always held as a classic
King movie when I was growing up.
And it sucks.
It sucks.
It's not like.
Well.
So pet cemetery strips away all of the divorce stuff
that makes the book.
I think extra interesting.
But it's sort of a lean mean adaptation of it.
Who knows the same way?
It strips away a lot of, it's the same thing.
It's divorced.
It's an unhappy marriage.
It's like the family splitting apart.
There's a lot of drama and backstory.
That's cut away in favor of just dog action.
Um, so the books are better read and it flushes it out.
But like, that's the case of most adaptations.
This is a tight 90 minute, you know,
jaws style man against the elements horror movie.
Like the edge or something.
It's great.
I love it.
I'm excited to rewatch it.
I have a scary stuff as well.
And I also have a news.
Yeah.
Uh, I read the, this apparently leaked a few years ago,
but I, I'd never read it, but I read the,
finally, the Colin Trevaro.
Screenplay for his installment of what was supposed
to be the third Star Wars movie.
Um, he was then, for whatever reason,
taken off the project, the script was ditched.
And they went with the JJ Abrams thing.
Um, it was called dual of the fates,
which is an awesome title because the, uh,
Phantom Menace, which is technically the beginning of it all,
episode one, the, the main theme from that is called dual of the fates.
And, um, and this brought it all full circle.
Uh, it's an excellent script.
I don't know why they didn't make it.
It did just the right amount of fan service.
It was a very different story.
It did not bring the Emperor back.
It did not go back to Death Star technology or any of that.
It was a very, uh, personal story about the balance of,
and the fate of the universe.
And it rested on Ray as the light side of the force.
And Kylo ran as the dark side.
These are spoilers if you're going to read it.
I apologize, but, but Kylo is not redeemed in it.
In fact, he, he, well, he's sort of redeemed,
but he did right before he dies, but it's very brief.
Luke is in it.
A lot.
Uh, no, Walker.
Mm hmm.
As a force go.
And they, and they, they, they build on the force goes.
Oh, I see.
I didn't go.
You were kidding.
Uh, Leah.
Look, my first assumption is because Carrie Fisher died.
They couldn't go with such a lay a focus story,
but lay is in it.
A lot.
She's awesome.
Han comes back in a flashback.
And it's a much better appearance than, than he got in the,
in the actual movie that hit the screen.
Um, look, it's just a great.
Thin's character gets an actual story arc that comes to a great.
Conclusion, where he actually leads a rebellion of other stormtroopers
that defect against the first order.
Like it's the whole thing is awesome.
The whole movie is awesome.
Lando's involvement makes way more sense.
Um, it was just a great script.
It was a great script and it, and it was tethered to the.
Requels and the, and the original trilogy.
Much more so than just in a way of fan service,
where it made sense story wise and whatever.
So if you want to read it, I suggest reading it.
Uh, it was very fast read.
I blew through it.
But, but I liked it.
And, um, and speaking of fan service.
Yeah.
This headline, I had to, I had to.
Walsh, I couldn't wait to pull this aside and read it to you.
All right.
This is from movieweb .com.
This is a new psycho.
Coyote versus Acme actor addresses leaks and shelved film, Colin.
You ready for his quote?
Yeah.
You can't cancel art.
Yes.
Yeah.
I've heard a lot of people saying, this is great.
I would watch this movie.
I actually liked Will Forte's message that he put up about how he watched it and thought it was great.
And he wouldn't have cared if he watched it and suck, but he thinks it's great, et cetera.
But don't come at me with it.
Can't cancel art when you're doing pay out of the acme.
Don't come at me with that.
Yeah.
I don't know who said it.
Uh, and people would say, I don't value myself enough.
No, you're an artist and what you do is, okay, I don't say that, you know, I don't think people
should really say that. Arts decided after you're gone. Why are they not released? I mean, it's
all just, it's all just a money play. It's all just, we don't care if it's good, we don't care if
it's bad. We realize now we can make more money shelving this and collecting the insurance
or whatever the hell it is, whatever that play is, then then releasing it. That's got to just be
what it is. They almost never go back and do a script that's been shelved that almost never happens.
I don't know why. I guess it's admitting defeat the first time around, because by then it's
usually a previous regime, because these people change office so much. It's a ridiculous thing too.
We fear these people who all have their jobs for about two years at a time. Why? Why do we give
them such a power? I don't know, Joe. Only because for two years they have it, but it doesn't
matter because half of the 90 % of the shit they get in motion in those two years doesn't go anywhere
because they're gone the next whatever. It's all just a fucking charade. It's stupid. It's all stupid.
I found what Tyler Perry said and did very interesting. He's getting some backlash,
but he stopped that expansion on the studios and he was like, I don't blame the guy. The guy's
like, look, I see the writing on the fucking wall. You want me to lose 60 million, whatever the
fuck he was spending to build those studios. He's like, no, I'm not losing this money. This is what's
about to happen. You're going to be able to shoot a movie. You're really going to lose the
port when we just come off of a big strike about this very issue. Do it quietly.
Well, it was kind of a slap in the face, but he's a strange guy.
There is no quietly with Tyler Perry. The guy, you know, somebody's going to,
oh, somebody, you know what I mean? Somebody, we live in a world of rats. Somebody was going to
go to the press and say something. Jimmy Fallon can't put his writing staff on hiatus without these
rats going into rolling stone and trying to do an expose. So I don't blame Tyler Perry for speaking
out about it, but I also don't blame him for the move. I don't think that's him being selfish.
I think that's him saying, guys, it's going to be an absolute loss. I don't know what to tell you.
Like, you know, what are you supposed to do? The guy's done more for independent
film and actors and creators than almost anybody. I think he's given enough of himself.
I've been down Atlanta. You hear all sorts of things about Tyler Perry. I just, I don't speak on
the man. He's also a guy who everybody has NDAs about, which I think says a lot.
Pat, by the way, I'm not exaggerating, has a black hood over his head, like he's in the skulls
right now, telling us secrets about Tyler Perry Jesus. The crew, Greg T Nelson, Joshua Jackson's skulls
Oh, yeah, that's yeah, but it is a real thing. The skulls is a real secret.
Yeah, I think I saw one and two and then I did not go the straight to video around.
I saw speaking up, so on Deadline Hollywood, which is like the really annoying, you know, Hollywood
up to the minute news site. They have a movie reviewer, but it's hilarious because it's just a Hollywood
site for Hollywood people. So the movie reviewer only gives good reviews. It's this guy Pete
Emmand, who's already been outed as being paid. He was a paid critic by the studios and then he got hired
by this site to write puff pieces. So he's writing these reviews. And I saw a review. And if it wasn't the
new Tyler Perry May, a culpar, it was one of these new movies that came out that's like notoriously
terrible. And he gave it this big rave and it kept going on and on. I think it was Ricky Stanickey.
And he keeps reading it and going, my buddies and my buddy Santino's in that movie. I hope
it's actually going to watch it tonight. I'm going to watch it tonight. Let's say it wasn't. Let's say
it was Michael. Let's say it was, I don't know what it was. Sure. Sure. But it's a rave review.
And I'm reading the rave and it just seemed so soulless and unconvincing. And then there was a
comment one lonely comment at the end of it. And it said, hang it up, Pete. And that really just made
me laugh. Just a man writing this like 5 ,000 word review and the comment, hang it up, Pete,
the guy who wrote it. I love somebody being so dismissive of something that's worked that hard on
it. It always just makes me laugh because that's the business every day. People are dismissive of
things you work really hard on. It's true. Do you want to go to the corner? The movie. Yeah, I do,
Joe. Let's talk. What have I seen? You know what I've heard is great that I'm going to watch tonight.
Actually, I'm racking up a lot of shit to watch tonight. But apparently there's an hour -long
documentary about the making of I of the beholder. One of our listeners recommended it to me on the
Patreon. I don't remember the name of it, but you can easily Google it. I have the beholder stars,
you and McGregor. I remember despising that movie when I saw it. I hated it. And this movie is
apparently like an hour -long dissection, kind of like the alien three documentary they did with
Fincher about how a studio can destroy a movie. So it works as kind of a film school, but an
anti -film school, like how to do it when you're dealing with nightmarried sex and stuff. So check that
out. Maybe that's something all those hellians can get behind and watch because they hear it's great.
Anyway, that's what I want to watch. Described as a mystery film that employs magical realism.
What's that? The I of the beholder. That's the description. I don't even remember that aspect of it,
but I believe you. Is Nick Holty in it? Or am I confusing it with Nightwatch?
I mean, these fucking films in the late 90s where Diamond doesn't set this all off. And it was like
kiss the girls. Right. What was the spite? Along came a spider. You know,
because the girls ain't bad. This girl's ain't bad. No, I'm not saying any of them are bad. I'm just
dignity is not in it, but Jason Priestley and Katie Lang are were you expecting that?
AD Lang. I was definitely not expecting. Yeah. Anyway, I sold my copy of the wrong guy for about
a hundred bucks because I was like, you know what? This movie's funny, but if it's going for a hundred
bucks, I might as well sell one. The selling's good. The stock is up in the wrong guy, which I bought
for $5. But if you haven't seen it, have you seen this movie, Joe? I have. I'm a big Dave Foley fan.
I didn't I didn't love it, but it was it was okay. I wasn't crazy into it though. Yeah, I'm a
Dave Foley fan myself. He's great in it. He does a lot of kind of silent comedy type physical stuff
that's really funny, sort of him taking on the anti -dick role. Anti -dick was always doing the
pratfalls on news radio. This came out in 97 so right around the time of news radio. The other
co -writers have like David Anthony Higgins has a subplot that's fun. It's somehow funny in my opinion
for the full 90 minutes where everything he calls in, he's a cop, everything he calls in is just to make
his life cushier like he wants like. He's like, yeah, you know, we'll definitely we'll need a hot
tub probably just to kind of sell the idea that we're on vacation. You know, he's just a cop using it
for the perks, which I think is a very funny bit. That they keep pumping Joe Flaherty's funny in it.
There's definitely funny, you know, tiny bits. And then there's gags that are clearly Simpsons
based. Those my guests come from Jay Cogan who was one of the co -writers with Foley Cogan wrote a
lot of the best of the Simpsons. But if you're a fan of the Simpsons, if you're a fan of kids in the
hall, the wrong guy is worth checking out. I wouldn't pay $100 for my copy of it, but I liked watching it
again. It was a funny movie. I will dedicate my corner to hard work as Pat was talking about hard work
earlier. And I will start with I went to the premiere of my friend Rory Scoville's new comedy
special. It is called Sex Religion and a few things in between. Very funny. It is a very funny
special and it is absolutely filthy. Yeah. I texted Rory the next day. I go, I had no idea you're
an absolute pig. Like, please never change. It was disgusting. I loved it. This was like a big
Jay Okerson level dirty set. I loved it. It was hilarious. Rory is very funny. And one of the few
nice people in the business. And I've known him from when he first came to New York. We've been friends
for a long time. So it was fun to see very well shot, very well directed, very fun. Conan O 'Brien
produced and check it out. It's just a lot of laughs. There's not really much more I could say than that.
I love the idea of producing a stand -up special. Yeah. What are you really doing?
Well, for Conan, I think it means my company will shoot this and my name is on it which will help
you greatly. Alright, fine. So I'm certainly was trying to take a shot at my dear sweet Conan.
I watched for the first time I made a blind purchase at half off of the 4K special limited dish
of Barbara Rella. Oh boy.
Starring Jane Fonda. I can see here I gave it three stars on letterbox which means I was trying to
convince myself. I didn't throw my money down the toilet. But Barbara Rella stars a young,
very foxy Jane Fonda. It is directed by Roger Vadim who directed a lot of sort of soft core of the day.
And you know, it's basically a space soft core porn epic with no porn or sex. So you're left with
these kind of vapid scenes with bad dialogue and lame sex puns and then maybe a glimpse, a fleeting
glimpse of like a side boob. So what you're left with is kind of the experience of watching USA up all
night when I was little, which is where these, you know, movies like bikini car wash company too,
but with the bikini scenes removed. Like you wouldn't see the nudity. So you're watching these movies
for the plot. That's how I first discovered Joe Bob actually. He used to introduce those movies.
But yeah, that's sort of what this felt like to me. And it's a legend, I guess, because it's kind
of a camp classic. It's style influenced among many other things, Austin Powers. You know, it's got
that kind of swing in 60s vibe and Jane Fonda is good in it. But yeah, I'll probably be selling that one
for sure. I did not really like the movie. Look for K, if you do like it, I really got it because
the flash Gordon one looked so great. I thought maybe Barbara Ellen would be similar, but not really.
I remember Mike Myers talked about how they loved our man Flint. Yeah, that was a huge influence
for Austin Powers, but I remember him specifying like we really liked it. We would not ironically liked it.
Yeah, I guess, you know, there's there's a set of movies that from that era that people just ironically
like. I'm sure. Anyway, another hard worker in the business, both in front of the camera and behind
and by behind, I mean his pursuit of children. I watched Jared from Subway. What a segue. What a
subway segue. This was one of the most stomach -turning documentaries I've ever seen. How many hours?
How many parts? It's two halves. Okay. It's like the bread that fit the sandwiches. It's two parts.
I think it's, you know what? No, I'm wrong. I think it's three parts. It might even be four. It's
multiple parts, but it's probably totals in about two and a half hours or something.
It's one of the most stomach -turning documentaries I've ever seen, flattering edits or they
pretty cold cuts. Cold medicine, folks. Yeah. I liked it. It's just, look, the guy is, I found it
fascinating because and weirdly, I did not find it exploitative. It sounds like it could be.
I felt like it did a very good job of showing you what kind of monsters walk amongst us and how
in certain ways human and in this case child trafficking works in this country with people like him
because I never knew that that's what he, what he was pursuing. I thought that he was in jail because he
like hooked up with a couple of 16 -year -olds or whatever, which I'm not saying is okay, but I didn't know
that it went to the length of what that it went to. Like he was actively interested in having sex with
children under 10 and he, whether he did or not, they're not able to confirm, but they got
in his house. He was using his subway fame to do so? Well, he was using the resources he got
from the fame to do so. It wasn't like he was going, like he did a lot of work with kids,
like he had a children's charity to help kids lose weight and stuff, but he didn't go after those
kids and he didn't roll around going like, hey middle school chicks, I'm Jared from Subway
or maybe he did, I don't know. It seemed way more like because of his status and the money and ability
that the job gave him, he started to open doors that he was able to suddenly open and it was,
it's incredibly disturbing. The woman that gets him all on tape is a woman he befriends early on
in his career and he admits to her that he thinks middle school girls are hot and she's a reporter,
so she starts recording him secretly and then she goes to the FBI and the FBI is like, look,
you're not allowed to record somebody without them knowing that's actually a felony, but if you do it
for us, we'll let it slide. So then they bring her in and she goes on and that's when it gets really
dark and she can't get out of it. It's a riveting story. I'm watching this going, how the fuck is this
not a movie? I'm sure they mean like, Jesus Christ. It's an amazing documentary but it is it's
disturbing. It's very disturbing. The lengths that he and his partner went to are really, really
it's dark and it's upsetting, but you know, I did think it was an important exposure that they made
with this piece of work. So Jared Frazier, Joe, come on, I didn't mean it like that. By the way,
it's called like, it's called like, it's the opposite of the dog days thing because this is Jared
from Subway calling, you know, the catching of a monster or it's like, guys, we don't need the second
part. We all know that he did something. Right. Jared from Subway is a great title. That's a great title.
You don't have to spell it all out, you know, how about Jared from Subway between the buns?
Yeah, I got got with a wink emoji next to that. Anyway, Jared from Subway, I went and saw on
the big screen here at the Los Filos 3 in my neighborhood. We need to talk about Kevin. Oh yeah,
which with each viewing, I am cementing as one of my all time favorite movies. I just got to say it.
Lynn Ramsey, I think more of her in color, I love, I'm probably not saying that right.
Rat catcher, I love. You were never really here. I love and I need to see again, but her masterpieces
we need to talk about Kevin, a movie I had a whole different viewing on this time on like my fifth
viewing of it. I saw it in a different way. I just think she really puts together hell of a picture.
I wish she made more than one movie every five, six years, but she probably has trouble getting
funding. She does movies about very difficult subjects like this one. I had also forgotten
that what the movie is ultimately about is kind of, I'm not going to say it, it's you know, it's
a end of the end of the movie spoiler. It's just structured in a very interesting way that
you know, that this is a movie I would call art because I would say it reveals something new to me
every time I watch it. I love it. I love till to swim in it. I love a young Ezra Miller in it.
I love the whole John C. Riley's great. I forget he's in the damn movie every time I see it.
It's just one of my favorites of made in my lifetime one of my favorite modern movies. I love it.
See it if you have. I own that courtesy of our friend over at
a silascope. So do I. Silascope. Yeah. And thank you again. Because I watch it often.
All right. My last one documentary, another man who worked very hard, but in all the right ways,
Albert Brooks defending your life. I finally watched this. It was great. It was really great.
It was great. It's just you know, it highlights Albert. I was shocked at how little
I don't know. There was. What is what is it? Why is everybody avoiding the topic of Bob Einstein dying?
Why is this not being addressed anywhere? They're not addressing it on curb. They don't even mention it in this.
Albert Brooks at length talks about the loss of his other his dad talks about his mother.
They interview his other brother that he never even mentions like the relationship is because of
how non -emotional Albert Brooks is throughout the interview with Rob Reiner. My guess is that he just
didn't want to be emotional on camera. I was like, it's too recent. I don't want to talk about it.
It's my guess. Yeah. Maybe that's what it is. Or maybe Bob Einstein was like, when I die, don't you
dare ever. Yeah. Sure. Sure. You know, who knows. They already made a documentary about him.
So. Yeah. So. But it was a great doc. It moves pretty fast once they actually get to the work,
which is interesting. They spend a lot of time talking about his childhood and his early years.
And you know, when he broke onto the scene and all that. And then once they get to the movies,
they kind of really start flying. But it's enjoyable nonetheless. I did realize something where it's like
and this is upsetting. HBO is doing this in every one of these things that they make.
They're interviewing people that are clearly not big fans. And then they show them clips clearly.
And have them react to those clips as if this scene has moved them.
And it's not real. It's not true. And it's very obvious that it's not true.
You can't trust anything you look at anymore. Jesus Christ. I was trying to say nice things about
this. I liked it. I love Albert Brooks. I hope he does another something. I just hope he acts
in a comedic way again and something. I would love for him to write and do something. He probably couldn't
get funding now with guns to their heads. But I don't know. But you know, Albert Brooks all day
every day. And it reminded me yet again that modern romance is the greatest romantic comedy of all time.
It's real classic. I think calling it a romantic comedy a bit of a stretch. But I love it. It's
calling it a romantic. Why? That's exactly a romantic. I wasn't trying to provoke. I don't think
there's anything romantic about them. I think it's sick. But I love it. And I relate to it. I just think
it's sick. Oh, yeah. It's a study of a sick man. I think they're both sick. Yeah, he's sicker.
Come on now. But that's why it's sick in that movie. He's beyond. That's why it's called modern romance.
It's like this is what a modern relationship looks like. Yeah. Look, it's one of my very favorite movies.
I own it. I love it. I'm just saying. You're right. You look criteria out of it. They should.
Here. What are you? A trash man? You're a garbage can. You know that?
They do. Yeah. Criterion did Lawson America and defending your life. It's time.
It also contains a lot. There are people out there. All they do is rape.
That's great. When she's walking towards the bushes, when she's mad, she runs out of the cabin.
Get that. That's full of snakes.
No, I think I love defending your life. I think it's the least worthy of the criterion stamp out
of his first four movies. I think good and agree more. I'm a huge fan of it. But I think real life
is so fucking funny because you add Grodin into this. For some reason, the Grodin Brooks pairing is just
perfect. Perfect. Anyway, all right. I guess where that's it, right? Yeah. I think we only did two
a piece, but we can end up there. I did three and you started. All right. So we must have
each done three. You say so, boss. All right. What do we got here? We got Conan, the barbarian,
Conan, the barbarian and Conan, the destroyer. I've never seen the rock Conan or really any
other version of Conan. Have you? It's not the rock. The rock was Hercules. Jason Momoa was the remake
of Conan. I thought you're going to say it's not the rock. It's Dwayne Johnson. No. By the way,
he's back in WWE and he's a heel and he's amazing. He's back to being like the rock and it is
stellar. Man, that guy, the second one area starts deflating a little bit. He just rolls right into
the next. He's just off to the next thing. He's he's doing all his old shit again. He's coming. He
can't come out a couple of years ago. He's like, I want to congratulate everybody. A record was
broken here in attendance this evening and everybody's cheering and it's like classic Dwayne Johnson
cheese like great job. Go for it, everybody. And they're all cheering and he goes, I'd like to congratulate
you on the biggest gathering of trailer trash ever recorded on that. He's so he slid right back in
to be an asshole. It's awesome. Uh -huh. Anyway. All right. No, I had never seen the Momoa one at zero
interest. The okay, so let's start with Conan the Barbarian. These are the movies that made Arnold's
words a nigger. This is what led to the Terminator. This is this is it. This is what really
cement or pushes him into the spotlight and then Terminator sort of cements it. But written by Oliver
Stone and John Millius. John Millius also wrote Apocalypse. Now he's a very famous like Hollywood
gunslinging nutcase and script doctor. Yeah. So he's a wild man who really got his big shot directing
here. He also did red dawn a few years later. But yeah, him and Oliver Stone teaming up to make
like the most macho movie ever. That's, you know, you couldn't find two more perfect guys to do them.
Plot of the movie is Conan is a young boy at the top of the film. His family is slaughtered in
an invasion by a tyrantical king played by James Earl Jones with the coolest name ever in movie
villain history. Uh, and of course, now I'm going to blank on it. Uh, doosa doosa doosa doom. What a
cool name. Um, he kills Conan's mother in front of him. And then he Conan is put into slavery as a child.
He grows big and strong and into Arnold. Uh, and he is the strongest of all those that was captured
as he grows. He then fights for them for sport and wins so many fights that he learns how to kill without
conscience and is set free. And when he is set free, his goal is he is going to track down this king
and kill him. That's all he wants to do. And there are the adventure starts. Uh, and it's so as
Lauren Hill said, it could all be so simple. Why do we complicate this shit? You mean, you know,
like that's it's the heroes journey. Yeah. You know, you mean this is simple to to amazing
screenwriters to do this, you know, but like we never learn the lessons. That's a simple story,
but an effective story. He wants revenge. You're on his side from a boy to a man. Right.
I thought, I thought you were saying this movie was overcomplicated. You're saying no, this is the
prototype. Exactly. The prototype for this kind of story. You don't need to muddy it up any more
than this. And if you're going to do an origin story, give us a little paste and move on with it.
This flick is from 1982. It is action. It is brash. It is bloody. There is nudity. It's
practical effects galore and some great, great. Like watching paintings come to life. Great stuff.
Great visuals, especially in the 4k. And I will say this movie epitomizes every movie that when
you think of the video store in the 80s, Conan the Barbarian is the movie that should be representing
it's up there with escape from New York as was like the 80s video store movies that should really
represent the whole concept. I don't think that the national amputation poster was parodying
Conan, but it may as well have been. They're basically the same thing like the on the big like
it's half Conan. It's half Conan and half Star Wars. It's definitely a mix of the two.
I mean, it's just an awesome movie. Every performance is pitch perfect.
It's the first time Arnold says to hell with you. When he's praying to his god,
Crom at the end, when two men have to defeat an army attacking and he goes, you know,
may two men defeat the army, you know, or at least stand valiantly. If you're not listening
then to hell with you, which is so great, because it's his final moment. If they can pull this off,
he can actually go kill Tholsa Doom. Right. And it's the moment where after an entire movie of him
praising this god, Crom, which there's even a scene when he meets up with his thief sidekick,
he talks about how his god is better than the thief's god. Crom is the greatest god of all.
And his whole goal in life is to be honorable enough, a warrior that when he dies, he goes before
Crom and is accepted. And then in this final climactic moment where he's got to take on a full army,
he says to hell with you, because he realizes, I've been on my fucking own from day one.
And here we are again. And I don't need anybody. I got this. And then by the way,
is this the first movie to do the home alone style,
booby trap ending? Like this is the whole image. Yeah. Right.
Movie ends with him decapitating James Earl Jones, as James Earl Jones stands in front of his
congregation of worshipers with a broken sword. So you actually see how many times Arnold has
to hack at his neck to cut the guy's head off because his sword has been broken. It's fucking awesome.
It's so awesome. And it contains many, many lines that my friends used to say long before I was
ever allowed to see this movie, including what is the best thing in life to cross your enemies,
see them driven before you and to hear the lamentations of their women. Right.
Love it. We don't approve of Conan's actions, but we love the line folks. Yeah.
I would imagine that Millius and Stone probably had a more rape and pillage heavy version of Conan
originally. I don't know that for sure. But what they got here is just like, it's perfect. You
want an R -rated version. It's more fun and pulpy than something like Excalibur, but I personally find
Excalibur to be too long, too slow and too boring. So for somebody like me who does not love
the sword and sorcery shit at all, I think Conan is really perfect and right up my alley. It's
enough of the wink, but not too much where it's just like Beast Master or something where I haven't even
seen Beast Master, but you just can't really take it seriously. Conan takes its nonsense just
seriously enough. And in the process, you got to kick ass action movie. I think it would make
as we'll get to Conan the destroyer, but I think it would make an amazing double feature with the
Northman, which is kind of the modern Conan and another movie that I fucking loved. It would be an
awesome night. It made me want to revisit the Northman, but I just we talked about the Northman. I
but Robert Egger is on the bonus features of this because this movie is the it is the Northman.
It's the same almost the same exact plot. It's also He -Man. I read up on on the Conan literature
and Tholsideum in the books has a skull -like face and I'm like, oh they just took He -Man from
that Skeletor and He -Man. I loved loved Conan the barbarian. It was my second time seeing it. First
time I saw it, I liked it. Second time I was like, holy shit. Where have you been all my life?
The 4K is really sweet. The 4K is real sweet. Oh yeah. Now, oh and then the last thing I'll say about
Conan the barbarian. I love at the end, it flashes forward to him Gray, long hair and gray. The voice
over talks about how he has found his own kingdom later in life and he's sitting on the throne and
they don't say it, but he's so bored. He's just sitting there like just like where this sucks. I don't
want to kill. It's just such a great awesome shot and it really saddens me that they were going to
make a third movie, which for some reason they were going to call it the Legend of Conan. It shouldn't
be called that. It should be called Conan the Conqueror. It should be Conan the something, so it stays
in line with the other fucking movies and Paul Verhoeven was going to direct it and it was going to be
about the King, King Conan. I'm like, please, please, please. A Verhoeven Conan could still happen. I
mean, that would be amazing. Please. What you want? Make it. Make old Gray Conan and he has to come down
off the throne and fucking destroy everything for whatever reason. Yeah. Yeah. Where is it? Anyway,
Conan the Destroyer. You got a downgrade in every way. It's directed by Richard Fleischer who's kind
of a generic effective action director but who was probably a hundred years old when he made this movie.
He was near the end of his career. He had just done the jazz singer starring Neil Diamond and
Amityville 3D. They liked him so much. They brought him back for Red Sonia, which I have not seen.
Joe, have you seen Red Sonia? It's all as a kid. I was I was reading up on it after I watch this.
You know, Conan Swartz and Edgar was supposed to be Conan and Red Sonia but couldn't because of
licensing issues or something. Okay. So he just plays another character that's Conan basically
and it is considered the sort of unofficial third entry and it's it's Swartz and Edgar himself says
that is the worst movie I've ever made. Which Arnold hasn't made a shitload of terrible movies but
he's made a couple where I'm like Jesus Christ. I haven't seen anything from his direct to DVD period.
I hear there's good and bad. I haven't seen any of them. The Destroyer is a step down but I will say
it is it is the shinier. This is where they're going for the action figures now.
They couldn't make action figures of Conan because it was an R -rated movie. They wanted to make toys
and they couldn't which is one of the reasons that he man happened. They couldn't they had to make
a new property to sell barbarian toys because Conan was an R -rated bloody sex rom.
The Destroyer is where they're clearly going now for action figures and they want to get the kids
in the seats for this one. The Destroyer actually has a lower budget than barbarian usually a
sequel would get a higher budget but you can tell. I mean the entire climactic battle as fun as it was
because I love practical effects and I love this kind of shit. I mean I haven't seen anything like
that outside of a Godzilla movie that was just a guy in a suit. In this big movie I thought that was
crazy how much that was just a man in a suit. Yeah that's true. That was done a couple times in
this. I like Conan the Destroyer. Let's put it this way. This is the best way I could put it.
If Conan the barbarian didn't exist and you were like there's this movie Arnie did in the 80s
called Conan the Destroyer and you saw it you'd be like that's a fucking great Arnie movie. I love it
but the barbarian sets the bar so high that as a sequel it pales in comparison. If they made a third
one that was awesome the Destroyer would be fine to just be sitting right in there with them
and you go that's the worst of them all but it's still pretty good. It'd be like if in I know
temple dooms your favorite but if Indiana Jones ended after Temple of Doom yeah I think people would
hate Temple of Doom way more than than than they do like they would just be now they're most people
like I don't like it that much but it's still good I feel like that's how people would feel about
Destroyer if there was another entry that was awesome you know well yeah I mean it's in his
pairings in this like he has awesome pairings in Conan and in this one he is paired with Olivia Diabo the
sister from the Wonder Years he is paired with Will Chamberlain who does not have a lot of on -screen
charisma. I buy Chamberlain though is the brute in this I enjoyed him. I'm also reading here that
in an uncredited role as the dag -off monster at the end of the movie Andre the Giant.
See which is pretty cool. It would have been cooler if they just augmented Andre the Giant.
Yeah you know I agree. I gave the film three out of four stars and liked it more than barbarian
you know I can't agree with that every once in a while the man's a little inflammatory but I
uh seeing this for the first time cold liked it I probably liked it more than I would have
because I saw it in 4k and I think that a lot of times it just gives a great look to these kind of
sword and sorcery movies but Conan the barbarian went up for me to like wow this is like the kind of
template for this kind of movie standard and Conan the barbarian is are the sorry the follow -up destroyer
is just not up to that level it's fun but it doesn't even really work as an effective sequel to
barbarian because the whole tone is just sort of goofy and stupid uh and PG frankly it's just not
it's not what you want from more Conan adventures. Well but it's in 80s PG you're still getting
decapitations you're still getting tons of blood true uh I liked I liked that they tie it to the to
Conan where he is promised by the evil queen that if he does this uh uh job for her he she will
reunite him with his slain love from the first movie I liked that there was some connective tissue
there I think the saving grace funny enough of the second movie is the theme music the theme music
is so good and it's so the music in both is pretty fantastic yeah but like the title theme of
the second movie is so rousing like when that kicks in and he starts fighting guys in the swords are you
you get really excited so second movies worth a watch 100 percent it's just not the first movie
yeah I couldn't agree more and the new set uh the new arrow set the Conan Chronicles uh deaf you know
it's almost like buying stocks with these with these 4k's you know don't buy them at the top don't
buy them when they're 80 bucks these places always have half off sales watch Amazon if at all possible
buy them from arrow buy them from criteria and they just had their big sale um but yeah this I was
this is a box set that I've really been having a lot of fun with all the special features and they
did an amazing job cleaning up the movie the Conan Chronicles if you want to see both I got mine on
ss deep discount it was 50 bucks well well worth it well worth 50 bucks and it's got all kinds of
little goodies there's a really beautiful little booklet they put in there uh you know it was cool
so I think I've talked about this in the pod before but on the uh third floor in my house the third
floor is just basically a room that's obviously not as big as the rest of the house but uh I've been
turning that into like my collectibles throwback whatever room and uh I was a skeleton in a rocking chair
my dresses my mothers dresses are all up there you're you're pretty gowns um but I've been putting old
posters on the walls so as I that's how I'm decorating it and as I was watching Conan I was like
I have to get a cone in the destroyer poster because it's the cooler of the two posters
even the lesser of the two movies and then I and I'm on eBay looking looking and then I realize
wait a minute the arrow said I'm watching has two posters in it yeah of the movies and I was like
what a how great is that like I can oh this is awesome I'm gonna go hang those up up there that
and they're perfect yeah and all the cool little postcards and everything yeah they do nice work
they really do arrow you know let's call it what it is it's the more fun criteria and although
obviously I'm much more criteria and loyalist but there you go I think I think arrow took I would not
I'm not contradicting you I would just my take on it is arrow took what screen factory is doing and
they're like yeah there were kind screen factories great but arrow was kind of like we got it from here
boys yeah take it from here you got to do that meme the nerdiest meme of all time
like you know one of those things where you go it's like a cowboy sample take it from here whatever
a shout factory on the guy on the horse yeah arrow arrow with an arrow pointing to the to John Wayne
yeah you know one of our listeners will make this stupid stupid meme but please do not give this
more than five minutes of your time folks if that's the thing you want to do I get up for the
Conan franchise you would agree yeah hog hog way more up for the original barbarian but coming in as
a newcomer I really enjoyed destroyer and I can't I of course I recommend the great new arrows set
um we will be back shortly um chill with American fiction and um
uh when's this come oh god well it comes that this is out now it's I'm at south by south west this
week if you're there uh salsa windfall is playing uh on Tuesday night the 12th uh of course I don't
know the venue uh I probably shouldn't know that but I don't anyway if you're a badge holder or
you want to come see us please come see us the joey roses pop up is also happening uh at levolta pizza
please come by and get yourself a sample all you got to do is show your south by south which west
bag bag badge Jesus Christ um I'm also doing the street meat which is a conversation about street foods
and proprietors of restaurants that specialize in those this is also on the 12th at 5 p .m.
uh and then late that night at estrus bomba still the the guest on that one yeah still a bomba and and
marion um so just to recap levolta pizza club during the day on Tuesday uh for the joey roses pop up
with a badge you get a free sample um uh followed by the street meat at the creek in the cave at 5 p .m
roundtable discussion of street foods followed by salsa windfall 8 p .m. uh at uh I'll try to find
that and then I'm also performing stand -up on the final show at estrus pop volleys those are all south
by south west events but but but if you're in portland i'm there thursday night for one show and if
you're in seattle i'm there for two shows come out i got a bunch of other shows coming up in beacon
new york and other places in april into may come check those out i'm going to be in connecticut and
some other spots joderosa dot com for all tickets and venue uh information and everything okay i'm sorry
i did too much plugging uh i would like to make it clear i've never been but if you are ever around me
this goes for joe and anyone listening if you refer to it as south by done our friendship whatever
relation we have is done can i say that no you didn't and that's what that's just what i'm saying
joe passed the test today i would have let you pass because you're i'm i haven't announced it
but going forward just walking down the streets of la going to meet a friend for a drink the other
night it's like uh so actually i can't i'm actually adding up to it's south by it makes me
wretch i don't blame you i'm not a Patrick Walsh on instagram we're at c u and help out on instagram
uh thank you all very much we'll see you next time and we'll see you in hell