I'll see you in hell, we're back again in the month of January, today we're talking
about wicked. Yes, folks, it's the origin story of how the word wicked came to Boston. How
the first townies started using it to describe somebody who was smart or a pissa. And I think
Ben Affleck following this up, following air up with this origin story was a miss quite frankly, that's
all they're doing now is origin stories. I keep getting pitched origin stories of products. Like,
remember when they made the how the mop was invented movie joy. Yeah, I've cited it frequently on
here. I've seen the film. Yeah, I love it. The David O 'Russell like lightning fast camera angles
about the invention of the mop. I was like, you're not making this more exciting, you're making me sick.
But who knew that would be the new the new like genre like it's they make more origin stories
for products than they do westerns. It's crazy. Starring Lawrence. Correct. Jennifer Lawrence.
Jay law. Joy was that the characters we've also discussed this is that I've never known as the
character named joy or the mop is called joy or something. I mean, you want to talk about obvious
writing the characters name was joy mop. Yeah, folks, I would be remiss if I did not shout out the good
people of Los Angeles. And for quite frankly, the bad people of Los Angeles who are going through
a crisis right now with the LA fires. It is not lost on me that one change of the breeze, one
whip of a tree branch could burn my house down. I realized how completely naive I am. I was asking
people like if your house burns down, I mean, insurance covers that. Not really. And they're also kind
of pulled out, you know, obviously, it's a big news story that they pulled their coverage. State farm
and other places, but unbelievable. This is where it's a crisis in every way. It's just it's one of
those crisis that exposes a million other crisis is crises. You know, this is a reckoning day. Yeah,
of sorts, horrible tragedy for so many people. And then seeing what the insurance companies are doing,
then also seeing celebrities asking people for money, this is going in so many wild directions.
I feel terrible for anybody that's been damaged by this obviously or injured even. It's horrible,
but it is just wild. Of course, it's been politicized to the bone already.
It's just nuts. Did you did you see the thing? Oh, God, I can't remember the girl's name and who she
was connected to. But I've never said this in public before. My girlfriend was telling me I have a
girlfriend. Now, it's not interesting. My girlfriend was telling me there was a girl, a woman in
Hollywood that was like months ago was like, there will be fire. They will say it is natural. It is not
natural. They are burning evidence. Yeah. And yeah, lo and behold, this fire happens. And now they're
not saying like whatever percentage of it is arson being added to it. You know, those aren't just
all crazy arsonists. Some of those people are like, we got a chance to burn the files, burn the
files right now. I mean, of course, and it could be coming from one of a million, like it's the setup
for a modern Chinatown. It really is who started the fires, follow the fires. And it could be LA
corruption who was completely unprepared for this. You know, the mayor every time the interviewer
looks like she just shatter pants. Honestly, it's like she just dropped a doose and they put the
camera on her every time they ask, which is not reassuring. Gavin Newsom is like a Calvin Klein
model. And he's got about that much depth. You know, I feel like he's between hinge swipes every
time they ask him about the fire. Like we're doomed. We're fucking doomed. And then you got P
Diddy. So that last night, I went to dinner with my, you know, good girl. I'm dating. You can't label
anything these days. And I go, hey, she's like, because she's like, well, what, what would possess
somebody if it was arson to do all this? Because they've already caught arsonists. It's not, it's not
a conspiracy. They've caught arsonists. They also let a guy go who emerged from the woods carrying a
blowtorch. Jesus Christ. They said, we can't prove anything. So we got to let him go. The neighbors
had to attack him. So anyway, I started talking to her and I'm just getting louder and louder because
I'm not drinking. So I have no way to regulate my emotions. And I'm going like, he, I was, I laid out
like, I was like that, you know, the Charlie day meme with, you know, connecting the strings.
But I'm, I'm like, here's, there's a million people it could be. And by the end, there's like
people listening into my conversation, but I might didn't care. I'm like, P Diddy from prison,
you don't think he has access to thousands of minions. You know, he can go to some, you know, poor kid
that he fucked up his life a hundred years ago and go, hey, I'm going to give you five million
dollars if you burn Los Angeles to the ground, get your little friends together and go burn the
city to the ground. It could be 18 year olds. He's sending out, you know, people that you'd never
suspect that would never get caught. And he's like, what's getting taken out? The Hollywood hills and
the Pacific palisades where the celebrities live who have probably have, you know, footage and evidence
in a blackmail on this one and blackmail on that one and everything else. It's all bad. It's all bad.
And we'll never know the truth. Yeah, it's, uh, this is dark stuff, man. This is a dark, dark,
dark stuff. Also too, just for the public, the, the general American public psyche, this is what? This is
the 36th tragic, hard, horrific event that we have no control over and have to be at the mercy of
in about the last five weeks. I mean, it's, it's, it's, this is unbearable. Everybody, I'm talking
on my friends. We're all saying the same thing. I don't know, man, I'm trying to bounce back out
of that holiday thing. But I'm still kind of drinking a little too much. I'm still kind of
cutting loose a little too much. I don't really know. I'm like, guys, we're having a nervous,
we're having a collective nervous breakdown. Nobody can handle this anymore. This is, yeah.
It's one thing after the next where it is horrific, it is tragic, it is devastating. It's just
that completely decimates the human spirit. And the worst part of it is there is no fix. You're just
horrible. And then you see the thing where the insurance companies are pulling what, you know,
what that does to the morale of, yeah. Everybody, the guy that lives in Idaho that's not even worried
about a fire. It's just, they're letting you know on a grand scale now, take it or fucking leave it.
We don't have your back. The, the, the writings on the wall, it's like the, the, the youngest generation,
you know, 40 years behind me coming up, they gotta just know they're fucking doomed.
I'm finally just pulling the trigger on that vasectomy. It's like, they're not going to be paying
out social security in about 15 years time. Like, you could at least sort of put your
faith in certain things. Like, oh, well, my life may suck, but at least I'll be taking care of
in the home stretch, not the case anymore. And then, you know, God only knows where we're going
from here. God only knows because it seems like it's only going to get worse. But folks,
we're here to talk about movies. I gotta know a psycho. Yeah, please.
Boy, you're gonna like this, Pat. I don't know if you saw this. Criterians, I mean, they're just,
I've been saying for years, criterion is just fucking with us. They're fucking with us.
These are the additions, the additions to the criterion streaming channel this month.
Oh, now if it's just the channel, the channel has all kinds of shit that doesn't mean they're
adding them to the collection. It doesn't matter. They put the criterion name on that goddamn chair
enough, fair enough, proceed. Oh boy, one is worse. I don't even know where to start.
Freddie got fingered. See, I knew I knew it was only a matter of time before they started calling
that movie art. My buddy, Scott Weinberg and I did a podcast about that movie. He did a podcast called
like it was called on. I don't know, something you can look it up. Scott Weinberg unfairly hated
or something about movies. And I came on basically to see if I still hated as much as I did when I
saw it theatrically. And I did. But there is something fascinating about it. There's something about
it that I get why people call it art, even though I disagree with them. Oh, it gets worse, Pat. Yeah.
Well, this is arguably the best of the ones that cocktail, which is, come on. Cocktail.
Wait, what's what's the theme? It's under the theme. I mean, I mean, anything that gets
added to criteria and is under a theme like holiday bummers or something. No, I don't know. This
doesn't say, it just says, this is just the March editions list. Are you sure it's the Tom Cruise cocktail?
Cocktail 1988. There was another cocktail. All right. Well, it did, it did give the world
Kokomo. So it's going to get far rumba, Jamaica. Ready? Yeah. Geely. All right. So they're doing a
disaster's month or something. No, no, no, no, no, these are sprinkled in with tons of like what you'd
expect. I very recently watched Geely. It is unfathomable by the mubbly bad. It is very bad.
This last one, I mean, this, this last one damn near sent me walking out into traffic. Yeah.
I'll do it two more. I'm saving the worst for last. Actually, three more. Zanadil, an epically terrible
fucking movie. Never seen the film roller skating musical, I believe. Well, they're remaking it with,
you know, fucking fish eyes from what's her name? Defrid? No. Oh, I'm not going to sit here and
guess girls with fish eyes. No, no, I'll get to declare who it is. I'll own my insult. Euphoria.
Fish eyes. The chick with you. Oh, Sid Swini. Yeah. Yeah. You can pick one defining trait about Sydney
Swini. And you went with eyes. Her eyes bug me. Her bug eyes me. The wicker man, the Nicholas cage
version. I swear to you, Joe, I'm going to what I have my own laptop here. They've definitely done
like a so bad. It's good month or something. I guarantee it. Well, no, no, no, Pat, this is all
March editions. Also in these is 310 to Yuma American movie. The master. You know, cruising,
what you could argue was maybe a misunderstood thing William Freken. There's there heavens gate.
There's a lot of it. These are all just mixed in as the March releases, but I save the best for last.
This is the one. Yeah. Barb wire.
The hand Anderson action movie. I've never seen it, but I know what it is.
Joe, I have to quickly point out. I'm so glad I googled.
Joe, you are reading us the criterion channels March 2024 lineup.
No, this was a new article I got. Joe, I'm looking at it. I'm looking at it, buddy, and it says,
and the rassy goes to featuring cruising, Xanadu, Barb wire, cocktail, Ishtar, Freddy Godfinger,
G. Lee, wicker man. Well, let me tell you then, and this is how sick this system is that we're
living in. This was shown to me as a new news story on Google sick. This is what we're doing, folks.
I mean, you know, I got it. Now I got to vet the time stamp of the news. They're telling me his news.
They pointed out. I don't want to say what I was either CNN or MSN museum or something,
but they proved the other night that they were showing footage from like a fire of a year ago,
saying it was live footage from the palisades. And it's like, guys, it's not hard to get live footage
of a fire. The city is still on fire right now. There's just so much. Are they really banning
TikTok? Yeah, but it'll just get bought and, and you know, turned off. They can sell it off to a,
okay. Yeah, it's, it's, it hasn't been bought yet, though, which is weird. I want to be free of it.
It works like a pacifier on me, a grown man. Well, even though these pictures are from last year,
yeah, right. Wrong in anything I'm saying. I mean, it's no, but it's doing what they're doing.
But it's a, it's a thing called and the razi goes to that's there is barbed wire under that? Yeah.
Okay. So they had like a bad movie month cruising. Okay, they're all under. Okay, never mind.
I don't think they should have put cruising in there. Well, this, but this also, and we've talked
about this. I don't think we talked about in the show. The reason I was so thought this was
relevant is their announcement that they just acquired the MTV movies. Yeah, which one good one
election, right? They're also now releasing, which I love the movie. They're releasing Jackass
in the criterion collection. I guess there's a world where you could argue that it got a lot of
John Waters in there. Yeah. You know, Jackass is our John Waters. There was a third one. Remember,
it was election. Jackass. There was the third. Beavis and Butthead. Yeah. Beavis and Butthead
do. Oh, and the original Kings of Comedy, which again, I guess you could argue it has, it has a certain
racial, I mean, it's a wonderful movie. It's hilarious. But I guess you could argue it's got a racial
significance. It's monumental for that reason. It's not just a stand -up comedy movie. It is a stand -up
comedy with a certain social significance. But at the same time, you know, I look, I worship the
ground George Carlin walks on. I think he was a philosopher decades ahead of his time. I don't think
the criterion should be putting out a George Carlin special. Yeah. Doesn't, I don't know. Maybe I'm
wrong. I don't know. The more I talk about it, the more it makes sense. Kings of Comedy.
I mean, I am a bit of a stand. I can admit that they've made some mistakes in the past. But yeah,
I could explain all those to you, I think. Not Beavis and Butthead do America quite frankly.
You know, I think I would be more receptive to a collection of the shorts coming out from the
criterion collection. That movie was not that show at its best for me. But, you know, I like it.
They did make a big effort in recent years to add more black films because they were called out as
being shamefully white. So usually they're spot on. I think, you know, like Malcolm X and they're
bringing out pretty much all the Spike Lee movies and deep cover and like all these really cool
interesting movies that they've brought out shaft and 4k. But like, I think original Kings of
Comedy fits into that world. If they put out a prior special, I'd be like, yeah, that makes sense.
Historical. Yeah. Give me some features. All right. Yeah, the feature will be his widow,
Hawking is merch, which she does in every fucking thing they interview her for iPhone camera.
Um, yeah, I guess we can get to the movie corn. Yes. You know, I saw I want to talk about
this. Kiss, kiss bang, bang. People love this movie. I saw it once it was fine. You know, it was,
it was one of those almost Tarantino movies that I just was like, yeah, that's fine. Joey, you get,
yeah, I was exactly like you once. I watched it. I might have rated it a little higher than you.
And then, but I love Shane Black. So Shane Black is one of the most highest paid screenwriters in
history, but he had a huge run in the 80s where he wrote, you know, last Boy Scout monster squad,
Lisa Weapon, last action hero, Iron Man. And then nice guys is kind of like, just a modern classic.
He said it wasn't successful enough to get a sequel. But I was like, what are some off beat Christmas
movies that I had and kiss, kiss, bang, bang pops up once in a while. There's a light Christmas
backdrop to it. Sure. Barely there. Um, it's every bit as entertaining as the nice guys. I got to
tell you, it's so fucking funny. And it's kind of got like, when you talked about blades of glory,
or I think you're talking about blades of glory, how you thought nothing of it and then you watched
it recently and were like, holy shit, it's really funny. The bar has gotten, the bar is in the ocean,
you know. So you watch something like this and you're like, what an absolute fucking delight.
And at the time, I remember there was 20 great movies in the theater when this came out. It was like,
I think it was around the time of like, good night and good luck and all these like, really good,
well -made movies. And yeah, it just kind of didn't stand out. And now it really jumps out, especially
the first hour of it. You know, it has with a lot of these mysteries. Sometimes the reveal of what's
actually happening is not the most fun part of the movie. You could say that about the nice guys too.
I don't even remember what the mystery was in the nice guys. I was there for the chemistry and the
banter of the actors. And that's the case here too. The mysteries, you know, not the most important thing.
But Downey Jr. is so fucking funny. This is like him right out of drugs. Shane Black was kind of a Hollywood
bad boy. Definitely partied with Downey Jr. in the 80s, 90s. So there's kind of a beautiful reunion.
Val Kilmer is hilarious as this guy named Gay Perry, who is a gay private investigator. Many,
many very funny of their timed gay jokes. I just got to say that Downey Jr.'s narration alone is
some of the funniest shit. It's up, it's not Lebowski level where the narration is like as funny as
what's going on in the movie. But it's really, really good throughout so many great jokes. Shane Black
is a great writer of dialogue. Chemistry's on point. Michelle Monahan, I was trying to figure out
why she didn't become bigger, why she's just been the wife in things for like three years. Exactly.
She's so hot and funny. And Michelle Monahan, like you definitely know her. I think she's playing the
wife in this new movie with Markey Mark. She plays Markey Mark's wife all the time.
But maybe she didn't want to go the story. Oh, no, no, bad, bad monkey. That's correct. Yes.
Yeah. And Trudy, where she plays a very similar role. She's great. She's great.
She's, and she, her and Downey Jr. are sparring. It's like it's funny. It's hot.
You got Corbin Bernson in the mix, which is just always a delight to see. And it's a fun L .A.
Kind of like modern Chinatown thing. I, I laughed way more than I expected to.
And I think it makes a great companion piece to the nice guys. You could imagine.
I mean, I, what a dream. These, a movie, sort of like a uniting these, these two worlds.
You know what I mean? These four cops unite to solve a case. You'd never get that to happen. But
it would be amazing. I'm a fan of these types of movies. I love it. If you've never seen it,
check it out. If you saw it and only thought it was okay, watch it again. Jump. I watched
juror number two. Yeah. Yeah. You know, we talked a lot about the fervor surrounding the movie.
The fact that it was, you know, disgraceful that they took, you know, Clint Eastwood's entire career.
In the eleventh hour, casted aside and buried his final movie on streaming instead of getting
behind it for a proper release. Yeah. Or any promotion whatsoever. I still do stand by that.
I think there's a level of respect you're just supposed to show.
Have to. Gone. And I thought this movie was good enough to have gotten that. I didn't think it
was a bad movie. It was okay. It was written a little. I don't know. I don't know what I wouldn't.
Let's put it this way. I think with a weaker cast, the flaws of the script would have been more
apparent or the sort of baseness of the script, rather, would have been more apparent.
You know, the dialogue isn't really bright. It's kind of obvious in places. It's a little dumb in
places. But you've got a great cast elevating all of it. Primarily Nicholas Hout and Tony Collette.
J. K. Simmons is probably the other most notable person in the movie.
We did a small part, surprisingly, small part for him. I got the feeling that a lot of these people
did this movie because they were like, it's Clint Eastwood. This is the last one. I want to work
with this guy, the legend. He really is one of the last of his time. I mean, this is it. There aren't
a lot of these guys left. I think that probably was what got him or got a lot of these people to do
the movie. And I'm assuming they probably won take of each scene as probably a lore into actors.
I'm sure the fact that he has won take of every scene is probably a lore into actors as well. Sure.
But well done. It twists and it turns and it keeps moving. That's for sure.
Um, but I don't know what it was. I just I ultimately didn't really care. You know,
you know what happens. The plot is just spoiler alert. The plot is a guy gets picked for jury duty.
It turns out the trial was a murder trial. And he realizes immediately that this woman was not murdered
by the suspected husband. But that in fact she is dead because he the juror killed her in a hit and
run accident. Uh, and it was and it was truly an accident. He, he, it's, he's driving on a stormy night.
The weather is terrible. He looks away from the road for a second because his phone dings and he hits
this woman. And doesn't say anything. Why? Because it will absolutely ruin his life. I got to tell you
yeah. As disgraceful as I think a hit and run is I kind of sided with him. I was like, yeah,
it was an accident, man. You didn't do anything. But then the problem is is now this guy is going to go
away from murder if he doesn't say something. Yeah. You're like, okay. But it also sucks that now this
guy's life is going to be completely ruined because a drunk woman who was out of her head was walking on
a road where she shouldn't have been walking in the middle of the night in a pouring rainstorm. Like
that doesn't seem fair either. So, you know, I don't know. It's, it's, it's kind of a, I guess that's
the challenge of the movie is what would you do? I guess that's the point. So that, that's interesting.
And the way it unfolds is, is I guess interesting. But there's something just missing about the,
there's just, there's an electricity that's not there that makes me care.
Yeah, I agree. I like Kiefer in it. But yeah, just kind of a sat there. I agree.
Kiefer's in it for two seconds. And just, you know, comes in and just goes, I'm your lawyer. This
is what will happen. And then you never see him again. So, anyway, it just likes it. He comes back
at memory service. I'm a fan. Folks, I saw the searchers, which I had seen before,
widely considered one of the best films ever made, often in the top 10 of all time best films
ever made. I don't agree. And I've never agreed. I, you know, when I was really getting into film
in my early teens, I was like trying to watch all the best movies ever made. And it was one
that I just scratched my head at. And I still do to this day. But Warner Archive, who puts out
a lot of great movies that might have fallen through the cracks. Otherwise, they put out
straight time, which is one of my favorites with Dustin Hoffman. But they're kind of a boutique label.
They put out, you know, probably 30 movies a year, something like that on Blu -ray. So they,
this is their first 4K release. And they put a lot of time and money and effort into it. I assume
there were grants involved because this is such a historical film. And I would, I mean, I give it
the highest of recommendations as a 4K. It's like something, if you want to show off a classic film
to your friends to show what the format can do for a movie that's, you know, 75 years old.
I thought this was one of the most beautiful transfers I've ever seen. It looks incredible.
Looks like art, you know, just like beautiful paintings going by in front of you.
It's a John Ford movie. He frames all his shots incredibly well. You can recognize a lot of his shots
in other movies because he's ripped off constantly. He's considered one of the greatest film
makers of all time. And the searchers is considered as masterpiece. I just personally think he made better
movies. And I think there are better Westerns and better great movies and etc. But I get its
importance. It was one of the first movies, much like how unforgiven, even though it came 100 years
into the life of the Western, it was one of the first Westerns to like sit and really deal with
the consequences of that life in a dark and believable and disturbing way. And the searchers
was one of the first movies. And it was much earlier, of course, that dealt with
the hatred for Native Americans and how kind of unfair and unreasonable it was. And to put John Wayne
in that role, a guy who had for his entire career been killing off the Indians.
It was a very interesting turn of events because what the movie is about, and it's also kind of
what taxi drivers about, which rips off the searchers pretty clearly, is John Wayne is going to rescue
his niece who has been kidnapped by Native Americans. But it becomes more and more clear that he's
less interested in rescuing his niece than he is just killing a lot of fucking Native Americans because
they fucked up his family, he wants revenge. And it's just about the ugliness of that and the
racism of that. So it's interesting. And it's a very well made and beautiful looking movie. I
personally don't, doesn't move me, I guess. It just kind of leaves me cold. But the transfer is
amazing. And I urge you to check it out if you got a 4k player. Joseph.
Joseph. I'm looking up who directed my next movie. I watched, this is my only other one.
Reagan. Oh yeah. Directed by Sean McNamara, who also directed Soul Surfer, the movie about the
girl they got her arm bit off. Sorry to laugh at that. Yeah. Well, it's, you know, we're not laughing
at her or I think we're laughing more at the movie. But you know, I don't want to undercut some of his
better work such as three ninjas, high noon at mega mountain, starring Hulk Hogan. I've seen the
whole trilogy or trilogy, if you will. Who could forget Casper meets Wendy? Okay.
And just before he did Reagan, he directed the biographical survival film on a wing in a prayer.
Okay. So this is the guy who would fall in out of favor with Hollywood and then
fell in with the right wing and started. I think so. Oh, oh, also, I can't believe I forgot. He
did cats and dogs. Three paws unite. Sister swap a hometown holiday and sister swap Christmas in the
city. I'm sorry. Pause unite is the best you can do. You can make any animal pun you fucking want.
And you come up with pause unite, not even a pun, not even a joke. Yeah. It's, it's wild. It also
sister swap. Well, airbuds out here doing world pup. Airbuds doing world pup. And you're going to
sit there and not even try. Okay. Golden receiver. Yeah. That's the best one is golden receiver.
I would do airbud colon wolf of Wall Street and make it a three hour improv heavy like emotional
downfall of a dog. Don't, don't stop there wolf of Paul Street. Come on, man. All right, Joe.
All right. We just want to make sure people get it. Sometimes you can put a hat on a hat.
Um, sister swap. He directed both those movies, which that to me, if I didn't know it a bit
or I think that was a swing or a porn. Yeah. Yeah. Uh, anyway, he also did aliens ate my homework and
aliens stole my body. This is my homework and bad. I'm saying that. Oh, I mean, these were Netflix
movies. Some of them. So he is working. He just, um, I, I feel like, well, Reagan was an interesting
exercise. Uh, look, it stars Dennis Quaid, Dennis Quaid, um, you know, whether you like his
politics or not, you might have seen him running from the LA fires this weekend. Did you watch that clip?
No. This man will not stop asking him questions. He is running things out of his burning home.
And this interview was like, Dennis, are you happy with the firefighters response? He just keeps asking
the questions to his credit. Dennis Quaid just answers the questions, but he also appears to be
stoned out of his mind. Go ahead, Joe. Whether you like his, uh, politics or not, Dennis Quaid is still
a great actor. Uh, and he's good in the movie. Like he's very convincingly Ron Reagan. Um,
um, uh, it's got a pretty strong cast, you know, Penelope and Miller plays, uh, Nancy Reagan. John
voids in it. Uh, mean as suvaris in it. There's a lot of people in it that are not as far as I know,
like outwardly conservative, uh, you know, and then there are people in it like Robert Dovey and,
uh, Scott Stap that very much are the big, all this hoopla about Scott Stap playing Frank Sinatra.
He's in one scene singing on a stage and the camera pans by him. Like there's no, I thought it was
gonna be like a, like a, cause Sinatra in the 80s was very good friends with Reagan and we go to
the White House a lot. So I thought that was going to be a part of it. Maybe it was and they cut it out.
I don't know. Um, Scott Stap, by the way, joining the long, not long, but the list of actors,
such as Ray Leota, who play Sinatra in a movie and clearly have never watched one clip of him
to embody how he actually moved on stage or anything. Um, I mean, unbelievable. Anyway, uh, I, um,
I will say Stap is not a dead ringer for, uh, Sinatra. He looks a little more like him than you'd think.
Mm -hmm, but it's clearly just like we're gonna get a singer who's conservative in here
should to play, you know, but look, it's, it's, look, it's definitely not a, it's so bad, it's good movie.
It's, it's not even really a bad movie. I was actually kind of surprised by the budget of this thing.
I texted you when I was watching it. I was like, this thing's got a higher budget than, you know,
it, it clearly was at least a 50 or $75 million movie. I mean, there, there was a budget here. Yeah.
It looks pretty good. Okay, you told me they got Penelope and Miller. I knew they backed up the
Brings truck. It's decently directed. It's well acted. The, you know, the actors are all pretty good,
but it's just kind of a cliche, you know, you know, Ronald Reagan was a hero and blah, blah, blah.
The one thing I was surprised they did was, um, when he starts to lose his faculties,
they leaned into that and they leaned into his stubbornness of how he wouldn't just accept it.
And it did portray, oh God, I hate dogs. I'm just at the end of my room with dogs. Everywhere I live,
neighbors got dogs. You know, you, sorry, they're barking in the hallway now as they always do whenever
they see another person. I don't know if they can hear me saying this right now. I hope not, but, uh,
I'm at a point where I'm like, you brought a wild animal into your house. Yeah. I don't have any
patience for it anymore. I used to love dogs. Hate them now. Um, anyway,
and you need more than one, you need more than one in an apartment, in an apartment that I get annoyed
if my lady is here 15 minutes too long. It's small enough that 15 minutes could, could make the
difference in a relationship continuing. You got two dogs enough. It's just insane. Anyway,
they can definitely hear me. God, well, um, the dogs, no, the person walking my neighbor,
I was like, Joe, you've lost your mind. These fucking dogs, I know they're talking about me.
I every time I walk by, they start whispering. As I say, at the camera should pan over and two dogs
are just sitting looking up at me. There's a paw with a glass up to the door. There's your movie.
There's your wolf of Wall Street. Yeah. Um, so anyway, the movie, look, it's, I was actually surprised
that in that part, they actually seemed to show a fair criticism of him. Uh, but outside of that,
it's, they, they show too how he kind of fucks up the Russia deal. And, and that's the thing
that, that W Bush, I, I'm sorry, uh, HW Bush fixed or whatever and, and, and, and ended the cold war.
Yeah. Reagan had a chance to do that and he didn't and, uh, but, but, uh, you know, I don't know.
It's, it's just a movie. It's just a biopic. It's, it, it, it fell a lot to me. You know what it
felt like to me. It felt exactly like the good shepherd, the deniro one about the, the math
Damon CIA biopic. That's what it felt like. I thought it was terrible, not terrible. I thought
it was like this. I thought it was like, it was like a well put together movie that was really boring
and I didn't care. Yeah. With a massive cast, every scene is a cameo. That's what it felt like to me.
So, so I was surprised at the quality level. Um, you know, I can't recommend it though.
I'm not going to watch it. Good. Um, I watched Jerry Springer colon fights camera action.
Now that's a pun I can get behind. It's a documentary on Netflix.
Uh, it's only two parts. It totals about 90 minutes. This, I look, I was a big fan of Jerry
Springer when I was a kid. Mostly because my grandmother was a big fan of Jerry Springer. She loved it.
Whenever I would stay over there, we would watch multiple episodes of it. She would laugh and laugh
and laugh. I have, I have fond memories of it. I saw a ringmaster theatrically with Jerry and
Jamie Pressley. I think that's where we met a young Jamie Pressley. But
this is one of the shittiest, most trashiest documentaries I have ever seen. Netflix
should be so ashamed of its documentary division. I'll just say it. The shit they throw up there.
Every once in a while, I wait until like at least two people tell me you must see this documentary
and there'll be something good. Now watch it and I go, yes, that was great. Otherwise, I can't do this
anymore. They are the cheapest, junkiest, most thrown together things. This movie is basically talking
heads interviews with four people that worked as like segment producers on the Jerry Springer show.
Mixed with clips of the Jerry Springer show. But Jerry is dead. They don't have Steve Wilcoast.
How are, you can't get Steve Wilcoast for your doc? Come on. I thought it was embarrassing.
They should not have released it. And maybe there's a four -part version that was even worse. I
don't know. But it's this guy who was a producer on the show back in the day sitting in a control booth
being interviewed control room. And he's like things just got worse and worse. You know, there was a time
where we had on a daddy and a daughter and the daughter called in and said, you know, my dad is
fucking me. He's having sex with me. And I want to come in and talk about it. And they wanted one
hotel room when they came to town. And I said, I don't know if I can do that. I want to get you in
two different hotel rooms. It sounds like you're in a bad situation. Trying to make it himself out
like he's a fucking hero 30 years later. You know, the guys clearly are wrecked. You can tell by
looking at him. And he goes, he goes, so anyway, morning of the show, I go over. I knock on the door.
This girl opens the door. She's in a pair of panties. She couldn't have been more than 14 years old.
And a dad comes out of the back and he's in his underpants. And I said, I can't do this no more.
You know, kept working there for like seven more years. So it is the the most
tall tree trashy. East is shit documentary. I felt gross watching it. By the way, I didn't feel
gross watching Jerry Springer. Jerry and his like great dry commentary on it sort of made me not
kind of fall into the muck with it. But knowing the behind the scenes of it is appalling and
disgusting. It's like the girls gone wild documentary that was on peacock. You don't want to
know how this sausage was made. And I think deep down, you knew you didn't want to know. Right.
But Netflix should have to have should have to have a minimum budget or something for these
documentaries. This thing, this thing is pathetic. And it's been the number one show on Netflix for
like a month now to show you where the brains of America are at. Although who will mind a judge?
I fucking watched it. Joe. Well, they, they love, you know, Netflix. I think at this point is,
it's, it's sensationalism. Yeah. If, if nothing else, I mean, that's just where they're at. But
yeah. All right. Well, anyway, let's get to, uh, speaking of sensational,
you know, the movie at hand wicked. I never thought I'd see the day where I'd be scoffing at a
wizard of Oz prequel. But twice now in the last decade, I've been forced to do so. Speaking of
downed junior, what, wait, was he in that one? James Franco as the wizard. Yeah. As the wizard.
Yeah. Christ. That one was so bad. Franco is the wizard. And, and, uh,
what's her face? Meal of coonus. Meal of coonus is the wicked witch. It's like, guys,
Jesus Christ. Can you even try? Can you even try to make this believable?
I'm directed by, uh, a sleeping Sam Raimi sound asleep for the entire production of the film,
apparently. So this film was directed by, um, Jonathan Xu, who directed, uh, never one good movie,
except for crazy witch age agents. Uh, he directed, crazy, rich agents, a, a title that,
I don't think we're going to be proud of in 40 years. No, you know, just going to say that.
Can I take you through Johnny's filmography? Please step up to the streets. Step up 3D,
GI Joe retaliation, jam in the holograms. All right, they did a live action jam. Now you see
me too. So this guy really gets off on, let me make a shit of your sequel to a movie that,
not many people care that much about to begin with. Yeah. Then he did crazy rich agents.
Then he circles back to snoozeville with, uh, in the heights. Oh, God, that sucked. God, that sucked.
And then they go, let's give him wicked and wicked for good, which is the sequel,
uh, which brings me to my first point of view. Real good. Yeah.
That's going to bring me to my first point about this fucking movie that there's two of them.
The play in its entirety is three hours. They made a two part version of the play,
the first installment of which is three hours because these fucking gluttonous scumbags
can't help but ring every fucking dime out of your, it's, it's, it's colonization of your
wallets, of your time, of your brain, of your interest. It is how the hobbit became three movies
from the shortest book, you know, it just, it benefits no one. You could at least argue. You could
at least argue with the hobbit that hey, we're going to try to do a balance, a prequel balance to
the Lord of the Rings movies. We're going to try to figure out how to make this movie, this book into
three parts so we can really hit every part of it. There are people that would argue, hey, any book
worth its salt on screen would need to be cut into at least two movies, maybe even three. You could
at least make some sort of argument for this. This is not an adaptation of the book. It is an
adaptation of the musical which was a very loose adaptation of the book. Yeah. They are bringing
the musical to the screen. They are not bringing the book to the screen and there is a working
version of it that has lasted for decades, a thriving successful, deeply successful version of it.
Yeah. For them to somehow cut this thing into two parts that that in each part as long as the show
itself is so insane and they do nothing with that extra time. Absolutely nothing. Nothing. The momentum
and pace of this movie is so robbed by needless, dramatic stalling and meandering. They take every
little moment they can to sit and dwell in it and sulk in it and sing more, even more.
And if I may, that is already a massive problem that I and I think a lot of people have with musicals
is the meandering. It's the okay, got it. Oh wait, now you're going to sing a six minute song about it.
No, I already got it. And when you already have that kind of laggy musical thing of like, all right guys,
you're taking three hours to tell a two hour story and the songs are not that great. So what are we
doing here? Now you're going to stretch that not only not only further but almost double it.
Like you're exactly right, Joe. There's scenes where it's like I feel like I'm watching like an
eight minute deleted scene that has no bearing on the plot at all. Why is this in here?
Watching the climax, the climax of the movie, there's like there's like the guards are beating the door
in in the tower room. They're in where they need to escape and she needs to fly. It's the only way
she can like escape and she's going to fly for the first time and it's this big exciting moment. It's
the big climactic scene and they sit there deliberating, singing back and forth, back and forth,
to the point where they just start to ignore from a direction standpoint. They just ignore
that the guards were almost through the door four minutes ago and now all of a sudden they're just not
because we have to show them sing some more. It is pointless. It is fucking pointless. This movie sucks.
This movie sucks. I hate this fucking movie. I'll get into what? Why? Let's start with fucking dumbass
Peter Dinklage. Let's start with that fucking idiot that took jobs away. Dinklage has destroyed
any sort of chance of working for little people. Yeah. He ruined it. If he sees little people about
to enjoy an opportunity, he speaks out on it until they remove it from them. He's a selfish little
fucking egotistical. I didn't mean little, didn't mean little shot. I just meant like I would have
said little either way. But he's a selfish fucking egotistical prick who wants to be the king
of the mountain doesn't want anybody else to fucking work. Okay. He ruined. I ran to it about this
on stage recently but I talked about it on Instagram too so I'll be repeating myself to some of you.
But I don't understand how many fucking jobs one Peter Dinklage interview can ruin but I mean the
munchkins in this are all five foot five. Yeah. They're not munchkins. Why are the fucking
it called munch? Now I did read in the in the original Oz book. I think maybe they weren't short in
that. Maybe they were just whatever but this is where these movies get confusing to me. You're taking
direct elements from the Wizard of Oz the movie but then you're also taking direct elements from
the Wizard of Oz the book that contradict what was done in the movie in vice versa. Then you're also
taking things that were in the wicked book but then you're also taking things from the play that
contradict one of the vice versa. It gets so goddamn confusing. It's like guys is this in this
universe or not? What are we doing? Are you starting a new thing? Are you not? Yeah. It doesn't make
you know. I don't know. I don't know. The whole thing of her. I'll come back to him but real quick.
The whole thing of her being green. Yes. That is the movie the Wizard of Oz. That is not the book
the Wizard of Oz. In the book the Wizard of Oz, the Elf rank bomb book, the witch has an eye patch.
She's an old lady with an eye patch. So right off the bat, if you're making her green,
that means you are following some of the mythology built and if you read the book wicked,
it follows more closely what is established in the movie the Wizard of Oz versus the Elf rank bomb.
It takes that version of it and kind of runs with it. Then this sort of does, I just don't get,
I don't understand. I don't know. Anyway, Peter Dinklage who took, who prevented
the Munchkins from being Munchkins is in this movie. Of course, he's not playing a Munchkin because
that would be uncouth, that would be undignified. He's instead playing a talking goat.
He's so annoying in this movie. He's so fucking annoying in this movie.
I hated the talking goat professor character so much. Yeah. I hated the voice work, frankly. How
often do you watch something? I hate that vocal performance. I did. It was too much and I didn't like
it. Peter Dinklage would boycott a honey I shrunk the kids reboot because the kids didn't rejoice when
they got shrunk. Okay. Did you notice too? This is one of the reasons I hated the talking goat.
Yeah. First of all, it's a subplot they go nowhere with, which is a big thing in the book. The book is
very politics heavy. The book's very dark. The book's very adult. I knew they weren't going to do that
obviously, but the book is very politics heavy. The one sort of socio -political thing they inject into
the movie is that magic is leaving us and these animals that were always, you know, the sentient
animals that could talk and act like people are losing their ability to do so and they're
regressing into their true animal form. That is a plot line that is important
to why the witch is motivated to do the witch things. They introduce it briefly in this. They explore
it not at all. You want to talk about something where they could have beefed up to make it that three
hours worth your time. Nope. Instead they're going to do 11 -minute makeover scene.
You're pitching a phantom menace version of wicked that might not have been super entertaining
either where we're watching a lot of like Senate hearings from the witches and wizards. But really
what I remembered once this started, I was like, oh fuck, I did see wicked with an ex -girlfriend
when I lived in New York. I saw the Broadway play one of the first productions and
it wasn't for me. I didn't get it. And that's how I felt now, but at least that version of it
written by Winnie Holtzman who did my so -called life. It was clear. She took what she wanted from the book.
She took what she wanted from the Frank Baum book. She took what she wanted from the movies.
She made her own thing and it's obviously hugely successful in his work for generation.
But not only are you fucking with that, but you're just stretching it to its absolute breaking point.
And exactly the makeover sequences, the endless songs, the only catchy song is pop, you know.
That's the only song I can remember. It's only because it's annoying. The moment in every commercial,
I'm not impressed. I don't care. And that's really just how I felt. Now, there are some moments
at the beginning when there's like bears and, you know, it's in this colorful world. They said they
used all real poppies and all real flowers and whatever the hell they say. And I'm like, all right,
they're doing an interesting job of giving me like a different vibe of the laws and this looks kind
of cool. But then almost immediately it becomes this, am I watching a peacock limited series event?
You know, it's like I talked about with Red One or with the Golden Globes where everything looks so
fake and filtered and high definition that it feels like you're not watching something tangible.
Certainly not a work of art or something you should take seriously. My very first viewing of the
movie Wicked, I felt like it's something that would be playing in the background while I'm drinking
in the kitchen at a friend's Thanksgiving party and his kids are watching it on peacock. Like, it just
feels like junk that's on in the background is how it feels the movie. There's nothing special about
it. And I thought Ariana Grande was was good. I liked her in it. A Revo I didn't get.
And I cert, you know, obviously they're they're press tours its own horror show. But,
yeah, it just left me ice cold throughout. Yeah, it's a bad movie.
Would I was getting at with the with the more fleshed out subplot of the animals
that and this is one of the reasons I couldn't stand the Peter Dinklage character.
It's the only character in the movie like that for the for the most part which which I'm
getting to my greater point, which is Oz could be fucking Montana in this movie. It there's nothing
that looks magical or far away fairytale land about it. It is visually fucking boring. You are 90
minutes into this goddamn movie and they're still at the school and the school. They don't even make it
like look hog warts in or something where where where even you watch Harry Potter. They could just be
walking down the hallway of the school and you feel like you're in another world that the architecture,
the mood, the aesthetic that there's paintings on the wall who are their eyes are moving and they're
talking as people walk by them. There's there's ghosts in the background. Whatever it is, it's like
they make the entire the teachers are dressed like wizards in which is and what they do none of that
in this none of it. It's I mean they call that world building which is something they always look for
now in projects and it's like this movie has none of it. You're right. It's it's a green screen.
People standing in front of green screens. Arianna Grande was funny. I will give her that. I thought
she was good. I was I was impressed because I never thought about Arianna Grande as an actor
and I thought she was very funny. I thought she did a great job. I thought the whole cast was
was fine. Like everybody was serviceable. You know somebody asked me like how was gold bloom? I'm like
he's good. He's gold bloom. He's leaning into the bundle fly fucking shit and being weird.
Like that's what he does now. And he gets paid millions of dollars to do it.
Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Good. A bad way to run. Yeah. So you know the cast was was plenty serviceable.
No bad performances and good performances. I thought Arianna Grande was the standout.
As far as the directing is gone goes I mean God knows how much of this Jonathan actually directed
versus the studio telling him what to do. None of it looks bad and the performances are there so
he did a good job. The pacing in my opinion is so off but that could be his fault or could be the
studio who knows at this point who's responsible for what. But I thought the script was painfully
fucking boring. I just didn't give a shit. And for a musical it was too much. There were too many
songs. A musical doesn't mean singing every waking second of the music. If you want to do that make
a fucking opera and that's what an opera is. That's not what a musical is. Yeah. Well you mentioned
Potter I mean that's like seven movies all between two and a half and three hours long. No musical
numbers in sight. And you're riveted for pretty much the entire runtime of every one of those movies
or at least I was. So what went wrong here. There's just not enough meat on the bone.
Frankly it's like they're trying to distract you with all this stuff and oh it's also going to be a
metaphor for racism and it's going to be a metaphor for this and a metaphor for that. And okay but
like the minute to minute of it is just flat and uninspired and boring and uninteresting. And the
songs don't the only songs that stick with you are out of annoyance. It's just not I mean it's not
for me. Here's the other problem to be nice. The other problem is and this is a thing they took
away from the book. You can't just paint a woman green and then everybody thinks she's a freak
in a land of where ghosts talk. There's got to be more text to my buddy two minutes in, Joe. I'm like so
wait this this movie is about this woman is ostracized for the color of her skin but there's a bear raising
people in town. Like it's exactly right. I'm like what are you talking about? Well a big part of
the book is she is very unattractive. She looks like a witch. She's got a big pointy bumpy nose
and whatever that's a big part of the book but because it's Hollywood we can't we couldn't
as we tell everybody to never shame looks as we tell everybody that it is wrong to objectify as we
tell everybody that beauty is on the inside and not the out. We will never put an ugly person
in the lead role of a film. We will not do it. And so then you end up with this you end up with a
scenario where there's a very attractive woman who's green who by the way is still attractive green.
Yeah and you're going I don't understand what the problem is here. I mean it was the same with
Menzel and the thing it's like these are very attractive women. I don't understand. And don't
she's going to turn me off. Don't you love him. I love a movie too. Oh boy. Oh boy do I love a movie
that's going to tell us it's going to teach us about racism. And the only non white person in this
movie is painted green. Everybody else movie is white. They even make Ariana Grande look white. Yeah
Yes. They were blonde there. They really de -de -Hispanicked. They did. Yeah. But the slap filter on her,
man. Well my wand is down for a wicked. I got no magic left in the pipe here on this one. I'm
sorry folks. I know some of you liked it. I believe our friend Matt McCarthy liked this picture.
Loved it. Honestly a big part of the reason I sucked it up and went to see it. Well Matt
fuck you brother. Luckily I said if I was sent a screener to my home maybe I'd do it and I was
and I did. But it just wasn't for me. It's not for me. We will be back later in the month January
as a notorious dead zone so we are kind of trying to figure out what our next moves will be but we
thank you all for your love and support. Please look for a GoFundMe or something. You could
throw a couple of bones at for these fires. We love you. We're on CU and HellPod on Instagram. I'm at
the Patrick Walsh on Instagram. Joe. Joe DeRosa comedy on Instagram. I'm touring, joystick tours
and full effect. Thanks to everybody in Toronto that came out made those shows awesome. It was really
unbelievable. A lot of fans, a lot of helians. Really nice experience. The comedy bar.
Go check out that club. They have two. They're both great. Awesome time. Big shout out to Gary and the
whole staff. I will now I'm supposed to be in San Diego unless things are further affected by what's
happening in California at the end of this month. There are plenty of tickets available. Please if
you are able to come out I feel bad even you know plugging a gig in California right now so you know
what if you're around in any of the cities I'm coming to DC Midwest Milwaukee so on and so forth.
Tons of cities, tons of dates. JoeDeRosa .com. If you're in New York swing by Joey Roses for a sandwich
and a beer or cocktail JoeyRoses .com we'll see you next time folks and we'll see you in hell.