i'll see you at hell
and when the sound of your screams becomes a thing on my dreams
I'll say
hey
Hey, you guys it's a bonus step. It's a bonus step. You got a bonus step with a big
old dick. Wow. Wow. Well, two, two big old dicks. Um, I was saying you're a big old
dick. No, no, I would. I'm hearing a lot of talking in my headphones. Uh, we're picking up some,
um, I got no control over almost like a full volume conversation. And then we're also going to
be watching a move. Once the movie starts, you won't hear that. We're just picking up some,
you know, like when a guitar amp picks up, uh, interference. That's the word. Sure. Uh,
Patty, are you ready to do this? Uh, joy was born ready to do this, which was weird. I came
out of the womb and I was like, I want to do a horror podcast about a movie that's coming
out in 15 years. My parents were like, whoa, it's kids smart. And then the doctor went, what
happened to Goo Goo Gaga? It might day you were lucky to get Goo Goo Gaga. Then he slapped
my ass. They still do that. They still slap a baby's ass when it's born. Uh, why did they do it
in the first place? I heard a doctor did it last week and is being sued for harassment. Oh,
why did you tell that doctor to do what he did? Uh, well, let's start the movie. I mean,
these, uh, commentary podcasts are endless. We are giving them to you guys because we love
you. We love you. And it's the craft this week. Guys, listen, we're going to give you a chance
to pick again. But, uh, oh, let, let me feel this one. Go ahead and start the craft. So,
we're going to do it with a, uh, Netflix, you know, it's going to be the standard one, two,
three play. We're on Netflix. You're at, uh, one, forty one, oh, one is on the right side of the
screen. That's literally the very beginning. It hasn't played it all yet. So one, two, three,
play. She's playing Columbia, try star pictures. You think she looks like
students ran in our Annette Benning. Annette Benning. I've heard both. I think more like Annette Benning,
yes. I'm going all Annette Benning. And they must have gone out of business and come back because I
started seeing this lady again, uh, before Columbia trashed up pictures like Zathura. Uh, I'm going
in Annette Benning 100%. I agree. I like Annette Benning. Credits just came up. There's a picture of
a crystal ball in a candle where at one forty thirty, thirty, one forty thirty right when I said that.
All right. We'll get into the craft. But, but folks, I thought, you know, last night,
Joe and I are like, well, what are we going to do a commentary on? I go, I got an idea. We'll give the,
we'll let the people decide. I put it on Facebook by midnight tonight. Give me a movie streaming on
Netflix. Obviously a horror movie, a movie that would fit into the format of the horror show.
Folks, right off the bat, there's 15 people saying they want Jackie Brown. Now, you know,
I love Jackie Brown. We've talked about that movie so much on this podcast. Um, I'm seeing good
fellows. I'm seeing these aren't horror movies. A no, um, but they were streaming on Netflix. So
congratulations there. Then for the next 10 minutes of reading, 150 movie titles were presented,
not one of them streaming on Netflix. I was shocked. The one that got some traction was the void.
Joe and I have not seen the void and I want to watch it with respect. We'll do it. We'll do it as an
episode of the show. I have seen the void. Oh, okay. And I liked it and I'd love to do it as a reviewer
or a commentary. All right. We'll do that soon. I'm going to watch that. Um, and a few of you get,
you got it right. But I would say 90 % didn't and it was shocking. And I just think you should all be
ashamed of yourself. Um, that being said, we appreciate the enthusiasm. We do. Uh,
be for effort, be for effort. And I, you know, I'm looking, Joe and I were sitting down and I was
going to do a dream catcher, which is awful. It's a movie I saw on spring break in Panama City beach
years ago. And it involves Jason Lee shitting out a demon. Oh, um, but it's not a Kevin Smith movie.
No, that's exactly it should be. But Joe looks it up. He realizes it's like 220. We got a
concert tonight. Uh, we're recording a couple episodes. That's a long time. The chat. We just
don't have the juice for it sometimes. This is a nice hour 40. Uh, it was down. It's still 40 extra
minutes. That's true of pod. It's true. It was down to the craft and teeth that those both had a few
a little bit of traction on. Uh, we went with the craft. We've heard that this title come up a lot.
I don't remember the movie. I probably saw it when I was 15. I saw it. I feel like you must have,
no, yeah. No, you're right. I saw it when I maybe you were 14. I feel like I saw this when I was
16 or top 17. Well, you don't have to see movies when they're in theaters. Oh, well, I thought maybe
you did. And my day they had a, you know, VHS rental system. Okay. So I saw it a few years later.
Okay. Well, I saw it in the theater with our dear friend James Pinkstone. Sure. Uh, he talked me
into seeing it. He said, it's a witch movie with Nev Campbell. I said, what have you lost your
mind? And he said, no, it's going to be good. I said, all right, because at this time, Nev Campbell
wasn't really Nev Campbell yet. She was still just the, the girl that was on, um, party of five. Yeah.
So I was like, I don't want to go see some fucking Dawson's Creek thing. But then, uh, but then when
we, I really, I really like the movie. I Dawson's Creek was not for me. It was now he was into film.
Dawson Dawson. He wanted to be the next Steven Spielberg.
Yeah. You know, who else was into film at one point? James Vanderbick.
varsity blues, baby. I don't want your life.
varsity blues is the very entertaining movie. He's in my favorite, um,
uh, Freddie Sinalis adaptation. Yeah. You see how well I know you. I finished your sentence.
Thank you. Thank you. Uh, finish your sentences. Um, the uh, that movie's awesome. And he's awesome
in it. I love traction is unbelievably good. And your boy savages in it. Savage.
Savage. Savage is in it. Yeah. Um, and that Roger Avery who was just kind of a cast aside by
Tarantino for Pulp Fiction and Quick Pause. Why did you tell Quentin Tarantino to do what he did?
He co -wrote Pulp Fiction, one of the greatest screenplays ever. Then he makes an amazing movie
rules of attraction. He makes a really good movie called Killing Zoe. And he's out of the business.
No, you know, he, he went to jail because he killed a man drunk driving. Oh,
well, that explains, we're, we're, we're, we're some alleged hold on alleged whatever you got to say
legally. I didn't know that. He was in some vehicular mishap where I believe he was drunk.
Somebody was injured and he like went to jail for it. Well, you know, who else has, uh, lots of
people. Matt Broderick, Ferris Bueller killed someone with his car. He's still working. He was,
he was like 18 Rebecca Gayheart. She's still opening pictures. You seen her? You seen Gayheart?
Wait a minute, girl. Uh, varsity blues lady. Rob and Toney, I like her. Was she in sister of the
traveling pants? I think that's right. But I don't know for sure. And in sister of the trailer,
man, she's playing a woman five years younger than her character in this film. Yeah.
That came out four years before that movie did. That doesn't make any sense. She might not be
in sister of the travel pad. You're thinking of Alexis Bladell from the Gilmore girls. Oh, okay.
Well, what happened to Toney over here? As always, we could look this up. We're probably not going to. Pat,
I got a microphone in one hand at a tall Jack and Coke in the other. Did I mix it too strongly?
You mixed it beautifully. It's good. Just so you guys know, Pat and I have a little table in front of
us here with a, I don't know what the big bottles called. That's a big one. That's your, uh, 1 .75
liters. 1 .75 libert bottle jack. I put ice into an ice bucket. So we don't have to get up. Is that
STP? No, no, it's one of the many rip off. And they were rip off themselves. What am I talking about?
Breck and Maya are ladies and gentlemen, recently dated a friend of mine, recently dated two
friends of mine, but that's not your business. How, now how I mix these drinks is I, uh, I poured
Joe's Jack and Coke, little ditty about Jack and diet. Then I poured the remainder of the Coke into
the 1 .75 liter bottle and I'm just drinking from that. And honestly, it's working for me. I feel good.
Now, none of these girls are around anymore. Even if Campbell's not really around much,
but they're rebooting party of five with, uh, with immigrants. Are they really? They're rebooting every
show that's ever been made this season on television. Wait with immigrants. Why with immigrants?
I, I don't know there. I, that's just what I saw. Party of five with immigrants. Wait, what was
party of five about? Party of five was about, uh, five children whose parents died in a car accident
and then they kind of took care of them. Oh, okay. Well, that makes sense. So it'd be like immigrate
because with the whole Trump thing, like the, oh, I think the parents get sent back or okay.
All right. Well, that makes sense. They're also rebooting. Let me go through these and give me your,
your brief thoughts. Murphy Brown. I, same cast. I mean, they're all in their 70s.
I, how old's that ball guy at this point? He's got to be 75 years old. The, the role in my show that
went to Joe Beth Williams, the mom from Poltergeist. Yeah. I floated the name Candace Bergen. I needed an
icy, uh, older woman and I floated the name. They were like, she's, she's, she's, she's lost it.
She's, she's old. She doesn't know anymore. She can't remember lines. I don't know what, maybe
this thing will never see the light of day, but Jesus Christ. They're also redo, as they're already
have done Will and Grace. They're bringing back Martin. Martin. ABC is redoing Martin. The one I'm at. ABC's.
Not Fox. Correct. And it was on Fox. Was it not? It was. The one I'm excited about is Rosanne. I think
that's going to be great. I don't know. Rosanne, but I thought you'd be excited about Martin. You
love Martin. Um, I've never mentioned Martin to my knowledge and I don't know that I've ever seen a
full episode. You see, we know each other so well. Haven't you told me that Martin was oh, no, it was
you thought that you so crazy was an amazing stand -up special. That's what it was. I don't think
that's true either, but I do think Martin Lawrence is very funny. I like nothing to lose. You saw him
in Vegas. Oh, yeah, he has stand -up. So there was hilarious. I think I said I was never a huge
stand -up fan of Martin Lawrence. Yes. And you said you're crazy. You so crazy is great. I
probably said you so crazy, Joe. And then I he's a funny stand -up. And then you did say,
run -tell that. And I did. I have seen you so crazy. And I remember, um, I always talk on here
about how I'd make it maybe 30 minutes into SNL on a good night. And then my dad would be like,
up to, to sexual go to bed. Um, and Martin Lawrence was hosting. And he came out for his monologue and
started talking about how women's pussy is be stinking. Yeah. No. And my dad picked me up. I was
probably 11 years old and ran me out of the room. He was banned for that. He was banned from the show.
I remember. I remember the, uh, I remember the, well, and you want to talk racism in Hollywood.
Louis went out there and talked about how, uh, pedophilia must be so good that it's better than a
he, uh, I remember that I've, I've looked at Martin while I go up on YouTube. And I believe the way
Martin phrases it is, ladies, you got to do a better job of killing, cleaning the Pilly Packers.
He calls them the Pilly Packers. Oh, boy. Yeah. Uh, now here's the audience. It's kind of like not laughing.
It's very tense. This kid, what happened to this kid? Skeet old rich. Well, I'll tell you what happened.
Don't sound like terms for come. Well, skeet is a term for come. Skeet, skeet, skeet, mother fucker.
Uh, I always say, oh, rich myself. Oh, rich. Well, that's because you're masturbating to shots of
skeet old rich in a pair of briefs. Yeah. Uh, skeet old rich was always the, the homeless man's
Johnny Depp. Yeah. He's also in scream. I just, uh, and I, you know, in scream, which I've seen,
he's, he's a good looking guy. He just walked up here. I, I'm amazed this guy made it anywhere. He
looks like a ferret. He, it's a look that was big back then. He has a very like 90s. He looks
like Sandler right here. 90s. Great. You know, I met Sandler finally in real life. I'd never met him.
Yeah. Very good looking man in real life. I think he, he got better looking as it goes. Not to say
that I looked at him on screen and thought he was not a good looking man, but I'm just saying,
like when I was like talking to him, I was like, he's like a handsome dude. I've always heard no one
did better with the ladies than Sandler and his prime dude. Are you kidding? At the time,
he was coming up doing all that cute shit like a. Yeah. Oh, yeah. Yeah. God. Man,
chicks love that threat and then comedy. The ladies love it. The, uh, well, it's like, uh,
when Russell Brand came out and it was like, he would act like sort of a feminine. Yeah. And he
would just, that was like at that time, that's like anything like the way you pick up people of the
opposite sex, whether it's men or men or women. Yes. We're of the same sex. Uh, wait, is this a cover
of how soon is now by this month? No, it's the actual version. Oh, it's definitely a cover. It
sounds like it's good Charlotte. No, that's the original version. It wasn't. All right. Well, anyway.
All right. Carry on. It, by the way, this thing is, this thing is like plus two volume. I can't
know what they're saying. Well, that's the only way I can do this. Uh, and we have lady,
which lady? The black lady. Sadly, sadly, sadly, I don't know where I'm at. That's okay. I've never
seen her. This is what I'm saying. I've never seen any of these people again. Yeah. The only person's
name. Oh, I knew. Well, I know Faruza Balk and I knew, uh, Dev Campbell and Skid all rich. But I could,
who was the other kid you called out? Linkham Nashfire? Yeah. Linkham Nashfire. Uh, you don't know
Linkham? That was Breck and Meyer, uh, who's been in a lot of shit. He was a sitcom star,
auditioned for my pilot. He was in, um, Josie and the pussy cats and, uh, she and can hardly wait.
He's in can hardly wait. He's very funny and can hardly wait. She played the main guy. Yes,
correct. Okay. Yeah. He was in that movie with David Keltner, Ethan Embry. That's Ethan Embry.
But he was, he was the, uh, guy acting black, basically. And no, that was Seth Green. But he was a friend
of his. He was in clueless. I don't remember. I know who. I mean, I saw his face. No, he was the guy
acting black and clueless. Okay. And he was, if I'm not mistaken, and can hardly win. Okay. Uh, now,
Faruza Balk, as I said before we started watching here. One of my favorite women that has ever lived
really, it, it kills me that she's never in it. She is, uh, in, I would go as far as to say,
intoxicating. Wow. Okay. She has got such a wild look. Her eyes, my band, when I was in college,
I had a band, uh, called Bernie, Bernie Headflap. And we had a song called Faruza that the lead guy
wrote about Faruza Balk. And it was about just how she was like the most beautiful woman. And that's
when I, when I like noticed her, yeah, I was like 20 or 21. I was like, Oh, yeah, you're right. She's
like really uniquely beautiful. And ever since then, I, it's never gone away. I mean, uh, looks much
like comedy as subjective. She's never done it for me. Um, I know where that location isn't Los Angeles.
I used to, it's right by the pure one imports. Right. Um, now I've offered, uh, you were in the,
the bookstore where they go and get the magic book. Right. Uh, now I've heard this pet tell me if it's
true. You know where this is because you'll hang around that bookstore hoping a, a gaggle of high
school girls will come in. Yes. That I could cast a charm spell on it. Right. Right. Okay. Uh, although
it's now just a pair of what imports. So it's just a lot of me sitting on a wicker basket kind of,
uh, gesturing to, uh, my hog, which is flopping around a pair of, uh, sweatpants that I'm not wearing
onto wear beneath. And if that's a crime, I guess lock me up two hogs up, two hogs up folks.
I just embraced hogs. We're, we're going with it. Well, the fans have spoken. They want to,
the fans have oinked. They want two hogs up in. I love. Biggies have oinked. And that's gonna be a great
t -shirt one day. Two hogs up is a good t -shirt. I agree. Uh, now where was I before I was distracted by
this? Oh, uh, yeah. If I, if I was, it's not for me. I think she is still in stuff. And she was on
some, she was, I think she was on a breaking bad maybe or something like that. But she's been on
big TV show. She still acts. Good. I'm glad to hear that. Um, and she also does like charity. I looked,
I followed her on Twitter like a couple of years ago. Yeah. And she has like, she has some very nice
cause or something. She does another thing outside of show business where I was like, oh, that's,
that's cool. She's like a normal person. Yeah, I think, uh, all the, I think all four of these,
uh, gals turned out pretty normal. They did an entertainment weekly, uh, 20 years later story,
interview with them and they all seem cool and funny. Nev Campbell, by the way, are those dildos?
No, they're candles. Pat. Jesus Christ. Right. That doesn't matter with you. Uh,
the book, the magic book that she buys is called The Craft. That's the name of the book
that she buys. What made them go here? Just for fun. Uh, it was when we were arguing about whether or
not it was a Smith's cover or not, they, they set up why they came to this store. These women, by
the way, what do they have a 3032 playing high school girls in this world? That was always the case.
I bet Nev's, uh, you know, 22 or something. I had a high school girlfriend who looks so much like
Nev Campbell. It's honestly disturbing to me, especially when I see her young like this.
But, um, we, and we were the homecoming king and queen, Joe. Oh, you were, you were popular in high school.
Uh, once my skin cleared up, I became popular, but only because I was a friend to nerd and jocke
alike. Okay. I bridged both groups with my humor as humor is the universal language of love and
friendship, as they say. It is. But I would still get, you know, shoved and, and, and ridiculed
fairly often. Right. And, uh, when they played our song because the theme of the dance was under
the sea, much like I'm back to the future, the song that I had to slow dance with my girlfriend too,
in front of the entire student body was kiss the girl. Oh, nice kill there. Nice kill. Now, hold on,
I don't put a pit in that because I just want to point out the crazy sort of homeless guy is chasing
what's your name, Tuddy? Robin, Tuddy. Robin Tuddy across the street. And he's saying, you,
you need to find Jesus. She's scared because she thinks he's crazy. He, he, he may, may,
I'm renapping the movie. We don't know yet. He might really be trying to help her.
But that was one of the fur and then a truck hits him. Yeah. That was one of the first movies I ever,
it's so hacky now. It happens left and right and everything.
That's one of the first movies I ever saw that device in where oh, it happens in every movie now.
Yeah, where the guy with the person gets hit by the car and you're not expecting it at all.
And, and then they showed his head go under the back tire, which I liked. The, the funniest of
those is in Meet Joe Black, where he bounces between the cars and it looks absurd. It's not supposed
to be funny, right? No, no, no. Meet Joe Black is one of the worst movies I've ever seen. Excruciatingly
boring. Um, so anyway, I had to slow dance to kiss the girl from the little mermaid, which you haven't
seen. No, uh, which is sung by a calypso crab. So it's like, she don't see a word and she won't say
a word till you kiss the girl. There's no beat to it. And I had to slow dance to this song, right?
Palm sweaty, probably the makings of a boner in my slacks, the entire school watching. I'm dancing to
an animated crab singing in kind of an offensive calypso voice. And about two minutes into the song,
which obviously I didn't pick the song. That guy stands up and goes, excuse my language folks.
Right, right. And at that age and in that year, you feel you rightly deserve it.
When that happens, when you're in high school, you don't know what to do. You're just like, I didn't.
I finished the dance. My face turned immediately bright red. I probably started sweating and then
it ended. There's no, regardless of whatever name or whatever the person yells at you,
there is no part of you in that circumstance where you go at that age in this time, where you go,
I'm going to go give him a piece of my mind. No, just go, well, that's what happened to me today.
Yeah, I'm homecoming king. I guess this is part of it. Even at the height of my popularity,
a man still stood and screamed a homophobic slur at me. Now, here's a weird parallel or connection
between our lives. You dance to kiss the girl as your song. The theme to my prom was kiss the girls,
the Morgan Freeman film. Okay. And it was held in a basement that Carrie L was without let you out.
And we had to figure out who murdered the prom queen. It was a lot of fun. It was a big, big mystery thing.
Remember when every three weeks, there was an Ashley Judd Morgan Freeman vehicle.
Or Tommy Lee Jones, when they couldn't get framing. Or Jo Lee, once in a while, I think, would pop into
one. They're all those movies are identical. Bone collector, kiss the girls, along came a spider,
double jeopardy. Double jeopardy. Let's look. I've seen them all. And they're not bad. Neither of them are
any, but let's throw in Holly Berry's gothic or whatever the fuck they ever saw it, but I'll throw that
in. There's so many of those those movies were so popular back then. Yeah. Now, here they are. And
she's two. Now, I think that Tuddy is very pretty. Robin Tuddy. Tuddy is like a mobster from analyze
this, I think. It's also Tuddy. Tuddy is also the Fred Gwynns partner in car 54, where are you?
The guy that would always go, oh, wait, the movie? No, the original sitcom. Have you seen that movie?
No, you don't replace Fred Gwynne with David Johansson. I'm sorry. And I like David Johansson.
Yeah. And I can't remember who played Tuddy in it, but Tuddy was, Tuddy is also the guy in good
fellows. You wasted six fucking aprons on that guy. We got a toughiness. Tuddy, that's what I was
thinking. Yeah. Yes. Skeet Ulrich was in a movie. So he had a little something for a brief
period outside of the Scream franchise. But I'm pretty sure his solo career begins and ends
with a picture called Chill Factor. And this movie was Skeet Ulrich and Cuba Good in Jr.
in a speed ripoff, except they were in an ice cream truck rigged to blow. And it was called
Chill Factor. And I saw this movie in the theater. Was your review? This movie is rigged to blow.
It should have been. Where's Nev Campbell these days? Campbell, you see and stuff. I mean,
I, she pops up and stuff. She was in a movie with James Tobak, beloved Hollywood figure, James Tobak.
Yeah. And she gets super naked in it. Yeah. And she plays like kind of a rotten person in it,
which is interesting because she usually doesn't play like a rotten person. But that's, I like that
movie. I thought that was a good movie. I was waiting to see if she was going to, if she had any
accusations when all the Tobak shit hit the fan. It was called what? When will I be loved?
Yeah. I forget who else is in it. It was, you know, it's Uncle Jr. from Sopranos was in it.
Oh, it's like all the Tobak movie. Dominic Shannon. They're disturbing and sad, but they're
well done. And I guess well done. You know, none of them are, I don't think he ever had anything great.
No, they're just interesting. He made a mess in his pants, folks. Did you see the,
did you ever see the interview from, oh, well, hold on. Sorry, I got to strike their folks.
Skiddlework just dumped Tuddy. And they were having a nice thing. And then he just shit on her.
So now obviously she's going to put some kind of craft on him, right? Yeah, from her craft book.
I'm going to, I'm going to walk over and grab my phone because I feel appalled that we know every
girl except the black girl's name. I only knew two of the girls. So don't, don't let me in with
your prejudice. I only knew two of them. I know this girl's another shit. Oh, look at that. The
young, what's her face? Boy, does she look pretty? Christine Taylor. Ben Stiller's wife. Not
anymore. They split it up. They split it up. That's right. So you're telling me there's a chance.
When did they split up? They, uh, they split up this year. Then they've been together about 20 years.
She is still to this day striking. I'll tell you, and I'm not naming any names, but I, I know through
the grapevine. This is, of course, allegedly as well, a former assistant of Harvey Weinstein who said
he was just obviously, obviously a terrible, horrible man and a terrible boss, but she said she'd
take Weinstein over Ben Stiller. She, because she assisted him. It's a woman saying this.
But not because, not because Stiller was doing anything untoward sexually, but that he is just that
unpleasant. And I really hope that's not true, but sometimes we sometimes this is TMZ on this
fucking podcast. Wow. Christine Taylor just said to the black girl, I don't like Negroids.
Did you see that? I didn't see that. I didn't remember. I forgot this movie goes like kind of
deep with, yeah, with the sexual, and that's not the right term, but with the, not just the racial,
but also the gender tensions and all that stuff. Yeah, it's, it's pretty dark. Oh, yeah,
and that's right. Now we're in the hospital. Ned Campbell is, oh, there's the Burralis woman from
Seinfeld. Oh, yeah, it is. Sue Ellen Mischke, the Burralis wonder. This is the thing, remember,
this part where Ned Campbell, her back is like burned. I don't remember anything about it. And she has
to get like this skin grafting done. That's her back. Yeah, she was like in a fire or something, and she
has to get skin grafting done on her back. And that's like her. So like the black girl's facing racism.
Tuddy is facing skiddle rich dumping her. Yeah. This girl's got a physical deformity from a fire.
And I don't know what for, and that for us a bulk, I don't, I think everybody just thinks she's a freak.
Yeah. And she ends up being the one that goes nuts at the end of this, I remember. Like she's the
one where they're like, we got to stop. Come, come back from the edge. And she's, oh, yeah, some of that's
being familiar to me. This, so the woman, the fourth woman is Rachel true. That's right. And I
don't feel bad because I didn't even have a guess. But I know what else do I know her from? She's in
half -baked. Half -baked. That's what it is. She's in CB4. Yes. And she's in one of the all -time great
jerk -off films, Embrace of the Vampire starring Alyssa Molano. Yeah, when I was a kid, I'd have to say,
skated a few over itches to that one. That's right. I knew I knew her from somewhere. She's,
man, she's, she's one of those ladies, like when she's like in half -baked, I am like, yeah, she's
Hachah. Hachimuch. And then she's 50 years old and she looks beautiful.
She, in half -baked, I remember just being in love with her. Yeah. And just like being like, this
is a dream woman, my god almighty. One of, just such a brilliant idea for a comedy scene is that
that date he goes on where it keeps a counter of how much money he has. I always thought that was
such a great idea for a scene. It is a great idea. It's very good. Jellis of it. And you do it and you
are terrified the whole time because you know, it doesn't have enough money. And the way he keeps
saving it, it's a great exhale every few minutes. Why don't we just share one and she thinks it's
cute? Sure. But the Sunday you're like, yeah, it's very funny. Very well done. Tell me, give me,
give me a little Farooza bulk. Yeah, I will. Google. Okay. So, bulk's mom is an alcoholic. Let's
see who's playing the mom here. And the dad is too. Look at this dad. Oh geez, you know, he smacked
his daughter on the ass a few times. Yeah. Look at this guy. Oh, I know that guy. That guy's been on a ton of
stuff. Bulk. Bulk playing a 16 year old chain smoking in her bedroom. This is the kind of family she's
living with to know where she's at. Her brother is Judd Nelson from the breakfast club.
The same house. Oh, here's an article called why you don't hear about this craft star anymore.
Those are all bullshit. Those are all bullshit. Those things they are. I see Brendan Fraser take a lot
of heat in those. I'm like, Brendan Fraser works all the time. He's also back in something that's like
got a lot of critical heat around. He's on the affair. He's it, which is a very, very good show. The
maybe that's what it is. Uh, he and he looks bad. I mean, he's playing like an ogre essentially
and he's they don't have men and he make up. Let's put it that way. Right. Um, she was in. I got to know
what there it is. The pranos. I knew it. God damn it. She was an FBI agent at sopranos and she was
great in it. What was she in recently though? Um, oh, it says original airing only. I guess they
must have recast her. They did. I remember that. You don't recast for Roosevelt. She it became a
much bigger role. I'm hopefully I just meant they couldn't get her, but I know exactly what happened
and it would be a spoiler to tell you. She was a the voice of Penny D in 2003's Justice League,
whenever the hell that is. Give me some, you know, post 2010. There's nothing. There's nothing big.
No, sorry. A lot of like kind of low -budge horror. She was in Bad Lieutenant Port of Call
New Orleans, which is a wild and wonderful movie. Oh, wait. She isn't that. Isn't she the,
isn't she the chicken, the parking lot that he like shakes down and he makes her like give him a
hand job or something? She I know. I remember that scene. I don't remember if that was her.
She was in a master's of horror. You know, she's, she's in pet. I gotta tell you, I think we might
have a shot of getting bulk on this podcast to talk horror. I'd love it. And maybe that's where I
propose. Just straight to proposal. Straight to proposal. So already it's like I gotta go to this
Strange Man's house full of horror memorabilia and video games. And then to put her at ease,
you're going straight to what I imagine will be a ringless proposal. What if I did this instead? What
if I was crossing to sit down on the couch to start recording my pants accidentally and quotes
fell down and I just went whoops. I think you should do like finger to your lips like whoops. And if
you could sit behind the arcade machine and do a slide whistle sound effect. How about because
I think the oops is going to be a little obvious. How about we slip a sausage in your back pocket and
have con take your pants down. Comfortone baby style. I assume we're doing this just to reveal your
sweet ass to her. Right. Because how could she resist? Because then if con does it, we can make it very
sitcom -y like no, no, no, no, no, no, it's not what you think. Right. Right. The we're kidding,
everybody. We're kidding. I feel like you have to say that right now. We're just kidding. I think
they knew we were not planning to put meat into your pants and have your dog take them down
in front of Byruza Bach who you're planning on proposing to. I don't know that we didn't need to
explain that. One of the funniest lines I've ever read in print ever. Did you ever read Steve Martin's
book? I did. Pure drivel. Oh yeah, I love pure drivel. The thing, the first chapter where it's just
him apologizing to everybody through his life. Yes. And I remember reading this on an airplane,
on a trip to LA. First time I ever flew out here right after college and just laughing hysterically.
And he goes, I want to apologize to the secretary to my secretary that worked for me from the years
1984 until 1987. For the time that I was trying to show her my new dictaphone and coincidentally,
my pants fell down just as I said, ever seen one of these before. I love Steve Martin's writing.
I love his books. I love his serious books. I love his plays and I love his movie scripts. I think he's
yeah, he's great. He's a real talent. I don't know if I'm telling you something you don't know.
He's great. Mainly he gets kind of a bad rap as being pompous and I think he's just kind of an old
daughtering man at this point. He's not as sharp and that's fine. I would like to see that
thing with him in short. I heard it's great. I kick myself all the time. They did it at the
fucking Glendale playhouse and we didn't go. And I didn't go see Rickles before he died. I got a
lot of regrets. I saw Rick at Nev Campbell. Yeah, she's a very pretty stunner. The four of these women
are beautiful. Yes. These are four very beautiful people. They've passed a spell on me for sure.
Which craft? What's Campbell up to these days? She's got to be pushing. I guess now that I'm the
researcher on the show, why you enjoy your beverage. She's about 50 now, too, right? I mean, I guess
they're probably covering around there. Nev Campbell, I hope she's getting a producer credit on that
reboot of 45. I mean, it's funny. I'm like, I'm like, she's got to be 50. I'm like, well, I'm 40.
So that would make perfect sense. They're also bringing Magnum PI back.
Hawaii 5 .0 was already back. They're redoing Cagney and Lacey. My mom's old favorite show.
I can't remember seeing one episode of Cagney and Lacey. It was just a very generic couple of cops
strongly hinted that there were lesbians, but they weren't. As a seven year old boy,
it wasn't their demographic, but right. Wild things. I mean, that pairing of like the good girl
Campbell and just the the porny Denise Richards. Yeah. When I was, I mean, that movie was my first year,
I could see an R -rated movie alone. I intentionally brought no one with me to the theater. I just wanted
to enjoy it alone. Now, who's the guy in Wild Things? Well, it's Matt Dillon, Kevin Bacon, Bill Murray,
which one? Bill Murray. But Dillon's the guy they're like seducing, right? Yes. Where's it bacon?
No, it's still in bacon as the cop shows his dick as we've discussed on the show. Bacon always plays
the cop. Bacon can't get a bacon, cannot get a break to play a nice guy. No. In the last 20 years,
I haven't seen him play one likable character in any. He's always a fucking. And when he does, it's
bad. Like the era up there is a terrible movie where he like attempted to be the hero. I never
saw it. Yeah. He's good in those like woodsman roles. He's good. I mean, I'm playing real creepers.
Yeah. Sleepers. He's so so great. And he's great in Frost Nixon. I love Frost Nixon. Where he's
like crying about like what has happened in Nixon. I love that movie. Yeah. Copcar is a recent
really excellent picture. If you haven't seen cop car, but he's a bad guy. He's a very bad guy in
that. Yeah. Also starring Miss Cameron Mannheim. I didn't know. Mannheim was in that. Yeah. Great movie.
So she it looks as though since scream four, which was actually fairly recent. She's appearing in a
movie called Sky Scraper with the rock. So that's good. Okay. And it's going to be in 3D. Yeah.
I think the rock makes a movie every three months at this point. Yeah. Oh, she did two seasons of
house of cards. I mean she's around. All right. That's good to know. I'm happy for. All right. Yeah,
these it's it's got to be scary like to be in like kind of a big movie. You think it's why people
go insane in the entertainment industry and then but if you stick it out long enough and it's
sad but true. If you maintain your looks, you'll act again because people have so much affection for
these old movies. You remember them. And then as you get older, you want to hire your idols and etc.
Yeah. That's yeah. That's that's real. That's like that's like real kids days in the picture stuff.
Yeah. Yeah. You know, I was down and out. The first kid I ever got got me coffee called me. I'm
the head of paramount now. I want to hire you back in Evans. That can happen. Yeah.
It can happen. Yeah. So it's why and believe me, no one learns this lesson but it's why it pays
in any industry but I think especially the entertainment industry to be nice to everyone you
meet because you're going to meet him again on the way up or down or whatever the expression is.
I think it's I think it's it's easier on the way down than on the way up is the expression be a prick
on the way up but be nice on the way down I believe. I don't think that's right. That wouldn't be an
expression. You sure? You'll I think it's you'll see that again on the way that I'm kidding. I'm saying
it exactly wrong. All right. They say be nice on the way up because you're going to see him again
on the way down. All right. I was saying it backwards. So it's an issue of mine. I'm always sarcastic and
then I can very rarely decipher when people are being sarcastic to me. Oh, and it hurts me because
it makes me feel like there's something wrong with my brand of sarcastic. It's all me. I think
it's tied into being bullied as a child. I always think people are fucking with me or I get mad.
I lash out. Look at those eyes on bulk. I can't get over those eyes. They're piercing. It's not
for it's not for me. The mouth is unsettling. Look, she's got a real wild girl look to her. I got
I got no I'm not disputing that. She looks like somebody that'll fucking cut a line of
meth on the table after you bring her home from the bar. But I but I I like it. I like her whole vibe.
Also too. It's hard to not picture her in the American history. You know, because she's I forgot
about that. She's so hateful in that movie. Yeah. And she's the only. No, that's not true. I was
going to say she's the only supremacist that doesn't learn a lesson in that movie, but that's far
from true. But it's been 20 years since I saw it. I don't I know I don't necessarily want to see it
again, but I remember watching it. I like American history. Actually, you know, it's it's obviously
not when you you pop it on a Friday night to have a few laughs. But I like the movie. I think it's a
very good movie very timely. Yeah, sure. Faruza Faruza. This is a man. This is a wild spaniard
putting on her name. Fy Rooza. I thought there was a name. No, Faruza. I've always said Fy Rooza.
And I dated it. You also consistently consistently still say Tiffany Hadeesh. I do say Hadeesh.
I thought I still think that might be right. It's not right. Might literally nobody says it that.
By the way, did you see, uh, so they might make sex in the city three without Kate, uh, what's your name?
What? Um, what's your name? Samantha. Kim Catrell. Kim Catrell. So Kim Catrell apparently,
it's one of these things, but I've been here in this for years. Well, but apparently there's a guy
who I'd rather not see get another fucking dollar might my former boss date. They, they,
they, her and her and Parker traded some insults recently again. Yeah. There's a real beef there.
And she's like, and, and Catrell was just like, look, I'm not fucking doing the movie because,
because Parker gets way more money than everybody else and it's bullshit and everything. You know,
it was one of those things. Sure. So, uh, I think those girls would have an agreement where they
all take you equal amount. Uh, I don't support you. I don't, I don't, it was one of those kind of
things. So then Parker is on Ellen. Ellen says so Sam says she won't come back.
Would you do the movie without her and, and apparently Parker said, yeah, we're still considering
doing it with like a new Samantha or something. Uh -huh. So Kim Catrell takes to Twitter very positively.
Right. Doesn't say like fuck you. You'll never do it without me or anything. Yeah. She just
goes, I, I, I hope whoever fills my, she takes the role has a great time. Here are some people I think
would be brilliant. Names two actresses. One of them is Tiffany Haddish. One of them is a woman
who I can't remember younger than Tiffany Haddish. She picks two people who are literally at least
20 years. Dakota fan. I heard junior. Yeah. And goes, I think they'd be great with the role.
It's like, what are you talking about? Right. If it's not, it doesn't, it's not even close.
Now, how did you see any of this? If you're off Twitter because I'm sure as hell didn't see.
I read it on, uh, like, you know, on like the movie websites. It was like, uh, apparently the
section on city three might still happen. You know, I'm clicking on that link. Of course. And, uh,
I mean, you don't, you can't do it without Katrina. Look, the only reason I want a third movie is
because I can see it with it. The first two were fucking dog shit. They like the first one.
It's terrible. It's about three hours too long, but I like the first one. They're both terrible.
The show is so beautiful and the movies are so terrible. And I want them to just have one good movie.
And I want it with Ketrell. And I want them to finally tackle. This is especially why I want it with
Ketrell. I want them to finally tackle sexuality and being an older woman, like truly tackle it.
These women are in their late fifties at this point. Tackle this for real. Like you, Ketrell's probably
60 years old. You know, it's like that would be such a cool, interesting movie. Like older women and
like their sexuality and how like they still have it. And it's not a thing that comes, it would be
such a statement to make. And they've just never made it. Yeah, I mean, they might not want to
acknowledge their aging or something, but that would have to be the next step. They went marriage,
then they did babies. Oh no, the second one was just racism was the theme of the second one.
The second one was so terrible. It was so bad. It's one of the worst movies ever. Let's do a
section of the city movie and take them out of New York. That's literally like if they were like,
hey guys, all right, this Han Solo movie is coming out. He goes to Earth in it. Yeah, no,
don't please don't do that. Please don't do that. It was a a travesty that movie. Absolutely.
So hope, look, nobody's looking for this recommendation. If you want a really great movie about
sexuality when you're older and I see nobody saw it because the subject makes people uncomfortable
unfortunately. Hope springs with Tommy Lee Jones and Merrill Street. It was such a sweet
entertaining movie and I loved it. I wanted to see that movie. I heard it was very bad. It's not.
I mean, so many things you just hear you hear are bad and never see them. I don't mean you. I mean,
people in general and then you check something out. Sometimes you're right. They're right. But that
was a movie that I thought handled that so well. Just a there's so many married couples. Most people's
parents, I feel like where they just they haven't even thought about fucking in 25 years. Right.
And you know, she's like, I want to fuck again. And she's trying to get her husband out of his
shell. And it's a great, great movie. It's really entertaining. Therapist in it.
Corel. That's right. I almost should Steven Colbert. It's a really sweet movie. I liked it a lot.
And if you want to see Merrill Street blow Tommy Lee Jones in a movie theater, I recommend it for
that reason as well. Holy cat. Neville going on here. Neville's Neville got her skin thing fixed in
her back. Did she also get her net implants? No, I'm calling her Neville. No, I think that's all
Neve. Holy moly. And she's coming in like kind of kind of showing it off a little bit now. She feels
like pretty for the first time because her back doesn't have all that shit on her. And God bless her.
Show it off. Neve working around that campus. I mean, this is a classic Hollywood, you know,
the thing that always bothers me is it's such a trope of Hollywood sitting in the quad.
Well, yeah, the first one of the outdoor high school sitting in the quad never happened. Really?
Where's this high school? But then also maybe I'll the four of the hottest women I've ever seen
in my life. And they're like, they're outcasts. They can't get a date either outcast and be like no one
is even glancing at these four women at the men's horneous time in their life. Yeah, you got
skied all rich up there looking like, you know, like somebody turned Johnny Depp's face inside out.
Yeah, the not another teen movie was a very funny spoof of a lot of these tropes about the girl who
like takes her hair out of a ponytail and everybody's like, who's this babe? She was so fucking disgusting
before. Have you seen not another teen movie? No, seriously. It was too late. It came out after
there had been too many scary movies at that point. It was just... It's got some really funny stuff
in it. All right. It does, you know, the scary movies eventually became like, they just thought
recognizing what movie was being spoof was the joke. Right. Do anything to it. Not another teen movie
goes into like very, very specific aspects of teen movies and spoof them and it's much funnier for it.
I, yeah, I don't doubt that it's funny. Like I said, it just came out the wrong time.
And I was just like, you know, I didn't have any interest at the time. Sure.
It was like the reason I never saw fatal instinct. Sure. Which might be very funny, but it was just
too... Fatal instinct sucks. Fatal instinct sucks. Armando Santé, there's another guy.
That's a man who's not funny. I'm sorry. But he was, he was going to be like the next deniro. Yeah.
And then like, he just made a couple bad, he's still in ship, but he just made some bad decisions.
I like the Mambo Kings. That's what put him on the map. Yeah. The Mambo Kings is great.
You know, I love in the mouth of madness. I see him left. Oh, wait, no, sorry. That's Sam Neal.
Sam Neal. Armando, I love Gotti. Do you ever see the TV even be Gotti? Uh -uh.
Do you ever see Hoffa? He's in Hoffa. Yes. Hoffa, I mean, DeVito does not direct enough.
That is a guy who does some really cool things with a camera as a director. War of the Rose guy looks
like he directed the shit out of the world. Scotty Landis. He looks a lot like Scotty Landis.
If you don't know who Scotty Landis is, he's a writer friend of ours. And there's a guy in the craft
that looks exactly like him. Yeah. He plays the lawyer telling Farooza,
bulk and her mother, how much money they're inheriting when the dad dies.
Uh, it might be Scotty Landis.
Has Scotty been aligned this all this time? Is he actually a 55 year old character?
I'd buy it. Scotty Landis, by the way, has a horror movie being made, starring Octavia Spencer,
and directed by the guy who did the fucking help. I mean, I'm so proud of him. It's awesome.
Yes, I'm very excited about that. One of the rare good guys in this world.
It's awesome. I was in the Astro Diner with him when he told me about that.
And then a month later, I saw the announcement on Movie Web, which I thought was very cool.
I would have been there where I not hung over from hanging out with you the night before.
It was a different time that you weren't there because you weren't allowed to do this other time.
It just wasn't about it. Yeah. No, that was a night where...
I never do this anymore. Tonight, I'll probably have three, four whiskies. Have a great time. Go see
it. We're seeing a concert. But that was a night where I was in a bad mood. I had been drinking whiskey
with a friend and Joe pours me a large glass of wine. Red wine. You can hear on the podcast,
Joe, going, drink the wine. I'm two glasses ahead of you. Sip the wine. Well, I'm about to start
again. And you've had this full glass of whiskey for 55 minutes. You're an enabler, Joe.
And you can't bring wine into the mix. That's fine. I'm not saying we got to pound these things,
but, you know, we're also recording several podcasts today. I know.
You know, paste yourself. I don't want us to be talking later and you're like,
throw it anyway. I'll tell you, dump you piece of shit. You know, find me attractive anymore.
Well, that could never come out of my mouth. No, that's me. That was me to you. Oh, yes, yes.
All I want in life is a jukebox. I agree. Oh, that plays nothing but County Francis records.
I disagree. So I would love a jukebox. Why don't I have a fucking jukebox?
Faru's just to bring you up to. How much of the jukebox?
Well, you know, I don't know because I was about, I was trying to find that out recently
by asking a person that worked in bars and stuff like what it cost. And they said they didn't know
because they were all rented for so many years. Yeah. Like those style ones, we picked the record
because it was a mob thing. It was a mob thing. They were like, we're going to put this jukebox in
your bar. And then we're going to come and take all the money that people put into it.
And then that was it. Like that was right. So I don't, I have no idea what a jukebox would call.
I would guess that, that nice one they just had there in this day and age. Three grand. Yeah,
probably. I mean, now they're all fucking digital. It's like, it's like everything else.
Do I like going to the bar and being able to play any song in the world? I do. But do I sort of
prefer having to choose from the 100 that are presented to me? Yeah, I do. I like being like,
oh, they got this album. That's great. At least the E rustic still has the old fashioned one.
I don't think E rustic does. Oh, drawing room. They replaced that. Well, they had the old one.
They did a couple of years ago anyway. Uh, drawing room definitely does. Look, I still,
I still very much appreciate what I can say to somebody. Good bar, great jukebox. Yeah.
You know, but now any bar that has the, the, uh, computerized one has every song. It's kind of
cheating. Yeah. Yeah. And it's, you know, I hear you. And they, and it is become, it has become
like Spotify or anything else. Like where it's like, no, it is every song now.
It's not just every popular song. It's like, no, all of the Fugazi catalog is on there now too.
Like everything that you can think of that, that never saw the light of MTV or anything is on
there. And what blows the mind is that there's a still one person every night who thinks I bet this
group of people wants to hear hotel California. Yeah. That they haven't heard hotel California in a
while. Well, Vincent, I, I don't know if I've ever told this story on the podcast. Vincent, I were in
the, uh, roost one day, this guy came in, man, had to be 70, 72 years old, put in easily $10
worth of Al Yankovic. Oh, wow. Weird Al Yankovic. No, I, I know. Uh, I didn't think it was, uh,
normal Al Yankovic. Well, I think Al Yankovic is a polka guy from the 50s. Okay. Look, I, I used to
obsessed with weird Al when I was a child. Yeah. Then he goes outside, misses all of it.
Oh, comes back in. It might have been a prank. No, and he's like, did I miss the weird Al?
Did I miss all my weird Al? Who's really upset? And then he started talking to us about weird Al.
Yeah. I was like, buddy, I don't, I can't, you know, Jesus Christ. I don't know what to tell you. Like,
God bless you. All right. You like weird Al was you playing that the classics are like,
there's some albums I haven't heard. I'm pretty sure he played some of those deep polka cuts
like the polka medley's. I like the polka medley's. When I went to, I was out on, uh,
Alapalooza, the Jurassic Park album. That's when I got out. That's when I got out too. That was the one
that had, uh, if I'm not mistaken, the, the Phantom Menace American pie parody on it. That's the one
out. Oh, that's running with scissors. Yeah. Uh, I got out on, um, I got out way before that. I got
out on like, uh, dare to be fat. Even worse was my last one was the last one I did. But, uh,
when I went to, uh, I don't mean to name drop, but Craig Ferguson. Uh -huh. Good friend of mine.
When I went to this Christmas party, I saw, uh, I don't mean to name drop, Chris and Shaw,
another friend of mine. Uh, and I went over to say hi to her and her wonderful husband. And, uh,
and, uh, they were talking to somebody and I turned and, uh, the guy goes, hey, I'm out. And it was
weird. And it was a very weird moment to be like, oh, yeah, you're, yeah. I've heard he's one of the
nicest. He was very nice. His daughter and his wife were there. They were very nice. And I would tell
you, Joe, about meeting weird out at six flags. No. When I was, when I was nine, ten, I was
crazily obsessed with weird out. And I saw that he was coming to six flags over Mid -America and
St. Louis. And I had never been to a concert before. I asked my mother to take me and she obliged.
We went and I'm so excited about the show. I was like shaking all day. I was going to be at like
eight, nine o 'clock right in the rides. And we're at the Buccaneer, which is the big ship that goes
all the way up and all the way down. I like the Buccaneer. It sucks up your stomach, but I like it.
If you sit on that back seat, you lift off the seat. Right. Yeah. Yeah. I like that. So I said,
hey, mom, so I was dabbling in joke riding even at this young age. I said, how much does corn
cost on this ride? She said, I don't know. And I said, a Buccaneer. Ah, okay. Very good. And she
laughed. And then she looks over and she goes, wait a minute. Isn't that weird out over there?
Weird out was there with a beautiful young blonde woman.
Now, what era of weird hour are we talking? Are we talking Afro, like Jewish Afro,
mustache? Are we talking like straightened long hair? We're talking straightened long smells like
Nirvana days. Okay. I'm trying to hear what song this is. I couldn't believe it. I was blown away.
He was 10 feet away from me. And this beautiful model on his arm. And my mom goes, you should go tell
him your joke. And I was like, mom, it's stupid. She goes, go tell him your joke. He's a funny guy.
He likes jokes. I walked over my mom hot on my tail. I said, hi, Mr. Yang, I'm a big fan of yours.
Can I tell you my joke? He was like, I'd love to hear your joke. I tell him my joke. He laughed.
Although, let's be real. It was probably a fake laugh. He offers an autograph. Doesn't even make me ask.
I ripped off some piece of paper he signed it. I still have the piece of paper somewhere at my
dad's house. Excuse me, my dad's studio apartment. Lo blow to dad. No, that's not a blow. I'm just
telling you that's where you're at. All right, all right. The way you said it is. I'm sure he threw it away
honestly because that's that's something that doesn't survive the trip to a studio apartment. But
who could have been nicer? Could have been nicer. Good. Good. That's all.
Dad, did you see him perform that night? So I'm performing. He was great. And I have heard
to this day he's great because it's it's weird. Like he'll do like a surgeon and come out
dressed as a doctor. Yeah, he comes out in the fat suit for fun. Then he runs backstage, comes
out in the fat suit and you're like, what how do you do that? It's very cool. What did he open with?
Yes. I believe he opened with eat it. Okay.
Bound, go, go, go, go. Yeah. Because I've seen recent shows online. I think these days he's
opening with like a polka medley kind of thing. I, he always does on his albums of polka medley.
I think they're ingenious. I think they're great. They're very good. And I really like the one
where he does closer by nine inch nails in it. You let me buy you late. Yeah. Yeah. And every time
he said, I want to fuck you like an animal. Fuck his replace with like a cartoon. I poke noise.
Yeah. He's funny. And of course, I love UHF and I used to have a VHS collection of his videos.
And those were great too. I was over Vince's one night watching some sort of wrestling pay
per view. Not to brag. Not to brag. And everybody had cleared out. It was down to me, Vince and
Georgia's wife. And Vince and I were, we were pretty tuned up at this point. Sure. We're a
little stoned and he started talking about V8 UHF, man. And I was like, yeah, I love the movie.
And we were laughing hysterically just quoting it. I kept yelling, you idiots at him, you know, the
dead mean dad or whatever. And he put it on. Georgia's like, you guys have fun. I've had enough.
It's not a movie that the ladies love. But I mean, I will tell you this, we watched it. We were pigs
and shit. We were dying. And sure enough, the mean boss dad's first line is you idiots. I didn't know
that was his opening line. So when he comes in and yells at immediately, we were like, we were coming
to fucking pieces. I bought the special edition. I have not watched it in 20 years. I need to
actually watch the thing. But I saw UHF at the drive in theater. I remember it well. What is in
the special edition of UHF? You know, documentary. It's, it's a shout factory. Great Bob Oden Kirk joke.
What's that? Never Sunco's video. Do I remember Sunco's video? Yeah, he goes, uh, spent most of my
childhood there. This is an old joke. He goes, I was at a Sunco's video the other day, saw a DVD
Bofinger special edition. And he goes, what could possibly be in the Bofinger special edition?
I pick up the box. It says does not contain the movie Bofinger. All right.
Why go after Bofinger? Look, I like Bofinger. That's such a funny, well -written movie. Why go after Bofinger?
I like Bofinger a lot. That's a very funny joke. It's a joke that could have been so much funnier.
And I don't mean you got to go obvious, like go, you know, 50 shades of gray or something, but
I was written before. I know. You know what I mean? Yeah. You don't have to go with a notoriously
terrible movie. But Bofinger is, is like a very good comedy. I would think Oden Kirk would enjoy.
I like Bofinger. Look, what do you want for me? It's a joke. He made a joke. It was very fun.
Maybe the joke is that he actually literally saw Bofinger special edition and thought that's ridiculous.
Yeah, that's true. And then just wrote that punchline for it. That's true. It was a funny joke.
All right. My favorite Bob Oden Kirk stand -up joke ever is he said he goes, I was walking down Hollywood
Boulevard. I walked past the costume shop and in the window it said Santa's costumes. Not Santa
costumes. Santa's costumes possessive. Yeah. And he goes, so I don't understand. You go into
the story of the guy's like, well over here we have Santa's pirate costume. Now, of course,
if you're going to rent this, you got to rent a Santa costume to wear under it or it doesn't make sense.
I don't think of him as a stand -up. And the times I've seen him do it, he always seemed very nervous
and kind of reading off cards. But that's probably just because he's not, that's not his number one thing
anymore. I think he started as a stand -up. Yeah, but it's very funny. And it's, I love the man.
I just don't care for his shots at Bofinger. It's that kind of humor. It's all very Mr. Show,
right? Ask. You know, why are these dolphins dead? What's happening?
They're, oh, they're praying. Okay, so they're praying now to the black god, not black like race,
like, uh, you know what I mean? Like the black magic god, I mean, yeah. And, uh, he's a black
magic god. Is that David Bowie? No, it's Santana. Oh, she's a black magic woman. Um, I think like,
that's why Faruza Balk was yelling, I'm your daughter now. He's everywhere. I think they're saying
where if a Rooza is going too far. Not yet. They're, they're all still with Faruza except Tuddy.
Tuddy's starting to be like, what's wrong? We got to cool it. Yeah.
I mean, she's running red lights obviously. Well, no, she made the red light turn green. Oh, okay.
She's powerful. Okay. She's got power, but with great power comes great tits. Come on. I'm
kidding, Pete. That should have been the tagline. This was a time where that could have been the tagline
of this movie. Not anymore. And I think probably that's for the best. This movie's making magic
in my pants. You had wand right there. You didn't go with wand. Oh, okay. Sorry. You always have to
outright me. All right. You always have to one up me. Not one uping. Isn't anything good enough?
No, I'm fair enough. I agree. Uh, yeah. I mean, so here we are. This is the thing with these
commentaries. You hit a point where you're like, well, I'm done talking now.
We're at, we're at an hour three. That's usually when we end. Yeah. No, it's just past when we usually
work. An hour three, we've got another 37 minutes. Look, we're going to make them sizzle for you.
And we, and this is a special, this is a bonus, this is a bonus app, which means we can't do any
segments. That's right. And I, I will say this on the regular app that we're doing today, which
will be when we discuss Winchester. Oh, don't give anything away. Oh, yeah. Uh, I'm going to bring
back an old segment that we haven't done in a while because I don't really have anything for,
for movie corner. I haven't really been watching much lately. Okay. But I'm going to bring back the news.
Remember I said I wanted to do a news thing where we talked about a horror story in the news.
Yes. Yeah. So I got a great one. Oh, okay. All right. And I'm going to bring that back today.
And I'm thinking the title could be, now I'm not as good as the puns as you are. Uh, I think we
called news psycho. Yeah, that's pretty good. Like called Walter's thing, news cycle. Yeah. Yeah.
Uh, but I got a great. Oh, it's a good one. It's a real good story. Um, you're going to be
disgusted. I can't wait to be disgusted. I always am. Now here's something, Joe, and I remember this
pretty vividly, when all my friends and I would go to see any movie, especially once we were able to see
our rated movies, something that always infuriated us would be a shit, as I'm talking when I'm 18 or
something, a shower scene like that where the girls are all wearing towels, the girls are all wearing
towels and you start to feel like the scene's going to end and they didn't even put somebody in the
background walking through naked because this is all we had. I did not have the internet. And I would
be livid. This is not an R rated movie. The craft is definitely an R rated movie. I don't think
it is. I think it's PG 13. I don't want to bet, but I don't think they haven't said fuck once.
It's an R rated movie. Look it up. I bet it's PG 13. I couldn't see it. I know everything
before I was 17. I know the rating of I guarantee. They haven't said one real curse word yet.
I wish you'd bet. They said one or two slurs. I wish you'd fuck it. Even the slurs, they turned into
like weird variations of the slurs. There's been no nudity. There's been no sex. That's right.
I don't know. But why? I'm not the MPAA. I'm not Jack Valenti. Who's the head of the MPAA?
I don't get it. There's nothing they didn't curse. There's no nudity. What's the? Well, maybe they couldn't.
One day ago, this news story came out, the craft star, Rob and Tony would love to do a sequel.
That's a news story. What's Tony up to these days? Let's check on Tony. And then we're also
going to check on fucking true. Yeah, of course. We already checked on true. But you didn't see what
she was doing though. She's not doing anything. You just showed me the picture of her being the hottest
woman I've ever seen in my life. Rob and Tony. Oh, wow. She was on the mentalist for
10 years. So she made a lot of money. Let me see what Tony looks like these days. She looks
the same, right? Essentially, yeah. She was on prison breaks. She's been acting forever.
All right. She's in good shape. So she wants to do an old she wants to do like an older craft.
Oh, no, I'm in the mentalist fan page here. Jesus Christ. Or maybe it's a thing where they
show their daughters, the black magic. Yeah, it would be they'd probably be the moms is probably what
they do. It's like that now and then movie. Remember that doesn't bulk die at the end of this?
I don't recall, but thanks for spoiling that. Well, you know, I mean, it's it's not like we're real
invested in this thing. We're no. Tony's. Oh, look, well, here's a this is graphic.
Skeet all reaches trying to rape. Tony right now. So I forgot that yeah, this really gets dark.
I'm wrong. It gets very dark. Hello, Tony. Yeah. How does exactly the same? All of every girl in
this woman in this really looks exactly the same. How does it happen that all well, not all, I guess,
but for the most part, Agresses kind of look the same throughout their lives. Is it just because
they're so beautiful at a young age, or is it that the business forces them to, you know, I mean,
she doesn't keep it up. She's had like plastic surgery or anything. No, I wouldn't say they
these the cast of this movie is aged very well. Yeah. They've aged very well. For some reason, Rebecca
romaine is Stan, Stanis. Well, no, it's just Rebecca romaine now is trending. What do you think she's
trending back? Tell me what true's up to. We know. I mean, she's she's not really doing much. Her
credits that came up were like from the 90s. Why would she, maybe she's just a family now?
And well, you didn't let me watch that seven minute video about why she doesn't act anymore. No,
that was about bulk. Oh, yeah, you're right. Yeah. Rachel true. Former fashion model.
She was on the UPN sitcom half and half that ran for four years. That's something. What the hell is
half and half never heard of it? She was in Noah, which I like the Russell Crowe movie.
Russell Crowe, yeah. Okay. Who'd she play in there? She was in. Oh, she was a voice. I guess
that's not as ideal. Okay. Dawson's Creek. Yeah, it looks like she's things have thinned out the
most for Rachel true. She was in Sharknado too. All right. Blood Lake attack of the killer lampries.
Attack of the killer lampries. Things have dried up. And bulk, bulk sounds like it slowed down too.
But maybe this is by choice. Maybe they just don't want to, you know, well, Joe, I think what it
probably is is that actresses far more than actors age out of Hollywood. They don't want them once
you hit a certain age. It's a sad but true fact. It's a disgusting fucking business. Of course.
In town and city. I'm ashamed to live in it quite frankly because if you're going to be a love
interest in a movie, you need to actually be 15 years younger than the male 15 to 20 years younger than
them. Or in the case of a Clint Eastwood movie, 40 to 50 years younger than the male. So it's
unfortunate. That's what it is. And nobody's making like a Rachel true vehicle. You know, she's
got to kind of take what she can get sad. But but but Campbell and Campbell and Tony are still working.
That's true. That's true. I think, you know, they're just names that stuck in the public consciousness
more than the other two. Okay. bulk is now seducing skid all rich. I and he's going to hurt him.
He's shoving it. Well, she's seducing him to I think to hurt him. But he shoved her away and he's
drunk. Now she's going to do something like she's upset now because he shoved her. So she's going to do
something really. See, this is why you're not attracted to bulk is because she's able to play this
thing so well. Yeah. Like this insane. She plays crazy very well. Yeah. It's intimidating.
Well, the truth is I did my I did my time dating dating crazy people. And I I don't ever want to go
back to it. Well, I don't think she's actually crazy. I'm just saying I think she plays crazy well.
But I think that I think you're right that I don't respond well to it to the crazy. And that's set
you off. That's me off. Yes. Tony going at it. Tony going at it. All rich getting more than he deserves
certainly. So all Rick got to make out with all of these gals in the course of one movie. No, only her.
He and oh, I guess bulk, right? No. Pete bulk tried to seduce him. He pushed her away. And then
she transformed into Tony. Gotcha. And he just rolled with it. Well, that's a bad wig. Well,
she went bald. Still, you could do better than that in the wig. Well, I think the point is that
she was the popular hot girl. And you know, she's obviously wearing a wig because she lost all her hair.
Right. What were you going to say? Did he what? Uh oh, now the real Sarah walks in.
And bulk is there. Nice prank. But I'm saying he saw her morph, correct?
Yeah. So why did he just roll with that? I don't know. But the first thing he yelled was
he shit faced. And the first thing he yelled was, you're a witch. That's what you'd yell. You
wouldn't be like, I had too much. I got to get out of here. Right. Her face just changed. I got
to get a lot to drink. I never thought that a lady turned into another lady in my presence. Yeah.
Well, sometimes they look a little different the next morning. But uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh,
me. Um, now, this is a very good Jack and Coke you made here. But uh, it's giving me a little acid
reflux for some reason, which I don't care for. That's not on me. I'm not saying you did it. I'm just
saying it's on drinking whiskey and coke, two things that cause acid. Oh, look at that classic
witch move. Like the feet, the toes dragging on the floor. She floats. That is a classic witch move.
It's kind of a feminist picture here. Uh, well, yeah, it's about four women underdogs. Yeah.
You know, fighting back. And, uh, and they all do a good job of it, except bulk goes a little,
bulk goes a little bulk. Let's be honest. Yeah. She goes a little Faruza in this thing.
I think she's going to kill him. She's going to kill ski. There he goes.
Skate. Skate. Skate. Motherfucker. Skate goes out the window onto the, look, now this is an R rated movie
and they don't show him hit the fucking pavement. I'm starting to wonder if they didn't intend to go
for a PG 13 because there's also a shower scene where everyone's wearing three. I'm telling you,
they wanted it to be PG 13 and the God damn suits said it had to be art. They haven't said fuck
one. I bet if it was man, witches, they would have gotten a PG 13 rating. Have you seen the film
Bert Wunderstone? Of course. It's one of the funniest movies in recent years. It's pretty funny.
It was directed by my, my friend, Mr. Don Skardino. He's a nice man. Yeah. Uh, I think it's a very,
very funny film, but I like it the beginning when he does the trick, the magic trick for young Steve
Buscemi and young Steve Buscemi goes, you're a boy witch. Yeah. I also like when, I thought the movie
had plenty of laughs and the cast for God's sake, Gandal Fanny. I like when old Steve Buscemi
says he's doing charity work by bringing magic kits down to starving children in third world
country and then they're showing the b -roll footage on the news and the kids are trying to eat the
magic kit. Yeah. Yeah. That's a dark joke. Very funny. Now, I'll say, and I'm still, I'm not even
halfway done here with the strength, but I, I need to eat. I need to order some food. I eat a late
lunch. Oh, you're okay. You're better off. But we can order something. You want to order pizza?
That'd be nice. And we could eat it during the next podcast. That'd be real nice. Yeah, you're
going to want to hear us chew. This is crazy. Sorry, folks. That's ice. Look, it's a party vibe. I
hope you're enjoying a cocktail while you watch the craft with us. I think people are listening to
this at work. Yeah. So I'd say if you are enjoying a cocktail at the moment, you might want to look
into something. Right. But program. I mean, it's, it's, it's one thing to drink a little slowly
impatient. This is absurd. An hour on a drink. Oh, right. Oh, Jesus, the peer pressure. It's
not peer pressure. I just don't want to feel like I have a problem. Can you talk while I pour
this? Yeah, please. I can talk while you pour it. Folks, the podcast itself, we got some stuff
coming up. We got, before I wake, the Netflix picture is going to be on Monday.
What are you dropping this this week? This will be out sometime this month. Okay. You're going to
have before I wake or maybe you already have it. We're also going to do Winchester, starring Helen
Mirren, which Joe and I saw at the theater together in Las Vegas. We'll also be discussing our time
in Vegas on that podcast. And then we're doing blade. And let's, let's say it blade two. I've never
seen blade Trinity, but we'll be talking about blade one and two. So if you want to prepare,
those are the ones to look out for Trinity. We can skip. I, you know, I don't hate Trinity,
but it's the worst of the three. It's a lot of Ryan Reynolds and Jessica Beale. Nobody needs that.
What role does Pat and Oswald play? A nerd. I believe he plays the nerdy comic relief,
surprisingly. And in a movie where Ryan Reynolds is apparently doing nonstop comic relief,
they needed additional comic relief. I don't remember if Reynolds is, I don't think Reynolds is
funny in it. I think it's before Reynolds became like Mr. Deadpool. Well, he was always Van Wilder
ring any bells. Yeah, no, but I don't know. Waiting ring any bells. Best friend, just friends. That's
a fun movie. Just friends is a very underrated comedy if you haven't seen it. I'm sure it's streaming
somewhere. Ashton, Kutcher and Eddie Murphy, Honeymoon movie. Oh, Brittany Murphy. It's like
Eddie Murphy. So you're talking about what happens. Not what happens in Vegas. You're talking about,
yeah, that movie was okay. Not great. Yeah, no, I know you're talking about. Yeah, Ryan Reynolds
was a guy who for years, I was like, I know I should hate Ryan Reynolds, but he's funny. How
is this guy not connecting? And then he he did at age, whatever age he is, 45. He's very funny.
Yeah, he's very funny. I watched the new Deadpool trailer and I thought it looked funny. I hadn't seen
the trailer, but I enjoyed Deadpool. This is again, by that's by not only the pair one imports,
but also Jumbo's clown room. Oh, was that the Jumbo shopping center? It's like right by there, yes.
Now, uh, Tuddy is back in the witch store. She realizes things are going wrong here. It's just
store for witch things. In a straight mall. Yeah, where the proprietor is always wearing a
flowing robe of some sort and you're supposed to think nothing's up. This proprietor, they should have
gone for like sissy space, or somebody a little nod to horror past. Yeah, you know, somebody with a
little something behind the eyes that made you wonder if they were okay. Yeah, this lady's a
little bland. And it's basically used to do all this shit. She was in fucking blast from the past with
Brendan Fraser. You want to talk about a bad movie? Was that movie bad? Oh, Fraser could do no right
back then. George at the jungle. Dudley do right. Dudley do right. More like Dudley do wrong, folks.
Blast on the past, uh, mummy quick, uh, war of the scorpion emperors, whatever the fuck that last
mummy was called. Yeah. Yeah. Boy, I hated the mummy movies. I know a lot of people have some love
for them. I think you're probably a kid when you saw them as the only explanation I could think.
They're not bad movies. They're just, they just weren't a time where CGI was not ready. Right.
And it's obvious. I mean, Lucas was the only guy at that time that could come even close. Yeah,
to making it look passable. Right. Anybody outside of that was it was just like it looked like made for
to sci -fi shit. Yeah. You know, played had some questionable effects as well. The first one.
It does. It was kind of on the line. It does. There's some bad blood effects in it. Yeah, but we'll
talk about that one, but, uh, but yeah, but I'm looking forward to the blade discussion because I
were special effects you've seen in a, in a theatrical release. Uh, I thought final destination five's
effects were so bad. It, I couldn't even keep watching it. I don't know. People say that's a good horror
movie. Uh, Texas Chainsaw, the 3D one that came out a couple of years ago, horrific. Okay.
Terrific effects. Uh, those are the two that come to mind right now where I was, I was pissed off
at how bad I thought the effects look. I'm usually forgiving. It's been since the 90s since I've heard
people like laughing at effects. Well, what's, give me a bad one. I don't think my, my memory's going
to be good here. I don't know, but I mean, people would really like yuck it up in the theater.
I just, yeah, I don't know like I can't, uh, I'm trying to think like, yeah, I remember, yeah,
the Texas, I found the final destination five. I, I, again, I didn't finish watching it, but I was
willing to give it a little more leeway because it's final destination and, right, again, these are
horror movies that are sort of bred and, and spawned out of the sort of Dawson's Creek kind of thing.
And, you know, it, who cares, ultimately, like it, it wasn't the end of the world. Texas
chainsaw having computer animated effects in it. I found, uh, holy offensive, uh, to add,
there was no reason to add fake blood to Texas chainsaw, right, except for the fact that they wanted
it to be 3D, and they wanted, I guess, the blood to come out of the screen. But even then, no, because
there were plenty of horror movies that were made in 3D in the 80s and they used real blood
and real objects and whatever. So I just was very, very offended by that. Have you seen that latest
Texas chainsaw that was like streaming leather face? The prequel? No, it got really bad reviews.
I saw a few that were all right. Um, I also didn't like that they called it leather face. There's
already been a Texas chainsaw sequel called leather face that was good. Um, I also don't need yet
another fucking prequel to these movies. Sure. Um, I remember just massively depressed by that
one with Jessica Biel. I just thought it was so relentlessly miserable that I, it's pretty
miserable. I like it. I wanted to be out of it. I liked it. But, uh, yeah, it's dark. I mean,
it's not, you know, but, uh, you know, I don't know. I just, I think I think they need to let the
franchise go. I think it's just, there's, you're never going to recreate the magic that Toby
Hooper created with the original. You're never going to recreate the fun he created with the sequel.
It's just, leave it alone. It's just done. It's done. There's no way to get back to any of that. Uh,
so I don't know. But, uh, I do hear, and I'm very happy about this. I've been reading reviews of the
latest hell razor film, which comes out. I think in a week or so on Blu -ray, it's supposed to be
pretty good. Solid sequel. First good sequel in a long time. Is it Clive Barker? It's not. But,
and it's not Doug Bradley, either as pinhead. It's a new pinhead. But apparently the new pinhead is
good. And apparently the movie is a deserving sequel. And it harkens back to the original films much
more than all these other sequels they made that weren't so hot. The why and Bradley on it anymore
is too old. He turned it. He turned the last two down. I understood why he turned down judgment.
That was a terrible, terrible movie. But I didn't get why he turned down this one. And the director
said it was over a non -disclosure agreement. Bradley said he would read the script. They sent him an
NDA and they said he got really pissed and refused to sign it. Huh. And he was like, yeah, you know,
basically like I am this fucking franchise. How dare you ask me to sign an NDA like I'm offended. Okay.
And the director was like, this is kind of just like part for the course, man. Like it's not
right. Like, you know, I'm not trying to demean you. Yeah. So I don't know. Oh, that's gross.
Yeah, this is gross. This whole sequence. It's a lot of snakes and scorpions and worms coming out
of toys. This is kind of a playoff of which, which is a beastwik. Yeah. Well, if you'll remember,
Skid Ulrich earlier called them the bitch of the beastwik. He did? He did. I didn't see that.
Did you like which is a beastwik? I love which is a beastwik. Yeah, it's very under time. And this
is similar. It's from the director of Mad Max, the witch of the beastwik. This is similar. It's
under it's a group of underdog women who are having a tough time. They start using magic to get ahead.
It goes a little too far. You know, Faruza bulk is sort of the Nicholson character, right.
But man, she's really, yeah, bulk, bulk's off the fucking rails. She's a she's now telling
Tuddy to kill herself. Did you like the witches with Angelica Houston? I found that movie very
entertaining. I own it. I think I love it. It's a wonderful kids film. It's genuinely scary. Yeah.
The witches are really scary in that movie. I agree. They don't even do more kid stuff that's
actually scary, man. For some reason, that just stopped. I mean, unless, you know, kids are scared of
things that were not or something. But when I was a kid, I was traumatized by shit that is still
very scary, including starring Faruza bulk returned to us, the scariest of the most. Turned
eyes, dark crystal, yeah, labyrinth, scary shit. You've pointed out before little monster that's
terrified me. Yes. Sorry. I know. Come on. I'm teasing you. I'm teasing you.
So, now, does bulk have Campbell under a spell? And true as well? Is that why they're following her?
It would appear that way. Now, I'm seeing a similar effect here to that episode of Perfect
Strangers where they're floating up in the ceiling. Yes. This is much like the haunted house episode
of Perfect Stranger. I wonder which influenced which. I would think that this was inspired by
Perfect Stranger. I think you're probably right. I think most great horror movies are based on
key episodes of sitcoms. Yeah. Yeah. That's what I think. Pat, I'm really getting tired here.
It's too long to talk. It's too long to talk. People always request a return to the commentary for
them. I think because they enjoy hearing us in a position of torment and torture. At what point
are people saying I'm loving listening to this? You know what? Like, at this point, they are
for whatever reason they are. We did on this show, the fucking shining, which is like 2 .30 or so.
In my mind, by the end of that, it was unlistenable, boring horse shit, and it gets sighted a lot. People
love the episode. I don't know. Now, here's the one thing I don't like about this film.
Is the witches can do anything they want? Yeah. There needs to be some limits to the powers.
Fruza bulk is making notes written by Tutti appear out of thin air. She's filling the house up with
snakes. Like, you got to come on. You can't just do anything you think of. You know?
I agree. Give it a, you know, come on. Then there's no, that's like, look, she just cut her wrists from,
she was floating in the air and she slid her wrists open. Like, Fruza bulk slid Sarah's wrists open.
It's like, if you could do that, just cut her head off or something. Like, you made skid or we
fall out of a window with your mind. Yeah. Just make her head explode or something if you hate her so much.
I realize, Fruza reminds me of Mary Elizabeth Ellis who plays the waitress on always sunny
and a very nice person. The wife of Mr. Charlie Dan. She is somebody else who I find has, I've never
met her. She's stunning eyes. Beautiful. Beautiful person. Woman, whatever you want to say.
Eyes just her eyes just they sparkle like the Nile. Oh my god. And I'll give you a recommendation.
Mary Elizabeth and Artemis Peptani who played art plays. Artemis on always sunny. Always one of my favorite
characters. They used to do this show at UCB called, it was a spoof of lifetime movies called
Mother May I Sleep with Mary Jane's Fist. And it was such a funny stage show and they did it with
Tim and Eric producing on Adult Swim. And it's extremely funny if you can find it. It is, they
aired it as everything on Adult Swim and aired once at midnight. I don't know if you can find it
but it is about a young troubled girl who is a ballet dancer played by Mary Elizabeth. Artemis is
the instructor and Artemis starts fisting her. And then at some point Mary Elizabeth starts really
enjoying it and they formed this uneasy alliance. And it was just as fucked up as I remembered. I
can't believe they aired it but I loved it. I loved it. I want to see it. And those two wrote it
directed at the whole night. Oh I want to see it. That's great. All right. I'll have to start
tuning into Adult Swim at midnight. Yeah. Very dark. When did this come out? Very dark. I
watched it about a month ago. Oh so it's new. That's correct. Oh good. Do you ever watch the
Tim Heidecker murder trial? No. I don't even know. I think it's was, I think you made it for
Adult Swim online or something but like if you go on YouTube you just watch it. He just has a
fake murder trial. I have not seen it. It's a lot of him just like they shoot it like C -SPAN
and everything. Right. It's a lot of him like leaning back and whispering to the lawyers and stuff.
Okay. It's really weird. It's really fucking weird. I like that. I mean of course I like the
original show but I also like bedtime stories which is their short horror anthology. Bedtime stories
is great. It's very entertaining. I also really like his cooking show that he did for Josh. I ain't
seen that. It's what you think it would be. It's him not knowing at all how to cook and make
like the most disgusting dishes. Right. And then calling them like party dips. Sure. We're
going to show you to make Tim's party thousand island dressing. Yeah. And it's like
cuts up a head of lettuce and mixes it with man. It's disgusting. I tend to not like the grosser
aspects of their stuff but it's just food. It's just gross because it's food. You know what I mean?
I do. I do. Do you wash? Now Joe, I've been meaning to ask you about this for years now
because your whole desktop is up when we watch these things. Yeah. What is Seaky Muppets?
C -I -K -I Muppets? What is it? Is it a script?
It's a segment we did. Seaky is C -I -K -I. That's Ken I kick it. That's the hip -hop show.
Right. The live hip -hop comedy show we would do it meltdown. Right. Muppets was a bit we did on the show
that I wrote about. We would play Mark AGM myself wrote it, the producer or me. We would play
a rapper's voice and then you'd have to guess which Muppet he sounded like. Okay.
Or like which Muppet matched his voice. Okay. Got it. So one of them was or Jim Henson creature really
was. So like one of them we played B -Rio from Cypress Hill and then it was the skexies from the dark
crystal. You know, it's like it was a funny bit. I think Ice Cube was the bear that or the dog that
played the piano. Ralph. Who I used to make Blum. Yes. Yes. Oh, I forgot about that. Yeah.
I'm sure Ice Cube wouldn't like to hear that. Well Ice Cube wasn't Ralph. He wouldn't even know
what the hell you were talking about. I know. So now Sarah is making roaches come out of Farooza
Bok's jacket. Pretty mild when you just slitter wrists. And now she's turning her fingers into snakes.
Right. I mean, I don't know. It's just there's a lot of gross out stuff here in the end. I mean,
it appears to me and I'm going to have to watch it without this commentary because I don't
remember any of it. It appears like a lot of things to be a movie that's really pretty interesting
and then just turns into a special effect deal. And if it's good and entertaining in this home stretch
great, but a lot of movies go this route and I tend to get bored with the shit. You have to do it.
People want the effects. I do agree that it's kind of just like we got to we got to fill out the
last 10 minutes. So let's do a bunch of weird effects that aren't really that weird. And then it's
never possible for me to give a shit when everything that's happening, risk cutting snake's hands,
et cetera, goes away in five seconds. How are you supposed to give a shit? Well, that's what I'm
saying. It doesn't mean anything. Yeah. It doesn't mean that they can do whatever they want. Right. Right
now she could have just made herself because they sure he did it. Faruza bulk just could have made
herself look like Sarah the good guy. Yeah. And convinced the other girls that Sarah was on their team.
Right. You know what I mean? I do. I do. So now Sarah puts a binding spell on Faruza bulk,
which means I guess she can never do magic again.
And now Faruza bulk is trying to do it. Could she just do a spell that says, wait, I can do magic?
Pat, I honestly don't know. Faruza bulk is waving a knife violently in Sarah's face. There isn't one
cut happening in this R -rated movie. There hasn't been one drop of blood in this R -rated movie.
Not literally not one. That would be true. So, you know, and then a dresser just smashed
her into the wall. Sarah, who is Tuddy? I'll say this. Rob and Tuddy was an empire records.
Remember that movie? I never saw it though. That was sort of the precursor to high fidelity.
Sure. No one here is good, but yeah, a lot of people love that movie. Or it was sort of a mystic
pizza and a record store. Rob and Tuddy is wearing a wig because she shaved her head for empire
records. She's wearing a wig in this movie. That's correct. Well, she's, that's a great wig I can't tell.
Actress Faruza bulk is actually a wicking and real life. Oh, that's interesting. You gotta deal with that.
Wikins are, I know a dear friend of mine's a wicking and it's very, it's very positive religion,
actually. Yeah. I'm just not into it because it's a religion, you know. If you said to me,
she's a Christian, I'd really get it. The Sarah Gilbert character on my show is both Wikin and a
Juggelow. She's a Juggelow. Yeah. Wow. Though, she cites those as sort of equal religious influences
in her life. The director Andrew Fleming who I'm pretty sure also did Dick, which is a very entertaining
movie. You ever see Dick? It's like all the president's man with Kirsten Dunn's. Yeah. I know.
And it's isn't a David. No, Bruce McCullough is in that day full. He's in it too. I was going to say
David's. It's bad. I was wrong. But isn't doesn't McCullough play Bernstein? I think so. I mean, it was a
crazy idea. McCullough is the record. Kids know, kids know nothing about Nixon. Dick McCullough directed
it. Andrew Fleming, the guy who did this movie directed it. McCullough wrote it then. McCullough had
something to do with it. I don't think. But Andrew Fleming says a PG -13 rating was sought. They
followed all the guidelines to earn that rating. But in the final outcome, the film was rated are simply
because it dealt with teenage girls using witchcraft. How about that? As opposed to what? I don't know.
They just thought it would be a bad influence. There's no way that's a wig she's wearing by the way.
Look at her hair. You can see it like connected to her scalp. That's not a wig.
They're saying it's a wig. I don't know. Maybe she's got extensions in.
Maybe. Or maybe they like weave the wig into regular hair. But I mean, Jesus Christ, you can see
the hair sprouting out of her fucking head. See that to me looks like a wig. I mean, they can get
them right. Can they? Yeah. Yeah. All the teen actresses were in their 20s at the time of filming
and Rachel Tru was 30. She's 30 years old. The black girls. Yeah. She's 30? That's correct.
Jesus. She looks younger than anybody else. I know. A lot of fun facts. Though the song,
how soon as now was originally performed by this mess, love spit love.
That's right. You got to wave your cock and everybody's facing. You know, nobody needs it. Nobody
seems to complain. Angelina Jolie auditioned and did not get the role. Seems like she should have
done it. Same year as Nev Campbell and Skidall did scream. All right. There were plans to release
the director DVD sequel, focusing on Ferruza Bach, but those plans were dropped for unknown
reasons. So the movie ends with Bach in an insane asylum. Yeah. And so yeah, that would be a good
sequel if she gets out of the crazy house and then, and then, you know, starts fucking
wreck and shit, right? Right. I'd be into that. I agree. The movie ends with her strap to a bed
saying I'm flying. I'm flying. I can fly. That's dark. Yeah. So she doesn't die. Yeah. Okay.
Well, that's good. They could have brought her back. And Andrew Fleming also did Hamlet 2 with Steve
Cougan, which is fucking hilarious. I heard it's a great movie. Hamlet 2 is fucking hilarious if you
haven't seen that. And it's weird. He's a comedy guy. He did like Lady Dynamite, Red Oaks,
difficult people, some really funny shows. But Hamlet 2 was his last movie crazily. What happened to him?
I don't know. He went into television. It appears. He directs the best of TV. And the writer
was Andrew Fleming, not Bruce McCullough of Dick had nothing to do with the film, Joe. All right.
Well, I just wanted to get all those your wrongs out before we wrap. Well, folks, that's our show.
The credits are rolling. Folks, I think we've proved what we don't do the commentaries. We're fantastic
for an hour. And then really tread water till the end. And we had done fucking Jackie Brown or
Goodfellas. There'd still be an hour to go. But this is for you guys and we hope you enjoy it.
Thank you very much. We'll see you next time. We'll see you in hell.