I'll see you in hell.
And when the sound of your screams becomes a thing of my dreams, you know I'll say.
You know I will.
I'll see you in hell.
Folks, it's we'll see you in hell.
Well, those are harsh folks.
I could hear it in my headphones.
I'm sorry about that.
I don't mean to startle you during the Christmas season, the holiday season, the whatever you celebrate season.
But the season is the reason we're talking holiday films today.
And that holiday film is Nutcrackers.
Nutcrackers.
Ben Stiller and four kids who are actually related wherein they shot the movie in their actual house.
Yes.
How about that?
Linda Cardellini.
I always love seeing Linda Cardellini.
Cardellini in a role that I don't even know if her role was written or if she just happened to be visiting set and they turned the camera on her.
I mean, talk about a part that was underwritten for Christ's sake.
Yeah.
They said, Linda, just show up and wince every seven or eight minutes and then you can be on your way.
Don't worry about it.
She's got it.
If the camera panned over two inches left, you'd see her caught where she got us all just be sleeping here.
Yeah.
Hey, while you're going to the bathroom, would you mind if we recorded you saying, boy, we're so happy you've changed Ben Stiller.
We might need to put that over the last two minutes of the movie.
Yeah, sure.
I can do that.
Can we do it while I'm in the bathroom?
I got to go.
Yeah, I guess it's probably fine.
We can set it up in here.
That's fine.
Folks, I what was I going to say?
Well, what are you doing for Christmas?
How about that?
What am I doing for Christmas?
I'm going back to Missouri.
Okay.
My one of my friends who lives in Kansas City has a giant costume holiday party every year that I've never gone to.
So I'm flying into Kansas City, going to that party and then driving into St. Louis with some friends, which should be a lot of fun.
And does he have this party on a riverboat with a bunch of high stakes gamblers and flappers as one would imagine a Kansas City party?
No, it's much more like owl masks.
There's big troughs of lube in each room, that kind of Kubrick eyes wide shut type of vibe.
All right.
This ain't your daddy's Kansas City.
No.
New Kansas City.
I got you.
The costume thing is cowboys, which I hate a costume thing so much.
I never participate.
And it's like if I'm going to be packing it in a suitcase, you know, like, I don't know.
I don't want to be the only person not doing it, but we'll see what happens.
It should be fun.
I'm going home for like five days back to Missouri, see my friends.
How about yourself?
You're doing your usual back home.
Yeah, the usual partying with friends up until the second of the dreaded actual Christmas day hang, which will be me and just my parents in my house.
It's going to be a lot, but we'll get through it.
The big thing this Christmas is I love my parents, but I mean, that's a tough that's a tough hang coming to you.
Yeah, at least that's happening.
But then you can't leave.
I can't leave.
I will go outside and scream repeatedly and come back in.
OK.
Everybody ready for dessert?
The big thing that's happening this year and I am excited is is Pinkstone and his wife are coming and staying.
They come up here every year, but they're staying with me this year, which is nice because they usually get a hotel and whatever.
So I said to stay with me.
So they're coming a couple of days early and I'm actually going to have Christmas morning with Jim and his wife, Jess, the three of us, which will be really awesome.
Yeah.
And then my parents will come and then they'll leave and then Jim and Jess will come back from their family's house and, you know, little shindigs and whatever would have you throughout the week should be nice.
Let me ask you this and it's a dark question.
Sure.
So you and I are a bit of a rarity in that we are men over 40 who are single, no family, etc.
Do you like I just did this at Thanksgiving.
My married friends with their two little daughters invited me up for Thanksgiving and I go and they clearly loved having me there.
The daughters love me.
I'm Uncle Pat.
We all laughed.
We had a lot of fun.
We were going to watch for the third year in a row.
We were going to watch a movie, but wound up talking too much and laughing too much and having too much fun and not doing it.
But then I drive home thinking I ruined these nice people's family Thanksgiving.
I'm the Del Griffith who they invite.
And I just rewatched Planes Trains and I didn't I never think when I watched that movie, this guy's going to be a big problem for them.
Steve Martin's wife must think he's so annoying.
She doesn't want, you know, because I flash forward to after that final scene, but something in my head, it's like when I see somebody eating alone, I'm like, they must be the saddest, loneliest man.
Alive.
Even though I do it every day and love it.
Like, do you have that feeling?
Are you like, I have it in my own way.
I spend most of the day believing that everybody in my life hates me.
Exactly.
Same.
If I don't get a text back or a return call, I'm convinced they hate me.
Yes.
I'm convinced I said something that horrifically offended them.
Then, of course, what happens is a week later, the person goes, oh, dude, I'm so sorry.
I never got back to you.
Can I tell you how much fun I had when I saw you?
You're like, really?
Because I've been telling myself that you've severed our friendship over that.
Like it's so yeah, I get it.
I get it in my own in my own way.
Usually, I don't feel if the time is fun and everybody's laughing or whatever.
I usually am pretty good at feeling like in that moment, like I brought something to that.
Look, I've been see you were you were married for a while and you've had long term girlfriends and stuff.
I've never even really had it.
My longest relationship ever was eight months or something.
Yeah.
I am very used used used to used to.
Being the sort of, you know, the Del Griffith, as you put it, or not even the Del Griffith, the like.
I'm trying to think of a better example.
I'm used to being the Fonzie.
You mean Dupree?
Yes, the Dupree.
I was going to say Fonzie, not because of the coolness, because he was 48 and still, you know, was single.
Yeah.
I'm used to being the Dupree at this point.
Like it's like and I have been told repeatedly by friends and friends spouses.
Yeah.
How much they appreciate that with me.
Because here's the thing.
You as a guy, you always think, well, your guy friends love it when you come around.
But the wife, the wives must never be thrilled.
I've I've surpassed all that.
I now have the wives saying to me, can you please come and hang out because it's more fun?
Yeah.
Don't make me hang out with just my husband, please.
You know, so I've been in that zone for a while.
But when I'm there with the daughters, I'm like, am I fucking up like a family tradition?
You know, like am I are these little girls like, why is this weird guy here for our special day?
And it's like, I don't think that's happening.
And they invited me.
But then I'm like, did they invite me because I'm fun or out of pity?
And you just shouldn't have these thoughts.
They're bad for you.
Which is what today's film is about.
It's about a guy in this exact position.
Yeah, pretty much.
And you'd think I'd relate to it in in any way, but you'd be wrong.
It's weird how it's no longer easy to find Ben Stiller relatable.
Yeah.
As the normal guy, only because you know, he's worth one hundred and sixty eight million dollars.
You know, it's weird that you can't just sit back and go, I get it.
He's he's the he's the fuck up.
He he did it so well for so long.
I mean, I rewatched Meet the Parents last week, and it's not like he wasn't a big actor at that point.
But like you still you watch that movie and you feel so terrible for him as the world piles pot shit after shit after shit on him.
Everything goes wrong for him in that movie.
A classic. But you're on his side the whole time.
Now, when you see Stiller for some reason, is it 20 years of accumulating wealth?
Is it us getting older?
Is it the fact that he doesn't really act anymore?
I don't know, but I just saw him and I'm like, fuck this guy.
Whatever happened to Terry Polo, by the way?
Who cares?
I mean, who cares?
They remember when they did her real dirty like five years ago and started talking about her a lot, the Seinfeld cast.
Did you catch that little mini -news story?
Why the Seinfeld cast? She wasn't on Seinfeld.
She wasn't?
Oh, yeah. Heidi Swedberg was the woman who looks exactly like her, who played George's fiance.
Yeah, no, that I remember. But Terry Polo.
Yeah, you're right.
I mean, I never thought she was an incredible actress, but like she was, you know, she was big for a while.
She was good, but she's fine.
There's her, there's Hope Davis, there's George's fiance, where they're all kind of like the same blonde woman.
And that's just not my type of, I never liked any of those actors.
Laura Linney is the one who jumps out of that pack.
Laura Linney's ex is amazing. Hope Davis is a great actor.
She is.
Actor, actress, whatever. But I will say this.
She, there are few people I've seen on screen that I can imagine.
I've never met her, but I just imagine it is miserable hanging out with her. She just does not seem.
Which one, Terry Polo?
Hope Davis.
Hope Davis, yeah.
Oh, God, like just seems like she'd be like, really, you're going to do that?
I don't think that is true of Hope Davis. I think that she mastered playing that type of woman.
And I think the fact that she played that type of woman so amusingly probably shows that she is not one of those women, is my guess.
But I don't.
I want you to Google right now Hope Davis and look at the three pictures that come up.
I imagine her nose is a little upturned, like she's smoking poop.
Look at the two big pictures.
Hope Davis.
Yep. Oh, okay.
The two big pictures. This does not look like a fun person.
Look, I'm not saying I light a room up. I'm just saying, yeah.
She's perfect in About Schmidt. She's perfect in that movie.
And The Weatherman. Like she was always in American Splendor.
Movies about the almost the inability to find happiness.
She's had been in three of the best of them.
Yeah, it's pretty impressive.
Yeah. I mean, who knows? Maybe she's a blast. I don't know.
That's only one way to find out, Joe.
We're going to Hollywood.
Maybe she's on Raya.
She's probably on Raya.
I
This week remembered, not remembered, not remembered like I haven't looked,
but I deep during the darkest days of the pandemic bought some Bitcoin.
Never discussed Bitcoin on this show.
It's not something people really tell you whether they have it or they don't
because of the shame surrounding it.
Really? I can't tell you how many fucking people I've had tell me about
their Bitcoin.
Okay.
I'm being serious. I'm not Joe. I'm not. I'm not saying so.
Don't tell me. I'm saying I hear.
I feel like I never not hear about people's Bitcoin.
Well, some people clearly do.
I've been dating a lot and women are like,
please tell me you're not one of these Bitcoin bros is going to talk my ear off.
I'm like, no, no, no, no, no, but I got some.
I got I got real bored during the old Panda.
I had a friend who was real obsessed with it and he got me on board.
And we haven't consciously decided to avoid talking politics.
We just really haven't.
Who cares at this point?
But regardless of how you feel over the events of the last couple weeks,
whatever happened between Trump and this Bitcoin,
your boy is fucking rich.
Your boy is fucking real.
And I'm selling it.
This is what people want to hear as everybody's struggling is you gloating
that your investment has popped.
Folks, I all I'm saying is if you get a time machine,
do not kill Hitler.
That's going to be your temptation.
You just go back and buy a bunch of Bitcoin with whatever money you have,
because it's going to go up in crazy ways.
Now, I watched a Warren Buffett interview about Bitcoin.
Yeah.
Not the singer, Pat Warren Buffett is a financial guy.
You're thinking of Jimmy Buffett.
I know.
He said, no, I don't know.
I don't have Bitcoin, but then I don't have an opinion about it either way.
I see the value or and equally, I don't have interest.
I could go either way on it.
But he said you could offer him all the Bitcoin in the world and he wouldn't buy it.
And he said, because you buy property, property has purpose and has value.
It has a use.
You buy a business, it has a use.
He goes, Bitcoin's only profit potential is to sell it to somebody who paid,
who will pay you more than you paid for it.
He was like, it doesn't do anything.
It's just a thing to buy to potentially resell.
So my question is, well, you can buy things with it.
I mean, it works as a store of value.
So where do you what do you do with it now that it's spiked?
What are you going to sell?
How do you do it?
This is the thing.
I mean, I'm not some big financial guy.
I have my money, you know, in SEP IRAs and retirement plans.
And I've been very, very, very good about that for my entire career.
I'm set for from the back half of my life, you know, but the Bitcoin,
I have no idea what to do with it.
And now that I'm crazily up, I've been up before.
And then it crashed in such a way that I was I had lost a ton of money.
That was like 2022.
I was like, oh, fuck, I just lost a ton of money here.
Oh, no. But it came back in this big way.
And I think I'm just going to sell it cash out.
You know, why why sit and wait and see what happens?
And everybody's like, well, now that Trump's in office,
it's going to keep going and going and going.
But what if Trump goes to jail?
You know, that's my issue with going to jail that nobody's going to jail.
Biden just got pardoned.
Nobody's going to that's true.
I mean, what are we talking about?
That's what I would say.
That all said, and let's let's, you know, before we get into a Bitcoin episode,
I just just sell it.
Who gives a shit yet?
You got your retirement money put away.
You made some cash, sell it, have some fun and then reinvest.
I think that's what I'm doing.
And if it crashes, then I buy in again in the hopes that it goes up.
And I think that's what a lot of people obviously are doing with this Bitcoin.
And I'm like, but isn't that isn't somebody going to catch on that people are
gaming the system and all my friends are like, what do you think Wall Street is?
Right.
Like that's the whole thing is people throwing in money, pulling it out, you
know, insider trading and blah, blah, blah.
I wish I were a little smarter about it, but I think it keeps me from getting my
heart involved.
It's why I wind up doing well with like fantasy football and shit is because if
you don't care, you wind up making smarter decisions.
Anyway, my point here was not to gloat.
It was just kind of like you guys always have great thoughts in the comments.
Like if you do know anything about Bitcoin and you think, oh God, please
don't sell Pat, you know, you could convince me.
I'd be open to your comments on this matter.
And it is nice to spare the women that you met one time on a date.
This discussion, but save it for the 10 year loyal listeners of this podcast.
I know these people like me.
Folks, let's I don't talk to women about Bitcoin.
I don't know.
I know that's what I was making the joke.
That was a joke.
He opened the door to my bedroom and go thoughts.
That's usually how I kick off a date.
I kick off a date with.
I have nothing.
What do you think of that?
Does that turn you on?
Does that get your juices flowing?
I'm not going to talk about Bitcoin.
I don't got nothing lady.
Yeah.
I look up.
She's gone.
I start talking into the napkin thing again.
I've been seeing some, but we talked about this a little online.
I don't know.
I always feel weird about this, but it's what we're supposed to be doing on the
show talking about shit in our lives and et cetera.
But I've been dating this girl.
I like quite a bit.
Fantastic.
Sex.
All right.
You know, let's get to the movie corner.
Have you been, what's going to happen here?
You're going to start talking.
You're going to go, can we cut this?
I'm not going to say cut this.
All right.
Go ahead.
Ask him.
Have you been with somebody who's big into the choke?
I've been with women that like that and I don't feel comfortable with it.
It makes me very uncomfortable.
Yeah.
I mean, um, what, what are we supposed to do?
It's like Pat, I'm telling you, not only do I like it, I like it hard.
I like, I'm telling you say harder.
I don't feel comfortable.
You're allowed to say that.
Well, and I have, and I've done it a little.
I've said that a little bit and you don't want to yuck.
Somebody's young, but the problem is you also just can't choke a young woman.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's true.
You know, and she, you know, I'm, I'm trying to gauge cause you're in this
stage where you're trying to get to know each other and we're really got this
good chemistry and we're having a lot of fun and everything sounds healthy.
I just don't want to be like the opening to strange darling.
Uh, but yeah, sure.
No, I mean, everything's, everything's great.
Whether we, whether we involve that or not, but here's, here's my concern,
Joe, is that two weeks from now, it's like, Hey, uh,
I actually need you to choke me until like my eyes roll back in my head or
else we're not going to be able to continue this thing.
Like I've had that too.
I had this woman who wanted me to choke her from behind while her
genitals were under bath water.
We got to get to the movie corner here.
I got, I got,
what are we talking about?
I'm saying, what do you do?
You say I'm not comfortable.
It's weird.
I don't know.
Like that's your thing.
Then you just pack it in, even if everything else is good.
So this lady was months ago.
If she says to you that's a deal.
Not rushing water on her genitals.
And I'm like, so every time we hook up,
we got to go to the bathroom and I got to do this?
I would say you got to, I'd say you got a deal breaker on your hands.
I don't know.
Look, I'm not judging.
It's a shame to do that to somebody.
Like, oh, that's, that's the thing you get off on,
but I guess you got to decide, am I willing to do that forever?
I'm not judging anybody's sexual preference.
Whatever you're into is what you're into,
but you got to find somebody who's also into it.
And if you're not into it, you're not into it.
And if they say, well, that's the only way it goes for me, buddy,
then you got to go, well, this was nice.
Take care.
You know, I've met a lot of seemingly perfect people in my life.
And there've been other things where you go, that's a deal breaker.
I can't, you're, you're married.
Yeah, that's true.
Or I just had one of those.
I just have one of those.
I know.
Well, speaking about weird sexual interests.
Norman Bates, I watched.
He fits.
He certainly fits.
Who I just watched all the psycho movies.
I'm not going to do the first one.
I'll do the second three or whatever.
And alarmingly, people, not anything in one of the psycho sequels equaled.
Choke me while hot water rushes all over my vagina.
Yeah.
Real life is often scarier than fiction.
I kid with you, Pat.
I hope you don't feel judged.
I'm just joking around with you.
Why would I feel judged?
Well, no, I don't know.
Because I know you don't think I'm being harsh.
I don't need hot water into my hole to come.
I mean, Christ.
Well, now that you put it that way, now I'm listening.
By the way, I did this for her twice.
And then you have to live with that with being responsible for turning hot rushing water on a woman's genitals.
I'm like, so what am I in?
Am I jigsaw now?
I'm trying to get laid here.
That's a perfect.
I did pedal into the bathroom with a tricycle also, which added to the spirals on your cheeks.
Yeah, exactly.
Which cheeks?
Oh, all right.
I watched.
I rewatched.
So I finally broke out this arrow video set.
Psycho.
Yeah, I got it.
Now, when we bought it from the sale overseas, I somehow mistakenly bought the Blu -ray and not the 4K, which was very disheartening.
I then said I'll return it and get my money back or get it replaced with the 4K.
When I tried to return it and get it replaced, the representatives from Arrow repeatedly said there is no Blu -ray version of this set.
There's only a 4K.
I don't know what was going on.
Yeah.
I never sent it back.
Cut to a year and a half, two years later, it's still on my shelf wrapped.
I'm like, OK, well, the only fix for this now is I have to buy a multi -region Blu -ray player so I can watch this.
And I thought that'll come in handy later anyway.
So I did.
I went to B &H and I got online and I got a region free all region Blu -ray player that also upscales.
And it does make the Blu -rays look pretty damn good.
So finally, I watched my Psychobox set.
And I will start with Psycho 2, which we've reviewed on the show.
And this, you know, it was certainly all of these were rewatches, but Psycho 2 is the one I was most familiar with.
That is the one on the set that they really get into with a lot of featureettes, a lot of making of stuff.
They really talk about the challenge of making a sequel to this classic 22 years after the original.
And, you know, in fact, there's the booklet that comes in the box set is like it's a beautiful box set, by the way.
It has posters and it has lobby cards.
It's an awesome box set.
But the booklet really delves into an analysis of Psycho 2 and the challenges.
And basically they said like, you know, what makes it work is it's a very it's it's directed by Tom.
No, Tom Holland wrote it. He didn't direct it.
But it's they said they basically you had to mimic Hitchcock style.
So so there was connective tissue there.
And and if they had gotten like people always say like Brian De Palma, could you imagine if he would have directed Psycho 2?
Because he was our Hitchcock.
And they say in this thing, no, that actually wouldn't work because De Palma would have put his own thing on it.
And this didn't need its own thing.
This needed to feel like the Hitchcock one to to a certain extent.
And in reading that and then rewatching Psycho 2, that was the first time I realized, oh, they're right.
It does kind of feel Hitchcocky.
The camera angles, the way things are shot, et cetera.
I still would love to see De Palma's take.
Yeah, of course. Right.
But anyway, Norman gets out top of the movie.
He is re reformed, fixed.
He starts receiving notes from his mother again.
He thinks somebody is messing with his head.
And it's kind of a whodunit. People start getting killed.
You're like, is Norman killing them? What's going on?
The big reveal at the end of the movie is he was being set up by the sister of Janet Lee's character in the first movie and her daughter because they wanted revenge for him being let out of the facility.
They were placing all the notes around. Why?
Because they wanted to make him snap and do something terrible so he would go back into captivity.
But they're not the ones killing people.
It turns out who's killing people is an old woman that works at the diner where Norman gets his work release job.
And at the end of the movie, she says, I'm your actual mother.
The woman that raised you was my sister.
And then Norman, for the first time in the movie, actually kills and he kills this old woman.
And the setup is, of course, now he's going to keep her corpse and go back to his old ways.
There's a magnificent shot at the end of this movie where after he kills her, he walks out of the house.
And it's like this hero shot and he's standing and there's clouds just barreling behind him and lightning.
It's this beautiful shot. It looks amazing and the music's playing and it's very much like Norman's back.
It's a very cool ending. Psycho 2 is a great watch, a very worthy watch.
And beyond impressive given the fact that it's the movie that it is a sequel to and that it scores as high as it does.
So I recommend Psycho 2.
Yeah, I like Psycho 2 quite a bit.
Famously, Tarantino thinks it is the best psycho film.
However, as I told Joe, I just listened to my first couple episodes of his podcast.
He does with Roger Avery, who he co -wrote Pulp Fiction with.
It's called Cinema Archives and they're watching The Love Bug.
Herbie and Herbie.
And Tarantino goes, all right, this is like the best car racing footage I've ever seen in cinema.
All right. This is actually the best car chase I've ever seen.
All right. Like it's it's nuts. He raves. They're raving about The Love Bug.
I've never seen The Love Bug. I'm going to watch it on Disney+.
But my guess is I'm not going to walk away saying this is the best racing footage I've ever seen.
The man is insane sometimes. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Anyway, I did see the Lindsay Lohan Herbie for some reason.
I don't remember why I watched it. Maybe babysitting or something.
By the way, I think it's a legacy sequel. I don't think that's like a remake.
Yeah. Yeah. You mentioned that. Yeah.
I watched Juror Number Two, which is a movie that got me real pissed off when I read about the story of this,
because Clint Eastwood has basically been at Warner Brothers for 50 years.
He has made them 50 movies. He has got them tons and tons of Oscars.
American Sniper is not a movie I enjoyed, but it swept the Oscars 10 years ago when Clint Eastwood was like 85.
OK. A long rich career.
You don't need you don't need me to tell you that Clint Eastwood had a good career,
but you may, if you're not a diehard movie obsessive, not know that all of his success for the most part happened at Warner Brothers.
Now, when he makes Juror Number Two at age 94, a good, well -written, well -acted little courtroom drama,
Warner Brothers dumps it on HBO Max after like a couple days in theaters.
I recommended it to my mom. My mom loves a courtroom drama.
She's like, it's not playing anywhere in Missouri. Just never got released there.
You're just talking about a time where there's no respect.
It's a business where with all its flaws, the entertainment business, there was always a respect for your elders, your legends.
And that's gone now, too. Clint Eastwood just gets treated like anybody else.
You know, like he made an animated Scooby Doo movie that they're going to take a tax cut on.
And I don't think it's good enough to get any Oscar attention, but I wish that it would.
You know, I wish this was the kind of case where like a label dumps a Yankee Hotel Foxtrot from Wilco because they don't hear a single.
And then the album winds up selling a billion copies. You know, that's I wish that would happen.
Unfortunately, it's not the case. The movie itself, I wanted to love it more than I did.
I love an underdog. You know, I was hoping this was going to be some lost masterpiece.
It's not. It's even a movie that's going to feel at home on HBO Max.
It just seems like a slap in the face to Eastwood.
But you see now with Costner and his Horizon movie, The Western, that if they don't see a dollar, they're just not going to release it.
They don't care what your relationship is.
This movie stars Nicholas Holt from The Menu and many other movies about a boy, Tony Collette, also from About a Boy,
the great J .K. Simmons, Chris Messina, Zoe Deutsch, Cedric Yarbrough from Reno 911,
Kiefer Sutherland, who I'm always excited to see as Nicholas Holt's AA sponsor.
But the plot of the movie is basically this. While serving as a juror in a high profile murder trial,
Holt finds himself struggling with a serious moral dilemma.
Did he commit the crime? Very juicy premise. He's a blackout drunk.
He starts to feel like, did I commit this crime?
So a great setup, a great cast, a great director and a solid little courtroom drama.
It's not as good as the last Friedkin movie that Kane Mutiny court martial, also with Kiefer Sutherland.
It's not as good as Anatomy of a Fall, but I like that the courtroom drama is coming back as a genre.
And it's an entertaining movie. Check it out. Good dad movie. Joe?
By the way, very ballsy move on Eastwood's part calling a juror number two.
Because critics can say number two is right.
All right, Psycho 3. Another very solid entry into the into the series.
I thought upon rewatch with Psycho 3, I was going to go out.
This is where it kind of goes off the rails. It's not.
It takes it picks up right where Psycho 2 leaves off.
Norman is back in the hotel. He's running things.
He's got the dead mom upstairs and and he's back to his old tricks.
It's that simple. Most of the cast from the first one come back and now all believe.
And this is the this is the twist now of part two is where everybody in part one doesn't know what Norman's up to.
And then everybody in part two is skeptical about what he might be up to because of his just being released in part three.
They believe now he's redeemed himself because they caught the people that were setting him up in the first one.
And now they give him a pass and turn a blind eye to what he's up to because they think he's reformed.
Super fun movie. Some very fun performances.
Certainly this one gets a little more, you know, grind housey horror sequel ish 1980s, whatever you want to call it.
Than the than the second movie does.
But great performances by Jeff Fahey, Diana Scarwood and my favorite character is Hugh Gillan is the once again is the sheriff.
I really like Psycho 3 quite a bit.
Little little bloodier than the first and the part two.
But very solid, very, very solid movie.
I recommend it.
Yeah, I've actually never seen four and it's been ages since I've seen three.
I only made it halfway through that set, so I need to do so.
I saw Martha.
The Netflix original documentary about Martha Stewart.
Did I give a shit about Martha Stewart?
No.
Do I give a shit about her now, having seen the film again?
But I didn't hate it.
Netflix has become this weird home for like the most generic least probing documentaries.
And I keep watching them and hoping that they'll they'll dig a little deeper or give us more of like a warts and all look.
And they're all kind of the same.
I like the Arnold one quite a bit.
The sly one was a huge letdown.
I didn't see the the soccer one because I don't give a shit about soccer, but I've heard it's great.
I forget what that guy's name even is Beckham Beckham yet.
But Martha, you know, I had to make sure it wasn't one of these six hour.
I wouldn't I couldn't have stood for six hours of Martha's life, but it's under two.
And it basically just touches on the basic points of her life.
And the whole time you're like, there's so much behind the eyes of this woman.
There's so much pain.
She is notoriously a monster to staff, difficult to be around, which goes very much at odds with her real life persona.
And when they ask her about things like that, she's very icy and cold.
Well, let's move on, please, to the next subject.
Thank you.
And you're like, OK, well, that's classic Martha.
But by the end, you realize you've learned nothing about a person.
And when you watch a documentary, you're supposed to learn everything about a person.
And if you have a subject who's not willing to open up to you, who's not willing to tell you anything about herself,
I would argue you don't really have a documentary because they don't have people who are close to her.
That they can find out about her because she doesn't let people in.
She doesn't have people who are close to her.
They talk about the friendship she forms late in life with Snoop Dogg.
But you're like, yeah, but come on, that's a business relationship.
I'm sure they like and respect each other very much.
And it's genuine.
However, it's not real.
And that's what I was left with and what winds up being kind of the only worthwhile thing about the documentary.
To me, is that it's a portrait of an unknowable person.
And I found that sort of interesting.
She is clearly suffering, in my opinion.
You know, you can maybe you can tell when you yourself have spent a lot of time in life suffering.
But like, there's something in her eyes, man.
She's not happy.
And the whole movie, I just found myself wanting to know more.
And that's a weird experience when you're watching a documentary because that's why you're there is to know more about a person.
But you don't get it.
Martha herself is sort of interesting when they ask her about her marital affairs.
She has this very, very businesswoman way of talking around her responsibility in each of the affairs.
That's kind of fascinating.
You get to see where the way her mind justifies her mistakes, her errors.
You learn, of course, about her cooking the books.
You also learn that that wasn't that big a deal.
You know, in my opinion, she's not that big of a crook, really.
I don't know.
It's an average documentary about a person who I think they should have chipped away at more before they released this thing.
Joe.
All right.
Last but not least in the psycho films, Psycho 4, the beginning, which serves as a sequel and a prequel to the franchise.
This one was made for TV, but was made for cable.
So it's still rated R.
Showtime.
I think Showtime.
Yeah, I think it was when Showtime was kind of coming into its own.
This one picks up a little after the third one leaves.
So the third one ends with him getting caught killing.
They lock him up.
The only real hiccup here in the series is at the end of the third one, the sheriff says, Norman, they're never going to let you out like you.
You did this again.
Like, that's it.
And you're like, yeah, that's seems to be the case.
But then this one, he's out and he's living in the suburbs and he's married.
And why is he out?
He says, you know, good behavior.
They paroled him or whatever.
That's the only part where I'm like, come on, guys.
But but whatever.
You got to get him out.
I guess to have the movie work.
But anyway, good supporting cast in this one.
CCH Pounder in particular and Warren Frost, who plays George's fiance's dad on Seinfeld, speaking of which this is the lowest rated as far as reviews go.
But I don't agree with the reviews.
I think this is another very solid installment.
It's fun watching the flashbacks where Henry Thomas plays a young Norman Bates, Olivia Hussey plays his mom.
It's fun, not fun, but it's interesting seeing their relationship, how it's inappropriate and it's mildly sexual and it's very uncomfortable.
And they do a good job with all that.
It's interesting seeing how he actually did kill his mother and why it's interesting seeing his first kill after that and why and where his sexually driven murders stem from.
And in the end, Norman returns to the house in the third act, almost triumphantly to with a plan to murder his current wife, who has become pregnant because he's like, this can't this this this has to stop with me.
This this child will be sick like me.
And he sees a bunch of flashbacks in the house and he's going to kill his new wife, who's there to try to stop him.
And he's chasing her around and you think he's going to kill her.
And then in the final moments, she convinces Norman, Norman, you have good in you.
You're a good person.
You're better.
This isn't who you are anymore.
And he succumbs to her, to her nurture.
And that's it.
Norman Bates is redeemed at the end of the psycho franchise.
And it's happily ever after.
It's not the ending you're expecting, but in a weird way, you're happy because if you watch commentaries about the first psycho movie, they say one of the most interesting things is that you are weirdly rooting for Norman Bates to get away with it.
When you're watching him sink the car into the bog and it stops sinking for a minute, you're nervous for him.
Yeah.
So I think all along, knowing the kid was he was an abused kid and this and that, whatever, somewhere in the back of our heads, we all hope that Norman kind of does the right thing finally.
And then in the fourth movie, he does.
I, it was directed by Mick Garris, who I'm a fan of and written by who wrote this.
There is a sort of like Kirkland, Toby Hooper.
Yeah.
Well, I mean, I think Toby Hooper is kind of Kirkland.
Toby.
I mean, I like Toby.
I'm a fan of Toby Hooper.
Poltergeist, baby.
You can't, can't fuck with that.
Well, I would say Texas Chainsaw, but.
Fair.
Yeah.
Poltergeist in Texas.
Look, Toby's got some, some classics.
I'm not knocking Toby, you know, life force.
Where the hell.
And I don't think Mick Garris has a classic.
I think he's got a lot of.
Mick is, yeah, Mick is.
Mick is great.
Mick is the guy.
If, if, if he is like the go -to guy for you want to make a really good TV made for TV
horror movie.
Yeah, I agree.
Joseph Stefano wrote this, who also wrote the original Psycho.
Yes.
Also, Bernard Herman's score is brought back in this and parts of it are brought back in
the other movies, but they use it fully in this.
Look, I'm going to say this without exaggeration.
I think the psycho franchise could be the most consistent horror franchise.
In horror franchise history.
There's not a dud in the bunch.
There are ones that you will like better than others, but there's not a bad one in the bunch.
They made four.
They're out the fucking door.
That's it.
Like, and that's it.
Anything they do after that, the Vince Vaughn one, or if they reboot it, that's completely
unrelated.
If you're talking about the core movies that star and are involved in relating to the original
players, I would be hard pressed to think, and you know my favorite franchise is Creep
Show, but Creep Show part three is called Tales from the Dark Side.
There's some technical things where you could say, well, it's not really, and you know,
psycho front to back, four movies, all of them enjoyable.
I would say it's diminishing returns, but not in a way that you're disappointed by the
last one.
I think it's a very strong franchise and an excellent four pack of movies.
Yeah, I need to watch four, but it is kind of hard to argue.
I think if anybody were to argue it, you'd be like, look closer at Friday the 13th franchise.
Look closer at Halloween the franchise.
You still think these are great franchises?
No.
Well, that's the thing.
If Halloween four was the last Halloween, yeah, you go.
Nice work, guys.
Yeah.
It's when they go to five, six, you know, it's like, you know, but I don't think we're
done with psycho.
I think they'll zoom that shortly.
Don't get me wrong.
But yeah, you're right.
This is a good, a great franchise and I'm happy I own the box.
My last one is La La Land.
I saw it at like a pre -release screening and I thought, what a sweet, beautiful little
movie.
Then everyone hated it.
Then there was a huge backlash.
Then they had the moonlight thing happen and it's become this oddly controversial movie.
Excuse me.
And I just wanted to revisit it, you know, five years on, see what I thought about it.
And I like it very much.
It works because of Gosling and Emma Stone.
Gosling is such a fascinating thing because in this, when he's in like an 80s cover band,
you know, covering Take On Me, and he runs into Emma Stone at this party and he's embarrassed,
that moment would never work with any other heartthrob.
That moment doesn't work with a Glenn Paul or a Zac Efron or whoever, because a woman
seeing him dressed like aha at a party, he still is the best looking man alive.
You don't feel that embarrassment.
You don't feel like, you know what I mean?
Sure.
Osling has a way of selling the embarrassment.
Like you feel bad for somebody who looks that great because of the way he sells being embarrassed.
He's a guy who is believably awkward and uncomfortable in social situations in a way these other
heartthrobs cannot do convincingly.
And he's something else, man.
I think, I mean, he's the best movie star we have right now by a huge margin.
I love Emma Stone as well.
I think she's really good in this.
The story is really good.
Where it doesn't work, unfortunately, for a musical is the musical numbers.
I just watched it this weekend and outside of City of Stars, which is the most boring
song ever written for a film, I think, and the biggest song from the movie.
The other songs are immediately forgettable.
They have no hooks.
They don't stick with you.
The lyrics aren't great.
And to make matters worse, Gosling and Stone can't sing.
So they don't put amazing singers in other roles in the movie because they would upstage the stars.
So nobody is singing very well in the movie.
And the songs aren't very good.
For a musical, that's a problem.
But it's funny.
It's charming.
It's very sad in the end.
It's got kind of a 500 days of summer feel in regards to relationships.
There's a real heaviness and a sadness to their love story that really works.
And I think in terms of how it's shot color wise, some of the choreography, the opening scene in the big L .A.
That's the good one.
And that's the problem is that everything else kind of pales in comparison.
So, yeah, not not one of the all time greats, but I do think it looks really beautiful in 4K.
I love the performances and it's a good movie, just not a great musical show.
All right.
Well, that brings us to it brings us to our movie of the day.
Nutcrackers directed by David Gordon Green, who at this point has had one of the strangest careers in movie history.
I mean, it's sort of admirable that he's done every genre, but he's basically coming back to do Nutcrackers as sort of a retreat,
an escape from the disastrous foray into the Exorcist franchise,
Exorcist Believer, which pretty much killed that franchise dead in its tracks.
He also did Halloween, which, of course, I see as a huge failure.
That trilogy, I know Joe largely sees it as a failure as well.
But Hollywood doesn't because it made a ton of money.
So David Gordon Green is like one of our biggest directors, despite, as I was saying to Joe the other day,
getting steadily worse as a director over the last 20 years, steadily a lot worse, I would say.
If you look at his filmography, and I'll do it real quick for you.
George Washington is an amazing debut.
Put him on the map, followed by all the real girls, which is where I first saw Danny McBride
and is such a beautiful, sweet, tiny little love story with Zooey Deschanel.
It's an excellent movie that not enough people have seen.
Undertow's great.
Snow Angels with Sam Rockwell, I remember thinking was one of the best movies of that year.
I fucking loved it.
Then he pivots to Pineapple Express, just one of the most fun action comedies ever made.
Your Highness, a bad stoner comedy, The Sitter, a funny adventures and babysitting style comedy.
Then he's doing these movies like Joe with Nicolas Cage, Manglehorn with Puccino,
Stronger with Gyllenhaal, these big star vehicles, Oscar vehicles that don't get Oscars,
then the Halloweens, then The Exorcist, and now Uncle Buck with the Nutcrackers.
It's a really weird career.
And The Sitter has a lot in common with Nutcrackers, oddly enough.
It's like he's going back to previous genres.
The Sitter sucked.
I like The Sitter a lot more than Nutcrackers, Joe.
I actually, wait, I'm thinking of, is that the one with, no, I'm thinking of the one with Barbara Streisand and Jonah Hill.
No, wait, no, Jonah Hill, The Sitter, yeah.
I don't fucking know.
Guilt Trip is Rogan and Streisand.
No, I'm thinking of Jonah, I don't know, I'm thinking of the wrong, it doesn't matter.
My point is, this is, first of all, as I said to Pat, you know, you're off to a bad start when you go,
I remember when Renee Zellweger made this movie.
I mean, it's like right off the bat, it's the big city rich guy getting pulled into the country
against his better judgment and against his will, and he doesn't want to be there, but he has to be there.
Why? Because family's there, and he's, let me guess,
I have a feeling he might slowly fall in love with his family.
I think that might be where this is going.
This fucking premise, the only premise that's been done more than this is alcoholic coach's underdog sports team.
That is the only premise that's been done more than this, but whatever, that's okay.
These movies have the same plot, whether it's sports or Nutcrackers or Uncle Buck or whatever.
It's they learn from each other that, you know, he needed to loosen up a little bit,
or in the case of Uncle Buck, he needed to straighten up a little bit, and the kids need, you know,
everybody learns to be a better person from the other, and fine.
And in Uncle Buck, at least, Uncle Buck is flawed. He's a fuckup.
Yeah. And you feel sorry for him. Why?
Because you start to realize the family doesn't want him around.
Yes. And that's so much more -
A quick pause for that. Just one human moment in Uncle Buck, one single moment in Uncle Buck
that when I was nine years old, this moment 20 minutes into the movie made me start crying.
Not the ending of the movie, which is very emotional.
20 minutes in, when Buck goes into his brother's house, he's looking through their photographs,
and he sees that they have folded him out of a wedding photo where he was the best man.
That is, that's John Hughes' genius. He has a million moments like that in his movies,
but talk about Show Don't Tell, talk about a moment that even hits a nine -year -old boy
going to see that in the theater, like, oh my God, I get that, I feel that, I understand that.
Just nails it perfectly. And this movie, there's a single second that feels like that.
There's a million moments in this where you think they're going to go down that road,
why were they estranged, what did Ben Stiller do?
You think that there's going to be a big reveal that Ben Stiller isn't the big city,
big shot that he's portraying himself to be, that it's all bullshit.
You're waiting for a million of these reveals, none of them happen, everything is face value,
it's exactly what it appears to be as soon as you see it.
Even the reason they're estranged, he and his dead, the sister and father die of these kids,
his sister, who's the mother of these kids, and her husband die in a car accident,
which is why he has to go back and take care of them.
Even the reason he's estranged from his sister has zero depth.
The husband asked for a loan, and he gave the husband a loan,
and the sister gets mad at him for giving the husband a loan. It's idiotic.
It's when you ask somebody in a job interview, what's your biggest weakness?
Well, I guess that I care too much or whatever.
We need our characters. The reason can be PG, gang.
It doesn't have to be he ran her over or he fucked her husband or anything scandalous or salacious,
but it has to be something bigger than that.
And it can't be Ben Stiller did something that was very generous and great,
and that's why the relationship ended.
Talk about not having a fucking conflict or a pulse to your movie.
We can handle it if two characters have a genuine reason to not get along.
We're not going to despise them.
Everyone on earth has problems with everyone else in their life, big and small.
You can't say husband asked for a loan, he gave him the loan, and that's why we're estranged. It sucks.
It's it does suck.
As I said before, at the beginning, these the four kids in this are our brothers in real life.
And the house that the movie is shot in is their house that they live in.
I'm not really quite sure why they went this route.
The kids are good. They're good.
Like they're for kids that have never really been on screen like they do a good job.
But it is also very obvious that an extraordinarily large portion of this movie is it's clearly just improv.
Yeah. And they're cobbling together scenes from extended improv sessions.
You know, OK, I don't really get why that furthers any of this.
But I also think there's no but there's no set up punch line joke.
You know, you keep waiting for that, but it's also they're not getting into these funny and exciting riffs that used to come with an appetite or, you know, even like a wolf of Wall Street or something like the improv feels like tired.
Well, that's that's what I was getting at is is because these kids don't have experience.
Yeah, I think they were unable to give them heavy lifting.
So then you just rely on just the improv at that point.
And you're just like, OK, that was pretty funny.
We edit it like this and you end up with a lot of that.
There aren't really a ton of emotional turns from the kids.
There's enough there that you kind of care.
Ben Stiller.
None.
By the way, this is a movie riddled with with gigantic asks for the audience to just go along.
Let's start with the fact that when he shows up, Linda Cardellini, Lamborghini, by the way, Porsche, yellow Porsche.
Yeah, which is idiotic.
It's like, why does he have a yellow port?
I think that's what Gordon Bombay drove in The Mighty Ducks, if I remember correctly.
So he shows up at the beginning and Linda Cardellini, who's the who's the child services rep
working with the family to try to get the kids fostered, goes, yes, sorry, the last foster family fell through.
So you're going to have to now stay here indefinitely until I find another family for these kids.
And it's like this was a this is a phone call you would make.
You can't just make a person do that.
You can't do that. And he's just what do you mean?
I can't leave. And she's like, sorry.
You know, like, what what do we what is this?
This makes no sense.
I completely fucking agree because I didn't even mind that it was formulaic because these formulas work.
A lot of my favorite movies fit this formula, but they don't even get the basics right.
They exactly what you're saying.
The whole the whole setup, which should be the easiest part of them.
It was the easy like the Mick, the Caitlin Olsen show that my buddies did really funny show on Fox.
You just get the premise, but you have to land that premise.
Otherwise, you're doing the Seinfeld thing of a judge sentencing somebody to be his butler.
You know, like in this movie, it just doesn't feel real.
It feels like, OK, well, we'll just rush this moment and get to him with the kids.
But you're like, no land one thing.
So we're buying into this world a little bit.
They don't. It's terrible.
It's really is Toby Huss hitting on him.
What was that bit? No, that's OK.
Let's get into the because I was confused by the comedy in that bit.
Let's get into the Toby Huss.
I love Toby Huss so much. I love that's why I was excited when I saw him.
Yeah. And let's get into the bit of Toby or just the place of Toby Huss in this movie.
Yeah. Toby Huss plays.
You ready for this, folks?
That guy that owns most of the town, the old rich man.
I mean, guys, it's we're not it's not it's a wonderful life.
This is fucking idiotic. Anyway, the kids say, boy, we'd love to be adopted by him.
So then Ben Stiller, by the way, folks, there's your goddamn original movie.
That's make that the whole movie.
Yeah, he's got to try to fucking get the rich guy to adopt the kids instead.
Well, then he's got Eddie Patterson is this kind of weird, like, you know, prospective.
It's like, yeah, that's a more interesting thing.
And these are funny actors go that route.
So they reduced this Toby Huss storyline to two scenes.
And Ben Stiller is like, I'm going to try to get him to adopt the kids.
And then he charms the guy.
And then the guy invites him to a Christmas party.
And then they go to the Christmas party, his house.
And then the kids do something terrible, which, you know, they're going to do.
And then they get thrown out of the Christmas party.
And that's the end of it.
But they actually want you to believe that Toby Huss, without even thinking about it,
is just going to adopt these kids.
He says to them like, like, like basically in the supermarket almost.
Toby Huss is like, yeah, I guess we could maybe do that.
Like, what? It's Joe.
But help me out. Throw me a lifeline here.
Why did that scene reek of sexuality?
Toby Huss is clearly flirting with Ben Stiller.
I don't know, Pat, because they, I don't know, because the whole movie.
Okay, he's a closeted gay guy. Okay, got it.
But no, I didn't even, I couldn't get the basics of the bit.
And I write comedy.
I don't know.
I think this whole movie.
And look, I think this happens.
I'm a fan of the McBride camp and what they do for the most part.
I don't, you know, every look, I just technically worked with them on tires.
Like I'm but I'm being fair.
Like I'm not going to sit here and say I love everything they've ever done.
I'm a fan, though, of the camp.
Yes, I am a fan of a lot of what Apatow did over the years.
I'm a fan of a lot of what Rogan did over the, but these camps, not all of them.
But I think a thing starts to happen where they start to think it'll be fine.
We've improved before.
We'll make it work.
We'll overshoot.
There will be a movie in there somewhere.
It's kind of like the story of Black Sheep where they talk about David Spade
talks about how they went into Black Sheep underprepared and without a script
basically like they did with Tommy Boy.
But they landed the plane with Tommy Boy, so they thought they could land it again
with Black Sheep and instead it was a fucking disaster.
Right. So I'm not saying this is a disaster, but it's like I think these guys
start to wrestle in their laurels a little bit and start to think, well, we've done
this before. We could do it again.
And it's like, no, guys, you need a rock solid script and you can't.
And if you're going to do a movie where you're going to have four brothers who live
in their house and we're going to shoot in their real house and they've never
really acted, but we're going for that, then you got to make that kind of movie.
Shoot this thing like a goddamn documentary, like make it loose and whatever.
But instead they have an incredibly scripted, incredibly structured thing that's
that's so by rote, it's insane.
And then they inject this frantic kinetic new thing into it.
And you can't do that.
It doesn't work.
Yeah. And it's shot like Friday Night Lights.
It's shot very like artsy, you know, almost like his earlier work, like in all the real
girls, it's shot in this very we're making an artful indie kind of way.
But the content, at least for the first half of the movie, is very like, you know,
slapstick comedy kind of vibes.
But it doesn't do any of that.
Well, I didn't feel the drama.
I didn't laugh.
I didn't think the look suited the tone.
And why Stiller chose to return to acting after like 10 years, 10 years off for
this, I can't wrap my head around it unless it's to work with David Gordon Green,
who, as I said, I think is becoming worse with each passing year.
I think I think Stiller did this for the reason we've talked a lot about what a
lot of guys are doing at this point.
I think he thought it's charming.
It's fun.
It'll put me back in that sort of familiar Stiller zone of family comedy.
Yeah.
It's a thing my kids can enjoy.
It's a thing my grandkids can enjoy.
And also, it's easy.
This isn't going to take much.
You know, I show up, I do my thing, I leave.
Like, it's not, you know, the undertaking of the secret life of Walter Mitty or
something like that.
So it unfortunately just doesn't work.
The ending is, you know, I'm a disaster emotionally these days.
So I still cried at the end when he stays with the family.
But that's really not saying much.
I'll cry at a fucking Amazon commercial at this point.
But the movie just doesn't work.
And here's the weird part.
I did laugh.
Like, I did laugh at some of the stuff he said and his reactions.
And I did laugh at some of the stuff the kids said.
But it's just not a good movie.
Man, it's not a good movie.
You know, oh, yeah, yeah.
It's not that that generation.
You know, Joe and I were talking about maybe doing this Dear Santa slash Satan fairly
Jack Black movie.
But yeah, our our comedy heroes are struggling.
Vince Vaughn's probably having the easiest time of it right now.
After a 10 year in the desert struggle.
But Stiller, you know, his directing career is his bread and butter now.
And he's an exceptional director.
So kudos.
I still love the guy.
I just didn't see any of that old Stiller charm on display here.
I hope the kids get something out of it.
I hope they do well.
I hope they go on.
They're talented kids.
Yeah.
They'll be in a movie with the guy who said, I'm the captain now and Captain Phillips.
They'll all do a movie together.
We'll never see him again, Joe.
These kids are dead now.
It's Hollywood.
They're not developing, you know, a lot of projects for four brothers who live in a house.
Unfortunately.
Fair enough.
We'll be back with what we're kicking around a lot of ideas.
But we talked about Dear Santa, possibly.
We talked about Red One, possibly.
We talked about Terrifier 3, possibly.
The point is, is will we be back with some sort of Christmas movie in the next in Episode 3?
Yeah.
Right.
And then Episode 4 could be another Christmas movie, but also might be When Harry Met Sally for New Year's Eve.
I'm about to do the Steve Weber Shining.
Is that something you'd be interested in?
Or am I going to take that to the solo corner?
I would.
I would do it.
I just I don't think we should do it this month.
I think let's push it for January.
But yeah, I would.
I've I own it.
I've seen it.
And yeah, I could I would do that.
I think it's worth discussing.
I'm not going to make you see Wicked.
Don't worry about it.
I'll see the Wicked.
So listen, folks, we got we got a lot in the pipeline and our pipeline is running under hot water.
And we're going to gas it all out for you as you choke it as you choke us.
I don't know.
Oh, geez.
Tie it back around.
Folks, happy holidays.
We'll see you next time.
And we'll see you in hell.