I'll see you in hell.
Welcome to We'll see you in hell.
It's the podcast you turn to when you want that movie talk, that movie news.
That movie juice, my name is Joe DeRosa, my name is Patrick Walsh.
How's everybody doing today?
Oh, you can't answer.
All right.
Joe, how are you?
What's new?
I had a hell of a new year, okay, New Year's Eve, and then I lost my voice for two days.
And then it came back when I woke up this morning, it still doesn't sound right, but it's
good.
What better than it was, so basically, we had a big bash at the bar, New Year's Eve, had
a DJ on the inside playing punk rock and hardcore, hardcore, hardcore, is that what you want
on a New Year's Eve?
People liked it.
I would have walked right out.
Very New York was very fun.
I would have said, Joe, I love you, I'm going to head out.
New wave.
Oh, well, sure.
You know, that kind of stuff.
New wave.
Great.
Hardcore, you don't need that.
What Fugazi?
Yeah.
It was a little Fugazi.
It was awesome when Fugazi came around.
I'll give you a waiting room.
Anyway.
For a party.
But that's about it.
You know, Walsh, it wasn't your party, so I don't really give a shit, but I have to get
shit for throwing on Tusk back in the day.
More party friendly than hardcore.
Tusk.
I, I, I, opium, dend, record, but then outside in our outdoor structure, we were streaming
the fish concerts.
It was like a hippies meets punk's thing.
It was very cool.
So as far as sounds like my nightmare, all of a sudden, oh, Jesus Christ, a fish concert?
The hippies outside liked it.
All right.
Do you like fish?
No.
I hate fish.
But I was inside with all the awesome punk and new wave and hardcore playing.
Okay.
All right.
Yeah.
What do you got?
A patio?
A little outdoor thing we're building.
I'm closed.
You get those many lights, people like that.
Uh -huh.
Yeah.
So anyway, it was fun.
As far as I know.
Are you in the red yet?
Are you in the black?
What's the good one?
The black's the good one.
I think we're okay for the moment.
All right.
But it was a great time.
And I don't think I got COVID.
And I got to be honest.
Watch at this point.
I don't give a shit if I did again.
No, I mean, even the president is like, hey, you're going to get it.
You know, that's where we're at.
Yeah.
He said that.
He waited my side for two years and then it's like, oh, hey, here's another one.
And we're just going to get it.
So forget what I said for two years.
Biden announced that.
And then and then jumped up like the guy and dances with wolves and screamed.
I just pissed my pants.
And there's nothing you can do about.
Is that?
Oh, what is that?
The fact that Colonel and dance with wolves does that?
Yeah.
There's like that wild.
That's the only thing I remember.
And then the actor's name is Mori Chacon.
Oh, my fan of.
He's going to be in everything.
But yeah, he stands up and he's like, I pissed myself.
Yeah, I remember that.
Yeah, he's going good luck on your trip.
And so I have the dollar show.
A three plus hour movie for one dollar was an intermission.
I mean, what a dream.
I've never seen the whole thing.
It seems like a real slog of a film.
I don't know if it would hold up.
I mean, it's big claim to fame.
Is it one best picture over good fellows,
which is just laughable and cost ner one best director.
Of course, Daisy for dances with wolves.
But I remember it being entertaining.
It's definitely what you would call a white savior movie today.
But they all were time to kill white savior glory white savior.
You know, they they all had that.
Was broader the white savior and glory or see the bad guy I forget?
Yeah.
No, broader was it was a savior.
I think L was was a bit more of a prick.
I don't know.
I broader was a hero in that.
Right.
I don't remember.
Man, I saw that when I was a kid.
Me and my mom rented it.
Yeah.
It's a little corneer today than when you're a kid.
But you know, we're just more cynical also.
I watch anything.
I watch another kid.
And I'm like, how did you like this?
You fucking pussy.
You know, it's just.
I've just become darker.
I was listening to Jessica Simpson's audio book.
I'm not drinking in 2022.
I'm going to go ahead and announce that up top.
Oh, yeah.
We've heard this song in dance before.
You've got the same reaction as my wife, but.
I am.
I'm going to surprise you all.
Those are going to do this.
Your text to me last night that we should all just be drinking around the clock.
We should be.
We're not going to be.
We're going to do weed.
We're going to see as it pops up.
You're definitely scaling it back, but the drinking is off.
So that's just what I'm doing anyway.
And I'll be honest.
If I break it, but I'm going for 2022.
My birthday is Wednesday.
I would say 41 years old.
Years young.
I said happy birthday.
But I would say it real quick before we move to your birthday.
It's a scale back the goal as my therapist once told me.
Let's just get through the month of January 1st.
See where we're at.
Everybody's doing a drag anywhere.
I'm better than that.
You know, you don't want to give yourself such a lofty goal.
You want to do it.
It's one day at a time as they say in the meetings.
Remember when you told me that Pete Pete Holmes had convinced you to quit drinking and you were done.
And then I think by the end of the week we were at the roast.
I've done.
I'm going to quit with you where we've been out and just said fuck it together.
I mean, it's just.
But listen, I support you.
And I hope I'm just telling you.
It's like saying I'm done with carbs.
You can't do that.
You got to just go.
Let me just try to get through that week.
No carbs.
Well, that's what that's where we'd comes in as a safety net.
If I'm feeling like I'm going to kill somebody, but so unfair planning on not drinking.
What was I talking about?
We were with dances with wolves or you're turning 41 on Wednesday, turning 41, turning Japanese.
I really think so this time.
But I was.
I know what I was talking about.
I'm listening to Jessica Simpson's audio book.
The last book I finished was Mariah Carey's audio book.
I have no interest in either artist.
I just enjoy listening to creative people read their own biography.
I don't know why.
But now I'm at the I'm at people I don't care about.
I listen to Sally Fields.
I listen to Demi Moore's.
I don't care about Sally Fields.
Never liked her.
Found her boring.
I just she's got no no grit to me.
She is a little white bread.
I also thought like you know like smokey would have probably fucked her for a week and then been like all right out of the car.
You know.
Sure.
Out of the car.
But anyway.
J Simpson.
I'm early on in the audio book.
She's kind of funny actually.
But she hits me with this story.
Gillen Joy.
She was trying to be in the.
The new new mouse cateers with Gosling and spears and Aguilera and you know all them Timberlake back in the day.
She was auditioning.
And they said, you know, your singing is great.
We need to work on your acting skills.
So she had to go to an acting camp.
And the guest speaker.
For for this camp, the like coach celebrity coach was Chuck Norris.
Teaching children to act.
And she says he walks in day one.
And he goes everybody.
Who was the most powerful actor in Hollywood today?
This was like 1994.
And they're all like, I don't know who is it.
He goes, it's Denzel Washington.
And they're like, okay.
You know why?
Because he doesn't move his eyebrows when he talks.
This is the opening speech of acting class.
So far, I mean, it's great advice.
He goes, all the power is contained in his face.
He doesn't have to move his eyebrows all over the place.
So she said she went to four of the classes before quitting.
But in each class, it would start with Chuck Norris taping the children's eyebrows down and making them perform emotional monologues.
And then finally, she told her mom what was going on.
And she was like, we're going to get you out of this class.
But then you, even if you look at the Chuck Norris gifts or gifs online, let alone his film work.
And I've never seen a Chuck Norris film.
I don't think the man doesn't move his eyebrows.
He practices what he preaches.
He straight himself.
I can respect that.
So next time you watch a film with his watch for that.
Has he ever made a good movie?
I've never even seen missing an action.
Missing an action was, you know, was was what it was for the time.
It was good enough.
I guess I remember critics at the time saying that the script was missing an action.
Oh, boy.
You know, yeah.
He made a movie that that sucks.
With Louis Gossett Jr.
When I was a kid, I was all excited about it.
Iron Eagle.
No, no, no, no.
Iron Eagle is Louis Gossett, but not Chuck.
Is he the star?
Iron Eagle, yeah.
But they made a movie together called like, oh, Fire Walker.
That's what it was called.
It was like, there was like an Indiana Jones kind of thing.
Yes.
I used to mix that up with Fire Starter.
So I never saw it.
I did see Fire Starter, which isn't good.
No, both suck.
At least I think the Barrymore could blame the drugs.
What's Norris' excuse?
Maybe when I was a kid, I watched side kicks.
Was that where he was kind of a karate kid with him and Jonathan Brandis?
I believe so.
And maybe when I was a kid, I watched a late sad Chuck Norris project called Top Dog.
Does that ring a bell?
A dog?
It was his entry into the K9 and Turner and Hooch world.
Let me quickly read the synopsis of Top Dog while we're here.
But also, there's a sequel to K9 starring Balushi and the dog again called K911.
Yeah, I know.
We've texted about it.
It came out in the aftermath of September 11th.
Top Dog Chuck Norris 1995.
It's a buddy comp action comedy directed by Aaron Norris, the younger brother of Chuck.
Wow, Jesus.
Wow.
It was his last film to release theatrically written by Aaron Norris.
In the film, Norris' character named Jake Wilder is partnered with a police dog named Reno,
whose handler was killed.
Together, Jake and Reno investigate a plot by domestic terrorists to attack a conference on unity.
Jake and Reno survived assassination attempts and several hand -to -hand fights with the terrorists
and eventually discover enough clues to foil the attack.
The film received largely negative reviews and its box office was negatively impacted by the timing of its release just days after the Oklahoma City bombing.
That's the excuse they're using.
Is this a comedy, by the way?
I assume.
Comedy.
Yeah.
Maverick Cop, he's referred to us.
I mean, here's a guy going to the bat.
Yeah.
Going to the mat, rather, for his brother.
This is his brother's.
Imagine this.
This is his brother's dream is to get this top dog movie made.
He wrote it, he directed it.
Yeah.
I mean, the guy and the guy does it for him.
I mean, we think entertainment sucks now.
We just weren't old enough to realize it always.
I mean, imagine you were living in your 40 years older than 95 and all of a sudden you're hit with a string of theatrical movies about guys
butting up with dogs like you just what is this business become?
My God.
It's just never been good.
But they were always kind of shuffled off to the side.
You know, they weren't there were at least good movies coming out.
Maybe we were just dumb.
You know, that's a huge was huge.
I loved turner and huge, but I was nine.
I was laughing right off the bat.
It opened as with every movie that came out in 1989 with our hero in a pair of blue briefs.
Flossing.
Every movie the hero wakes up.
If it's a R rated movie, he's hung over.
If not, he just bounces out of bed and is underwear and he flosses he brushes his teeth.
And some are mentally cracks an egg on the on the dashboard hilarious bits.
Sometimes you get funny bits.
But oftentimes the opening credits would just appear over our hero getting ready for work with no jokes.
It was a simple time.
You know what?
It's not though because I just saw a preview for a movie called dog.
Starting Channing Tatum and a dog.
And who's left that Channing Tatum himself.
I saw.
I saw the.
And for that it looks.
It looks terrible.
And then Benedict Cumberbatch.
Power of the dog.
So simultaneously released.
With a movie where he plays the guy that painted cats for the first time.
I mean, this guy is just somebody put him in a corner for a minute.
Jesus Christ.
You painted cats.
That's the plot.
He's in like this whimsical comedy like you ever see like the man who invented Christmas.
The movie about Dickens writing a Christmas Carol.
No.
It's a charming movie.
But it's like nothing more fun than a movie about somebody writing something.
The most character usually spectacular thing you can watch.
But I mean, it's like one of those kinds of movies.
It's like this whimsical period piece.
Yeah.
About this guy that became famous.
He's a real artist because he painted cats.
And everybody was like at the time.
People like cats are disgusting.
They're vermin.
Like nobody wants to look at cats.
They're street creatures.
And he apparently helped like make cats popular.
But I mean, I would have sworn you're making this up.
And then when I looked it up, my heart sunk even further when I realized that the name of it is the electrical life of Lewis Wayne.
I mean, what are we doing?
The electrical.
I thought it was the eclectic life.
I read it wrong.
I'm looking right at it.
Director Will Sharp brings to life an unusual and brilliant man who revered cats and wanted to harness electricity.
That's where the electricity comes in.
What?
I mean, who's, I mean, imagine pitching that.
And people being like, I like this.
Well, you get it made because there are lunatic actors like Benedict Cumberbatch that are like what have and I played this year.
A guy that wants to create electricity and loves cats all I can get to challenge. I'll do it.
I mean, they get into this Johnny Depp syndrome where it's like, dude, just some challenges. I mean, it's good.
No.
And I feel like he played two different people in the past five years who harness the power of electricity.
Wasn't he in that one called like the current war or something about electric?
The battle for the phone or Alexander Graham Bell or some shit?
Probably, you know, anything with one of those stupid fucking those called bully tie.
One of those ties called at least aware sort of like the two strings hanging down with the bow up top.
What?
It was like old Western Elizabeth and whatever ties.
I'm talking about a Bolo tie.
Bolo tie.
Anything with a Bolo tie.
I thought you were referring to a hat or something.
I will play it.
But when we look up the current war, if he was in that, then yeah, Benedict Cumberbatch.
And this is the story of the competition between Thomas Edison and George Westinghouse over which electric power delivery system would be used in the United States.
He's obsessed with electricity.
I mean, what a snooze, man.
That was like, I'm enamored.
I'm enamored by Nikolai Tesla, the real man.
I'm enamored by him.
I think he's the fascinating individual.
Okay.
And did amazing things.
But Jesus Christ, that Ethan Hawke thing where he played Tesla.
Yeah.
I mean, it's, it's just so fucking boring, man.
I don't understand.
It's not a payday, obviously.
Like it's like, nobody sees them.
They all just appear on Amazon Prime.
You see the trailer, like it's coming to the theater.
It never happens.
And then one day it's on Amazon Prime.
My guess is four people watch it.
And they're all British ladies who whack their bean to Benedict Cumberbatch.
By the way, sidekicks was also directed by Aaron Norris and stars Chuck Norris as himself.
That's right.
It's like the kid meets him.
It was like a, I don't see that one.
What year did that come out?
Was that around last action hero where they were?
I was 93, yeah, right around the same time.
You know, meta.
Sidekicks.
Here's some trivia.
It was the pet project of well known Houston furniture outlet owner Jim mattress Mac Mac and Vale who in partnership with Chuck Norris and his kick drugs out of schools campaign invested eight million dollars in producing this movie.
Folks.
Today's topic is boring cinema.
Yeah.
We'll be reviewing Nightmare Ali both the nineteen.
What is it 42 version in the 19 or excuse me in the 2021 version.
47 and and 2021.
By the way, boring or both boring.
You're going to have to wait to find out.
This is I guess a little screaming at just something I'm noticing.
Everybody.
Or vast majority of people do not like.
The films don't look up.
Yeah.
Directed by Adam Kay, which I have seen.
And also.
The one we're talking about today.
Nightmare Ali.
These two directors.
Guillermo del Toro and Adam Kay, who each have.
Make no mistake.
$50 million minimum.
In the bank.
Or retweeting every hour.
Just casual people fans on the on Twitter that have said.
I don't know what the big fuss is about.
I actually thought don't look up was pretty funny.
Adam McKay retweets it.
Sick.
It's like it is sick.
I knew when I when I had sitcoms or wrote on shows or whatever.
You don't retweet compliments about your.
It's just a bad look.
But to do it when you're at that level is just pathetic.
Like they they're not going to like everything.
And you're right.
Did the same thing with Soho.
It's like, yeah, I'm going to find every good review and retweet it.
And make it seem like the feedback on the movie is good.
But we all read all the other shit on Twitter.
And we know that it's not that re and Johnson was doing that with last Jedi.
Yeah, you know, it's like it's it's just.
Oh God.
Everyone's so broken.
So deeply broken.
It's like retweeting, you know.
These are these are big gigantic Hollywood.
Powerhouse productions.
And then these gun for higher directors getting all fucking powdery.
You know, that people didn't like what they did.
It's like, it's like if you may, it's like if you created an ad for Pepsi.
Yeah, criticized.
And you got like mad about your artistic integrity getting.
Give me a break, guys.
These were not blood, sweat and tears projects.
Yeah, what Brian, you know, all week shitting on.
NFTs and and cryptocurrency and all the stuff.
And it's just people have completely sold out creatively.
Any artist who would do this is sold out create a.
Brian, you know, produced cold play.
Like two years ago.
And I've had it with him.
I've had it with his dumb name.
I've had it with.
I just had it with him.
You know, it's very funny.
Take in 2022.
Yeah, I mean, look, I'm a fan of what he's done.
I'll get me wrong.
You both on his own and with other outfits like Bowie and the talking heads.
Shall we go to the movie corn?
Yeah, and we'll keep it.
I'm going to keep it on topic with the sense of boredom.
Yeah.
I'd like to.
I was going to do three Christmas movies I watched, but I'm just not in the mood.
Okay.
Hey, and if we're if we're keeping you awake, Joe, just.
Just not off.
I see some pillows right there.
No, I got to leave.
No, no, the pillows are here because I got a.
My couch is too deep.
So you got to sit against a bunch of pillows.
Okay.
Or you're like too far.
It's ridiculous.
The mic won't reach.
Anyway.
Well, it's like the fucking princess and the pee over here on the zoom.
Oh.
It was the story of the princess and the pee.
There was a pee under her mattress.
Yeah.
And like if they stacked them up.
So she couldn't feel it.
It meant she wasn't a whore or something like that.
I don't know.
I don't recall that aspect of it.
It was literally like if you go if you can feel the pay your marriage material.
Like literally that's what the plot is.
I think it was.
Yeah.
Anyway, maybe because like the prince had a really small dick.
They wanted to see like if she could feel very minor intrusions into her nightly routine.
I tried to do a gritty remake that was based on the prince urinating on the woman.
It never went any further.
Okay.
There's a metaphor for Christ.
The prince.
Oh, I thought you meant Prince the artist.
Okay.
No, I wanted to cast Prince in a meta.
So for a referential move.
But he wouldn't pee on the prince.
He wasn't into it.
Yeah.
All right.
I watch speaking of boring.
I read.
I read that one of Prince's friends once referred to him as being gay for pussy.
Which is just.
It's it's it's everything.
Everyone.
Everyone who's ever asked like, what was Prince by or what was the gay for pussy is the best answer?
I want a t shirt that says that fans.
If anyone sends me one, I promise you I will wear it.
And I will take a picture.
I'll go for it.
All right.
I watched.
Aaron Sorkin's latest slog.
And watching people sit around the table and talk for three hours.
Yeah.
Being the Ricardo's.
The worst title movie since I've said it before and I'll say it again.
Hotel for dogs.
Being the Ricardo's is such a bad title.
You see, I don't tell Rwanda for dogs.
I thought that wasn't really poor today.
I did too.
And for Cheatle to sign on again.
You know, I.
It's just the worst title for a movie.
I don't know what they should have called it.
Maybe just Lucy.
I don't know.
It's a biopic at its worst.
It is all talking.
No action.
It's yet another one of these biopics where it's like.
Hey, remember how you liked these people.
Yeah.
Let me show you how much they suck.
Every person in this fucking thing.
You know, JK Rawlings.
What's his name?
JK Simmons plays.
Plays a.
William Frawley.
Right.
Grunk around the clock on the show.
The lady from Tower Heights that played the Russian studying for a law degree.
I got to tell you him, you know, Simmons being an asshole to everyone.
And then all the actors in this sitcom going like this sucks.
And I hate this and everything.
It's like.
And then they're kind of portrayed as heroes.
Like at the end, he's like a fun curmudgeon.
It's like no, I hate these people.
Yeah, I hate them.
And I don't want to spend any time with them.
But you spend two hours and 10 minutes with them.
Viv Vance is portrayed.
Like the neediest person on earth.
But then.
Ricardo has played basically just like or does he aren't as excuse me has played basically just like.
You know, he's a lethario and he's charming and he's not the best husband.
But he's a lover.
And he said, do sir.
Right.
You know, whatever.
So it's, it's stereotypical.
It's not terribly offensive.
As far as like his personality is concerned, they don't, they at least make him seem like a likable guy in most aspects.
Lucy.
Dear God.
They portray her in this thing.
Like, first of all.
Kidman plays her like Samantha late sex in the city Samantha.
Yes, like she's like quippy and like wink, wink and all this.
And then she's a fucking asshole to everybody and not in that.
Bet middler.
You know, doing her one woman show for the first time.
Like, sorry, you got to be a bitch because they'll steamroll over in this business if you're a lady.
Not like that.
Just a terrible fucking person.
She won't let Viv Vance ever look attractive on the show.
She degrades her.
She tells the director, I have no faith in you.
You're terrible at your job.
She hammers the writers incessantly.
And then they think that they balance this out with these stupid fucking moments where they'll like.
They'll be like a scene where they're pitching Lucy a famous scene that everybody remembers from I love Lucy.
Like Lucy stomping on the grapes.
And it starts playing that music that sounds like a cash register like.
Because her gears are turning.
And she's going, I see it, I see it.
Why does she fall into the grapes?
She loses an earring.
And you're supposed to be like, oh my god, this woman just didn't turn it off.
Yeah.
So there's there's comedy writers.
The writers room is like two or three people.
You know, which I guess was the case back then.
But they're like, okay, so Lucy's stomping grapes.
And then she falls in the grapes.
So they've got the whole scene comedically.
If they had pitched on it for 30 seconds, somebody would have thrown out, she drops an earring.
I mean, how many reasons are there to fall into a vatic grapes?
But they give it to Lucy like, really?
And for Sorkin, who is a television writer?
To just keep pushing this thing that like the actors are creating the dialogue.
Let's pause.
Let's pause for a second.
Sorkin is not a television writer.
Sorkin is a guy that has a staff allegedly, allegedly.
And when he takes things on to his own, you can tell he's not a fucking writer.
This guy doesn't know how to write.
It's terrible.
It's all exposition.
Writes every episode of his own shows or at least puts his name on them.
But he has a room generate ideas.
And then he goes, or at least in the West Wing days, he'd do a bunch of blow
and write all the scripts by himself.
And then the writers don't get the script fees and everything else.
It's just a legendary monster.
And every movie he makes, he's on the side of the artist and everything.
But it's like, this movie is really shitting on writers throughout.
And acting as if Lucille Ball was the only one who knew what comedy was.
It's also the second thing Sorkin has done about comedy, including that awful studio 60.
He's not a funny man or writer.
He's one of the least funny people on earth.
Why didn't he?
And then pontificating on comedy.
The hacky, hacky, hacky, biopic thing.
It opens with the interview to camera.
Yeah.
I was there in 66.
I remember how tense it was.
Oh yeah, that was a hell of a week on set.
We all knew when Lucy walked on the stage that morning that something was off.
It's like, come on.
God, this movie sucked.
And I wanted to like it too, because I was a, I love Lucy fan growing up,
because my mom, it was my mom's favorite show.
And I used to, I used to get joy out of watching my mom watch it,
because I loved how much she loved it.
I remember when Lucille Ball died, my mom cried.
Yeah.
I was a huge Lucille Ball fan.
And it made me admire Lucille Ball.
And I wanted to, I wanted to like this.
I was excited.
The trailer got me excited when it would have played the theme and all that.
I was like, oh, this is going to be like a fun.
You know, and it was, it's just not, it's just sucks.
Oh my god, it sucks.
They feel like if you made a Sinatra movie and the whole movie was just Sinatra arguing
with his wife about he might have cheated on her.
Yeah.
Who wants to see this part of it?
Nobody cares about this part.
Well, what people care about even less or what I cared about even less
was the entire thrust of the story, which is that she is, it's hinted that she might be a communist.
Like, they've made them, they've made this story a billion times.
I didn't even know Lucille was ever thought to be perhaps a communist.
But I don't care.
And from the jump, you're like, oh no, I went to a meeting once and it's some innocuous thing.
But that's what they try to drag the dramatic tension out of.
And there is none.
Then it builds to a save the day phone call from Jay Edgar Hoover.
The worst human being that's ever.
Right.
We're all supposed to cheer because Jay Edgar Hoover saves the day.
It's just by the way, by the way, there's no tension whatsoever from the jump of the movie.
Because if you have been alive for more than six years, you know that Lucy had 86 TV shows after this one.
And that clearly she was not blacklisted.
So even if you don't know the story, you know the outcome.
What a waste of fucking time.
That's a big issue I have with biopics in general.
Is that you know what's going to happen?
So the tension is gone.
But in a story like this, it's like, I guess that's probably why they went with this communism angle.
Like what's something we don't know about her?
But it's not interesting.
And you could have made the same movie about any of the hundreds of stars who were blacklisted.
You know, so there you go.
If you want to, I'll do mine.
I basically talked about that one, too.
But the another portrayal of Lucy on screens this holiday season is in licorice pizza.
Have you watched that one yet, Jim?
No.
So very briefly her name's Lucy something else.
But there's a lady playing with seal ball and she's played like a monster, too.
She's basically hit beating kids.
You know, it's like running around screaming at people.
She's not in it very long, but she's, you know, the lady plays her as I think better than Kidman.
Who did a good job?
You know, by the end, I was, I thought I was like, okay, Kidman, I'll buy her as Lucille ball, which they all did a decent enough job.
I just the movie sucks.
But yeah, licorice pizza.
I watched again.
And I think I mentioned it on here about a month before it got released.
I didn't want to talk about it too much.
But now I think everybody's seeing it.
For me, you got to watch every Paul Thomas Andrews movie a second time.
I was very surprised at how much my opinion of inherent vice went up when I watched it again.
Licorice pizza to me is the, is the bottom of the barrel for, for PTA, even though I think it's a B plus movie.
I really like it.
And I put it above inherent vice.
I put this ranking up.
And it would change every day.
Magnolia number one.
Boogie nights, punch drunk love.
There will be blood, the master, phantom threat, heart eight, licorice pizza, inherent vice.
The comments here again, letterbox is getting as annoying as Twitter.
I'm about to get off it.
Guy wrote guy who doesn't follow me on here.
This is the worst PTA ranking I've ever seen.
Is that what it is or do you disagree?
Like, of course, we wouldn't have the exact same list.
Idiot who doesn't follow me anyway.
I like worst.
He's ever seen the worst PTA ranking.
I've ever seen.
Any PTA rankings have you seen by the way?
Why don't you make a list of your top PTA rankings and put mine at the bottom?
Idiot.
This is the worst ranking of PTA rankings I've ever seen.
This seems like a very fair list, although I really can't take heart eight as seriously as the man's other work.
Oh, okay.
I didn't ask you to, you know?
I like that movie.
I like gambling and it's a gambling movie.
People have different opinions and different tastes for Christ's sake.
Well, and this is the reason I never got on the letterbox is because it's a place for a bunch of fucking regular people to pretend like they're on at the movies.
Yeah.
It's another one of these goddamn platforms where now everybody's going to be, you know, an expert to everybody.
Everybody on there is going to be an aficionado.
And it's a place for the nerds to all just like the fucking review section on Amazon started out just like the review section on rot tomatoes is it's time to be review section, which I used to be on a little bit.
I'll tell you, it drives me crazy.
Can I tell you something?
Yeah.
And I'm sure this pisses you off.
I'll look up something on Amazon.
Like for instance, like the Dune 4K.
Yeah.
And I was, you know, you go into the reviews to be like, because you're trying to find out how's the transfer.
What are the bonus features like?
And people are like, one star.
This is a poor adaptation of the, and it's like asshole.
This isn't your review of the movie.
It's your review of the release.
That's what I'm trying to figure out here.
God damn it.
Now here's something I hate even more on Amazon.
And I'm going to try not to get the rail to Amazon talk because I could go all day.
But another thing they'll do is let's stick with Dune.
You look it up.
You're like, hey, I wonder how this look, what the extras are, whatever.
And the review is, um, Amazon.
Do you really think you need to leave my package out in the rain?
Okay.
My discs were completely out of whack.
They'll just start reviewing the delivery experience.
Yeah.
One star case was broken.
Okay.
Anyway, the case is always broken from Amazon.
There's no quality control over there.
I've had good luck with my cases.
Big thing I keep updating Joe on.
I'm making a lot of sales and running them up to the post office every couple of days.
Sales of old vinyl and blue rays and stuff.
The big thing now is people order it.
I ship it while it's in transit or even a week after they've received it.
They cancel it wanting a refund and Amazon immediately refunds them their money.
They do have to send the product back to me.
But it's like found it cheaper somewhere else.
They'll give that reason.
They own it.
It's in their home.
They found it's cheaper somewhere else.
And they want to mail it across the country to me.
Ridiculous.
Yeah.
Lickerspeed to start.
Philopsy more Hoffman son.
Cooper Hoffman.
Alana Hame.
Hime from the bad.
Hime, which I love all three.
Himes sisters play the sisters in the movie.
And it's a love story between a 15 year old boy and a 25 year old woman.
There's been, of course, a lot of think pieces about that on Twitter.
There's no sex between them.
It's just kind of a crush.
But it is.
It's a love story that's taken pretty seriously that might make some people uncomfortable.
Definitely would have if the ages were reversed as they are like in red rocket.
But it's a sweet movie as long as you're willing to accept that premise of a kid and a woman.
But I like it.
It's it's not.
You know, it lacks focus.
There's a long sequence where she hangs out with Sean Penn who's supposed to be William Holden.
Basically, she's dating all these wrong guys for her.
And then she, you know, it's this is your classic story.
She dates all the wrong guys, older guys, weird guys, you know, let she guys.
And then comes back home.
Yeah, comes back home to her.
The guy who's been nice to her all along.
The Sean Penn scenes where he plays William Holden are very boring.
The Bradley Cooper is John Peter's stuff that everybody's raving about.
Says she went for the Oscar.
I don't get it.
On a second view in the movie kind of fell apart from me as just a string of things happening and not necessarily a story that frustrates me a little bit.
But I think Paul Thompson can't make a bad movie.
That I've seen.
They grow on you.
They're interesting.
He has a different approach to filmmaking that I like a lot.
I enjoyed it.
Check it out.
I'm going to stay on the bio picks.
Yeah.
Slightly better than being the Ricardo's.
Much better, I would say.
Not still not great, but much better.
Eyes of Tammy Faye started out hating it.
For, you know, normal biopic reasons, you know, you know, immediately cuts to Tammy as a child.
And her mom going, how do you wear that makeup on your face here like God's sakes.
Anyway, as the movie went on, it grew on me.
Jessica Chastain is wonderful.
It gave me, I already admired Tammy Faye Baker, but it gave me a higher admiration for her.
It increased my disdain for Jim Baker.
And Jerry Falwell.
It's I, you know, now here's a movie where you're kind of waiting for the other shoot a drop because everybody knows the sex scandal thing is coming.
But there's a lot that involved that was involved in that that I wasn't aware of.
I didn't know that Jerry Falwell basically swindled them out of their own channel by offering to take it over to do damage control.
That was an interesting turn of events that was very reminiscent to me of Hoffa when Fitsy takes over the union temporarily when Hoffa's in jail and then pushes Hoffa out.
It's the performances are tremendous.
It's an offrio.
It's not weak, but the weakest of the three Garfield, I was hesitant to buy as a Southern or whatever guy in the beginning, but he's really, really good.
But obviously the show is stolen completely by Jessica Chastain. She's just unbelievable in this thing.
It's directed by Michael show Walter.
We've discussed it on the show Mike does a great job.
A few hacky turns with the biopic like he once or twice he does the freeze frame, right says like the characters name.
Yeah, you know, I could do without that, but you often wonder to is that just a studio note, you know, you have to do that thing here, whatever.
But all it all was good. It's got a very strange, surreal ending to it with her singing in front of an audience, but I like the picture. I liked it. I don't know if I watch it, but I liked it.
He really came around from when you were texting me mid movie last night.
But I liked that one a lot this for his first show, show Walter goes this year. I expected to love shrink next door and loathed it.
And I expected to be bored by Tammy Fey and loved it.
So I, you know, show Walter kind of can't see each other out this year, but I think it's a good director.
Yeah.
I saw the new Wes Anderson, the French dispatch.
A movie my wife referred to as the worst movie she's ever seen.
And I think that's extreme, but I don't disagree that strongly. And I love Wes Anderson. It's, it's really, really, really, really bad.
And the reviews were all great like they always are with him, but I also saw a lot saying his best film, his most mature film and stuff.
And these people have been inside too long. There, there is a sort of a collective snapping of the minds of critics that's going on where they all like exactly the same one percent of movies, a lot.
And then they'll just kind of like say everything else is good. It seems like it, I don't know. Well, everyone is just wrong all the time.
And I don't, I find myself not reading any film criticism. I used to love it. You know, it's just not nothing's hitting me anymore.
But the French dispatch is really bad. It opens with a great story. It's three stories. Joe, I'm going to pause here for your, your reaction.
I didn't realize till it started that it's a tribute to the New Yorker.
Fuck you, Wes Anderson. Yeah, I mean, this thing, by the way, there's already like a thumbnail, this thing on the Barnes and Noble website, because criterion is clearly already just decided before it was released. It's going to go in.
He's the only director where every one of his movies is I've bitched about it before. It's insane enough with this already enough.
They put him right in. Yeah. And I think he said just about every film in the criterion collection. But the first story is great. It's, it's, it's an anthology. I guess you would call it. They're linked by Bill Murray is playing basically the head of the New Yorker.
He's not funny in any way in the movie. It's his usual cast of characters.
You know, cast of actors that are playing, Tilda Switton's playing like a coup, who's kind of like narrating. There's different narrators throughout.
Just a bunch of fucking theater geeks. That's exactly right. It's the theater kids.
And they're wearing funny teeth and funny voices. And yeah, it's just stop it. It's the theater click at your college.
It's so annoying. Stop it.
And you can just picture them howling after they wrap these things. It's like when you go, when you go see a Woody Allen movie or when you, when you used to go see a Woody Allen movie and people.
I still remember seeing midnight in Paris and just being disgusted by the fake performative laughs all around me to say like I get this. I know who Ernest Hemingway is.
That's what the whole kind of vibe is. And Anderson is definitely inherited that and his audiences have inherited that.
But the first story is great. It's nice little Toro. He's in prison.
He's revealed to be an amazing artist. And he, one of the guards was played by Leah Sedau, who is completely naked for the entire story, which is very odd in a West Anderson movie.
I've never seen nudity in a West Anderson.
I've only seen 12 year olds touch each other.
Yeah, but that story really works. It's interesting. It has a great theme to it. It has a great point. It doesn't wear out. It's welcome. And of course, Del Toro is great in it.
There's all kinds of really cool visual jokes and stuff.
The man can shoot a movie. I mean, every, every frame of it looks like a man plan with fucking doll house, you know, for, you know, it looks like he spent a tremendous amount of time making every shot.
Look, like a perfect little, you know, diorama at the school science fair or something.
But that can only be impressive for so long until you just want to pull your hair out. You're like somebody in the movie show me a human emotion here, you know, like they're all dolls acting in his little stories that he makes.
And you don't connect with anybody.
But when the first story ended, I was like, okay, I'm into this. The second one is Chamolet.
I mean, Chamolet walks off a set onto a set. And he's been doing it for three years now. I mean, he's in every film.
It's him and Francis McDormand.
Oh, Christ.
It's black and white.
Oh, my God.
They're like revolutionaries. They have a sexual relationship.
Chamolet and McDormand.
It's, it's so bad. It's basically about halfway through this story, which probably the last 20 minutes. I was just, you know, I was saying to Heather, like,
what happened? This is, this is getting awful. And it just goes from there.
The last story is back to color. It's Jeffrey Wright, who is the one black person. Wes Anderson knows, apparently.
I guess he fell out with Danny Glover, you know, after they forced him to put one black person on the rail.
Ten of Bob's 20 years ago.
But now it's always Jeffrey Wright.
And his story, it's him and Leo Schreiber, an actor who aren't we done with Schreiber?
We're done.
You had your, you did your Donovan and you're done. It's enough. You cashed out and.
That's what I thought.
I always thought when you get to, you get the TV show, that's it.
You're done.
You, you cashed out and you're done. And we're done with your wife too, by the way.
You know, old Naomi, she's, we're not, we're not into it anymore. It's fine.
But these two talk, like on a Mike Douglas style set in the 70s.
Jeffrey Wright is doing some weird voice affectation.
And I almost couldn't tell you what this story was. It was so boring.
It was about a chef.
And they're bringing in various foods. It was a very princess in the P type story.
Actually, it was stupid.
And this sounds up there with like coffee and cigarettes that Jarmish movie.
It's worse than that.
And at least Jarmish certain people were like, it's an interesting thing and whatever.
It wasn't praised like this.
No.
I started to think at a certain point I might have enjoyed it more with the sound off, honestly,
because visually, you cannot fault him. He, he's a stylist, you know.
But he needs to either write with Owen Wilson, who is funny.
Again, or he needs to write with somebody who's a human being again.
He's writing with every movie now with one of the copula sons,
one of the lesser copula sons.
And like he just is in this world of rich privilege and the New Yorker.
And all anyone talks about is the New Yorker.
And he spun this into a movie.
And thinking about any normal person who doesn't routinely read the New Yorker.
Watching and enjoying this movie, I can't imagine it.
I just can't imagine it.
His head is so far up his ass at this point.
And it was the first, well, first one since Darjeeling limited that I hated.
And I love dogs, I guess.
So there's three.
My last one.
Was a biopic.
That I loved.
Okay.
You don't agree, but.
House of Gucci.
I loved it.
I really did.
I thought I had a blast with House of Gucci.
Okay.
All right.
I thought it was a good movie, but I had a blast.
I thought it was a good movie.
I thought I thought it was an interesting biopic approach.
Why?
There was no talking to camera.
Yeah.
Fake interviews.
There was no.
This is them as kids.
There was none of that bullshit.
It got right into.
They meet.
And it's going to go to shit real fast.
Yeah.
That was it.
Driver was tremendous.
I thought.
Lady Gaga was spectacular.
Arguably performance of the year for me.
She deserves another Oscar.
She deserves praise.
She's I can't wait to see her in something else.
She's so she was so good.
I really enjoyed Pacino.
There are two types of Pacino I like.
I love crazy Pacino.
And I love charming Pacino.
Mm hmm.
I hate sad sack Pacino.
Right.
He was neither he was not sad sack Pacino in this.
He was charming Pacino up until he gets fucked over.
And then he's crazy Pacino.
And it was what I wanted.
It was what I wanted.
Um.
Uh, Leo was insane.
And over the top and ridiculous, but I did enjoy it.
It was ridiculous, but I enjoyed it.
Um, he's, he's a less, he's doing a less talented version
of what Nick Cage did.
You can always count on him to do something insane in a movie.
The difference is I loved it when Nick Cage did it.
And I usually hate it when Leo does it.
But with this movie, he did give it a certain kind of.
Spunk, you know, like anytime he's on screen, you're like,
I wonder what he's going to do.
And that can be kind of fun.
Yeah.
I liked it.
I thought Jeremy Irons was, was, was good,
but laughably cast as the, as an Italian man.
But hey, pass me another plate of spaghetti and meat bowl.
I liked the movie quite a bit.
And I got to say,
I, I, it didn't pull any punches.
I mean, the Gucci family was mad because they said that it victimized patritia.
I didn't think that at all.
I thought from the jump, they made her look like a gold digger,
who was manipulative and power hungry and eventually destroyed her life.
Right.
And the lives of many people.
I, that's just how I took it from the junk.
You know,
Payout, no, Maurizio, who is played by Adam Driver,
he certainly has his flaws in his unlike abilities.
But they definitely come off in this movie and this story way more as a result.
Of being in a marriage that is being dominated by this, this woman.
I didn't think they once made her seem sympathetic,
except for when she cried about him cutting her off.
Right.
But even there, I was like, she's just crying because she's,
that to me,
all of it was cemented by the final line of the film where she says in court
as she's being sentenced, call me Miss Gucci.
Yeah.
You're like, no, this all was just about the name to her.
So I loved it.
I thought it was, I thought it was really great.
It had a bit of a score, say, as you vibe to it.
At times.
But it was fun, man.
And it was fun going back and kind of reading the Wikipedia after to see the specifics.
The real story isn't quite as cut and dry as the movie portrayed it,
but the movie had a great pace that you kept it moving.
I got to say Ridley Scott's an odd choice for it.
And if they let Dupalma direct still,
Brian Dupalma, I think,
would have made a great house of Gucci, but he's,
he's in director jail probably till he dies.
But you know what I mean?
Good was a 10.
Yeah.
For sure.
I think of the two Ridley Scott movies this year.
I'm a bigger fan of.
Last duel.
But I like the bowl quite a bit.
And you know, my last one here folks will be don't look up.
I don't know much to say about it.
It, I love, I love Adam Kay's early funny work.
His SNL, his anchor man, his step brothers, of course, and the other guys.
The big short I liked.
Vice lost me completely.
And with don't look up.
You realize he's trying to be like the broad comedy version of Oliver Stone.
And it is just absolutely not working.
I don't doubt that he's a very smart man and very politically minded and, you know,
but the entire joke of the movie is that there's an asteroid coming for Earth.
And everyone ignores it.
Everyone in politics ignores it.
Everyone in the world ignores it.
And there's people saying don't look up.
That's the catchphrase of like the the trumpers saying like let's pretend that climate change isn't real.
That works as a sketch.
You know, that's a very funny SNL sketch where there's a comic coming for Earth.
And you realize a couple minutes into it.
Okay, it's, it's an allegory for climate change.
Got it.
This movie is two hours and 20 minutes.
And they never vary the approach.
It's the exact same joke told the exact same way over and over and over for two hours and 20 minutes.
It's the most miscast movie I've ever seen in my life.
You've got Leonardo DiCaprio and Jennifer Lawrence playing scientist nerds who have no charisma.
So like you're asking the two biggest and, you know, two of the most attractive celebrities in all of Hollywood to be dorks, you know, they able to be funny.
I can't stress enough how not funny they both are.
Okay, it made me like Jennifer Lawrence has as I guess done comedy kind of if you want to consider silver linings playbook like a dramatic comedy.
DiCaprio has almost never done comedy and you really understand why I mean, can you think of any outside of growing pans that he's done.
No, and it's why it was wall street, you know, you can call that a comedy, I think, and he's hilarious in it.
But the man doesn't have a funny bone in his body outside of that.
But that's the thing. That's the thing.
He's good at.
He's good at playing outrageous characters and sometimes those characters are funny.
Yeah, it's funny watching him have a nervous breakdown in wolf a wall street and Rick cut his couch open and start doing coke that he hit in it.
You know what I mean?
But DiCaprio is not funny in a comedy.
I would think.
And then something like this.
Where it appears to me from the trailers and whatever else, you would almost need like a Kevin James sense of sitcom sensibility of like here's how you make this funny without make or the will feral.
You know what I mean?
Like exactly.
Here's how you make it funny without making it look like you're trying to make it funny.
Yeah.
Yeah, you know, like, so I, you know, I don't think either of them really has that, which is fine.
I don't have it either, but.
Now, it doesn't work.
There's a sub plot with Ariana Grande and kid cutie who's also acting a lot.
He's the new common in terms of rappers who should have never been allowed to act.
It goes one of two ways.
You have amazing actors, your ice cubes, et cetera.
And then you have these people who just hang in there.
I mean, kid cutie is nothing area.
It's, you know, in that whole sub plot is like.
We're also some success with celebrity culture.
You know, like the, the points are just made really obviously.
Meryl Streep as the president is fine.
You know, the only person who really keeps the thing propped up and keeps you laughing from time to time.
Is a small supporting role by Jonah Hill, who's basically playing Donald Trump Jr.
So, and then even that they do too much in his opening scene.
He sniffs, he sniffs 50 times, like they cut to him sniffing.
And you're like, okay, like you're doing too much.
And it's also really hard to satirize the world after the last four years.
And the Trump presidency, you almost can't, you can't go bigger than what happened.
So what you're left with is you're being lectured for two and a half hours by a guy who's insanely rich.
About how people are too rich and how they don't care about the climate.
And it's like, hey Adam, I've never read about some big donation you've made to climate change.
But I do know this movie costs 200 million dollars, you know, could you have maybe made a comedy for 50 million.
And then donated the rest, you know, it's just, it's strange.
It's strange what gets rewarded.
And then the people who are like, Adam, okay, you know, takes, okay.
It's fucking hypocriticals, not the right word.
But it's just show boating, it's virtue signaling, it's bullshit.
Yeah, you know, he just came out and said, I'm so shocked that my telling of my breakup with Will Farrell
got so much press.
Fuck you, McKay.
Fuck you.
You know exactly what that was going to do.
Yeah, this is what people don't realize.
Those interviews, all interviews you see from celebrities are generated by a publicist.
They, you know, once in a while they'll kind of do a hatchet job on somebody.
But usually Adam, McKay can read a, read a piece about him three times before it hits, you know, the press.
They're all liars.
But the movie is, you know, it's just too much.
It's going for like Doctor Strange Love, but, you know, that movie was making fun of a very repressed time.
This movie is trying to make fun of how over the top everything is.
And that just doesn't work when you're, as over the top is what you're satirizing.
I don't know.
There's a reason nobody likes movie.
It doesn't work.
Alright, let's get to a movie of the day.
I mean, this is really more about the remake of Nightmare Ali than the original, but the original.
Nightmare Ali, if you've never seen it, it's a film noir made in 1947.
It's starred, I forget his name, but he was a teen idol at the time.
Yeah, Tyrone Power.
And he was a Zorro if I'm not mistaken.
We're not a teen idol, but he was very wholesome, wholesome actor.
And he wanted to do something that kind of sellied him up a little bit that was a little edgy or it was very controversial for him to do that at the time.
It was also very controversial for them to be adapting this book at the time.
It's a racy book, especially in considered in the 40s and bringing it to the screen.
But what they ended up with, and you can get it on the criteria and I highly recommend it is a great black and white film noir.
That is disturbing at times that is mysterious and is the story of a guy who's got nothing who figures out how to work his way to the top of.
Basically circus culture, which is weird, but it's so I love film noir and it's so weird that it matches perfectly with like a carnival movie.
It's like you're wonder why they didn't do more carnival based film noir is because it works so well.
Some of my favorite tales from the crypts are the ones that take place in the carnival.
And I love the show.
There's something about a carnival setting that's very ominous and creepy and sad, but it was a lifestyle gig for a lot of people during the dust bowl up through the 50s.
You know, and maybe still is to some extent, but that was really I think your prime carny years there and you know it was.
It's interesting. It's an interesting thing to watch this guy who has been sort of cast out by society in his own way.
Come into something with decent intentions and then become corrupted as it goes, and you start to see his, his true self, which is manipulative, which is greedy, which is a lot of things.
He works his way up into high society.
And he eventually betrays himself to the point of destroying everything he's built.
By becoming too greedy a con man.
And he goes from doing simple dumb mind trick and magic shows into doing what they call spook shows, which is where they start to tell people they can actually summon the dead.
He's warned not to do this that it's dangerous that people get hurt.
He doesn't anyway, it does ruin his life.
And he ends up back at the carnival where he's not the same carnival, but a carnival where where he started with nothing.
And now he is ready and willing to take on the lowest job at the carnival, the job of the geek, which the geek's job is to bite the heads off of chickens in front of an audience.
Right.
And it's somebody that will do the job because they're so drunk and so desperate, they'll do anything for the alcohol.
At the beginning of the story, he says, I can't imagine anybody could live like that.
At the end of the movie, his closing line is I was born for it.
Yeah, it's really a perfect structure, especially for in war.
And it's kind of the structure of like there will be blood, you know, like just a steady rise to power.
And then it overtakes you.
Absolute power corrupts absolutely whatever.
But I love the 1947 version so much.
And especially to think that it's, you know, what is that 70 plus years old at this point.
There's not an ounce of fat on it.
The black and white looks beautiful.
The acting is great.
Every part is played by somebody just killing it.
And I'm like, the only thing I would have done more is was your exact point, Joe, when you watched the OG one was, oh man, imagine what they're going to do with this.
Geek character, you know, imagine what Del Toro will do.
And I felt the same way I was like, yeah, it's going to be awesome because it's going to be this perfect story matched with modern day.
Effects and coolness and Guillermo del Toro creatures and everything else.
I can't wait for this.
And almost immediately I was just bored out of my fucking mind by the remake.
He makes the most kind of obvious choice every step of the way.
Del Toro kept saying, well, I'm adapting the book.
I'm not adapting the original.
And I think the reason he did that is because he didn't want people to compare it to the original.
Because it's so much worse.
Well, it's so boring.
The original is, I would say a bit truer to, I didn't read the book.
I read the full plots inopsis.
So for what I could tell.
The original seems a little closer to the book than Del Toro's.
This is another one of these things where these guys come out and go, you know, we're going to do the book this time, like Burton did with Charlie and chocolate factory.
Right.
And you see it and you're like,
well, this is sort of the book, but you changed all this other stuff.
Like, for instance, in the book.
So the thing that the one thing they tacked on the original movie, they only all they did was complete things they couldn't put on camera at the time.
The one thing they tacked on was a happy ending.
Where the guy, the woman that this that Tyrone Powers character loves and eventually hurts an abandoned finds him at the carnival where he has been reduced to the geek and brings him makes him human again.
That's it.
And that was apparently, you know, the studio at the time kind of insisted on that ending because it's a very dark movie.
That's the, to me, the one area where the new night morale kicks the ass of the old is the ending.
The ending in the new one is much better and Bradley Cooper is awesome in that final scene.
Beyond that, it's, it's every, every single point goes to the 47 version.
So the new one yet ends with the line, like we're saying, brother, I was born for it.
And that's it. Like he's just this guy's, this guy's finished. That's the end. Right.
I don't think Cooper, I thought Cooper was awesome in that scene until they hung on him for 30 seconds, cry laughing.
Yeah.
And I'm like, for Christ's sake, guys, come on, don't do the, I'm crying, but I'm laughing thing.
Like I did that in a short film called hysterical.
It was nominated by the way, watch for what?
The best short film that's something I forget.
But the derives. That's how that movie ended.
You know, and I had I known better at the time, I would have said, I don't want to do that.
But, but tell Toro and Cooper, they know better. Come on.
But anyway, it's still a good effective last scene.
But then leading up to that, they added a bunch of stuff.
So when, when
movies two hours and 30 minutes, 45 minutes longer in the origin.
Holy shit, it's way too long.
Like Cooper's character kills a bunch of people in the finale.
And that does not happen in the book.
They also took this route with his relationship to the characters where none of it seemed developed.
I didn't understand how this movie was 45 minutes longer than the original.
Yet it failed to help me understand why these characters were even connecting.
For instance, Tony Collette plays this sort of sex pot medium.
Totally.
Yeah, so it's strange.
It's strange.
Not because she's not sexy, although she's not sexy in this film at all.
I just think she's completely wrong for the part.
She, she, she, they made her, they make her really worn out like in your life.
I don't understand like this is like, and she, she fucks Cooper within seconds of meeting him.
And you're like, but it's her throwing himself herself at him.
And you're like, where's this coming from?
Is she a process?
I don't even understand.
Like he pays her to use her bathtub because I guess that was a service back then.
And she fucks him.
And you're like, okay, was that what this is?
Like is that a bath that like is she a hooker?
Or is it like, or she's just trying to fuck him?
Because she never fucks any other guys in the movie.
And then she almost seems like in love with him.
But none of that is ever explained.
She's cheating on David Strathane, who was her husband.
Strathane is so boring in this movie.
But yeah, the relationships are all sort of instantly clear in the old version.
And like you're saying, it's not the case here.
You don't, none of the connections really stick with you or make sense.
And the cast, although, yeah, it was the same in 47, don't get me wrong.
But in 2021, for Guillermo del Toro to make a movie with 15 lead speaking roles
and cast them all with major actors.
And they're all white.
I find very odd.
Like I was thinking, you know, if Spike Lee made a movie with no black people in it,
people would say, what the fuck are you doing?
You know, like even when he makes quote,
whiter movies, the normal, let's say 25th hour or something like that,
he makes sure that it feels like New York.
You know what I mean?
There's like a rich, diverse cast.
Now, at a time where all anyone can talk about his diversity, this movie is so white.
And it's all the more boring for it.
Everyone is cast by the person who would play that part.
If you just came, like, okay, who would play the creepy guy who works at the carnival.
And fucks people over and has, you know, dark intentions.
I don't know, Willem Defoe.
And then it's him.
You know, everybody is played by the exact person you would expect.
And that's just boring as hell.
You know, everyone is just doing exactly their thing.
Blanchette is playing like a spoof of a 40s actress.
So boring.
She's so boring.
And she says every line in the most slow over an unciated way that I stopped being able to listen to what she was saying.
I was so bored.
And I love her as an actress.
Don't get me wrong.
But so boring.
Cooper brought very little dynamic to the role.
I never thought I'd see Willem Defoe and something and be underwhelmed.
I never thought I'd see Ron Proman and something and be underwhelmed.
What's your name that plays Molly?
Oh, my God.
Oh, yeah.
Roni Mara.
Jesus.
I mean, it's just.
It's as though everyone, it's a movie that felt like COVID.
Everyone felt like they were coming.
They were just starting to be diagnosed with COVID.
Everyone is zonked out.
Everyone looks tired.
And the movie is directed in a very kind of tired on energetic, unimaginative way.
The geek stuff is, you know, you just do see the guy bite the head off the chicken.
But it's like, I think this was sort of more effective in the black and white version, you know.
The black and white version, you never see the geek.
You only say in the shadows.
And that makes it more.
Yeah, spooky because you're like, what does he look like?
And like, oh, boy, you know, and in this one, they just show him flat out right out of the gate.
It's the one thrill, the movie, you know, we're supposed to throw bites the head off the chicken.
There's nothing to it.
It's stupid.
Yeah.
The movie is.
You know, for Del Toro saying he wasn't doing a remake.
It's directed seemingly very much inspired by the way the first one was directed.
Yeah.
It's cat.
In my opinion, the cast was looking at the 1947 movie and saying, if we did this now, who would, who would the good guy that there's going to play a bad guy?
Oh, Bradley Cooper.
Right.
He's sort of shiny.
Yeah.
Who could play this strong man?
Oh, Rod Pearlman.
He looks kind of like this guy.
You know, that's, that's how it felt to me.
Where your Jenkins comes in for some weird abortion subplot that they added on to the new version that isn't really.
Anything, you know, it's not as creepy as they intended to be at all.
He's in the, he's in the original, that plots in the original two.
There is more explicit here, of course.
Yeah.
It's much more explicit.
It also makes no sense.
Yeah.
Because he's threatening at one point to kill Bradley Cooper because of all the money he's given him and what a scam it is.
And then in the next scene, he's like begging him to help him.
It doesn't make any sense. It's just poorly executed.
It's, it's.
It's just poorly executed.
It's just not an interesting film at all.
It's really, really, really boring.
And I agree with you.
I was so excited when I got the screener in the mail.
I was going to go to the movies that night to see it.
And the screener came that day.
And I was so excited.
It felt like a jackpot.
And I put it in.
I cooked dinner.
I was ready.
I was so ready.
And I sat down.
I didn't all sit up at a bottle of wine.
It's like, oh, this is going to be a great night.
And within seven minutes, you're just like, yeah.
I'm bored already.
Like, what?
Why?
I can't tell.
You know, like, I'm just bored, though.
I don't give a shit.
Yeah.
It's really a time of like, there's, there's all, there's these great directors who made
a bunch of brilliant stuff.
And some keep doing it for their entire career.
And some get lazy.
But like, I thought while I was watching this, if this was Guillermo del Toro's first movie,
that'd be it.
He'd never work again.
It, hey, it lost $100 million.
I mean, and it's opening weekend with 15 big stars in the cast.
It made $2 million.
Now, there's a pandemic, but Spider -Man made a billion dollars.
So there you go.
But everyone talking about how Spider -Man making so much more money than Nightmare Allie is a scary
thing for our culture because it's just superhero movies now.
And you know, that's how I feel generally.
But this is not a fair balance.
Nightmare Allie is not the artistic, entertaining, well -made, great movie choice.
And Spider -Man is the superhero choice.
The movies aren't good.
It's just isn't a good movie.
So I don't, I think the reason nobody went to see it is because you watch the trailer and
you're like, this doesn't look good, you know?
And I thought the shape of water sucked, too, while we're here.
I liked Crimson Peak somewhat, but Crimson, was it Crimson Peak or Crimson Tide?
Tide was the submarine movie peak was the other one, but he's just a guy.
I think his movies have sucked for a long time now, man.
Yeah, it's strange because they're going to keep letting them make movies, of course.
But it's like, at some point, they're going to have to knock his budget down.
And that's probably when he's going to get interesting again.
I mean, this movie is just too much, too much money, too much, you know, too many stars.
And everyone is just going through the motions.
It's hard to, it's hard, it's a hard movie to get excited about, I guess.
And I, I can say you should watch the original because it's great.
And it's a very cool story, but too hot, not a big remake.
Two hogs down for Nightmare Alley.
Two hogs up for the original Nightmare Alley.
Yeah.
And that's our show.
We'll be back on the next episode with the Matrix Resurrections.
Jotaro's a comedy on Instagram and Twitter.
Taste buds on YouTube .com slash no pressure network.
Come to Joey Roses in New York, please.
The Patrick Walsh Instagram and Twitter, we will be back with the Matrix Resurrections.
Check out my bonus episode each month.
About an hour of just kind of going through the movies I've seen over on the Patreon.
Tell those in your life about the Patreon.
Thank you so much for supporting us.
Happy New Year.
Stay safe out there.
Yeah.
See you next time.
And I, wait, wait, before you wrap it up, I forgot one plug.
I apologize.
Apologies.
Step on a nice wrap up.
It was going so well.
I know.
I'm going on the road again this year.
Now that we're in 2022.
Uh, if you're in Buffalo, New York, I'll be there at the end of January at Helium.
If you're in Rutherford near New Jersey or near that area, I'll be at bananas in February.
Early February.
And then in March, I will be at the punchline in Philly, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, hometown.
So come out to one of those shows.
Take a throw on sale now.
All info available with Joe DeRosa info dot com.
And we'll see you in half.