Welcome to will see you in hell. It's the podcast that you turn to for a movie review or two, sometimes three, sometimes four or five, six, but not today folks today. It's a Q &A all day for the holiday.
Some way more than I thought it was going to. It did. Some podcasts just give you the cues. We deliver the A's as well. Some podcasts just give you the A. Yeah, um, folks, how are you? We, we've had a disastrous week. I'm looking at myself now in the zoom. I mean, might as well just be a corpse.
You know, the hair is out of control. I walked straight out of bed right right into this podcast. So did I, which says a lot about where I'm at because we got a three hour difference. Go there. That's true.
We tried to record this week and just everything went awry.
Yeah, but you know, we're recording things. We're trying this again. Yeah, it's a kind of good feeling. And we lost Mike. We lost Mike. Not because of any sort of, you know, not because of any sort of drama. It's just pat and I realized with about 30 seconds of research on the internet that we are able to record these without a third person getting involved.
And that we could do this, you know, a little more flexibly with on our own time without having to worry about a third schedule to to bring it into the mix.
And also too, we just wanted to see what it felt like to get rid of a guy right at Christmas. Yeah, yeah. I actually had had a pink slip made up. I went to a local paper company.
And then we're like, we don't really do like official pink slips anymore. That's more from like warehouses of the fifties. And I actually took the money I would have paid Mike for helping us and tipped the guy so that he would give me a pink slip as sort of an extra slap in the face to Mike on the way out.
And it's hard to slap somebody in the face on the way out. Usually it's back of the head or nothing because they're facing away from me.
In all seriousness, we love Mike. We just were being funny. We just we honestly just had to figure out how to do this on our own schedules because, you know, because who's got time, who's got downtime these days and flexibility with their schedule.
Well, I mean, podcasts have become this even huge or thing than they were. So Mike, Mike was always juggling the Legion of skanks.
And who else did he do the doe boys? He did a moral baby. Yeah, the doe boys, the party crew, last podcast on the left.
No, not them. Or wait, the doe boys are real one. I thought we were making up names. I thought that was so doe boys is real.
Oh, okay. So starting with party crew, it's officially we're riffing what was party crew was just made just I just made it up. I thought doe boys was fake. So I just went, the party crew, I think he records the male boys.
They tested who kind of mayonnaise each week. Yeah, you eat a big spoonful of mayonnaise and then discuss it with the man is in their mouth. I mean, it's really hard to listen to, but that's kind of their gimmick very hard to equally as hard to listen to his pickle suckers his other one where they suck on a pickle and describe it with the sure without removing the pickle sure.
There's the bingo kids, you know, which is live from kind of grandma's bingo game. Yeah, the amount of times they've gone with the B4 and after material is shocking to me.
And then also too, let's not forget he's flying up to Vegas every week to do slots, slots, slots. Yeah, yeah.
Which shows I would listen to by the way, I would literally one of these show just a guy pulling on the slot and telling you what happens with each pool.
Yeah.
Cherry bar bar.
Another cherry.
All right, let's pull it again.
These aren't grade podcasts, but we wish you luck with them. Mike.
We do wish, Mike. Well, and I still be working with Michael without a country. So he'll still be in my life. Pat will never speak to him again. That's how Pat rolls. He's dead to him.
Do you do your other podcast do better than this one?
It's hard to say. Honestly, because each podcast, it's funny. We were just talking about this the other day.
And Chris and I did the Jim and Sam radio show to promote the no pressure network that new YouTube podcast channel we're doing. And we talked about exactly that. And Chris and I in particular, we're saying like
there's no crossover really between podcasts, like having one big one or one successful one in one area doesn't lead to immediate success to the other one.
They cultivate their own audiences. There's very, and Chris was even saying like people.
And I've experienced this too.
People will like write on his Patreon wall for history, heinous his other show that he does.
Like fuck you. I'll never give a fucking dime to you and Sal's podcast, like you know, like whatever, but they'll keep paying him on the other one.
And then like I was saying to him, like, yeah, I got a message the other day from a guy that was like without a country sucks dick. Nobody wants to hear your stupid ramblings about the news.
You're an idiot. Nobody cares. We'll see you and hell is genius. It's the only good thing you do.
Like, like so, so they're slapping you with the one hand and right and gifting you with the other. It's very strange.
That's very odd. Why not let me unless it's like a possessive quality. Like you should only do ours or something.
And it's weird. Like, like this podcast has probably so far at least in the years that I've been doing it out of the three that I do.
Easily the most loyal. Yeah, for sure.
You know, like it's a smaller audience overall, but it's an incredibly loyal audience.
Whereas without a country might have a little bit of a wider reach, but I also see a little more over there of people week to week taking issue with one thing or the other or whatever.
You know, here they say it seems to be anything goes. I think we can start dropping racial slurs on.
And we don't have anything to worry about. No, no.
We're doing today, by the way, folks, we're not doing our usual segments. We're doing your question speaking of listener loyalty.
I hit up Emily the other night. I said, hey, can we get some questions from the fans? We're going to be recording shortly.
A couple hours later, we had 50 plus cues.
So I hope the Facebook page is still thriving. I hope you all are keeping civil to yourself in there.
And I hope you found a good friend base in there, but I'm glad to see that the Facebook page is even still going to you too.
So let's just jump right in, drum. By the way, has there been an alpha episode by episode podcast?
No, and you can go find somebody else to do that with you. Like, you know, Mel Mac attack. I'll get Mike to record it.
I didn't, I didn't even like that show when I was a kid and it was like supposed to be like, you know, geared right toward me.
I just never liked alpha. I never, I never got into it.
It was very big for me. As, as you know, but it was, you know, I think four birthdays were alpha centered in the show last two years. So I was real into alpha.
I got your title.
Ready? Alpha, alpha males.
No, that's it. That's good. That's better than Mel Mac attack.
Well, Mel Mac attack, you'd make a segment now. You always make the secondary title. Yeah, the segment on the show.
Yeah. All right. Let's get down to this Q &A. We got a lot of work here to do. So let's do it.
And you start referring to this show as a burden. No, I'm just kidding. But we got a lot of questions answered. I actually got me and Joe both on track this morning.
We were heading into one of our classic shit on things spirals over text. And I thought, why are we, why are we typing? Let's just get on the show and do this.
Right. You know, when I was shitting on folks, I real quick here yesterday, they announced on the Fox network my former home and and what a home they treated me like family.
Jason Biggs literally did treat me like my family by which I mean like absolute shit.
It's Jason Biggs hosting a rebooted game show called Cherry's Wild, which sounds like a old town Vegas hand job parlor with an OU in the parlor.
And it is a Pepsi funded game show. This was part of the headline Pepsi funded game show hosted by Jason Biggs called Cherry's Wild.
The industry is over. And I'd like to point out that I saw Pat's bet and raised him with the announcement of Scott staff will be playing Frank Sinatra in the Reagan Ronald Reagan biopic.
And then Pat immediately wrote back. This is not a legitimate movie. And I wrote back. No, it is Dennis Quaid is playing Ronald Reagan.
Not an end of Penelope and Miller's in it. It's a real movie. That's happening. Well, if you got P .A. Am. I didn't know that you mean the star of the gun and Betty lose handbag.
Well, I remember that one. Yeah, I do. I know she hasn't done a lot since the freshman. But, you know, yeah, she wasn't, I mean, Carlito's way. Why was she in Carlito's way?
She was, she was like the, you know, I always associate Penelope and Miller with Bridget Fonda. They were very similar. Yeah, not just looks wise, but but like the types of roles they did and the type of notoriety they had. And then they both just kind of self imposed sort of walked away, you know, yeah, I think I don't think Penelope and Miller's been around. But I think it's her doing.
Bridget Fonda is still around. Who? Penelope and Cruz?
Why am I blanking star of Penelope's gun?
Oh, oh, oh, the Spanish woman. Yeah, Penelope. I don't know where I didn't remember what her name was. There's no, Ann. I just made that up. It's just Penelope. Oh, that's why it threw me off. Okay. Speaking of Cruz, you hear Tom Cruise screaming at everybody yesterday. I thought it was great.
Yeah, you know, and then everybody's like, before you praise him, remember, he's a Scientologist. It's like guys just, just give him something. You know, I'll say this. Here's what I loved about it.
I love just hearing a good old fashioned boss reaming. It's like, yeah, we need more of those. That's why quality sucks everywhere. You need a boss reaming that doesn't somehow turn into a social media lawsuit about my feelings were hurt.
So I love still time for that. But yeah, I mean, it's deserved. You're playing with people's live. You got to get screamed at by the biggest box office draw in the world. Yeah. So I loved it for that reason. The thing I didn't like about it was
you're the member of a religion that perpetuates not using medicine. So it's like, why are you so worried? Like clearly you don't give a fuck about science. And to me, a virus falls into the category of science.
Yeah. So I love the idea that Tom Cruise is is punching out at 10 p .m. and then call calling the studios. Like, and maybe he is. I believe that is. I don't doubt it. I picture him going back to his hotel room and sleeping not sleeping, but just immediately getting into that upside down thing that Bruce Wayne hands in. Yeah.
And then meetings for like seven straight hours and then like a two hour workout and then back to the set. Right. Just two hours of just pushups. Yeah. I don't picture him having any sort of enjoyment like the food intake. Nothing.
No, you know, weirdly like for for his big box office draw as he is and has been for years, you don't see that guy have sex in movies.
It's because he's gay, Pat. Well, yeah. You also you never see hangs which I prefer to not see hangs, but still. Well, hangs doesn't ever do a movie that requires a sex scene.
And maybe it's time, you know, maybe it's time for the old man that runs a train for children or something. You know, it's like some you can get his role. Yeah, once they go to bed, you know, you grab a lady from the bar card.
Yeah. Yeah. I'm going to send out a script called Tom Hanks fucks. Yeah, yeah. Yeah, this this express ain't going to feel polar when I get my hands on you, baby.
The pole. Yeah, you're going to heat up. Right. All right. Let's get to Emily's first question. Okay. Emily asks, if you could be a character in a holiday movie, who would you be and why?
Me, I'm going to go with my favorite holiday movie George George Bailey. It's a wonderful life because I feel I'm deeply depressed, not at a jumping off a bridge level like George was, but I could benefit from some ghosts are from an angel taking me around and showing me what life would be without me.
I just hope that it's not people celebrating like in the married with children episode.
I'm going to change my answer from the first time when we tried to record this to I'm going to go with Ebenezer Scrooge. Okay.
Because he epitomizes that classic thing that everybody at Hollywood does now where he made millions of dollars being a complete piece of shit.
Yeah. And then the second he realized he needed to be forgiven and loved, he was like, I don't want to do that anymore, but still got to keep all the money.
So I'm going to go with Ebenezer Scrooge, plus he gets to go on a fun filled adventure with ghosts.
That's true. I don't want to do that. I want to do that.
All right. Fair enough.
All right. Chris Goodnight asks, what is the best Christmas present you've received? What's the worst?
Best I ever received was when I was three years old my mom gave me a talking bugs bunny doll had a little voice box in it.
And it said things like, what's up doc? You can imagine what it said.
Anyway, the toy was recall, it was my favorite toy. I was obsessed with it. It was the only thing I played with all Christmas.
And then the toys were recalled because they were defective and they stopped voice box, stop working. So my mom brought it back to the store and then they never replenish the supply.
And she said I was devastated.
Cut to 20 years later, Christmas.
I open a present. It's a bugs bunny with a talking voice box in it. And she retold me the story. It was the most touching gift I'd ever received.
And by that, I mean, I would touch it at night when I'd go to bed.
It was your elf.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. No, it was really just a heartwarming gift. I don't mean to make it bad. And then the worst gift I wear is that now do you still have it?
Yeah. I have it in a box of like memorabilia.
Okay.
I don't have it on display because that would look insane. Yeah.
And everything else in your apartment looks completely normal.
Right. I mean, you know, it's one thing to have 67 video game systems on a shelf.
Hey, don't trip over that third VCR that I had on your way to the bathroom.
Yeah.
I believe it's in the same box as my new material sign filled puppet, which I also put away because people were like, that's freaking me out. Please.
Anyway, worst gift I ever received also came from my mom when I was 25. I got a game cube, which was awesome.
But it was the only gift I got. I was like, I just all I wanted is a game cube. And they were like, I remember they had gone on sale because they were kind of on the way out. And they were like a hundred bucks or something or 150 bucks.
So that, you know, and I just said, I just want a game cube. They're on sale now. I just want one. And my mom got me one, which was awesome. And she gave it to me on Christmas Eve because it was my only gift.
And she said, you know, you can have it tonight. You're grown up. And you don't have to wait so far. And then I opened it and I said, oh, thanks mom. This is awesome. And then she went.
They were expensive. So I had a game cube with no games. What system was the game. It was the Nintendo system after the N64, a great system that I eventually.
I got rid of my original one when I thought I didn't want to play video games anymore. And then when I started collecting again in my late 30s, I repurchased a game cube. And it's still a great system. I have a lot of fun with that thing.
Okay. My best in terms of excitement was the original Nintendo. My sister and I were thrilled. We jumped around the living room like maniacs. We played Mario all day and duck hunt.
Yeah.
It was very exciting. And we assumed we had no chance of getting an Nintendo because our parents were like, we can't afford it.
On that same tip, the worst present, and I talked about this on Pete's podcast 10 years ago or something, but my.
I had asked for a play dough set. And I got this set that was like clay dough K. L. A. Y. D. O. H. It was knock off play.
And I was a real cheap skate move, man. I mean, play. What are you saying that X power? Yeah. Yeah. Come on, man.
So I was sitting there at the kitchen table and the clay was so hard that you couldn't even really mold it into even a ball. It was just like.
Like just no give. My mom was suggesting adding some water to it.
I'm sitting there getting more and more frustrated. And then finally I slam it down. And I said I specifically asked Santa for a play dough set. Why would he give me this clay dough set. And I looked up and my mom was crying. And I said, what are you crying about? And then I put it together that there was no Santa Claus.
And that my parents did not have a lot of money. Well, they afforded the Nintendo. Yeah, they did. They did.
I love the I'm picturing you at six as like an abusive husband like wife beat or with spaghetti stains on the front.
What are you crying about? I'll give you something to cry about. Yeah. I grabbed a rolling pin off the counter. All right. I would say about the couple young couple way younger than I was.
At the river boat casino by my house. And I was coming out of the men's room to go gamble. And they were crying and holding each other. And I even dropped and learned that they had gone there.
It was the night before Christmas Eve because they thought they didn't have enough money to buy their kids presents. So they decided to let it ride and lost what money they did have.
Oh, they lost either you say they were crying because they won. No, they were crying. Like, what are we going to do? What are now we have nothing? What are we going to do? I told you this would happen. That kind of thing. Oh, God.
December 23rd.
That's why I like going home so much. It's always a spirit lifter.
All right. Next question.
Next question, Eric Law, which can't be his last name, but Eric Law asked for you to judge. Maybe it is. It's just it's too short for a last name, frankly. It should be law -fontaine or a lobbyada or something.
Favorite movie soundtrack. Great question. I've actually never given that any thought. I have judgment night judgment night soundtrack. Love it so much. I bought it on vinyl on record store day when it was finally released on vinyl again.
I absolutely love it. It is a mashup of every song as a rap group with an alt 90s rock group.
It was the thing that got me into many of my favorite bands because I was such like a straight up rap guy in my early years of high school.
And the orchestrations on it are just really great. Like the bands and the rap groups pull the best out of each other. The songs make sense. It's not corny like limp biscuits style rap rock stuff. It's it's it's rap. It's it's bands playing stuff that is suitable for rappers to rap over and rappers delivering performances that match the sonic.
The qualities of the of the of the rock. It's great. It's just a great soundtrack. It's really well done.
I'm a fan too. They they talked to Kim Gordon on some radio show recently and she was talking about her experience recording with with cypress hitle and how they were adamant about not just doing exactly what you're describing a rap rock type thing. I like the teenage fan club song on there. I'm a big fan of that band. It's a good soundtrack.
Everlast said that's the one with day lost soul right. Yeah, Everlast said Everlast from house of pain basically came up with the concept for the entire soundtrack and he said on tell them quality's podcast that the day lost soul.
Teenage fan club song is like the basically like the masterpiece of the record like and it really is an amazing song. Yeah, I'm a big fan of those guys.
This day lost soul and teenage fan club. My favorite or most listened to soundtrack is probably one of the Tarantino's. I listen to Jackie Brown constantly.
Pulp fiction was a favorite for many years and then in recent years I like drive a lot. I think that's got a lot of great new. That was a cool soundtrack because it wasn't a greatest hits of things you've heard before. Like Tarantino does. It was all new songs and they were all pretty cool.
That's a great soundtrack. I hate the movie, but the soundtrack's great and that that is like that was when like that electronic sort of 80s throwback stuff started to really come into the mainstream. Yeah, and all for bangers. Yeah, that's a great soundtrack.
Okay, Drew Tiberius poll asks Joe who are your three favorite members of Wu Tang clan and then Pat for you. What's your favorite song off tusk? Okay, so Inspector deck is my number one method man is my number two.
And my number three is the Risa.
Okay, I think the inspector deck choices is nuts. Are you he's amazing. Everybody in Wu Tang says he's the greatest MC.
I mean, nuts, you don't know what you're talking about the greatest verse and hip hop of all time. I guess I just haven't heard of some solo material from him as man. I've heard everybody else. He's got, well, there's an interesting story with that. The Risa said in a recent interview that Inspector deck solo record his debut solo record would have been probably the best of all the Wu Tang solo records, but there was a major flood in their studio.
They lost half of the material and it delayed the record and then by the time it came out like everybody was so distracted with other things and like it just didn't it just didn't come together. It was just very unfortunate, but his verse on triumph. He's the first guy on triumph is argued to be one of the greatest rap verses in hip hop history, let alone in Wu Tang history.
Fair enough. Now have they heard Will Smith's on Wild Wild West when he says I'm the quickest they is. I'm the slickest they is. Did I say I'm the quickest there is.
He rhymes quickest with quickest and one of these things about the plot of Wild Wild West, which everybody loves. Right. And what few people realized was that Will Smith's interpretation of that character was that he had Alzheimer's.
So he really was trying to channel a man and the guys like, yeah, you just said it will.
How happy we were in the Willenium. That was a good time. Whoever thought you'd miss the Willenium. Only why 2k was our worry at that time and it wasn't even real.
Yeah. What's your favorite song off Tusk? Drew wants to know. Oh, I think they're going to ask my favorite song off Willenium. My favorite song I had questions to.
Favorite song off Fleetwood max classic Tusk is I know I'm not wrong, which is the coakiest of the coked out Lindsey Buckingham tracks when he was just completely losing his mind.
So I know I'm not wrong on the deluxe edition of Tusk. They have 10 different versions of Tusk.
And it's just him each time and each one you hear it and you're like, that sounds awesome. But then he was like, no, and he did it recorded it in a completely different way.
That's why every time you listen to that album, it sounds different depending on what pair of headphones you have, what kind of speakers you're listening to.
Because every song was just mixed with an inch of its life. So you're hearing like weird things come out in the mix. It's a wonderful album. I know what's up. I'm going to revisit Tusk.
Do it with headphones. I'm going to be that guy, the steely Dan guy. But I know I'm not wrong. I listen to every day over and over and over and over on the way to living biblically.
Because I was being told all day that I was wrong. And looking back, I was just listening to that. I know I'm not wrong as some sort of weird meditation to calm me down.
I have an OCD thing where I listen to the same song over and over for like a year. This year my most listened song was called Forget About Life.
Do you think that tells you anything?
My band called Always. It's a great song. But when I saw that was my number one Spotify tells you what you played the most, I was like, I probably want to go get checked out.
Fair enough, I agree. Yeah. All right.
You're up Mary Ann Hoffman asks.
Wasn't Mary Ann Hoffman the weird presidential candidate? Mary Ann Williamson. Sorry. Sorry.
What's your favorite discontinued snack food? And Joe, you should you should feel this because you do a snack food podcast.
I do, but I'm going to say I'm going to do a thing that doesn't count sort of.
But I think you could continue. You can consider fast food as part of snack food. I don't think anybody's thinking for the most part that fast food is substantial food. It's, you know, it's junk food. We all agree on that. But it's great.
The McDonald's in the 1980s during the peak of the Burger King McDonald's East Coast West Coast battle released as a just a fuck you to the Whopper burger. It was called the McDLT.
And the whole marketing campaign was that the Whopper was disgusting because they put all the whole thing together cold and hot portions of it, you know, the cold condiments and the hot burger and cheese into the same packaging.
And that it was just basically when you unwrapped it just slop because you can't can you can't maintain the integrity.
Okay, different ingredients when you package it that way. So they introduced the McDLT, which was just a Whopper basically.
But it was in a flat styrofoam container and one side had a burger, the bottom bun and the cheese and the other side had the top bun with the lettuce tomato onion pickles, ketchup and mayonnaise.
And then a flat lid went over that. So both sides maintain their different temperatures. Then you take the flat lid off and you press the two sides together because they put a hinge on it.
And then make the burger perfectly and they were like, look, you can get it fresh every time. And I got to say it worked. It worked like get it worked. It was a great burger. The little device worked.
Yeah. And they got rid of it. And now they have like a Whopper type burger. It's basically called the quarter pounder deluxe.
But they just serve it all together because even McDonald's was like, oh, who gives a shit.
Well, it sounds like it's a ton of styrofoam, right? I mean, that's what it was. But these were the good old days. They didn't give a rat's ass. You'd fucking, you know, you'd you'd get a quarter pounder pull it out of the styrofoam.
You know, shove, shove the styrofoam box into a dolphin hole. Yeah. You know, it was a, it was a good time back then.
You know, the first playboy I found in the woods was underneath this giant chunk of styrofoam that somebody had used to wipe their butt.
Oh, all right. Well, big piece of shit covered styrofoam. And that's that's how little we had back then because I still took the magazine out from underneath it.
You still took the styrofoam too, correct?
I like to smell it while while reading the playboy. That's just my thing.
Right. Right. Right. You pretend that's how the woman smells.
All right. Yeah. What's your, just continued. Great question, Joe. I mine has been re continued, but I still have to say giant chewing nerds. And thank you
to those hellians who brought me a couple of bags on the last trip, which I ate on the way home from Chicago. But they are the best candy giant chewing nerds. And luckily, I never see them because I would buy them all the time.
They're out there, but they're hard to find. I don't think I would. I've never had one. I didn't have one that night. I don't think I would like them. I feel like it's too much of that. How big is a giant nerd?
It's not like a softball. They're giant in comparison to nerds. They like an ant would think of a beetle looked giant.
Right. I just feel like it's way too much of that flavor. Well, you haven't tried it. So I don't really value your opinion. Fair enough.
All right, Beth.
Beth Gaston asks, where will you travel first once COVID is behind us?
Favorite to come on guys, favorite TV shows of the past 10 years. This is these are two, just she just has two questions. They're not even kind of related.
I'll take the, you take the first half. I'll take the second half. How about that?
Where will I travel once COVID is behind? I mean, really lately I've been thinking about, I've been watching a lot of like epic movies, like the trip to, you know, trip degrees is not an epic movie, but just movies where they go to like crazy exotic local.
Love the trip degrees. I did too. But honestly, like Hawaii, I went to Hawaii as my favorite place on earth. I'd like to go to Hawaii.
My sights are said much lower because I'll be destitute by the time this is over.
I got to be honest, I first trip for me, I can't wait to just go back into a neighborhood bar. Yeah, randomly.
Like because you can with no mask on at 11 .30 p .m.,
everybody out there is, you know, it's so fucking paranoid. They'll be wearing masks and doing temperature checks until 20 to 25. You know what I mean? Yeah.
Anyway, I don't mean to rub it in. So you need to go to Hawaii as my point. Favorite TV shows of the past 10 years. Let's just pick one each.
For me, and it's a little more, maybe it's 11 years, but my favorite comedy is these bounded down of the past 10 years. I think without question. My favorite drama would probably be.
Man, has there been like a great one that I'm always excited that's coming out? You know what?
I got there's probably one better, but right now I'm going to say normal people on Hulu. I really love that recently.
I'll go with, I don't know, man, I don't know that it shows come out. I'm going to go with the Mandalorian season two has been everything.
Everything I hated season one season two has been everything and more I ever could have wanted out of Star Wars. Wow.
What's changed?
They just kind of changed the season one was all set up and they they they they parcel it out very sparingly.
Season two is like they jumped in with everything. Everything is a payoff. They're introducing all kinds of characters that you know and love from other Star Wars things. It's just awesome. It's like it's like this. You're like, this is what I thought the show was going to be in the first season. So it's a classic case of
Castle Rock. Yeah, where like that first season was just clearly a lot of very slow pace setup for what was to come and then in season two, you were like, oh, this is what I thought it was going to be like.
Right. So that's what they didn't Mandalorian and man, it has been awesome. So I'll give it to Mandalorian.
All right, question seven. Chris Longo asks, if you had one shot with a time machine, what would you use it for? And I am saying, you can't say kill Hitler. It's just it's everyone knows that's what you would do. So let's let's do something different.
I wouldn't do that. It's going to change. No, no, because you can't that's one that's classic Doc Brown. Don't do that stuff. Yeah, you don't know where it's going to go.
You can't do that. So you got to leave that alone. I already know my answer. And I've said it. I've already played out this. I would go back to the 60s, the Vegas in the 60s. Sure. Go and have I would see the rat pack.
I would, I would, I would, oh, man, oh, man, I would live it up. Man's like I would that would be like that was my time.
It was boy, I mean, I'd go with Joe. You don't want to go alone. Yeah, no, I'd want to bring a drinking partner. Yeah, and I would just get barrelled and, you know, and, and, and then, and then cruise on from there to Sanny Fran and get into some drugs and the weird shit like, oh, man, that would have been a fun time.
I don't think you'd like the people that are going to be in San Fran like in 1965. It's going to be here like a man. I would hate them. I would hate them. So the other thing I would do if I wasn't going to go to 60s Vegas is I go to 19 like 75.
Yeah, and just start score a bunch of blow and go to a bunch of Sabbath concerts, shit like that. Yeah, in addition to going to Oldtown Vegas with you, I would like to walk into a bowling alley to disco and Ferno like Woody Harrelson does in the flashback in Kingpin and grab the guys pizza.
All right.
All right. Ashley McCarty asks, Joe, how do you feel that your friend Bill Burr has made into the Star Wars franchise? How do I feel? I'm jealous. I can't even pretend like I'm happy for him.
I texted him the other day to say great job on the newest Mandalorian season. He really was really great in it.
I didn't like the first season and I actually didn't see his entire episode in the first season. What I saw, I thought was good.
But that was obviously not against him. I just wasn't into the first season and I watched it.
I watched enough of it to understand what was happening, but I just couldn't get into the storylines, but I thought he was good in it and I was happy for him.
This season, I was particularly happy for him because he got to be, I don't want to ruin anything if you haven't watched it, but he's in a, he's in several scenes with a major, major, major Star Wars character, which I was like, you asshole.
So really cool. Yeah, I was charge our biggs.
Who's the bird?
Yeah, and no stories to relate because everything is, you know, that's like a knife to your throat, non -disclosure agreement kind of show, you know, like, so he's never able to tell me anything.
But yeah, that's it. Paul Merci asks, what's your favorite Christmas movie?
You know, for me, it is, it's wonderful life, and a close second is home alone.
I wouldn't pick either of those.
And I'd even put it over die hard because as much as I love die hard, it's like, for some reason, it doesn't, even though I know it is a Christmas movie.
And I'm so tired of watching people argue that, but, you know, I don't want to watch it at Christmas time as much as I do home alone.
I'm going to have to go with, I mean, you know, you know, my affinity for Rich Little's Christmas Carol.
I love it every year.
And obviously, a Christmas story, I mean, it's been beaten to death with that stupid 24 hour thing they do every year, but, you know, there was a time where I, you know, I don't want to disqualify it just because they've played it too much on TV.
But I don't know, I might have to go with love, actually, I really love love, actually, and I know it's not in fashion these days to say that.
Because every joke doesn't have an uplifting punch line, but, but I love love, actually, I find it incredibly heartwarming and beautiful.
I like the movie too.
I like that it's like a Tarantino love story, yeah, like all these different stories.
Oh, yeah, I've always been a fan.
Alexis Taylor Ackridge.
There's a full name for you.
Oh, that's a full name.
In your personal opinion, what's the best TV mini series of all time and any thoughts on CBS choosing to release this newest adaptation of the stand?
See, there's two questions that are linked.
That's helped.
Yeah.
Also, what are your thoughts on ham?
This is easy for me.
It's 100 % 80s it.
I've already stated my case for that on the show.
And, and I think this remake of the stand is a complete waste of time.
I think the casting and some aspects of it is great.
I think casting and other aspects of it, like Randall Flagg is terrible.
I don't want to see a gorgeous Randall flag.
But I think it's pointless because the reviews are even saying now and I haven't seen it yet that it doesn't really go by the book and it's fucking pointless.
It's stupid.
Yeah.
I have not seen many, many series to be honest.
They were too adult for me when I was a kid and they went out of fashion when I was 16 or so.
But I never saw when I liked more than it for sure.
You know, I like it more than the Salem's lot many series, but I haven't seen a bunch.
Mom was always watching the Thornbirds when I was growing up.
Yeah, I've never even seen roots or the Thornbirds, but I should go back and check them out.
I saw a recent kid, but I should rewatch it.
I haven't seen it and so on.
I barely remember it.
Yeah.
For me, and it's, you know, the CBS all access stand.
I had, I had high hopes, you know.
But the other reviews are starting and they're all C plus, you know.
It just seems like it's going to be a lot like the it movie was where it's kind of like you already did this except the original stand is not great either.
You know, I watched it very recently and it is not a really good adaptation.
They do their best.
It's not here's the thing.
It's not great.
It's not bad.
No, for the undertaking that it is, it's not bad.
They don't do a bad job.
It's not great because I don't think this stand is a great book to translate into a movie.
A lot of what is scary about it is lost in that translation.
It's not that scary when you put it on the screen.
It's not that interesting when you put it on the screen to watch a bunch of people gather in Vegas and a bunch of people gather at a farm.
And it's just not, you know, it's, it just doesn't work as well.
There's a lot to be interpreted with the read of it.
And I don't think it's a good thing to, you know, everybody thinks because it's this huge book and it's a masterpiece by this author that it means it's going to work on the screen and it doesn't.
Yeah, I don't think there's not an adaptation that could work with the right person, you know.
If they got a William Goldman out of retirement or something, but if he's even alive, I think he is.
Yeah, I just, it was a real bummer to see those reviews come out and just be like, yeah, it's just going to be another average take on things.
And then the fact that it is entirely about a deadly pandemic, I have a feeling it's going to just be not fun to watch.
But I'm going to try, I'm going to try to convince Joe to do it on the pod.
I mean, I'll do it. It's, it pisses me off that I got to give money now to CBS.
And it's like, it's like, did any of us think CBS was going to do a riveting retelling of the stand.
I mean, they might have even done the it minutes, many series, I don't even know, but the current CBS, it's like, come on, man.
And why not do it like it, you know, it's so crazy that it, the it moves with the two biggest horror movies of all time, if I'm not mistaken.
So like, how they wouldn't just go, okay, so we'll do four stand movies, you know, like, why not three stand movie?
I don't know.
We'll ponder for good friend asks, what is your ranking of Christmas horror films you could do top three or just top pick?
Let's just do a top pick.
Yeah, there's actually, and looking at this recently, there's not that many great ones.
You think there is, but there's a lot of shit.
I'm going with Silent Night, Deadly Night 5, the Mickey Rooney one, because it is so fucking insane.
Oh, you watched it, finally.
We watched it. We reviewed it.
We talked about it on the show.
We talked about it on the show, but I don't think we had watched it.
I think we were talking about it like as a, can you believe this is what five is about?
I have a phone.
I definitely, maybe I did it in a movie corner then.
Yeah, I got the, I got the, I got part one and two on a set, and then I got three, four and five on a set.
Oh, right, right.
And five is, it's fucking crazy.
I'm going to watch it on to be crazy, but I mean, if you're talking quality heart, I wouldn't say it's a quality film.
It's just nuts and really fun to watch quality gremlins, 100%.
Yeah, there's nothing that even comes within a mile of gremlins.
You're a big black crest was fan, the ridge, but I love it.
I wouldn't put it as my use a little too disturbing to be like, let's throw this on every year.
Yeah, I think, you know, gremlins is one of the best ever blends of comedy and horror and the Christmas and the mix icing on the cake.
Kyle Kinsland asks, what was your most epic drop the mic and walk away moment?
And I'm assuming you don't mean just on the standup stage or something.
I would never do it on the standup stage.
I don't, I don't know, I don't know.
I usually have that drop the mic moment in my head while going to bed that night and what I actually did was nothing in the actual moment.
Yeah, mine's always like the stands are driving away.
That's what I should have said.
I mean, look, and I think I've set it on here.
I put it on Twitter the other day, but it was a big one for me was that interview for the Martha Stewart talk show.
They go, take, they go, this was a great meeting, but take 24 hours.
Come up for a promo as if Donald Trump was going to be Martha's guest on the show.
And I said, well, I don't need 24 hours.
There's Donald May rule the boardroom, but nobody trumps Martha in the kitchen.
And the lady extended her hand and offered me the job on the spot.
That was pretty exciting.
I had to eventually turn the job down as it offered 17 ,000 a year with extreme overtime.
I always fantasized about a drop the mic moment where somebody said, have you considered a public interview where somebody says,
have you considered apologizing for that joke?
And then I go, yeah, I'll apologize.
In fact, I have an apology ready. It's in my balls. Come get it out.
That's a fantasy I have.
I thought you were going to go with the reaching into your pocket and pulling out the middle finger.
Now I like the balls one.
No, it's better. It's my take on it.
Anyway, Drew Tiberius pull.
Wait a minute. Didn't he already ask one?
No.
Yeah, he did. He asked number four.
Well, just do the question job.
What are you, what are you, what are you, the question police?
You were just complaining that people were doubling up.
Go ahead.
You can't ask a number four and then a number 13.
Who would you cast to play yourself in a movie?
Paul Gianmati.
And I'll go Ryan Gosling.
I guess that wasn't so.
That's what people would want.
That's what people would expect to play.
I remember Jamie Lee used to tell me I look like Ryan Gosling.
No, like even my wife would laugh.
Yeah, I would be like, all of you need to shut up.
But I just Jamie, let's talk louder, Jamie.
I really appreciated it.
Evan quarrels asked, is listening to an audiobook?
Count is reading a book.
I mean, I think it does.
Who are they to judge me?
I think it does too.
I definitely don't get the same feeling of accomplishment as like closing a book.
But yeah, I love audiobooks.
So, and again, this Alan Partridge from the host house podcast is as good as it gets.
Please check it out.
I'm not getting any money from them.
Ethan Garall, I guess, Pat.
What is the best screenplay you've ever read?
And Joe, what's your favorite Super Nintendo game?
You know, I should read more screenplays.
I tend to just read those of my favorite movies.
So, I got a huge kick out of reading all the John Hughes scripts.
Somebody sent them to me a while back.
You're talking planes, trans, Uncle Buck, et cetera.
Because it is just like reading all these deleted scenes.
And it's so easy to imagine those characters doing them.
Beyond that, you know, you read Chinatown in film school.
And, you know, there's a reason they're famous.
They're beautiful scripts.
So, yeah, I should read more.
I don't read the ones that the writers guild sends me every year.
Well, because they'll send it'll be like Avengers Endgame plus the screenplay.
You're like, who gives a shit?
Yeah, I'm like, who sent me a Bible?
And I open it and I'm like, oh, it's just the screenplay for Avengers 12.
Yeah.
My favorite any Super Mario world, which somehow impossibly took Super Mario 3 and made it even better.
I think it's the pinnacle of all Super Mario games.
I think it's it was amazing to me that that was a launch title with the Super Nintendo.
I mean, talk about like as good as it gets.
It's like, hey, the new Nintendo's out.
And in the box with it is a new Super Mario Brothers game.
Like, yeah, it's a perhaps it's a childhood dream come true.
Did you play the as good as it gets name game for Super Nintendo?
Where you know, Jack Nicholson, you got to try to walk without stepping on the cracks.
Yeah, it's very, yeah, it's a bunch of mini games.
One of them is aligning your utensils.
It's not very fun.
Yeah.
People on your walk.
Right.
I thought the game where you, where you gave Ash Greg Keneer was in poor taste.
I couldn't agree more.
Phil Burrell asked Joe, did you see the new Zapadok?
Yes, I did.
I thought it was fantastic.
I think it's the best ever Zapadokumentary ever made.
Congrats to Alex winner on that.
And I think that there is probably out there a four hour version of this thing for diehard fans.
And I hope that that does get released.
And then Pat, he asks you,
who were some of your influences when you briefly did stand up?
Yeah, I also saw and really liked the new Zapadok despite still not loving the music of Frank's app.
Or even the man.
I just thought it was a good documentary.
I liked it a lot.
My influences, you know, I mean, I, it's the people I grew up watching.
You know, your Jerry Seinfelds, your, you know, a lot of the comedy I like.
I don't think really made it into my comedy like Chris Rock, Dave Shapel, etc.
I wasn't, um, I don't know.
I always feel like an idiot talking about influences, you know, but you sound like an idiot.
Yeah.
I mean, I did it for, for a year.
So.
All right.
Dave Krain asked, Joe, I'm also a big patent fan.
Patten.
I haven't read.
Mike Patten.
Mike Patten, I think my nose won't.
And I pop when you've mentioned him on the pod.
That's disgusting.
How did you get into patent?
What are some favorite projects?
And then there's another one for me.
All right.
I'll answer a patent.
I got into Mike patent.
Uh, King for a day full for a lifetime.
The third faith, no, faith, no more album that he was featured on.
Was one of those records that I heard in college.
Uh, when I was, no, I was high school.
Sorry, I was 17.
And it's one of those records that you hear when you're a teenager for me.
Um, and, and where you go, I hate this when you first hear it.
And then on the fourth time you hear it because your friend Dan won't stop playing it around you.
You're like, I think I love this.
So that was what was my gate.
That was the gateway for me into Mike Patten.
Uh, I then quickly acquired Angel Dust, which is often considered the masterpiece album of Faith No More.
Uh, I love that.
And I just got deeper and deeper into Faith No More.
And then because of Faith No More, I got into Mr. Bungle.
Um, and I just kept expanding outward and outward and outward.
So I love everything he does.
Uh, Faith No More is.
Well, no, that's not true.
Faith No More is my favorite band that he's in.
But Mr. Bungle, California is my favorite album of all time.
So I guess that would have to constitute a favorite project.
Okay.
Pat, without naming names, can you tell the skiviest encounter or story about the Hollywood elite that you've experienced or heard?
I mean, there's a million of them.
But one that stuck with me recently, it's one of the biggest shows on television.
That's all I'll tell you.
You'd know the show.
And I heard this story and it's been confirmed that in the writer's room,
there was a woman who was out on script.
And the room starts talking, which this was a recent, pretty recent story too.
But they start talking, hey, do you know that she, this female writer,
is having an affair with this male writer on the show.
They were both married.
And the room starts kind of talking about it and buzzing about it.
And everyone kind of is keeping it light like it's a joke.
And then the showrunner grabs the guy's phone when he goes to the bathroom and texts the woman,
a provocative message.
And she responds in kind to it, confirming the affair.
And he shows the whole room.
What an asshole. Why would he do that?
The showrunner is literally going into one of his employees phone and then playing a trick on a married woman to expose an affair.
So shit in front of the entire room.
And this guy still has his job.
But that's pretty skeevy, something I heard about.
Can you give us a network?
No, I don't know.
I'm not even supposed to know the story.
So the last thing I'd want is to be, you know, have to go talk at some trial or something.
But you'd know the show.
All right.
Tegan McLeod asks.
Yes.
If you had to swap out the main character in a movie for Alf.
What movie do you think he would fit into best and what movie would he stand out in most?
I can't even answer this.
I want him in Lenny.
The Lenny Bruce story.
I think he's got a natural stand up comedians.
You know what I never realized is Alf was probably inspired by Ronnie Dangerfield.
Yeah.
Yeah, of course.
That never crossed my mind.
Yeah.
And like a WC field is in there.
So maybe Alf and back to school would be nice as well.
No, it wouldn't.
It would be a worse version of back to school.
Alf was going to.
If we're going to do this, you know, I want to.
Peter Travers has already called it out of this world.
He's already reviewed it.
I'm going to go with the head.
Oh boy.
You know what?
I'll be changed this slightly.
I'm going to go with Kevin Bacon and sleepers.
I mean, is he using the nose on the kids?
I don't know, but just in that restaurant eating that meatloaf.
I taught you kids to be tough.
Yeah.
No, again, it sounds great.
There's not many movies that Alf wouldn't improve.
I will.
All right.
Heath Kane.
Heath Kane, excuse me, says cast your dream buddy cop movie.
I've been watching a lot of the old 70s ones lately where it's like, it's always either Elliott
Gould or George Segal.
And then, you know, they have our Alan Arkin.
And they got.
I watched one the other day with Robert Blake as one of the buddies convicted murder Robert
Blake and Gould.
It was called Busting, by the way.
It was the name of the movie.
No, dream buddy cop.
I guess what I'm trying to say is those are all serious actors doing comedy, much like with
Gosling and Crow in the nice guys.
And that's what I want to see more of.
Is not Zac Efron and the rock, you know, trying to be funny.
I like when serious actors loosen up.
You know, your midnight run is the perfect template for that.
I agree.
I want to see now Charles Grodon, 85 years old and now to Nero, 75 years old.
They were going to do it.
They were supposed to do it.
I would watch that in two seconds.
Look, nothing's going to ever beat if I get to cast this thing.
I'm going Eddie Murphy and Eddie Murphy.
We have to go Eddie Murphy and Eddie Murphy and Eddie Murphy.
And then he's playing a woman in the, in the pre -sync.
Eddie Murphy and some kind of fat suit.
Yeah.
And then like, you know, like in fact, I'll go Sherman Clump and Buddy Love next to each other.
I would hide, watch that.
I thought this was supposed to be the thin blue line.
He says when he shows up for the first day.
Oh, hell no.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
A lot of gags were the one side of the cars dragging.
The parks are coming out of it.
We're going a little broad with it.
Yeah.
I mean, that's that.
I would enjoy it thoroughly.
All right.
Braden Love.
Hello, the name asks favorite movie posters.
Isn't easy one for me.
All of the nightmare in Elm Street posters.
For three, four and five that the design they went with for those.
When they were doing like the dream state posters with like the floating claws and like a weird eyeball coming out of Freddy's head and like this ghostly Freddy and.
And the bodies of these teenagers sort of just they're floating and just very, very, very, very cool artwork.
And they were always my favorite movie posters I'd ever seen.
And me I'll go with one that just always makes me smile.
I have it in my kitchen.
It is playing trans -automobiles.
I love candy in the giant blue parko with his arm around Steve Martin spilling his coffee down the front of him.
It's just an iconic poster.
You look at it and you're like, I know what this is and I want to see it.
And that's what a poster should do.
Have we talked by the way?
I texted you about it.
But we haven't talked on the show yet about the deleted scene that I finally saw of playing.
We talked at length about it on the show.
We did.
Yeah.
Never mind.
Sorry.
Okay.
Next question.
Christian Reynolds asks, what do you think about, ooh, here's a juicy one.
What do you think about Warner Brothers releasing all their 2021 movies on HBO Max?
I could give a shit.
I don't have a problem with it.
I don't know.
I'm a little confused as to why everybody is so angry about it.
But I don't care.
Well, the filmmakers are disgusted like the guy who made Dune is like, look, I tried to create this giant world that I wanted people to experience in the theater.
And this is what you're doing.
I wasn't excited about any of the movies they're talking about, but I do think it's gross.
And I think it's one more nail.
And we're getting very, very close to the final nail in the coffin where the movie theater experience is done.
AMC is going out of business.
I do think it's a terrible, terrible thing.
I don't care so much about like, oh, I don't get to see Wonder Woman 2 on the big screen.
I didn't like the first one.
But I do think it's a huge mistake.
And it shows...
Well, what it shows is putting commerce about art, but that's what the business is.
But none of this is art.
None of this is art.
If you want to make art, maybe Dune's art.
Please.
Another fucking adaptation of this book.
I mean, it's like, come on, man.
I was thinking about this earlier today.
If you want to make art, you bleed, and you sweat, and you cry, and you rewrite, and you rewrite, and you re -edit, and you hone it away, hone, hone, hone, hone, hone, hone.
And you strive for protection, for perfection.
If you want to make money, you send out the first draft, and you don't think about it, because that's all this shit is.
So, like, it's...
It's...
I like a lot of it.
I find it very entertaining.
But, you know, and I do think it is tragic that movie theaters will close, but here is the thing.
Big movie theaters will close.
Arthouse theaters aren't going anywhere.
They'll reopen.
And new ones will open, and they'll play old movies that they're able to get their hands on.
You know, kind of like Tarantino's theater does.
And they'll play foreign films that they can get their hands on.
And they'll...
I think that'll have...
I have no doubt in my mind that that'll be the case.
What's...
It's a little hard to feel sorry for AMC crying poor house when they've gouged us at every fucking turn for the last 30 years.
It's hard for me to feel sorry for the director of Dune.
Like, what do you mean this business is choosing money over my picture?
It's like, you knew what the fuck this was.
You all know what the fuck it is.
You all turn a blind eye to it when it works in your favor.
And the second it burns you on the ass.
Now it's, you know, now it's screen bloody murder.
I'm sorry, I don't feel bad for any of them.
Walk the fuck away from Hollywood then.
Put your money where your mouth is.
Take your millions of dollars.
Go produce independent film.
Put it into a fucking theater that wants to screen it.
Drive around with your movie in the trunk like George Romero did or shut the fuck up.
That's it.
It's like working at Walmart and then crying that Walmart, you know, about Walmart policies.
You work at Walmart.
This is what it is. Hollywood is Walmart.
Right.
Get Walmart and shut up or don't.
That's it.
Right.
And I think, you know, the people who were upset that the Irishman came out on Netflix and the people who are upset about the streamers kind of infiltrating the movie business.
Are right to be upset.
I don't like it either.
But I know full well.
I'm trying to put together a film project now.
And I know full well.
You need Netflix.
You need Hulu.
You need these places.
And they're becoming the Maramax is the small studios that are, you know, willing to take a chance on smaller projects.
So there's pros.
There's cons.
I said from the, I said from the two year beginning point of, of the chip script process with, with the movie I'm trying to get made now.
I would rather this go to shutter and be made for shutter original.
Yeah.
It means we can do it right for the fans and people can see it in the way it's supposed to be seen.
Then take a chance of a, a major studio fucking this up.
And that's what I'm saying.
It's like everybody wants to go to heaven.
Nobody wants to die.
You know what I mean?
And it's like, so it's like these, these filmmakers that, that, that, that purposefully dive headfirst into this crazy studio system, that they know how it operates and everything.
You know, they know what this is all about for them to still boo who.
Get the fuck out of here.
I don't feel bad for any of them.
Yeah.
Walk away.
They can always cry on their millions.
You know what I'm saying?
It's the guy that, it's guy that cheats on his wife and then cries when she dumps him.
Sure.
You want to be alone?
Be a fucking man and be alone and, and go have sex.
Yeah.
I was actually just talking to that guy in my life the other night.
Kevin Regoti.
You can always count on me to really bring it to a place way too real.
Yeah.
Pat, can you tell us a classic Walsh family Christmas story?
I mean, I've told a bunch.
Have I ever talked about the, the Pulp Fiction soundtrack when I got that?
No.
But I mean, nothing's going to top the story you told earlier.
The husband and wife crying away on the river boat gambling.
Yeah.
I mean, I don't know how you're going to top that, but go ahead.
A real quick one, if I haven't, is that I, you know, the one year from my big gift,
I really wanted a boom box, a really nice stereo system, much like Radio Rahim.
And I got that.
It sounded great.
And among the CDs I asked for were the Pulp Fiction soundtrack.
And I was like, hey, if you're not going to let me see the movie, at least I can do the soundtrack.
So I get it and they're like, let's hear it.
Let's hear it on the, on the new sound system.
Come on, put it in.
So it's me, my little sister, who's probably 11 at the time.
My parents and I put in the soundtrack, push play.
Any of you fucking bricks move.
And I'll execute every last motherfucking one of you.
And my mom and dad dove for the machine.
They made me return the thing.
It was the first time they had noticed the parental advisory sticker.
And that was it.
I had to return it to the store and I eventually bought it when I was in college or something like that.
So this is the second story of your family buying you an extravagant gift.
But skimping on Play -Doh.
A stereo and a CD?
They skimped on Play -Doh.
Yeah, no, I know.
I think, honestly, what I think it was is my dad would be laid off or lose his job constantly.
He was a construction worker.
He would get fired or quit out of anger all the time.
And there were definitely, you know, experiences where we were getting ready to leave for like Disney World.
And the trip would be canceled because he had lost his job.
I think it was that kind of thing.
The money wasn't there.
Some months it was there, et cetera.
Jared Smallridge asks Pat.
No question.
Just wanted to say what a pleasure it was to hang for a bit with you and your lovely wife after the NYC show this year.
It was definitely the highlight of this shit year.
You believe that was this year?
Feels like college.
I can't.
I was there.
Where was I?
I guess I didn't hang out.
Yeah, I was somewhere else.
Joe, what was it like to work on wet -hot American summer series?
Any good anecdotes?
It was a pleasure.
It was a dream come true in certain ways.
I was always a big fan of the movie.
It was great to get to work with Michael Shaw while they're in David.
David Wayne.
You know, I was a big fan of the state growing up.
So I had a great time.
And there and a lot of other involved in a lot of other projects that I've often been a fan of.
So it was great.
I met a lot of really great writers.
And it was exciting to write things that eventually you, you know,
a year later saw Elizabeth Banks saying.
Right.
You know, it was kind of wild.
It was certainly my first step into that like wider arena.
So I had a great time.
And no, no anecdotes really.
It was a very short process.
And it was, it was fun.
That was it.
Really.
That's all there is to it.
Okay.
Next.
Is it me?
Am I reading it?
Yeah.
Okay.
This is one of my dear friends, Mikey Madrigal.
Go to his, he's got Mr. Shoot Records and Lancaster PA.
Hello, Mike.
I wish I could go to a record store right now.
That's where I really want to go when this ends.
I'll tell you that.
Best and worst music biopics, biopics, or documentaries.
I mean, a music biopic is one of my least favorite genres.
I like them more than political biopics.
But, you know, I think if I'm being real, I got to say walk hard.
It's so beautifully parodies, music biographies, in such a loving way.
The songs are good, the acting's good.
I'm going to go with that one, even though it's fake.
I'm going to pick worst.
And I haven't seen it yet, but I'm going to bet money on it.
And the man's a friend of mine.
That Mark Marin Bowie thing coming out looks.
Yeah, it looks rough.
Fucking terrible.
I mean, they're hitting every cliche note in the trailer.
David, you're not from out to space.
Yeah.
You know, and then the other guy going, David, if they don't accept you,
create someone that looks, I mean, it's just, you know,
and then like them sitting in the car and Marin being like,
this is the one radio station that likes you.
Don't say anything crazy.
Yeah, you know, it's just, it's just, oh my god.
It looks terrible.
There's so many of them that are just fine.
You know, like nine times out of 10, you watch one and it's fine.
And the reason one I liked that everybody hated was Bohemian Rhapsody.
I really liked that a lot.
David Belinger asks, if you could be transported into any TV show or movie,
what would it be?
You know, obviously for me, movie wise, it's going to be star wars every time.
Okay.
TV show.
I'd love to be part of the Frazier family.
Yeah, I mean, I'd enjoy having a beer at Cheers, you know.
No, no, no, I don't want to have a beer at Cheers.
I want to be part of Frazier's family.
But I'm saying my choice.
Oh, oh, oh, sorry, I'm sorry.
Much rather than hanging out with those uptight snobs would be to get a little dose of Frazier
but also get to see everybody else.
And they know my name.
And they're glad I came.
Mick Mack asks, what's Joe's favorite sandwich from his sandwich shop?
And here's a good question.
Does Pat get a sandwich on the next menu and what would it be?
A most proud of the Eastie and the beefy.
The menu is online.
You can go look and see what those are.
I like the queasy.
But the Eastie and the beef here are my two, probably my two favorites.
I'm very proud of those and they sell well, which makes me feel really good.
And does Pat get a sandwich on the next minute?
It depends.
I name the sandwiches after items or people that they are related to.
So there's a sandwich on the menu called the Rosie, which is named after my mom,
because it's my mom's favorite sandwich.
And the dad is named after my dad, obviously.
So if some, if Pat really, how about the patty and it's two all beef patties?
Not something I do.
Not something I'd make.
But you know, there's always a chance.
How about the patty and it's it's a standard classic Italian,
but you line the top piece of bread with York peppermint patties.
Now, now this is something I could get into.
Okay.
My order has shipped.
I just got an eBay.
So what?
I just got an eBay notification of my phone.
My order has shipped.
What did you get?
I purchased last night a reproduction of the Texas Chainsaw Massacre Atari 2600 game.
Okay.
What you do.
It is so out of print that the reproduction was $100.
Okay.
The original copies of itself were starting itself for $5000.
And that's just the cartridge only.
I bought a reproduction of it from a nice lady on eBay.
She did a really nice job.
And she was even kind enough to message me afterwards and said,
you know, this isn't an original, right?
This is a repro and I wrote back.
Yeah, this is as close as I'm ever getting to an original.
But I can't wait to get it.
And she did a nice job.
Yeah, looks nice.
Comes in a nice box that she made that looks like the original box and the cartridge looks like a
original Atari cartridge.
And you know, as a horror fan and a video game fan,
how do you not own a copy of the Texas Chainsaw Massacre for the Atari 2600?
It's insane that the game was ever even made.
Yeah.
Is it super violent?
I mean, for Atari, it is, you know, it's not a great game.
Right.
But it's just kind of one of those things you want to have it on your shelf, you know.
For the ladies.
For the ladies, you know,
again, you know, I like to pick and choose what goes on display.
And Jeremy Griffin asks, do you have a favorite episode you've recorded together?
If so, why that one?
And what is your least favorite?
I mean, the least favorite's got to be the one where we almost ended the podcast and the friendship.
We were just at both at very tense, miserable points.
You've heard this.
And I know a lot of people asked to hear the footage, but you don't want to leave it.
It's been deleted.
It turned it out.
It turned into the Logan episode.
Yeah.
The original recording of that was, was, was, was, yeah, I agree.
That's least fair.
My favorite episode.
I really often, and it's often reminded, I'm reminded of it.
I enjoyed the one where I really made fun of Pat's sweater that he was wearing that he was giving his dead.
I just thought that was a nice moment on the show where you saw two friends.
Yeah.
You're having a good time.
I mean, Pat wasn't having fun, but I liked that one less.
No, there's a bunch.
I mean, I had the biggest laughs recently, just because it randomly came up on my phone, listening to the,
the young stories.
Yeah.
Which one of the many podcast studios we were on, unfortunately put a giant ad in the dead center of that story,
and I hope that's gone away.
But they do good work, don't they?
But that one's great.
I mean, I've heard some, some best of's, but like, I need to sort of figure out how to edit and put together like my true official best of,
maybe I'll do that sometime soon.
Patrick Monster asks, could you please act out a scene of Sam Elliott going to pick up his laundry,
but he has misplaced the ticket receipt needed to pick up clothes.
I mean, this isn't, this isn't a pitch.
This isn't a question.
And then he adds another thing.
Pat is saying.
He's casting it.
Okay, Pat is saying, Joe is the laundry clerk, who is just not having it today.
If no, then I'd just like to say hi, and I love you guys.
Thank you for making life better.
All right.
Well, thank you, Patrick, for putting the little, you know, yeah, the B option.
Yeah.
You know, I had a pair of blue jeans and a sort of leather vest there.
Being dry cleaned, and I can't for the life of me find a ticket.
Oh, no.
And we go through this every week, Mr. Elliott, you can never find the ticket.
I've told you a dozen times now, you come in with the ticket or that's it.
No ticky, no sticky.
Who else has a leather vest?
I see it there right behind him.
Well, I don't know.
That could be yours.
Could be somebody else's.
I have no idea.
So now you're going to have to wait until we get everybody else's orders out.
The people responsible enough to remember their tickets.
And then if that leather vest is still sitting here, I will give it to you.
Sweetheart, do me a favor.
And I know you're a man.
I'm calling you sweetheart because you seem like a real bitch.
You know this kind of behavior got your co -star in trouble.
No, he raped a woman.
He raped a woman.
I'm trying to get my leather vest.
They're pretty different offenses.
Why don't you grab that leather vest and tell me if there's not a monogrammed S -J -E.
Won't do it.
I can show you my life.
Step aside.
I've got a line.
Show you that my middle name is jibbidiah.
Sam jibbidiah Elliott.
Now, if you get step aside, I have a line.
Oh, I thought you meant a line in the sketch that we're doing.
No, no.
I mean, not only does he give us a sketch, he gives you the thing and improv you're never supposed to do.
He's telling me to know you.
Yeah.
I was, uh, I also realized that I was doing, um, curl from slingblade.
I've lost my Sam Elliott over quarantine.
I need to get it back.
All right.
Your turn.
Jake Payne.
Who I believe isn't Jake Payne a video game hero?
Max Payne.
That's Max Payne.
Joe, I've heard you mentioned the herb cratum often on the pot, cratum often on the pod.
I don't think I've heard it.
Or I don't remember it.
Do you still take it and have you had any negative effects?
Uh, we got more questions.
How did your eraser head Halloween costume turn out?
Did you do it?
I didn't do it.
All I did on Halloween was I put on a Freddy Krueger t -shirt and I went to, uh, two bars with my friend Paul.
And we got fucked up in ways.
I can't even explain right now.
You did it.
Do I still take creative?
I occasionally not, not, not frequently.
Um, did I ever have negative effects?
No, I never did.
But other people have.
So if you're going to take it, you really need to research it.
Uh, you really need to make sure you know what you're getting that it's been lab tested and approved and all that stuff.
Um, and you, you got to be careful with that stuff.
Uh, John Wolf asked, have any of your past ratings slash hogs changed?
If so, which titles have you reversed?
Depending on Pat, did your dad like the North Face jacket?
That's a quick answer.
He liked it.
I've never seen him wear it.
So here, somebody just brought that up.
I just taught.
I know.
Okay.
He said he liked it.
Never saw him wear it.
Um, yeah.
I mean, some ratings of mine have definitely changed.
I think the big one was.
Hellraiser 2.
I bailed out on that soil mattress.
Suicide scene.
I was like, life's too short.
Was my thought at the time.
It just kind of was like, my life was just so miserable.
I was like, I don't need to watch this.
And then I watched it when Joe Bob did it and absolutely loved it.
And now I own it.
So that was a huge reversal.
And I'll, I'll offer another Pat reversal.
Because I'm blanking on mine.
I'm sure I've had one or two or three or four.
Uh, but I'll offer another one.
And you reversed on you reversed on pet cemetery.
Twice.
You had said you loved it.
And then you watched it so we could review it.
And then when we reviewed it, you said, it's not good, man.
It's rushed.
And it's this and that.
And then we saw the remake and you were exactly saying that the original was pretty good.
Yeah.
I mean, when once you see how low the bark and go, sometimes you're like, oh, okay.
I love pets after.
Uh, the only reason I, I don't, I think I didn't love it.
The, what we talked to a whole episode about it.
But I had just read the book and the book.
I think it is maybe Stephen King's best.
So you were mad they left out that sex scene.
Yeah.
The weird bathtub jack.
Stuart Garrity asked, my girlfriend has a completely different taste in films, TV shows, etc.
For me, I've either viewed out with this problem and any tips on how we can find stuff to watch together.
Uh, I don't really have any look.
No, I do.
I have had the, I have run into this.
And I have found that it has never been a problem because I think if you show the person,
and I don't mean this selfishly, I mean genuinely, that you have it a true excitement.
To introduce them to something that they're not familiar with.
Um, that person usually is excited to see it because they like,
they like you for a reason.
They find you interesting and they want to, they want to experience this thing that gets you all excited.
Now they might not like it.
But they're usually willing to, to, to check it out.
Now, if you're in a situation of where it's just like somebody saying, I hate horror,
I can't watch it.
And you love horror.
You're kind of shit out of luck on that one.
And I will tell you this, I've not proceeded in relationships over stuff like that.
So I'm like, what are we going to do?
Like we got to, you know, there are people like that.
Like our buddy Vince won't watch horror.
You know, but if it's your, your spouse or your person, in my opinion,
you watch horror when your significant other goes to bed,
you watch it on your own time, and you come together when you can find middle ground.
I, I know what you're saying that you guys have different tastes,
but there's got to be certain things that you just both want to watch.
And, you know, when a show comes out like Queens Gambit or something,
that's when Heather and I are like, look, these are of us give a shit about chess.
Everyone says this is good.
Let's sit down and watch this together.
You could, you know, let the public decide if everybody loves something,
let that be the thing you guys watch together.
What?
This guy's name is awesome.
Where are we at?
Lawrence Crazy Horse, Anderson.
Anderson is what makes it for me.
Yeah.
Anderson, a name as plain as Anderson up against Crazy Horse is really funny, man.
It is good.
Maybe hopefully his real name, I don't know.
Well, you guys be doing more live shows after the pandemic is over.
If so, what city do you think you do it in?
May I suggest San Francisco or Sacramento?
You may suggest both.
I would love to come to both.
And I think we'll definitely do, I think we'll do a return to Chicago
and a return to LA and a return to New York also.
So yes.
Yeah.
Heather's from Sacramento.
I'm up there often.
That and San Francisco would both be very easy for me.
Less easy for Joe.
I would love to do a St. Louis show.
I know we would pack that with my old friends there.
But, you know, there's travel costs and everything too.
But we do definitely want to do that for sure.
I'd love to do Philly too.
Yes.
You guys have been a great source of relief from the stress school.
The school has caused and law school.
Graduate in a couple months.
Congratulations.
Oh, you both a huge thank you for helping keep me sane.
So thank you.
You're greatly appreciate it.
And I appreciate here and that means a lot.
It means a lot to me too.
Glad we could get another lawyer out into the world.
I'm just kidding.
Congrats, buddy.
That's a huge undertaking.
Chris Marsh.
Do either of you struggle with self doubt?
Have you listened to the show?
Yeah.
When do I not?
Do you compare yourselves to friends and contemporaries?
Yes.
Yeah.
Even though you give other people relief, thank you.
What gives you relief?
Nothing gives me relief.
To be honest, it used to be movies and music and even they don't work anymore.
It used to be weed.
That doesn't work anymore.
But all I do is struggle with self doubt and compare myself to friends and contemporaries.
And I never noticed the ones in my life who are struggling
as much or worse than I am.
I only focus on the ones who are doing well.
And it's the worst thing you can do.
They say comparison is the thief of joy or the enemy of joy or something.
And there's nothing truer.
It makes you miserable, but I can't help it.
I'm an envious of Pat's answer.
And I don't think I could do as good of a job.
Did it?
I texted this to someone the other day.
It might have been you, Pat.
I don't remember.
But I wrote the word, we're in a tough time, obviously, everybody.
We all are.
But I wrote the words.
I'm at the point where I just have fleeting moments of, of, of, of brief joy in the depths of drunkenness.
Yeah.
That's kind of all it is at this point.
Oh, I can ask for it.
I'm not miserable all day.
Yeah.
But like, like, the, like, you know, I can be, I can be content and, and not upset, you know, but that's kind of as good as it gets.
If you're talking like, no, but, but what about moving the needle into happy.
That usually takes some type of, yeah, some substance abuse.
Yeah.
It's pretty much off the table at this point.
Aaron Eskietz asked, what was a present you wanted the most for Christmas or a birthday,
but your parents wouldn't purchase for you.
And, you know, another one popped in much like the, the clay dough.
I wanted the tournament table, if you'll remember, which had air hockey, ping pong, and something else.
But it was a huge item, maybe the year I was 10 or 11.
And I asked for that, and my parents got me the knockoff version of that, which was like Chinese checkers, backgammon.
It was cheaply made, and we just got a lot of stuff like that.
They would give you their version.
They could afford of what you asked for, which in many ways was sadder than, than getting it not at all.
I know exactly what this is.
And it haunts me to this day to the point where I've gone on eBay and looked at it to consider purchasing it and only stopped to be like, oh, my mom was right.
I wanted the he man slime pit as a kid.
It was a he man toy.
It was the, the hoard where like these new, this new gang of villains that they introduced into he man.
And they had a thing called the slime pit where they would take their prisoner and put lock him into this throne.
And there was a big like dinosaur mouth skull at the top of the throne.
And you hit a lever and it would puke slime down on the action figure.
I mean, when you're eight, yeah, this is as good as it gets.
I mean, this is, this is everything you want.
It's gross. It's awesome.
It's got a skull.
Like, come on.
And my mom wouldn't buy it for me.
She was like, that's a piece of junk. I'm not buying you that piece of junk.
That's a waste.
And she wouldn't get it for me.
And then my friend Kevin Lutz got it.
And I was so jealous.
And then I, and then I, he also got it at a birthday party.
I was not invited to.
So I never even got to play with his.
And I just, it was, that was it.
I just never, you know, I never got the slime pit.
And then recently meeting within the last year, I went on to eBay.
And I was like, I'm buying one of these fucking things.
And I saw it and I was like, that's all it is.
Like it is a piece of shit.
So I didn't get it.
Also, what would I do with it?
It's like, you know, you can't,
this is people always ask me, why do you love these video game systems?
Why do you have so many video game systems?
Because they're toys that you can play with.
That's it. That's all it is.
Right.
Like I light up when I see cool toys.
I, you know, old Star Wars toys and things like that.
And then I go, what would I do with it?
I can't play with it.
You know, like, and I don't want something that just sits on a shelf.
Right.
Like, I don't know, an old video game system or any video games,
it's a toy you can play with.
It's interactive art.
Like so what's not to like, you know, but anyway, that's it.
Fair enough.
I just want to tell you Joe.
So I, but the most important meeting I've had all year yesterday was cancelled.
45 minutes before it started.
They always are.
You told me that.
Yeah.
And just now while I'm talking to you, because I'm supposed to, they were like,
all right, let's get it in before Christmas tomorrow.
We apologize so much.
Let's do it tomorrow.
I said, great.
130 tomorrow.
And I just received the notification that that's cancelled.
The time they are offering now, January 18th.
I know it.
I just know it.
Of course.
This was like the one meeting that was going to remove some anxiety from my life.
Like get a game plan together.
And now I got to wait a month.
Now I have a meeting tomorrow about a new script.
And I'm, I, I actually want to postpone it because I'm rushing from a,
a COVID test to get home for this thing.
And I'm just.
Yeah.
It's making me nervous.
Sure.
But then you postpone and you got to do it after Christmas.
Anyone can't postpone.
Yeah.
You, you got to let them do it.
Well, anyway, I'm.
I'm out of this terribly shit year we've had.
I think there's your answer.
I mean, not there is not one single thing or one aspect of life that has improved this year.
Everything has gotten worse.
And I truly, truly mean that.
My only relief.
Not only.
I mean, but, but the, my favorite thing, the, the bright spot for me.
Has been the good people at Lucas films.
Altering the course of action with Star Wars and making awesome, awesome fan friendly announcements.
For Star Wars.
So the most recent was they announced Hayden Christensen will be portraying Darth Vader in the Obi -Wan Kenobi miniseries.
And then two days later, you and McGregor came out and said, we're going to fight again in the series.
They don't worry.
Like stuff like that that's happening with Star Wars right now.
And happening as many series and Disney plus TV shows versus theatrical releases.
It's like such a pivot for Lucas film because they obviously understand the direction the business is heading in.
And instead of punishing people with it, they're going no, we'll just change it and make it.
We'll just adapt to this environment is, is pretty impressive and astounding to me.
And I think it's pretty cool, even though I hate Disney.
I, I am a member of Disney plus because of Lucas films.
So that's the one kind of cool thing that that was a sort of a byproduct of all this.
Outside of that.
Yeah, not much, man, not much.
Yeah.
My answer is goose egg, nothing.
Jessica Longo asked, who would you have cast as the colonel in the movie lifetime made that we didn't know we needed?
So I believe this is referring to the new Mario Lopez colonel Sanders romantic thing.
It's got to be some sort of joke.
It is.
It's a, it's a short film.
It's a 15 minute short film.
And it's a promotion for a KFC thing.
It's a cross promotion.
It's a joke.
I mean, I was thrilled when Norma Donald was the colonel and to see him in a romance would be a thrill.
I think a fantastic colonel would be Kevin James.
He's got a little meat on him.
A lot of meat.
Yeah.
I mean, I mean, if you see pictures of the actual colonel, he was a robust man.
He wasn't like, or a ton man, excuse me.
He wasn't, you know, he wasn't like, anyway, thin.
Maybe I cast Roseanne as a progressive, you know, you do like a trans take on it.
They did read the McIntyre as one of them.
Oh, they did already.
Harry, they beat me to it.
Taylor Sprouls asks, this is aimed more towards pet.
All right.
Well, I'll go fuck myself getting, but feel free to comment as well, Joe.
Would you ever eat the leftovers of your significant others cold breakfast cereal if offered?
Ooh, that's disgusting.
I personally feel in doing so is a crime against humanity.
Yeah.
You don't feel bad, Joe.
He didn't want you to answer because you don't have a significant other.
See, see, you're all alone.
It's weird that that does sound so disgusting because like, it's one of those things where like,
you'll make out with somebody, but then sharing their toothbrush is weird, you know.
It's Seinfeld almonds in the mouth thing.
It's gross.
There's something gross about it was in their mouth.
Now it's out of their mouths.
It's gross.
Like, it's just, I don't know what it is.
It's like, it's slopping out of the mouth back into the bowl, etc.
Would I do it?
Yeah.
If you're saying, would I like to do it?
No.
Mason Scan asks, would you guys please do a commentary episode on Mothman pack and talk about what could have been,
Joe can enjoy the cheese.
It's on YouTube.
Look, I get it.
I see, you know, when I was on the social media more, I saw the request from Mothman.
I get it.
I know that you think that I would have some sort of like really funny recollections about it.
The truth is, me and my old writer partner wrote a really good, exciting, funny script.
Then had to in like a day just make it into this shitty version of itself that we don't recognize or endorse.
So like, I wouldn't have any emotional ties to it at all.
I wouldn't know what was happening or what was coming up in each scene.
I have no ties to it.
I never want to watch it again.
And not because it's painful to me.
I just know that it sucks.
And I hate that my name's on something that sucks like that.
But it's not that it hasn't been before.
Did you say it was funny?
Did you say our original version?
I mean, there are notes where guys this is great.
We get what you're going.
It's like a tremors type thing.
But they're like, we don't do comedy.
We need a death at each act break.
There are eight act breaks.
That's where we want the deaths, you know.
So they had this formula that we were just unaware of.
And it's a soulless, non -enjoyable.
It's not so bad.
It's good.
You know, there's nothing to recommend.
So I don't want to watch it again, Frank.
What's it called?
Mothman.
It's just called Mothman.
Yes.
Oh, it is on YouTube and you got to rent it.
I'm not paying for this thing.
Oh, no, it's free.
It's free.
I'm on YouTube now trying to find it.
I mean, watch that thing.
Somebody, one of the hellians gave me a DVD at the live show,
which I appreciate.
You know, maybe when I'm an old and gray,
I'll take it out.
But that's what I'm trying to explain to you is I won't recognize any lines of dialogue in it or anything
because I don't have any attachment to the movie at all.
Melinda Ring asks, what is your take on home for the holidays?
I never saw it.
It seems like a flick you guys might agree on.
What do you think of the performances now that you're real?
I'm sorry.
I've never seen it.
Home of the holidays is my second favorite Thanksgiving movie.
I think it is fantastic.
My dad took me to see it in the theater.
And I think it's Robert Downey Jr.
Downey Jr. Charles Durning and Bankroft Holly Hunter.
Steve Gutenberg.
It's an amazing cast.
It's very, very funny.
The romance is good.
The comedy is good.
The drama is good.
I really love that movie.
Jesse White asks, do either of you remember the first R -rated movie you went to at the theater?
I do.
It was a double feature.
Oh, blues, brothers, and American.
Where were often London?
Orlando's.
Double feature.
Yes.
The first R -rated movie I saw in the theater was diehard with a vengeance at the dollar show.
I begged my parents.
I was 14, I think.
And finally, they caved.
I was just like, he's running through the city.
Nobody could be naked in it.
It's just got to be violence.
He's running through the city.
Right.
So that was it.
I saw a Rambo 3 at the drive -in with my parents.
That's the first one I remember.
And I remember desperately waiting for the I'm your worst nightmare line to come up.
Because I felt that me and my dad would laugh and bond over how cool that line was.
And we did.
It was a nice moment.
Good.
Chris Cicac.
If you could have one superpower, what would it be?
Favorite city to travel to outside of California, New York.
Flight.
Philadelphia.
You could use your power to go to Philadelphia.
Well, he's not saying that's, you got to use your power to go.
I was just making a nice little transition.
Being a smart ass.
Yeah.
Mark Mouth.
Yeah, it's hard to argue.
Flight.
I mean, what a dream.
And again, I'm going to go with, you know, I love Austin.
But Kauai is the best city in America.
In Hawaii.
It's the most beautiful.
It's like going to Jurassic Park.
Jesse White, without the dinosaurs mind you.
Jesse White asks, what is your favorite opening credit sequence to a movie?
You know what?
Don't even have to think about it.
It's when good.
It's when.
In departed.
When like 30 minutes in, the titles come up.
I just remember.
I laughed out loud that the titles were starting a half hour into the movie.
It was so crazy.
And then just something I love about that.
I just rewatched the departed and that lit me up.
That's one of my favorite things about that movie is that decision.
So I would, I would go with that.
I would.
I have to get the number one to good fellows.
I mean, it's just the slam.
Almost said good.
Yeah.
Like it's just, it's just the best opening ever to a movie.
Yes.
All right.
Ben.
Right.
Yeah.
Ben Lee.
Australian pop sensation.
Probably.
Who has written not one, but four questions.
Well, let's do them one.
Let's lightening around favorite drinking game.
I guess quarters.
Beer pong.
Yeah.
I guess beer pong.
Any thoughts on quibi crashing and burning?
Good.
You know, good riddance.
They designed a whole network over screwing over riders.
You can read into it.
It's gross.
Could a short form streaming service work in the future?
It could if it wasn't run by Hollywood.
And I just feel like people are like, I got you two, but I don't, I don't need this.
I don't think anyone's interested in short form streaming.
Especially if they're not blowing all the cash paying seven figures for Reese Witherspoon
to narrate nature documentaries.
Yeah.
I mean, some of the footage I've seen from some of those shows.
It's like this thing deserved to go down.
And everybody involved is going to be fine.
So it's hard not to.
Yeah.
Fuck you.
Goodbye.
I agree.
A loop of Peter Pichecco asks is on with the Joe gone forever.
Ooh.
You know, it hasn't been a conscious choice.
I think I just got burned out.
But I'm not going to do it now because it be forced.
But I will bring it back in 2021.
You.
Next, Joe.
Luke Physioc.
Pat.
Matt, would you say the best way to navigate the criterion channel?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I read that wrong.
Pat, what would you say is the best way to navigate the criterion channel?
Everything I've seen tends to be good, but it's kind of intimidating because they don't use
genre all that much.
I was just going to let you.
Yeah.
No.
It's the criterion channel.
I think in terms of content is second to none, especially if you're like getting into film history.
It's the best.
However, it is terribly set up.
And, you know, I wind up with two of the same movie in my queue all the time.
Which is like, why is that even possible?
You know, like I'm going through my queue and I'll have two of the same thing.
So they need an overhaul.
I think the best way to navigate it, though, my recommendation is to do it on the website.
Do it that way on your laptop or you have more control and you're not using the annoying Apple TV remote to try to get around.
And the best way to actually see what they have and the only way to see what they have, which is nuts,
is to go to A to Z and actually look at their entire list of films.
And you can only do that online for some reason.
So I agree with you.
They have problems.
Joe recently got a Wii U.
Got Mario Kart Zelda Breath of the Wild.
Any other recommendations?
Yeah.
Yeah, I get Super Mario U Deluxe Super Mario Brothers U Deluxe is great.
Get the deluxe one because that has the Luigi version of the game, like these sort of unofficial sequel to it.
But that's a lot of fun.
What else to have for my Wii over there?
I can't really see Captain Toad is kind of.
Captain Toad puzzle tracker, something like that is a lot of fun.
And Rayman is really great on it.
Donkey Kong Country Tropical Freeze.
Those are your those are your big hits.
I'd say check out.
Okay.
Book Adams asked any recent vinyl recommendations.
I've been revisiting the AC DC catalog.
And I think that that's just you can't really go wrong with all the bond Scott records up through the Brian John.
And stuff up through flick of the switch.
I think that's, you know, that's about an eight record run.
And I think you if you're into that kind of thing, you're going to really have a nice time.
I would also highly recommend the entire T Rex catalog.
I have listened to T Rex lately myself.
The slider is a fantastic album.
And those ones that came after they get like no lover and peccable pop rock albums are really great.
My recent sort of discovery was Marvin Gaye's Hear My Deer, which is an album he wrote while going through a horrible divorce.
It also name checked Star Wars, by the way.
But it's so much better than what's going on in these albums that are like considered the best ever whatever he's done way better work, I think, than what's going on.
But Hear My Deer is a dark, funny, double album.
It's very, very like cool, funky.
I hate to use the word funky, but it is.
It blew my mind.
I immediately bought the vinyl off eBay for 20 bucks.
It's on Spotify though.
Hear My Deer loved it.
They say he gets down with his bad self.
I would.
Yeah, they apparently he was like, my wife gets half this next album.
So I'm just going to turn out a turd, you know, like who cares if she's getting the half the money anyway, what do I care.
And then at the last minute, he was like, no, instead, I'm going to make the whole album about her and how much I hate her.
So he did.
And then she tried to sue about the content of that album and so on and so forth.
Love spite.
It's great.
All right.
There's light at the end of the tunnel, Joe, we're nearing the end.
You guys had so many questions.
And these are all good questions.
Thank you so much.
And thank you.
For more via.
By the way, there's four more via.
Okay.
Janet O 'Loughlin C asks favorite 90 day fiance couple favorite trash TV binge watches.
Never saw 90 day.
So I couldn't speak to it.
I am finally done.
I finally got burnt out on it.
But for a long time, I was, I thought I had discovered just the best thing on earth.
It's very addictive.
And of course, my favorite couple is.
You know, the girl who Coltie Colt and Larissa are the best couple.
And I should say Colt Larissa and Colt's mother who really make up that couple.
But they are some of the most fascinating people I've ever seen on TV.
And other than that, I, I got to be honest, I really got into Vanderpump rules.
Eventually, after about six seasons, I had had enough.
But those are my two trash TV ones.
I got a lot of favorite TV binge watches.
I don't think anything is ever quite top.
The excitement of stranger things with the first two seasons of that.
I couldn't like pull myself away.
But that's not trash TV.
Oh, trash.
I didn't see that trash TV binge watches.
I don't watch any trash TV.
What do you want me to say?
All right.
No, I don't watch.
I can't watch reality TV.
It makes me, I get visibly angry.
I can't do it.
It's, it's, and I don't watch like, you know, intervention or any of that shit.
Like, I don't know.
I'm just, I'm just not into it.
If I had to pick one, it would be cops.
I would watch your house.
I would binge cops.
Cops is, is a wild watch.
But even that, I don't care enough to binge watch it.
But I have.
Yeah.
And I guess I'll give it to that.
J, oh, wait, wait, did I ask that?
No, my turn, right?
Yeah.
J Miller asks, Joe, have you played the game inside?
I have not, I've heard of it.
It looks good, but I've not played it.
Seems like it'll be right up your alley, considering how much you praise a little nightmares.
Pat, can you please make your NBC page stories a monthly installment?
Yeah, I don't think we'll put it on like the schedule.
But I'll definitely try to pepper some more in because I've got some good ones for you, for sure, that I've never told on here.
And it's, I like to just make sure I keep my memory alive, you know?
Sometimes you don't think about something from 2003.
It's gone.
Chris, that's a tough name, Chris.
Chris Schwalgy, I believe, asks, have either of you ever been asked to join a Scientology or Transcendental Meditation Group?
Yes, both.
I have not.
But well, I mean, I was asked to join.
I'm open to it.
I was asked to join Scientology by the people in the street.
I mean, it wasn't like a friend asked me or anything.
Right.
Transcendental Meditation, I was suggested heavily by a friend that I should join.
And I said, I'm paying a thousand dollars to get a word to repeat.
Right.
And you're also telling me in the same breath, there's no wrong way to do this.
I'll pass.
But you might meet David Lynch.
Do you want to?
I do.
I mean, do you want to?
Briefly.
And then I want a conversation to be over, but be a disappointment.
Scott Birchett.
Birchett.
That's the TV show of 2020.
Or you do two in a row.
You're doing two.
You just said the last one.
I thought, I didn't know you alternate, but you did it because you said, remember, you said, that's a tough name, Chris.
Oh, you're right.
Sorry.
That's okay.
Just go for it.
I mean, we don't have to strictly do that.
It's just like Monica and Brandy on the boy's mind where everyone has.
Did you know they each had to have the exact same amount of syllables on that song?
Yeah.
Did you know that Monica actually got mad at Brandy during the shoot because Brandy put her hand in her face?
I did.
You don't do that to me.
And it's like, it's a fucking dumb thing.
It's not real.
Yeah.
Best TV show of 2020.
For me is normal people.
The Mandalorian.
All right.
Kevin Marcenic.
Any recent quarantine shame eating stories.
Oh, God.
Yeah.
I mean, that could be a monthly installment.
It did just terrible.
Went and got a chocolate cake at Trader Joe's the other night.
I couldn't find one.
It was by the way, my third stop.
I went to three different grocery stores.
Because I couldn't find what I was looking for.
And nothing that the other stores had was in quotes good enough for me.
Meaning indulgent enough.
I was just.
It doesn't look like I want like chocolate cake.
And then I finally I went to Trader Joe's third.
And the shelves of the desserts were pretty bare.
It was late at night.
And just by like the grace of God, I saw out of the corner of my chocolate cake sitting on a low shelf and it was shoved all the way back.
So somebody had missed it.
So I had to get down on my hands and knees, fighting a rat for it.
Yeah.
Drag it out.
Then I wasn't sure that it was exactly what I wanted because it had a strange name on it.
So I googled the cake that now I'm doing research in the Trader Joe's.
Yeah.
To make sure it's what I want.
And I saw it was what I wanted brought it home and I texted you Pat.
I ate about half in one sitting and I had to stop myself from going any farther.
Yeah.
And for me, it was seeing these pictures of Joe's sandwiches deciding I wanted to get into sandwiches and then having a week where I just ate a lot of sandwiches.
Including one car, one meal that was a two sandwich.
Don't leave out in your car.
Yeah, I did have some of the sandwiches in my car.
Not all but some.
And now I'm already past the sandwiches.
I just, I had to get it out of my system.
They were delicious.
Now here are, and here are the last four from the thing.
So the one is from Jose, Archimedes, Ebera, Rea, beautiful name.
Can you bring the all with the Joe's back?
That's all I want for Christmas.
I just said, yes, I would.
Why didn't you listen to me, Jose?
Brett Allen says any recent stories about the post office or any other retail establishment I could listen to a podcast just to these stories.
What I do now, I'm selling a lot of stuff on Amazon is I buy the postage through Amazon.
And then I print up the label, I take it and I drop it off.
I don't have to interact with anybody.
So that's way better for me and worse for you because I'm not going to have any good stories unfortunately.
Couldn't deal with them anymore.
I mean, I think my trader, Joe's chocolate cake story probably is going to take the cake.
No pun and death on that one.
I don't think I can beat that one.
Edmond Agado asked, would you consider doing episodes on the following as mentioned before on the pod Jurassic Park three.
No, only because it's I would do the franchise, but then that would mean having to watch these fucking Jurassic World sequels, which I don't want to do wax work 100%.
I just watch wax work.
Fantasia just watch Fantasia, but we wouldn't do it on the pond.
I wouldn't, yeah, it's the lack of dialogue.
I think affects that the buy by man, we did.
We didn't do the buy man.
I've still never seen it.
If it if it had stuck around like the snowman did where it became like one of these like legendary bad movies then yes.
But like right now I just can't see myself going back and watching.
So it's fine.
I reviewed it on the movie corner then.
I never remember talking about it.
So there you go.
And then later some good suggestions and I'm going to rewatch dress park three because I haven't seen it forever.
So I'll do an Edmond.
Yeah.
That makes more sense.
Like it's more of a movie corner.
Okay.
And then loop a pita.
Peshako.
Would you guys do a commentary on the extra system?
I'm going to say no because it is too long.
And the only version of it you can find these days is the director's cut version.
And after that shining marathon.
It was too much man.
It was very long.
Two and a half hours.
People bizarrely love that one.
It's just maybe because it's so long book.
That's a lot of talking.
All right.
I've watched both of these new Friedkin documentaries.
The one on shutter and the one Friedkin on cut.
So we might do one of those.
Thank you all so much for sending these in.
Barry Christmas.
We know we owe you one more.
It's coming.
And happy Hanukkah.
I'll post them both together.
I'll wait till we have the other one done.
Okay.
So you've got the other one.
Happy holidays to you all.
We love you.
We'll see you next time.
And we'll see you in hell.