Welcome to will see you in hell you know where you're at it's the podcast you go to when
you need that good good juice on a sci -fi horror fantasy action drama comedy film whatever
your taste is whatever your pleasure is we're here to please it and feed it know I'm saying Pat
I do indeed Joe speaking of feeding I'm watching Joey the plate of cold cuts right now
ham and cheese I have to go I have to go after that we finish here after shower uh -huh and I have
to go host co -host the Legion of Skanks podcast yeah Lewis Gomez is not there uh -huh and then from
that I have to go to a very very late year holiday event uh at the uh comedy seller holiday event
they're they're holding their holiday party very late uh -huh which is why I can't hang out tonight
now you're welcome to come with me to the live podcast taping and have a few drinks and watch if you
want um I'm meeting uh I know it here we go a couple of for a couple of friends for swinging swinging
session I hope no I got to see them before they put their kid down you know it's what getting old
is all about you doesn't have to be it can be a three month late holiday party no we're gonna go up
drink have fun you know where do these people live and what do they do they live up by the
daily show like 52nd and 11th or 12th or something okay that's that's people making money up there
well they're fine what was my buddy Josh who was a uh NBC page with me oh old Joshua yes
I see him sometimes wife and daughter great family I'll see him in the street and I'll go
Joshy boy yeah how's that page job and then he goes uncle Joe how many times I gotta tell you
I'm not a page anymore yeah I forget do it all again the next time do you got an amazing pizza pit
pizza pie place around here right across the street it's amazing don't say the name of it because
I don't want to give away exactly where I live oh yeah but uh this mobbed the the place across the
street is very good uh if you get slices solo it's fine if you get a whole pie it's great
may I strongly suggest a Sicilian the Sicilian pie over there is real good
well I would just be getting a piece of pizza then I'd get a Sicilian slice it's great all right
it'll say to huh look it's better than any of that you anything you're gonna get out there what makes
the pie better that you have more pizza to eat no it's a fresh a fresh pie is gonna you know oh
sure I see you're saying you're getting something versus the thing that's been sitting out that
they have to reheat six times you know what I'll bring a pie up to my friends apartment bring
us a Sicilian genius get us a Sicilian and get half pepperoni half plain yeah you bring that thing
up there pipe and hot and by that I mean your genitals right I'll put them through the heats I'd
bring cold yeah uh but yeah you're you're gonna make those people very happy up there now why do I
keep hearing about this Legion of Skanks is being like persona non grata is it because like it was
at Louis C .K. was that the whole issue they had him perform at that thing uh there were in the
news big time over somewhere they were in the news because they do a festive comedy festival called
Skankfest which is the most fun I've ever had in my life doing comedy right it's a three -day
event of non -stop comedy shows it's a party it's a blast okay uh so the last time they did it was in
Brooklyn and Louis C .K. showed up and and he went on like you know he wasn't booked or anything he
just came through right and uh and he ended up going on and everybody there was thrilled to watch him
and see him and it was all fine uh and then you know of course it came out that you know how could this
have happened sure sure so it's like look so they've gotten some try and then they've gotten into it with
some you know there are people out there the Seth Simons of the world or the Jake Allison's of this
world Jack Alice whatever's in these precious little fucking worms uh that have nothing better to do
than attack comedians of all walks of life I'm talking from Sarah Silverman to Shane Gillis to you
know what I mean they're hidden people in every fucking zone because that's what they do uh you know
it's the kind of podcast that guys like that would hate but uh but man it's a lot of fun and uh
meeting what is just like an unfiltered on there is comedy in it yeah a lot of people I think would take
issue with gotcha uh but it's always funny so it's like I don't you know that's well I don't know
promote the concept of you know it's okay if you don't like a thing that I do or
think my friend does or whatever it's okay if I don't like a thing that you do right you can still be
friends right you know it was one of the best things about doing uh when I go on Nikki Glazer show
not that we drastically disagree about things but like we definitely have different perspectives
on stuff and it's such a cool time to sit there on the show and talk to her I saw the day I go that
was such a fruitful conversation we have it was so productive right that we were sharing opinions and
there was no anger there was no nothing it was just you know Louis was one of them it's like it's okay
if you don't like Louis or whatever I disagree why does it have to be shut the venue down it's like
guys yeah let's all fucking you know we're gonna have a public stoning at some it's like Jesus Christ man
so which is why also why and I keep bringing up why I liked what uh Phoenix said at the at the
Oscars I thought that was really cool that he was like instead of canceling how we start nurturing
each other a little bit and trying to help win another grill and then he said let's inseminate some
cows and that's the part I agree with so anyway is that I'm not trying to get all heavy over here no
but folks uh I'm still a New York City here with Joderosa and if you could see if you could have
seen the glaze on Pat's eyes during that last three minutes to be talking well I'm always like
should am I supposed to distance myself from these Louis CK remarks or what am I supposed to do
with distance what is there to distance you can have an opinion that's different from mine no I know
if somebody is going to to cancel you yes or fire you over uh from from a job because you're on
a podcast where a guy said I think Louis CK should be allowed to perform stand -up comedy again
right is this a job you are these people and I want to be a slap the mic out of your head yeah I
mean what it's like you're you're gonna go down I mean I I think like everyone in the world of
course I have a complicated relationship with with Louis CK I don't approve of anything he did
nobody does nobody saying hey right I'm Louis right whip it out I think if you if you knew what a lot
of people do uh that you do support and endorse you'd probably be pretty shocked you mean you're
starting to general public right I sort of look at entertainment as like you know I bet everyone I
enjoy has done something awful my whole thing will always you did something pretty awful my whole thing
well my whole thing will always be this we have established and agreed on what punishments are for
certain things yes he he did the punishment uh and and then he popped up in a few places and did
some stand -up I don't think that that's out of line or or the end of the world or anything I really
don't but other people disagree and that's fine right you know uh folks I saw some by the way
I'm jerking off right now in front of Pat that's what makes my feelings even more complicated but
uh somebody who has never really been controversial uh Mr David burn I saw on Friday night
and it was I think the best live musical show I've ever seen the reason I'm telling you about it
is that he announced today this is what always happens I'm like I got to get to New York and see
David burn before this closes on February 16th I saw him on February 14th right before it ended
and this morning two days later they announced he's gonna do 17 more weeks at the end of the year
but that's a positive thing if you get a chance to see the show do what you have to do
save up now spend a little extra it's well worth it I got on stub hub I had the great benefit of being a
lone one man person uh going to see the show on Valentine's Day so I got a great stub hub ticket single
down front and I'm walking down I'm supposed to be in row B so I'm like oh man I'm gonna be in the
second row this is awesome it turns out there is no row I am in the front row I go to sit down there's
two like 50 year old real sex HBO looking couples talking and laughing and having fun and they're like
this is so crazy I'm standing there waiting for them to get the fuck out of my seat they're like we live next
to each other in Connecticut and we come down and we're sitting next to each other this is crazy
they're drinking it seemed like it was really gonna lead to like wife swapping or something
so I go okay and I'm standing there standing there and the guy goes what is this your seat
I go yes actually the seat your wife is in as my seat I'm sorry so he's being a real kind of
perk about it then he stands up and goes would you mind trading with us would you mind going down four
and I go I look over four puts me in the dead center seat of the front row okay
so they all slid down I was like thank you so much appreciate it David burn I learned
of 67 he's running around the stage like a fucking maniac the choreography was awesome it's a band
who's all like free to go where they want no plugs or anything but he's got a ton ton of percussionists
he's got a bassist you know he plays guitar on and off okay at any given point there's 20 -25
musicians on stage at one point he's like everybody thinks we use a backing track I just want to show
you and he builds a song piece by piece kind of like what he did you know in the stop making sense he
built a concert song by song okay this shows you how uh our band member by band member this kind of
shows you how a song is made so like one guy's playing like one drum beat another guy comes in then by
the end it's a full song up and running it was incredible and I was a little high and I was front
row center and I have just never seen a better show go see it how much of the talking head stuff does
you do it is 70 % talking heads uh it's what you want to hear but it's I would it's not like a greatest
hits you know I I have been obsessing themselves a little kid remember in the other day I used to roller
skate around my basement listening to this talking head song and you still have the short shorts right
yeah listening to the talking head song sugar on my tongue which is like a very obscure song and
as you can imagine very sexual and I was like eight roller skating around listening over and over
to sugar on my tongue but I love David burn the whole show had a real message of love and compassion but
as you can imagine from him there is no sentiment of any kind he was just really had interesting
things to say between the songs he's a cool as fuck dude the songs are still banging and I love
and is it just a music show on Broadway or is there something that takes it to it's just a concert
basically just a concert but yeah I mean the band is very much feels like you know they feel like
characters in a way okay you know they're all very very well one thing I didn't care for being in
the front row is that the band members and burn we're all doing a lot of looking directly into the audience
to connect and that's not something I enjoy like full eye contact with somebody I see but uh
no there were awesome any you know the band was like not your usual like beautiful people which
was cool is a variety of ages and shapes and sizes and everybody's dancing had a blast had a blast
great yeah I didn't see that show well we'll be back for 17 weeks I would go I really didn't see
calculus quest yes and man is it awesome I am having a great time if you don't know what the
Oculus Quest is there was the Oculus Rift first which is a VR headset that connects to a PC computer
pretty incredible they then came out with a cheaper standalone model called the Oculus Quest Quest
because it doesn't need to connect anything and you can travel with it if you want to
oh that's interesting completely wireless the only the only wire on this thing is the plug when
you charge it uh then that disconnects obviously uh two wireless remote uh you know hand controls
whatever you want to call them and then just the mask wifi capable bluetooth capable downloads
everything directly into the the headset itself that's it that's that's the whole thing it is
fucking phenomenal and if you buy it this sounds like an ad and it's not if you buy it now well
if you buy it in the period I bought it and I don't know when now is when you're listening to this but
it came with and this was the main reason I got it they put out three a three -part
uh Darth Vader game called Vader Immortal that's VR Star Wars and the plot is your some bounty hunter
that Vader apprehends to help you to to use you to do some unlocking of a secret force bullshit thing
whatever uh so I got this thing because I had played that for five minutes at big jayokerson's house
and was like I'm buying this immediately this is everything I ever wanted from Star Wars uh I love it
and I boot up my helmet and I go into the store to buy it it says purchased already I look online
it's the free download special uh uh promotion when you buy the headset from such you know X date to
X date I don't remember what the dates are anyway the other reason I got it was for exercise because I
kept hearing from people that there's a boxing game on it that if you do it you're boxing and you
literally can exercise like this and I started it today it's called the thrill of the fight
and I boxed three men you know fake men in the game but it felt real yeah one the first two lost the
third but god damn it was a workout I was sweating I was had a breath like I was like all right what
if you short out the helmet with your excessive sweat you know it's funny I did and I think it's
just a matter of positioning and just getting the right adjustment so it fits my head perfectly
but I was getting a little the lenses were getting a little foggy at times because my like islands were
getting sweaty um but overall it was fine okay uh it's just an amazing device so I did that a lot
yesterday and a little bit today um and I can completely see myself becoming one of these people
that like goes home at night like you know like black mirror character style gets into a reclining chair
puts the mask on and slips away into another world where I'm you know I'm like the emperor there or
something right uh it's pretty great well and Joe mentioned this might be a solution for us to
podcast on different coasts if that ever needs to happen so I might be getting one myself uh I thought
it was a game system I'd have to hook up so to hear that it's a standalone is incredible I might get
this right when I get back it's completely by itself you might have to order it because they're kind of
something that I got one from Walmart but they're sold out in a lot of places but you order it
meaning you'll get it in two weeks or something okay but yeah they show it in the commercial but there
is a virtual there are virtual movie apps and you can send in a virtual movie theater next to a friend
who's in a completely different city and watch a movie in a theater with them so I said to Pat you
know if you get one of these we might be able to uh do some really fun movie commentaries while we're
in completely opposite coasts right but weirdly sitting next to one another watching a movie so you
have download the movie and watch it in this thing I'm assuming that's our rented inch yeah or something
but uh because I haven't done it so I don't know the specifics but yeah how does it not hurt your
eyes being like watching something that close because it's because this is the thing with virtual
reality there's depth in the image yeah it won't look like you're sitting against a screen it'll look
like you're in a seat in the theater looking at a screen I'm gonna get one crazy dude it's not like
you don't get it until you put the helmet on because you think you think it's gonna you're like
I get it you put it on it looks like you're in the rocket ship whatever right and then you put it
on and then you're like holy shit like I'm in this fucking thing uh and then you when you turn
around and realize it's a hundred percent behind you like in the Star Wars game it opens your
in an asteroid field right and you're turning around and your entire ship is behind you in front of
you you're in a ship yeah there's a part where a star destroyer flies over your ship and you watch
it pass over you and like a shadow drops and everything it's awesome man sounds awesome it's really
awesome anyway uh that's what I did instead of going to David burn also while I am here at tomorrow
and I'm seeing beetle juice oh you're here another night yeah okay and uh Wednesday when I am also here
I am seeing uh to kill a mockingbird with Ed Harris okay Aaron sorkins to kill a
mockingbird my next theater experience will be the revival of American buffalo oh sure they're
doing with Lawrence fishburn and Sam Rockwell sounds awesome I will be there probably in me but I
can't wait for that yeah yeah um all right well let's get ourselves over to your favorite place
in mind Pat's movie corner uh I have seen a lot and I would like to start with a film cold
we're doing the dark crystal today by the way we're doing the show and the movie and the movie
okay um I watched the confession killer which was a five -part documentary series on Netflix and the
reason that might be interesting to all of you is the Chicago show that we did on Henry Portrait of
a serial killer this is the same guy basically so you know I'm not really spoiling anything to say
there was this guy who was taking credit for basically every murder that took place uh in and around
the country in and around where he lived and then all over the country and the Texas Rangers were so
eager to have some of these cold cases closed they were just like cool even when at times there was evidence
saying there's no way this guy could have done sure so we don't know if this guy actually killed
anyone really it seemed like he probably had at least a couple under his belt but he took credit for
like hundreds of murders so I don't know when they did Henry Portrait of a serial killer if this was
during the period where they still thought he was the killer I think it was but um Netflix does a
great job with these true crime things this was not one of my favorites it's a solid B but I think
they stretched it out to five parts when it could have been an easy three and also it's not really
that interesting just a guy who's pretending to have killed people is not that exciting a story well
I would say I won't only watch your crime doc if it's produced by the duplash brothers
well they they've got enough that you could watch probably one a night for a week
um anyway it is interesting an interesting companion piece to Henry Portrait of a serial killer
lots of interesting stuff in it and on Wikipedia about it but you know it's not something you got
to rush out and watch all five hours I'm going three higher films today I'll start with a film called
well one was a watch on highly recommended to me by Ken Hamley the man responsible for starting this
podcast um he told me after the live show I really should check it out um and that I would enjoy it
I went as a shutter original so it was easy for me to watch uh almost immediately uh it was good
it was good it it was fun it was well directed they did a good job uh in building suspense
and playing with your assumptions of where something was going to go
uh or where the scare would be uh the makeup effects were great um you know and it's it's it's
basically the basic plot is it's five teenagers go to a haunted house and wouldn't you know it the
haunted house turns out to be real and the people inside the costumes or psychopaths trying to actually
murder them um it was uh so so if you like that sort of thing you'll you'll enjoy this quite a bit um
I would say that you know it was it was not one of my favorites it's not something that I'm going
to go out and buy it's not something I'm not sure I'd even watch again but for an afternoon watch
I enjoyed it uh the one thing I was trying to figure out the whole time and maybe I just missed it
was what the motivation of these killers was uh I mean I guess it was just they're crazy and they
want to kill people um I didn't quite get why they were luring people to this house like you know
in like in times you just want to see them die you know like in Texas chainsaw massacre it's like
well because they're going to eat them like you know so like just just give me a little explanation yeah
that would be tone deaf I talked about a few weeks back the Robert Patrick one his motivation was
he was about to die uh and he just had never he thought he'd experienced a lot in this life
but never killing somebody that was like a that's a cool simple motivation I agree um my other one
criticism or my other one my my second criticism of this is it did rely a little too much on jump
scares it was it was very jolt scare heavy uh which you know I've complained about that on the show
before I'm not a huge fan of that a couple was fine when it's sort of seen after scene after scene
I get a little tired of it but that being said didn't ruin the movie for me by any stretch cast was
great uh that a kid from Disney who played like the sort of loud kind of fat guy and he was fantastic
I enjoyed everybody in the movie the killers were great they were truly menacing and scary
uh and the makeup effects were awesome there was some really grim makeup work in this and I really
enjoyed it so uh check out haunt if you like written and directed by the guys who wrote a quiet place
oh really that's right I thought verdensky wrote verdensky did a rewrite on it for sure but
okay how much a resinsky whatever it was named a resinsky uh resinsky that's right I saw
for the only Brian to palma movie I had never seen and I'm a big big fan of Brian to palma and the
documentary called to palma but it's called obsession came out in 1976 like uh you know this was
right around the carry days same year as carry uh it ain't no carry it's a pretty stupid movie
this is when people are really like you just ripping off hitchcock whatever and of course he is
always was uh who cares lots of people rip off hitchcock um it's well directed but it doesn't even
have the fun of like sisters or his other kind of like trashy early work um basically it's this dude
whose wife and daughter are killed in this botched kidnap attempt
come on this guy Cliff Robertson who is wildly miscast his business partner is John Lithgow of course
second to see John Lithgow you're like wonder if he's got anything to do with these horrific crimes
right um you know it's it's all pretty obvious what the story is except years later he meets and falls
in love with this woman in Italy because she looks so much like his ex -wife um you learn
that this is actually folks his daughter oh so I am reading a fascinating book uh by Paul
Hirsch and I'm gonna recommend it to you now when I remember the name Joe you'd like this movie too
I mean this book too excuse the book not the movie I would like the movie if it took place
it eatily the Mario Battelli Italian market uh Paul Hirsch has edited over 35 feature films
and I know you might not think you'd want to read a book about a film editor but if you're a movie guy
at all it's got tons of great stories he edited Empire Strikes Back okay Ferris Bill's Day off
plans trans and automobiles uh and then well if there's a chapter on secret of my success
for some reason the Michael Jackson Fox vehicle I like that movie I like it too but um he edited tons
of huge movies and then he directed most of Brian de Palmas movies uh and he talks about obsession
and basically the people who financed the movie saw it and we're like wait a minute there's a sex scene
earlier in this movie it'd be like if instead of the Luke and Leia thing where they have that kiss
that later on becomes a little like creepy if you had watched them like fuck and like you know have a
full romantic relationship and then you learned their brother and sister right so the people watching
it were like we can't do this this is insane right let's not do this and uh the editor Paul Hirsch was
able to step in and save the day by just cutting it down to like them getting married and stuff but
also through the use of like putting a gauzy filter on it having it be like a dream of what life
would be like if they did get married so there's all kinds of cool stories about like him fit I mean
he is an editor he paint he paints himself as the hero of a lot of these situations but him saving
movies there was you learn a little bit about that three -hour playing strains cut I wanted of course
a whole book on that but you get to learn about what came out of the movie uh what came out of it
all kinds of shit they like they eventually had to do the thing uh where Steve Martin goes back
to get him that was all editing tricks okay so like it's very well worth reading about like originally
the audience and and there was a bit where like once they cut it everyone loved John Candy
but it made everyone hate John can't like imagine watching plants and all be as you hated him there was
this scene where it was very clear John Candy was taking advantage of Steve Martin and his kindness
by like freeloading off of him but instead of Steve Martin pointing that out John Candy was just
brazenly like taking money from Steve Martin and then the preview audience was like we hate this and they
couldn't figure out why right until they cut that two lines and then everybody loved John can
okay so you know it's fullest great stories like that about some of your favorite movies and the title
here's the reason I couldn't remember it is a long time ago in a cutting room far far away my 50 years
editing Hollywood hits star wars carry Ferris Bueller mission impossible and more Jesus Christ
some certainly long title but I reckon where was the editor on that title folks all right uh I watched
sessions not good don't say it I rewatched the carry remake oh with uh
team uh Judy what's her name kidding uh the blonde uh Sarah Jessica Parker what's this kid
grace morat's low yeah there it is yeah that one sucked with Julian Moore I liked it uh I own it
because I got it into one of those harry pack subscription boxes yeah I don't know that it's
something I would have bought otherwise I don't know if it's something I would have seen otherwise
but I was like okay carry remake I'll check this out um I watched it once a while back remember not
thinking too strongly one way or the other about it this rewatch um I enjoyed it I you know it
look is it a masterpiece no not by any stretch um but it was something I enjoyed rewatching uh I
thought the performances in it were very strong I thought they did a good job uh with the characters
the character development throughout the movie um I liked that carry went a little more
bat but or buck shit I should say at the end of this thing she was a little more she had
you know uh even less I mean look though the revenge sequences the revenge sequence but I felt like
they gave her as little sympathy as possible in this version of it yeah and I kind of like that I
thought that was kind of cool because then it let you kind of turn on her a little bit and go well
she's taking it too far now um uh and especially for a modern movie I was surprised that they stuck
with the period scene I was glad they didn't change that also the scene where uh Judy Greer
carry like isn't hysterics and she slaps her yeah I was like oh well for a modern film that's
a pretty uh edgy thing to put in there was Judy Greer her mom no she's a coach you know it doesn't
have the texture of the diploma version it doesn't have uh I would say the the the the the level of horror
of the diploma version but I did think that it was good I you know I did enjoy it and it's a
fairly faithful adaptation to the book I think the most strangely faithful adaptation is the TV
movie that is supposed to be was supposed to be a pilot for a carry TV show where it was going to be
like she left the town and then became this you know sort of vagabond I guess that it powers that
went town to town like the incredible Hulk or something like that uh but the TV showed and get made
but the the pilot was well reviewed Patricia Clarkson plays the mom and it's supposed to be solid
I've never seen it but I did read the full synopsis and it did seem like that one followed the ending
of the original a little bit more at least because Carrie lives uh the Chloe Grace Mortez
Carrie is very much a remake of the diploma version and not so much an adaptation of the book
which is always a weird thing to me because it's like you're going to remake it why not just
adapted from the book the way the book did it and then and then people then it's still the
updated version of the movie yeah and then you also get to justify why it's different like I never
get why they don't just do that but they don't right um bad CGI effects uh but thankfully there aren't
a ton of them uh and some very cool kills at the end of this thing so I dug it they leaned a little
too heavy and I don't know if the book does this or not into the foreshadowing of her powers uh
it was just a little too much uh I wanted a little more um you know mystery with that but then again
that that might be from the book I don't know anyway it's worth a watch I wouldn't go out of your way
but if you own it like I do because somebody gave it to you and again a delivery subscription box
I also wouldn't toss it folks I saw uh one other Brian de Palma picture and it's one that I saw like
15 years ago thought was absolutely terrible and I thought I should give it another shot now de Palma
had a rough run there in the 2000s the uh good lord what was oh mission of Mars oh my god was that a
bad movie but um his black dollia lately my wife has become very interested in the black dollia case
they did that show with uh Chris Pine about it recently I think it was on TNT Star Trek yes uh
but um you know she got real into the case and I was like well you know I've read the book and
he there's a movie so all let's watch the movie it's so bad and Brian de Palma and that material
should just be a slam dunk but it's real but have you seen that no I remember seeing the trailers
and thinking it was the same time that Hollywood land came out exact same time yeah and I remember
looking at both of those and thinking these look like like almost like SNL sketches that take place
in the 40s like I'm not buying the visuals any this it all looks very fake for some reason yeah
you know and I think a lot of that had to do with the dawn of whatever film stop you know whatever
the film stock being used the new you know the newest technology cape you know all of a sudden there
was this new brightness and sheen on everything and it looked like shit but I just I never had any
interest yeah I mean all the Potter effects are pretty much great and then there's one right around
this time period where they don't look right you know like effects are a weird thing they go through a
lot of transitions but um black dollia the big problem really is with its fucking cast uh this
thing stars Josh Hartnett uh which is always just a kiss of death Hartnett I'll never understand how
the man became successful he's kind of attractive but he looks like he's got a mental problem to me
he's a good looking guy he's just not a good actor and he's fit uh but so are tons of people you
know they can just act better Scarlett Johansson is in it she should be perfect playing like you know
this Bavavum lady but she's real bad in it Aaron Eckhart's real bad in it and then for like the
other sex pot character and I think she's attractive I think she's a good actress but you know don't
take this personally but Hillary Swank cannot play us a 40 sex pot give me a break I mean she is
trying to like flirt and you're like oh my god you have to look away from the screen at times it's
embarrassing and you were worried about the Louis CK comments yes I'm sorry uh it is horribly done it
is horribly written yeah I I'll never get past the fact that Hillary Swank reminds me of my buddy
you're male buddy yeah I think his name was Josh uh I can't get past it right you know like I
think she's and I think she's an attractive woman I just that will always be in my head yeah
that will always just be in my head I'm sorry so I hear you it's like you can't you know well you can
it's just for me it's not gonna work I read another fantastic book about the movies of 1999 which is
considered like the modern day best year of movies the old one is 1939 uh and boys don't cry as a whole
chapter in that we're we're the weird kismet here because I didn't know you were going to talk about
the department thing yes and I talk about the carry remake yes then you start talking about this you
bring up boys don't cry right the director of the carry remake was the director of the game cry
right uh hasn't worked since I know I think she's directly like two movies well I think
I think it was one of those deals of they gave her you know a couple quick you know shots at some
stuff and none of it really I mean I don't remember much after the boys don't cry I think that was
kind of and let maybe she walked away I don't know yeah she did one movie after boys don't cry that
I guarantee you've never heard of right well they always say and you know from talking to
anyone in this business there's a lot of truth to it that female directors had to work a billion times
as hard to get a second shot now they don't now you know there's a huge push to get female directors
in TV and movies and etc but um oh yeah she did stop loss which was not a good film yeah and if you're
following that with the carry remake you're not you're you're dancing on thinning right but uh yeah
she basically talks about how of course her management team she'd been in the next karate kid and
stuff hilarious like and they were like why you can't play this trans character everyone's going
to think that you're like trans or male or something and that'll be how you kick off your career
and what happened was she won the Oscar she got cast in tons of great parts but you still can't
shake it you I still see her as a man I just and I don't know why I can't help it because she played
an extremely convincing male she was great in a movie well then it and then a million dollar
baby it didn't bug me because she's playing like a tough butch boxer and that movie is incredible I
love million dollar well million dollar it's a great movie yeah I was boi's a great million dollar
baby that character ain't shaking off the the brootness of that's what I'm saying yeah she's a tough
like boxer yeah but when you get to something like black dye and she's like in a slinky black dress
coming down a flight of stairs I'm like nope like you can't help how you first see somebody it sticks
with you but uh yeah Kimberly Pierce that's a very confusing career boys don't cry one episode of
the L words seven years after that stop loss was ten years after boys don't cry so really that's
a movie every decade now I'm looking at pictures of Hillary Swing yeah she's unquestionably a pretty woman
yeah I'm not saying it as a as a criticism of a book I wondered if I could date her because she
runs into this problem a lot with guys well is she still with Chad Lowe her husband and she forgot to
thank at the Oscars who was sobbing I don't think so I remember that vividly they cut to him and
he's hysterically crying I think they split up honestly the moment she didn't think it was probably
the moment he was like well this is over well and then also there was a moment where she went
I'm married to Chad Lowe what am I doing yeah so all right my final one before we review
the gate to okay I'm an either gate I'm a big fan of the original gate it stars excuse me sorry
I just belched a little bit sorry I'm eating ham what do you work for me it stars Steven the young very
young Steven Dorf his parents go away for the weekend they leave he and his older sister home alone and
then Steven Dorf and his best friend are digging in the backyard where there's a hole there because
they're going to put a pool in her some ship but there's a hole in the backyard and they're playing
around in it and they open a gate accidentally to hell that demons come out of and now they've got to
stop it and terrible shit is happening it's a really fun movie it's a great like childhood horror movie
you know it's right up there to me with like stranger things and you know or gremlins or you know
or even like a goonies where it's just an adventure thing for kids like it's just a lot of fun monster
squad same characters as gate one well this is I'm describing gate one right now okay so gate two
was a sequel years later Steven Dorf did not return because he was too busy crushing all of the ass
in Hollywood yeah five feet tall yeah but I don't think he was I think he was probably just kind of
starting to get on his way so he said no I'm assuming yeah because it's not that long after it's not
like suddenly he was grown and he said no and he doesn't die in the gate I said no he doesn't die yeah
so the second one revolves around the best friend who one of the plot points the first one is that his
mom has died and he's sort of a troubled kid because of this in the second one his dad has sunk
into the depths of alcoholism and he realizes that oh we we opened the gate wrong but if you open
it right you can control the power and I could use that power to write all the wrongs of my mom dying
I can get my dad the job he deserves will sober up all these things okay so in the midst of doing
this it's it's it's early in the film he this this ritual he's conducting is interrupted by the bullies
of his school excuse me and also Pamela what's her name from again well this is it from Louis
Adlon yeah Pamela Adlon yeah who's like 18 in this thing uh huh and I'll leave it at that
just in case he's just in case she wasn't 18 but she's the love interest okay and she's way out
of this made kids league uh huh anyway she's great in it um they're all great in it it's it's
starts out as a really fun movie the bad guys the bullies are a lot of fun they're menacing bullies
but they're also kind of funny and bumbling a little bit the main kid is endearing and sweet and
you're rooting for him and then Pamela is lovely playing like the tough girl that kind of falls for
the geek it's a nice group of people yeah in this cast uh and then they summon a demon and then they
put it into a cage uh and and because they don't know what to do with it and then the one of the bullies
kills one of the other demons which I guess sets off the chain of bad events that's gonna happen now
the whole setup is great and then from there which I'd say is about the 22 -minute mark
it is a fucking just oh it does slug I mean slug isn't the word for it well that's why they didn't get
dork bug baby yeah it's it's so slow it's so boring nothing happens you don't give a shit about
anything and the basic plot of the movie is when you wish for a thing through the power of this demon
you'll get it yeah and then the big twist is it goes away by turning to shit and by that I don't
speak euphemistically it turns to literal shit uh so so there's like a scene in a rest this is
actually the only time they do it right where it's kind of funny there's a scene where the two
assholes wish for all this money uh and they get it and then they go to like uh you know those restaurants
you only see and but you know they always do what it's all on it's always sunny they always go to that
restaurant that's clearly like just some ballroom they've converted for a shoot you know you're like
there is no restaurant like this yeah there is like good genus yeah yeah like but they do that in movies
it's like there isn't like Ferris Bueller there is no restaurant where the Peter D has a tuxedo
already it's absurd maybe in the 80s or something I don't know but yes so they go to one of those kinds
of restaurants it's a French place uh and they're ordering all this stuff and you know of course the
waiters are annoyed because they're like you punk kids aren't gonna have the money and then they start
throwing hundreds of you know yeah and uh they have the big meal and then the check comes and it's
like four million dollars yeah and the kids like uh no problem my good man and then reaches into his
pocket to grab the money and then his pocket filled with feces and I was like that's the one part
where it's kind of funny uh or no it's not even I'm wrong it's not that that's what I thought it was
gonna be he pulls the money out of his pocket and very arrogantly throws it down on the check
and it cuts to the money hitting the check and turning to shit splattering all over it uh but I mean
that's a long way to go and this has played for like child laughs it's supposed to be funny yeah um
but that's a long way to go for you know one funny gag sure uh it's a bad sequel it's a sequel
I I had always wanted to see because I loved the first one and it was a sequel that was always
very hard to see because it wasn't really um screaming anywhere and I think it's out of print
so there was a little bit of a fantastic fester one of those things out in uh LA they had
like Jonah Ray hosts a lot of those screening yeah yeah old 80s horror and and stuff that's not
available on VH or it was on VHS but not on never made the transition rad played there which is
one of the worst movies ever made via next biking classic um well I'm gonna watch the gate one
never seen it so there you go gate one is 80s horror classic easy you'll you'll like it all right
and we've done our three right yeah all right speaking of 80s classics today we talked the dark crystal
and then the subsequent television show made 30 40 years later almost 40 years yeah 84 I want to say
85 to the first five years later whatever yeah I mean uh I'll give you my little uh history with it
and then I'm gonna pee joe be right back but I saw the dark well hey when I was a kid I loved all
things muffins my favorite great mouth of k for by far but I think they're all pretty fantastic up
through Christmas Carol then I saw a labyrinth it scared me to death but I fucking loved it I used
to watch it probably once a week with my little sister for a decade I watched it probably once a week
dark crystal if if you told anyone in the world I loved labyrinth what else should I watch they
would spit out the dark crystal yeah you know like they're the same team the same feel you know the
same style everything but for whatever reason even when I was little I watched the dark crystal and
I was like not for me and scare you labyrinth scared you but the dark crystal never scared me much more
and I think it was because everything and this is my issue with the dark crystal everything
in it is puppet I only give a shit when it's human beings I don't get scared in animation or
anything else but these are drawings they just it doesn't work on me that way and even when I was
a kid it didn't work on me that way but then what the hell scared you in labyrinth because anything
scary and that is puppets but it's humans and jeopardy it's Jennifer Connolly who I was in love with
and then you know at the beginning they're trying to capture a baby you know they're trying to steal a
baby out of a crib these monsters and I was even scared of the good guy in labyrinth the guy who
peas into the bog and all that the toggle yeah the giant dwarf guy never liked him that was a Brian
Henson voice target yes I'm gonna go ahead and press through I don't have to pee as bad as I
thought moving on dark crystal didn't work for me then I have watched it every 10 years since I
watched it two weeks ago and it still doesn't really work for me now but not a movie I hate
but that's my my overall take I love the dark crystal yes I think it is a masterpiece it's almost
in my top 10 movies okay but there's just not enough room I think visually there's just never been
anything like it the reason that it's all puppets is the reason I love it so much right I found it
horrifying as a child when I saw the commercial on TV in the commercial he said from the mind of
Jim Henson I ran from the TV crying hysterically to my mom that I saw the most terrifying thing on TV
just now why would Jim Henson do this to us he's supposed to like kids uh eventually I worked up
the guts to see it it did scare me but man did I love it I really loved it and I still do
and I also love what the behind -the -scenes story is this was a passion project for Henson he couldn't
get the money he put everything he had into this himself they were working with just on a shoe
string budget to for what this was to get it done everybody told him it was a mistake Frank
Oz co -directed as well so she's given some of the code yeah well yeah yeah everybody said this is
you're making a real like wrong hard turn here uh came out was not initially well received and
then eventually became this unsung classic that everybody loves yeah um and to this day I feel
that way about the film the basic plot of it is is uh there's a land called Thra it is opens with
the land being just desecrated and uh and desolate and dead you know there's really no nothing it's all
rock and everything seems dead uh and the skexies who are these hideous like vulture -like creature
humanoid things uh run the land and they get all of their power from this thing called the dark
fear is that the prophecy says a being called a galfling will destroy them and they have
since eliminated all the galfling and think that they're safe and will live forever uh and then
they find out no there's one galfling still alive and of course this galfling is now going to get
sent on the quest to defeat these kexies in it and an unfolds from there um real simple plot
says basic as it gets it's all you need start to finish good guys bad guys farm boy star wars
kid on the farm suddenly has to leave the farm to go do the daunting task uh in the death start was
shooting uh uh you know a proton torpedo into a three foot by three foot port that would blow up
this massive space station and this it's replacing the one missing shard from the crystal that will
return light to it and unify the good beings of the land the mystics and the skexies the bad beings
into uh into one cosmic you know race or whatever i think that all made sense uh yeah i mean really
this was the first time i watched it and followed it i and it's a simple story yes but like my my brain
doesn't go the fantasy route aside from sexual fantasy uh i just never i don't i never like hard fantasy
lord of the rings whatever else it may be is not my thing dune whatever so uh that's the difference
for me labyrinth is much more of a adventure i guess uh this you know i never liked and still did not
like the lady who has boils that keep popping under nose oh great they don't so does he just
gross so gross yeah uh i love the one sort of the snake of the skexies world it keeps going um that's
chamberland that's everybody's favorite skexies great care he's great uh so this all said yeah they
announced about ten or fifteen years ago they were going to do a sequel that i guess there were some
notes that they had uh unearthed of hensons or something and they were going to do a secret
sequel called the power of the dark crystal that was going to center around the gulf the tour
many gulflings gen and kira they are now married and they are the king and queen of thraw which is a
thriving land but in there uh you know as they've gotten older and they're aging and and in their
you know in their power or whatever they have now become uh a little out of touch with what the land
needs and now suddenly the crystal is in peril again and a girl made out of fire is that's the way
it was described has to fix the crystal uh i thought great um in i want to see this this is going
to be awesome it's coming from the henson company year after year after year they offered updates
nothing ever happened then they started releasing these comic books that you know more
like graphic novels that were released volume one volume two volume three uh that uh that that
kind of covered the they did one of them the story of this the sequel idea they did another one
called um called like i forget it's called like origin tales or something like that that was
played as a prequel to the movie uh they did it another way they did a bunch of these things
and none of them were really that good they had their moments but they were all kind of missing
something and you were like where is this going and then finally they announced we're doing a sequel
series series no prequel series excuse me called the dark crystal age of resistance right off the
i don't like the title it's a bad video game title uh it's like terminator dark fate yeah that's
what you call the ps4 terminator game that's not what you call terminator seven yeah it just seems
like picking two words out of a hat basically yeah so and you look i wasn't crazy about it in the new
Star Wars movies when they said the rebellion is now called the resistance i was like that's just a
bad word it's just been used too much in movies about resistance uh you know so but
but they announced this thing i'm excited they're gonna do a 10 episode sequel's prequel series
on Netflix great it's gonna cover the decimation of the galflings and how the skexies rise to power
okay great sounds pretty cool to me let's do it then they announced the cast list of this thing
and i'm like oh boy i'm a little worried again because it's what always happens you take a cool thing
that's sort of born out of passion and grit viscerally and turn it into star fuckery
it's why i hated that last beastie boy's video when mca was sick and couldn't do the video and the whole
video is like Seth Rogan and Jonah Hill and i'm like this isn't what makes the beastie boy's cool
i don't want to see every famous person on earth in this video and then you read the the cast list
of this thing way before it comes out and it's like taren ederson and keegan michael kee and you know
and i'm going uh Andy samberg and all this stuff uh and i'm going look i don't have anything against
any of these people yeah but this is turning into the cool kids table and i don't want it to be
that but still keep my mind open then i know i'm rambling but but there this is all worthwhile
information i'm sitting in the movie waiting for a little piece of magic called midsummer to begin
i'm bored because i'm waiting for the lights to go down i go on my phone i said let me see what's going
on with this dark crystal series i look it up they've added to the Wikipedia page
what each skexies does so in the movie who gives a fuck they're just these creepy birds walking around
like that's all you need to know right on the Wikipedia page it's like it's like skexo
organizer of all the skexies banquets skeptex voiced by aqua -thena in charge of all the skexies
wardrobe i immediately text Jared Logan i go uh because this is what the man detects in that
situation yeah this is what the original movie was was missing right a Harvey firestein voiced ball
organizer literally that's the thing that's real uh uh what is this but still i'm excited i see trailer
one i go uh pretty cool yeah but why are they not playing them theme song oh they're going to say
trailer two she trailer two that's pretty cool right then i play the theme song what is the theme song
same for the show uh you wouldn't know because dark crystal dark dark crystal yeah it's baby got back
uh yeah next time then the show starts i finally watched the the first episode it opens with this
ungodly voiceover by sugerny weaver it goes on for a while it's terrible the movie opens with a voiceover
by a man i have never heard of and have never heard of since with the most frightening voice of all time
when he's like uh the dog christ uh the skexies twisted in evil right it's it's it's literally like the
voice mic mire's does before he does dr evil and so i married an expert when he goes would you say you
are evil right it's that kind of i'm like this thing opens with yet another famous person ruining the
opening monologue it goes through kingdom after kingdom after kingdom i'm like uh for fuck sake guys so
now it's game of thrones there's a million kingdoms we have to be aware of guarantee they pitched it with
the game of thrones reference on the pitch yeah then they show the title card for the for the series
and it finally plays the theme and i go all right here we go it played the theme music
and that theme music played for precisely seven seconds and never was played ever again
now is that a huge deal no but what it is to me is quite indicative that these people are
tonally off the fucking mark all of these strikes i mentioned the skexies having jobs the uh the
cast being overrun with with famous people and hot shots and whatever not playing the music from
the movie all of these things are misses because you don't understand the tone so you go from a movie
that is essentially a punk band with a four track saying we're going to get this thing done with no
budget if we've got to put it out our fucking cells we will to the follow up album where the band is
now on the major label the lead singer has left and there's suddenly a horn section in every song
because they can and you're going the sucks the sucks all shine there's no substance um i agree with
a lot of that i i wouldn't even know what the music was and like i said i don't have some real personal
attachment to it but like i'm with you the soul was gone the heart was gone i do not hate the movie
the dark crystal i i respect a lot of it i watched two hours of behind the scenes footage on it when
i was done because that's honestly what i'm more interested in but uh the story is i didn't care
this right off the jump they had been saying like this is the you know the biggest puppet production of
all time whatever else and and uh it's from the director of the transporter by the way
the adjacent state yeah i looked up who directed who directed this this franchise all of them were
directed by the guy who did that move um there you go so and the hensons were involved you know but
who knows to what extent i only watched the first two and that was enough for me this thing is so dense
the pilot feels longer than the movie or honestly does it's so boring it goes on and on and on the
only i mean the voice stuff yeah there was a lot of famous people the only one i really picked out was
Edgerton and Sigurd and we were of course maybe because i just heard Edgerton read Elton John's
autobiography on audible and i'm like you're not Elton John dude like you have to separate right but uh
the movie is there is something kind of magical about it but i think it was 82 i looked it up by the way
but for me labyrinths is just more my style i love the henson company i love everything they did
when you hear the later stuff like when they get the different kermit and everything you get to
something's off each each year jim henson goes away the muppet loses more of the magic yeah then they
did that movie with Wilson McCarthy where it's like puppets jerking off and fucking they're trying to be
edgy and it's like guys this isn't what you do stop yeah i think that the henson companies really
been lost without jim and the closest they came to the magic was right after he died when they did
muppet christmas carols so jim probably had a hand in the early stages or something but um it looks
like it's a big swing and a miss going forward you made it to the end i did not i had to muscle through
these things they do they do the clat now granted there were some sequences that really worked right
there's a sequence where they apprehend the skecs he's apprehend one of the galfling women and
they're like dragging her off basically to enslave her by draining her essence okay and they're like
the way it's shot they're dragging her on the ground and she's kicking and screaming and they're all
over her like cackling and laughing and everything yeah and it's very disturbing and very haunting and
i'm like this brought me back to the way i felt as a kid watching these things right um
but i mean it was it they did they did a lot of you know characters dying and then coming back
including augura which you're like we know she comes back uh -huh so where is the what is the point
of having her die we already know she lives uh but they did that all right yeah they did that a lot
with uh characters yeah sucks they had characters in there that were not in the movie like like
aquafina plays this this i think this is why you thought augura was always oozing aquafina plays
a skexies who always has like snot and shit coming out of her nose and it's just kind of gross
and dumb comedy and like it's like that skexus wasn't in the right it was in the show i mixed them up
yeah so then like when they kill a skexies you know like kill that one she's not in the movie and
instead they invent another one that's not in the movie to kill it's like right it's so fucking
convoluted and stupid um and then they changed they changed the story yeah the story in the movie is
the skexies uh crack the crystal uh or the mystics excuse me the mystics nothing sorry the mystics
and the skexies when they come together they're like these sentient supreme beings or whatever
those beings crack the crystal because they thought they what they could do was divide its power
so they could be more capable as a group and when they crack the crystal it's it's it's it causes a
divide in them and they're they're good went to one side and they're bad went to the other
they change it they change it in this it's like the skexies crack the crystal the skexies couldn't
exist when the crystal was cracked that's the fucking point like they just kept changing little
things like that where i was like and look i really tried not to nitpick over anything but by the
11th one of these you're like guys i'm just confused at this point right you're changing so much
you're doing so much wrong what is the point i can't remember who the fuck is who you've got eight
galflings with blonde long hair right they don't exactly look that different from one another i don't
know what the fuck is happening right now um and the biggest grievance really to me is that there
is so much of this that is CGI and not puppets there's no way some of this stuff was done just puppets
i don't buy it there's i mean i don't know a lot of it was yeah i mean look when you see like a
the there's like a part where like though there's like a warrior skexies who is actually kind of a
cool character but it just didn't serve anything i guess you see where he's like running up like a wall
it's like yeah it's obviously not a puppet but they're using CGI and the backdrops and stuff you
know it just it doesn't feel as handmade when they drain the life out of that uh you know puppet in
the first one of the face like melts basically remember that yeah that's like a haunt in the movie
it's like a really haunting image that stays with you even though it's just a puppet blah blah blah
but in this one you know everything is done way more in my opinion with special effects maybe they'd
prove me wrong if i watched that making and it's i didn't buy it i think they did a lot of extra
help after the fact by the end of this thing when the skexies it's so bad the last episode
the skexies show up this is the big extent or supposed extinction of the galfling they don't it
doesn't happen but the skexies are like we got to wipe these guys out they show up to a galfling village
to battle them um literally like an after school fight you're like these eight
creatures from this castle that rule the the planet they left the castle to come fight you got it's
what the fuck is going on yeah and again in the movie they have those things called the garthum
and the garthum are wiped everything out they're like these beetle soldiers and they're really
fucking scary they're the coolest part of the game but at the end they use those as the button at
the end of the series they get the end of the series they create the garthum like go it's come
in bay it's like no too little too fucking late you guys fuck this up there's probably not
going to be another one because it cost eight gejillion dollars to make this god damn thing
and then it's like it costs so much money and i don't think anybody's watching it no and then every
idiot online is going oh my god can we talk of maize balls you fucking idiots you fucking idiots
you you you Avengers loving idiots that think just because there's 27 celebrities on the screen
and a lot of flashiness it means there's substance there's not this thing was indicative of
everything wrong with fucking entertainment right now to me huge hog down i hated it
that is for the show not the movie which Joe said he absolutely loves i like
show for me man there is no conceivable way i would have made it to the end of this thing i i
i got out quickly and easily but uh let us know if you feel differently chat about it on the old
facebook page i'm on twitter and instagram at the Patrick Walsh i'm going to be on punch up the jam
with my friend miel i'm going to be on i said no gifts with my friend bridger wanger uh jodoros
a comedy on instagram and twitter jodoros a comedian on facebook go to jodorosinfo .com for dates
i'll be in a town near you sometime soon uh i hope that's it we'll see you next time we'll see you in hell