I see you, I fell Everyone is trying to hear your screams
Bake on something on the dream You know I'll say
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, Yeah I see you, I fell
You know I see you, I fell Welcome to Will see you in Hell
It's where you get that fat baby back
For the smack diddly smack how you doing cruisers and crushes
This is Joe de rosa
It's kind of like the warriors DJ. Here's the warriors. I did and I hear what you're saying
I thought
Your hair's also got a curl in front that made you look kind of like a greaser
So I was thinking like Wolfman Jack from American graffiti. Yeah, that too, you know
Anyone of your famous radio DJs
A .O .U .T .D. Bobbys and Bobbittinis. Yeah, that kind of shit. Yeah, yeah, Bobbittinis
Do you did he get the name Wolfman because of his voice or was he just
Because of his voice he's in the end of America Fiddy Richard Drive is finally finds him
At the studio and you see him. It's kind of like the Oz thing where you see the Wizard of Oz and I like this piece of shit
Oh, we talked about Wayne's world two in the last. That's what Dorothy says, right?
And that's a famous scene when she finally sees the Wizard the real Wizard
She looks at the lion and goes this piece of shit, right? Yeah
She then she grabs him by the crotch and goes listen you fat cock sucker. I
Gotta get back to Kansas town
She
That was one of the funny parts I forgot to mention in Wayne's world. It's a great or Wayne's world to when we talked about last episode
There's that really funny thing where they go to the radio station to talk to handsome Jack the DJ and
Ted McKinley comes out and they're like Jack. How are you when he's like I'm not handsome Jack and he just walks away
I then Harry sheer comes out just like
Weddy with the log curls right right I'm sure they that's the kind of situation where Harry sheer is so pompous
You know, he's very funny, but he's a very like blow hard
I imagine he went and he's like, so what did you want me to do to myself to to seem?
More unattractive and an unappealing and they're like, oh, I guess we'll put a crazy hair on you like as if they didn't just cast
That's what he looks like
Did you know the female Garth in that is the sister from the wonder years?
Oh, I guess I you know, I probably knew it at the time, but I might not have remembered. Yeah, that's the sister
That's like the hot sister from the wonder years Olivia Diabo. Yes. Yes. Yeah
We're gonna talk about
This is a I guess it's a new psycho sort of what we were just saying we want to talk about this
We were watching a video that's up on we should plug the kid who's video it is, but does a kid on YouTube that does
Really cool little movie
Vignette videos that are like, you know, celebrating Gene Wilder celebrated, you know, John candy or whatever and he did a video about the three -hour cut of
Plane strains and automobiles that nobody's ever seen
But he actually has read this can actually read multiple versions of the original scripts
And this this dude is hats off entertainment on YouTube and the title is the lost version of plans trans automobiles a doc you many
Yeah, so they go he goes into I mean, this is the most in depth, you know
Analysis of that version that I've ever seen
He shows you passages from the script he tells you what how scenes were edited and what they were originally what they shot and
blah blah blah this footage seems to be lost forever as has been confirmed and reconfirmed by
Not only John Hughes, but several other people involved in the film, but
The one great thing that in this video that it led me to
was and I mean and also let me say who knows I mean, I don't know if I would love to see the stuff that was missing
I don't know if the movie needs
I don't know if I need a three -hour version of it, but like you know
I would love to see what was missing and he does point out cool little things like the kid that breaks into their room
And robs them is actually the kid that delivers the pizza that you never see and candy
Only gives him a dollar tips and then the kid comes back and robs them
There's stuff like in there like that
That cut because that's the kind of scene where like you love John candy so much
But if he's the kind of jerk that stiffs people on tips a that doesn't seem like that character would do that
And be it makes you kind of not like him
so
I'm glad they cut that and from what I've heard and I've heard in this thing and other sources is that John candy or I'm sorry
John Hughes had a three and a half hour version of the movie that everyone agreed obviously they're not gonna air right
So he gets it cut down to two hours
So I'm sure Hughes himself was like yeah a lot of this stuff is funny, but you just don't need it
Here's the nuts and bolts of it and they said we want you to take another half hour out of the movie and in that
Half hour that was cut. I guarantee there's some gold in terms of both story and comedy
I'd love to see that additional hour and a half just to sit back and watch two of my favorite comedians go at it with each other
um
I have read one version of the script that I was able to get my hands on
And it was very long it didn't seem like anything that was gonna run three and a half hours
But I know that they improvised a lot too
so
I thought the script everything that was cut from that script even though some of the stuff
I was like oh thank god
That's out it would have ruined the flow whatever all of it was funny
I mean John Hughes just sat and wrote funny dialogue all day
Everything he ever wrote dialogue wise for the most part was funny the most critical oh sorry
No, I'm just saying to give it to those to give his dialogue to those dudes
It's gonna be something you want to see
Paramount the vaults it got burnt during one of these vault fires or something
But that sounds like kind of horseshit sounds like maybe John Hughes didn't love everything he shot
Which I get not everybody wants their outtakes to be brought out to the world
What bothers me though is that John Hughes did record a commentary for plans trends
That never got released and it was going to be on this blu -ray and when the blu -ray came out
I didn't have the commentary and they said John Hughes wasn't happy with it
but
Criterion just did breakfast club which means they've penetrated into the world of John Hughes
And his family and got they got his blessings on everything. I'm sure
That that is very exciting to me that we might someday see at least like a half -hour deleted scenes package or something
Or is here that commentary finally something yeah, I um
Well, they'll just betray John Hughes's wishes now that he's dead as they do with everybody and print that you know
I just read uh, who's the guy that died Alan Rickman
Yeah, I just read like Alan Rickman's diaries to be published. It's like they're his diaries. They did that with Kerkoban
And I was so disgusted by it but I bought them yeah, so um
We're all gross, but I mean my god. I look. I love Alan Rickman as an actor
But I mean, yeah, I can't imagine the somberness of these diaries like it's like what are you Jesus Christ?
You know, but I am forced to act with Timothy Allen again
On the set of galaxy quests
I just did a picture with a fat man named Kevin Smith. Oh
Yeah, that's right
The man wore jean shorts or as they're cold in the States
Why am I do an Alan Rickman impression? Why aren't I doing it? I don't know
I don't know you didn't even know you did one. I mean, it's fine. I'd have to remember it. I haven't done
I retired it when the man died
That's the area. I was gonna do a George bit, but now I'm mad at myself. Go on, Joe
um
When Bob looks good, but he looks like he's made of wax
What who like he looks good Kevin Smith lost the weight
Yeah, but to me now he looks like this sort of fake human like it maybe get a skin tight and clear something
Something is too clear. Yeah, it's weird
My friend when Bob Hope was still my friend chip that I started out with who doesn't do stand up anymore sadly because it was very funny
It was during the second golf war and he said uh the great, you know
Like many comedians the great Bob Hope inspired me to get into comedy
I would like to do now close with my impression of Bob Hope current commenting on today's war
And then he would drink water and just start shaking and drool it all over
Anyway, um I
This my favorite thing about watching this video about the lost version of traplanes trains was I never knew
There was a deleted scene that that was released sure and I got to see it man
I got to see it and my god almighty. It's
hilarious like yeah, it's them eating dinner on the plane
It candy does that thing about I know a woman that worked in the kitchen of one of these
The sliced off the top of her finger chopping carrots yeah slice it right off look for it look for it look for it look for it look for it look for it couldn't find it
You said they served it uh on the 505 fly it over to moan
At the the him taking you know
Uh, Barton's got that disgusting lasagna meal that looks terrible. Yeah, he doesn't want it. He's like to you mind
taking it splitting the brownie with the old man sitting next to them
It's also a funny scene man
What's also very funny and a really really good character moment that you know
That's what Hughes did really really well is that it's not just jokes. You're usually getting a better picture of who the person is
but
He is talking about what the best meals to order are on each airline
And candy makes it super funny, but really it's just like a great character detail that he travels so much
He knows what to order like he gets I get the kids meal you know they give me a girkin and they chicken nuggets
He tells me yeah because he goes
You know Southwest I tell him a child
Yeah, he gets me all he goes hotdog
Some french fries
Little girkin and a nice little bag of Oreos very tasty
Yeah, he's the best. I mean that that is my favorite comedic performance of all time
You know what another one of them is
Is Eddie Murphy and the nutty professor which I caught half of the other night just what a fucking great movie the scene with
Chappelle and Eddie Murphy is so good and just painful
Because like everyone's been that person in the audience where you're praying that the the the asshole comic doesn't pick on you all of a sudden
And got it that it's like a hard it's it's similar to the scene where Steve Martin finally goes off on John candy
And tells him how boring he is. Yes, is the scene where Chappelle goes off on you know the fat Sherman clump
but
Anyway, I'm going to this because Eddie Murphy is one of my favorite comedic performances in that movie and
I just read that I listen to this audiobook
Written by a PA about the making of the big Lebowski
Right, it's a two and a half hour audiobook and if you have audible it's free
But it was a very fun lesson and it's got all kinds of backstage gas up and shit
But my favorite detail was that he talked about how he was amazed that the Cohen brothers never had any interest in
Art movies like they were always like rolling their eyes at any of like the critically acclaimed movies
but
In particular he said
Ethan Cohen was obsessed with the nutty professor
And would just like come in every day talking about it and just pick I think that's the funniest movie
I've ever seen in my life
That's the beauty of the Cohen brothers is that they're geniuses who love actually funny things and then they make genius actually funny
Shit, that's that's that's what it is and the payoff by the way nutty professor the revenge scene when he goes back
Oh amazing and takes down Chappelle's character. I mean, it's just so good man. What a payoff
Yeah, it's so good to buy you buy completely that that
The Sherman clump who is also Eddie Murphy is so like mortified and embarrassed and and hurt and wounded by this
and
Clearly you're like this because the comedian is funny. It's Dave Chappelle and his materials really funny
So you're kind of laughing at that too and feeling uncomfortable about it
But then when Eddie Murphy comes back as thin Eddie Murphy
He demolishes Dave Chappelle to the extent that like
You're like Dave Chappelle should be embarrassed
That's how talented Eddie Murphy is and he get not only can he sell that because he is that much fun here
Then our greatest comedian Dave Chappelle
But he is also great at playing the other side it would be like if Steve Martin played the Steve Martin role and the John
Candy role that would never work. Yeah, but that's how that's the level of performance. That's that
Yeah, it's interesting in that video the planes trains video we're talking about
There's an interview with the three of them with candy Martin and Hughes at a press conference
And they specifically talk about the scene where Steve Martin flips out
I want a fucking car right fucking which is one of the funny scenes in the movie
And they talked about like
Was there any backlash over this scene because it's so vulgar
And Steve Martin's like no, we feel that we did it tastefully and nobody has complained not one person
Which is great and it's like man times have changed man like that's wild. Yeah, that that would even be a point of discussion
But the one storyline
That I actually do think is is a shame that was cut
Is that his wife Martin's wife through the movie thinks he's having an affair
And that's why he's not coming home and that adds so much weight
To when she meets John Candy in the end and realizes her husband wasn't lying like it
There really is this other guy
Yeah, and I was like that's that's a shame that that that stuff wasn't in there because that would have really added some real tension to the film
You know, I'm torn. I mean the only thing I would change about plans trans is the music the score is embarrassing at times
It really is. It's it's 80s, but it's also like beyond even other 80s movies of the time cheesy
And then when they're doing the rap version of Steve Martin going you're messing with the wrong guy
Yeah, it's terrible. That's that's the worst thing I've ever heard in a movie
It's not worse than the actual rap at the end of the movie dragnet
Get the anachroid and hunks do good good point you make a good point anywhere anything in the rap world in the 80s was definitely worse
But um, I talk of movie rap. Yeah, so um
What the hell was I talking about
The only thing you change in planes trains. Yes, so
I don't know how much I would love that because then you're kind of like
Why does his wife you'd have to get it done so quickly? Why does his wife think he's cheating like how about bad a husband to Steve Martin at home
Right now. I just think of him as this great husband you see his happy kids getting their beautiful pies and everything
and if I think of that this their relationship being so dark as for
her to think that he's cheating
over what seems to be a very innocent misunderstanding is kind of crazy
but
the like my buddy
John I saw
Plants trains in the theater with him a couple years back around Thanksgiving and we obviously love the movie
But at the end he's like man she is crazily overacting how emotional she is when Steve Martin comes home from this trip
Yeah, and then you realize that's why
For whatever reason to me I never thought it and it's actually a very very sad reason when I saw that when I was a kid
I was like that must be how happy families are
I was like I thought yeah, I was like oh that's how it plays in the movie. This is their right, you know
Yeah, I was like yeah, you know my mom doesn't give a shit when my dad comes home from being gone
But that's just because they don't like each other and happy families
I'm sure they cry and they're excited to see each other whatever. I thought it was a beautiful thing
So I don't know that you did need it however when he and what what made me convince is that when he's talking about it in that
YouTube video which is great and go watch it is
He talks about how the misunderstandings that they have are are like this and that he read this dialogue exchange
We'll just make sure you don't wind up with Dell's panties in your briefcase
And he goes you know, it's the funniest thing I had Dell's panties in my face this morning
Referring to the scene where he holds up his giant briefs to dry his face right
And she hangs up on him out of anger
That's a perfect strangers level
Kind of exchange to me that that that can't sustain the weight of are these guys
Gonna get a divorce or something, you know, right like any reasonable woman and that woman seems very intelligent
Just from the little we see of each other see if her in the movie
I just can't believe she wouldn't go
Hey, what the fuck are you talking about had her panties in her face?
And he goes oh no, I had his underwear, you know like it's one of those things where you just ask my
My assumption is that it's not played as if
They're in a terrible relationship, but that it's that the the it's alluded to that
He's always traveling and oh my god like is this why he's never home
And it's just sort of a paranoid thing that starts to build I don't I don't think it'd be played as our relationship
I may but maybe it is me to me
That's interesting though because if it is played that way
Again, that adds a little more dynamic to the characters where here's a guy that's got a perfect family
And is never there because he's a workaholic right and then
You got this other guy who all he would you would trade everything in the world to have this wife back who's dead for eight years
And he still talks to her picture. Yeah, you know, it's it's interesting
But I hope one day we get to see a little more of what was deleted and
You know, it's a great film. It's a great film
It is I'd love to watch anything they put out I think the
In terms of the cheating stuff my my guess is that every minute you spend away from those two actors
You're getting kind of frustrated. So for me now just seeing tiny flashes of his kids and his wife getting ready for Thanksgiving dinner
Is all I need to know
Sure, that's my guess is why I got cut because I just feel like that movie you just want to see those two guys interact
But that's me who know but also too when you when you watch this video and you see what they were
Lopping out of this film and the way the edits worked and that it still works as well as it does right right
Leagues to the ability of John Hughes and I don't know who directed that movie, but John Hughes. Oh, we directed it too. Okay. Sorry
That this is the kind of stuff where like as a writer I would be like I can't cut that out
What do you nuts like we need that right and like he found ways to make this movie still work
It's pretty pretty impressive pretty pretty impressive
So and the fact that he'd write these scripts in a week or less, you know
He wrote home alone in a weekend. It's it's kind of annoying to be honest with him. Yeah
I have a
I have a scary stuff
Yeah relates to today's film today's movie is
Maximum Overdrive
Which
Most people know at this point acdc did the soundtrack for it's half
Some of their you know already released songs and hits such as hell's bells and you shook me all night long and
They did
I think they did who made who for the movie
Yeah
so
So
I want to plug
It's not plug. I mean, it's just the thing I like
Push if you will given nod to acdc's newest album came out
It is called power up
It is a record nobody thought we'd see because if you know acdc
You know that in the last few years they've hit some real
turbulent times
Phil Rudd was fired again from the band this time because he was embroiled in a
scandal of trying to have his wife murdered potentially
happen
So he was kicked out
Malcolm sadly young died
Which is terrible and then cliff Williams the original bass player left the band
So the original lineup of this band had been cut down significantly
And then Brian Johnson had some hearing issue where he didn't know if
He'd ever be able to perform ever again
Um and over the course of the last couple years since then or whatever you know at one point they were touring with axle rows on vocals
Everybody else in the band was a villain except for angus
It just was sad. It was like this is it acdc's done. I guess it's over. We they had an amazing run
But all of a sudden all these secret rumbling started coming out of
Apparently the lineup is back in the studio working on stuff and more and more information came out
And then all of a sudden this year
acdc starts cryptically
Hinting on their social media power up get ready power up
And then sure enough it's announced new album
Cliff is back
Phil is back
Angus's nephew
Is filling in for Malcolm so they kept it in the family
Brian is back. They they were able to halt the hearing degeneration that was happening
Uh, and they put out this record power up
That I'm sure people were probably excited about people were probably skeptical
You know, are they going to be able to do this? Is this going to be some hodgepodge you know mix mix mix bag of whatever
thrown together
Turns out it's all songs that Malcolm wrote
With Angus before Angus passed so Angus is there pray you know in a way
and it is
Their best album
Since the original Brian Johnson years like since those first couple Brian you know back in black flick of the switch for those about the rock
those are kind of the three
Really really classic Brian Johnson records and then they've done a bunch since then and they've done some good records since then
But this album is so
fucking good and to hear these men of 70 whatever years old
playing and wailing like this like
It's just awesome like what a gift to the fans that we just thought we would never get it's it's
It's an incredible incredible record if you like acdc. I implore you to go listen to this record
Um, but isn't scary
Well, it they did the soundtrack to a horror movie so I'm just plugging it as
folks a little bit of a show never would have let the slide back in the day, but that's fine
But I want to it's it's worth talking about now. What is scary?
And I've also put it to the scary stuff
Amazon calm is selling arrow blue rays right now they always do but
They are insanely priced at the second at this moment really
An arrow we've talked about on the show. It's arrow and shout factory
That's where you're going for your special edition horror blue rays
I got reanimator special edition blue ray 4k transfer
For 1999 and then they added a additional discount to it
So I got it for like 16 bucks
And I got American Werewolf in London special edition blue ray
4k transfer for 16 99 that they added another $2 discount to
so for under $30
To just amazing blue rays of two classic classic horror movies and the arrow stuff for whatever reason is
Very well priced on amazon right now arrow has a lot more sales than screen factory ever does. I love screen factory
But it's a little tougher to get a sale out of them
Um arrow seems to kind of always be discounting things and and putting on sale so
I would say get your ass over there and they're not part of the black friday or cyber monday deals or anything like that
They're just they're just very well priced
Yeah, I um grab yourself some this will be posted
Probably while that's still going on on amazon. So we'll just throw some free advertising their way as we do
I mean maybe they're they're having a tough time
I also got by the way final it's finally out
Criterion collection the Irishman for 1999
blue ray
You know, so you can find some real nice deals on there right now. I have many
Both shout factory screen factory arrow films arrow though you got to be careful that you were not getting a
Overseas region unless we have a region free blue ray player
Because a lot of them are pretty region K own like okay at this point
Many of them are UK only so you got to be careful and actually some of the titles you most want are only over there
But they're doing a good job lately of doing both at the same time
But arrow is interesting to me because arrows a little
Lines a little more on the artsy side of it
You know
They do stuff where it's like this movie should have gotten more recognition
Arrow I would say arrow in their horror choices and releases. They take a little bit more of a criterion type of approach
Yeah
Scream is
Factory is great, but screen factory is a little more just like your classic 80s
Not so whatever harf you know, I mean like
You know you'll get stuff from screen factory and I have that is across the board considered a terrible film
But if you like that kind of thing, it's a lot of fun
Well arrow just put out a new giant flash Gordon and I still have never seen it
But I bought it side unseen because there was a great deal on it the 1982
Yeah, yeah, the one that great flick. Yes, hell of a lot of fun never seen man
The blue ray is really fun to watch because it's so crystal clear
It makes everything look extra fake
Which I think would be a
To to a to a disc credit. It's not it meant for some reason it makes it so much more wild to watch
It's really crazy. It's all right. It's a fun flick man
Into it
Yeah
Um, well, let's go over
folks to Pat's corner of movies
My I have all each one of my devices
Laptop iPhone and iPad are all broken in different ways right now
Everything is annoying the hell out of me and they're all broken you got a lot of bad luck with with tech man
Yeah
Sorry
I'm not that's not a judgment. I'm saying who I am
I feel for you. You're just one of those cursed tech guys
Uh
Joe I rewatched
Jiminy glitch in la la wood
Oh, let's talk about it babe
Now as has been well documented on this show the one thing
And Joe loves him as much as I that can always bring me to laughter in my worst of times my most stressed out times
I would always watch a Jiminy glitch interview before going to bed and find something to laugh at
The man has brought me untold hours of joy
So I was very excited about the movie especially when I heard that Martin sure was also going to be playing David Lynch
I was like this thing sounds insane
And it is the movie is insane
It's really crazy
There's a lot of improv stuff with just way too big of characters, you know
Like people trying to out big Jiminy, you know, and I'm most I'm talking about
John Michael Higgins who is ordinarily hilarious the dude from the Christopher Gas movies
um
But he plays some sort of almost like Borat type
Foreign character and it's just way too much. It's not funny for a minute
um
That stuff is kind of a problem
But what I was not expecting is how much I laughed and I think that's just because the bar is lowered so much
That watching it now with just no expectations
Any of the stuff with Jiminy and Jan Hooks is hilarious as husband and wife
Every one of those scenes is what yeah when she's trying to find her napkin
My napkin my napkin
Yeah, Jan Hooks is so funny in it. It's awesome
And I love a good showcase for her because I think she's so funny. Yeah
And I think much she's I think she's much funnier than
The women that came out Saturday night live they got much more attention your anagastias
Your shariotaries your Nora Dunes, you know for the reason
Hooks was always in like the very very minor supporting role and I always like she was like uh
She's well, it's like she she to me. She was like the J a second Jane Curtain
where I'm like and Jane Curtain is so good and she's had a great career
But like I don't think anybody ever thinks of her as a go -to like
SNL, you know heavy hitter, you know
Much obviously gilderadner from that period, right? You know right
But Jan Hooks, you know, she's always like she was the uh tour guide and Peewee's big adventure with the can you say a doby like she kind of
Steels that section of the movie at the Alamo and but that's how they always used her as in like one scene roles, which I never really got
It ain't a meritocracy as our buddy David Crumholts always says when I complain to him about Hollywood
Jiminy Glick and Lala would uh is insane the David Lynch stuff doesn't work at all
It's a pretty good impression, but like to what end, you know, it's it's such a weird choice and it just doesn't make any sense
But all the interview footage and there's some interview footage
You can only find in this movie makes it worth watching it makes it
You know a solid B -comedy the you who to Steve Martin that you always quote is incredible. It's one of the funny
Yeah, there's four outtakes at the very end during the credits. Yeah between Steve Martin and Kurt Russell
It just goes back and forth between so and
They are coming to fucking pieces like they can't keep their shit together. Yeah
Yeah, the Kurt Russell thing when he's like everybody said this would stiff
I should skip this and I mean Goldie Hahn just said it to me out in the hall
Yeah, it's a thrill to watch
I mean like Kurt Russell you never really see his private life at all so just to see him cracking up is great
But Steve Martin like you can count on one hand the amount of time you see in Steve Martin like crack up
He's just not he's so dry. He's not really that guy
Yeah, but anytime he's on jimmy click
He's like drying his fucking eyes and he he's got no comeback
And you see that like Martin short just can do rings around him in terms of improv. I mean
I saw him I saw them live together
And they had a lot of you know pre -plan bits that were very funny, but anytime they'd go off book
It would be Martin short saying something brilliant and Steve Martin standing like a deer in headlights every time
Yeah, it's uh
Yeah, it's uh my favorite line in the movie is when he starts choking at the dinner table
Jimmy glitz starts choking at dinner table and then he eats more food
He keeps chewing as as he's choking and a Jan hooks goes Jimmy stop eating and then he finally gets the food down he goes
I know it's how I'm strange, but sometimes when I'm choking more food helps. That's a very very funny line
Pat has stepped away from his computer, which is why you're not hearing any laughter
In reaction to that once in episode. He'll do this just I'll be mid -sentence. He'll step away
To to do god knows are you by the way, Pat? Are you at are you at home? Are you in Vegas right now? I'm at home
What
What room are you in now? This is we're just up by the deck. We set up our
Oh, okay, looks like you're in a Vegas like hotel room guy. I don't know
Um
I was just talking about the more food helps line when he's choking. Oh, yeah, yeah
I sometimes I find more food helps. Yeah, yeah, that's a great line
Yeah, it's just it's a it's a it's a really funny. It's a really really it's not a really funny movie
There are parts in it that make it worth watching. Let's put it that way. Yeah, it's a mix of just huge swings that fall
Completely flat and then really funny shit
I watched uh finally I finished it finally
And man I was kicking myself that it took me so long but it came in handy during these dark times. I finally watched cober guy straight through
Not only did I like it. I loved it. Uh, I can't believe
They got this much weight and mileage and depth out of a karate kid sequel 30 40 years later whatever it is
Just an awesome show. I mean, there's nothing I can say about it that hasn't been said already
but
The way they the nuance they bring to these characters the way you feel sorry for Johnny the way you recognize that Daniel's kind of a dick sometimes and
That you love both of them
You know, it's it's just oh and Mike just pointed out great TV show from a movie we were talking last episode name a good TV show that came from movie first
We're having a hard time thinking of any cober Kaiser great example. Yeah, that's true
um
Because you know, I was a big fan of the karate kid as a child and the three sequels. I mean could take a fucking walk. I mean they were not good
Um, but this is just
God damn it. It's good. I love it. I love it. And I just love how they get into
The the just the the themes of like a bad kid isn't just a bad kid
He's driven to being a bad kid because he's
abused in some way and he's hurt and he's lost and he's looking for a place and you know
seemingly great guy isn't always a seemingly great guy because they forget about what other people go through and how people struggle and they make a lot of assumptions about where other people are coming from to protect themselves or whatever
I just I loved it and they really
Really set this entire show so deep in like the mythology of the samurai and the dojo
And you know down to like
The almost mystical elements of it where like Daniel has a leader, you know a mentor from beyond the grave and Mr. Miyagi and
and crease comes back as the evil notorious, you know
uh warrior samurai and and and Johnny's conflicted and will he go to the light side of the dark side?
It would it's it's all just very very classic
archetypal
Good versus evil like it's just fucking great man. I just I love the show. I can't wait for season three
Uh, I'm excited. I will relay that to my best friends in L .A. do that show. I've been friends with them for 12 13 years
Uh, they have deserved this for quite some time and oh yeah, I want I'm I've gone to Vegas with them several times
But it's my buddy john her what's Hayden Schlossberg and my other buddy Josh healed who I met through them
Josh healed also did hot tub time machine john and Hayden also did Harold and Kumar
Anyway, I love Cobra Kai as well
See if you can get me a part
I'll see if I can get you a part as a bully or something
No, I want to come in as like my own dojo guy like I start a third dojo
See what me to pitch them on using a major
Driving force and the next season of the show. Yeah, maybe like a swords expert or something
You know, maybe bring up weapons into the mix, right? You know, that kind of thing
Nothing major. I don't like to ease in with a favor. You just like to go for the big time
I mean if you call that a big favor. I hate to see what you call it small favor, but uh, yeah
Uh, I
So
a picture
Called the right stuff
The astronaut show astronaut shit while the original movie. Yeah, but now they're making it into a TV show
Maybe that'll be a good movie that makes out. Yeah, um, not why I watched it
But I thought I had seen it. I know I rented it. It was one of those two VHS cassettes fused together with like hair covered velcro
That always really grossed me out and made me sick. It would make me really think about all the homes
That the tapes had been in all the hands that have touched them
And sometimes when I got one of those velcroed disgusting
VHS packs it was hard for me to deal with as a as a child with OCD
but
That may or may not be why I didn't watch it. I just never watched it. It was like three and a half hours long
About astronauts. I don't care about astronauts, but I watched the film. Yeah, I could give a shit
I
Fucking loved it. Wow
It was done by Philip Kaufman very underrated dude who was a big part of Raiders of the Lost Ark
He did the amazing invasion of the body snatchers remake with Donald Sutherland that we have both raised about on this show
He did the wanders which I recently watched which is a really awesome
sort of like
50s gangsters type thing that I thought was great as well
Very interesting director and the right stuff definitely his masterpiece
I
Loved it. I wasn't bored in the entire three hours plus running time
It's a lot of great actors in their early starting out days. You're Dennis Quaid
Ed Harris Fred Ward all you know all these great character actors pop up and it's Sam Shepard
Excuse me dialogue is great
Shepherd wrote it or he's just in it. He's just in it
Kaufman wrote and directed it but
You know it covers it's one of those things like JFK where it covers like 30 years and and it goes into all sorts of side plots and everything
but in the end I just felt like
Above all I was entertained, but I had also kind of learned some shit
Usually I don't like a movie that's trying to teach me things
But I felt like I learned a lot about how kind of America came to be
Through the space program it made it interesting even though I don't give a shit a great great movie
Ebert headed on his like top three of the 80s list
Um, and you know, it's that kind of movie. It's a big epic movie. I'm glad I watched it
I watched the wrong stuff which was a Leslie Nielsen spoof
Uh -huh, I watched the wrong guys. You remember that one with Richard Lewis as a Boy Scout
And Louie Anderson. Oh, yeah, Jesus Christ. What's it? I used to rent that all the time now. I'm leaving
But I'm telling you why I need water because my lips are smacking hang on all right. I'll do my next one
I'll go back to my
Theme from scary stuff tonight
I two other blu -ray as I got from Amazon that were also insanely well priced
I believe both of these were under $20
Uh, the first is dead of night
Uh, dead of night is a horror anthology. I don't know how many of you may or may not have seen it or if you're familiar with it or not
Uh, there was a sequel to it that was also called dead of night that was made in the early 80s or late 70s
It's okay, but it does have a story in it about a young boy
That has died who is sort of haunting his mother that is considered often one of the great anthology horror stories of all time
It makes a lot of those lists, but that's when I'm not talking that's not what I'm talking about the original
Dead of night was made in the late 30s
Talking the black and white British. Yeah. This thing was I watched that recently. I'll fucking love them
Yeah, this thing was out of print forever. You couldn't get it anywhere the first time I saw it
I actually saw a bootleg of it
That one of the guys from Monster Party podcast gave me
Shout out to the Monster Party guys great fucking podcast great dudes
Um, but that was the only way you could see it. You couldn't see it anywhere
And finally they have re -released this thing for in all of its 4k glory
Which anything that old and black and white and 4k looks fucking astounding. It's gorgeous
Uh, and it's the original horror anthology film
Uh, and some of the stories are a little freaky or than others
Uh, some of them are quirky
Some of them one of them is actually kind of comedic, but enjoyable
And it's just a great flick uh, if if for nothing else
just to get some horror history under your belt to see
What something like this uh in the style of horror film how it was done and handled and executed
At that at that time, you know, it's god. It's it's so old, but it's
It's so ahead of its time uh, I highly recommend watching it. It's an enjoyable watch
Martin Scorsese has claimed it's one of the scariest movies he's ever seen
I don't quite understand how that's possible other than when he was a kid
Yeah, so I think it's from the 30s, right? Maybe the 40s, but I think it's from the late 30s
I'm looking I would have thought later, but um, it's just a great flick and it's in 45
45 okay, and you can't beat this deal that you know, I think again
I think I got an Amazon for like $20 or something like
If you're a collector, it's something you should have on the shelf
Yeah, I saw it on uh Turner classic movies one night bought the blu -ray myself. It looks amazing and
But you know, there's one kind of goofy story about the two golfers that it's kind of yeah, that's like the comedy one the comedy one
Other than that it's all gold
The final one you can't go wrong. It's about a ventriloquist who thinks this dummy is alive and uh the best story is always about a dollar a dummy
Yeah, so check that out. I recommend you purchase it
I would like to say that I finally watched
David Cronenberg's naked lunch. I checked off the last Cronenberg that I had not seen. There was only a couple of them
It's a toughy. It's not an easy
uh
Naked lunch not my favorite, you know, it is
Near the but there was definitely a reason it was this one an M butterfly where the two I hadn't seen and when I watched them both
I was like, you know, interesting glad I saw them. I think there's a reason
I didn't rush to see these two movies, but naked lunch
William S. Burrows, you know famous kind of junkie poet author
It's like an adaptation of his book
But also incorporate some biographical information from the life of William Burrows
I don't know enough about the man or care enough to kind of go on this journey
Peter Weller is not my favorite actor out certainly outside of the Robocop franchise
but
Cronenberg does make it work. I mean, I was entertained throughout but mostly because of his disgusting aliens and creations that you meet along the way
Including because the asshole talk thing and I was just gonna say including no no no including having to look at a close close tight close up on a pucker to asshole talking
For what seems like 20 minutes of screen time
uh
So look not it's not a favorite, but uh, I do love all the like I mean he clearly got a big budget to work with and came up with some truly
cool creations sort of like Star Wars bar type creations
If there's the roach that types next to him or whatever. Yeah, and like typewriters that like emerging into aliens or whatever
And it's all kind of cool and gross
uh
Little too much asshole time naked lunch not one of my faves, but but worth checking out
I have the criteria on you know, maybe there's cool features on it. I don't know. I don't know William S. Burrows
He used to guest star on a lot of 90s old songs
Was that your third or your second?
That was my did I go first? Do you go first? I think you
No, you did right because I did Cobra Kai second
I don't know man. Oh jeez well anyway my final
Uh, and again another another blue ray I bought that has been transferred to 4k of a classic horror film that I'd never seen
Uh, I'm almost embarrassed to say I hadn't seen it till now. Uh, the old dark house starring Boris Karloff. Sure
uh
Again, not the scariest film in the world, but certainly creepy certainly us at atmospheric the transfer looks tremendous
And this is one that you can grab on Amazon again. I think it was 20 bucks
It's just so worth it to have something that's this quality and this will done. That's also such a classic of the genre
You know, it's about a group of people to get stranded at an old dark house as you might have thought
uh overnight and
there's
a lunatic upstairs that is possibly going to get loose. I mean, it's a pretty basic storyline
But it's a lot of fun a lot of eccentric characters Karloff is really great in it
It's a role that uh that I don't think he gets enough recognition for because much like Frankenstein
It's him in a very interesting get up makeup wise where he doesn't really have dialogue
He's got to do a lot through grunting and and body language and facial expressions and he's fantastic
There's a reason where that guy's a legend um
If you haven't seen it you should get this if you have seen it and you like it you should get this it's it's it's
It's hard to go wrong with uh and they're just doing such
Yeah, there was a time where blu -ray just meant
They put it in a blue case and it where you were like it looks like the fucking DVD man like it's like there's not that much of a difference
Now with these 4k transfers. They're doing such a good job and they're really really painstakingly restoring these things
And it's not a restoration in the sense of like they've colorized it and ruined it
They just make it look exceptional and I won't buy a lot of things on on 4k blu -ray
In fact a lot of my horror I like to buy on DVD because it has a little more of a grain equality to it
Some of it I even buy on VHS
But with these classic old black and whites in particular
I I think nothing can beat these 4k transfers. I think like you're just
It's almost like you're seeing the movie for the first time like when it came out in the theater and you know in 1940 whatever
So it's worth checking out
I think the old dark house was like 1920 or something. It's on shudder. I've actually never seen it
But that one might be from the thirties. I mean it's a talk to you so it's not yeah, but uh
But yeah
Pretty cool stuff now Joe isn't it true that sometimes you'll even buy a horror movie on an eight track tape
Mm -hmm, and then just listen to it
Yeah, sometimes I'll call
Clint Howard and have him come over and just act it out for me. I'll pay him enough
That he'll do it. I will say
Clint Howard has appeared in every single one of Ron Howard's movies. I'm as far as I know
And he wasn't in hillbilly elegy and of all the movies that Clint Howard would fit right into
Ha
It's hillbilly god damn allergy. Yeah, yeah, he does have that look. Yeah, maybe he read the script and was like yes
Sorry, Ron. I'm gonna sit this one out
Yeah, maybe the star of the ice cream man was to be surning in this case
Yeah, it's weird because he did put him into solo. He's in solo. Yeah, he's in every one. I think yeah
I like Clint Howard. I think he's I think it's fun seeing him pop up and stuff
He's my favorite Clint Howard thing is when he's playing that on Star Trek the original series where he's playing like
That baby that runs the planet
Yeah, like that drinks that like green. Oh, right. Yeah, it's really whacked out man. Yeah
Disturbing but a lot of fun a lot of fun
Well, that's all I did three. That's all I got
Well, if I am doing another one
I'll do and butterfly and finish that off the other Cronenberg piece I hadn't seen
By the way a real thrill to go through the man's filmography. He's got
I mean definitely like periods where he's like at his peaks
definitely like the history of violence and
Eastern promises era was a huge comeback for him and then his 80s rise up through the fly his masterpiece
You know pretty hard to beat. I love the dude. I love kind of following him on these journeys
And butterfly video drone too. You just watched right just rewatch that one amazing movie
um
And butterfly again not one of his best so I hate to focus on these two negatives, but these are the ones I hadn't watched
It's Jeremy Irons. He falls in love with this
sort of gaysha
singer and
Learns that
She is a man the actor John Lone
um
And he's still kind of wants to continue the relationship and this was based on a true story and it like went to trial and the judge is like how did you not know
Because you follow their romance
And he's like so you guys fucked thousands of times and you never felt as dick or anything and and it's very weird
They don't really even answer the question in the movie. They're just kind of has this thing where they're like we made it work
So I guess they like he just kind of fucked this dude in the ass for all this time
and
Then it's like the question is to what extent did Jeremy Irons know
And wait, why do they go to court? Is he like suing her because he's like you didn't tell me your man. She was a spy
Okay, so there's espionage involved in it. It's not as exciting as it sounds
For me the issue is unlike the crying game where like you completely believe that this was a beautiful woman he was hanging out with
um
This it looks like John Lone in
Drag and not really good drag
So the first scene when Jeremy Irons is like oh hello like enchanted to meet you. You're like wait a minute
That's a dude. It's like it's very glaringly obvious. Yeah, it's like a in Jack and Jill when Pacino falls in love with girl
Exactly, so like and believe me. I'm not trying to make any political statement about my reading of this movie
I'm just saying I'm knowing that John Lone is playing this part and then seeing this guy who looks like a man
Um, I just it was hard it was hard to believe and that's whatever review at the time said
I read a lot of them to kind of see what other people made of the movie um, but for all of them
It was just like it doesn't work because you don't buy it. He's got stubble in some scenes, you know, and he does
so
I think in the end
What you're sub left with and Kronenberg is too smart to not notice this
I think what he's trying to say is that Jeremy Irons probably knew
Right and was happy to be in a homosexual relationship
But then couldn't come out with that information to the world
But it was so subtle that every major critic at the time just seemed to completely miss the point of the movie
But um, it does throw you at first. You're like, you know, it's a very Mrs. Doubtfire form of drag that you're not really buying
When you first see him
but um
Again, just like naked lunch interesting not one I'll revisit all right
So we get on to our picture at hand
Yeah, today's picture is maximum overdrive uh, which some consider to be
The worst of the Stephen King adaptations uh, some consider it to be a fun, but terrible 80s classic
Many consider it to be one of the worst films of all time as I live doing a little research on it
I'll say this right off the bat. I was expecting much more of a shit show
Uh, it is not a good movie, but it was not bad. It was not outrageously bad enough for me
Uh, there there's plenty to pick apart in this thing
But I right off the bat. I was disappointed that it wasn't
It wasn't fun bad. It just felt like a mediocre 80s movie
My exact same issue we were talking about with hillbilly algae like I was I told my friend like it's just not even fun
It's just too bad to even be fun and that's what this felt like to me as well
I got no entertainment out of it. I don't think it worked in any way
I think certain scenes were definitely staged and edited in a very baffling manner
Uh, we've come to learn that Stephen King directed this film while blazingly high on cocaine
He didn't know what he was doing and he doesn't really remember doing it
Yeah, if you watch the trailer where he says if you want something done right you got to do it yourself. I watch that today
It's yeah
He is he is cocked in this fucking trailer. I mean, it's like
Yeah, and it's the official trailer. He's like I'll throw you a solid
I'm going to do the press for this movie and really get out there and do a trailer like I'm Alfred Hitchcock
But Alfred Hitchcock wasn't doing this like coked out hillbilly character that you're doing
It's like I'm Stephen King. We're like, so are we supposed to believe that you're scary
Like what's the point of that? And did you notice and I've pointed this out to you before for some reason one of his eyes is slightly crushed in the trailer
Which is very gross
That I've ever noticed with him, you know
So yeah, it's weird like
Now he's he the trailer is nuts. It's well worth checking out
um
Dino D. Laurentus who was doing a lot of these kind of mid -budget pictures at the time making a ton of money off of them
He you'll see his name in a lot of the classic 80s films and 70s films and beyond kind of when you know you're in trouble
As soon as you see Dino D. Laurent you're like oh boy, you can be you can be but the man behind red sonia
You know, it's like yeah, but also Conan
But very interesting interestingly
In Virginia when this film they were right around the corner from where blue velvet was filming
And the but the two were both Dino D. Laurentus productions
I think the man did it make some great work
So he did blue velvet and he got the productions lined up right next to each other like Roger Korman style
And he would go back and forth between them
And the rumor and it's a big rumor that you can look up on the internet. It's out there is that
David Lynch was brought in to direct one scene from maximum overdrive
What's seen
That they won't say and and a lot of people don't believe it
But that's the that's the lore is that he came in and they brought him in like we need David let him direct this scene
I so you to assume it's a scene that feels lynchian in the movie
But none of them do the movie feels like they're choked out randlings of a madman
There's one sort of lynchian scene and it's the opening scene when Stephen King does the cameo
Holy shit, I bet he directed that yeah, yeah, he's at the ATM the ATM says you're an asshole. Yeah, and it does
The most insane close -up on Stephen King's face and he's like honey
There's ATM just call me an asshole like that's straight out of like twin peaks, you know
That they did that they were like you need another director and he's like I'll get you David
Yeah, but um if you don't know the plot of the film it's based on a short story called trucks by Stephen King
And a meteor and which which of his books is it in night gallery? I don't know which one. It's end to be honest
I've never had any interest in the subject matter. It cars coming to life to me does not
Christina was his
What's that? Have you seen trucks the remake of it? I've tried to watch it three times since we decided to do this podcast. It stars
uh
Timothy what's his name the redhead from 30 something Timothy busfield. Yeah, yeah, I look like him big compliment
It's it's it's I don't think you do but uh it's um
I will say this from what I saw of trucks before I fell asleep every time I tried to watch it
It seems like it captures the spirit a little more of a Stephen King short story things feel a little more desolate
And a little more desperate right off the bat to me
uh Stephen King's version of his own story opens with uh
I mean and again right away, you know you're in trouble. There's a text blurb on the screen
That the world is in the orbit of this meteorite. Oh, yeah
And you're like okay, so that's what's causing this and then throughout the movie
They're like married with children level direction like like like scenes like directed like it married with children segments
Where like there's a customer reading a newspaper pulled up over their face on the front page just says
Meteor travels close to earth some say weird things are happening. It's like
It's really heavy -handed. It's really ridiculous. The machines all come to life
halfway through the film a married couple comes
Uh consisting of the wife is the voice you know the lady that you yearly smith
I think her name is that does the voice Alisa Simpson
Um she plays the wife and the husband. I don't know who he is
But this is why the movie's problematic for some reason their car doesn't turn on that like
Everybody else's vehicles are turning on them and whatever and yet they're able to just operate their car and get safely to the place where all the other cars are being crazy
Yeah, the point where the other cars kill their car like run over their car and smash it and right it just doesn't really make sense
At some point the the trucks and the cars start communicating through Morse code
And a boy there is able to read and understand Morse code
And he learns that the trucks just want fuel they just want fuel and everything will be fine
So then you get a big montage of them feeding the
trucks fuel. I mean I
It was a disaster. It was the disaster of a film. They want fuel
Everybody is trapped inside of a roadhouse diner right while the trucks circle the trucks need fuel yet
They are constantly burning their own fuel that they need so desperately by just doing donuts around the parking lot
And you're saying that also just drive over the diner you're a truck
Well, yeah, and you're saying why are they not driving over the diner just killing everybody because that's what they want to do
And then you realize oh, it's because they need the people to give them fuel
But the people also figure out pretty early on. It's this comment that flew close to earth
All we have to do is wait this out for seven days and you're like
Yes, so wait it out. You're in a fucking diner like there's a week's worth of food in there just cook the food and hang out some flapjacks
um
Halfway through I was talking to pingstone about the movie halfway through the obligatory 80 scene of a fat guy taking a shit
with like
Leslie Nielsen sound effects going on as he reads a porn omag, you know
Uh
King really goes for the dumb joke in this like repeatedly man. Yeah, we're repeatedly
um
Well, the big the famous scene is the guy getting hit in the nuts with the the cans out of the
vending machine, you know
Always wanted to see somebody get hit in the nuts, but like that's all I really knew about this movie was that happened
That's not a sequence is is kind of cool like a steam roller comes in and like runs over the kids in the little league team and kills the coach and all that
Like so that seems kind of cool. There's a really great sequence on a bridge
Where the bridge opens while cars are on it
And like all hell breaks loose, but the problem is and this is my biggest issue with the movie
It's this the events are so out of sequence
So you basically start with this huge showpiece of a bridge opening
Because the machine decides to open it while the cars are on it everybody's in peril, but then nobody dies
Because it's clearly too early in the movie and to have that big of a disaster that early in the movie is gonna take the outside of anything you do on a smaller level
Right, so you're sitting there going this this this should be like act two stuff this should be like
You see a couple you see the little league guy get hurt
And then killed and then all of a sudden you see how much bigger this can get yeah, but when you start off with like the biggest
You know most tragic event of the movie
And then anything you follow it with you're just not worried at that point
You're not really that concerned if these six people in this roadhouse get out or don't get out
I read that originally
The the test cut that went to preview audiences that kids had exploded like scanner style
With blood all over the place and like everybody just flipped out
So they removed that from the movie, but king was just not making good choices at this time
No, there is a cool sequence where the the kid that survives rides down a suburban street on his bike
And sees like dead people everywhere as a result of their machines turning on them
But for some reason those cars that have killed people that have dead people in them
Aren't moving or doing anything like all the other cars do after they kill people
So again, there's no real rhyme or reason to any of this. It's very unclear as how to all of it works
Meteor logic it. I mean Stephen King as everyone knows
You know everything's good until you got to explain it and then he just falls on his face time and time and time again
And if I'm not mistaken now I did say this
Uh off the off the show
How's that look band? It's not really any worse than most of the Stephen King adaptations
You know, I mean like there's a handful of killer Stephen King adaptations most of them you're like
All right, you know
But it was but I would say even if we're talking like even if we're talking lower end like we'll say thinner or something like that
Um, this is significantly worse. I love well thinner is one of my higher up ones
I really like thinner, but I'm talking like riding the bullet
Sometimes they come back
You mean silver bullet? No, riding the bullet is one about a highway called the bullet
That's a movie
Yeah, I own it. It was Mick Harris. I think directed it. It was made for TV
I bought it on blind faith because the on the back of the box
It said it was a quote from Stephen King that said nobody has ever gotten my work more right than in this movie
And I was like wow, this has got to be great. Yeah, and then you're like boy, it's not it's not really that good, but um
You know
It's okay
You know, it's an okay movie like if you want to see a goofy -ass 1980s Emilio Estevez ridiculous nonsensical action movie
I mean, there's tons of action. There's tons of violence
Um, it's good to see you on the soundtrack. Yeah
It's good enough, but I do believe
I believe we talked about this when we reviewed pet cemetery
when uh
The exec was trying to get that made
She talks about repeatedly her boss being like don't bring up that fucking Stephen King's script
Nobody wants to see Stephen King movies
Which is hard to believe that there was a time where that was happening
But I think this movie was probably what did it? This was probably the thing that made everybody go layoff for this guy
Man like this sucks. Yeah, you know
You put yourself out there in that kind of way where you're the trailer
It's like if you're not Alfred Hitchcock you can't be pulling something like that. It's just embarrassing and
I'm way harsher on this the new joe. I thought it was an embarrassing movie
I didn't see why anyone throughout the years has found this movie fun
Feel like maybe like silver bullet is another example silver bullet was much better
But I feel like people see these movies a bunch on cable when they're kids and they start to feel they're better than they are
I have many movies like this myself
So I understand it
But like catching up with something like this now. I just thought this was absolute shit to be honest with you
Uh, yeah, I look I can't argue that
I can't argue that
Yeah, uh, the the real kicker is at the very end
They all escape on a boat
Right which for some reason the motor boats aren't alive right which are two feet from the trucks that are controlled by the meteor
Yeah, and then so they all get away
Almost nobody in this diner dies like they all kind of pretty much live except the asshole boss played by the guy that plays
Commissioner Gordon and the Burton Batman film
Who is playing this thing like he's the bandit and some are uh smokey
Smoke is that guy's name smokey?
Well, it buford teed justice is that buford teed justice that's what I'm trying to think about he's smokey
Yeah, yeah, I mean, he plays this thing through the roof as I'm sure he was directed to do by coke doth Stephen King
Well, and then you got the least Simpson lady like
He's like doing gags with her through the whole thing movie ends with her barfing
Yeah, like it's it's rough stuff and he
King himself should not act
Obviously, you know, I want to make that real clear
He's he's worse than Tarantino. Uh, he's worse than Tarantino. I disagree with that see I think
You know, you know how much I love creep show
I think the loan some death of Jordy Varyl is the greatest creep show story ever and that's king come solo the whole time
I think he's great in it
You know, he can play a certain type of guy, but he he's
There's enough know -how here behind the camera that I'm like if he wasn't completely rocked
He might actually have done a decent job with this. I don't know
But um, I read this oral history like
It was an oral history written by as an offshoot of the how did this get made podcast?
So if you wanted to google it, that's how you'd find it
but the guy was
Doing kind of this oral history of the making of the movie and they asked about this alleged cocaine problem that even Stephen
King himself has said he doesn't remember doing the movie
And everybody's like oh, I didn't see that I never saw that side of my never saw that side of him
But then they all said well and they all had these side stories and the one said, you know, we would start shooting at
7 a .m. And he would have his first beer and then by the time we broke for launch he'd had he'd have had 10 beers
And then he would have an additional like case of beer as the night went on
So if you're doing that and blow will I mean lord knows what was going on forget why he's doing the blow
Yeah, I'm tired. It's like yeah, he hits 12 beers
They say he'd go into watch dailies and he'd be like so bored and and antsy and like I gotta get out of here
I got to get out of here and I'm like yeah, that was the coke that you're claiming you didn't see right right
The uh and then at the end of the film another text blurb comes up on the screen
That not only explains that seven days later as the
Meteorite passed out of Earth's orbit everything went back to normal adds another element
That a Russian weather satellite satellite was shot down
Over the orbit in over the United States
So then you're like well
Wait, what was wait a minute was it the satellite that caused it or was it the meteorite right right where's the meteorite
Just was a cover up for the satellite. It's so fucking confusing man. It's just
It's just uh none of the details in the right place in this movie
It feels and you know, it's hindsight you wouldn't have known it if you watched it in 1987 or whatever
But it in hindsight it feels like the kind of story you come up with when you're rambling on coke and a bar
You but Stephen King had had the level of success where somebody would go okay
You know like I just agreed to it
But it's all like and then what if then then this and then the the machines are actually the ones
That's what it feels like and to me I was it just annoyed me
I found myself usually in my old age. I turn movies slowly up and up and up and up
And this one I kept turning down and down and down. I just wanted it to be over. I hate it
Yeah, I picture him pitching this to a 10 -year -old Joe Hill like as he's trying to put him to sleep and these exact like
Sounds good, Dad. Yeah
Not a good movie
Sadly, I was really hoping it was gonna be this wild ride and like I was gonna be like this is so bachelorette
I can't deny it. I love it, but I just didn't I just didn't it's just not a good flick
Same here, you know
I was hoping for something along the lines of like a sleep away camp or something where like you know
When I stumbled upon that I was like oh shit
It's a lost classic and this is I kind of always held this one out as like someday. I'll be ready for this
But it wasn't it wasn't today folks
Well, the trailer are also kind of paint. I remember seeing the trailer a lot as a kid and it really
Showcase that that truck the toy truck with the green dragon's face on it or goblin's face
And I always thought that looked so cool and then I realized as I was watching this
It's literally just the green goblin from spider -man. They just ripped it off and put it on the truck
You feel like they maybe got it from a party store and it just was the green goblin. Yeah, yeah, it is the same thing
So no the movie sucks
Uh, anyway, my my name is Patrick Walsh. I'm at the Patrick Walsh at Instagram and Twitter
Um, I recently dropped an hour -long Pat solo movie corner and I'll be doing it again next month tell your friends
We're on patreon. Thanks all of you so much for sticking with us throughout these troubled times happy holidays
Thank you also for me folks. We really really appreciate the support we love you all. Thank you Emily Simpson for
Being our fine fine controller of the merch store and and the
Facebook group and all that stuff. Thank you Emily
uh
Go check out the no -press network
You can find our page on youtube
Uh, you can find us on instagram. You can find us on twitter
Uh, it has launched launch shows our hay babe featuring christus definitely and
salvo cano and then
salvo cano and myself doing taste buds where we debate food. I think you'll like these people come check them out
we're gonna have a patreon with
three full video episodes of each show every single month and one full video episode will be released for free on youtube every month
And then audio will be available wherever you get your podcast or free um
Also come by joey roses the sandwich shop pop -up at the stand in new york city 12 to four every once at a friday delicious sandwiches for a great price
judo rose a comedy on twitter and instagram. We thank you. We love you
We'll see you next time and we'll see you in hell