Welcome to We'll See You In Hell. It's the podcast that covers those flicks you like to watch
and then hear other guys talk about. My name is Joe DeRosa. I'm Patrick Walsh folks and today we're
talking about Bill and Ted's excellent adventure, Bill and Ted's bogus journey and Bill and Ted
face the music. Yes. I think you're going to say something else. No, that's it. That's what we're
discussing. The whole trilogy. Yeah. And it's not a terribly painstaking trilogy to go through.
Usually when we do these franchise episodes, we don't do the segments, but you know,
there's not too much to delve into with Bill and Ted so we can... You can't discuss face the music
without discussing the 30 -year journey that brought us there. You know. Yeah, I agree. A journey
through space and time. I've been on a real animal farm kick. The book. The book. The cardio book.
The cartoon. The made for hallmark television movie that the Jim Henson company did the puppet
and animatronics for. Why are you so into animal farm? I listen to... I've become a staunch audible
listener. Throughout the pandemic, I always liked audible, but throughout the pandemic,
it has really served me well. And I have taken two going to bed almost every night to some form of audio
book on audible because I find it comforting. And most recently, I said, you know what? I always
liked that book animal farm. I bet that's a fun like sort of bedtime story. You got your talking
animals and whatnot. Sure. So I downloaded it. And it's great in audio form. If you're on audible,
I highly recommend the audible audio book. I forget the name of the gentleman that reads it,
but he's fantastic and he does a really, really nice job with it. It also includes a really
interesting forward about the author who George R. Wells who also wrote 1984 and his take on the book
and you know, sort of blah blah blah. So in listening to that, I remembered also really liking
the made for TV movie. Ralph Koschum is the narrator. Thank you, Mike. Mike is on it with the info.
I remembered really liking that movie when I saw it in college. So I rewatched it. It was on YouTube.
I could you just watch it for free. It's legally on there, but you could watch it. So I rewatched it
and realized, oh, I was high out of my mind in college. This movie is terrible. And then I watched
the old cartoon, which is also on YouTube because I thought, well, maybe that adaptation is more accurate
to the book, which it is. And it still sucks. I guess there's some nostalgia factor there for you.
If you saw that growing up or something. But it's one of these things where I'm just like,
this is such a simple story. It's so simple. And the idea of it is so intriguing. Animals are being
mistreated. I overthrow the farm. The powers that be, meaning the humans that are thrown out of
their own farm try to retake the farm and fail. And then as the farm becomes prosperous, the animals
become corrupted. And it's the cycle all over again. And it's it's a great allegory for this is
absolute power. Power brings, what is it? Absolute power corrupts absolutely. It's great. And for some
reason, they fuck this up repeatedly in the adaptations of it. They change the speeches the animals make.
They change the sequence of events. They change. They add like a happy ending to the hallmark one
where they're excited about new humans moving in, which really undercuts the whole point of the book.
I just don't get. It's just the simplest thing. It's right there. It's like, it's like so in the book,
Old Major, who's the old pig with all the wisdom, he's the one that creates the the you know,
the league of animals, whatever the hell it's called. And creates all their rules and everything.
And then he dies early on in the book. So he's not there to guide everybody. But in the book, he gives
this amazing speech about how the animals are mistreated and why they need to rise up and all this
stuff. And in every adaptation they've done of it, they rewrite the speech. They change. You know,
it was written by George Orwell. Yeah. It's perfect. Just copy the speech and paste it into the
script. Yeah. Why are you changing it? It sets everything up. It must have been some like we can have
people revolt. And when they watch this pig talk or something like that, who knows what it was?
I read Animal Farm in junior high. I don't remember it. But it must have been the message was too powerful
or something. But then why do it? I mean, the TV movie, there's no excuse for as to why it doesn't work.
The cast is great. The voice cast is great. You got Henson's company doing the puppets. Yeah.
And still somehow they missed the fucking mark on this thing. But I mean, the voice cast is like
Patrick Stewart, Ian Home, Kelsey Grammer, Julia Louise Griffis. It's like, how is this not working,
man? I just don't get it, but it just doesn't work. Did you see this week, Kirstie Alley tweeted about
the new Oscar guidelines and the punchline in all caps was Oscar Orwell. Yeah. No, I didn't see that, but
the guidelines are a little nutty. They're a little nutty. And then when you really kind of look at them,
it's like you have to do two or four of these things. What's going to happen is that they'll put more
people of color on their advertising and promo departments since that's one of the four. They'll find
ways around it. But it's almost like they intentionally set up a system that people could go around.
And you know, there's going to be people saying, well, hey, this Hispanic guy who has four lines,
he's a supporting member of the cast. You know, it's it's got so many ways that it's going to blow up
and go wrong. But let's see how it plays out. I do I think looking for more inclusion is a bad thing,
but I think if you're going to say the awards, it like have to have like if you want best picture,
you have to be the I was just thinking about the movies that would not have been allowed to be nominated
for best picture. And you know, even though it wasn't, I think Glen Gray Glen Ross would probably be
one of those movies, you know, that certainly movies that just wouldn't meet the criteria.
But I think by and large, most of them in 2020 will. It's just sort of odd to put
I think I think and win an award. I think diversity is a just cause. Absolutely. I think the prejudices
of Hollywood are terrible things and need to be cast aside. But I also think legislating this
and its own in their own way is bad. You know, and you know, it's like the example I will always use
is I support Black Lives Matter. But if I was somewhere where they said you have to wear this Black Lives
Matter t -shirt, I would say I don't have to do anything. Tell me what I have to do. Let me express
myself and support the things I want to support. I think it's dangerous when you start getting into
telling people they have to do this, they have to do that. That's just my opinion. I also think
that it's despicable coming from Hollywood because as we've said before in the show, Hollywood created
these problems. We didn't create them. The artists didn't create them. Hollywood created them.
So them now making all these outlandish rules about how you have to play in their game.
This is the equivalent of the guy that has such a fucking coke problem.
You know, he has to get a friend to hide his coke from him. And then he yells at the friend if he
finds the coke. You know what I mean? It's like you're at the asshole, man. Like this isn't my
problem. You did this. Why do I now have to have this weird responsibility because you can't control
yourself. So that's what bothers me. And as you pointed out when we talked about this on the phone
the other week, it's really doing a disservice to independent filmmakers because there's a lot of
independent filmmakers and everybody knows that if you're going to make an independent film as we
talked at length about the trauma guys and all that, which that would never get nominated anyway.
But there are plenty of independent films over the years that have broken through and gotten nominated.
When you make a truly independent film, you have to use the resources available to you. And just
because you don't have a diverse group of people who are able to fill out your crew or whatever does
not mean that you're against diversity. It might mean it's all you have access to. So now given
these guidelines, you could in theory make a movie, for instance, like Trans America that highlights
the struggles of a trans woman. But if your cast and crew don't meet the diversity criteria,
well, forget the message doesn't matter. Forget what it does for the cause doesn't matter.
It's not eligible anymore to get the notoriety that it could have gotten. And what this is eventually
going to lead back to is what always happens every time these diversity conversations and debates come
up in Hollywood, it goes back to being all white because everybody is so fucking scared to offend anybody
that they start. So now now you got a movie and they go, well, the hero was going to be not white,
but we didn't want to do the condescending thing of the ethnic savior of the white people.
And then the other people that were being saved were not going to be white. But then it was going
to be a white savior incident. And we couldn't do that. And then we were going to make the bad guys
not white, but then it was going to look like we were criminalizing minorities. So now just make
everybody white. And then we can't offend anybody. And then you're right back to fucking square one
again. Yeah. You know, meanwhile, if they had cast a trans person in the lead role in Trans
America, then it would be fine. However, the Oscars already nominated her Felicity Huffman for playing
a trans person. Right. So like, which in this day and age would have been a problem. Which is interesting.
You guys have been nominating, you know, let's say Jared Leto for playing a gay man. He won the Academy
Award three years ago. So now you're saying, okay, these are wars that we said, and at the time,
not only did they just give these awards to people, they saw it as an amazing thing that they themselves
were doing for for awarding gay representation or trans representation Hollywood. They couldn't have
padded themselves in the back any harder. But now it's that that was gross. They're acting as if
they didn't do it. It's very Trumpian as well. It's all it's all gross. But I don't think anything
that leads to more diversity is a problem. I don't think this is going to really fucking anybody up.
But if it is an independent film and it's four friends in high school or let's say like host that we
talk about in the last episode, host isn't going to be nominated for anything. But that's an all white
cast. Maybe one, I don't maybe one of the girls was the Gemma. I think there's the name, the girl
that I said, it's sort of the bad guy in quotes. Right. Yeah. She's Asian. Yes. That's correct.
Why, you know, white director, white writer, whatever else. It's like, okay, these guys
using the resources they had available to themselves and limited money really tried to do a
production and made something really incredible. I don't know that they should be punished because
in their little circle of friends, there wasn't a black person. Should you have black friends, of course,
should they be in the movie? Yes, maybe. But it's it's it's that's an odd precedent to me. I don't
I don't know. It's good and it's bad and then that's okay. But as for right now, I think they're
going to run into problems. Let's say I were to write a movie about three old racists, you know,
three Archie bunkers who are in an old folks home. And let's say it's like a mammoth thing,
like a play almost where it's three old white guys in an old folks home. And they through the course
of discussing the black lives matter movement at the end aren't racist anymore. Let's just say as
a made up movie, obviously, we know it's made up that that movie couldn't be nominated for things
even though it is dealing with issues of race, this fictitious movie I made up. And maybe it's maybe
it's the movie that helps people understand racism better. You know, maybe it maybe maybe maybe maybe
maybe I'm just saying, when you put on these hard guidelines like this, you must do this to win
our award even though we've actively gone away from this for a century now is a little strange
and very hypocritical while also being a good thing. Well, also too, it's you brought up the
Leto thing. Jared Leto, that was a huge, in my opinion, that was a huge step in the right direction
into mainstreaming this conversation that needs to be had about different types of lifestyles
that certain people are unfamiliar with. That was a movie that allowed me to discuss the value
of a trans person's life or lifestyle with my parents. Yeah. Who were in their 70s when they saw
that and had never in their lives met a trans person. It opened them up to go, oh, wow, this is like
not what maybe I would have imagined or whatever. That's a huge step in the right direction. Not saying
that from now on, those types of roles should just go to anybody or shouldn't be considered more for
trans people first. Not saying any of that. All I'm saying is to set up this criteria where it can
only work in a certain way is madness to me. I get that the intention on paper is coming from
the right place but I think the intention is being made out of guilt. I think the intention is being
made to it's a gesture to overcompensate for their past mistakes in that community and in that
industry. And I think it's also incredibly condescending to the people that they want to help
supposedly. I help. And it's something that I don't think people can criticize. You know, I don't
even know we've just been canceled. Even diverse people, trans people, LGBTQ people.
I'm sure right now they see some issues with this and maybe can't speak out on it because it is
a step in the right direction. And I think it is coming from a place of let's do better, let's help. But
I think you made a great point that I hadn't even really thought of in that like
Lithgow playing a trans person in world according to Garpe in 1982. You know, people go to see that
movie and it's like, Oh, okay, what a beautiful performance. I get this. I like this person.
If you cast Hugh Jackman as a trans person, your family will go see it. If you cast
you know, one of the up and coming trans actors in Hollywood and good on them,
your family will not see it. And it will be an independent movie that will never cross their radar.
Never. Oh, you because of the exposure. You mean it won't get the same note. Right? Yeah. Yeah.
You don't have a big trans actor that is going to get my mom and dad out of the out of the house to go see
the new movie starring a trans actor. Now hopefully in 10, 15 years we do have that. And this
initiative may help. And that's great. I'm just saying like, you know, people are still furious about
Green Book winning best picture. A movie that everyone I know kind of out of the side of their
mouth is like, I thought I was pretty entertaining, you know, but everybody is pissed about Green Book
because it, you know, it was the white savior thing and et cetera, et cetera. And I get those issues,
but for if you think that this country that is half voting for Trump is going to go watch say
moonlight and learn about the black LGBTQ experience and watch that two hour movie or watch any movie
where two men are having sex or whatever it may be, you're just wrong. And that's unfortunate. It's
a terrible thing about the world, but those people will watch Green Book and it will make them better
and slightly less racist people. And for that to be a bad thing to you is kind of nuts. Every movie cannot
be this groundbreaking thing like so a 24 or whatever, they make these amazing artistic movies for
a very small audience. Those movies are not going to help change the world. They're going to help
people who already are very tolerant and accepting of different lifestyles who are not racist people.
They'll say that's a work of art, you know, I love and they are that's a good, so it's an amazing movie.
I'm just saying we also still need the movies that help inch the discussion forward a little bit
for people who are racist, who are homophobic. Joe Biden saying that Will and Grace made a more tolerant
of gay issues, you know, absolutely. My parents became more tolerant of gay issues watching Will and
Grace and also to it's also to it's like kind of like the criticism that Bohemian Rhapsody got from
a lot of people. Whether like they didn't show the the gay experience enough for whatever it's like,
look, it was in there. It was apparent to me. It was evident to me. I don't know if people,
like I feel like some people wanted some real hard like butt fucking scenes in this thing. Yeah,
to really drive at home. It's like guys, like there's there are things that depict that sort of thing.
Like searching is a show that really will get it like they will have graphic sex scenes in it.
You know what I mean? Look and or looking. I'm sorry. Yeah. That's something that will have graphic
sex scenes in it. Bohemian Rhapsody isn't. Bohemian Rhapsody is also something that makes people that are
unfamiliar with or lets people that are potentially unfamiliar with the gay lifestyle see it and start to
accept it. You know what I mean? It's it's kind of like there's no concept. I mean and it's and
then it's odd because on the last show we talked about how tame the lesbian scenes were in disobedience.
Yep. And that's the exact same problem from the other direction where now here is a movie that is
supposed to be depicting the passion and sexual vigor and lust or whatever involved between two
women. And none of it is shown. Yeah. You know what I mean? So I don't understand how we're
picking our spots anymore. It's like I get the criticism of the of the lack of sex when it comes
to a disobedience. I don't get it when it comes to Bohemian Rhapsody and it feels like to me we're
always picking the wrong targets. There should be complaints to me about disobedience. There should
not be complaints about Bohemian Rhapsody. Especially when none of us know what Freddie Mercury might have
wanted. Exposed or not exposed about his own personal life. We keep picking the wrong targets.
Everybody's mad that Ghostbusters gets slammed the remake for not being that great of a movie.
But then nobody is championing the other 18 movies that came out that same year with a female
driven cast that got no respect and no attention whatsoever. I don't understand why we focus on the things
we focus on. Me neither. Bohemian Rhapsody you know the big issue there is that it was a big Oscar
contender and that to me should not have been an Oscar movie. But fine who cares. The movie itself
no his performance yes but that was it yeah. Bohemian Rhapsody was rated PG -13 and it was to make them
as much money as possible which is good because then you know Bohemian Rhapsody I wish more movies like
that were made and they were not if you want they can't. It makes me mad sometimes. I want every
movie to not be a superhero movie. I'm so sick of everything being a remake or a superhero movie.
Okay so here's the story of Queen with you know it's beautifully shot and put together it's got all
the songs it's not perfect by any means but it's a lot of fun and it's getting families to watch a movie
about gay life together and people still have an issue because we don't see penetrating the anus
you know this is a PG -13 movie there's no sex in movies anymore. It's not like if we were doing
the Rolling Stone story we're gonna see Keith Richards take his shriveled cock out and put it
into a woman either. Well that's what and that's what also that's to me is the condescending part of the
whole thing yeah and it's strange that sometimes people in support of the cause are the ones criticizing
and I mean that gay straight whatever you are it doesn't that's I don't I'm not saying gay people
specifically I'm saying anybody at times and who are in support of the cause are the ones to me that
are harming the cause because when you say bohemian rhapsody should have had more
graphic sexual content and whatever then you're saying that anything about a gay person has to go
to that place that is what you're saying yes okay it's like saying why doesn't this movie about black
people have more soul it's condescending it's stereotypical it's gross you wouldn't do that about a
movie about straight you would never watch this is 40 and go why isn't there a scene in this where he
can't get it up for his wife and we're not seeing the problems that man have with an erection and her
pussies to dry because that's a sex thing that happens with people in their 40 you would never do that
because you're looking at it as well that's not what the story is about this is about two straight people
but it's not about sexual straightness it's just about straight but let me wrap it was not about
gay life no it was about this guy's journey through life that I saw I saw rocket man by the way with
the edgerton out in john movie which was fine but they did have a kind of awkwardly shoehorned in gay
sex scene in that movie and when you're in the theater it just sort of feels like this is
tonally not this movie like it felt weird to me because it would have felt the same in bohemian
rhapsody if we see ramen malloc you know fucking or getting fucked it would have felt
out of place it's a biopic you watch Malcolm X Malcolm X isn't you know bear -assed fucking some
lady in a hotel room like what it's it's insane what an even an even agreeing with you angrily I agree
with you can play even the even the violence which it's a great example you brought up with Malcolm X
even the violence in in Malcolm X with the racial struggles and everything in America is not
highlighted extremely no so to me it would be like if you watch Malcolm X you'd say why were
there not more scenes of a man having his head graphically beat in on and it's like that's not
I get it that's part of it but that's not what the movie is it's about this person and this person's
journey and they talk about that stuff you don't always have to see the thing that's not the focus here
so I mean look they won't say I'll say this this is all said if I ever see a movie about Hispanic
people if there's not a scene where a guy hunks his car horn and it goes I'm offended at that point
that has to be in my opinion in every certainly every 70s depiction of the of a Hispanic person
there were um I watched bohemian rhapsody with my mom and my stepdad Tom
and Tom is a you know he's a Missouri man you know we started this movie he's you know he's 65
he likes guns etc we are an hour and a half into bohemian rhapsody he has his paws it so he can go take
a piss and he said boy this star is born is great which is very funny he thought it was a
star's point but wasn't joking he really thought it was a story okay but this is a man who
and I you know let's just be real he's a 65 year old Missouri man there's some homophobia there there's
some things there that are not great he's wanting me to pause bohemian rhapsody so that he doesn't
miss a moment of this gay man's life this is quiet and I guarantee if at any point in that movie we
had seen Robbie Malik's balls you know swinging back and forth uh fucking some dude he would have
been out the door he would have said turn this shit off and left that's not great it's also not my
it's not my issue you know I somebody could throw on some gay porn I'd it wasn't bad and I I'm saying
most people in America and everybody has parents that's why I don't get are not comfortable with seeing
a gay sex scene so if you're making a big budget movie that costs a hundred million dollars that
you need to recoup it it would be career suicide but also to sex scene and we'll take it to the other
side of the coin just so you know everybody knows we're we're we're approaching this with a very open
mind who's the dipshit that made Buffalo 66 that fucking moron Vincent Gallo Vincent Gallo yeah
Vincent Gallo guess what people everything we're saying right now applying to us or our parents
if my parents sat down to watch Buffalo 66 was it Buffalo 66 with the blowjob scene
that's brown bunny all right brown bunny I said my parents on a watch brown bunny the same thing
it's not just a matter of of is it gay sexers it's straight sex right to matter of tonally
what the fuck does this have to do with anything right now why am I watching a fierce blowjob in the
middle of this movie whether it's male to female or male to male whatever
sure if I put on the brown bunny with with with my mom and stepdad they would have shut that off too
it's just kind of the point is the movie's PG 13 gang not every single thing has to depict
the the most gritty aspect of what that thing deals in right now if it's a movie dealing in grit
if it's a movie about for instance if you remade midnight cowboy yeah and you said
why are you not showing any of the sex yeah because that's really what this is about that's different
that's what we're talking about right the Billy Friedkin Al Pacino movie cruising it is still
thought of as being a horrific and homophobic because it looks at the fisting underbelly of
you know leather bars and stuff like that but at the time that was one of the few depictions of gay
lives so that was too explicit for you you know why it is called the fisting underbelly because when
you fist you're literally under their belly yes you know folks I mean nobody's watching modern
family and going why are we not seeing more because and actually that's a great example because
modern here's modern family here's a show that depicts couples period it's that's it that's couples
it's family and this is a thing where you're putting straight couples and gay couples right next to
each other yeah and you're seeing the gay couple just as you see the straight couple where you go I
don't need to see Ed O 'Neill fucking uh uh what's her name I was called her Carmen Electra Jesus Christ
yeah so fear of regard and I also don't need to see these two guys fucking that's not what the show is
about right so anyway you get that point I hope you do because you know modern family is a perfect
example for better or worse and you can like it or not modern family has done more for
America at large accepting the gay lifestyle than any hundred indie movies about gay life that comes
out that shouldn't be the case but it is the case because the people that the people watch it you know
well so did my mom or my mom and dad are never going to well embrace another example but my mom
and and dad the most they'd ever go to is like broke back mountain and that would be pushing the
extreme of their comfort and they may not make it through the whole movie so modern family and shows
of that nature are doing way more than this gritty indie movie where they show you a five minute
butt sexy because the people that you think are gonna watch it will never see it by the way by the way
according to these new rules that we all a new rule okay according to these new rules Eric
McCormick should be fired from Will and Grace he would be he's a straight man playing a gay man
yes and then what that does is that ends Will and Grace and then Will and Grace means that Jack
Breyer no longer has a job Jack Breyer is actually a gaming yeah being part of a gay show Jack Breyer is an
out I think he is is he not I could have sworn he's 30 rock Jack McBrayer or not Jack McBrayer I'm sorry
no Jack or Jack's the character name on Will and Grace yeah uh which is Sean Hayes Sean Hayes yeah
sorry he is yeah so it's then so then Sean Hayes is out of a job that's like well great it's like
the the moon I know Sean Hayes is Sean Hayes is gay yeah but I'm saying you take if you ended
well in the ring yes you see I'm saying they hurt Sean Hayes just like when Green Book won although I
thought a hundred and ten percent black clansman should have won over Green Book um so then what and
I said this before so then nobody talks about how the star of Green Book won an Oscar two years in
a row or or or two years apart whatever not even mentioned not even mentioned uh nobody nobody
thinks about well what does this do to Octavia Spencer who you're now saying fuck her because she's
part of this movie yes you're certainly you're saying that I just don't get it man George
Carlin at a great joke about people who are against abortion and he said people who are against
abortion are also against homosexuality well who has a less abortions than homosexuals you'd think
they'd make natural allies and that applies to this it's like make natural allies
yeah I'm hurting the people you're trying to help to make some bigger point that can't be solved
overnight right it just can't be uh but I don't know I think it's really what it's going to come
down to is I think anybody would sense whether they're gay straight white black trans whatever
are going to continually move away from Hollywood are going to continually do things on their own
we're in a place where we can now deliver the content directly to the people that want it as we are
doing with this podcast and people are going to just start to say hey man I'll spend my money elsewhere
I'll get my content elsewhere uh you know Netflix isn't a lot of trouble they're there they're stocks
down 20 % now because of this whole cutie's uproar now I need to see cuties before I can make a firm
opinion on it but they're in a lot but then I know get put on a list yeah so exactly I'm a it's like
they're stocking down 20 % because of this fucking cuties apparently it's down yeah so uh but I mean
you know look now here's the thing cuties might have a message I haven't seen it the overall point
might be that we're addressing the over sexualization of children and that we're addressing it in a
challenging way and we're saying that it's bad what that's what the filmmakers are claiming they're
trying to do with this movie but at the end of the day here's a network that just fired crystallia
for an allegation that he might have tried to sleep with somebody who was underage and a month later
they're pumping out a movie where there is literally footage in it of 11 -year -old girls grabbing
their crutches how does any of this line up anymore how does any of this even make sense I don't
understand where the consistency is it one Sundance stuff you know like it's apparently a good movie
with a message but nobody's gonna care or pay attention to that I do think when you market it like
that you're enticing purves to watch it but as I did say to Joe little Miss Sunshine had a very sexual
strip tease scene with the young girl that was played for laughs it is a very funny scene bad
grandpa went even more extreme it was the little boy in drag doing a very like seventh veil aggressive
strip tease and bad grandpa and these things were not mentioned so I don't know this cutie's
thing started because there's this cabal in the world that thinks that that all of Hollywood is
pedophiles and that I anytime I start to see those things come on like well that's such an extreme
cult of people that think this I don't even need to read about this story but little by little it's
becoming a big part of the world I feel like it's they assume that everyone it's a pedophile it's
crazy it's a little nuts it's more than a little nuts it's nuts but I guess my point with the consistency
argument is when you leave yourself no and this is not me saying Chris to Leah is guilty or not guilty
this is me saying when you leave yourself no breathing room for the possibility of the counter
argument in that case being maybe he didn't do this we don't know whatever when your reaction to
everything is hard action you end up in the Pelosi position now she's getting crucified she went
through a fucking salon with no mask on yeah and in the in the grand scheme of things big fucking
deal who cares but because she's out there this is evil and we got it bad not a mask can you
gotta do it then you get caught and it's like well now you're you're getting bitten the ass and now
your cause is going to get hurt because everybody needs to take a fucking breath everybody needs to
get back to a place of some rational thinking and consideration and we just need to work through
things this demand for a lynching onsite is insane and it's coming from every fucking direction at
this point it's coming from every direction and I think it's a sad thing but I think what it's
going to lead to again is people moving away from the Hollywood construct just as a lot of people
have moved away from shopping at Walmart or or eating at McDonald's or whatever it is Hollywood now
is officially in my opinion a major and it was already but now in the mainstream
interpretation of it it has been recognized as a major corporate conglomerate people are kind
of getting tired of the bullshit and people are saying you know what I can go make my own
stuff I don't yeah whatever guys like I don't need a little gold statue I don't need you to like it
right you know you got people making a hundred fifty thousand dollars a week on podcasts
it's like do you need NBC at that point to tell you your idea is good yeah no not us no not us
125 a week but I I think you know honestly it's just that people want awards they want recognition
but in the same breath they're furious about what gets awarded so basically you're saying why doesn't
my taste get awarded and not the taste of the country the taste of the country is green book might not
be your taste you're you're a much more extreme person the taste of the country is green book so you
can't both say the Oscars have to change so that I can be more likely to win an award and also
these awards are stupid and they never award the right people let it go you don't need it let it
you don't need it you know what everybody knows when they look back that good fellow is this fucking
better than dances with wolves are you fucking kidding me everybody knows that do the right thing is a
better movie than driving Miss Daisy are you kidding me right so so on that on that you you get
something that's respected but also I'm but also too driving Miss Daisy is what helped catapult
Morgan Freeman you know what I mean it's like that's a good thing so it's yeah it's just a it's a
little it's a little maddening but yeah you gotta you gotta just it's like what why do you want this
thing it's it's almost to me like saying I hate Trump but I want him to say that I'm good yeah you
shouldn't want him to say you should hate him you shouldn't want him to say that you're good right you
should just hate him and say I don't want to be involved with him yes it's the same thing anymore
with this Hollywood shit don't look for the approval of it it's it's stupid it's it's they're hypocrits
and I guarantee you that if the day if the sun rose tomorrow and all of a sudden they said
you know what man really what's gonna do it is just hard white all white all the time
let's get back to the good old days where it's white guys making inappropriate jokes all the time
constantly they would do it that's the part you have to remember they're not going to become
better people it's like saying oh you know Wall Street is better off after Occupy no it's not
it's the same shitty Wall Street yeah got bailed out and there we are here just back to fucking
square one that is what will always happen with Hollywood yeah they will never be better people
ever ever ever ever ever they'll do whatever it takes whatever it needs to get you to back off
and then slowly discreetly return to how it was right so this this big Oscar push you know we've
got these great new deadlines our guidelines you know they're putting it out there but fundamentally
this business is not going to change that's ridiculous I'm gonna uh you talk for a minute I'm
gonna refill my drink and then come back to discuss Bill and Ted all right uh yeah we we should also
probably I'll I'll bring it up there is a plan strands automobiles remake occurring now with
Will Smith and Kevin Hart look plan strands automobiles is probably my favorite comedy of all time
I think that Will Smith and Kevin Hart are both extremely funny and extremely talented but you are
taking a perfect movie that is pretty much beloved by everyone starring two of the funniest men that
ever lived why why do you need to do this and again I don't know why this whole podcast has become
focused on the issues of the day but um I love Kevin Hart I love Will Smith they are not right for
either one of these parts I don't even know who's playing what I assume Kevin Hart is in the John
Candy role but these remakes tend to feel like just throwing darts at a board and going okay let's
do that there doesn't seem to be any real reason for it any passion for it um flipping this movie on
its head plan strands automobiles and making a black version of it there's no political statement
there there's nothing interesting about making them black men um I hope it's funny I mean the the
already they already did this one so a white remake of plan strands called due date it's the exact same
movie uh sucked it's horrible um I hope this is better but I I gotta think and I I mean there's no
one paler than me so I'm not the right person to be speaking on it but I gotta think black people are
not saying boy I hope we all get uh remakes of white classics with black actors I just can't imagine
that that's what black people are looking for so you know telling a white person's story I you know
with with black actors is like that's that's not it's not a specifically white story two guys going
across the country but like if you have Kevin Hart and Will Smith two of the biggest stars two of the
most charismatic men in the world why are you why are you doing this why are you putting them in a
remake that is not going to outdo the original almost guaranteed yeah put them on their own
fucking awesome story try try to come up with something no it's it's terrible it's terrible the it's
it's everything is I just I feel like I just misspoke I don't mean two guys traveling from Chicago to
our New York to Chicago is a white person's story I'm saying the plan is what you mean is a movie
about a couple of white guys no no no you made sense okay good you made sense it's it's it's it's it's
point um but I'll be there opening night I'm excited to see it but man or just do a do a different
buddy movie with those two you know like yeah I know it's just crazy uh the uh while we're I mean
today's topic seems to sort of roundly or vaguely beat around Jesus God all right I've had a couple
uh Scotchers uh no but today's topic loosely is sort of uh reboot I guess you know because we're
in sequels and things so so before we get to the bill and Ted uh trilogy as you called it on the
last episode you said you wanted to discuss on this episode new trailers movie trailers one of which
was dune yeah I just just called them all I watched all the big new ones last night and by the way
it's scary to log into uh the trailers app on Apple TV and see like six movies yeah you know like
through the end of the year this dune trailer yeah I and I texted this to you when it came out the
other day I didn't think you could possibly make a dune that looked more boring than the lynch one yeah
this fucking thing I mean it just looks like cookie cutter like like you like you went to the
the like there was like there was like there was like there was an independent contracting office that
you went to that specializes in sci -fi design yeah you said give me the give me that palette met that
background of it this looks so cookie cutter straightforward every fucking sci -fi movie that has ever
existed yeah so boring just so nothing it just there's nothing of course and
asgar Isaac back again once again and what's great like I don't know if you saw him on the interview
circuit for this last Star Wars movie but him and boyega were talking all kinds of shit about especially
the latest Star Wars boyega has a much more real reason based in race and the abandoning of his
character but asgar Isaac's clearly was just like you know fuck this franchise whatever but he
does them all he's in all of them so you know great actor by the way yeah but you know just like
it's like you know like again like Sarah Paulson great actor but Christ almighty take a breath yeah
Jesus and you can't be Mr. Cool Indy who bad malice the big blockbusters when you do five a year
all right you gotta pick a you gotta pick a fucking lane um this thing I'm paying five million dollars
and you go to do an interview and you're giggling about how stupid it is you get it buddy this is this
is Halloween adventure costume like like hey do you have a costume that looks like a guy from the future
and they're like yeah it's this thing it's all black with buckles on it yeah in this scarf you know
so that's I mean that's it every part of this looks so fucking boring man like oh dude book is boring
dude is the in my opinion the only like bad David Lynch movie and this just looks like you know it's
not for me I know that much but god I just don't care I hate that villain you uh is now doing like
he did Blade Runner and now this and now he'll just be another guy who makes these big blockbuster
prisoners prisoners is my you know my favorite like adult thriller of the last 20 masterpiece
an amazing movie and this guy this guy made that movie work that was a beautifully directed movie
he did it amazingly well then he does Sicario another very interesting movie it's very well shot
everything's great and you're like okay we're gonna have one guy doing adult intelligent movies for us
and then sure enough it's just Blade Runner then it's doomed then it's well I mean for Christ
Shakespeare like the all right so at least with blade I thought Blade Runner was painfully fucking
boring but beautiful but at least stunning yes visually stunning for sure it looked him now granite he
had a palette to work off of you know he he he had the Ridley Scott template or whatever yeah
this thing doesn't look visually stunning it looks it looks just drab it looks boring
and maybe a later trailer will prove to be greater and then everybody just wedding they're
fucking pants over this trailer on the internet Kevin Smith anymore I mean and he said accolades about
Bill and Ted face the music as well yeah I don't even know what he's looking at anymore man like
he you know you sent me that tweet he wrote today I'm like let me share the tweet let me share what
he's talking about me sure and I'm a Smith fan but like what are you talking about dude uh he wrote
and this is particularly embarrassing uh even by his standards the spice must flow
and it all just flowed out of my underwear after watching this dune trailer this haunting epic glimpse of
a future best picture winner will not fade f -e -y -d I guess that's a character from my memory anytime soon
I know what I'm dune on opening night oh god okay maybe it's cool why is every why is every actor
in the movie directed to say their lines in a monotone why is that the go -to now because it's the
future personality because it's the future and in the future everything is uniform and they must
talk like that because they're sandworms and the sandworm even was underwhelming the sandworms
yeah beetle juice looks more thrilling to me than this fucking thing it looked like a vagina like
every other alien or creature the stars it looked like the starship troopers thing 20 years ago
and then the trick is by the way this is what they do hey guys it's uh it's like the latest
installment of dune and we've done the sandworm thing a million times so I could do it different
make it bigger yeah just make it so big it's crazy and there will never be a version of dune
that will outdo what Jordorowski's version of dune was supposed to be ever yeah you watch that
documentary and you see the artwork for this thing as as one guy says at the beginning of that movie
it's a movie that has never existed and it's my favorite movie of all time the the artwork for that the
the concept art the fact that he was gonna pink Floyd do the soundtrack and then that's like an
easter egg in this is that they have fucking pink and by the way not even pink Floyd a shit reworking
of a pink Floyd song in the fucking uh trailer reworking or a slowed down version of
the song man it sucks uh by the way that's been done already in the fucking shitty uh in the in the
faculty they did that terrible remake in the trailer of we don't need no education uh everything
about it it's just it's territory that's been tread on a million times it's so fucking boring man
uh the other trailer i watched was freaky starring Vince Vaughn freaky freaky what's this i don't
even know what this is so freaky is uh from the guy who did happy death day which was kind of a fun
little horror movie groundhog day style horror movie okay freaky is a Vince Vaughn is a serial killer who
switches bodies with a teenage girl is it a comedy it's like comedy horror but it's almost like a uh
like a vice versa except horror correct uh steven king yesterday tweeted based on the trailer of
freaky Vince Vaughn has got to get nominated for an academy award this looks fucking awesome
now steven are you skipping your naps are you skipping your naps
i love Vince Vaughn i thought this movie looked kind of fun what are you talking about um i feel all
the time like i'm going crazy i feel like i hate everything people love um i i don't know but
freaky actually does look a little fun it looks like a low budget kind of rom but i thought that was
kind of crazy uh the new james bond trailer looks like every other james bond trailer it'll probably
kind of cool kind of boring the bond trailers the bond trailers always give me chills and then i
never want to see the movie but bond bond to me is a 90 second experience yeah i want to see the car
fishtail i want to see machine guns come out of the headlights and i want to hear
banana banana and then i'm like i'm good i saw it i'm good that was great and then you realize the
running time is is 148 minutes yeah yeah yeah they all are 148 minutes um also saw like watch
half of the trailer for guest house starring polysure and then i jump shit uh i watched the whole trailer
everybody said it was a return to form for polysure which god knows what that means sure maybe it is
man it looks it looks i mean look a return to there was never formed to begin with
does anybody does everybody lost their fucking mind everybody's like it's good to see polysure
back at what he does but the weasel was never that funny yeah he was an MTV vj who was a bad stand -up
comic but his mom owned the comedy store so he was in the mix in hollywood as a kid that's all it was
okay sudden law is not a great movie it might have a few laughs in it but it's almost like saying like
you know uh like oh oh the director of half -baked is back it's like it's not anything we need to go
back to it was never that great no and that's not a shout -out to pal that's i think half -baked is funny
but it's like i would never rest my drink on it it's like a good movie come on man uh i finally
watched the Wonder Woman trailer you know i like that new orders in it um but whatever the Batman
trailer i finally watched you know we'll see i i don't know it said it's a first trailer i've seen
that said in production at the end of the trailer yeah yeah yeah that was the Batman so Batman trailer
excited me uh because a you know how i love the dark brooding comic book style thing i'm glad they
went back to that and the scene alone where he beats the living shit out of that like street thug
it was i was like this is awesome like this is like we've never seen brutal Batman i'm excited for it
so that that that i like Wonder Woman i will see i'm i'm pretty excited i'm i'm excited it might
be too strong but i'm just curious to where DC's going with everything so i'm curious about Wonder Woman
looks good um and then i i really just want to close with i i was one second into this trailer and i
just thought this is going to be a rough one the war with grandpa starring robert deniro uh i watched that
trailer as well so look deniro has been on a slippery slope for 20 years i mean i remember when the
adventures in rocky and bullwinkle trailer came out i was like oh i couldn't even look at it
this is a new love this is like robert deniro starring in a direct to video three ninjas sequel
i mean this thing looks like absolute garbage how do they pay him for this thing um it doesn't look great
i laughed one time during the trailer when i don't remember but i remember at one point i laughed and
i went oh that's weird that i laughed i didn't think i was going to laugh it all the only reason i
want to see the movie is i'm like i can watch this with my folks at christmas and it'll just be like a
fun thing to watch with my parents that's that's how i remember the movie he did with uh
was it deniro what was the stalone boxing movie wasn't it deniro versus storeable yeah not a great
movie but i saw all my folks it's one of those things you shut your brains off it's like watching an
extended episode of everybody loves raiment or something you know you laugh and you just go okay we
we had a nice time i just felt like this was a new love it's not it doesn't look great especially after
the guy comes back with scorsese in the Irishman gives one of the best performances he's ever given
scorsese immediately is like my next movie it's de caprio and deniro you're like this guy is back
but i also heard that this movie was made a while ago i think it's been sitting here like on the
shelf for a bit yeah so i think it was sitting on the shelf for a minute and now it was like oh we
can finally release this because we can ride the coattails of the hype so we'll see rough stuff i mean
like and when alpuchino does shit like you know he when he's in jack and jill the soundler movie
he's the funny is part of jack and jill he does that that don't kachino commercial and it's really really
funny and he's he's trying to sell it deniro in this movie looks ashamed you you smell it on him he's a shame
yeah it's uh yeah i know um speaking of wait a minute we were just talking wait you said
you know trailers that's the last trailer i watched i had something to say about oh oh trailer uh
hubi holloween i'll see hubi holloween i'll see hubi holloween
the new adib sanler film uh that i just the premise i was like this is absurd it's like hubi has to
save holloween because it's dangerous so i mean i don't know how holloween is in danger i don't
know how you save it i don't even really know what it is uh but uh it's the director of the water boy
or no i think it's the director of little niki he's doing that style of character he's doing that style
character again and i'm watching the trailer i'm rolling my eyes going my god this looks terrible
but again got me with one laugh when uh there's a gag in the trailer that he keeps going to the police
station and telling them there's a problem in the community and it's never anything big and it's always
annoying uh and they do a montage of him going into the police station and complaining about things
and one of them he walks it and he goes i heard a voice in the sewer
that's kind of funny i thought hubi holloween looks uh like a masterpiece compared to the war with
grandpa i mean i it's got to get argue that down to the smallest part i'm like dim meadows my
root off you know i'll check her out root offs in there she's always great meadows meadows is an
underrated assassin like a pop star man he is funny and i'm happy to see i'm happy to see guys
like samler giving meadows his just two meadows to me is is similar to a Garrett Morris in the sense of
yeah this guy was underused and overqualified like he doesn't get he doesn't get the exposure and
the attention he deserves so i was happy to see him in there always happy to see keen and Thompson and
anything of course um you know kevin james is in it hey he's hit her miss but uh you know i'll see
what he's got to offer you know i love that samler movies are the last comedies where they're still
dusting off funny wigs you know oh yeah they'll still get every character in a crazy way oh they
got they got james in this thing and like it's absurd it's absurd it's i mean it Ben stiller would
have scoffed at the fucking wig yeah uh which is saying a lot and then of course Rob Schneider's in
there who i don't understand i never will understand but uh for some reason samler's got a real soft
spot for this guy have you watched his stand -up special which is like asian wife mexican mom or
something like i watched the trailer for it and my god it's terrible but i did do a zoom with a friend
of mine who works at netflix uh we were doing a sort of reunion zoom but your friends hadn't seen each
other while resuming and uh yeah in the middle of it i said uh i said hey i just i really need to thank
for that rob Schneider's stand -up special thank you it's really getting me through some hard times
uh probably probably rates great i don't know maybe he's a nice guy i have no idea uh never
heard that no let's get sure never heard that about him or james or katana i've heard some stories
about james these nice other stories that are horrible katana i've never heard one positive thing ever
literally ever yeah Schneider i've heard a couple good most like and he's kind of a dick but whatever
katana's the one that i've never heard literally one positive thing ever
i've heard way worse about james than katana but as i've talked about on the show the katana
autobiography is a classic of of people being out of their fucking minds uh we do in a movie corn
now i think we need to get to the we're deep in mike where we have time wise here i think we need to
get to the movies already all right well let's we really did a uh we did a new segment on the show
today uh two artists bitch about hollywood we're just under an hour we should probably get to the movie
fair enough so yeah we're gonna talk about uh bill and teds trilogy uh and let's briefly just discuss
our history with the franchise for me you created it i created it yes yeah bill and teds excellent adventure
came out when i was like nine years old it was when i was really getting into
movies and i was excited to see it what i still don't understand is how wanes world and bill and teds
existed at the same time and when you look online they're both sort of parroting a type of guy that was
around back then but like when you hear bill and teds go not it's it's kind of shocking and i guess
they were it's hard to do that though do bill and teds do not do not do not do not do in the old ones
yeah okay um and way and you know a lot of stuff that waning grout that um for me there's no contest i
mean wanes world one and two are ten times funnier than any bill and teds movie in my opinion i agree uh
well from a straight comedy standpoint wanes world one and two are better comedy pound for pound
it's no contest yeah uh i think bill and teds the original carries it could compete in the adventurous
spirit department you know it it does bring its own vibe to the table that's really truly touching
and endearing but uh there's a sweetness about it you know having George carlin in the mix is fun
when i i rewatched the original there's a shout factory uh collection that went out of print in
the pandemic and i sold it made made an isle profit but uh it had a it has an amazing uh two -hour
documentary about excellent adventure and bogus journey that's great you can tell right up to the
present one that these are labors of love that people love these characters etc excellent adventure
is really fun to me it almost works better when i was 10 years old and it was like a book report come
to life kind of thing there's almost an educational vibe to it wherein you're meeting the figures of
history and so forth that gives it a sweetness gives it an innocence even while they're using the uh
the gay slur which they do in excellent adventure and bogus journey and wanes world by the way does not
do that and it was a time where they probably could have but they're calling each other
f you know that that happens in bill and teds which is interesting really i didn't know that
yeah i mean it was used as an insult you know oh no i know yeah back then sure the uh
let's i mean i would say let's start with face the music and then kind of revisit the other ones
through that i mean i was just starting with one my opinion of one is that it's a it's a sweet cute
almost kid -friendly movie with some odd uh you know artifice at the time there's so many things that
connect they're they're they're like i'm just gonna say this flat out and and people listening will
probably not agree i thought bill and ted faced the music sucked uh i thought bill and teds bogus journey
sucked but i thought at least bill and teds bogus journey captured what bill and ted was yeah i felt
like bill and ted faced the music failed greatly in that department which we'll get to and i will
start by saying that there were things that were set up in the first film that were never followed
through with in the third film the first of which and we'll be back to explain why that they write
the song that unites the world that's a huge glaring issue for me right uh and we'll get to why
that's an issue in when we get to the third movie but one of the things that bothered me most was
in the third i'm just gonna kind of jump back and forth in the third film there were several moments
where i was like how did they miss that joke mm -hmm i don't understand how that jokes in there and one
of them was in the third film they are dialing a number in the phone book to travel to a point in time
and the number starts with 69 yeah and they don't look at each other and go 69 that joke was in the trailers
for bill and ted's excellent adventure yeah and you're sitting there going guys how are you not
doing the call back to that joke right now it's confusing to me it would have been funny and
kind of sweet if they had just done an acknowledgment of were too mature now to make the 69 joke make
that the joke sure anything yeah anything but with the first film i agree with you
it's uh it's an endearing sort of edutainment kind of picture i remember watching it i rented it on
video i loved it and then i said mom you got to watch this with me i was 11 or whatever it's time
yeah and i watched with my mom my mom loved it because she thought they were very funny but she was
also like i love that this kind of teaches a lesson and uh and and actually does a moral lesson but
then also kind of teaches a lesson about history and things like you actually do learn some stuff
for watching it for sure interesting um and it's just a really funny movie that captures a
personality type of that time like that was that was a thing like there was the valley girl and the
sort of surfer skater dudes like those were things um the what's interesting is that you never i
never think or thought of Wayne and Garth as stoners like in fact i would argue Garth never
tried a joint and maybe Wayne smokes every couple months a joint but Bill and Ted
seem like stoners and they always uh like people ask all the time were they meant to be stoners
and they have said no they're not they said that they're not stoners um which is part of the endearing
quality is like there's an innocence to these two characters um which is why uh just something to put
a pin in the innocence to these two characters is why to me the two sequels don't work because they
betray that innocence in certain ways which we'll get to um but the adventure of the first one
the the concept of kids being in trouble and find it scholastically in trouble uh in school
the you know the powers that be when you're a teenager the teacher the the parent whatever
all of that being there and being such a prominent element in the first film and then two
teenagers finding this magical fantastical way to resolve the problem and not only that but somebody
from the future who's highly intelligent and whatever from this from this uh prosperous
futuristic society coming to them and saying i know everybody thinks you're morons but you're not
you're actually going to save the universe uh that element is what makes that first film work
and it essentially in my opinion goes completely out the fucking door in the second two films
uh i just rewatched but i watched all three of them in a week but to bogus journey when i was a kid was
sort of unsettling to me like almost yeah scary it's not now but it's a it's a much darker movie and i
i think i like one and two about equally one is more likeable uh more funny sort of more fun
two visually is way cooler way better um i like the dark aspects of it i like how crazy it is i like
the bad villain Ted the this this is my cat scratchy she got that cat scratch fever the uh the station the
little like midget creature sorry little most not even a person but the little creatures that
form at the end and combine to form one big mutant do you remember that in bogus journey yeah yeah
um it's just like very very weird and uh i don't know when they go to hell and all that the effects
are pretty good so i to me they both have pros and cons and wind up about equal when i watch them now
i don't like the second one i appreciate aspects of the second one and i appreciate it's really neat
yeah visually it's pretty cool i appreciate that it's more of a sort of gremlins two versus gremlins vibe
they're like let's go batch it in this one let's just go out to to the fucking far corners with it
yeah i think that's kind of cool cool um but i hated the evil villain Ted and the reason i hated it was
because i love the good villain Ted so much yeah so every moment that evil villain Ted are on
screen i'm sad because i'm seeing two guys that i really like be assholes and that's what i mean about
the innocent sort of being lost i don't want the bad guys in the movie to also be villain Ted
i want the bad guys to be people from elsewhere coming in to compromise these two great guys and i
don't i did not like seeing an evil version of them in the second one uh the second one also
is where the logic of it all i mean look there's not a ton of logic it's fucking time travel movie
but the logic of it all starts to be uh broken in the second one because suddenly now it's not
just about time travel it's sort of about like interdimensional travel and it's a little too crazy
where now you're bringing religion into it and all this other stuff um cool idea yeah little too
cartoony for me from what i wanted from the sequel uh there was a villain Ted cartoon that Alex
Winder and Kiana Reeves did voice there was also a live action tv show both were called villain Ted's
excellent adventures uh both sucked um but had they made i remember the cartoon not the live
action very few people know the live action one but uh but had they made the villain Ted bogus
journey into a cartoon series for Saturday morning i would have been a little more into it i would
have been a little more accepting of you know hey man we got to go on this weekly thing now so it's
going to get a little crazier yeah that's fine but as as a follow up to a movie that i loved so much
uh i was really disappointed as a kid it just got a little too and it it's one of those movies too
that never came around for me like when i saw return to Oz as a kid i hated it because it was too dark
just released that this week as i got older i loved it like i like return to Oz better than Wizard of
Oz now because it's just way more up my alley you know but it's it it villain Ted's bogus journey
just never turned over into that for me uh and i also thought it wasn't funny there were there were
no jokes like the death stuff is kind of funny like the death snow is is funny uh it's it's but yeah
the rest of it is almost more comfortable in it like a weird place as opposed to a funny place
but uh it's almost like Werner Herzog made a villain Ted movie which i think like was what they were
trying to do i think it was very clear that they were like you know kind of like Nightmare
and Elm Street 4 where they're like what if we went like crazy European with this one
right it made it just fucking wild and insane and like and which is interesting but i just didn't work
for me uh i hear you i i i respected it more as an adult and then you know heading into three
i didn't really know what to expect but they i'm glad i watched it opening night or you know the night
they dumped it on on demand because the amount of raves i have seen about this movie and the guy who
wrote it so it's Ed Solomon is the guy i know on twitter and there's there's another guy who did it
it's the writers of the original film yeah Chris Matheson and Ed Solomon they are not still writing
partners but i also learned that Matheson is the son of Richard Matheson the famous one that's
pretty cool but um Solomon and i follow each other on twitter very nice man i think he's uh once he
joined twitter he became this like very oh it's cool this guy who wrote these legendary movies is
this fun and funny and talks to us and everything else that's the only way i can maybe wrap my head around
the love that this movie has got but you know mike our producer here right before it was like
what you guys didn't like it and that's the attitude across the board everyone i know has loved it
except a few people like me and you who you almost feel like you have to whisper or like this thing
fuck i actually thought it was an f i wasn't let down by it because i never had i never held
bill and ted in the highest esteem anyway i just thought it was a really bad movie and there's
this guy another guy i kind of know on twitter zack heitzel who said it looks like a super bowl commercial
that's a really accurate critique yeah i agree with it it's in that the and it's the guy who did
galaxy quest which is well perfect director for this type of material but yeah so so that's the thing
so when they first announced this and said it was going to be the galaxy quest director i was like okay
that's a good call he also directed red to i think you directed red one as well
is it okay that's that's a good fit galaxy quest seems pretty perfect yeah
this thing started into production it was a independent film from the jump
but there was a lot of hype around it and a lot of fan demand kind of put this into motion
which soda bird kind of kind of got it to the screen which i think it's great yeah soda
birds and executive producer on it yeah um it i was excited i was like i want to see what these guys do
this will be fun my first sign of trouble was the title
it should have been called bill and ted's righteous return or whatever it should have followed suit
with the titles of the other films bill and ted faced the music right away i was like
but that doesn't fit with the other it's excellent venture bogus journey uh it should be another thing
about traveling because that's the point wouldn't be in my top thousand issues but i hear you uh i'm
just telling you from the jump the title i was like i don't i don't know man that doesn't sound right
to me something happy on second sign of trouble to me was when they announced so the bill and ted's
daughters was like now here we go with the reboot bullshit now they're gonna have their kids in it
and whatever which hey man i get it we all get older we all develop as people i'm not against the idea
that these characters now have families or whatever but i was concerned because what happens as we all
know in these reboots is they bring in the kid they did it in crystal skull they did it in uh
jane solemn bob reboot yep uh they did it in this always bad always bad they bring in a kid and
you're like oh god they did it in Paul blard mall cop too his daughters there they have what
appears to be a 50 -year -old woman playing his water yeah they're doing it in the reboot series
Prince of Queens which i'm not happy about uh i was serious about Paul blard by the way oh i thought
you're kidding no um this is what they do you go oh shit man they're kind of you know following uh
the typical course of action with these things um but i was still optimistic i was like it's okay
i'm i'm excited to see this uh and then i the trailer came out and well that first then covid hit
and halted as far as i knew halted production or halted the release or whatever and they were saying no
it's still coming out it's still coming out we're on schedule on schedule and i thought well that
doesn't really seem to make sense with the time it takes to make a film and whatever
and sure enough when the trailer finally hit there was not a laugh to be had in it even though i was
terribly excited to watch it and i thought to myself this doesn't look
quality like the scenes where they're in the future it's clear to me that they're like in
a skyscraper in downtown LA that has a lot of windows that they added some green screen effects to
but more importantly that the committee from the future is now shitting on them
and being like bill and ted you're idiots like you haven't done what you're supposed to do about it
it's like this doesn't make sense you're the society that saw them doing the thing
that believed in the underdog losers now you guys are saying they're losers and turning against them
i was like this isn't good i don't like this this is like when they did that first scubi do movie
and uh they like it start the movie with breaking the gang up and then the whole movie is like
you're building up to the climax of the gang getting back together guys i'm here for a live action
scubi do movie don't send everybody's they're separate ways in the first five minutes
you know what i mean so like it's just like don't have shaggy get out of the mystery machine and rent
at dots and to go off on a zone let's keep them in the mystery machine yeah so i just was like this
is i don't know and then they're the internet comics started started coming out about
kiano seeming sort of expression less throughout this thing and i was like yeah he does kind of
look like he's stuck in like john wick mode or something like he's not laugh even when they do the like
guitar thing that they do together like when they're supposed to like be happy like that's their way
of saying awesome and then they do it and like he's not even smiling and i'm like this just doesn't
something seems off but fuck it let's wait for the second trailer second trailer came out
and i was like okay the daughter character seem like kind of funny in this like there's that shot
of them dancing that's kind of cute and funny like okay this might be cool death's back blah blah blah
all right i'm in i'm excited let's see what we got and then it was just the waiting game till the movie came
out in the period between that second trailer and the premiere of the movie i saw several reviews
uh one of which was from kevin smith who said he leapt watching the film and then also
say now granted i was super high that's not a review you want to hear by the way i'm often super
high i i with a gun to my head couldn't have worked up a tear for billington i got and we'll get to
it i got a little choke yet the end mike saying he cried mike said it okay i got a little
choke yet the end we'll get to the end but you saw this before i did new text in me and you said uh
this bill and ted is not good it's reminiscent of jane salibat reboot which you all know how we
thought about that film yeah i was very concerned once you said that i don't think there's a huge
difference in the quality of the two movies i really don't there's not the only differences is that
in bill and ted they tried to do special effects yeah and it's painfully obvious yeah um
but i mean for christ sakes guys in a world where you can deep cut uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh
or deep fake the president's face on like a fucking uh uh uh uh you know uh um uh uh uh
a hound dog and a commercial and make it look like trump is barking eating dog food how the
fuck can't the bill and ted third segment how can it not have better special effect i don't understand
and it's like that we can,
this stuff is all very doable at this point.
Like, I mean, I'm glad that your criticisms are coming
from AFAN standpoint and be a,
this movie looks like shit standpoint
because I completely agree as a fan,
it would have disappointed me too.
The effects look terrible, the whole movie itself looks terrible,
the whole vibe of it, the feel of it,
the look of it is hard to look at.
But, for me, really the biggest and only issue was the fact that,
in its 90 minute running time,
I couldn't point to a single laugh,
a single joke that worked,
anything that felt clever.
When Kid Cuddy shows up, Kid Cuddy,
a rapper who was popular 10 years ago
and has not had a hit single in years.
So, clearly they asked 10 different rappers and wound up with Kid Cuddy.
But, I don't hate the guy.
I just, like, when he walks in and everybody goes,
Kid Cuddy, because they have to do that to let everyone know who he is,
then maybe we don't need to do a celeb cameo here.
Like, you're not getting any points having him in there.
And it's that terrible joke of like,
isn't it funny that this musician is steeped in astrophysics?
Yeah.
And they just literally have Kid Cuddy be the guy
that knows everything about astrophysics to save the day.
It's such lazy writing.
It also feels a little racist.
It's sitcom, it's sitcom 101 writing.
Like, guys, we need an out here.
Let's get Steven Tyler to show up in the last five minutes
and give us the formula for this thing that we,
it's terrible, it's terrible, terrible, terrible writing.
Which, by the way, the joke of that was completely undercut
in Billy Madison.
Yeah.
When he goes on the speech and you're like,
oh, they're doing the thing where the dumb guy is really smart
or the guy you're not expecting to be smart and smart.
And then the guy goes, we're all actually stupider
for having listened to you just now.
Amazing.
Yeah, that is like the fuck you to that joke.
So anyway, that movie came out 25 years ago.
And here's the thing, Kid Cuddy could be steeped
in astrophysics for all I know,
but you gotta let us know, guys.
Yeah.
Can't just throw it in there and expect me to accept it.
So, and the joke is like, can you believe this rapper is smart?
Is that at its core what that joke is?
But the, the death stuff, so they, they know it.
Wait, let's, can we just, before we get into that,
can we just go back for a second?
The first 20 minutes of this, I was like, okay,
like I was kind of laughing.
Again, knew we were in a little bit of trouble
when the opening credits had,
credit, credit had such little fanfare.
Yeah.
It's the third villain Ted.
The title for this thing should pop.
Like you, you gotta, it's Star Wars.
Like we're here, so it to us.
Yeah.
And the title comes up with very little fanfare.
It starts with a voiceover from the daughter,
which again, you're in, you're in dark waters at this point.
Yeah.
This is lazy writing, something's wrong.
But that said, the entire beginning of the movie,
I was like, okay, I'm laughing.
I was laughing at some of the jokes at the wedding
and when they're playing at the thing
and missy's there and she's now marrying the brother
and all these things.
What was happening when they were playing that bad song?
What was happening?
What was the joke?
Why was that in the movie?
What was going on?
As an art rock fan, I thought that was funny
because it was like, they're doing...
They're not art rockers.
But I got the gag of that, which was like,
this is like when yes, did tails of the top
of graphical lotion or whatever that almost goes on.
Listening to yes.
Well, I think that was their hair.
I don't know guys.
I think the point was here's them trying to do their rock opera
and it's terrible because they're desperately trying to find...
Whatever.
But here's the thing.
Here's the thing.
They never explain in the movie
how they get good at their instruments.
Right.
It starts with this opening montage about like,
now wild stallions is this big, famous band
and everybody loves them and now they suck
and now this, they never stop and explain to you.
This movie would have been better soon
but it's starting out with Ted.
We're 45 years old
and we still don't know how to play instruments.
Yeah.
Right off the bat, you're like, this is funny.
These guys are in trouble.
You know what I mean?
Like they never explain that.
They never explain what happens to Rufus.
They just start talking about Rufus in a past tense
and you're just like, I guess he died?
Yeah.
Can you die?
He's from the future.
I thought they could come.
I thought they were gonna be like Rufus isn't around.
He is transcended to the interdimensional plane
or something interesting.
They just talk about him in the past tense
and never explain it.
And that's to me when the movies start to really have problems
where I was like, they're jumping into all these things
that we're just supposed to assume we understand
and they're going against what the other movies were.
The gag was, they didn't know how to do this.
And now suddenly they do, but they haven't done it.
Like this is already convoluted.
It's too confusing.
It shouldn't be this confusing.
It should be really simple.
We're in trouble.
We've got to get in the fucking phone booth.
We've got to go back through time
and find the best musicians that have ever lived
and create the best song that has ever been created.
And instead, it turns into our wives
and the movies are going to go on this journey
to find a version of us they love, which they never show.
They just send them out of the picture.
You have to imagine maybe they filmed stuff with the wives
because like, say it again, you cut out.
You have to imagine maybe they filmed something with the wives
or else why even have them, why even bring them up?
My theory is COVID hit and they couldn't finish the movie.
Honestly, you might be right.
It feels like it wasn't finished.
Things weren't acted up.
Maybe they ran out of money.
Who knows?
But I think that's why the future scenes look the way they do
because I think that was all shot
with everybody individually and they cobbled it together.
Yeah, like that arrested development season,
that was so terrible where they could get everybody at once.
So it's like, it's like, it's like so many of the wives
going on a journey we never see, who cares?
Nobody cares.
Nobody wants to see it.
Right.
You have the daughters going on the journey,
Bill and fucking Ted should be going on,
which is to assemble the musicians.
Yeah.
Then you have Bill and Ted going on my least favorite
Bill and Ted journey into the future
in two -year increments, that's not the future.
It's the same time basically.
To meet asshole Bill and Ted's that I don't want to see.
If you're going to introduce the daughters
and they almost gave them enough of a showcase
that they could have had their own movie,
like they're planning a new young female Bill and Ted.
And what do they do with those characters?
They have them do exact impersonations of Bill and Ted.
They have no new traits of their own.
Really, the one girl is just doing Keanu Reeves.
When death does come into the movie.
Which, by the way, if I get interrupted.
Which makes no sense.
Yeah.
Because nobody talks like that anymore.
No, they don't.
So it makes no sense that their kids are like,
whoa, a most excellent.
Like your kids wouldn't talk.
This thing is so fucking convoluted.
Right.
They would go, Dad, why are you talking like that?
It doesn't make any sense.
So all of the stuff about it that doesn't,
I mean, from a story standpoint,
I thought it was a mess from a, from a,
really all I care about at the end of the day
is even if this looked as bad as it did,
made as little sense as it did,
but made me laugh, I would have been fine.
They got the, you know, the Dave Role cameo,
the kid cutie cameo, I was talking about pop star
and what a perfect use of cameos that movie was.
This is the opposite.
This is that disgusting thing.
I'm like, can we find anybody famous
to pop by and be in this movie?
Okay, let's use them.
There's no reason for it.
Bill and Ted would never like, listen to
or know who kid cutie was.
The death, when death comes along, great to see him,
you're excited.
You're like, okay, here comes the laughs.
They have him do five minutes of riffs
on what he's been up to and the different albums
and bands he's been able.
That is some of the most painful comedy I've seen in a while.
I turned it, I watched this with Jay Ogerson.
I turned to him during that death scene
and I go, what the fuck are we watching, dude?
And he's like, I know, I go, why,
why are we watching a five minute riff
on death solo records?
This doesn't make any sense.
Why was death in their band?
None of it makes sense.
Makes no sense.
If you want to do that bit, like Mighty Wind
actually did those jokes over dialogue.
They would put up album covers while they were talking
just to get bonus laughs.
But this was like, the jokes weren't funny.
None of the albums that came up with were funny.
So you're just kind of like, what is this?
Um, so let me say something.
What, and this is again, Walsh.
We've written things, you're more of a writer than I am,
but we've both written things professionally.
This is writing 101.
Make the daughters not get the fathers
and then the daughters go on the journey with the fathers
and then that makes them appreciate one another.
That's all you had to do.
The magic of the first Bill and Ted
is them going through time, meeting their wives to be
and saving the day.
Make this them going through time
with their daughters to be in a connective sense
and saving the day.
That's all you had to fucking do.
Why am I watching Bill and Ted's daughters
meeting Jimmy Hendrix?
Well, then the Ted are nowhere to be seen.
The assumption is that, is that Reeves couldn't be there
for all these scenes and they had to send them off
in their own journey is my assumption.
But who knows?
They have Keanu Reeves and Alex Winter who is fine,
but they have them doing character comedy
and scene after scene after scene.
They're playing really old guys.
They're playing Jacked Prison dudes
and the whole time I'm like, is there a worse
character comedian in the world than Keanu Reeves?
Who, if you could, if you could name anyone
who is the worst person at like
inhabiting a bunch of characters SNL style?
Keanu Reeves would be at the tippy top.
And Alex Winter winds up showing him up
in some of these scenes and they're not good,
but like when Alex Winter's playing the old rocker guy,
you know, the kind of like rolling stone type guy,
he's mugging the hell out of it.
You know, he's like flipping his hair around
and mugging like he's in a mad TV sketch,
but he's at least knows what comedy is.
Like that's not Keanu's, I love Keanu.
It's not his strong point.
Right, right, well that's that.
Yeah, and it's just like the,
I don't know, man, oh God.
It just sucks.
So anyway, so then at the end of the movie,
they, Bill and Ted realized,
and this is what I was alluding to earlier,
Bill and Ted realized that it's not them
who's supposed to write the song.
It's the daughters that are supposed to write the song.
And they're just there to help the daughters.
And it's like guys, this isn't the story of the franchise.
Like, right.
God almighty, there's a way to do this.
There's a way to show them connecting
and celebrating with, and celebrating their daughters
without you betraying what the story of this is.
There's a way to do it.
And it just doesn't make any fucking sense.
And then all of a sudden it goes into this whole,
it's like back to the future three.
You know, I've argued back to the future three
with tons of people and there are plenty of people out there
that think it's a decent third installment.
I think it's dog shit.
And my argument always, every time with back to the future three
is you betrayed the formula of the films.
You betrayed what the films were about.
These films were about the McFly family,
and that family staying together
through time travel whatever, in a certain way
that it kept the fabric of society together.
Yeah.
Then suddenly you get the third movie
and it's like, we're gonna focus on Doc Brown in this one
and what he's got, no, that's not what it's about.
It's about Marty McFly saving his family
so somehow the fucking universe doesn't end.
And in this, it's that same mistake.
It's like, no, we're gonna actually go off track here.
Say it's not really about this.
It's not really about these characters
but these other characters who we met five minutes ago.
Yeah.
We don't care about yet.
And who are and who you have to make us care about
because we don't know them.
We're bringing a lot of nostalgia to this.
So if you're gonna introduce new people,
you gotta make us like them.
And not only do they not do that,
they just have them doing generic impressions
of the characters you do like.
Yeah, and it's like, it's likable to an extent
but they could have really done a journey,
if you will, an adventure, if you will,
of the dads with their daughters through time
and it would have been awesome.
It would have been fucking awesome.
Instead, we get the spider webbed six plot line thing
that doesn't make any sense that is solved
in a lazy ass sitcom kind of way
in the last three seconds where it's like,
oh, there's a way for you to be everywhere
all at once in the space time continue.
It's like, what the fuck are you guys even talking about?
What is happening?
And then,
Louis Armstrong, I just suddenly had a flash
of Louis, remember that?
Louis Armstrong.
The Hendrix thing, the way they convinced people,
they were traveling through time, didn't make any sense.
It was so, it was so goddamn confusing.
And then this thing ends.
Now I did, as I said, I got a little, a little teary
at the end when they were playing the song
and they were showing the whole world playing the song
and I was like, oh, they did it, the song, this is it,
this is what they've been building up to.
That was kind of cool.
And then, it just literally ends with the voice over
of the daughter going, they wrote the song and it worked.
The end.
That's literally the end of the fucking movie.
It's like, what is this?
Yeah.
The person I've seen raves about the most
is the guy from Barry who plays the robot.
And he was Johnny.
The only guy who got me close to it, to laughing,
but near the end, when he's doing like a big scene of stick,
the robot really has just some clearly kind of improv,
sticky moments.
My wife, who had never seen any of the built -in movies.
It had been going on for a bit and she turns to me
at about the hour 15 mark and says,
this might be the worst movie I've ever seen in my life.
And I don't really know how to argue with her.
I felt stupid and embarrassed.
I didn't want to share the franchise with her
because I felt like.
And that's the other thing too.
It's like, why are you doing this thing
like with the reunion with death?
Yeah.
I was confused because when they meet up with death finally,
and they're like, and death's mad at them.
Yeah, I was like, wait, why is he mad at them?
I thought like it ended okay in bogus journey.
And then I was like, oh yeah,
because in the half ass montage at the beginning,
they kick death out of the band.
That's something I'm supposed to remember,
didn't even remember it from this bullshit like montage.
Like why are you over complicating this?
Make it that when they meet up with death,
death is ready to help them.
Instead, they do this thing that you're confused about.
And then death even says to them,
if you're looking for a way out of hell,
I can't help you because I don't have the pull down here
that I used to, I'm demoted.
And then the second that death likes them again,
he's like, okay, I can get you out of here.
And it's like, you just said you couldn't do.
Yeah, like this, this thing was written,
it's, I've said it about Jansal and Bob Reboot.
This feels like it was written during somebody taking a shit
over 22 minutes of just blurting out a fucking outline
and going, oh, it's good enough, whatever.
Now, I know that wasn't the case.
It probably went through 1800 rewrites.
Right.
And they were probably working around dilemmas like COVID
or Keanu's not around because he's doing John Wick 5
or whatever the fuck it is.
But it just didn't work.
And to me, the greatest slap in the face of the whole thing,
I was really, really disappointed by was the fact that
Rufus was never explained.
Like, I thought it was cool that Carlin's image was in it.
I was like, oh, that's cool, they worked him in.
I was offended that they were never,
they never explained what happened to Rufus.
They never seemed to have any mourning over the loss of Rufus.
And then the fact that Rufus's wife is now the head of everything
and she's an asshole.
Yeah.
And you're supposed to just kind of laugh that off.
And it's like, but Rufus wasn't the head of everything.
Why is his wife now running everything?
None of this fucking makes any goddamn sense.
It should have been the wife being like,
hey, just just off the top of my head.
Hey guys, the futuristic societies against you now
and they want to kill you.
But I'm Rufus's wife, so I'm here to help.
Yeah.
What the fuck, something?
Why would Kristen Shaw be the daughter of George Carlin?
The two have such different, like it doesn't,
none of it makes sense.
Yeah, have some.
And if you're gonna have Kristen Shaw, whoever,
have her come in with the slick back hair ponytail
and the glasses, do a joke about like,
oh, that's buddy, that's Rufus's daughter.
That's absurd that she would look like that.
But that's her, something, anything.
Mike, are we changing your mind on this movie, by the way?
Oh, Mike says.
Absolutely not.
Yeah, people, people really love that.
Mike, I'm idiot.
I can answer every one of these questions.
You guys have brought up about the show so far.
I've been biting my tongue the whole time.
But yeah, no, you guys just more pain.
You guys weren't watching the same movie I was.
I think it's people being trapped inside with no entertainment
is why everybody is loving this movie, is my opinion.
But what I will say to close my thoughts,
I got nothing else to say about this franchise, except
the difference to me, the reason it's a inferior franchise
to a Wayne and Garth is that I could list 10 different major
personality traits about both Wayne and Garth.
Anyone who has seen Wayne's world knows which one is Wayne
and which one is Garth.
I have never, up to and including right this moment,
known which one was Bill and which one was 10.
I got to be honest, I did either.
I thought Bill was always Keanu because he was the bigger star.
And I was like, I don't know, Alex is Keanu.
They, I saw a clip this week, some interviewer called him,
called Keanu the wrong one and he had to correct him
and got all fake this and it was kind of funny.
But the characters have no difference between them.
They're just dudes.
There is no, and maybe that's what people like about it.
But Garth is a paranoid, scared, socially anxious,
sexually inexperienced, et cetera, et cetera, guy,
who idolizes Wayne, even though Wayne
isn't cool himself, but to Garth he's cool.
And who can't relate to that?
Garth, you know, idolizes Wayne because he can talk to people
and he's cooler and et cetera, et cetera.
Like Bill and Ted are the same character.
And when you're adding on extra characters
like their daughters and also not distinguishing them
from each other in any way, it just starts to look like
shitty writing.
I'm sorry.
Because the plot doesn't work and the characters
are the same and et cetera, et cetera, et cetera.
It's bad writing.
Mike, before we leave, we've never done this.
I will see you in hell.
This is a groundbreaking moment.
Mike, what do you, what is the face?
I want to hear what Mike's counter argue with us.
I want to hear this.
We've never had that.
Oh, please, I was reading him talking about the Missy subplot.
I don't remember there being a Missy subplot.
Can't believe you haven't covered the Missy subplot.
No, I said that that she's now marrying the brother.
I said that.
Oh, you did cover that.
Oh, yeah.
That is my favorite running gag through all three of these movies
that she was married to.
I agree.
I gave it credit.
Mike, in a minute or less, you tell us why you think
through the world wrong, please.
OK, so this actually covered evil Bill and Ted
in a funny way, unlike Bill and Ted too.
OK.
I thought too was a better film than one.
And I think this was better than even two.
Totally.
So you just said that this is the best of the franchise.
Do go back and watch the first one.
It is easily the weakest of the installment.
They do 20 unnecessary minutes on the polling in that movie.
The second one, obviously, they replaced that
with the games with death.
For this one, it's like the daughter subplot,
I really enjoyed when Louis Armstrong is playing
the trumpet and all that got me.
And just that, the ending, when I put it together,
that it was going to be the daughters playing the side turn
to Frank, who I was watching the movie with,
like, dude, it's going to be the, it's so cool.
It's going to be the daughter.
And then it was.
And like, I don't know.
I saw it coming a mile away, but it was heartwarming.
And I cried a little bit.
I've been literally watching Bill and Ted since I was six years old.
This is the now 32.
I've been with these guys for 26 years.
I loved it.
My first off, you don't mind me bragging about being 32.
Just because we are old men.
But I don't fault you for that.
If you loved it and anything brought you joy during this time,
Marvel, by all means, muzzle.
I just, I will say to Quote Billy and Addison,
we are all now stupider for listening to your,
he's in good company.
Everyone loves the movie.
But, geez.
For me, having just watched them all,
excellent adventure, B,
bogus journey, B,
face the music, D minus,
excellent adventure, B,
bogus journey, D,
whoo, face the music, F.
Yeah.
And I feel like, I feel like Mike's talking about a world where
this is like B plus B plus A plus.
I'm sorry about this thing because it's the Irishman.
All right, that's our show folks.
Joderosa comedy on Instagram and Twitter.
If you want to see what the latest and greatest is,
Joderosa comedian on Facebook.
Thank you all for listening.
Thank you all for being a part of the show here.
Announcements coming soon regarding me and Salvo Cano
and Christa Stefano's new project.
One of which will be a podcast featuring me and Salvo Cano.
Get you news on that soon.
Enough, thank you for listening.
Thank you for subscribing.
Thank you for your support.
We can't thank you enough.
Thank you, Mike, for your production skills.
And thank you for being with us.
The Patrick Walsh Twitter Instagram
and having the most fun lately on Letterbox.
If you want to see what I'm watching in real time.
Once a month, I do my Pat Sola movie corner on the Patreon.
Check those out.
You should have access to all of them now.
We have two tiers to the Patreon,
a two episode a month and a four episode a month.
Thank you to all of those.
No matter what tier you have come in at,
but thank you very much for supporting us on Patreon.
We would not be doing the show without your Patreon support.
Believe that.
Please remember to download the apps off the Patreon site
as opposed to streaming that way
you will never lose access to any of them.
And, yes.
Oh, next month's episodes.
We're probably going to do color out of space, right?
Sure.
Capone, we're definitely going to do.
We've talked about the lot.
Yeah.
You know, so that's, you know, those are...
We need some big juicy title.
We'll come up with something.
We need a juicy one.
But those are probably in the very near future.
Thank you all very much.
We will see you next time and we will see you in house.
Stay healthy.