Hey, folks, it's we'll see you in hell. The podcast you turn to
hear fucking Christ. Keep going. When you want to hear a movie talk. I couldn't even get that out.
Jesus God. It might be time for me to take over those reins. I mean, let's be real. You got it.
You got the job. I don't want to do it anymore. All right. All right. I'll put in the necessary
rehearsal hours that you refuse to do for our openings. Yes, folks, this is we'll see you in
hell. We're talking today about the empty man, which is steadily becoming. I think cult classic
is a little extreme, but I've noticed it getting a cult following. They dropped it on HBO Max. Also,
I spoke about it dismissively on here before I saw it. I was thinking of it as like the bye -bye man,
slender man. I was just associating it with that shit. And now having seen it, it's much different
and much better. I assume movie. I never saw those other two, but a really interesting movie
that we'll talk about in a bit. Joe, what's new with you? Old friend. So in between episodes,
I went. So this Instagram account called turned yellow turns people into Simpsons drawings.
It's a fan. I guess it's I don't think it's run by anybody that's actually with the Simpsons,
but anyway, they DM to me and they're like, can we do? Would you? Can we do one of you?
And I'm like, of course. Thank you. Pick whatever picture you like. And that I'm flattered. Thank
you. So they sent it to me today and it was pretty cool. And I was excited and I posted it.
And the comments under this thing, it's just what is wrong with everybody? What are the,
what's the issue? What are they saying? Some of them were funny. Like it doesn't look self loathing
enough. Like those ones are funny. Okay. There's 87 fucking the shoulders are wrong.
Why does he have shoulders? But those are half funny. It's just, it's where does that come from?
Who started the, you don't have shoulders thing, Patrice O 'Neill. Okay. And then it was, it was
around the seller for the first five years that I was in New York. And then it leaked to ONA when
I started to go on ONA. And then that was over after that. Yeah. So the shoulders thing is,
it's followed me forever and it's, it is what it is. There's another siren coming by for this
episode. That's good. Have you considered implants or Paula Poundstone style? Just,
you know, slip some pads in your sleeves. I do squat on a stool these days on stage
and wear a tie. So I should just add the shoulder pads. No, but the,
so the shoulder comments are whatever it is. It's part of the course, but then the ones that
there's ones that are just like epic fail. What, you know, this sucks. Why isn't your hair curly?
It's like, what is wrong with everybody? What is wrong with everybody? This is on Instagram,
by the way, it's not even Twitter. Now, remember when it used to be, you'd see that shit on Twitter
and everybody on Instagram was like, Oh, your vacation looks so fun. That would be the credit
you got. It's just fucking miserable everywhere. Everybody's miserable. There's no other way to
slice that. So anyway, bad time. It's a bad time. I mean, I, I've stopped essentially posting anywhere
and you feel better when you do it. You know, I just watched the scream trailer.
Yeah. You're not missing much, Joe, but I didn't have a chance to say, damn it. I forgot. We said
we were going to do that. No, it's I'll walk you through. I mean, it starts with an unknown
actress to me anyway, getting the phone call. Hello. You know, same voice, same guy, same voice.
Sounds a little older. Sounds like he's, he's been through some shit through the years, but yeah,
you know, she's like, wait a minute. How did you know my landline is ringing? You know, like it's
already like, they're just taking extra steps that don't need to be there. It's clunky as hell.
Nobody has a landline anymore, but she opens the door, the guy slashes her, and then it's like,
scream is back. So they cut to Neve Campbell, who's jogging, of course, around a reservoir,
as these characters always do when they get that call that things are happening again.
And she goes, they go, do you have a gun? David Arquette asks her because why wouldn't you ask
that question? Do you have a gun? And she basically into camera says, of course I do.
I'm Sidney Prescott. And it's like, I mean, look, I'll keep an open mind. I already saw Scream 4
and Scream 3 and this, this franchise, you know, it's already kind of limping along.
This was the plot of four, wasn't it? That after all these years, it comes back for her.
Yeah, exactly. But for her to say, well, this one, it looks like she's coming to town to help a new
group or something. But of course I have a gun. I'm Sidney Prescott is like that. Who is that line
for? Who is it to that? That's, that line is strictly for the viewer. It's like, we're not
even giving it the slight effort of making it appear that it's happening in the real world.
Uh, it looked, it looked boring. It looked lethargic to me. It's Cox and her running around and
you know, it's like the wisecracks suck. Like she goes, Hey, are you ready for this?
And Courtney Cox goes for this never. Cox, by the way, plastic surgery to the point that she now
resembles the actual ghost face mask. I said, look, we got two ghost faces here. And then my
eyes kind of adjusted. That's a novel twist, two ghost faces, but, um, no, it's the same.
Have I talked on this podcast yet about the Nicole Kidman AMC thing? Um, that show that is
the exact same thing as the other show. We kind of talk. No, no, no, no. When you see it now,
I'm an AMC Stubbs member. And now before every movie, there's like a two to three minute
infomercial type thing where it's Nicole Kim and walking up the stairs of an AMC
and narrating it. I mean, I of course was reminded of her because we're talking about
horrifically botched faces, right? She's walking up the stairs and then the narrations like the
movies are back at AMC week. You know, it's, it's a disgrace. And then they show her sitting
in a theater and they cut to what they're watching. And at first it's a clip of,
professional boxing. Like it's not even a movie clip. So she's like, we come to cheer on our
heroes to be scared. And then it's like her biting her nails. I mean, it's, it's just awful.
It makes me not want to go to the movies. It has the exact opposite effect of what it's supposed
to have. I'm the, I'm in the regal club. Yeah. For no reason greater than the, the, the title
AMC stubs has always grossed me out for some reason. It's got a Porky's ring to it. Something's
weird about that title. But I'm in the regal club. And when I go, they have one of those videos,
but it's a character. It's not a celebrity. Like it's a character talking about like the movies are
great. Again, he's called like captain watch them all or something. And he's like an explorer that
like watches every kind of movie. And I would have liked to see Nicole Kidman as captain watch
them all with a hat and a cloak kind of, um, did I tell you, I, I must have told this story
when I went to regal, one of the first times I went back and I was at the counter buying,
you know, an $8 and 50 cent water. Sure. And, uh, the, uh, the girl behind the counter goes,
would you like to just make it an even nine to donate to donate to, to regal?
Are you who it was? I think it was, yeah. Like support your theater. Like, like it's like,
it's some mom and pop or something. I was like, are you crazy? I'm already doing a $14 pin on
M and M sweetheart. Exactly. Take it out of that. Exactly. Which by the way, Sal made a claim
yesterday that Reese's peanut butter cups are readily available in every movie theater. I have
never seen them once in a movie theater. I don't think I've seen them either. Uh, AMC carries a
very delicious Reese's mix, like a checks mix type thing with, with all kinds of different things
in the bag, but I've never seen the, I've seen, I've seen pieces and I've seen the snack mix.
I've never seen the cups. What's in the snack mix, the pieces and like pretzels. Yeah. It's pieces,
pretzels. It's a salty, it's a sweet. It's very good. All right. All right. I'm listening. I'm
Stubbs is very good about giving me like perks. So you'll have like $10 added to your account
out of the blue and you know, why not? I, for a while there, when I was, uh, not, not exactly
thriving, I would buy the small bottle of Jack Daniels and a large diet Coke and pour the bottle
into the large thing of diet Coke. I don't do that so much anymore. I try to have a little
respect for my, myself. Um, but yeah, I, uh, I don't think scream looks good. They can prove
me wrong. We've got several months till January, but I don't have the highest of hopes after seeing
that. Uh, it's a tough time. I mean, we got over the next couple of weeks, I'm going to see bond
tomorrow night and IMAX, which I'm very excited about, but this three hour runtime is really
sticking in my crawl. I mean, I, I just rewatched the, the Craig ones and like casino Royale is so
awesome. I forgot how good it was. And then like, as, as you go, they get longer and there's just
like, he's like sad all the time. It, I don't get it. It's just this sad, miserable bond,
like looking out at the ocean. And, uh, I hope this one remembers to include some action. That's
off. So I guess they pulled out all the stops. It sounds like Cavill is in the running for the,
to be the next one.
And I really didn't go with it. I thought that they would go with them. It's time and it's not a, um,
you know, it's not the old, like we're trying to be controversial thing. He'd be perfect in the role.
He'd be a great, uh, I don't know. I don't, I'm curious to see what they do. Did you, um, or
aren't we ready for a Jane Bond? I'm sure it's been discussed. Yeah. Yeah.
Emily Blunt is Jane Bond. I was talking with Joe this week cause they had, well,
I don't know how we've, we've haven't talked about this, but, uh, hell raiser,
the new one, also David Gordon green is, uh, who's doing Halloween kills. It's a female pinhead.
And I'm all for this blind casting and everything else, but it's really hard to wrap my head around
that. And then Clive Barker's like, that's how the character was intended all along.
Well, I will say this. I will say this. I, first of all, I received that text when I was in the
middle of driving. That's why I didn't respond initially, but I will say this in the hellbound
heart, the original novella, the main centibyte is not pinhead. In fact, he doesn't even have pins in
his head. He has shards of glass instead of pins. Um, it was redesigned for the movie.
The main centibyte is the female centibyte that has the wire like through her cheeks in the first
two movies. She's more of the leader. That's why if you watch the original hell raiser,
pinhead, they both talk like it's not like pinhead is the guy. It's in the second movie. All of a
pinhead is the guy because everybody just like loved it, loved the character. So there is truth
to that. I don't think it should be a female pinhead. Make it that other character, like make it
a different centibyte. It's, it's, you know, to go, to go back to the, to the, when I was bitching
about the Kevin Smith, he man stuff, it's like, I don't have a problem with you doing a masters of
the universe show that's based around this Tila character, but don't call it he man and the masters
of the universe. So why does this character just have to be a genital switch on a male character?
Just make it the other character and be like, we're not going to do pinhead. We're going to
follow the book a little bit more closely. Um, also it's a fool's errand to try to recreate pinhead.
Like it's just not going to work. It didn't work with Freddie. It's not going to work with pinhead.
They've tried it with pinhead. It didn't work in two movies. So, um, you know, so hopefully that's
what they do. But, um, but yeah, it's just the, the, I have a joke about it on stage with like,
you know, how about create some new characters, like put some effort into these solutions. Like
it's, it's so insulting. It's such a bandaid fix to just take, you know, Batman or whatever.
And then all of a sudden he's just, you know, now we, now it's gay Batman or what,
you know what I mean? Just make a new character. Well, that's, that's the news this week. So when
they say that Superman is bisexual now, that's not canon. It's just one comic book that has him as
a bi Superman or what? It's his son. They just, they're designed in a lab basically to upset
nerds. These, these news announcements come out every day. And then of course, then Fox news gets
this is what they're trying to do to our children, a bisexual Superman.
I, unless I'm mistaken, it's one comic book, right? They're not making it like,
that's the new thing, right? It's his son. It's not Superman. It's John Kent,
John Kent. So I guess that's super, I don't, that's not even super boy. That's super boys
different. Um, so it's his son. So I guess his son. Yeah. No, I think that's like the permanently
for the character now. Like the new Robin is, is by, okay. Robin's always been by them. He
might not have been out, but in my mind, he's always, I agree. I agree. They really toughened
him up on the Titans TV show. Yeah. You know, they got rid of the green booties, right? Right. Right.
And the boy shorts, but at one time, I think Marlon Wayans before it became Chris O'Donnell,
the world's most boring actor, I think Marlon Wayans was going to be Robin. And then I guess
decided to just make him a boring white guy. But yeah, he was for Tim Burton's third. Yeah. Yeah.
There's a great story. Tim Burton's told it in endless interviews about that, where he,
where he's pitching. He's with Keaton and they're pitching the third movie. Yeah. And he said,
the executives start going like, Tim, you don't want to make another one of these. Are you tired?
Don't you want to do whatever? Right. And then finally Tim Burton goes, you don't want me to
make this movie, do you? And that was what it was. So they could go turn it into Batman forever. That
fucking travesty. Yeah. I was weird. I've never heard that story. But yeah, I was telling Joe,
you know, I'm sure Michelle Myers and Betty Krueger cannot be far behind, you know, and
look, there is no notable female horror icon to my, am I, am I wrong here? There's witches,
of course, but I can't think of like a great female horror icon, unless you,
maybe you want to talk about Linda Blair, but that was possession. No, there there's, yeah,
Linda Blair, you know, that's certainly one of the faces you see on the collage poster is,
is Reagan from The Exorcist. That's kind of it. Like, you know, I agree. I think there needs to
be one. And I think every time they do it, or excuse me, every time they attempt to do it,
they fuck it up with still in some way, victimizing the woman,
you know, like, no, even I was going to say monster, but that's a true story. But like,
even in that, it's like, she's a victim of men, and then she becomes a serial killer. Like,
it's never just, yeah, man, like, like, you know, and I guess, I guess I shouldn't talk,
because I'm working on a thing right now about that centers on a female character. And there is
an aspect of her being wronged by men in it. So I do find that interesting. So I saw a hypocrite,
I guess, right now. But yeah, it's there should be there should be an icon to me. That's just
it's a it's a lady that kills people. And she's got a fucked up face or something. And right. And
why does she do it? Because the town's people threw her into a well or something, for some reason.
Yeah, I mean, there's there's Kathy Bates in Misery. But that's, you know, it always is just
a regular woman like our buddy, Scotty Landis wrote Ma. And that was an attempt and a fun attempt.
At doing sort of a female horror lady, but it's always just a lady. You never get like the,
you know, the Freddy Krueger or the somebody who's got a big legend behind her. And it's time.
They tried with they tried with Darkness Falls. It didn't stick. They tried with Dead Silence. It
didn't stick. Yeah. Well, Dead Silence was a puppet, wasn't it? Yeah. But it's a lady that
was like a witch behind all the puppets that are right with children's souls into him or some shit
like that. It's a terrible movie, but but a cool premise. I'd love to see a good old
like, yeah, like, like a witch, you know, like a creepy fucking witch. Yeah.
That comes in your dreams or some shadow. Yeah, it's time for a good old fashioned
witch and the witch. For some reason, wasn't it? You know, there wasn't like a memorable
witch character in that. No. So we go to the corner, Joe, the movie corner, if you will.
Sure. Let's do it. Let me see. Hold on. There was something I wanted to mention. Give me one
second. Sure. I want to see if. Oh, oh, this is perfect. I'll do it in the movie corner. I got a
new mean old bitch. Oh, great. Rex Reed's review of Free Guy. Well, I hope he hated it because I
know I did. I keep seeing that hailed like I'm seeing Oscar talk for Free Guy. This movie is a
D, folks. Did you see it? Yeah. Did you talk about it? I just remember talking about how
much you thought it stupid. Yeah, no, I don't know if I did talk about it on the show, but I
despised it. And it's it's like they give roles sizable. I mean, not supporting, but pretty big
roles to these like PewDiePie types, the kids who do like game commentaries on YouTube. There's some
in the film. Then they cut to at one point, Chris Evans, Captain America, like Free Guy's like,
let me call a friend real quick and calls Chris Evans. The theater exploded into like applause
and cheers when they saw him. And I described it as being like Travis Bickle in Taxi Driver when
he kicks over the TV because couples are dancing and he can't understand them and he can't relate.
I just looked around this theater like I don't want to be a part of this society anymore.
But in what what is the context of him calling? He's playing Captain America, like because it's
Disney and they own everything now, there's a lightsaber gag. Captain America makes an appearance.
It's like they're doing the fucking Ready Player One shit in Free Guy. I'll say this really quick,
really quick because it relates directly. It'll count as a sort of movie corner thing. I watched
I started finally watching The Letterman Show on Netflix. I enjoyed it very much. David Letterman's
a pleasure to watch and it's really lovely getting to see him sit in a real interview setting
and actually talk to people. What's the best one? What should I watch? I watched Tina Fey and maybe
Jay -Z, I think. I loved the Obama one. It was so cool to see what I consider to be our last
charismatic president. Because then you got Trump who was very boorish and then or charming,
I should say is a better word, because Trump's got charisma, but he's boorish and gross, whatever.
And then you got Biden who I believe is a hologram at this point. I don't think it's a
person exists. So it was just great to see a president in that casual setting. I don't
remember ever seeing anything like that except for when Clinton did like Arsenio, but that was
before he was president. And Obama is really fucking funny, man. He breaks Letterman's balls
in the way a comic would. He's making fun of his beard and he's like, you got a staff somewhere
to go with that thing. I was like, Jesus, he's fucking funny, man. Well, they always say the
whole reason Trump ran for president was Obama breaking his balls at that White House Correspondents
Center and making great funny jokes about him. And they cut him in the audience fuming. And
apparently that's the moment he decided to run. That's amazing. I know, I know. But out of spite,
a spite presidency. But I watched, I'm bringing it up because I like the show, but I watched the
Robert Downey Jr. one. Yeah. And at one point, Letterman, when he introduces him, refers from
his Mr. Box office, which is true. They talk about how he's come to the end of the Marvel thing.
Robert Downey Jr. says, you know, look, it might sound a little arrogant or whatever he goes,
but I don't mean it this way. I think I'm pretty much in a position where I could do whatever I
want now, which he can. Yeah. And Letterman goes, would you, would you do like a, if the story spoke
to you, would you do like a million dollar picture? And Robert Downey Jr. goes, million is tough.
Right. I like that honesty. Yeah. And then he turns to the audience and goes,
that's my dry cleaning bill. Like it makes that joke. Sure. Which is funny. But like,
I do appreciate the honesty, but it's like, what, how much more do you need? No, I know. You made
it like, go make, go do an awesome small thing that like, we'll still get seen. By the way,
you'll make it back at the box office, pal. You're Robert Downey Jr. You know, and then it's
these little movies that got him where he is. He did kiss, kiss, bang, bang. And then Favreau was
like, I'd love to see this guy as iron man. You know, like that's, they forget it quickly. You
know, they get dazzled by the money. I have a couple friends in this business who are multi,
multi, multi, multi millionaires. And they'll complain about not having money and needing to
I won't name names, but I said to the one guy in particular, what the fuck are you talking about?
Like you have more money than you know what to do with. What are you talking about? And he goes, no,
I, unfortunately, my wife and I started living like people who have a shitload of money.
And then you have to keep up that lifestyle. And then you're scrambling. Like me, I'd always
want to keep my overhead low. When I made good money, I saved it. And that's why I'm not scared
to death that I haven't worked in two fucking years. But it's like, yeah, I think that's what
they do. They just start living and going bigger and harder and like, okay, we need the five
gardeners instead of one. And you just got to keep up that lifestyle. And then you never do anything
good and interesting again. He owns, he owns and occupies with his wife, who is a lawyer, by the
way, in Hollywood. So they're both making good money, but she produces his shit too.
She was his handler on a movie. Because he was so fucked up. And he said they start the date. And
then finally she was like, look, it's the drugs are me. And he got sober. But they live on a
huge farm that has like, they just rescue all these animals and stuff. They're not all rescues
with it. They got like llamas and shit. And it's hilarious because they're walking, they show footage
of it. They're walking around at one point and Letterman, every question he's like, he's like,
what is this thing? And Rob Jones years like, um, I think it's, um, and he's, he's trying to
make it look like he has. He's, you know, such a big party for these animals. Yeah. At one point,
he starts naming them to his wife in the audience and they cuts her. She's shaking her head. And he
goes, am I getting the names all wrong of the animals? And she goes, yeah. And he's like,
sorry, hon. Anyway, when I was doing chaplain or whatever the fuck they were talking about,
I could do it. Um, anyway, I guess there was that judge movie, uh, with it, with Krumholtz in a
little role. And other than that, has he even done anything that wasn't a giant budgeted spectacle?
I mean, there was, it's like in his downtime from Marvel, he did fucking do little. It's like, dude,
don't you want, don't you want to be in things that are good and challenge yourself? And I guess
not. You know, so I don't know. He's a brilliant actor. Um, yeah, he's great. He's great. But he's,
he's, uh, well, he, he doesn't follow the scripts at all. Right. Yeah. He says he thinks that
there's always room for improvement, which is such a fuck you to an actor like that. Yeah. Uh,
he said that he went in, he told a story about going into chaplain and goes, he goes, I go to
Dickie Attenborough and Letterman laughs at like the audacity to call him Dickie Attenborough.
But he's not kidding. He's like, calls him Dickie Attenborough. Right. And he's like,
here's how this movie should be. And this is what you've left out. And he said, like Attenborough
was like, get, indulged him to do a read through of his version. Uh, and then just at the end of it
went, okay, great everybody. Uh, we'll see you with my script on Tuesday and, uh, go fuck yourself.
That's crazy. I mean, I just saw circling all week on Twitter, bro. They had the succession premiere.
I'm, I'm excited. I love succession, but, uh, Brian Cox, star of trick or treat is saying,
you know, like the writer is the only thing he's like, I, I've been working in this business for
such a long time. I know now that the script is the key, the writer is King. He goes, and, uh,
I got to tell you the, the UK values the writer about a million percent more than the U S he's
it's embarrassing how little respect and regard they have for the writer. And boy, is that true.
I don't know if the UK is, is I, I assume I guess it's better, but like, man, it just,
they're nothing here. We're like below the line at this point, you know, we're, we're the crew,
which I support the crew fully. It's just like, you almost don't have much say at a certain point.
They think that writing it, I don't know, they don't have any respect for it because they don't
understand it. It's a shame. Yeah. So I hope the OTSI, by the way, the crews get what they deserve.
I hope so too. When I was coming into work at 8 AM and leaving at 9 PM, my life was a living hell,
but the crew had already been there for two hours when I showed up and they were there for an hour
after I left. And they're the people who make these things happen and they deserve everything
they're asking for. Uh, I agree. And there's been some excellent points made about like
the waste that goes on on these sets and how the product suffers. And it's, it's, this needs to
spread to everything, to craft services, to all of it. It is an exorbitant waste of fucking money
and time. Yeah. And it's money that could be on the screen for sure. Uh, let me take,
let me take you to the movie corner because I really want to showcase my favorite movie of
year. Although it's, it hasn't exactly been a banner year, titane, uh, a movie that I saw.
It's, it's from the lady who did raw, which we taught, which we reviewed on this show and both
really enjoyed the cannibal movie. Uh, Julia do Cornell. This is her followup. She's got more
and it is just an amazing, amazing movie. It starts, I mean, for, for almost an hour,
it's pure horror. It's this lady who is in a car accident or as a, as a little girl and gets,
it's never quite explained, but she becomes sort of half titanium. She's almost like half car,
half human. All right. Uh, at some point in the movie, she fucks a car.
I mean, kind of like Cronenberg's crash, but she's sitting in the back seat, holding onto two
seat belts, bouncing up and down. You don't see what's going on, but it looks like she's being
fucked by this car. All right. Um, she is a stripper. She is a very sort of androgynous,
interesting looking woman. She's naked throughout the entire film and she gets impregnated by the
car. Uh, so instead of blood coming out of her throughout is like oil coming out of her. And
look, if you need an explanation as to why this is happening or what's going on, titane is not
going to be the movie for you, but at some point she goes on a kill spree. These are some of the
grotesque, exciting, violent, disgusting kills I've seen in ages. My buddy who I saw it with was
like, what the fuck was the first hour where she's killing everybody? And I was like, that was my
favorite part of the movie, right? It's an excellent horror movie. And then it becomes something much
deeper and more interesting because she pretends to be this firefighter who has lost his son.
She pretends to be his son. So she tapes her boobs down. Um, you know, she already looks kind of
androgynous, but to basically, to escape being arrested for her crimes, she pretends to be this
guy's son and the two find that they really need each other. And it becomes kind of a beautiful
story, even though it's very disgusting and very violent. And I've never seen an audience look away
more in my life. A lot of people walked out, but, um, look, if you like the extreme in your cinema,
if you liked raw, this movie is fucking awesome. It's not always realistic. There's a scene where
all the firefighters are shirtless dancing to future Island. Like it's, uh, you know, a gay
nightclub. And you're like, I don't think firefighters do this, uh, in the firehouse
necessarily, but it's, it's her vision. It's a filmmaker that I am so excited to watch. Now you
get these, maybe one a year, you get a filmmaker where you're like, I can't wait to follow this
person's career. I definitely feel that way about Duke Cornell. If you haven't seen raw, see it.
And please see titane because I think you're going to love it. I loved it myself.
You can go three, three in a row and then I'll just do mean old bitch.
Okay. Uh, well that I'll do the Joe Bob. I watched him this week and he did, uh,
terror train, which I had never seen. Jamie Lee Curtis, a good one. Didn't like it. Gotta be
honest. I thought the, the, I mean, they, they talked about how Roger Spottis would, who later
directed, uh, a couple bond pictures or one bond picture is not a horror guy. Joe Bob just keeps
saying there's no kills in this movie. He doesn't know how to do kills. It's like there's nothing,
but he loves the movie. He gives it a good rating, but, uh, basically he says the guy who came up
with it woke up in the middle of the night, told his wife, I want to do Halloween on a train.
What if we make Halloween on a train? So his wife says that's the worst idea I've ever heard and
goes back to bed, but he wrote it down on a pad. They got it made. It is Halloween on a train,
but it's nowhere near as good. I, I was, I was pretty let down by territory and I gotta be honest
with you. Um, and they also did angel, which I remember seeing the box for. And I also remember
using as jerk off fodder because when I was a kid, I used to just like take a mental picture
of a VHS box and that's what I used to jerk off. You, you youngsters don't know how lucky you have
with the access to pornography, but angel is, keep in mind, I was 10 because this girl's supposed
to be 15. Uh, it's a 15 year old prep school honor student who moonlights as a Hollywood prostitute.
I checked out of this one. I didn't watch it because I was like, this isn't a horror movie,
right? Or is it? It's not a horror movie. Apparently David Gordon green picked it,
which is a very odd choice for a middle -aged man to want to watch angel and acknowledge that
he wanted to watch angel, but, um, it's a serial killers who stalks and murders prostitutes. So she
is kind of going up against him, but it's not horror. The killer is a very weird dude who like
sucks the inside out of an egg at one point, which is a really unsettling scene. Um, there's
good stuff in it. It's kind of a fun trash eighties classic, but there's better versions of this vice
squad. Uh, Linda Blair did a couple of really good kind of movies like this about sort of teenage
then, uh, vengeance angel kind of let me down, but I do recommend watching Jason Bloom and David
Gordon green and Joe Bob. They, they had some really great conversations on this, this Halloween
episode of the show and I liked it. All right. Um, that's it for me, but lamb, the new, the new
one from a 24, I go in hard on, on my, uh, my little solo movie corner, which I'm recording
and I'm going to post shortly, but how little is the most a 24 movie that there has ever been
and they, it's, it's a shame. It's a shameful movie. Uh, how little, how not horror is this
horror movie that they're touting as terrifying and whatever. There's zero horror in lamb. It's,
doesn't work as horror. It doesn't work as anything, but it's a couple who has a baby
who's got a lamb's head, but the rest of it's human. It talks, um, and it's never explained.
It's just never explained. Did the husband fuck a lamb? The only reason you're watching really is
to find out, did the husband fuck a lamb or was the wife infertile? Like what happened? Never
addressed. It is such a dumb and bad movie that has nothing to say. And it's just this big empty
thing shot with the a 24 filter. At this point, it's like they put a filter over the camera to
make it look exactly the same as the other ones. But, um, no, I, I spend quite a bit of time
dissecting lamb. I really, I, a 24, I mean, you heard what I said about Blumhouse on the last
episode. A 24 is right there for me anymore. Like I can't stand this fucking company's product at
all. Yeah. And you know who you never hear mentioned and nobody knows is neon and neon,
I would say has a higher success rate. They put out titanium and you know, they must've gone to
a 24 as well, but, uh, I personally love what neon is doing. I see them lately as more of a sign
quality, but whatever. So, uh, mean old bitch, here we go. Yes. Rex review, Rex Reed reviews,
free guy, a zero star Ryan Reynolds vehicle with zero animation, computer generated action,
forced frivolity and a lack of originality define Ryan rent Reynolds latest nonsensical film,
which I think he means he only makes nonsense. Yeah. Yeah. Another Ryan Reynolds movie is hardly
anything to recommend or write home about, but he's undeniably wholesome looking, nautilus pumped
and camera ready, which is all today's movie industry cares about. True. True. He possesses
enough crude charm to make even a lump of forgettable fluff like free guy and occasionally
tolerable way to waste two hours in the middle of a summer heat wave. That is not a recommendation,
not a, uh, a recommendation at all. No, it's a good start. It sucks. I mean,
it's, it's exactly what it looks like in the trailer. It's Ryan Reynolds who has 14 visible
abs stuttering and stammering. And he's a nerd who can't talk to women. It's like we used to have
Rick Moranis play that part. Yeah. And now it's the best looking man in Hollywood and everyone has
to be amazing looking. I read that big article about Kumail. He had for some reason, three
different articles this week about his body that were released online. And, you know,
they were talking about how he got all jacked for this movie and he thought it would open up
all these kind of like big action star roles for him. But instead it opened up like dad roles
because to play a dad, now you have to be Jack like that. And it's, it's sick. And also I wonder
as a kid, as a kid, I had huge body issues that stay with me to this day, but if you're seeing
Ryan Reynolds playing a guy who's like ugly and can't talk to girls, what does that do for the
self -esteem of an actual chubby kid? It can't be good. I know it's not an even field for men and
women in this department. I know women get away worse with the body stuff, but it is a thing for
men. It doesn't make us feel like shit when, when the nerd is Zac Efron or whatever, you know,
right. You're like, yeah. So, um, anyway, Rex Reed goes on under the, I'm sorry. Oh no,
it's fine. Under the unfocused direction of Sean Levy, a tirelessly prolific director responsible
for an interminable list of gimmicky TV shows and sci -fi flicks, including the horrible night at the
museum franchise and written by the equally unimpressive team of Matt Lieberman and Zac
Penn. The unbearable free guy is another incoherent entry in the current disturbing trend toward
movies about artificial intelligence and alternate realities that take place inside computers. He is
hitting on all cylinders in this thing. Am I Rex Reed? I mean, this feels like how I talk about
every movie I see. This time, Ryan Reynolds plays Guy, a shy, brainless, button -down banker
whose empty life is defined by the same daily routine. Rise early and pale, freshly launder
baby blue pajamas, eat a bowl of tasteless cereal, select the same uniform from the closet filled
with neat rows of baby blue suits. You get the point. This is all because Guy, you see,
is a peripheral character called blue shirt guy in a video game called free guy. So he goes on
about the plot here. I don't want to read his breakdown of the plot. I will skip to the end.
Guy wants to be more than another non -playable character, but it's hard to become a leading
player when the game's inventors are planning a sequel and he's not even going to be in it.
Can he get off the screen and rejoin the real world? Can he bring his consuming passion for
gum ice cream to the video game? Can blue shirt guy find true love with Molotov girl?
The movie makes a feeble attempt to say something satirical about online gaming
and something critical about the evils of capitalism, but every idea is borrowed from
so many other sources from Wreck -It Ralph to Lego movie that you couldn't find a trace
of originality with a microscope. And then it just says free guy in theaters now.
It's honestly refreshing to hear somebody's shit on this movie because you start to feel crazy
when you read all these good reviews of something like this, something that is so shit. I agree
with Mr. Reed. Reed is in for this is it, dude. He is like, this is it. He's out for blood, dude.
He's out for vengeance. Yeah. Holy shit. That's fucking funny. Jesus Christ. He's on the money.
Folks, we're talking today about The Empty Man. And no, it's not a story of me and my life.
It was based on a graphic novel. It stars James Badge Dale, who I guess had a little part in the
Departed. You recognize him. He's a character actor. And then Steven Root would be the other
actor that you know as sort of a cult leader. The movie had a very troubled development.
So apparently they went shot a bunch of it in South Africa. And during the final week of shooting,
production halted due to poor weather conditions. During this time, Mark Roybal left Fox, who was
the essential executive towards green lighting the film. This stuff happens a lot. Somebody who's
really passionate and like the reason your project gets picked up will get fired because executives
get fired every week. Then they realized that the new executive has zero interest in their movie.
So the budget was approved for $16 million. They noticed the budget started getting less and less.
It went down to 11. The final week of production resumed back here in the States. Test screenings
occurred and they told him to assemble a cut. The day production ended, they were like, just make
cut of it. And he's like, well, no, it's a long movie and very involved and complicated. It got
low test scores. The studio panicked. The producers assembled a 90 minute version of the film, 45
minutes shorter than the director wanted. And that tested even worse. This led him to do his final
cut of the film, which is I will say needlessly long. It's about 220. But there are so many movies
that have these just disastrous productions and this guy may never work again. You know,
the only way he's going to work again is if this cult following builds and builds and builds.
And people realize that he's a director with some talent because I enjoyed The Empty Man,
although it is a very unorthodox movie with a lot of problems.
It's very unorthodox. The trailer doesn't do it any favors.
No, it looks like a teen horror picture, which it is. It's a slow burn of sorts.
It's got one of the best cold opens I've ever seen in a movie ever.
Similar to The Departed where like the credits come up and it's like 25 minutes into the movie
and you're like, wow, that was a great kickoff. Awesome. And look, something I complain about
constantly on this podcast that they nail a pet peeve of mine. They nail the logic of this thing.
It's a wild story. It's a wild premise about an urban legend where if you blow into a bottle on
a bridge, you hear The Empty Man and then you see The Empty Man. And then on the third day,
The Empty Man takes you. Yeah. And the way they tie it back into the original
cold open, the way they explain why what happens in the cold open happens.
It gets into this whole Scientology cult kind of thing that is behind the summoning of The
Empty Man and that eventually ties into who your main character is. It's really a lot to take in,
but it all makes sense. What do you call that? It's airtight. So I really like the film. It stars
a guy I can't remember his name. The only thing I know he was in, he was one of the kids in The
Lord of the Flies remake. Yeah, James Badgedale. I said his name. I said his name. I kept thinking
he was the kid from Big, but it's not him. That's the kid from American Werewolf in Paris, right?
Tom Everett Scott? Tom Everett Scott wasn't in Big, but I know who you're referring to. I don't
know that that kid acts anymore. Maybe he does. Okay. Well, anyway, I thought it was the kid from
Big, but he's in Lord of the Flies. What's -his -face is a great cameo in this. Your boy.
Steve Root, who I also mentioned. You really don't listen when I speak.
No, no, no, no. I remember you mentioning Steven Root, but do we talk specifically about his
scene? I want to speak to his scene. I really like because I've never seen him play
this type of character before. He plays like a real, he's creepy. I've never seen Steven Root
be creepy. I don't think he's done it a few times, but this is like, usually it's got like that crazy
eye and he's kind of hamming it up a little bit. This is a very like, he's like, feels like a
cult leader. You know, he feels like he could break your neck at any second. He's got a real
menace to him. And he runs the Pontifex Institute, which Pontifex, I believe is,
it means the Pope. It's referring to things to do with the Pope. So I don't know if that's some
sort of shot of Catholicism or what, but yeah, the cult, you know, it winds up feeling like this big
epic sort of global movie because the beginning is set in this like Aguirre wrath of God, like,
you know, I guess it's South Africa, but like really out in the wild and there's this big
rope bridge that looks a lot like the one in Temple of Doom, but even more kind of scary and
intense. It opens when she's throwing everybody over that cliff. That was the most effective
throw over the cliff scene I've ever seen, even more so than Cliffhanger. It made my stomach do
flips watching it. And you know, the movie is always chasing that opening. It never quite gets
back to that good, but it's all done in Missouri. Basically he's trying to find out what happened
to this girl who vanished. And it leads him to sort of piece together what's going on with this
cult and kind of try to stop it. And in the end, he winds up sort of elevated to the head
of this cult. It's a wild ride. I mean, I will, did you feel like the running time was warranted?
It was a little long, but they made up for it with certain things. I got to tell you that when
she's throwing the guys over the cliff, that was amazing. Yeah. No, I'm just joking. I'm
fucking with you. Yeah. No, I did think it was a little long in runtime, but I did. And the,
in the very end, I was like, no, I, I needed all that information. Like it was, it was,
there was a lot to do here. And also too, I want to go back to the Pope thing.
I didn't know that. And I do think you're, I think you're correct. I think it is some sort of
analogy on Catholicism because three days, the empty man, yeah, that three days Christ rose
from the dead. He's the God. He is the one that will lead us, blah, blah, blah, blah.
When is Jesus coming back? Well, seemingly never. We can't wait any longer. We now have to create a
Jesus. Anyway, I do think it was, that's an insightful thing that you said. I think it's
accurate. And that's interesting because then that makes Steven Root the Pope. And if you're
Catholic, you have to believe the Pope is infallible. That's the belief and that he is the
conduit between you and God himself. And that's what Steven Root plays. He'd say he delivers the
message to them directly from the empty man. Yeah. You know, so that's, that's interesting, man.
Well, thank you, Joe. You're welcome. Yeah. I mean, looking here, it's the critical response
to it was, you know, just, just as dismissive as a lot of critics are with any horror movie,
you know, so many critics just don't get horrid, don't know how to separate the good from the bad
because all they see is people getting killed and they're uncomfortable by that, you know,
but it got bad reviews. It says here, they started, they put out trailers for it a week
before the movie came out, whereas even an indie, generally you start seeing previews two months
before. So they clearly just wanted to bury it, kill it. Film school rejects here says,
as happens with most cult movies, the empty man's audience has started to view the film's alleged
weaknesses as its strengths. I think that's a very insightful point because
oftentimes that those cults are wrong. In my opinion, Southland Tales is a cult that,
that after rewatching that I can say that cult is wrong. Like sometimes when everybody hates
something, there are people who just decide that it's good and that because they want to be
different and contrarian. I've never seen, just a quick diversion. I've never seen Southland Tales.
It's terrible, right? It's, it's, it's terrible. And I, I think I discussed on this show that I
got the aero version, which had like the three hour Sundance cut. And I was like, okay, now I'm
going to see what I was missing. And this thing was botched to hell and it just sucks. And I,
I love Donnie Darko. It almost seems like how could these two movies be made by the same guy?
But it's, it's bad. And I think the longer version is even worse because it's longer.
He gives, you know, dramatic roles to like John Lovitz, Sherry O. Terry,
like it's a, it's a rough, rough movie to watch the empty man though. I think there's something
to be said about that. The, the, the film's alleged weaknesses are that it's, it doesn't
make sense. It's, it's a bore. It's, it's, uh, you know, there's so many critics who gave it bad
reviews, but I think the surreal elements of it are what it, what is most effective about it.
And what Joe is saying is, is totally correct. If you're paying attention, they do a really good
job of explaining all this and making it make sense and making it add up. So any critic being
like, like this guy here gives it a D minus and he's like, it's a total bore, the bastard cousin
of the bye -bye man or whatever, you know, that's just somebody who's not engaging with the movie.
Who's not even trying. And that's somebody who saw the trailer and, and made a decision. That's,
that's why I thought this was the bye -bye man. That's how bad the trailer did representing this
film. But then you watch it and you go, Oh, no way. It's so much more. I would equate this film.
I almost, it reminded me quite a bit. It's, it's, it's a less intense, but it reminded me quite a
bit of like prisoners or something like that, where you're following a guy on a very weird
journey. You're not quite sure who you trust or who you don't. And in the end, you don't really
know how you feel about that guy anymore. You know what I mean? Like it all kinds of turns,
it turns on its own ear. But it like, I, I, I thought it was, yeah, I liked it. I really liked
it. And I got to tell you, I was dreading the runtime when you said it's cool. I was like,
awesome. I want to see it. And then you, and then I put it on and I was like, mother fucker,
this is two and a half hours or whatever it was. Yeah. I was like, God damn it. Okay. But once that
cold open hit, I was just like, this guy clearly knows what the fuck he's doing. So what, you know,
it's like a Scorsese movie. It's like, you know, like you said, the departed, you, you get past,
if you never saw a Scorsese movie and you saw the departed, you get past that cold opening.
And when that title hit, you'd be like, all right, this guy knows what he's doing. Like,
I'm going to stick around and there's going to be a lot going on. I still remember in the theater
when the, when the departed came on and the dropkick Murphy's over. I mean, I was pumping my
fist. There's something about it. It's a real like dick on the table move to just put your credits
up that far into the movie. So I think the reason the runtime doesn't bug me that much is that it
almost feels like it's its own self -contained short. And then the movie starts after that,
even though they tie in together very well. Yeah. It feels like two kind of different movies, but
that, that short film that opening 20, 25 minutes is some of the best, uh, horror filmmaking I've
seen in a while. This guy, David Pryor got his start doing DVD special features for David Fincher's
movies. He was handpicked by Fincher to do all the extra features. And if you own a copy of fight
club or seven or gone girl or any of Fincher's movies, he loads them up because I think he's a
and extras and stuff. So if Fincher gives you the stamp of approval, I would hope this guy would
have a nice long career. But when your first movie is something like this, that loses a lot of money,
that, that gets really bad reviews on warranted or not, he's going to really have an uphill battle.
I think unless somebody loves what he did, somebody loves the empty man and gives him another shot.
And I think anyone who sees it, especially a horror fan is really going to enjoy this movie,
even though it's, it's an unusual ride, you know, that's what I like about it.
I like that it wasn't going through the beats of like, cause there's a version of the empty man
that has the same premise and just feels like some piece of shit, teen horror movie that gets
dropped in theaters and nobody pays attention to the problem is that everyone thinks that's what
this is. And it isn't, I would advise you to check it out and make, make your own mind up.
And the randomness of that pisses me off where, first of all, you know, we liked it quite a bit.
If we're not giving major spoilers away. Right. But also too, that's what pisses me off about the
randomness of this business. Cause this guy will, like you said, we'll have to scratch and claw
probably to do another thing when he's got so talented and he, and he, it's not his fault that
they mismarketed this thing and that they were hit with disasters. Yeah. You know, but meanwhile,
they let this fucking fantastic four guy, whatever his name is, you know, give him eight shots at
whatever, you know, it's like, come on guys. So, um, my hog is up definitely up. Uh, this is on
HBO max right now. I don't know how long it will be there, but, uh, if, if you have that service,
I'd add it to your queue. It's the kind of generic, nondescript poster and title that almost
ensures that this movie will fall through the cracks unless people talk it up and recommend it
to their friends. And that's why we chose to spotlight it this week. I think anyone with a fan
for the offbeat, a fan of horror will get a kick out of the empty man. I agree. Treat yourself this
holiday season. Uh, and speaking of which, excuse me, sorry. Uh, November 1st will be another dose
of Halloween, uh, for you with Halloween kills, which we will review on that day. And we're
kicking around with the second film will be, it might be dune. So if Joe can, if Joe can stomach
it, we'll do dune. Yeah, we'll see. Uh, if nothing else, I think we'd have a blast discussing it.
I want to see it. It's the three goddamn hours. Isn't it over? Isn't it over three?
I thought that because he divided it into two, that it's a reasonable running time,
but I don't know. It definitely looks like it's going to be three hours, but I don't know
that it is. I think what they did is create this incredibly expensive world and incredibly
expensive sets and all that, and then just tore them down. And now if it's a hit, they'll have
to put them all back up. It's so stupid on their part. It really is. But he, he divided into two
meaning he just shot half of the book. He didn't have the book. And apparently when it ends,
the story isn't done. You're just like halfway through it. So well, and that's the thing
that, and, and, uh, you know, we all know Lynch's dune was even though I kind of enjoyed it,
it's not good. Yeah. And then Jaredowski said his, his never went anywhere. And he said,
when he saw Lynch's doom, he rejoiced cause he was like, I'm not sad. I didn't get to make mine
now because it's clearly an unfilmable idea. I don't even think he's wrong there. So that's
what worries me about this is that there's so much in that book that this first half of it is going
to be three fucking hours. Yeah. You know, no, even my, even my friends who re like, I got a
buddy who really loves hard fantasy, like that kind of like beyond, uh, uh, Tolkien stuff, like
really hard fantasy books. And he said, he's tried to read dune 10 times and it's just so dense and
he gets nothing out of it and can't finish it. And I really do think it's a lot of people are
going to go to this thing, expecting some big wild action fun house and then get dune. I mean,
dune is so boring. And if they're faithful to the book at all, the movie is going to be boring too.
But I do love Villeneuve. I think he's one of our best directors. However, when I saw that
Blade Runner 2049, which everybody tells me I should revisit, blah, blah, blah. But that's a
who is no stranger to making a long, boring piece of shit. And, uh, that may be what's coming up
with dune. I don't know, but I will see it in IMAX. I'm excited to see it in IMAX. It's two and a
half hours. That's not terrible. It's less than bond. And it's got a 90 % on Rotten Tomatoes,
which could mean it's great or could mean it's free guy. We don't know. Yeah,
you never know anymore. I think their reviews are being bought more than ever.
I mean, I might. All right. I'm closer to seeing it than not. Let's put it that way.
Close. All right. If we don't do dune, we'll do something, you know, great for the Halloween
season. Um, anyway, my, uh, my solo movie corner will be up shortly. It's going to be over an hour
because of the, uh, the kind of less than great nature of my last one, but I've been recording
a long discussion after each movie I watch and it's funny stuff. I'm excited to post it.
We will be back. Uh, definitely Halloween kills, probably dune. I'm on Instagram and Twitter,
the Patrick. Well, I don't even know why we say that anymore. Everybody knows where we are.
You know, I don't get anything to plug. Uh, I got nothing inside. If you're in New York,
go to Joe's sandwich shop. We are the empty men, Joe and I. Yeah. The pop -up is open at the stand
every Wednesday to Friday, 12 to 4 PM. And the actual spot is opening very soon. So keep your
well, uh, I am going to pop in. Well, I don't know when this is going to post, but I probably
already have popped in to, uh, the discussion group that's going on. We love that that's
happening. We love that you guys are finding a friend group out of this podcast. That's so
cool. And I, I'm going to definitely pop in tomorrow night and say hello, uh, cause I'm home
and I got nothing to do past few weeks. I've been busy. Is the movie watched or just discussed in
group. They, from what I gather, they discuss a movie last week was Donnie Darko and, uh,
they also discuss mental health. I mean, I think it kind of spawned off this mental health solo
corner that I did where I kind of just put up, put my problems on the line. And, um, yeah,
just talked about the importance of connecting with people. You know, I realized my most depressed
times during this pandemic were, were the weeks where I isolated myself. It didn't talk to anybody.
So it's a good way to communicate with like -minded people. All right. As far as I can tell from Emily,
it's been a great success. Thank you to Emily, uh, for all she does. Thank you to all of you for
following us on Patreon and telling your friends and the audience is growing, which we were not
expecting. It's fantastic. Thank you all. Thank you all. And I will also try to pop into the group
at some point. Uh, and, uh, we love you guys. Thanks for everything. We'll see you next time
and we'll see you in hell.