Howdy folks, We'll See You In Hell is back at it again.
I'm Joe DeRosa and I'm Patrick Walsh.
Good morning.
How are you, Joe?
I'm fine.
I, uh, I know it doesn't look like it, but I rose early this morning.
I, uh, I did my little exercises.
Yeah.
Uh, I drank some coffee.
What are those?
Do you like shoulder lifts up and down with the shoulders?
I do the, I got dumbbells.
I do these.
No, I was doing the shrug.
Like what you ever see that as an exercise where somebody just puts
their shoulders to their ears and down literally the least you can do.
It's, but it does, it does a lot for in here.
If you ever do it, it burns like hell.
Uh, I should probably bring those back in since as a man that needs shoulders,
but, uh, and some reps, I do the curls.
I do the presses and I do pushups.
It's very simple.
I do, I do 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10.
Yeah.
That's something, you know, and then in the house here, when I'm down
at the house, I I'm up and down the stairs all day, but down, up and down,
up and down, so I don't know.
You know, this is the workout regiment of like a 68 year old retired woman.
Well, you know, I I'm up and down with the laundry all day.
So, you know, I figure I don't need to go to jazzercise.
I've real I'm realizing why all those years growing up, women would say it's
the hardest job in the world is being the house mother of life.
It is.
It's a lot.
It's a lot of moving.
It's a lot of bending.
It's a lot of squatting, you know, like I rearranged my storage unit last night.
And it was like, Jesus Christ, man.
Yeah.
You know, I, um, these activities like rearranging or alphabetizing my vinyl or
my movies really scratches the, uh, the OCD itch.
And I know on days I wake up when it's bad, I like, I just sit and do that.
So this week I've been doing books, getting books, you know, collected by author.
It's sad while you're doing it.
It's like, if you, if you just, you're, I'm having a nice time enjoying myself,
but if you think about it, the sadness creeps in, which is pretty much the
case for everything I would say.
It's dark.
I've been, uh, since yesterday, cause I had a zoom yesterday and you can
see my movie shelves behind me and see that the middle shelf, uh, that,
that one right there has a lot of, it's a bigger shelf on that area and it's
got a lot of negative space and it's driving me crazy when I see it because
I'm like, it looks like I don't have a collection.
Did you, did it come that way?
Yeah.
And I guess I could just buy extra shelves and just insert them there and
put some more stuff up there, which is what I will do because I'm psychotic
and it has to all look packed to the brim.
But I don't think you put that shelf in the middle.
I don't think it's going to be exactly spaced out.
Right.
No, then some are going to have to go flat.
Yeah.
Now my friend told me you should, he goes, just put little like statue,
statue things on top of the DVDs.
They're figurines or something.
It's an idiot.
It doesn't get it.
Interior design.
That'd be a funny, uh, that's, that's funny.
That's a funny something like the interior designer that focuses
only on collectibles and knickknacks.
Well, what I would do is I'd have a wall of knickknacks here and the person's
like, I don't, what do you, I don't know what, what kind of couch should I get?
Precious moments.
Um, yeah, I think that would be a very funny sketch.
I know an interior deck, or how about an OCD interior designer who just gets
swept up and like things being slightly askew.
Like that's what I do is I'll rearrange after my cleaning dude is here, I'll
rearrange a picture for like 25 minutes.
Yeah.
I think that's very funny.
And the, and the couple that she's doing it, he or she's doing the designing for
is obviously they're not OCD, right?
Cause there's the other way you could do it where it's like, it's a person for
OCD people who also has the OCD.
But I think it's funnier the other way.
I do too.
That's why I pitched it that way.
What's going on with you, Pat?
What's happening in your neck of the neck of the, um, not a lot.
I'm, uh, doing pretty well.
I'm in a period of sobriety.
I'm in a period of non -dating.
I pulled the apps, just me, it's me in the house.
I get dinner with a friend a couple of times a week, two, three, four,
keep myself occupied, but mostly I'm working on bettering myself, my writing
projects, keeping in the zone, baby.
That's great.
Yeah, but pretty boring life at the moment.
That's why I had no response.
Nothing to say to it.
I think I like this little life.
What, uh, as on tick tock, I'm sure the sleep is better.
The sleep is always better when you cut back on any of the substance.
Sleep is much better.
And then I'm also doing a 45 minute Peloton every day, which puts yo ass to
bed, and then I also, uh, do the big heavy weights, you know, I do what you're
doing, but man style and that's very exhausting as well.
That's weird that you still see gender.
I don't see that.
What, um, what, um,
but to the hotel special, I think, yeah, I think my favorite joke of the whole
thing is he goes, my, uh, my mother, I love my mother.
She's 85 years old.
Everybody that claps is, you don't need to applaud.
She's not trans so hard.
It really did.
It's not appropriate people, but fuck off.
The whole special is amazing.
That, that whole run of jokes about his mom, when he's like, I built her a ramp.
It was time for her to come back inside.
She's been in the yard feral for two years.
Yeah.
It's just, yeah.
I mean, it's 40 minutes, but I wasn't aware.
It's like a padded 40 minutes with that little bit of him playing the
recorder at the end and everything.
And I was kind of like every show.
He does it every show.
Yeah.
Every show he does the recorder.
I didn't realize that he's been doing it since the pandemic.
Like like pandemic shows.
He's been doing that.
He, that's when he started doing it and he kept it.
And I will say it's gotten funnier and funnier when he first started doing it.
I was like, what the fuck is he doing?
Like that's weird.
But now I'm like, Oh, it's really funny.
Yeah.
It's the, it's the first special in quite a while where I wanted more
jokes to come because I thought it was too short, but I did love it.
I loved it.
I always thought his best capture, the best capture of David Tell was, uh,
his, his half hour comedy central presents, um, which is, you know,
with commercials is like 22 minutes, but I felt like it just was so rapid fire.
And I felt like this is what it's like seeing him in a club.
Like when he goes up as part of a showcase in New York or whatever,
there's just no room for anything else.
It's just him with a barrage of jokes.
And then he did that road work special, which was really funny, but it had a
little bit of a hook to it because it was like jumping around to different
clubs and whatever, but it was still good.
Yeah.
This one I liked, I actually liked that it was only 40 minutes.
I liked that it was like, it captured him where I was like, this
feels like you're seeing him live.
People are yelling shit and he's like turning to the camera and yelling
things into camera and like, he's riffing and like, and it's so concentrated
that like the 25 minute mark, I was like, I was like, I guess it's near the end.
And I was like, no, holy shit.
There's still another 15 minutes.
It is a, it is a, it is a nitro.
What is that stuff called?
Cold nitro brew, whatever the fuck.
It's like that.
Yeah.
I mean, at a time where you're hard pressed to locate a punch line
in a comedy special, it had like, you know, eight jokes a minute.
Just dumping out of them.
It was great.
Which brings me to, yeah, I think I know where you're going.
I'm friendly.
I'm friendly with both of these guys.
One of them, I think would actually say is my friend, but I'll talk, they
ain't never, they ain't ever going to hear this, this Gerard Carmichael
heavy quotes reality show.
The fact that he, I guess he's doing an Andy Kaufman thing, but the
fact that he's
I don't think so, man.
I mean, when I, I don't reach out to you with the severity I did or, or a
failed Andy Kaufman type thing.
I thought that was, uh, insanity.
Okay.
So you don't think you, you don't think it's scripted reality that
he's passing off as reality.
That's what I think.
Well, there's an element of that, but I think like he's there with people.
He's just fucked.
And yes, they could be actors, but what it feels like to me is that they are
people who agreed to show their face after they fucked Gerard Carmichael.
Um, the scene where he's asking out Tyler, the creator who has already told
him, I'm not interested in you reads as really weird behavior, um, but genuine
behavior didn't read like acting to me.
It read like Tyler, the creator was super uncomfortable doing it on camera.
Said I've already given you the answer, which is no.
And, um, I don't know.
I don't, we, I'm sorry.
I saw poor things.
I don't think Gerard's that good an actor that he can pull off that show.
Sorry.
I, uh, I felt like with this, I felt like it was, he was like, we're
going to shoot it like a reality show.
It is going to be based on things that are happening.
I am going to blur the lines with people coming in that I actually know.
Like, I don't think the Tyler thing didn't happen.
Yeah, I think it happened and they probably talked about it.
And then Gerard said, I want to do this as a storyline for this thing.
And then you come back in, we'll, we'll, we'll make it look like a reality show
and let's amp it up a little bit.
You could maybe, and then Tyler's like, what if I said, you're,
you're crazy bitch or whatever.
And then they laugh and they go, okay.
So you think it's, I'm not there.
Yes.
Joaquin Phoenix.
To an extent, but, but the difference is, is I'm not there was supposed to be,
look at Joaquin Phoenix losing his fucking mind.
And this is supposed to be, let's all sing Kumbaya for Gerard and be proud of him.
Um, I'll tell you what, what it's, it's just, it's, it's
the most self -indulgent thing.
Here's the thing.
If you're going to do, if my interpretation is correct,
make it sort of funny or something, dude, like, or entertaining,
there's nothing entertaining about this.
Nobody wants to watch you.
Well, maybe people do, but who the fuck wants to watch a guy sit on stage
pensively in silence, pinching his brow, trying to
his standup.
Now I sent Joe a picture, you know, he's sitting on stage next to his Emmy,
uh, in a white floor length, King style.
Like Liberace coat.
Yeah.
Um, holding a microphone in theory, doing standup, but mostly just like,
I really messed up this week and seconds of silence.
Yeah.
I was talking to this friend.
30 seconds of silence is like, what are you doing?
I'm going to take even farther in the standup sequences on the show.
I don't think there's an audience there.
I think that could be, that could be, you never see the audience.
I think it's fake.
It's all, this is why I cried.
Now here's the thing.
The stupid ass paid off fucking, uh, payola entertainment press in
this fucking country.
None, none of them are writing anything like, is this real?
What's going on here?
They're all just praising Gerard.
Cause it's, it's what you're supposed to do right now is praise Gerard.
Like you, like he's one of the guys you're just supposed to praise.
But here's the thing.
I started to cry bullshit immediately because there's too many
perfect moments caught on camera.
Right.
There's too many perfect clips of him saying the exact right thing with
perfect rhythm, with the perfect amount of dramatic pause, whatever.
There's the scene where he texts Tyler and he does the whole montage
of him writing it, deleting it, writing it, deleting it,
writing it, deleting it.
He finally sends a message.
He then rolls over on the couch in and bunches up in terror of the response.
And then the phone goes ding.
And you see him dramatically roll over in peak and it's the text response.
Give me a fucking break guys.
None of this is happening.
This is all staged.
It's all bullshit.
And quite frankly, could you imagine, by the way, when Rob Schneider put out his,
his fake, you know, like his curb, your enthusiasm, real Rob.
Yeah.
You know what I said?
Boy, Rob Schneider is really coming off like a fucking asshole here.
Yeah.
I get that it's a scripted, like amplified version of himself.
He's making himself look like a fucking asshole because he's rude.
He's self -centered.
He's demeaning Gerard.
I'm going to say the same thing.
You're making yourself look like an asshole.
It's you going these, these twinks, I fuck and what it's like, how is this any
if this was a dude saying this about women and talking about what's the male
grinder or the straight grinder?
I mean, Tinder, Tinder, cheater.
If this was a dude doing this, you'd be like, I mean, not a straight dude.
I mean, not a gay dude about women.
You'd be like, this guy is gross.
This is gross.
And like, because Gerard's doing it and talking about men, by the way, isn't
twink sort of not, isn't that sort of not okay to just, I was, am I wrong?
I thought that was like sort of a demeaning kind of I've asked about that
because of a script I have and apparently twink is fine.
So anyway, it's, it's, I guess so.
Cause bear is fine and whatever.
Right?
So like, my point is, it's just like a guy being like, yeah, these, these fucking
dudes, I fuck and whatever.
And like talking that dismissively about it, I'm like, I don't know guys,
like none of this stuff, I have no problem with us exploring all of it.
I think we should be, I think we should be depicting different lifestyles on camera.
I think it's a good thing.
Uh, and I think it's a needed thing.
And I think it helps people and especially children who feel
marginalized and not seen, it helps.
But, but, but when we do it like this, I'm like, guys, all we're doing is we're
taking, you know, Carlin had that joke about a lot of modern feminists where
he said, if all you're going to do is imitate the worst behaviors of men, I'm
not impressed, you're going to go get a man tailored suit with shoulder pads.
And become corporate and imitate all of the worst behaviors of men.
Like that's what, and that's how I feel about this, where it's just like, all
this feels like to me is, well, straight guys did it, so now I'm going to do it.
It's like, yeah, but it was gross when straight guys did it.
And now it's gross when you're doing it too.
It's not, it's not inviting behavior.
And it doesn't make me feel sorry for you.
It doesn't make me feel, uh, uh, that I want to sit and understand you,
especially when you're showing a storyline of you making a friend of
yours feel fucking uncomfortable.
And because they got clearly Bo Burnham, they're pretending it's a mystery
figure, but it's a six foot seven white guy who talks like Forrest Gump.
It's Bo Burnham and they're good.
They're best friends.
So he comes in and then I'm like, that's the one thing that I thought
might be a joke, a pitched joke.
You have Bo come in, everybody knows how tall he is and how, what he sounds
like, and we pretend he, we don't know who he is.
If that wasn't a joke, then he just thinks we're idiots.
But I did read a couple interviews about the show and he was like, I would
never reveal, uh, who the person behind the mask is.
Who knows?
I think whatever it is, you know, I'm not there was a crazy ride.
It was funny.
It was fun to watch.
Um, this is not that at all.
I don't know if it's real or fake.
Bo Burnham's like, you know, you can't construct these moments.
There's cameras everywhere.
So it's not real.
It's not reality.
So clearly they're playing with that a little bit, but my God, not in some
sort of interesting way, not any more interesting than Vanderpump rules or
any other reality show.
Bo is scripted elements.
Bo is why I thought was the initial moment where I was like, this is fake.
This is the moment in the first episode where they're telling you this is fake.
This is the commentary.
Now, if it's fake, then perhaps some of what I am criticizing it about, like
the, you know, him exhibiting behaviors that gross straight men tend to exhibit.
Um, and by the way, there's nothing wrong with being promiscuous.
Lord knows folks.
I ain't no stranger to it, but it's, it's, it's when you talk about the people
as if they're cattle is when it gets gross and that's the gross part.
Um, but my point is, is if, if it is fake, then maybe Gerard doing that is part of
some sort of overall commentary or whatever, but I immediately started
looking up articles and reviews and I couldn't find anything that suggested.
This is staged, we think.
Um, and then also Bo coming in and doing that.
I'm like, Bo, you did the same.
You put cameras on your, and it was brilliant.
The, the special inside or whatever.
You, you shot yourself.
So why would you be so against this?
Well, but that was clearly a, he was performing written songs and
written material and et cetera, et cetera.
This, you know, is not that.
Well, also too, why would you, why wouldn't you just not appear on it?
I think they thought that would be hilarious because they think that they
are the biggest stars in the world, Bo Burnham and Gerard Carmichael, and
they're like, the second you walk in, everybody will know it's you.
And I think they thought that that would be a big laugh reveal.
Yes.
Cause they're in this world where we are.
And obviously we are, we watched the fucking thing.
We're dying to see if, if they make it to the Emmys in time.
The first episode of your reality show is called Emmys and it's like every,
you know, 10 minutes, five days till Emmys title card appears on the screen.
You know, it's not, it's, it's like everything else.
Now it's not, they don't go far enough for it to be satire.
And if they pushed it a little bit further, this could be brilliant satire.
Um, and it also, as you're saying, does not feel like reality.
It winds up being nothing.
And I feel like most comedy these days is if you're lucky, interesting,
it's not making you laugh.
Uh, and that's been a real bummer to me.
And I think the cause of a lot of my bad mood over the last five years is I
don't have reliable sources of laughter.
You know, that brings me to.
And this is the guy where I'm like, I think he would say we were friends.
I've known him since he was 15 years old.
So I didn't see this one.
So, but Rami, oh yeah.
Hey, yeah.
Let me use steps.
I like Rami.
And I think I'll say that you've talked about the Drew Michael.
And I finally put that on and like, there's, there's this run of specials
on HBO max where the, the picture is the most serious thing you've ever seen.
It's not even the comic smiling or raging or something.
It's always the comic like, you know, looking pensively and the, you know,
very muted colors, you would never know it was a comedy special.
And I think that comedians are somehow getting ashamed that they're comedians
and thinking they have to win Emmys and be fucking Nana Gatsby, Hannah Gatsby.
Well, she's the one that, that she was the catalyst for all this, I think.
I mean, it was, they think, oh, we can be, we can be truth tellers.
We can be part of the public conversation.
We can be this, that, that you can do all that folks and be funny.
Let me tell you what you really can.
Let me tell you, here's what, here's my take on it.
I hear what you're saying, but here, and I don't disagree, but here,
my take on it is this ethics are a commodity.
Morality is a commodity.
It not only will get you views, it will sell tickets for you.
It will get you jobs.
It has been proven.
It is, you will sit in a job interview in Hollywood and they will ask you about
your Twitter feed and all these things.
And if you've had a questionable tweet or whatever, you will be cast aside
and canceled and, and, and you might most likely be able to come back.
But the point is, is ethics are an economy period.
It's, it is absolute fact.
And, um, comedians and I'm speaking generally, obviously are the most lowly
bacteria on planet fucking earth.
I come from a breed of people that disgust me in ways I can't even explain.
They are the most self -centered, self -serving, fucking childish,
fucking babies that have ever lived.
So when the baby sees what's shiny, the baby wants it.
And now I'm not surprised at all that you've got a gaggle of fucking baby
people going out and doing all this stuff to try to make it look like, not
how funny I am, but how good I am.
Now, the other side of this are the guys that go completely hardcore, you know,
in the, in the like, you know, Tucker Carlson, whatever the fuck you want to
call it, and I don't like that either.
Okay.
I hate all of it.
There are so few people that are just kind of going, I'm just going to kind
of be over here doing my thing because that's kind of what we were supposed to
do as comics, hence why the Attell special is so great and, and, um, I mean,
this Rami thing, he, I like Rami.
He's a nice kid, but like, Jesus Christ, it opens with a tight, and God bless his
opener, I'm not knocking this guy, but his opener is a disabled person.
Um, and Rami opens with a guy from Rami's show and the, it's probably, I
don't know, I think he's like small, skinny.
Yeah.
I open to the show and I think that's the funny character on his show.
It opened with a super tight closeup on that guy, doing a joke about how, you
know, they said he would die at 16, but he, here he is now at 33 and the
audience is cheering and is that a beautiful thing?
Absolutely.
Is, am I happy for that guy?
Is it great to see him doing his thing?
Absolutely.
Would I like to see him get a special?
But I'm sorry, Rami putting that as the cold open of his own special is the,
the most arguable, uh, and potentially criticize -able, if that's a word, virtue
signal ever committed to tape.
It's Rami, what are you doing?
And then the guy is closing with a joke about how he re and where he references
Rami and then Rami comes out and starts his set with all proceeds tonight
are going to Gaza, not come off.
It's like, Rami, what are we doing here, dude?
What are we doing here?
Then he goes into this thing about like, I do what I can for charity, but I
have, I have never in my life and I've watched a billion comedy specials,
someone say the proceeds from tonight are going to some charitable cause.
Maybe they said it off camera, but I have never seen a comedian
drop that into their scent.
Huge applause.
Of course.
Right.
Then he says, then he goes, I can't, the audience feels like they're
heroes now, even though they just went to see a comedy show and didn't
know where their money was going.
Now they feel like heroes.
The audience is predominantly, uh, Arab people.
So, so, so, which was interesting.
I've never seen that and I'm Arab.
Uh, but, uh, um, but, but then he says, see, now here's the thing.
You could give up everything I just said, right?
Everything I just said that I'm criticizing.
You could absolutely go, Joe, you're being too cynical.
Da da da da da.
Here's the counterpoint.
And you could absolutely be right.
Here's the nail in the coffin though.
This is the part where you go, this is suspect.
He then tells a story about how, you know, he does what he can for charity.
He can't do everything, which is, you know, humble bragging, whatever.
And then he tells a story about how Taylor Swift came to one of his shows.
And then his friend texted him after the show that Taylor
Swift came to see him at.
Not, she just happened to be there.
She came to see him.
Um, did you convert her?
And Rami's like, I got to be responsible for everybody.
This is okay.
No way.
First of all, that never happened.
The friend texting you never happened.
The Taylor part happened.
Who are you responsible for?
Rami, what the hell are you talking about?
This is what I'm saying.
It's like the superhero thing that everybody's doing.
Yeah.
And it's like, it's that whole crew of comments.
That whole crew, it's like, look at me, love me, but for reasons
other than my comedy, nobody, forgive me.
I haven't seen the special.
Nobody's saying it reminds me of that great Rami joke.
I will say his show is great.
So I like the people love his show.
It's a very good show.
And he is a funny kid.
There's jokes in the special where I was like, Oh, that's funny.
Yeah.
But it's so goddamn buried under whatever else.
And you know, this, but like, and by the way, to maybe protect us both, we're
saying we don't care for this style of comedy, obviously billions do.
I think those millions are dumb.
Kind of agree.
Joe kind of agree.
I mean, I'll never even push play on that.
What's it called?
Like hard feelings or something.
What more feelings or feelings then, you know, a comedian who I, who I
respect more certainly, but what's going on with Neil Brennan?
What happened?
What, what'd he do?
Now the ending of his last special, uh, I had to have a bucket in front of me
to watch where he sits down and is like, I think when I really look into my soul,
but, um, this new one is called crazy good.
Neil, now Neil is a friend.
Neil, what are you doing?
You can call a special anything.
Why are you calling it crazy good?
And maybe it's that I struggle so much with self -confidence at times.
I'm doing a lot of things to improve self -talk in the mirror and shit.
Like I'm in a full on midlife crisis.
Um, but you can't, can meet a comedian who's calling themself great is not
unless you're Steve Martin, who I'll get to in the movie corner coming out.
And that's your thing.
I'm a pompous character.
Um, God, it's so weird to me.
They, they really are like, we're America's heroes now.
And God, it's gross.
It's also, also to Neil does a lot of self, you know, who put up a clip from
his podcast of Jay Leno being like, you're just brilliant, you're brilliant.
You know, and that's the clip.
You're like, cheese.
Okay.
Yeah.
So there you go.
Right.
So like, but here's the thing.
Anything from this hour, I don't like Jay Leno, but it's an hour and a half
long interview with his legend.
You can pick any clip you want.
And the clip he picks is, you're one of the greatest comedic minds I've ever seen.
You're absolutely brilliant.
Jay Leno says nothing funny, but Neil says nothing funny on the clip.
It's like interesting choice.
Neil doesn't even go, I'm humbled or stop or he's nodding.
Like, yeah, go on.
Now, if Todd Barry called his special crazy good, it would be awesome.
Cause you'd go, he's being ironic.
Yeah.
I think the Todd Barry special that I know is called spicy honey.
Spicy honey.
And that's what a comedy special should be called.
He's got one called super crazy.
Like, you know, like it would be funny if he called it crazy good, you'd be like,
oh, he's being a shit.
That's funny.
Yeah.
Like, um, I don't know why Neil is...
Did you agree that that was crazy good?
Did you all have a crazy good time tonight?
I mean, I'll, I'll tell you, I've not seen the Neil thing.
I'll watch it at some point.
But I watched it too, cause I respect him.
But I mean, come on.
I thought the Sandler special was very funny.
I had a real problem with it being called a hundred percent fresh.
Fuck off Adam.
Yeah.
Fuck off.
However, he was doing that because his movies get such terrible reviews.
Oh, okay.
All right.
And that, that special is a great example.
That special I watched twice, which I can't even recall doing.
Um, and it was so exhilarating for me because of just how silly it was.
A silly comedy is gone.
I just saw the work.
We're getting real close to a Liam Neeson naked gun.
Ladies and gentlemen, I, I am in possession of the screenplay, Joe,
if you want to read it.
How is it?
I haven't looked at it yet.
I'm scared, but I'm pumped.
A silly comedy is what we need.
I stumbled into 10 minutes of high school high the other night.
I had tears in my eyes laughing with John Lovitz just cause it was funny.
I'm like, yes, funny.
I put on, you have to have desperate.
I put on the live action fat Albert the other day.
I was like, maybe there's some funny stuff in this.
It's Keenan.
It's not, there's nothing funny in it, but, uh, I couldn't get through it,
but it's a kid's movie though.
But, um, I legendary story on the set of a fat Albert Bill Cosby, obviously
producing it and Keenan standing there in the full fat Albert suit and everything.
And, uh, they're getting ready to do a take and Cosby comes up to him,
leans over and he goes, you know, so, and all the pussy you're about to get.
You're going to need a second Dick.
And tells the story of course with, I mean, Keenan is one of the funniest
people alive, but he tells a story where he like turns the look at Cosby,
like excuse me, they're surrounded by children.
You know, anyways, God, there were signs, there were signs.
Yeah.
The, uh, the, the Liam Neeson casting, by the way, as odd as it is, makes
perfect sense because two, for two reasons.
Number one, I always said, if they're going to, they originally were going
to remake the naked gun with Ed Helms.
I like Ed Helms, but I said, that's stupid.
You don't do it with a comedian.
You do it with a straight actor, which is what they did, which is why the original
works, um, and Liam Neeson has proven to us he can be deathly funny while
being completely dry that, that whole thing on the Steven, the Warwick Davis
show, when he's doing the, like, I have AIDS or whatever, it's so fucking funny.
And I'm like,
he also did a particular, probably the most insane celebrity cameo I have ever
seen on the last season of Atlanta, Donald Glover's show, which I, as another
brilliant show, but Liam Neeson playing himself runs into, I think Donald Glover
in a bar, the details are a little sketchy to me, but they're talking about
that incident when Liam Neeson was on morning television and he said his
female friend got raped by a black man.
And he said, I was just walking the streets with a bat looking
for any black man to beat.
Yeah.
And he said this on the news five years ago.
So he came on and did a cameo on, you know, Atlanta where he's like making fun of
that sort of, I'm sure his publicist begged him not to do it, but it was really,
really well done and he was really funny in it.
That's why I hope for the best.
However, when Liam Neeson does an interview, there's no twinkle in his eye.
There's no, you don't see the comedy lurking below the surface.
You do with Leslie Nielsen and you always did.
Well, I wonder if you saw it though, before, um, yeah, it's hard to say.
Cause I saw naked gun when I was eight.
So I didn't see him before that.
Yeah.
I mean, my God, I have a lot of Leslie Nielsen here and there in my movies
behind me here.
And I mean, you know, he, he didn't, he, he barely even played a likable person,
let alone a funny part.
Like, you know, there's an episode of one of the best episodes of night gallery is
where he goes, it's like, it's funny.
He still has full white hair.
He's probably 32 or something.
He looks like he's 70 the whole time and he's like bullying grown men in a bar.
And he's like, you're a little sissy and you make me sick.
And the, and the premise is, is that he, he gets bet $10 ,000 or something to
spend the night in a haunted house.
And he's like, that's kid stuff or whatever, you know, it's a great episode.
Easy peasy lemon squeezy.
But I mean, yeah, I think he's got an eye patch in it.
He's such a prick.
Like, you know, so it's so weird.
Even if you watch police squad, the series, he's, you should, he's not
likable as driven yet he becomes likable and naked gun and police squad.
He plays it very much like almost like a dirty cop.
That's true.
Like when he's doing his rants and like ignoring the needs of whoever, like
suspect or whatever, like victim he's interviewing or whatever, it, it
definitely doesn't, it comes off less bumbling and more like, I truly don't
care about your husband being dead and on the show.
Yeah.
Um, anyway, let's get to that corner because we've been really yamming it up here.
I kind of exhausted all of mine already.
I think those were what I was going to talk about.
I had to puke it all out.
I couldn't wait, but it's fine.
Hit us with a couple and we're moving along here.
Um, since we're talking standup comedy and somebody who went prematurely gray,
uh, I gotta shout out the new two part three hour plus Steve Martin documentary,
Steve, a documentary in two parts.
Um, Steve Martin from when I was a kid, you know, like really for me, it was Steve
Martin and John Candy, the, the buildup, the begging of my father to let me see
plans, trans and automobiles is probably what made it one of my favorites because
I needed to see it, but it was rated R and it was a battle, but he was my
favorite when I was a kid, I was obsessed.
I've seen all his movies a billion times.
I was obsessed with the standup, the SNL, the specials, everything, everything
I can get my hands on.
And it was great.
The first half of this is his rise from a kid with no real talent who just knew
he wanted to be in the show business who becomes the, by the end of the first
part, the biggest stamp comedian in the world.
They say the biggest of all time.
I think that's debatable, but certainly up to that point, there had been no
bigger standup and then he walked away and then went into a movie career and
he's never done standup again.
Great story told about as perfectly as it could be by Steve Martin himself in
his book, Born Standing Up, one of the great memoirs, one of the great
autobiographies, one of the great comedy books.
So it's really familiar ground because I've read that book twice and yeah,
good to see it all.
Good to see some clips, but as is the case, even with the great standups,
Carlin, even Albert Brooks, Albert Brooks usually brought the funny no
matter what, but some of this stuff is dated, you know, like you watch it and
you're like, I can't even fathom people finding this funny.
It's 50 years old.
But if you're a comedy enthusiast, you know, it's a great, great
documentary about him and about really the nature of standup itself and how
he flipped it on its head.
Then part two is where the water works come part two is where the emotion comes
in part two meant so much to me because Steve Martin is like, I was closed
off emotionally.
I was an asshole.
I was impossible to date until I was about 65, 70 years old.
And he goes, so he's like, I had a kid.
Um, he, you see an eight year old girl come in and give him a big hug while
he's getting interviewed for the documentary today at age 75.
And when the girl leaves the room, he's got tears in his eyes.
He's like just her coming in to give him a hug.
It makes him cry, which of course makes me cry.
You can't fathom Steve Martin crying.
He's, um, he's just had a kid now, like 10 years ago.
Yeah.
So that gives me hope that's and his wife, um, I wouldn't say this to his
face, but I think he fell in love with Tina Fey when they were acting together.
I've seen clips of them and he's like smitten and he married a woman who
looks identical to Tina Fey.
Now you wouldn't, you wouldn't bring this up to Steve when you guys have lunch?
No, not, not, wouldn't be the first words out of my mind.
You know, your wife looks a lot like, um, sure.
Well, try to hold it back when you meet up with him.
There, there's a clip of this.
He's in his room with all his old scripts and he's got them all bound
in his library and he pulls out plants, trains, and he talks about how John
Candy had a monologue at the end when he goes, Hey, what are you still
doing at the train station?
And in the movie, he goes, I don't have a wife.
I haven't been home in years, but it was a monologue, a full length, like
and Steve Martin goes, I wasn't even in the shot.
I was just supposed to be there listening to him.
And he goes, I was sobbing.
I, I was completely sobbing.
Of course I didn't know he was going to pass or anything, but it was some of
the best acting I've ever seen.
I was blown away by it.
And then he goes, and it was cut from the movie, which really bothered me
because I thought it was his best performance, but he's reading the
monologue, he goes, I can read it to you here, what the original script said.
And he's reading the script, starts crying.
And he's like remembering John Candy doing it.
And he's like, he was my friend.
He really was, he was a beautiful man and all that.
There's so many moments that really got to me, but the most beautiful thing for
me as a guy who kind of struggles with life is to see him 75 years old daughter,
who's his entire world, uh, wife, who he loves, and he's sitting at the kitchen
table with Marty short, his wife, and they're playing like Uno, they're
cards together.
They're, they're Marty shorts riffing on them, you know, making fun of them,
being an old wash up, uh, having two young, a wife, whatever they're cracking
each other up and it's a beautiful thing.
You know, he really says I structured my life completely wrong.
I couldn't do anything but work until way too late, but I'm getting my life now.
It's a beautiful, beautiful, great documentary.
I urge you to check it out.
Great.
Yes, I will.
Okay.
Uh, I got Apple TV.
I got to save mine for the next round, but I mean, we've talked so much for
the next episode or I won't have any people because I talked to, I blurted
it all mine out, I was going to do a tell Gerard and Rami, but I will, I will just
to, this one was one I wasn't going to do, but I I'll talk about it briefly.
Uh, I watched some of the dark side of comedy series on vice.
Vice is so divisive, no pun intended.
It's just,
is that a new special?
Yeah.
It came out like 2020 or something.
Okay.
So series, but, uh, I watched the dice episode cause I was very curious and
I thought like dice flies dice fights.
Yeah.
I was like, well, this is cool.
They'll get into it.
Cause I saw the Farley one and I thought the Farley one was kind of
exploitative and you know, the fact that none of his family participated
said a lot to me, but, um, but I thought, well, let me watch the dice one.
Cause the dice one, it'd be interesting to, to learn about like, what was it
like, like when everything crashed for him, you know, like what was that fall?
And all they did in this thing and it's a good show.
It's well -made Dave Foley narrates it.
And they were interviewing Scott Thompson from kids in the hall and
some other interesting people, uh, Mike by Mike, uh, binder got interviewed
binder and George Lopez, I'm sorry, binder and Paul Rodriguez.
And, um, I don't know, there were, there were a couple of comics that
were friends of dice that nice things to say, and then there were people
like Scott Thompson and whatever that didn't know him, but we're like, you
know, I was not a fan and, and I felt that he was very bad for minorities
and gay people and whatnot.
Uh, and, and they did get into like how, you know, uh, there was a fervor
at that time in the country, uh, you know, that, that, that, you know,
and the dissection of when is it just jokes and when do jokes start to become
like the mouthpiece now for like this group of people cheering for all the
wrong reasons, which I can relate to.
I've talked to other comics about that where, where, where any of us have said,
you know, I think I'm going to get rid of that one joke because they're laughing
for the wrong reason.
So I'm aware of that.
And they did say about that a lot.
It's part of the reason you went to Africa.
Yeah.
And they did say, you know, you gotta, you gotta take an inventory on yourself
and know when it's going too far or whatever.
And that was the main criticism of dice was that it went too far
and he didn't check it.
Sure.
Which whether you think that or not, I think it's a fair take
and a fair discussion to have.
What would bug me about the show though, was it then only became that.
Yeah.
And all it became about was he has yet to apologize for the potential damage
he did then and what, and all this.
And it's like, guys, this is supposed to be a documentary about the
rise and fall of a comedian.
Yeah.
So I watched the Brett Butler one, the Brett Butler one, which she interviewed
for, he probably said no to the interview.
And then I think when you say no, they go, okay, well, now we're
going to, you know, tell it the way we feel like telling it.
Yeah.
But the Brett Butler one, she interviewed for, and Brett Butler, who
was very, very well liked in the business.
But also too is renowned for having, you know, you know, it was never a secret
that she was difficult to, you know, and had problems, whatever.
And she talks about all that and they approach it like that.
They don't approach it like, but Brett, why did you know?
So it just kind of bothered me with the dice one.
I think it was a little bit.
The final product of that episode was a little bit of a byproduct of the period
and the national discussion of what was going on with sexism and all that stuff
and, and abuse and assaults and all that.
And I think it could have been a better telling of him.
It could have had all that criticism in there, but there could have been another
side of it where, you know, we saw a broader discussion, but.
You know, again, it's just, it's, it's a magazine show, man.
It's, it's about even with the Brett Butler room, with her participating,
it focuses so fucking hard on her alcoholism.
Yeah.
And you're like, guys, you're reducing this to a doc.
This is now, this is now an episode of a docu -series about alcoholism.
Right.
Why are we not just talking about, you know, her comp more completely and not
what, you know, they, they called me and asked me to do the Opie and Anthony one.
I said, no.
Yeah.
And I said, and I did, I went as far as the pre -interview and I said, uh, I'm
going to tell you, I, and I said it this bluntly, I go, I'm going to tell you
right fucking now, don't ask me to do this.
If it's going to be, you're expecting me to apologize for things that Anthony or
whoever has said, I'm not doing that.
So if you want to talk about like what it was like to be a part of the show and
the fun we had, and I'll even talk to you about how it all kind of fell apart, but
do not fucking expect me to be here and be responsible for things other people
said, because there's a lot of people pissed off at things.
A lot of people said on the show over the year and they were like, no, no, no,
no, we would never, yeah.
Yeah.
Right.
But, uh, probably best not to be associated with it.
Yeah.
Anyway.
All right.
That's my corn.
That's all I got.
Uh, I rewatched the movie waiting.
You ever see waiting?
I am a fan of that movie, boy.
Have times changed.
Boy, they sure have.
I lately get a real kick out of watching comedies from like the early
2000s, mid 2000s, because even the PG 13 ones are shocking.
They, you know, they would never be made today.
The rampant misogyny, sexism, all that stuff.
I haven't revisited American pie, but like they talk about how, when you watch
this movie now that everyone loved and thought was hilarious there, the scene
where our hero sends out a naked video of a foreign exchange student to everyone
in school without her consent doesn't play as gangbusters as it did back in 99.
So waiting right off the, it's Ryan Reynolds.
And I think this is, I always liked him on two girls, a guy and a pizza place,
but he's really funny in this.
Like it's easy to forget with him becoming a king of America that he's was very
funny and I hope we'll get back to that again, but, um, his character in this is
the older guy who works at, uh, you know, it's like a TGI Fridays type restaurant.
And the receptionist, the girl who checks you in is, uh, 16.
And that's a running bit storyline throughout the movie that Ryan Reynolds
is dying to fuck her and waiting for her to turn 17.
And by the way, by the way, not just that, but absolutely that's, that is
a, is a primary joke and a point of discussion.
They don't even shine a light on the fact that all of them are bringing the 16
year old to their after party that they have it at, uh, Justin Long's apartment
every night and she just gets shit faced.
Yeah.
Like miners go get shit faced with it.
It is a, it was a different, and I re I saw that movie in the fucking theater.
And I remember watching it and being like, Oh, this is really funny.
Like there wasn't even a moment where I was like, wait, is that, that's not
the same thing.
And like the other running gag is that they're, they're all trying to show
their dicks to the other workers, you know, while they're at work and, you
know, it's got a lot of the movies of this time, I used to laugh sometimes
with the gross out, um, when I worked at a theater, I would go in and watch, you
know, the cum scene and something about Mary with an audience, just because the
audiences would go so nuts and it was fun.
But then we got to this point of like Tom cats with Jerry O 'Connell and these
kind of movies where it's like even Van Wilder with Ryan Reynolds.
Like, I remember a scene where the bad guys are eating like a hundred donuts
that are full of dog come and they're like zooming in on the mouths as they
open and close and the come stick into the teeth.
And I'm like, guys, like I'm the audience for this.
I don't want this.
It just, at some point it started going further and further to gross out.
And now there's no gross out comedy for the most part.
But, um, the movie is definitely a document of its time.
It's got a great cast.
Justin Long and a Ferris, David Kechner, John France, daily, just a
bunch of great people in it.
Louise goes mom.
Keck and it's Dane, Dane Cook, Dane Cook's like first movie.
Yeah.
Uh, Andy Mellon, knock it.
They're all Perl and knock us.
They're all a J and silent Bob rip off, but they're pretty funny.
They're all perfect in it.
Everybody like they just, they, they, I worked in restaurants like though I
worked at an Applebee's at one point, like it's like, this is pitch fucking
perfect.
The lady who, she's the same lady that played on a lot of Ubach.
Yeah.
That she played the crack head on Frank's pretty woman episode.
It was always sunny.
She, she is the like 30 year old waitress that's been there too long.
Like she's fucking perfect.
Everybody is so good in that thing, man.
Like it's.
Yeah.
I never did food service and I just would go pick up my friend on Friday and
Saturday nights and hang out there with them while I'd close up and stuff.
And it, it feels like an exact, like somebody who definitely did the job and
knows it inside and out.
Critics don't look at that though.
Like they look at it in drama.
Yes.
How the re the gritty realism of it, but they don't talk about that in
comedies, like waiting in office space and movies like that.
They really feel like what they are parodying and that's not easy to do.
Like it, like if somebody who's worked there goes, yeah, this feels real.
Then they did their work.
I think waiting is a, not a masterpiece, but underrated little comedy.
It's funny.
Much like just friends with Ryan Reynolds.
Another point I like just friends, you know, it's depressing is I like just
married too, with a culture Murphy, the, you know, what's depressing is, um, in
the sequel, the, the straight to video sequel, uh, starring what's his name
from all the Christopher guest movies.
Michael, uh, John Michael Higgins, um, uh, uh, long Justin Long has a cameo
in it where he comes back to the restaurant and, and you learn that he's
become like a regional manager and never chased the dream.
He never, like the big triumph triumph of his character at the end of the
brand finally leaving and he's going to go do the right thing for himself.
They just, they, they ruined the character, like Luke Skywalker style.
Where you're like, what did you do?
This guy was like a hero.
Yeah.
But I, I'm sure they were like, dude, please, cause he was hot at that time.
Like that was, you know, anyway.
All right.
Well, let's get on to the movie at hand, which thankfully I don't have really
anything to say about it because we're almost wrapped up with our time, but, um,
Spaceman Joe, I mean, I saw this a month ago at this point.
I'd be hard pressed to tell you what it's even about.
Um, Adam Sandler portrays an astronaut.
He is called in to investigate a mysterious cloud of dust and particles in space.
He is lonely.
He misses his wife played by Carrie Mulligan back home.
And there's, there, you know, on the outs and he befriends a spider, giant
spider, um, named Hanus, anus with an H.
Voiced by Paul Dano.
And then the spider looks into Adam Sandler's memories and helps him.
I provide insight.
Yeah, this is so, yeah, yeah, the spider, you're not sure.
So Sandler is alone on the ship.
Yeah, they, they, they highlight that he's been up there alone
for probably a little too long.
He's very much like, I, I'm fine.
I'm fine.
I have to finish this mission.
And then suddenly he starts seeing this giant spider and you're assuming this
is probably all in his head.
Um, and the spider of course provides insights into how, despite being in the
vastness of space and on a grand mission to define all of the galaxy, uh,
Sandler's true journey is within and needs to find himself.
That's basically what the premise of this is.
This movie has been made countless times over and over and over again.
They did it with, starting with 2001.
I'm sure there were movies before that that kind of explored.
Solaris and the remake of Solaris.
And yeah, yeah, uh, there's, there's definitely a lot of moon,
Sam Rockwell's moon in this, um, uh, interstellar, uh, contact.
The list goes on and on.
You know, with one crucial difference.
Those movies were good.
Some of them.
Yeah, this, I think, let me see here.
This movie is pretty old.
Oh no, it's not as old as I thought it was.
I thought that they hadn't released it for a while, but they definitely held
it on the shelf for like two, three years.
And you see why.
I mean, when a Sandler Carey Mulligan movie gets dumped on Netflix, like in
the middle of Oscar season, something is amiss clearly like I, again, with
Netflix being this thing that everyone in the world has in their home, I have
yet to encounter a single other human being who has even heard of Spaceman.
Uh, and it stars huge stars.
It is a very, very boring movie.
It is a very trite movie.
The dialogue is fucking painful, painful.
The, uh, it's just the dial it's so, I wish I could find, hold on.
Let me, let me, I actually wrote down, uh, some of the quotes.
Give me, give me one second here.
Um, Sam was usually really good at this picking one for him uncut gems, et cetera.
And then picking two or three for the masses, but you know, his
picker is off here for sure.
I don't know if it was just like Netflix had him in a deal.
And we're like, look, we need you to do this, but I can't imagine somebody
reading this script and being like, oh, this is great, unless it's Sandler
going, oh, I never played an astronaut.
Like that may be the only appeal.
Okay.
So, uh, me and Pinkstone, we're going back and forth about this.
Uh, uh, all you can see, this is one of the lines because his wife's gripe
with him is, is all, you know, is your work.
You don't know how to be a human.
You don't know how to whatever.
Right.
The spider actually says at one point, all you can see is yourself.
By the way, by the way, I'm done with Paul Dano.
I'm done.
Get out of here.
I've had enough of the same.
I kind of feel the same.
I'm done.
I've had enough.
He's one of these actors that is so proud of the work and he's, and he's so
obviously proud of the work as he's doing the work.
It became evident in the Batman.
It's, it's, it's just so fucking annoying, man.
Like, uh, the most important discoveries are within, but sometimes
they are the farthest to reach that.
I don't know if that's a real line or if Jim made that up either way, the
lines are that fucking stupid.
And it's all Dano going, the discoveries are within the most important thing.
A big spider, like at the end of it.
Well, don't you get it, Pat?
Spiders have a lot of eyes.
They can see everything.
That's probably as much thought as went into that choice.
How about the fact that he repeatedly says to him skinny, he calls Adam Sandler
skinny human repeatedly, and you're like, well, this was clearly a detail in the
book and you didn't get a skinny actor.
You got a normal size actor and you would never go out of your way to refer
to Adam Sandler as skinny.
No.
You just also like he has other movies where everyone in the movie is
calling him fat, like his comedies.
They're all like, Hey fat ass.
It happens all the time in his movie.
Um, written by Colby day, who I've never heard of, has no other credits and
directed by one of the people who directed Chernobyl, um, and Chernobyl
was great, but there's no real layer to this.
I mean, I don't have anything that I could really praise here.
It was really hard to even pay attention.
That's how dull it was.
And, and I just didn't like it.
Um, yeah, it sucked.
It sucked.
I fucking hated it.
Um, I, I, I found it indulgent.
I found it self -serving.
Uh, I found it stupid.
Um, I found the details.
It was also one of these movies too, where the details they have, they're
details are an aspects of the film that don't, that don't make any sense.
And it's because they're there for symbolism because they can't get out of
the way of the fucking symbolism in this thing.
So there's a scene where he's on like a video call with his wife, Karen, poor
Carrie Mulligan, by the way, who's been reduced now to only playing the sobbing
wife that, that wife back home crying while the men are out in space or whatever.
That is the most thankless role in American movies.
That was the, how every woman got a supporting actress
nomination in the nineties, which is sad.
Catherine Quinlan and Apollo 13 going like, just hope he makes it home.
Okay.
It's, it's, you know, and this is like what she's been, you know, I thought
she was very good in maestro, but it's like, yeah, stop making her play like
this sobbing wife that, you know, while the guy that's a role that's truly no
better fleshed out than any of the love interests in the big Sandler comedies
back then, the same exact level of, of a painting of a character.
So, so she's, there's a, there's a part where they're on like a video call.
Yeah.
Any parts.
And he has to hang up, even though she's talking to him about how I think she
lost the baby or something.
Yeah.
And he's like, he's, he's cooking eggs and then his eggs catch on fire.
He's like, I gotta, I gotta go.
I gotta put out the fire.
It's like the eggs clearly representing the eggs, whatever.
Even the spider says when the spider comes in, I have, I've always
wanted you to taste your human eggs.
The symbolism is so, it's so heavy handed.
You know, like guys, eggs don't catch on fire like that.
It's never happened.
Yeah.
It's like, but, but they have to make the food eggs because they got to tie it
all together, her eggs and whatever.
There's a lot of that kind of shit in the movie where you're just like, this
is just really fucking dumb.
By the way, we're living.
What's this?
Now he's making baby carrots.
Interesting.
Yeah, it was, it was stupid.
We're also dealing with some alternate modern time or some near future version
of, of the world we live in where immediate, like, like not instantaneous,
but like very, very fast space travel is possible.
Like, like he's far enough out that it's like, no, you would, this would take you
years to go out that far and come back.
But so clearly, and they're talking just like, no, you could be home
in like a week or whatever.
So I'm like, okay, clearly we're dealing with a reality where technology
has advanced to that point that you can, you know, travel that quickly through
space, but then when his video phone doesn't work, they show him getting
on a landline on this.
I'm like, it's that kind of shit where I'm just like, guys, I don't know.
This, this is just the, these details aren't very consistent.
And then of course, at the end of the movie, I thought the floating phone
booth in space was a weird choice as well.
Him, the spider having a quarter on him.
Of course it flips it to him.
Yeah.
Um, and then, you know, and then of course everything goes wrong.
Sandler has to, the spider gets stuck outside of the ship.
Sandler gets outside of the ship to save the spider.
They're like, you don't go out there.
You'll die.
Sandler doesn't care.
He goes to save the spider and in saving the spider, he dies, but
in dying, he regains his humanity.
Oh, oh, oh, who gives a shit.
My hog is a way down on spaceman.
No gravity in my heart.
No full gravity of my hog for spaceman.
Yeah.
It's, uh, it's just a bad fucking movie.
It's as generic as its title.
Uh, don't watch it would be my recommendation.
We will be back with, uh, Roadhouse, the remake and we will see you next time.
My name is Patrick Walsh, uh, the Patrick Walsh on Instagram and we're
on see you in hell pod at Instagram.
Uh, Joe DeRosa got live dates coming up.
Please come see me.
Uh, go to joderosa .com for tickets and show info.
April 12th town, crier cafe and beacon, New York, April 19th, Wilmington,
Delaware, the queen, uh, May 3rd, Hamden, Connecticut space ballroom, May 25th,
Newport, Rhode Island, Jane Pickens theater.
And if you're in New York, come on through to Joey roses, seven days a week,
sandwiches and drinks.
It's always a good time.
Joey roses .com.
See you next time, folks.
See you in hell.