I'll see you at the podcast you turn to when you need to get that dirty
dirty dirt on the latest dishy, dishy dishes coming out of the Hollywood. What he would you call the
landscape industry? You could call it the industry landscape doesn't make sense, but that's also
you're also not really telling them what the podcast is. You're lying to me. We review movies. Yeah,
that's bad. That's that's that's that's that's that's that sounds so boring, you know, it's well,
but but anyone here knows that we bring so much more to the table. That's that is true. Speaking
of movie reviewers who aren't boring, I sent Pat this week, let's let's revisit quickly a segment
we only did once called mean old bitch. The trials and tribulations of Rex Reed. I sent Pat
a video interview of him talking about the best films and the worst films of I guess it was
2018 because get out was on there. It was a 2017 and this thing is my God, man, you see you see
the bitterness in this man. He's sitting there. He goes they go, what do you think of the movie the
post? Rex Reed goes, the best film of this year of the post. Yeah, and he goes, he goes, these young
people, they try to make movies, but they don't know what they're doing. You take a guy like Steven Spielberg.
He knows how to make movies and then the guy goes, you're going to watch the Oscars. This is the last
line in the interview. He goes, you're going to watch the Oscars and Rex Reed goes, I always watch
I like to watch it in bed with a club sandwich and then it just cuts off. Yeah, it was great. He hated
everything and then it gets to get out and you're like, well, obviously he's going to like get out.
It's just shits on it. And he's like, what are I'm supposed to care that they're turning black people
into zombies? No, it's just robots, robots. Yeah. No, he goes, he goes, I don't care that any of these
black men were turned into robots. Yeah. Maybe, maybe that's saying a little more about you than
you want it to Rex. And then I also sent you a blurb from his Wikipedia and said, Reed was caught
shoplifting at a tower records. Nuts. He purchased two CDs, but then had like four other CDs in his
pockets. Yeah. And then it just said Reed, though. And I said to you, and then you responded
Lou, because obviously you think Lou Reed, right? He was on some heroin binge or something. And I go, no,
Rex, we had talked about Rex in a long time. And I thought because the titles were like
you know, Peggy Lee and these like kind of embarrassing people, I thought Lou Reed, the punk icon,
was embarrassed to be buying like, you know, these shitty CDs, but I guess old Rex just
couldn't. And he got off. Yeah. I mean, look, I don't believe that he was shoplifting. He's
eccentric enough that I truly, I truly do believe he, he had two in his pocket and he just forgot.
Like I'll buy that. I'll buy that. Oh, have you ever been in a store and put anything in your pocket?
I, I did once. I did once. I did a my cousin. Okay. I put something in my pocket and I paid for
stuff. And then I walked out and the, and I was like, Oh shit, I never paid for this thing. Right.
You know, but he's like, he's, you know, he's such a flamboyant like, you know, old new, you're like,
you know, he's the kind of guy that would do that. And then then be like, Oh, give me a break for
Christ sakes. What was I supposed to hold all of them? You know what I mean? Like it just, it just made
sense to me that he puts things in his pockets as he's shopping. Yeah. I agree. Anyway,
I also have a scary stuff right off the bat. Great. What do you got?
Yesterday, so we're the yesterday, meaning the day before we recorded this, not the day before it was released.
Friday the 12th, the Nintendo Switch, what again came to the Nintendo Switch Super Mario 3D world.
It was a game that was initially released for the Nintendo Wii U. They have repurposed it and
re -released it for the Nintendo Switch along with a new game called Bowser's Fury, which is an
open world Mario game. I have not played that yet, but I have played finally Super Mario 3D World
for the first time. It was a sequel to a 3DS game called Super Mario 3D Land that I loved so much
that I played through it twice. And this game is, in my opinion, after playing through two full
worlds last night after purchasing it, arguably the best Super Mario game that has ever existed. It is
so awesome. It pulls together the entire Super Mario franchise, elements of two, elements of three,
music from the first one, stuff from the original Mario Brothers game, the plumbing game.
It's 3D, but it's also a platformer. It just brings together the entire franchise. In my opinion,
this should have been the game they ended Mario on. It feels like this was the final voyage, but
it's not. They've had a few since. But my god, what a fun, fun, beautifully crafted,
awesome fantasy escape game. It's just awesome. I can't say enough. This is Mario Switch.
Well, as I said, it came out initially for the Wii U, and now it's out on the Switch. So it's
called Super Mario 3D World. I'm wondering what I played on the original Wii. I played Mario on a
Wii, and it was an amazing week of my life. Probably for the Wii was Mario Galaxy, maybe? Super Mario
Galaxy, which was Gamecube, but I could be wrong. I don't know. It was at least 10 years ago.
Well, you might have played this one on the Wii. I'm out of it. It was amazing. I loved it.
Yeah, so anyway, it's so worth it. It's 60 bucks, which is your standard going rate for a Switch game,
but you get Bowser's Fury, the new game, as a complete bonus, which I haven't even played,
and I'm excited to have it. But if it was Super Mario 3D World by itself, I would have been
completely satisfied with the money I spent. It's an awesome game.
My bit of scary stuff is Mattel. Actually, this is the Scream and Anne, excuse me. Mattel is developing
a movie based on the Uno card game with Lil Yachty in the lead role.
Now, look, I have a lot of friends who can't sell their projects out here in Hollywood.
So, when you see a news like that, it hits pretty hard. Lil Yachty, the star of the shutter,
creep show, holiday special. I guess they were so dazzled by his performance in that that they
brought him to. I just, I did read some interview with Lil Yachty that I found very funny where
he has a line in a song where it's like, I'm going to blow that girl like a cello
and they interviewed him and he's like, look, he was very funny about it, but he's like,
I guess I was thinking of a flute when I saw a cello, but he's like, I will say nobody in my camp,
nobody at the production company, nobody at the record company stepped in and said, Yachty,
you don't blow into a cello. That's a flute.
So, look, I like that aspect of Lil Yachty. However, what Uno is a card game?
Even if you love the game of Uno, are you dying to go see a movie about it?
It's going to be one of these things. We talked about this when they announced the Rubik's Cube
movie. It's, you know, it's going to be like the battleship movie where by the time it hits the
screen, it's like, it's independent stay part two. It's like, what the fuck does this have to do
with the game battleship right now? Right? So, it'll be like, you play these, they find a magic
deck of Uno cards and it sucks you into a colorful world. Who the fuck now? I mean, it's just out
rate. I mean, I'm sitting here talking about Super Mario, brother, just right for the plucking,
you could make eight movies out of these games. You know, and they're going with you have to have
a real good pitch because that is one of the most notorious flops in film history as the original Mario
Brothers. What's your opinion on that film? It's a piece of shit. It's horrible. It's really bad.
I mean, I never read the oral history of it. It's really great where they talk about just how drunk
Hoskins and leg was on. I'm aware of the whole time. Yeah, I read there was an accident on set. I think
they hit somebody with a truck or something or it was a crazy. And then like, yeah, the people that
they gave the movie to had like never made anything. It's there's tons of YouTube videos about it. It's
a fascinating. I can't believe there hasn't been an official like theatrical documentary release about
that movie. Like, it's nuts. Well, we're getting another street fighter. We're getting another
mortal combat. I mean, somebody's going to walk in there and pitch. There's another street fighter.
Yeah, they're doing it now. The new one, by the way, if I may, you know, I mean, you want to talk about
that you guys get it right one time. So they're they've been hyping up this new mortal combat
movie for the last year and a half. It's going to be Uber Violin. It's going to be mortal combat.
I don't like great. I'm in. I actually like the original moral combat film. I want to see it. I'm in
great. Let's do it. They showed some stills of the characters. I'm like, they look like the characters.
I'm in. Then they announced that the main character in this thing is a character they made up.
It's a new character they're bringing. It's like, guys, there is no franchise in video games with more
expendable characters than mortal combat. You could do six mortal combat movies and kill
popular characters five at a time in every one of those movies and still not run out of characters.
Yeah. Why do they have to fuck everything up? I don't understand. I just don't get it. It's the same
shit when they brought the muppets back. You know, like there are 25 grade A muppets and there are
75 grade B muppets and the new muppet movie adds a guy, just a guy muppet. He's just a dude. His
name was Walter. He was even more boring than Scooter who was the previous record holder for most
boring muppet. I just was watching this like, why? Why is this guy getting more screen time than
fucking Gonzo? A kid doesn't go in and go, oh sweet, we've got a new muppet to enjoy. These are the
new muppets to them. It's to make them as special as they can be. Make them as special for them as
they were when I wouldn't saw fucking great muppet. It's literally some dumb shit executive saying
there needs to be a muppet that the children can relate to and identify with. There needs to be
a person muppet. So the person is Kermit. That muppet is all the muppet. Kermit's a frog. Kermit's
Oh god. Thank you for the movie that came out 12 years ago. I hate everything. I just can't
I do too. I do too. Anyway, yeah, so this is this is this is what happens when I stop drinking.
What are these noises? What are the close encounters noises I'm hearing in your apartment? You can
hear that? Yeah, loudly. It's like the elevator or something. Yeah, it's like the elevator or
something. It goes off throughout the day every day. I have a nice apartment. I really like this place,
but but that that that's the one that's the one thing I don't like is there's that weird. I'm used to
it now. I don't even notice it anymore, but is this the one I was at? No, that place was a dump that I lived
in temporarily because I needed a place to to plant down in New York immediately. Have you counted up
the amount of apartments you've resided in? Even since I've known it, it's double digits.
No, I never counted, but yeah, I you know, but this one I've only stoned. I'm in the best
apartment I've ever had in my opinion, and and it's right in the heart of New York City and I love
it and I love New York and where a strong city will be back. Speaking of where you are in New York,
I don't want to say, but you know, I'm here. I mean, the I mean, the in the upper west side or
what? We have stalkers. I'm here. You'd be surprised, Pat. You'd be surprised some of the messages I
receive online. All right. Okay. All right. The yeah, I'm the what's it called? I a Cuomo in a bunch
of trouble again. I know out here. And this is bad. The New York Times reported this. Rivers Cuomo?
Rivers Cuomo. Yeah. Yeah. Bad news. Look, you should be in trouble. He's releasing another album.
New Weezer where it's like all piano songs now. It's like for Christ sakes, Rivers. Call some of
these solo records. Like, I haven't heard the new thing. I was talking with my buddy the other day.
I heard the food fighters on Howard Stern while I was driving around and I was like, oh, sweet.
Listen to them. And they're funny and liked hearing some stories from the road. This is a band
that I loved so much. Them and Weezer like 99, you know, 1999 era and beyond. And now like, I haven't
listened to their last six albums of either band. I don't care. I never thought I would get to that
point, but you just people stop having the goods. You know, I met Dave Grohl in a complete blackout.
Uh, uh, I do remember elements of the conversation. And the one thing I do remember is
we talked so much about Motorhead that I felt obligated at one point to say to him, Dave,
Nirvana is great too. I'm not undercutting anything you do. But I do remember I didn't even think
to mention food fighters, which I feel really bad about because I love color in the shape. I think
that's a great record. I like the first record after that they kind of lost me. But
but first two are excellent. Third one is really, really good. And that that's what I would say
about Weezer as well. Uh, I don't think that an album is really, really good. I think I think
what's it called as good, though, the one after the green one, uh, Dweezer for whatever the fuck it's
called. Malodroid. I think if you take the best songs from Malodroid and the best songs from the
green album, you've got a good Weezer album. I agree. And I did that. I made a list. Yeah, I'll do
that. I make playlist where I redesigned the record. And I did that with Weezer for those two
records. And it was a great Weezer record. Yeah. Sure. After that, you're really in trouble, though,
man. Holy shit. It is. I mean, they used to always have one good single. Like I liked
pork and beans when that was the single. I liked, uh, if you're asking if I want you to, I want you to.
And then the rest of the albums are embarrassing. Now they don't even have good singles. They'll,
they'll never do any worse than Hurley. The album with Hurley from Lost Face on it, which contained
the song called like, it was, it might as well have been called Turn on Your Heart Light or something.
It was about world peace. And it was just embarrassing. I had a sitar in it. It's like, guys,
you're not the first to discover the, the Indian music for Christ's sake. It's just, it's just
shit. It's not Indian music Weezer. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You're a big fan of Indian music. I, I'm
worldly. People wouldn't expect it. But I'll lounge around the house in a disheaky.
Yeah. You know, I'll play my bongos. You know, that kind of thing. You know, I got a lot of beads
the yurt. It's what you call it. Your, your house. Yeah. Um, all right. Well, let's go to the, uh,
let's go to the movie corner. Let's go to the movie corner. Let me bring up the letter box.
I go ahead. Sorry. Go ahead, Jeff. You want to start? I do actually. If you don't mind. I don't
mind at all. I watched the dukes of hazard movie. I've never seen it. You went on a Knoxville run.
Yeah. I, uh, I was sitting one day on my couch. I was miserably depressed. Sure. I didn't want to see
any news. I was like, what's just going to take me way out of everything and, and lo and behold,
they're on, I think it was Hulu. Was the 2005 release. The dukes of hazard starring Johnny Knoxville,
uh, William Randolph Scott. What's the kid's name? Sean William Scott. Sean William Scott. William
and Jessica Simpson. I said, what, what could, this is, there is not going to be a lick of anything
that reminds me of the real world and this, this is just going to be escape. I was right. It wasn't
escape. Uh, not a good one. It's not good movie. It's not a funny movie. It's not an interesting
movie. No. Uh, it's, it's a bad movie. Uh, it's a real bad movie. Uh, Bert Reynolds, not one funny
thing in it, uh, which Ebert said was like, it was basically like, I feel like this was, was, uh,
penance. Bert Reynolds was paying for, to, to complete his smoky and the bandit arc basically. Um,
it's just not a good movie. It's bad. Uh, there's one scene where I, where they hit each other,
where I think Scott is really hitting Johnny Knoxville and it's kind of funny because it's,
Johnny Knoxville getting hit. Uh, and then there are several scenes where Jessica Alba is in
the hottest shape slash hottest outfits of her life. And I remember the trailer at the audience was
essentially like, go on like, oh, oh, oh, I mean, she was unbelievable at that time. Yes. Yeah.
And now I like Jess Simpson. I still think she's gorgeous, but it's, it's, it's a strange character arc
in the movie because it ends up making you feel sad because every man that she encounters
desperately wants to marry her or at least have sex with her and she won't give any of them time
a day. And yet they keep using her in the movie like she's like the, the, the decoy, they send her in
to distract everybody while they do some crazy duke boys shit or whatever. Right. And you just
realized this woman's gonna die alone because she won't entertain any, uh, she won't entertain any
men because she thinks every man is just out to, to have sex with her because she's so hot.
It actually makes you kind of sad. There's this little weird bit in the movie with Willie Nelson where he's
like, where are you at Daisy? And she's like, I'm in the shower, Uncle Jesse. And he's like, oh boy.
All right. And he starts smiling. And he's like, you just wait right there. Uncle Jesse's coming right
and you're like, this is like an ins, fucks his niece or whatever. And then you realize the shower
is where they bootleg the moonshine. And that's the gag is right. He doesn't fuck his niece.
He's not like every other uncle here in Hazard County. Uh -huh. And there is one kind of funny part when
they get the, the, the generally at the beginning of the movie is just, is just the chow, I think it's a
challenger. It's just an orange car. And they get it like souped up for the big race. And when they do
that, David Keckner is the guy that works on it. And, and that's when it comes out looking like the car
in the show. And they're driving and all these people are going by them being like, hey, where's the
clan meeting asshole? And they don't know why anybody's saying that to them. And then they realize,
oh, there's a Confederate flag on our wrist that we didn't know is it? I was like, that's pretty funny.
Uh, aside from that, I mean, the guy playing Roscoe is an actor I'm unfamiliar with. And they
make Roscoe like this sinister, he's not funny. And you're like, why are you, why do you not have
like Paul Gianmati as Roscoe? Like wide eyed and like getting furious the whole, they would have
been hilarious. Why would you not do that, you know? Uh, it's just a bad movie. It's just a bad, bad
movie. I saw it theatrically. All I remember is Jessica Simpson in the in the short shorts, uh,
a slightly better TV reboot is the star scheme hutch one, but that sucks too. The, the Todd Phillips
one with it's not good. But I do love the lines a little bit better. I do love the line. They
didn't always made me laugh and it always well. When they're in the kitchen and they have the two
girls in the living room and they're deciding who's going to try to hook up with Hill.
And Owen Wilson goes, yeah, all right. Which one do you want? And Ben Stiller goes, I like the
blonde and he goes, good, cause I'll take anything. Yeah. I remember that. Funny. Yeah. And you got
been spawn and that is the bad guy and he's funny in it. You know, like there's, there's some redeeming
quality to it, but some redeeming qualities for sure. Yeah. And I, I saw, you know, when I rewatched
folks was Montscore Saisy's after hours. Great flick. It is a great flick. It's, um,
you know, it's like Scorsese trying his hand at like a real low budget, real, um, you know, just
was shot down in dirty 20 days or something in New York. Amazing supporting cast, including
Catherine O 'Hara, Cheech and Chong, you know, it just all kinds of people. Terry,
it's one of those flicks where you're like, why was Griffin done not in more stuff? You know what I mean?
Like, why did he get maybe it was by choice? He became a director, but you're like, why was he
shuffled so quickly out of the leading man thing? He's a great actor. He's very funny. He really is.
And I think, you know, he just was never quite enough of something to become a star. You know, like
he, he, Goldblum is similar, but Goldblum amps it up way more. So you get why he's a little more
popular that he just, he plays an every man really well. Well, and I think too, had he been born into a
stiller type movies back then and they're just weren't. After hours is really funny. It was
written by the guy who wrote Vampire's Kiss, which is an insane Nicholas Cage horror movie. And then
he never really did anything else, but the guy clearly had a very dark view point. The movie feels
more like being alone in New York than almost anything I've seen other than Taxi Driver,
Lawrence Crusades movie. But it's just great. It's very, it's bleak. It's, it's one of those where
you're, you know, you're laughing just at how bad everything is, which is always one of my favorite
styles of comedy. And it's, it's like this, it's a Kafka -esque tale of a man. At the beginning,
he's working in an office with Balkey, Brownson, Pinchel, if you'll recall. He's bored. So then he
takes off and just has one wild night in New York. Then at the end of the movie, he's back at work
the next day as if this insane night didn't happen. That's what New York is like. Or it's what,
what it's like when you're that age. You know, when I first, when I lived there, I would go out
till six in the morning and then come into work like at eight and be like, God, or people gonna notice
whatever. It's a wild ride. It's very fun. It's one of Scorsese's most underrated, although I think
people are catching up to it now. Not, it doesn't have a blu -ray release, which is nuts, but you can
watch it on HBO Max right at this moment. Check it out if you never seen it. I rewatched something
I'd seen years ago and I bought it on blind faith and then watched it and was thoroughly impressed and
really enjoyed it. And I broke it out again because we had a blizzard here in New York. And we're
literally snowed in for two days. So I watched Stephen King's Storm of the Century. I own it.
Three -part mini -series each episode is 90 minutes. So it's gonna take you some time to get through it.
But it is hands down the best Stephen King television adaptation I have ever seen.
Really, rivaled only by the it adaptation, which has its problems, but I really like and we've
talked about it. But as far as made, what is Storm of the Century? Is that a novella or did he write the
screenplay? It wasn't a book. King wrote the screenplay for TV. There is no book. And he said,
this is a novel for television. And it is classic king. Great premise. There's a major storm coming
in this New England town. And as the storm blows into town, so does this mysterious man who starts
kind of causing havoc and knows everybody's secrets. And it kind of unfolds from there. I don't want to
say much more because it really is worth experiencing. Great cast, well -directed, legitimately scary
at times. It's classic king. It's awesome. It's an awesome, awesome movie. And again, as far as the
made for TV stuff that they've done with King's work, you know, and I own almost all of them,
Langeliers, which is terrible. It, which is great. Writing the bullet, which is okay. You know,
the stand, the original stand, which is okay. You know, this one is great. It's great. It really,
really is a good piece of work. And I highly suggest it. It's spooky. It's a lot of fun.
I own it and I can't wait to check it out. I know we said we were going to do the CBS All Access
stand. The reviews have been so bad. Do you still want to? No, I can't do it either. My friend called
me last night and it said, Hey, I know you're a horror guy. They just finished the stand. The last
episode just aired. And then he went on a 20 -minute rant of this is one of the worst things I've ever
seen in my life. I've heard that. And he told me that it ends with the line, get the behind me Satan.
Okay. Well, then the flash as a Miller, is it the guy who punched that girl and still has a
career? I can't tell if that video is real or not. I feel like it's their joking around. It looks
real real, but he plays the trash can man. And apparently it is one of the worst performances in the
history of the medium. That's a shame. He's a good actor. He's a good actor. I don't know why he would
do the part or why he would be that over the top with it. But apparently he's bad, the movie's
bad. I really, I was excited. I mean, I listened to the audiobook of the stand, which took 40 hours out
of my life thinking I'd be pumped to watch the new one. And I just can't muster the excitement.
I mean, look, I said, I think I said it on the show before my biggest gripe and the thing that turned
me off immediately was Randall Flagg. It's too pretty. Yeah, sure. He's too pretty. He looks like, he
looks like Jared Lido, who by the way is one of the stars of today's film, The Little Things,
The Little Things. A lot of things to say about The Little Things. But he's too pretty.
And it's just I get it. Randall Flagg needs to be like intriguing and and and and
alluring in his own way. But he can't look like a runway model. I mean, come on man.
So great. Anyway, I got a couple of four year considerations from the Apple company, Apple TV.
I don't I don't subscribe. So I watched this thing called visible out on television, which is a
five part, five hour documentary about the history of the LGBTQ movement on television. So starting in
the very earliest days where like they would have to kind of code that the character was gay,
there's a there's about a half hour of time here presented to Paul Lind and actors of that
nature who that's a dark story, by the way. Yeah, I mean, it's almost a whole episode of these
actors who everybody knew was gay. They they just didn't allow him to say it. There's a there's a
huge fan. Why have you never been here? We we've been asking for you to come down and why couldn't
we get you? And Lind is like, well, I was scared to death. I he's like, I'm scared to be myself. I'd
rather play a character than then and really what he's saying is I was terrified you'd make fun of me
for being gay and I wouldn't know what to do or say. So I only bring Lind up because we've talked about
a bunch on the show, including Joe's love with his Halloween special. But the it goes right up
through the present, you know, where it actually has a little bit of overlap with the documentary on
trans actors that aired on Netflix, which I liked quite a bit, but it's really, really good. I watched
the whole documentary in one night and was never bored. It's five hours long. They get a lot of great
talking heads by which I mean the people they're interviewing. And it's really, really interesting. I
thought it was a great documentary that I didn't even know existed. So if you do have Apple TV,
it's well worth a watch, especially if you're sort of a student of TV history as I consider myself.
It's one of the few things I actually give a shit about. So check it out, visible colon out on
television, not visible colon, visible than a colon. I'll close out with I've been rewatching the TV
show Monsters, which I've discussed, discussed on here before I believe I think I have. Monsters is
what they did after Tales from the Dark Side ended. Richard P. Rubenstein, one of the producers of
Tales from the Dark Side, went on and did a show called Monsters, which was an anthology horror series
that was made for syndication, syndication, much like Tales from the Dark Side was. Every episode,
as you can imagine, centers around a certain monster. Is it a good show? No. But does it have great
episodes? Yes. I think it's a lot of fun. It sits right in that fun pocket of television like
phasing out of animatronic and practical effects, but still pre -CGI.
So it's got a certain feel and look and vibe to it that only TV from that time period has.
We're talking very early 90s, probably. All -Star casts, crazy. Some of the people popping up in the
Steve Bouchemis in an episode. There's all kinds of big names in it before they were big.
And it's just a fun show. And the reason I'm revisiting it is because I found out about the Roku app.
There's a Roku TV app that's completely free. It's yet another app where you can watch stuff on
demand with commercials in it. And they've got the first season of Monsters on it. I own the entire series,
at night I put it on the Roku app and just stream an episode or two as I go to sleep.
And it's just a lot of fun, man. Some of the episodes are absolutely terrible, like cringe -worthy
horrific. And then some of them are just really fun, little monster stories.
The episode called Glimglim, which is a Christmas episode is pretty interesting.
There's a great episode called mannequins of horror, which was also a story in asylum.
It was adapted for asylum. And I think that's when I talked about monsters a little bit.
There's a great episode called the match game that stars, I'm blanking under name, but the actress
that played Kirstie in Hellraiser. There's an awesome episode of the age here in Barbell called
all of the day's work about a doppelganger. It's just a fun show to check out.
That's it. I recommend it. It's hard to get the DVDs now. They went from being $17 .99
for the entire series to like $300 now because they're out of print or whatever. So you might have
missed the boat on getting the DVDs for an affordable price, but you can at least stream this on the
free Roku app for season one and decide if you want to go any deeper.
Fair enough. I'm not familiar with the program. I watched also on Apple TV on the rocks,
which is the new Sophia Coppola picture. I like Sophia Coppola for the most part. I love
verdant suicides. I really love lost in translation. I like Marie Antoinette, blah, blah, blah.
She's good. This felt like that movie you make when you've got just too much money,
and you know you can get whatever you want made, and you can call up your old buddy Bill Murray and
just hang out. It's Rashida Jones, who I'm sorry, to me, is just kind of the most average actress
there is. I do not know how she has this stranglehold on the entertainment industry. I like her fine,
but it doesn't hurt when your dad is Quincy Jones for sure. She's fine. Bill Murray plays her dad,
and basically he comes into the city. He's kind of an emotionally distant father. Of course,
it makes you wonder, is it Francis? She's talking about her blah, blah, blah.
But he comes in. They hang out. They talk about the issues and their relationship,
and then her husband who was played by Marlon Wayans, who's very good in the movie,
she suspects him of cheating. And Bill Murray and Coppola decide to track him down on his business trip
and catch him in the act, cheating. Now, if you do this in a multi -cam sitcom this plot,
they would go, come on, they did it on the fucking golden girls. They probably did it three times
in the golden girls. Let's all go see if we can find him cheating. It feels like a really generic
sitcom with big actors in it. It feels like Coppola's phoning it in. There's no real laughs to it.
There's no real suspense to it. The reveal, if you could call it that when it comes, is a big nothing.
I think the only reason it's up for Oscars and stuff, at least in the mix, is because this year
has been so weird, and there's not that many titles available. You know, if you're a Bill Murray fan,
and I'm one of the biggest, it passes the time, but it's very, very, very average, aggressively average,
I would say. All right. There you have it. And I want to make it confused where they're not golden girls,
where they went to find out if a guy was cheating on them. No, I was just thinking about how much
I don't want to watch this movie. Oh, okay, fair. On the rocks is also the name of the new Brian
Reagan stand -up special. Really? Is he? He get better from his COVID?
I guess. Well, it's a Netflix special. They could have shot it a year ago. I don't know,
but it was, it's kind of crazy. He's fully gray now. Yeah, I saw, I've seen him. Yeah, he was, you
know, he's one of a lot of people's favorite stand -ups, but for sure, one of mine. And the only
special of his I haven't loved was his latest Netflix one. So I hope it's a step in the better direction.
I think so. I think that last one he did amidst I think a divorce and stuff. Like I feel like
that was rushed out very quickly to coincide with that sketch show that he was doing, but right.
So I look forward to seeing it. I love I'm a big Reagan fan. Anyway, our movie today
that premiered on HBO Max. If you have it, you can watch it. The little things,
starring Denzel Washington, Jared Lito, and Rami Malik. Is it Leto or Lito? I say Lito.
I say Lito. Maybe it's Leto.
Directed by John Lee Hancock, who did the blind side. He also wrote a perfect world,
which is one of the most underrated Clint Eastwood movies. He did it right after unforgiven,
and it was him and Costner. And the only reason I saw it is because me and my buddy were Devastate
that Mrs. Doubtfire was sold out speaking of Doubtfire. And man, if you've never seen a perfect
world, it's really fucking good. John Lee Hancock wrote this screenplay in the early 90s. He makes a
point in every interview of saying he wrote it before seven because I'm sure everyone that watches it
is like, so it's a lot like seven, right? Yeah, the end of it feels like it's going to be seven at the
very end. Yeah. Um, he's not a bad writer or director. I think, you know, this movie was attached
to numerous actors through the years. It almost got made many times. Steven Spielberg almost made it
in the early 90s. And all it feels now is just kind of boring dated. There's a, for about 20 minutes,
you're like, oh, sweet. This is going to be one of those movies. There used to be so many of them.
Copycat seven, kiss the girls, you know, and they were always a reliable good time. You know,
they were always pretty good. They had good twists and, and then good actors in them. Yeah, but this,
I mean, it just loses its way fast. And it's biggest issues are a, the story is just not even remotely
exciting. You don't really know what's going on. You just feel like you're kind of being dragged
along as opposed to like being eager to get to things. You're just kind of like WhatsApp. Who cares?
Yeah. Tommy Malik is playing a, by the way, really, really quick before you go in. By the way, it's
a, you know, it's a detective procedural. There's murders happening. And these guys are on the case.
And that's, you know, right. Uh, Denzel is a guy who's been kind of thrown out of the LA police force.
And he's up at a, in a northern California sort of smaller precinct, but he goes down to LA and gets
back involved in this case. Um, so he's partnered up with Ramy Malik. And that is one of the biggest
problems in the movie. I, I chuckled to myself imagining Denzel having to being a being probably the
best actor of his generation. And then be having to share scenes with Ramy Malik and Jared Lito who
think they're the best actors with their generation, but they are definitely fucking not. So Malik
cannot even convincingly play a normal person. The whole time, I don't know about you, Joe, the entire
movie. I thought, well, this guy's the killer. No, no, no human being could operate in the police force
and, and be this insane acting at all times. Malik is, uh, yeah, he's got a, he's a weird guy. Uh,
and he, and that comes through in this. I, I didn't hate his performance in it. Um, but it is,
it is irritating because it's needlessly eccentric. And I think part of it is supposed to make
you think is he the killer. I think you're also supposed to wonder if Denzel Washington is the killer
because he's clearly hiding something throughout the movie. Um, and then Lito is so obviously
a lunatic character in it that you're, you know, I felt like that was all misdirection done on purpose.
I, in fact, text knew what while I was watching it and said, if this turns out to be like Denzel's
a killer, I'm, I'm gonna break my phone in half because it feels like the thing you see coming a
mile away. Right. Well, I thought it had to be Malik building up to that scene and, and Heather and I
stood up in the living room and we're like, what the, it was one of the worst constructed scenes ever
where Malik drives Lito out to the desert. Before you get to this, though, let's, let's, we're jumping
the gun a little bit. Let's go back through the movie a little bit and do some setup. Okay? Just,
just a little bit of setup before we get to this scene because I think that's important with this
movie. I mean, first of all, the opening scene, the, the, my biggest grab of this movie, the entire
thing felt cliche from front to back. Now, if he wrote it 20 years ago, fine, but that doesn't mean
the fact that, that doesn't change the fact that a million of these movies have been out since this
movie wants to be prisoners and doesn't even come close. Young girl driving at the beginning,
singing along to the B 52s. It's, it's the exact same scene as the girl driving singing along to American
girl in Silence of the Lambs, you know? Right. It's exact, exact parallels between classic movies
throughout. And there's a car on the road that sort of might be following her. You don't know.
And then it passes her and she's a little freaked out. And then as she continues to drive, the cars
now stopped on the side of the road. And that freaks her out. So she barrels past it. And this is almost
immediately the movie lost me. She starts panicking in a way that is so absurd. Yeah. And against
any survival instinct you would have, that she pulls over at a gas station to allow time for the guy
that was stopped in his car on the side of the road that she was afraid of to catch up to her.
And almost murder her. And you're watching this. You're going, the, who the fuck, what kind of idiot
would do this? This is ridiculous. When she pulls off the highway and is like running through an
open field, I'm like, get into your fucking car. What it, it's, it's exactly right. From the opening
moment, you're like, I don't even believe that this woman is in jeopardy. They didn't even do a good
job of making you feel that that was her only option. No, not even close. And it was, and like we
talked about with Antibellum, when the main character in that movie escapes finally at the end on
horseback, there's like 40 minutes before that where you're like, why wouldn't you just get
on the horse and ride out of here? You're just, you're like, what the fuck is going on? It doesn't
make any sense. So that's the first cliche sort of paint by number scene where you're just like,
okay, then enters Denzel. And immediately it's the like he's the broken down sheriff in the small
town. You know, people are saying things about him like, oh, you mean the guy that had the case
that broke him? You know, went through a divorce and that case all in six months, you know, and you're
like, oh, for Christ's sakes, then you got rammy mallet comes in in like a suit with slick back hair
with a press conference. That's how they introduce his character. And you're just like, this is, this
is just so cliche. And then it hits my favorite cliche of the whole movie.
They go, they, they partner up and they go to the first murder scene to, to investigate. And the
coroner says, you had your lunch before they go into look at the dead body. That is such a cliche
that 20 years ago, when I started in stand -up comedy, my friend John Kencil, who's a hilarious comic
had a joke in his act where he said, here's my impression of every corner and every lethal weapon movie.
And he would take out a handkerchief and put it over the stool. And before he pulled it back, go,
I hope you boys had your lunch and then pull it back. You'll get a huge laugh. Because it was so,
it's so dumb. They do it in every movie. I was like, you left that line in this, that, I was like,
we're in trouble here, man. We're, we're in a lot of trouble here. It's, it's generic to a fault.
Heather has seen sounds of the lambs once and she was like, isn't this like exactly like the beginning
of sounds? It's, and it's so weird because I read this big interview of him about the long journey it
took to get to the screen. And he's so adamant about talking about when he wrote it and, and that it was
before these movies and everything else. So clearly he knows. And the, the fact that he didn't
just update the movie is so insane. Instead, he sets it in 1991. Which is like not a time period where
you need to set a movie. It has no reason to be in that time frame, except they said, we'll make
this script. Why don't you take a week and update it. And he said, no, I don't want to do that work.
Let's set it then so we don't have cell phones because you knew that introducing cell phones into
this movie would end it. It's like sign felled now. All the issues would be done with cell phones.
So instead you've got a period piece, even though they don't like put up on the screen that it's 1991.
So he's driving down the 101 at one point and I go, well, there's a good fella's poster on the
side of that building. What the fuck is that? Then I look up on Wikipedia and I'm like, oh, it's supposed
to be 1990. Like they just do such a shit job of everything in this movie. One of my favorite
things in this movie was that so you know, it's a murder mystery and there's dead girls everywhere.
And then there's also the dead girl on the case that Denzel worked five years before this.
And he thinks that the killer of these women is connected to the killer of the women he was investigating
five years ago. So you got a lot of moving parts here and there's a lot of names. He's the ghosts.
Yeah, yeah, he sees the ghosts. And throughout the movie, you know, so you got a lot of names
and details you got to keep track of. And their main victim, I laughed out loud when he said
they're main victim. Rami Malik goes, well, what do we do about Mary Roberts? That's the
the name. They're, they're spitting names in every scene in this thing. And they name the main
victim Mary Roberts. The most forgettable name you've ever heard. And I was like, wait a minute,
is that somebody important? I just want to know who that is. Like it's terrible. And then Denzel
for some reason, which they kind of justify at the end is obsessed with this concept of the little
things. And you could tell that when this guy wrote this, he was like, I'm going to call it the
little things. And in the trailer, you're going to see the cop go, it's the little things. And that's
going to be the chilling end of the trip, which is exactly what they did. And throughout the entire movie,
Denzel is just like, it's the little things, it's little things. What kind of beer was she drinking?
You know, stuff that gets to a point where you're like, why do you need to know that? Well,
sometimes it's not the big things that solve the case. It's the little looks into camera.
It's a little thing. And they do, they do a bit at one point where the the new like corner or whatever
that he's friends with. For back when he was on the force, she goes, she's like examining the pizza
they find in Jared Lido's trash, because he's their main suspect. And she goes one other thing.
He's from the East Coast. And Denzel goes, how do you know that? And she pulls up the pizza
and folds it and shows by the bite. She goes, folded slices, which by the way, that detail never
comes into play again. There's never a part where they're like, we need to thank God we knew he's
from the East Coast. That's how we solve this thing. It's just stupid. Joe, generally you and I focus
on different little things or details, if you will. That pizza thing set me off so fucking much
because I was like, how you're you're using this as proof that because he folded his pizza slice,
he's from the East Coast. Like, if you have a pizza slice that's bigger than normal, you have to
fold it to eat it. I lived in New York for three years. I fold my pizza slices. If they found me
dead, they'd go, I bet he's from New York City. And then Denzel would go good enough for me. Let's act on
it. His or police been. It's a and then does he have a romance with that lady corner with the
big mole on her face? Like there's a weird flirtation between them. You're not sure what's going on.
You don't you don't even know like you don't even know your bearings in the romance subplot. You
don't know what's going on. That's how badly this story has been told. And then even like stuff
that they could have used as a device to make you question characters more, for instance.
As I said, they make it clear that Denzel is sort of hiding something. You don't know what it is
till the end. But like there's a scene where he visits his ex -wife. And his ex -wife is very happy
to see him. And he's like, how the girls and she's like, they're good. You know, you should call
them. And you're like, maybe use this scene to create a little more of a smoke screen on what's
going on. Maybe the ex -wife is a little set off when she sees him. And you go, maybe he's shady.
Maybe he's this. Maybe he's that. And it's like, no, he's just a good guy the whole way through.
And then what you find out at the very end, because they keep flashing back to this pivotal night that
made him leave the force. And you know that there was a cover -up of some kind or whatever. And what
happened was he was in the wilderness looking for an escaped victim that got away from the killer.
And he hears a noise in the bushes and shoots the girl by accident thinking it's the killer.
And they have to cover it up. So because he's a good cop and it was an accident and they don't
want him to go down over this. But it makes him break mentally for obvious reasons, the guilt and whatever.
And then this movie culminates with Rami Malik being taken to the desert by Jared Lido,
who you think is the killer. Well, I also thought was pretty good in the movie. I thought let it
let it play. Interesting. I don't disagree. You know, to me, it's the kind of role he should play is
just your garden variety psychos. He's pretty good enough at it. So this is your scene now that
pissed you off. Yeah. So, I mean, we were not into this thing. I mean, don't get me wrong. I was
bored. I'm obviously having to Wikipedia to even find out what year it takes place in. But
I'm in the middle of complaining about how they're supposed to be like, I had just watched
Los Angeles plays itself. This amazing documentary that our buddy Vince Avril gifted to me. I don't
know, he gave you one too, right? Yeah. Yes. It's a great documentary. But there's a big section
in it about how when you live in LA, you hate watching movies because they're always they don't
use the right sense of direction. So it's like, let's go to Hollywood and then they go south or
whatever. They don't bother to make it correct. So this kind of gets ruined for you when you're like,
oh, this murder scene takes place at the taco stand. I go to you're like, that's not a scary place.
Yeah. Yeah. So in this movie, he's in North Hollywood. Then he's getting on the the 101 from Franklin,
which is right by my house. And then some parts of it just look like Vancouver. They don't look like
like Los Angeles at all. And I'm complaining about this until I realize what's happening is that
Rami Malak, who's supposed to be our good cop, is driving Jared Lito out to the middle of nowhere to find
out where this girl is buried. Jared Lito, as far as we know, at this point, is a raving psychopath
who has killed dozens of people. He gets in a car with him. He's driving out. He like,
Abandon's Denzel. He doesn't tell him where he's going or get back up, which is why they had to
set it then because he would have just texted him where he's going. Right. He drives out into what
appears to be the same stretch of abandoned desert that they shot the climax of seven in. It looks
like the exact same location. Just shot at night. And it's about 4 billion percent less suspenseful
and effective. But they go out there. And so at this point, it's the one moment where you're like,
okay, now I do want to know what's going on. Is Malak the killer? Is Lito? Is Washington? What's
going on? The way they shoot this scene, and I couldn't tell if this was intentional or what,
but at one point, Jared Lito is insisting that Rami Malak, Doug, dig, excuse me, Malak
is, he turns his back fully to Jared Lito, who is as we are assuming at this point, is killed dozens
of people. Turns his back fully to him. His gun is not just exposed, but loosely hanging out of
its holster. Yeah. Six inches from Jared Lito's hand. Yeah. And Malak has his head down and his
digging and digging and digging to try to find out where this body is. So at this point, it's like,
okay, I guess they're saying Lito isn't the killer because if he was, he'd shoot Malak.
Is Malak trying to bait him with the gun because he's not gonna, is he trying to hit him with the
shovel? What's going? And the scene is shot so clumsily and executed so poorly that there is no
suspense. You're not confused. You're kind of, you are confused, but you're more angry than like
wanting to see it resolved or see what's going on because everyone's just being so fucking stupid.
You can't root for people to succeed if they're being so stupid they deserve to die.
It's that. It's, it's rat. You're not. Unless I'm mistaken. They don't let you know who did it.
They don't. And that's the, that's your big, well, before we get into that, they, they then show
that Malak digs about four three -foot holes in a matter of 20 minutes.
And this was the, I'm guaranteeing he was like, it's like in the conversation when Gene Hackman,
you know, it's the same thing. He's so obsessed. Maybe that's it. Maybe the point is he's so obsessed.
He doesn't notice his gun as exposed. That's the only way I'll buy that scene.
And then Lido says, I've never killed anybody in my life. You just want me to have killed people,
whatever, something like that. But then you don't know if Lido's telling the truth. And then Lido
starts egging on Rami Malak and Malak hits Lido with a shovel, killing him accidentally.
And not confirming whether or not Lido is the killer. Then Denzel shows up and says,
I, we're taking care of this. Dig a four -foot hole deep right now, a four -foot deep hole right
now. We're going to bury him in it. And that's what we're doing. He leaves. He goes, I'll be back in a
few hours. Leaves comes back. The hole is barely dug. They then have to, Denzel has to pitch in and
help him dig the hole. So just, just basic little details like this. It's like, it's none of this is
making any sense at this point. Again, you assume that Lido is the killer and that this was
unfortunate. So they bury him in the desert. While Denzel leaves Malak alone, he goes back to Lido's
place, clears out the entire apartment, and then finds a secret box, a hidden box in the floor boards,
that he looks into. And it's insinuated that he discovers something inside the box. Your assumption
is it's a red barrette. The red barrette is the thing they're looking for because one of the latest
victim wore a red barrette when she went missing. And that this and Lido apparently is keeping souvenirs
from his victims. And then the big conclusion to this thing is, you see Rami Malak at home, almost
comatost or catonic rather. He now, you realize, is in the state that Denzel was in after Denzel made
his mistake of killing the victim by accident. You see the press a new guy in Ramiq's job,
Malak's job doing the same press conference Malak was doing at the beginning saying,
we know this about the killer. He can disappear in an instance. We've been to his apartment,
nothing is there. And then you realize, okay, that's why Denzel cleared it out. They're making it
look like this guy is still alive somehow. Then it shows Denzel burning all the evidence, right?
Then it shows Malak getting an envelope from Denzel, like via courier or whatever,
which is funny because you're like, I thought having the Harry Potter I'll do it was a little strange.
Yeah, you think it's like, you know, this is like police forensic evidence. You just said he
did an envelope. Malak opens the envelope, it's got a red barrette in it. You're like, oh, okay,
that's to give him closure. It was Lido. Then it cuts back to Denzel burning the evidence.
The final thing he burns is a package of barretts. The red one is missing. You realize Denzel sent
this to him. So Malak thinks that's that they've solved this and that he can move on with his life.
But if you stop and think about that for two seconds, you're like, no,
Malak's going to see the investigation going on continually and is going to think that the killer is
dead because he made a stupid mistake and that's going to drive him even more crazy now.
Yes, makes no sense. I look, I did use to write reviews back in the day and just now I thought of
what because that's what you have to do is kind of think of an angle for your review and I just
realized my review would be writing and directing is also about the little things. And if you don't
land the little things, we're not going to buy the big things. That's the problem with this movie.
It's like they they botch even the most simple just what we were saying. If you're botching the
flirtation with the woman at the coroner's office, if even that leaves the audience confused as to
what their relationship is, have they fucked? Are they going to fuck? What's going on? Then of course,
we're not going to believe your your intense murder mystery like nothing in this movie was done
well. So nothing works. And it would have made more sense at the end if you saw Denzel holding the red
beret and then putting it in his pocket. Right. Because then you could go, oh shit, he can't let
Ramy Malik know that the guy was caught or that was definitely their guy because that will allow him
to allow the investigation to keep going without thinking about it. Right. Or shit. Was it Denzel?
Wait a minute. He's got the red beret. You know what I mean? Like, yeah, I don't know. And that's
not a good ending either. But the movie here will happen is sucks. Is Spielberg and Eastwood and any big
director worth their salt are going to have a two week period at least where they sit down with
the screenwriter and go through the script and check every box and make sure everything makes sense.
That's a big part of the film making process. And I think that when this guy heard 25, 30 years ago
that these big names wanted to make his movie, he thought it was perfect. In truth, Eastwood's made
a hundred movies exactly like the little things over the course of his career, whether it be dirty
area or or not. Eastwood would have known to sit down and go, well, this doesn't work. This makes no
sense. I'm not I can't have Malik out there with the gun hanging out of his pocket. You know, you know,
a bigger director would have called him on the bullshit and made the script work and not let him
be lazy on it. I think and I'm speculating to some degree. But I think when he decided he was going
to direct his own screenplay, he simply didn't do the work. If you're not even going to do the work
to make updated to the modern day, you know, like I'm still laughing about a 1991 period piece. It's
like it's it's just ridiculous to me. But yeah, everything about this is so lazy. And at the end,
I just thought if I bet if he had put a week more into this screenplay that this ending could have
been something special, the three of those guys out in the desert being weird, I'd watch that,
but it doesn't work. Right. And quite frankly, it plays like a made for HBO movie versus a theatrical
release, which is what it was supposed to have been first off. And then secondly, it plays very much
like what I would expect from a Steven Spielberg directed murder mystery, even though he didn't
direct it. It's it's it's two tame in places. It's two ridiculous in places. It's not logical enough
in places. And to me, it plays like something where it's like, yeah, this does feel to me like a
popcorn movie guy directed a murder mystery and didn't you know, they'll review some of the interviews
with the with the writer director. It's like, he says he wrote a script so dark. And it's like,
it's not that dark of a script. No, there to have the shit that's been out there. It's a movie that
thinks it's being dark and it's fucking boring. Yeah, it's and and also he seems to want to
paint himself as some sort of pioneer. Silence of the lambs is is an infinitely darker movie and
infinitely better movie as is seven and etc. And I part of me thinks he's he's talking about all
those movies to like act like he's in the same conversation. But I do have on fairly good authority
that HBO air or Warner Brothers was like, we can't how are we going to release this thing? Like,
how are we going to get this out? And I think what happens is
these movies that are coming to HBO Max and granted they they're coming to all the streamers,
but they're the HBO Max was the most notorious. If you really look at these titles, the little
little things, that might have had a good opening weekend because of star power maybe. Wonder Woman
might have had a good opening weekend, of course, it would have. But when I'm looking at like
barb and star now, which is being dropped when I'm looking at pretty much anything that's come out,
but Bill and Ted, all these movies that have come out straight to VOD or straight to HBO Max,
they are movies that I think they knew they had kind of a turd on their hands. I really do.
I just I think they none of these movies that they'll the Soderburg one with Meryl Streep,
I think is really bad and they would not have known how to market it. I did not let them all talk,
not a good movie. So I think now we're just kind of being lied to all the time with these movies.
And it's a little frustrating because you'd want one of them to be good.
Actually, you know, I like Judah and the Black Messiah, which premiered on HBO Max last night.
That's a good, exciting movie. But beyond that, it's rough. It's rough. These HBO Max things are like,
you know, it's supposed to recreate the movie going experience. Some new big movie comes out every
weekend. Netflix claims they've got a big movie for every 52 weeks of the year coming up.
But God, the titles, you know, it's rough. Shout out, though. Shout out to a great performance.
The kid from Kate and Ali playing a sexual offender in the middle of this thing. He was great.
He was. I didn't even recognize him. Yeah, he was great. He's a great actor.
Denzel's lazy is working a while. I got to say he seems like he was sleepwalking through. I bet
those two annoyed the shit out of him is my. Yeah, I feel like he was well, he said to an interview.
Somebody was like, did Lido pull any of his method acting stuff? And he was like, no, method acting is
bullshit. And he goes, if Lido had done any of that with me, he would have been paid a visit.
Whatever that means. The he's the best. I love it.
Anyway, two hugs down for the little things. That's our show folks. Thank you for your support.
You know the plugs. I got nothing else to say.
Thank you very much. You got a new hour long solo movie corner up as well. Thank you for your support.
Thank you for your love. Thank you, Emily for always promoting us and for keeping the people
aware of what's going on. Emily also sent me, by the way, a bunch of requests you guys have for
commentaries for Joe and I to do. That is a little bit trickier with our Zoom setup and internet
connections and everything, but we will definitely take them into consideration. Thank you for those.
And Emily's film festival is coming up soon. Yes. Got to mention that.
What was the date on it? Let me look it up. Hold on. I am bringing it up as well.
It is called the Terror's Texas Film Festival. Emily is one of the curators or the head of the
festival or one of the heads of the festival. And you have until February 15th to get your ticket,
which is today. The day that you came out is the last you can get your ticket. It's 30 short films
all under 20 minutes each. It's eight bucks. Can't beat that. And we'll probably review some of
this at some point. So that's our show folks. We'll see you next time. And we'll see you now.