I'll see you in the next one.
Welcome to We'll see you in hell, your favorite podcast discussing horror sci -fi action.
Fantasy all types of genre films quite frankly people we got your bases covered and we're on those
bases covering them my name is Joe de Rosa my name is Patrick Walsh hello again thank you all
for being so patient with us during that lengthy hiatus today's film will be mid -summer the latest
from Ari Astor director of hereditary we'll get there eventually Joe how are you what's going on
Pat as as we were suffering during the last episode episode we suffer again with my downstairs
neighbor yeah cranking techno music really the third guest of the podcast and then it stops do you hear
how it just stops and then it'll start again in a minute what are you what is he doing I assume
that's between songs right who listens to techno songs individually who's not doing no because
it's the same song comes back you know that's the part where where it gets all quiet it goes when
that they call that the drop yeah what a fucking idiot that's something when I would occasionally go
to these EDM type festivals or you'd go for the people you like but then wind up having to go see
a couple of these EDM things every song does that the music drops out the whole place looks at each
other like oh fuck and then it starts up again here and it's like every time you're gonna get this
excited about this I'm gonna say you're on drugs but still I'm gonna say this yeah it's music for
dumb people no absolutely it's music for dumb people absolutely or or people on drugs I mean when
you're on drugs it sounds even when you're on drugs if you're into this you're dumb yeah I've been
on drugs yeah I'm plenty of times I you know I can think of one or two times where we listen to
some sort of EDM thing and I was like yeah man this is pretty cool I can see the beat man you know
whatever but usually I want to hear shit that I like like good music I feel the same you couldn't
catch me at a fucking all night rave on drugs what are you nuts you know hang out these assholes
and blow my buzz yeah I want to fun tonight they sometimes they dance up with the the glow sticks
or the the glowing rings and and encircle them in front of your face like a stranger will come up and
do this in front of your face and then you're like cool oh god and I I'm working on a bit about this
I'm actually gonna write a bit about how techno music is music for dumb people yes that is my opinion
in my own opinion it does not reflect the opinions of Patrick well it does I mean it's time is
kind of coming gone it's time was really five years ago people are still listening to but I really
am working on a bit about how much I hate pot culture I hate weed culture so much especially now
that it's all cold oh you know I like weed but the people who it's like dude like you gotta like
try this and that it gets very tires I was at a weed friendly comedy show the other night
who I the my friend Alexis Fox runs and she's lovely I love Alexis you're I'm a fan you know I'm a
fan you're lovely one of the sweetest people I've ever met she she's big into weed she's not
annoying about it she just smokes weed and whatever but somebody else at the show I hear yell at one
because it was a weed friendly venue where you could smoke in the venue here's somebody go
Todd do you have any flower okay that's too much and I almost that's too much puked on the
fucking ground yeah I hate weed culture so much I want to do a dab trees I want a dab so I hit it like
when I'm right before I go on I want to do a dab shut up shut up go go buy a neon green something
the slang is a tree's flower all that's rough oh my god green herb oh my god oh I can't
fucking stand it I can't stand it and it gets like this big pass over booze like oh it's so much
better for you is it because every guy I know that smokes pot is a fucking moron well I smoke
yeah well my my I rest my case you're out of their questions yeah yeah I anyway I'm well
otherwise other than the techno people and the weed people I'm doing fairly well sure I'm a I'm judging
roast battle tonight at the comedy store okay always fun Jeff Roth still doing it or not yeah Jeff
comes through usually and my buddy Brian Moses hosts it and it's a lot of fun all right doesn't
start to eleven fifteen usually it's a great time to go over and have a few drinks yeah I'm debating
not I'm debating a drinking pause okay I mean Pat I don't know what to do with this shit I stay
off for a couple days I'm like clearly this is better it clears my head I'm better up and then I
sit there and go what am I gonna do tonight I'm just gonna go sit like it's fun to have a few
drinks and cut loose I know I'm not gonna be a disgusting mess right I'll have five drinks and I'll laugh
and I'll go home and whatever the fuck yeah it's it's really a tough one man I took five full weeks
while you were out of town which made it much easier off of drinking and a lot from people which
frames me off of drinking and weed and I felt good but yeah it's like it's not such a hindrance to
my life you know that I can't do it once in a while so I wish that I had felt better but I felt good for
sure if I had felt amazing then it would be easier to just say I'm done drinking and smoking for all
time but I still like it I'll tell you one thing I'm gonna join a gym there's a gym in New York
near the apartment I'm staying in and it's a legit gym but it is only 15 bucks a month and they
have trainers I'm gonna go over there I'm gonna get a trainer and I'm just gonna say look man I
fucking hate cardio get me pressing some weights whatever I gotta do to stay in reasonable shape here
if you want to do 10 minutes on the fucking bike I'll do it yeah but I hate cardio I find it painfully
boring what other way can we do this I'm gonna do it the training is great I really enjoy it I like to
do it uh right when I wake up so that you barely remember that it happened which is nice yeah yeah
I'm gonna go in there at a cool 4 15 a .m. I might go in before I go to bed we're coming off a night
a bar hopping yeah that's it what do you got bitch this thing give me the way it's bitch what I'm
going to man trainer a bitch by the way I'm that's not a just not a gender thing I come home now and if
I were to lay down I would just go to sleep at 10 a .m. for the rest of the day I have to force myself
because it's exhausting but it's it's works yeah who are these psychos are like I just get a charge
for the rest of the day sick what do you want lunatic I get a charge out of cardio running or doing my
elliptical or whatever you know I get I get some energy but the the weight lifting my body is destroyed
when I'm done and in a good way I like to do it man three days a week yep just go in and say look
man I'm just not going to be one of these 30 minutes of cardio every day guys I like to smoke a
few sigs I like to have a few drinks and I like to eat what I like to eat tell me what to do to not
die that's it that's fair that's it that's fair and count me get rid of these luscious breasts of my
and they are luscious I want to see those go but I wish I could donate something to science it be my
breasts now Joe why do you have the Lion King video game I bought a what is called a haul
off of you about another gaming system McCarrie well yeah but about the haul is not the system I
bought a game you say a game gear okay this is this was Sega's foray into the handheld market
remember game it's great it's a I never had one so it's great so a guy for a hundred bucks
was selling a fully functioning game gear which is hard to come by because these are notoriously
have rotten capacitors in them okay that need to be replaced he had a fully functioning
game gear which is very hard to come by that plus all of these games for a hundred dollars it was
such a great value and one of the games was the Lion King video game but believe it or not those
Disney games from that period are actually very good Craigslist McCarrie McCarrie is my new favorite
site to buy stuff on McCarrie is eBay without bidding okay it's just you buy it and the prices
are usually very fair you great contact with the sellers why McCarrie who's gonna remember that
I don't know it took me a long time remember it but I've been doing it for a while now I wish I had
the guys info in front of me it's like when when somebody calls a movie like earth you know like
you go to Google earth you're never going to find that movie why do they do it well people don't
think there's a there's a philosophy in in marketing that if you give it a weird name people will
remember it all right you know look Twitter what the fuck did that mean when it came you know what I mean
sure it's like but you had a little bird mascot that helped not really I didn't make that connect
I know it was the egg in the beginning I didn't understand what the fuck again bird related
Twitter it has nothing to do with birds it does what doesn't there's a bird mascot tweet tweet
but tweet tweet wasn't a verb back then it was just called Twitter and you were like what does
that mean you know what I mean I made the connection I made the I doubt that you did I did Pat why don't
you take us on down to the to the movie corner I will because I know you're gonna run your mouth
about God knows what well let me do some documentaries today I'd like to start it's on Hulu it's
called minding the gap this is a porno film no Joe absolutely fantastic documentary it's done by a
very young man my guess would be like 18 or something and he spent his whole life shooting him and his
friends who are skateboarders in rockford which is like Chicago where cheap trick is from
and they're skateboarders and at first it's like okay this is going to be one of those
dog town and z boys thing where we learn about like the beauty and the power of skateboarding
and I was not interested but little by little this thing becomes deeper and deeper and you basically
watch as all of his friends and himself become men you know some quicker than they should this guy who's
like 18 with a lot of issues knocks his girlfriend up and there is a cycle of abuse you know the the
guy who's doing the documentary was abused by his stepfather he confronts his mom on camera why did
you let this go on a friend of his who you think is like the sweetest funniest guy in the movie you
learn is beating his girlfriend and the mother of his child obviously the guy doing the documentary
has some questions about that as a guy who was beaten it gets deeper and deeper and more intense it
builds to you know a credit sequence that had me in tears a great song choice that I will not spoil
for you but it's such a good movie and it's on hulu I recommend it strongly minding the gap
alright I'm gonna go comic book okay on this one I watched half of the DC universe exclusive
original series swamp thing canceled already by the way it made me not finish it yeah because I was
like well it's just canceled why do I want to potentially get more in love with this right now right
canceled like as it's premiering you didn't make any sense I don't understand because it is
excellent it must have been spiked it must have been some sort of spiked cancellation where somebody
pissed somebody off it's excellently directed and produced and acted it's just so well done and it's
the first time I feel like they've really truly captured swamp thing and what it is and what it's about
and they barely scratched the surface of this universe and what it unfolds into I mean this thing could
have got into eventually justice league dark and you know they're like they barely bring in one of
the swamp thing villains the fluoronic man yeah you know like like Abby arcane's in it but her
uncle is not in it yet and he's one of his adversaries and it just could have really
cool expanded into a lot and I think one of the mistakes was I don't think we needed an hour long
episode for 10 episodes I mean these that's my problem with a lot of these streaming shows is they go
way too fucking hard in the paint and it's like guys make eight tremendous half hours yeah keep the
person hooked I'm so much more likely to watch a half hour show you know I like a half hour drama
these days but you do 10 hour episodes you know you got to put in all these B plot nobody cares
like just get in there and get out so maybe that is one of the things that led to it being cancelled
or whatever but I don't know but what I saw of it which again the first five episodes or so
they did a terrific job the makeup is unbelievable the special effects are unbelievable it's dark it's
creepy it's very hard movie you know it's in that tone so if you're a fan of that stuff with DC which
you all know I am this is a great capturing of it and I like what DC universe is doing with that app I
liked it they're leaning into the darker stuff you know team tightened or the Titans excuse me
was dark this is very dark I know some of the stuff on the horizon is you know that this joker movie
which is in theaters obviously looks tremendously dark I love that they're leaning into that stuff I
love that they're leaning into I felt like DC when they do a graphic novel you could really put an
emphasis on the novel part of that term so well I learned more now that Todd Phillips basically
approached whatever the head of DC or Warner Bros. and said look they can do these 400 million dollar
superhero shit why don't we do and it's called DC black or some other side name but why don't we
do 40 million dollar movies using these great characters that we have and using no special effects
of any kind so he says there's no green screen and joker great all effects and of course these are
gonna be the ones I'm much more interested in seeing I don't know that that goes for everybody but for
me that's gonna get me into these movies a lot of DC characters are are much more rooted in that world
which is why I like the DC characters more that's why I've always in DC is a little less
tights and flying and a little more you know lunatic with a costume kind of thing so a little more
hobo with a shotgun yeah yeah you know what I mean anyway it is the best mercy I recommend swamp thing
swamp thing is on what channel it's on DC universe it's a streaming app god how many of these fucking
things are there there's a lot but here's what's great about them and I was talking to my manager
about this you know I'm trying to sell this harm movie scripts right now and he said well where do you
want to go and I said honestly my dream goal for this I want to do a made for shutter original be awesome
let's take this to the place that delivers directly to the fans direct the the concept of direct to
DVD yeah it's finally being executed in the appropriate way it's going right into the hands of
the people that actually care which means now these things are being made with quality and care
shutter absolutely does it right and whenever they premiere something by the end of that day there
are 50 fan reviews of it it's great because people are just waiting for the new one it's great back
in the you know back in the early 90s with a direct to video or direct to DVD it was like you know I love
full moon but full moon had to compete with everything else in the video store right so they have to
cut all these corners budget wise and whatever and they have to broaden it to a certain extent that they
can just kind of put this stuff out there and hope that somebody that may or may not care about horror
looks at it and wants to watch it whereas now it's shutter it's like you only have this service if you
care about horror right so if we're making this revenue off of these people that subscribe we know what
to deliver to them yeah and for them you get de Wallace in it she's the mayoral streak of heart that's
a huge get and these are very gettable people that want to work yeah you know the guy what I want to do
the curator of shutter did this thing and they're like two or three minute genre things it's it's one
of the if you look at collections on shutter I don't remember the name of it but he basically will tell
you what the must -season each genre are and it wasn't really surprising to me a guy who's been obsessed
with movies my whole life but it's such a great quick little encapsulation of like you like which movies
here are the best which movies I just I like what they do I hear their podcasts are awesome I haven't
heard them but it's a great site I mean where else on earth are you going to get the the Joe Bob
Briggs where else on earth are you getting that guy along with uncut versions of these movies that
the academy wouldn't even spit on yeah it's you know right now I want to be right now they have 10
high -quality titles that I've never even heard of in a lot of cases queer horror it's like
what like I didn't even know there was a genre right but I liked that they're all inclusive I like
that when you go into these comment sections everyone is nice and respectful I hated a movie they
premiered a couple weeks ago called party hard die young shot really well but you know as a big shutter
premiere and I'm like yeah okay that one sucked but I'm glad I got to see this movie I had no idea what
it was and they they do really cool interesting stuff and because they don't have a thousand titles
getting dumped on there every month like your other streaming sites right they curate it they
take the time to really care and make sure you're getting good product or at least interesting product
and it only I my it's my opinion that I know well this won't only keep getting better yes as shutter
I hope this doesn't happen I hope shutter doesn't morph into what some of the bigger streaming sites
have morphed into they don't have the money it won't where they sort of be well needed the other ones but you
know you I hope that they never become the sort of the more problematic version of themselves but
even if they did I feel like shout factory streaming is just going to get more into original content or
or night flight is just going to get into more original content or or to be you know any or whoever I
feel like you know this is this is a good place to be right now well the jewel of the crown that might
really set them off is this new creep show that's starting in two weeks I am or starting whenever
so fucking excited and we will definitely be reviewing that for sure I can't fucking wait same here
hope it's good my next documentary is on HBO it is called I love you now die colon the commonwealth
versus Michelle Carter this was a two part three -ish for a shower documentary insanely balanced
considering the subject matter very fair and balanced real depressing and miserable but it's a case
you might have read about a few years back where a girl about 16 convinced her boyfriend via text
message to kill himself so the kid there a couple the boy is very depressed he they're clearly
very in love with each other it hits this moment where he is sitting in his car and he's like I just
want to end it all I want to kill myself and she's like do it do it kill yourself finally he's like
I'm getting out of the car I'm not going to do it she goes get back into the car and do it don't
check it out I'm sick of hearing you say you're going to do it not doing it kill yourself
Jesus and then it's like to what extent is she responsible for this kid's death obviously the family
thinks he she's very responsible but the kid had serious problems the girl also had serious problems
these were two very depressed mentally ill teenagers who should not have found each other because
they really kind of fucked each other up the girl you can't help but hate her even though they
don't paint her as a villain you look at her as just being a really evil person she clearly needs
a lot of attention it touches on the online obsession and she immediately once he dies is like booking
events honoring him and like come to my my town not his town come to my town where we'll have a
celebration of him and she's clearly enjoying the attention she's getting oh dear so it's very
upsetting but to its credit even though this sounds like a clear cut case of this girl sucks I hate
her she should go to jail it really does sort of make you see all sides it's a very rough watch
I recommend it if you like true crime to me there's not much more fascinating than than an issue
like that who's to who's to blame who's at fault very interesting stuff very dark check it out
I have a similar documentary I watched a film called I love you now design that focused on dixie
Carter okay okay much brighter picture that sure one you what is she alive dixie Carter
I think she passed no I think she died a while ago I'll look it up go ahead what you're now my
next one is Gotham by Gaslight again I watched this on DC universe but it's also available you know you
can buy a DVD of this and or Blu -ray and I think it might be streaming in some places else where but
Gotham by Gaslight is one of the coolest Batman comics and this is an animated adaptation animated
feature and the plot is it's Batman back in like the sort of Victorian era okay very cool and he's
hunting Jack the Ripper okay so hence the title got them by Gaslight and he's trying to sell the
mystery of Jack the Ripper and it's just a very cool sort of steampunk Sherlock Holmes style Batman
story that has some famous Batman characters in it Harvey Dent is in it Selena Kyle is in it
Jim Gordon is in it and of course Bruce Wayne and it's just a really fun cool dark R rated Batman story
right you know there's not much more to say than that stylistically it looks great my one issue
with these DC animated movies that I think they do a really great job with them is you know it's you
can tell that the animation is a little stunted it almost looks like it's like a slower frame rate
or something and it's clearly a budgetary limit limit you know limit on the budget that they have
where you know that these things can't be as fluidly moving as like a Disney you know
theatrical release or something but it doesn't buy any stretch ruin the
experience and the voice acting is always top notch so I strongly recommend it this one does not
feature what's this face as a son of a bitch it's not the guy I'm blanking on his name but it's
not the guy from the animated series doing Batman the most famous Batman voice actor but it is
somebody very good who who is let me see a second this is going to try me now but Kevin Conroy is
the one that's mostly in this very mostly you know he's done Batman the most in this one it is an
actor named Jimmy one second Gotham by Gaslight it is I know I'm going to kick myself as soon as I read
this Bruce Greenwood does Batman oh sure oh and Jennifer Carpenter I believe plays Selena Kyle so
I actually recently wonder what happened to Bruce Greenwood he used to be in every movie like
yeah well the Kevin Costner movies and Shen so it's a it's a good watch it's a it's a lot of I mean
fun might be the wrong word it's pretty fucking dark but I enjoyed it all right I'm going to
veer off documentaries for a minute mention one with with some interest for you horror fans called
The Dead Don't Die directed by Jim Jarmoosh independent film legend I have pretty much across the
board always liked what Jim Jarmoosh does he's a little too laid back for my taste at times this is
and I don't think I've seen all of his movies but I've seen pretty close to it this to me was
far in a way his worst I loathed The Dead Don't Die it's got an all -star cast led by Adam
Driver and Bill Murray it's got Steve Bishimmi it's kind of a Maga guy Chloe Sevinney
Selena Gomez etc I I was blown away by how bad this movie was I'm sorry it's one of his biggest
releases because of the cast I think it probably did fine at the box office but basically from the
jump they're talking about Sturgel Simpson who was a country singer -songwriter that I enjoy
they're listening to the song called The Dead Don't Die and he goes why don't we keep listening to
this song and Adam Driver goes it's the theme of the movie oh god so that's right off the bat and
you're kind of like who I didn't like that but then they don't do that anymore so you're like all right
it's a quick little cold -open joke from the movie they listen to this song 800 times and every time
they do it the two characters look at each other and go Sturgel Simpson and for some reason this
started annoying me so much I almost left but basically it's a zombie movie it's in this small town
the people wind up wanting not really brains but wanting whatever they they loved when they died
so like the big joke in the trailer is the Carol Cain zombie is like shawda nay does Carol
Cain have a speech impediment or is that an accent she's got all the slight speech impediment she does
right it's her charm I mean no but I mean that I'm not imagining that right she's got something with
her arm yeah yeah okay you know not not a joke really works the special effects are pretty good
considering Jim Jarmer's I mean like the zombie blow -em -ups and etc aren't bad but really it's
boring as shit and when it reaches the end and I texted this to Joe they say it's it's Brody and
Bill Murray and they're like going what what did I tell you this one Brody I'm not a driver okay
uh let me bring this up I want to make sure I get the line exactly right Bill Murray everybody's
I mean it's kind of the style but my god he's sleepwalking through this thing all of them Bill Murray
everybody else Murray Murray hasn't looked content in a movie and I don't even know how I hope he really
brings it in this new Ghostbusters like some of that some of that Murray charm please right Bill please
so the ending of the movie is basically the moral is we're all zombies you know like like the
ending of all these movies and it's like we're all just consumerists or whatever it's been said
better than ever by George Romero right don't it's said in a much less effective way but the ending of
this comedy gets very serious in somber oh and it's basically because there's like a maga theme
running through it and it's basically like the world is ending blah blah blah but then as the zombies
are attacking Murray and driver are kind of trying to fight him off and then driver goes this isn't going
to end well and Murray says you keep saying that how do you know and Adam driver says I read the
script oh god damn it and Bill Murray goes you got the whole script Jim only gave me my scenes what a
dick oh boy Jim this is the only other time they do this why would you do that Jim not only not only
does he do it but he includes himself so like he's breaking the fourth wall but it's also like
aren't I cool Jim Jarmish much like many of my cinematic heroes George Lucas
Spielberg fuck off throw Polanski on the pile not good at comedy as soon as I try to be funny like
you're funny referencing yourself yeah I never like a fourth wall break unless it's your style
unless it's Ferris Bueller to shave the humor you know for for the Kevin Smiths of the world
or or or the Todd Phil or whoever please just don't you don't do a comedy this and this is five
minutes from an ending that attempts to be unbelievably serious tonally off serious tonally separate
from the whole rest of the movie they're cracking wise about how what a dick I didn't get the scene
there was maybe ten people in the theater and every one of them went you just heard this like
collective sigh and groan I think it's one of the worst movies of the year and I hated it there we go
all right I will go documentary for my final entry here all right life after flash flash Gordon yeah
to the scene flash Gordon do yourself a favor all right it's I mean it's campy as hell
but do yourself a favor it's a really fun watch and do it on the Blu -ray because the Blu -ray
puts this whole new sheen on it where it looks insane it's almost like you're looking it's almost like
if you were looking at like if they were doing like the most tremendous special effects ever on
on the set of mom's family like it is so clear where the Blu -ray makes it look too good so you see
the faults it's so clear but it looks awesome for some reason do yourself a favor all right yeah life
after flash and it's about Sam J Jones who was the guy that played flash Gordon discussing basically
how this movie was supposed to be the big break and it didn't happen and then you see it from all sides
told through all different people that were involved in the movie half the people without the movie go
I felt sorry for for Sam he got a raw deal yeah the other half were going the guy was a complete
fucking arrogant asshole and he burned his one chance to make it uh I found nothing up lifting about
the film I found no hope uh it's got an 88 % on rotten tomatoes which I'm surprised about because to
me I just felt like we were just trudging through a man's bad experience well that's I love a movie
like that maybe I'll check it out it made me really sad but at the end of the movie why does he
consider himself such a failure I don't think you're making your life off of one quasi successful you know
you know I don't think the movie was I can't remember if it was or not but I don't know more with less
on this down I'll tell you that much it was kind of supposed to be you know like I saw Brandon Routh
talking about this recently about Superman Returns and you know he he's done other things and he's a
level headed guy that movie just didn't work out right so he's coming back to play Superman again
in the DC TV universe because they're doing like an alternate timelines thing where they're
gonna have multiple super minutes spacey back as uh look little spacey's not bad okay uh
so but but Brandon Routh was like I'm just delighted to be coming back he goes you know when I got
Superman Returns I thought all right here we go I'm just gonna do this forever now he's like
clearly not the case right but you know he went off and did other stuff um you know but but you
don't get that and I didn't get that impression from Sam Jones like I got the impression of
it was supposed to be the big break it wasn't it didn't turn into a franchise uh and then he was just
also he was not an you know it was going to his head in all the wrong ways and it just didn't work out
now the one thing I'm happy about is he can still go to these cons and sign a zillion autographs
and people are very excited to meet him right he does seem appreciative of that he's also extremely
religious now which I guess helps you know yeah good you found something yeah for you um but not a
pick me up film uh anyway what's that on prime I think I saw it on prime I don't remember it might
have been on Hulu um anyway uh let me do a quick scary stuff and then we can keep it moving here
to our movie um very fast scary stuff today uh I did myself a favor recently the other day at amoeba
records I bought the Star Wars original DVD trilogy there was a limited release of a of the Star
Wars trilogy we're on the first disc of each movie it was the special edition from that time
which have been altered even further now for the blue raisins the most recent blue raisin and then
then the second disc as a bonus feature was the original theatrical cut transferred straight from
the laser disc um I hadn't purchased these yet I had bootleg versions of them I had the original cuts
on video and I thought finally let me just buy the actual best available versions out there because
I'm such a Star Wars fan right I bought them if you find the right version of this trilogy meaning the
one that's not in the tin box the tin box was a best buy exclusive it gets a little pricey but if you
find the the the right version of this trilogy which there aren't many versions of it um you can get
it for 50 bucks or something like that I paid 50 bucks if your Star Wars fan do yourself the
favor I watched Return of the Jedi last night or two nights ago for the first time in its original
with its original edit and it was a fucking joy it brought me back to being a kid again because
they're the DVD because they're the laser disc transfers they've got pops and fucking
film flaws in them and it adds this whole graininess to the experience and it just took me back to seeing
Star Wars as a kid again um the aspect ratio is an issue you know because they're in widescreen but
they were in widescreen for your TV for your fucking tube TV so if you're watching it on like a 4K
TV like I have you're getting a picture in the middle of the screen you know with lines on all sides
but if you go into your zoom feature or whatever you can stretch it out and it it doesn't harm the
picture that much like it's it's still a fun watch um it's just exciting it's exciting when you turn it
on seeing Lucasfilm limited at the beginning and just green hellvitica text fun you know like like
just the little touches like that that you forgot about are enjoyable and uh it's also awesome to see
return to the Jedi once again without a song and dance number in the middle of it and I'm not a
hater of the special editions I didn't like what they did in return to the Jedi that was the only one I'd
problems with but um do yourself a favor as a Star Wars fan grab yourself one of these for 50 bucks
because it is a finite product as my friend Mike Burns often says about these things we all like to
collect I mean there aren't many copies of this out there that people are willing or wanting to sell
so if you can grab one grab one I think it's worth it Kathleen Kennedy has repeatedly said she's
not gonna touch the original trilogy because she's too afraid of what the psychotic fans might do she
phrased it more eloquently than that but but anyway do yourself a favor and grab that and let's get
on to our film well I got a scary stuff oh I didn't okay you usually don't I'm sorry uh also I guess
I'm allowed to say I had a meeting at Lucasfilm you do I've been I had one oh you did
yeah for what sort of a general meeting and it was it was very cool to be there that's all I'm
gonna say I had a general back in the day at Dreamworks yeah and that was cool because you got to see the
Indiana Jones posters yeah I you know I I think I signed an NDA so I'll stop there but uh it's
yeah it's one of those places where you you're like you just sign in you're like okay and just put your
thumb here it's just indicating you'll never speak about this meeting again yeah yeah okay um real
quick I actually have a scary stuff that works uh I read a book called The Man Who Heard Voices
or how M. Night Shyamalan risked his career on a fairy tale and lost there's this about the
lady in the water the lady in the water the disastrous Giamatti's lucky he got it that far I know clean
Jesus Christ I saw and hated lady in the water like everyone did I read the book and now I need to
watch it again but there are so few of these types of books and it's really my favorite kind of book it's
a shame that most directors very wisely don't give a writer access because what goes on behind the scenes
of a TV show in a movie most people don't want to get out I assure you but uh it is a day one you know
Shyamalan trying to set up the script he's coming off if you'll recall six cents unbreakable and
signs three massive hits and he's like just three cramps yeah and he's like here's the next one so
anyway can I get about a hundred million for it and the executives read it and they're like hey uh
night uh we got a couple issues with this one his feelings are so hurt because he is the golden boy
you understand why the feelings are hurt he does not come off like some sort of pre -Madonna he's just
oh shit it really gets into the self doubt of being a creative person and it follows it from trying
to set up the script to casting to shooting it to the release and then it obviously not going
doing what he wanted it to do but it is so good it's comparable to the devil's candy which documents
the making of Brian de Palma's bonfire of the Vanities that is another amazing book documenting
the warts and all process of making a movie but this thing I think is pretty much out of print I
don't think Shyamalan or the studio loved how they all came across in it but it is and it's very
worth it's like big debut she's lucky she skated out of this fucking thing that could have Sofia
copalowed her and now for six years man there's so many little details you know like Shyamalan says
to Jimati he's like hey so it looks like you're putting on a little weight and we're about to
start shooting so maybe if you just want to rain it in a little and it's the one time Jimati comes
off as anything less than a hero in the book he's just like man fuck you he's like this is why
I don't do this you wanted Brad Pitt you get fucking Brad Pitt like he blows up at what you get you know
to Jimati's playing a plumber in a fuck it's like let him who cares if he's 400 pounds exactly
it is just a terrific book I got it on Amazon used for five bucks you can do the same
you like it's like I said they used to do this kind of thing in terms of DVD special features
but you never got the warts and all but they'd track a movie from like inception to sure to being shot
this book really gets gets behind it gets under it I recommend it strongly okay
uh let's get on to our picture which is Ari Aster's mid -Summer let's get into it buddy boy
Joe and I already had kind of some battles about it one thing I would like to share a quick
personal anecdote I a buddy of mine had a baby and hasn't been out of the house since and I was like
hey man 4th of July 10 am I'll I'll meet you up there real early we'll meet halfway in the valley
and see a movie it'll be fun get you out of the house we go up there we sit down pack theater
as the opening scene of this very tense movie begins the giant valley earthquake took place
it knocked the projector out of focus for the first 15 minutes of the movie and people went
fleeing from this theater screaming I did sort of a half stand half sit like what's going on
but it really upped the intensity level of this movie I assure you it's a shame that that couldn't
have happened during the last hour folks uh listen mid -Summer by Ari Aster uh it must have an
opposite writer and creator of hereditary which we've discussed on this show you know our thoughts
already we don't need to revisit it masterpiece uh not a masterpiece uh far from it not even a good
movie but let's move on master pit mid -Summer uh you got a movie here about a woman who is in college
I think it's grad school I believe they're all in uh she is uh going through an emotional the
spoilers plenty coming ahead this movie's been out two months you got uh she's going away or she's
going through an emotional time because her sister who is bipolar has killed her parents and herself
uh with deeply unsettling opening scene incredibly unsettling uh which hits the gas on her
already shaky relationship with her boyfriend he's about to break up with her he already doesn't
want to leave her stranded or hanging because she's going through a tough time then this murder suicide
thing happens and he's like well now I can't leave her which is a bad decision right uh they
trudge on both their parts and they sort of both just sort of trudge through this relationship
they end up going as a uh sociology uh for a thesis experiment or project whatever they go away
to this to this place in where does it take place in Denmark where is it or Austria or something
I it was shot in a different place than where it was set so I forget but they go to one of those
everybody's blonde and blue eyed places yeah and it's always sunny the other ones yeah uh for the mid -Summer
Festival that happens once every 90 years Sweden Sweden that's right which happens once every 90
years we'll come back to that detail because that makes zero fucking sense um and things go awry at the
festival uh starting with her having a bad trip on mushrooms as soon as they arrive we pause to say
a super realistic portrayal of what it is like on mushrooms in a very cool way yeah and let's
I want to come back and go through all that I'm not I'm not skipping it uh I just want to get through
the synopsis things go awry and things end poorly uh it's go awry went where things I would say
truly start to become like what the fuck are we doing here there is a ceremony in which
well wait a second don't don't don't let's go back to the beginning of the film all right no that
I don't mean to be pushy but I just mean like I want to talk about all this stuff and because to me
this is all important sequence um so let's go back to the beginning of the film as you said a very
disturbing sequence of a murder so as apps are fucking lootly this movie starts brilliantly
yeah brilliantly that entire build -up from her worried about her sister to the tension between her
and her boyfriend to the sequence of the cops going through the house and finding the the
the fixated parents and the sister with the tube taped to her face with the vomit all down where
you can see she threw up as she was killing herself and then the camera pushing out to the blizzard
outside and the music starts a 24 percent I was like holy shit here we go yeah that sequence like many
others in this movie like many others in hereditary are what to me make any sort of nitpicking about
this guy sort of in consequential because I just sort of look at it as how it made me feel for two
and a half fucking hours and I don't think anyone any horror filmmaker is as in command of the medium
right now uh as as are yester so well that's why it's a shame that he fucks it up every time
and I I completely disagree and maybe if I watch this five times I'd see that I'd see the the seams
but all I know is for two and a half hours I was just fucking riveted on the edge of my scene
I will say this about the movie and we can go through the reasons why yeah for the first
90 minutes of this fucking thing I was in I found it riveting I found it interesting
I found it completely tense performances are great the most it was one of the most intense films
I had ever seen for that first 90 minutes Florence Poog who's the lead is excellent as a girl going
through a lot of trauma will uh polter who was the kid from we're the millers uh I had no idea
he was not American but I guess he's British he provides some really funny comic relief the movie
is surprisingly very funny at times I thought uh yes go on uh first 90 minutes an incredible experience
last hour unnecessary unnecessary it becomes exhausting after a while as hereditary did
how much of this woman screaming an agony do I have to watch how much of it how much by the time
they're dragging her out of witnessing her boyfriend fucking the other women in the ritual which by
the way okay let's let I don't want to get ahead of myself first of all let's start about why it
makes no sense that this thing takes place every 90 years there's a big suicide scene the elders of
the town are jumping basically off a rock to their death yes horrifically graphic horrifically
graphic scene that had people leaving the theater and them without the earthquake an amazing scene
portana note on all the 70 years old these people are 70 years old all time horror movie scene I would
say a classic these people are 70 years old yes that's important therefore it makes no fucking sense
when they say no no this is what we do when we turn 70 that they're fucking festival
takes place every 90 years and they're impregnating women at the festival it should take place every 70
years first of all second of all well if you're not at the festival what do you do at when you turn
seven well real quick I didn't think that because I didn't have that thought you might be right I
would be surprised to be missed that plot hole but oh he misses he this guy is the king of missing plot
holes couldn't they have the festival every 90 years but do this when you turn 70 thing all the time
they don't do it all the time it's part of this festival for sure yes and they go when we turn 70
we release ourselves before we get all the way it's like okay so when it seems like quiet and oversight
when you're at yeah welcome to Ari Aster's world of film it didn't occur to me in anywhere hereditary has
shit loads of these shit loads of oversight okay the one I'll call out right now because that's not
diverting to it is Gabriel burn for no apparent reason catching on fire when she throws the thing
into the fireplace it makes no fucking sense he does this all the time so so so right off the bat
it's shocking great it's tense great doesn't really make sense also the people with no face because
they bashed it on the rock yeah becomes less shocking when you show it eight fucking times after that
and they keep showing it over and over and over and over and over you know like I think it is added
to the horror of the scene and you're like I get it this is disturbing you and I will always have
this battle horror is not a genre I need to make perfect sense I go for feeling I go for mood atmosphere
and I think his movies have that in spades in my opinion when you don't have logic behind it it's the
expendables okay so and here's what I mean by that somebody that really gets off on what it takes
to create a brilliant action sequence in a movie yes we'll watch the expendables and go what a
fucking picture and you go no it's not what a fucking picture it's a bad movie with a lot of killing
and explosions in it they'll go no no but two cares that you're focusing on the wrong part do you
understand what it took to shoot that boat sequence where there were the eight and I go I don't give a
fuck you're you're you're I didn't like any of the expendables and I don't understand the comparison
at all you're dealing with how neat a movie is at this point with with mitza how neat a
bases the entire base the entire value of the movie on we actually made that car do a corkscrew
through the through the air that's an impossible thing to do that nobody else is doing and it's like
okay well I appreciate that how it's not a good movie I'm following this lesson less with each
you how can you not be following what I'm saying it makes perfect sense what does this have to do
with a hell need a movie what I'm saying to you is is what are yester is great at is shooting
sequences that work very well in a genre what he is not good at is storytelling he's not good at it
I would say this tells a even more what I mean certainly more clear and concise story than her
editor it's clear and concise it doesn't mean it was well told and it's not concise for an hour
at the end of this fucking thing I mean how many times are we gonna show the visuals of
everybody's on the drugs get it how many times are we gonna see them sitting at this fucking table
and talking and discussing things how that dude that's tension building I mean to me were you tense at
the end or were you just you there was no party with the end of this movie you're like get to it they're
gonna die they're really they're really wasn't and like at the end when you know when he's running out
naked when there's probably still a half hour left to go at that point I just kind of sat the entire time
with my jaw sort of open watching this thing in in disbelief at how continuously intense it was
from start to finish I did care about the people in it much more than I almost ever do at a horror
movie I cared about all of them I loved how the relationship was not painted in 80s teen movie
tropes of this guy's a fucking asshole he was at times comically insensitive and people would laugh at
that but also like they didn't say he forgot her birthday he he didn't notice with the the
changing of the sun and all that if it well he knew it was her birthday they kept it fairly balanced
granted he was not there for her a hundred percent I don't feel he deserved obviously what he got
at the end being trapped in a bear costume and burned alive but these two were clearly not right for
each other I like the balance in that relationship I thought this movie had a lot to say about relationships
it made me look at my own relationship and the question of does this person feel held by you are
you there for that person oh yeah maybe go at what times if I not okay I get I get all that I get all
that but when there was a lot going on I get listen I'm not saying there wasn't but when you jerk
yourself off with every single shot in the movie it becomes a fucking masturbatory experience by the end
of this thing by jerk off a ship hold on let me finish has a bunch of amazing shots let me let me finish
let me finish when you draw out everything by the end of this it was overkill by the end of this
thing when she sees him fucking the woman during the ritual right I don't feel sorry for anymore when
she's screaming and going I don't feel sorry for you dummy you know who this is we've been down this
road get the fuck over it get out if you want to you also are trying almost cheating on him with the
other dude I no longer feel bad for you I no longer feel bad for the boyfriend by the end of this
movie you you're I'm over both of you I'm over both of you right now you've put yourself in a
weird situation you refuse to get out of it and you get what's coming to you there were the audience
was cracking up I'm talking like caddy shack level cracking up at that fucking orgy scene it was so
absurd it was supposed to be funny it was it wasn't supposed to be funny Joe the director himself
views the movie as a dark comedy and many reviews refer to the movie as a comedy that was not see
it as a comedy I was very disturbed that was not supposed to be funny Joe she walks up behind him
and is pushing his butt into her yeah supposed to be funny it's not supposed to be there's an old naked
woman pushing his butt into her I felt like he got way too into into the into look at look this is
the ritual man in and and they're singing man he even said he he said himself in an interview he goes
I try to make everything operatic and maybe I get a little too indulgent sometimes that says it all
not for me that says it all this is a guy that knows how to shoot and I've said it a million times
on this podcast you want to fucking shoot pretty pictures go make music videos you want to tell a
story make me say I want to see this again and I don't ever want to see this again there is no
part of me that would ever sit through this three hour fucking extravaganza ever again it's the movie
I will watch numerous times and come back to I will I'm gonna keep tabs on that one because I don't
believe that you will it was uh easily my favorite movie the year if not then it was tied with our
our previous uh review once upon a time in Hollywood but I a movie that I found way more indulgent than
this and way more sort of lack of daisicle with its pacing and plotting than her retic. I gave a huge
fuck about her retina and I think if you look at it you can look at it in the summer wait wait wait wait what
what was more indulgent than this I thought you were saying Hollywood but yeah exactly oh
oh god there was a point by the end of it there was a fucking point he didn't have he didn't do and
there was a payoff this thing and no payoff at the end it was just fine that insane I find that
insane what did you find was the payoff why did they need to sacrifice nine of their own to the gods
why did they say to the guy you take this so you will have no fear and no pain and then their own people
had to fear in the pain of the bad guy or family did her family wanted uh basically abandoned her
in her mind her family is now all dead the person that is supposed to be taking care of her and looking
out for her does not care and is not not the right partner for her so she finds family and love
and relationship and happiness in this cult I got all that I got all that and she's done with this guy
and killed that's the payoff of the movie I got all that 45 minutes before it happened but I think it's
also a commentary on how people stay in relationships way longer than they need to until they're actually
willing to kill each other as opposed to just breaking up and ending the relationship by the way
oh sorry I'm sorry you know I think that's a part of it I think the reason it's it's dragged out is
like I bet a lot of people who saw this movie are like I need to break the fuck up with my girlfriend
or boyfriend what am I doing and I think there's so much being said by this movie and I think
oftentimes you get bogged down in the minutiae or this doesn't quite add up and maybe I'll watch it
again and agree with you but that won't matter to me because of how I felt for two and a half
full hours when most of the time I go see a horror I just watched not at all okay I saw it 10 am
okay I was I was not bogged down in the minutiae it's the same reason why I don't like 2001
it's too fucking long and too self indulgent and after a while I go please just get to it
because I'm not in an art gallery right now I'm not here to look at pretty pictures a little bit
of that is fine tell a fucking story and get to the point I think it told an amazing story with lots
of horror lots of comedy lots of commentary lots of drama lots of you know it had everything I really
would have wanted for me but I get what people would say it's a little long whatever but I think that
sort of these long takes of you going what the fuck is going on I think puts you in the mindset
of the characters in the movie saying what the fuck is going on everything listen everything for the
most part was answered I I I'm not saying I have problems with a little with details here and there
that to me take a my problem with the details of the end of what the how the drug affects their own
people versus how it affects the guy they hate my problems in that scene are not this doesn't totally
add up so it's going to ruin it for me my problems in that scene are this takes away from the poetry
of the ending now it takes away from it that's that's just my opinion my beef what the hell is it
is going to say my beef with this movie is and with this guy's movie and I said it to about something
about the Johnson's which I liked that was Arias short film yeah which was 30 minutes in and out
fucking beautiful but I will say this about every one of his movies and I challenge you to defy it
if you take the shock out of it you don't have much of a fucking movie you don't the guy is graded
conveying shock but you take something about the Johnson's you take out shots of that guy having
his dad suck his own dick the movie becomes a very thin boring movie where you don't really care about
the characters is shock that's not true that's not true horror is giving a fuck enough about the
characters to want to see them prevail in the situation which I 100 % did the exorcist has very
little shock considering what it is the exorcist has a tremendous amount of shock jacking off with a
crucifix in a 12 year old that's one scene that's one thing is I bet if you asked a hundred people what
is one of the most shocking movies of all time 90 of them would say the extra but that's one scene that's
one and then puking and that there's a there's so many scenes that are shocking in the extra
do you I think I think I think it is a concise story and I think it's got a bit of shock and I think
if you took that shock out of it here's the here's what here's how it would make that argument if you
when I the first time I saw the exorcist I saw it on the edited for TV version scared the living
shit out of me if I saw any ariester movie edited for television I wouldn't give a fuck well why do
you think that you need to compare hereditary are I'm sorry mid summer right to the best horror film
of all time why can't you compare it to the piles and piles and piles of shit horror that are dumped
into theaters flushed into theaters every single week I why do you have to hold it up to the exorcist
and I feel like you do this a lot you don't look at it in terms of I'll compare it to unfriended
dark web and say that this guy has a lot more going on with what he's doing why does why if everybody
likes something does it have to be compared to I the all time just because something is self -indulgent
doesn't mean I think it's good I don't like bad movies period so to me I'm answering your question you
thought was a masterpiece for 90 minutes you think is a bad movie I think it's not a good movie when
you have an hour of exposition and boring bullshit at the end of your film that yes that hurts
your movie 100 % it hurts your move well I disagree I mean I was let me answer your question let me
answer your question what you're saying to me right now is if you hate Burger King I eat dark web
whenever the fuck unfriended not a terrible movie by the way why don't you like the gourmet thing
well some of the gourmet things I do like what ariester is to me though is the guy that
carves a radish into a little fucking swan and then goes look and it's like okay dude you know how
to show off you know how to make something look pretty at the end of the day do I want to eat this
dish or not and at the end of the day a lot of the time in a five star restaurant I don't want to eat
the dish but on a horror movie podcast Joe what what horror movies do you feel are coming out lately
that can come anywhere near hereditary and midsummer in terms of somebody just giving a shit
and putting it all on the screen okay Mandy which is not a horror movie really oh yes it is stop it
I mean it's more of a horror movie than this is no it isn't yes it is
Mandy has supernatural monsters in it yeah it's far more of a horror movie I mean it's it's an
action movie I would say and this is more of a drama with very shocking scenes you can point to one but
like I just don't get how you can't look at it in terms of a scale of horror movies and say
clearly this is one that is significantly better than most but you have to compare it to the
all -time best I think the guy because I because everybody is sucking me while if we watch like some
Netflix can I answer any question or can I answer a question yeah when you watch one of these Netflix
things where it's like okay this is probably going to be a D and it's a C you're like hey it was
pretty good actually surprised me do the same thing with comedy all the time your expectations are
aligned in a weird way I knew you're gonna hate midsummer as you walked into the movie you're
texting me about how you're gonna talk you're just gonna keep talking at me go ahead you're just
gonna keep you get so fucking condescending with this shit it's unbelievable I'm just saying no it's
very condescending I'm trying to understand it's trying to understand you don't sound like you're
trying to say it sounds like you're saying you're wrong and you don't get it that's what I do think
you're wrong and you don't get it but I'm not totally get it every but that's what everybody says about
a movie when they like it and the other person does it you don't get it no maybe you just like dog
shit how about that no I don't know how about that I thought Gerald's game was a better fucking hard
movie than this was you know why it got to the fucking point it had the moments of shock it had the
moments of scary it had the moments to be going in like I'm gonna see this hereditary and it's going
to start I'm gonna say wait or once upon a time in Hollywood walked out saying it was one of the best
movies I'd seen all year okay I just don't know why you do it what do you mean why do what why you walk
into a movie like this is going to suck I that affects your obviously I went into enjoyment of the
movie doesn't I went in saying if this is another hereditary I'm gonna be disappointed for the first 90
minutes I said I was wrong about this guy this is incredible the last hour I was like this is a
bunch of jerk off bullshit I'm fucking bored I want to go home every fucking scare in the movie by
the way was lifted from another horror movie guy wearing a face on his face Texas chainsaw massacre
stuffed dummies with with skin faces Texas chainsaw massacre hitting the guy in the head with the
hammer Texas chainsaw massacre it's all fucking lifted and then people come along and to me it
becomes like the Beatles versus pet sounds where everybody goes the Beatles the greatest they did this they
did that did it and it's like but nobody's ever acknowledging pet sounds nobody stepping back and
kind of calling well guys can we all calm down to quote you can we all just calm down when you saw
the the the bad the super bad remake with the two young girls and you go look it was fine can we all
just calm down and stop talking about how this has redefined the genre it hasn't and neither did midsummer
and the reason I attack it is because everybody talks about this guy like he's the the next coming
a fucking Scorsese and it's like well god damn it Scorsese knows how to tell a story and a great
example of what I'm talking about is in once upon a time in Hollywood I got more out of Brad Pitt's
conveying of I'm on acid then I did an Ariaster's showing it to me this entire movie the shit is moving
in front of you and it's doing this and it's doing that and he just keeps doing it over and it's like
buddy I got it you figured out a cool way to show you people what mushrooms looks like by the
30th fucking time you've shown it you're just showing off at this point I'm bored I'm bored that's
fine I I cannot understand your anger about this movie it makes no sense to me at all my anger is with
you saying that I don't get it I get it I just I think you you'd enjoy things more just not like
like you saying this whole he's not reinventing the genre walking in and saying if he doesn't
reinvent the genre I'm going to be mad no is not a way like you're you're looking into the reviews
and expecting something that this movie doesn't have to be he's not but you do the same thing
you do the same exact thing okay I don't know what you're talking I'll tell you exactly what I'm
talking about let's talk about the time you walked out of suicides squad and said Jared Lido should
be shot I'm done forever with superhero movies remember when you said that I do I don't why are
you screaming at me right remember when you said I hated the movie suicides squad remember I
hated this movie I didn't go you don't get it you did you said you don't get the DC world or
what you always about that man versus Superman but I I'm not you're jump at the pet sounds in the
beetle you hate the beetles I don't know what's going on you do know what's going on I'm making a
counter -argument to your argument you have said to me why do you I'm saying why do you expect this guy to
to make the best or what do you expect him to change the game I don't expect him to what can you
just go in and try to I don't expect him to when you're telling everybody's telling me that's what he's
doing and then I watch it and go okay here are the flaws with it and people go nope nope nope nope
no flaws it's like well I'm not saying it had no flaws I'm saying I didn't feel that I was
riveted by the movie you don't like when I go to the reviews you go to the reviews all the fucking time
when I trash aliens when I trash Cameron your first defenses this is a beloved movie people think
it's the best so you know let's let's I'm just saying it's a good backup you know but people
also loved mid -summer and loved hereditary okay so that doesn't mean you have to doesn't mean
that's backing up my argument but you act like everyone's crazy for liking something I don't act like
everybody's crazy I think everyone and myself included when a movie comes to you like for your
consideration you look at it like all right I'll consider this you know when I think a better way to go
would just be to walk into a movie and see what happens that goes for everyone it's not a personal
attack on you I think this is Art House bullshit what do you want for me just because it's Art House
bullshit doesn't mean I have to think it's better than Nightmare on Elm Street I don't think it's
better than it I don't find it more entertaining but I don't know why you can't look at the genre of
horror and say this movie has so much more going on and so much care and so much just you know passion
being put into this movie when we watch shit after shit pet cemetery whatever you know terrible
obviously terrible but you can't see that mid -summer is a million times better than pet cemetery
you can't say I love 90 minutes of a two and a half hour movie that's not nothing in this day and age
I don't I don't agree with you I don't agree with your approach to that you said it about you said
recently about a comedy movie you saw there was one big laugh out loud moment at the end and I go
pet you told me this was a pretty good movie and you go for me these days with comedy that's
enough for me that's not enough for me a few big laughs in a comedy these days is enough to say it's
a better than average comedy that's not enough for me I don't I don't think that's great or ideal but
mid -summer is a movie that puts so much time and care into it it's not doing the jump scare shit that
you have a problem with it's doing what you seem to be asking for a week after week on this podcast
I don't know what you're talking I don't know what you're talking about with that but I don't
have a problem at all horrors jump scares it's all jump scare yeah and then you see a movie that's
all about mood and tone and and creeping dread and you don't like that either that's all I'm saying
this movie is at least trying to give you what you say you want every week I am listen I am
grateful that a guy like Ari Astur is out there doing his thing I think that he is a talented man
but I think he does one thing very well and then disregards a lot of the other aspects of a movie
to me that make it a good movie now for instance I will compare him to this guy whose name I constantly
fucking forget to what's this guy's name you're holding the DVD I know it's not on the back it's
like S Kevin something or I don't know what is it the drag to cross concrete Zoller Zoller Craig Zoller
Craig Zoller makes movies they have an intense amount of shocking violence in those movies yes
however the story moves I give a fuck about the characters at the end of the movie I don't feel
that I wasted any time I feel satisfied I say I want to see that again these are the boxes I
tick for a good movie you know I love drag to cross concrete I think everyone I've spoken to
including people that loved it thought that movie went on way too long well we didn't we didn't
that's true I don't care with those people thought I'm saying what I thought right so it annoys me
with with Ariaster Astor is and it's not just you it's it's everybody I've discussed this film with
the second you go thought it was too long I just didn't like this but really oh come on dude
they're entitled to that opinion as well all right as am I it's condescending it's like this this
guy is flow Joe if I wasn't bored for two and a half hours that's not condescending that's my
opinion of the movie which is as a valid as your okay fine but here's my I'm not saying you're condescending
I'm saying that the attitude towards this guy right now is he is flawless and perfect and I
don't agree with that that's that might be some that's not even my attitude of man I love him I
think the guy is the Paul Thomas Anderson of horror right now and and I'm including the flaws of
Paul Thomas Anderson who can be a self indulgent filmmaker but I'm saying he is a guy who is trying to
make his brand of movie hereditary and midsummer are different but they are other piece and it is a
director who is really trying to do something cool and interesting and exciting I praise him for
that at a time when no one is trying to do anything let me ask you this I think that's a great thing
let me ask you this you take out the shots of the severely deformed in bread person you take out
these which there are five okay you take out the shots of the people hitting the face on the rock
you take out the shot of the guy beating the guy with the hammer you strip this thing down to all
implied horror or implied violence and implied shock without seeing it do you still give a
fuck about this to me it works just as well I didn't need the you know the shoving it in my face
of people having their face exploded or whatever else I was shocked by it I agree they went back
to it several times and I especially felt it because I was watching it in front of a man in his
seven -year -old daughter so I was watching it like a parent almost like what the fuck is this girl
doing here and looking at it in a more like puritanical standpoint than I would have I mean that's also
to me I was I was just like in that which I consider the best scene in the last five years the long
party scene in her red it's here and I know you disagree with me where it all building up to her
getting her head knocked off and the ants on it and everything else I was so tense that I didn't
breathe for about 25 minutes that alone is enough to give this guy credit as a great shaper of horror
a great creator of mood of tone of scenes and I think midsummer held it for the full two and a half
hours to me it didn't kind of lose it as hereditary did when they went up into that tree house I was
riveted the entire time and the shock cuts had nothing to do with that for me I when I think about
what's memorable about this I think about the emotional terror the horror the pain the loss etc I'm
not thinking about somebody having their face blown up on a rock I want to hear your review after
another two watches because one thing that you will do with movie sometimes is you'll go that's
a classic and then you'll go I rewatched I think it's terrible that can happen if I'm higher drunk and
rewatch it I saw this at 10 am I also think an earthquake happening in a seven -year -old sitting next
to your certain qualifiers for a movie going experience within this type of a seven -year -old wasn't
helping my enjoyment of the movie but I say I think it I think it ramps up like oh my god from
stark to finish the tension that to me that had nothing to do with this the uh you just said it
Mandy I tried to watch it a second time with Heather and liked it significantly less because I watched
that high and that's the way to watch Mandy because everybody in the movie is high I like Mandy a lot
less and I think the seams of that movie really showed on a second view all right visually it's
incredible but it's got some problems I will gladly watch mid -summer again hereditary I thought I was
going to watch again and found myself not wanting to go through that experience again and I think
that is also pretty impressive that's what horror is supposed to be and so rarely is that you come
out and you're like I want to see it again I don't know if I have it in me to watch it right now the guy
is making movies that put you through the ringer and there's no other horror happening that's even
remotely exciting right now so I don't know why he wouldn't be praised that's not true that's not true
his as I said about a quiet place which we disagreed about and then you saw the second time and
said it wasn't as good quiet place or to say the scariest movie of the year I said no it's the
scariest movie that's been in theaters there's a big fucking difference there's a ton of good horror
going on right now that gets that gets completely overlapped even with a thousand problems with it
on a second viewing quiet place is a great example of fun just spielberg type mainstream
but I haven't seen anything on Netflix or anything else or shutter or whatever else that can
compare to this for me personally I liked I liked 19 what ever this feelberg I mean there
the Stephen King adaptation was better than this I put light years between the two so it's just a
difference of a pen the and I would never watch that movie again 1920 whatever I don't even remember
what it was about somebody getting buried alive it's about a man killing his wife yeah the strain of
the relationship between him and his son the haunting you know it's it's a lot of sort of similar
themes it that that movie I thought worked but that's that's a good example for me of a movie I go
yeah a little more craftsmanship than your average horror movie so I'll say it was fine this was to
me somebody doing something on a completely different level I think that the guy is a great filmmaker
he's one of a few people where I'm dying to see what he does next and I also don't think we can
really judge the guy or his whole body of work off of a short and two future films well I mean
I don't let look I will admit this very openly I don't like being told who I'm supposed to admire
that bothers me so when a guy comes along and everybody's going this is the second coming of God knows
who or whatever it pisses me off and it annoys me I will admit you mean critics or you mean friends
or you mean everybody everybody right now it's just a ball wash with Ariaster it's just a complete ball
wash and but he's it's a me he feels deserving well but you can't in the same breath you're saying
we can't judge the guy off two movies in a short and then in the next breath you're saying he feels
deserving so so which is it that's what I'm saying it's like it's like I'm reacting to people saying
that this is a beautiful perfect five star movie and I'm saying no it's not it's got a lot of issues
and people just are overlooking those issues with the with the excuse of or the justification of
well it's better than that and it's like well that doesn't mean that it's good saying it's better
it's like that's that's that's me trying to understand you that's me trying to understand your
your anger and point of view about it is it's it's not anger I'm passionate not look at it in terms
of the state of horror how I'm looking at it is this is the best horror movie I've seen in a very
long time and and I don't even I don't even consider a second place right now I want to be clear
that it's not anger it's passion I get passionate when I talk sure it's not anger not angry that
I already asked him not angry at your opinions of him I do get passionate when I debate these things
what I'm saying and it's really the same thing for aliens is that okay I think these movies are
unquestionably great and in an attempt to understand what you're saying could you compare them to the
state of horror and not say okay this is much better I'm just asking can you do that and oftentimes
you can and I'm just trying to figure that out here's why I can't because a movie for aliens is
going to be a tough example for me because I'm not a huge fan of the movie and don't you think you're
harsher on a mid -summer than on almost anything else because people like it so much I'm harsher on it
I will admit that I'm harsher on it not just because people like it so much yes but also because of
what the director is trying to do and when I see a guy going look how good I am at this it's
annoying to me honestly that to me that attitude does not even cross my mind watching either of these
movies I think and in interviews he seems like a humble dude he seems like a normal dude fine fine
and so so does it you know I look so can so can anybody it doesn't mean you know right I'm trying
not to why not why not try to make the best movie you can make I don't why do you see that is
showing off like good fellas for example is a show off when you come in and you know it please good
fellas is my favorite movie of all time it's show off you boogie nights is show off look at all these
crazy scenes I'm going to have people talking to the camera at the two hour mark I would I would just show
off I would I would well I guess look I guess at the end of the day to me by the way this guy came in
with a three and a half hour cut of this fucking thing I'm going to watch the three hours that's going to
be my next viewing good enjoy yourself it's it's know your limits man that's it know your limits
you can't tell a good story because you spend too much fucking time dicking around tell a good story
chop 45 minutes out of this fucking thing you would have had a nice picture on your hands
and you didn't because instead you want it to fucking be self -indulgent and keep going and going
and going and be operatic as he is admitted to and you know what I don't want to sit through a
fucking opera either for the same reasons I don't want to see it I was also two and a half
hours so Spirio worked for me this didn't I don't know what to tell you okay so Spirio got so Spirio
got very similar praise to this now and I went into so Spirio thinking I wasn't going to like it
if you recall when it was in theaters I said I refused to go see this because I keep being told
you're stepping inside somebody's vision but so Spirio I think the the last the last 15 is what
makes that movie really pop yes so why not look at the first 90 of this being amazing as
something to commend because as opposed to the ending not working because here's the difference the
when the last 15 or 20 minutes whenever of a movie works yeah in the case of once upon a time of
Hollywood in the case of Spirio which I compared to you the other night when that works which it
doesn't both those movies what happens is is your finale suddenly justifies the rest of the picture
when it's done right okay and in those two movies that's what happened in those two movies the
finale justified everything you had seen leaning up to it and then you walk away going back playing
back and going oh my god yeah oh oh fuck oh yeah oh shit oh oh yeah what this guy has done twice
now in his movies is according to you it well according to a lot of people and the one criticism of
I'm sorry I shouldn't say a lot of people but the one criticism I've heard of hereditary and this
guy has done it again with this movie is man really comes out swinging when they finally explain
everything though it's a little bit dumb and same thing in this one it's like dude I knew where this
was going I know where it's headed get the fuck to it get to it it's just like with us I don't need
this third act of you you go into the underground facility and here's the explanation of what the
government was doing keep it with you on that but nothing in us worked for me including the ending
this this for two and a half hours worked perfectly for me I thought the ending was right in line with
what it was but if you're saying that a movie can be not great for two hours and then if they land
the last five minutes then then it's a movie that works for you or that's how I'm saying I didn't say
I didn't see not how I feel I feel like if the first time I work in the last half hour doesn't
I'm happy to have seen the first that's not what I said I said what I said was is in
Susperia when your finale works properly suddenly it has justified everything else you've sat through
and it redefines it it reframes it that means that the first 90 minutes does work so the ending is
very important to you is extremely important and to me when you don't botched ending if everything
else is great I'm like all right and when you don't land an ending to me what it does is it unjustifies
the entire thing I just sat through well why was I here why don't you shift through all this
that's just a different way of looking at movies if I'm if I'm super happier on the edge of my seat for
90 minutes and the last half hour is a whiff I'm like I'm glad I had that 90 and a lot of that's
because movies are so terrible but you know I actually win because I have AMC movie pass now and I saw
the fucking three hour and 15 minute Avengers movie you know that's the sort of movie that makes
you go all right I can appreciate somebody being a craftsman and trying to make something special
it didn't work for you it worked with a vengeance for me it worked in ways horror doesn't even always
work for me where it had me thinking about my life my relationships I had a huge connection to this
movie I loved it and you did and that's fine I think there's a bridge I think there's a gray area
in filmmaking and when you find it with certain filmmakers it works brilliantly I think
Dupama, Scorsese, Woody Allen at times yeah Tarantino I think these filmmakers are people that
understand the value of popcorn cinema and also understand the value of art house cinema first I think
they bridge the two very well when one person or filmmaker goes far two in the direction
in either direction I don't like it so for me Ariaster it might as well be Troma I'm bored oh I would
I'm not I'm not into it I go okay well that effect was kind of fun and cool but this is not
enough for me to ever go back and watch it again I would say just like once upon a time mid -summer is
a a perfect blend of both and I think that judging by the audience I saw it with which was screaming
and laughing and clapping and everything else the big mainstream horror elements worked and these
people wound up seeing an art film too in a way that I think he bridges that gap a lot better than say
David Lynch and I love you know I love David Lynch but or nowadays other than drive Nicholas
winding Reffen you know he's doing art films at this point and not connecting with his audience
in any way I think Ariaster is definitely doing both he's freaking people out while also being
artistic and and more power to him I think he do he sued himself to to pay a little more attention
to logic be weary maybe his next movie we'll do that weary of the plot holes a bit and that's that's
just my and and higher of editor I don't think there was any scene and I you know I loved every scene
of it but I'm looking at it from a average Joe standpoint I don't think there's any scene in a
red itary that is sort of more draggy on a necessary than watching margo roby watch a movie that she's
in for 20 minutes or that wasn't for 20 minutes watching there was a total of four minutes watching
de caprio shoot a scene that and I get the reasons and I enjoyed both scenes but mid -summer I did
not think had anything like that that was just sort of a did not need to be in the movie enjoyed
seeing that dance the full dance contest you enjoyed watching I did higher dance contest in horror that
rhythm that long that long feeling of what's gonna happen here you've already watched the terrific
things this dance contest is spiraling out of control and you're like what's gonna happen and sometimes
when nothing happens that makes when something does happen much scarier that's a a tactic of horror
that I've long enjoyed all right I love the movie I think the two best movies of the year are the
first two we reviewed back on this podcast I think one of the worst movies in cinema this year is
mid -summer one of the best is once upon a time in Hollywood and and so real quick you can say I
love 90 minutes but also that it was one of the worst movies of the year when some movies are 90
minutes I'm being inflammatory all right I'm breaking balls all right look again it's it's it's it's
like they say with comedy and I don't agree with necessarily with this critique when it comes to comedy
but it is the one we all go to when a joke works it's funny when it doesn't work it's not funny and
it's offensive okay yes I wasn't offended obviously by mid -summer but my point is this it either works
or it doesn't work this didn't work for me as a whole and for me to want to watch a movie again it
has to work as a whole sure that's it right and and I can see a movie with a botched ending and
if everything else is in my opinion fucking fantastic I will watch it again but I don't think this
movie botched anything I think it's a much more confident assured piece of filmmaking then mid -summer
then's then hereditary gotta keep mixing them up but I'm not mad at you I'm not mad at you
did you think I was mad at you I get loud but I'm not mad at you it's fine
I come from a family of silent rage and and ignoring you I get very passionate about this stuff
but I will say I did look but I as do why I mean I I could talk about both these movies for days and
I think that alone is enough to say yeah here's a here's a movie that means something if you can
argue about it great how many times do we talk for five minutes about a movie and go anyway I'll tell
you what if you want I'll tell you what first ever on this podcast first ever we both rewatch mid -summer
right separately I'm gonna watch the three -hour cut together please don't make me watch this we don't
have to but I'm gonna watch it but we both rewatch mid -summer and we do a part two to this with a
review because maybe I'm being too harsh because I get annoyed that everybody goes this guy's brilliant
you should love him and then I go oh fuck you you know what I mean yeah I mean like I would
get that if somebody was saying that about a comedian for you but like movies you're not trying to
to be a filmmaker you know well okay I just mean you know you know what I mean look yeah look I just
I'm thrilled for the guy I I don't I can't wait to see his next movie and I can only say that about
people who have been around since I was in high school in any walk of life I don't like when people
tell me this is the guy to watch it bothers me it bothers me and stand up it bothers me and acting
it's why I don't watch the golden globes I don't care if it's a sitcom right don't tell me that this
is the show you know when you tell me that suburban housewife or whatever that fucking show is
is gonna redefine the way I step into comedy yes I get pissed off I get annoyed so and that's all
I was trying to press you on earlier is like good because you saw him in summer opening day and
your text to me were like I'm gonna go watch this piece of shit and I'm like well Joe look I I wanted
to see it I want an hour in each direction to see it yeah you know I I didn't not want to see it
I was excited to see what it was gonna reveal and to see if I would be wrong and look I said the
I don't I don't need to retread I say we leave it at this first ever on this podcast we do a
re -watch separately or together maybe we do it together great and then that way you can go see as
long as I can be sighing throughout I won't sigh throughout but then if we watch together you can
go see that works for this reason and I can go pack come on that didn't make sense okay and maybe
we change each other's opinions a little bit I was so riveted the ninety seventy thing didn't even
add up to me that seems like too big a plot hole for a guy to miss but maybe he did I don't know
I I find that there's a lot of that in his movies where I go look all three I'll say this in closing all
three of his movies have ended in a way where I was like even the thing about the Johnson's where it
was just the mom just kills the son and I was like I think a guy's college is hard to count as part
of his film I don't think that was his cut no he did that that was a much later short for him okay I'm
not shitting on the guy but it's the thing that got him all of this would you agree he the man
is a skilled filmmaker up to a hundred percent and in terms of creating that tone that mood
which eludes so many horror filmmakers he's got it in spades if he and if he matches that filmmaking
ability which I feel he did with midsummer you disagree if he matches that with a story like
let's say a story that's as powerful as that first 15 minutes of this thing I don't know if I could
stand to sit through it I a hundred percent agree with what you just said or the first part the
second part about I don't know if you could sit through it I don't know because I haven't seen it
but I'll compare him to a guy that I love and I'll take a shot I love David mammoths plays I love
them I think he's got an impeccable skill for writing dialogue right sometimes he completely fucking misses
it and gets in his own ass yeah and you're watching two men talking about ducks for an hour and a half
on a bench and you're like Sam Shepard is the same way where you're like Jesus fucking Christ buddy
please yeah and these are these guys are visual stylists in any way that's all I'm saying I'm saying
it in that sense I do not deny the man's talent I would like to see him stick the landing for once
and get it in under two and a half fucking hours that's all yeah anyway that's our show Joe
DeRosa comedy on Instagram watch Joe's comedy central shorts you let me down yeah I forgot about
there's very funny thank you I am the Patrick Walsh on Twitter and Instagram occasionally and that's
about it we'll see you never get on with the again we forgot it so now we're getting on with the show
and on with the Joe we back next time with something you know we're gonna do Annabelle we're gonna do
Annabelle we're gonna do the new child's play and also sort of along as we did with pet cemetery sort
of put it in the context of the whole franchise I recently watched child's play one two three and
the remake and those are things to look forward to hog house page on Etsy the hog house for merch
thank you all we'll see you next time we'll see you in hell