I'm here for Bet Rivers Online Casino and Sportsbook with poker icon Phil Hellmuth.
And now, thanks to the excitement of Bet Rivers, I'm also a slots icon.
That's great.
And a same game parlay icon.
Cool, cool.
A blackjack icon, a money line icon, a roulette icon.
Take it from Phil Hellmuth.
If you love games, Bet Rivers is the place to play and bet.
Bet Rivers.
Games on.
Must be 21 plus and present in West Virginia.
Void were prohibited.
Terms and conditions apply.
Gambling problem, call 1 -800 -GAMBLER.
The football season is full of guarantees.
And here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the Fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October.
If your football bet loses, you'll earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with Fanatics, you're either winning or winning money back in fan cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to Fanatics Sportsbook.
Winning hits different here.
Must be 21 plus.
Gambling problem, call 1 -800 -GAMBLER.
Offer not available in all states.
Terms apply.
See Fanatics Sportsbook app.
Hello everybody.
Welcome to another edition of We'll See You In Hell.
The podcast about horror movie commentaries.
Not about them.
Where we do them.
And then you can watch the movie along with it if you want.
How shitty would that be?
A podcast about commentaries.
We review commentaries on horror movies.
I'm Joe DeRosa.
I'm Patrick Walsh.
And we're pleased to be here doing this podcast.
Now part of the Fangoria Podcast Network.
For more information about the network, including other programs, how to follow this show,
other shows, find episodes of this show or of other shows or past episodes or whatever
the hell it is.
Visit Fangoria .com.
Let's get down to it.
Today's movie is Hellraiser.
Just a technical note.
I am on one side of your head right now.
Pat is on the other.
We do that so we're in separate ears.
So in case you do want to watch the movie along with this commentary.
The movie sort of goes up the middle with us on either side of you.
Stereo sound.
I'm on your right.
Joe's on your left.
Very good.
We are aware the past couple weeks I have been mixed too low.
That'll be corrected this week.
They're already saying it's corrected.
Terrific.
It's already corrected.
Also, we are now available on iTunes, which was a question a lot of people had.
You can download it, subscribe, review the show.
Give it a nice review would be great.
We're starting out.
Be very helpful.
If you have questions or movie suggestions or recommendations or things you'd like us
to discuss on the show, you can tweet me at ThePatrickWalsh or Joe at JoeDeRosaComedy.
That's right.
Now, in this little preliminary bullshit talkie period before we start the movie Hellraiser,
which is what we're watching today, now's the time for you to get on your device,
get on your Netflix thing and find Hellraiser as we talk here and hit play and then pause it
as soon as the picture comes up so we can start it all together in a few minutes here.
Pat.
Yeah, Joe.
Can I tell you what I did this week?
Please do.
Masturbated into a cup.
Okay.
Explain.
Went to the urologist, had a prostate issue.
Nothing serious.
Relax, Pat.
I know how you worry about me.
I didn't really care at all.
What was it?
What was the issue?
I mean, we don't have to get into all the details.
I take a step forward, you take a step away.
That's the dance.
Prostatitis, which is a very mild prostate issue.
Look, it's probably prostatitis, we just got to make sure.
You got to go do a urinalysis in a semen culture.
Not crazy about them calling it a semen culture, by the way.
We're living in a semen culture.
That's what I'm saying.
I hear you.
So I'm like, okay, I got to go to one of these places and
you go into the room and you masturbate.
Sure.
I even asked a friend, I go, what do they do?
Can you bring somebody?
And she goes, you can bring people in if you need to.
Anything to get that nut into the cup.
Uh, this woman with the, uh, speaking kind of with the
language of the street.
Yeah.
Well, she's from the street.
Okay.
Uh, as am I, but, uh, anyway, I go to this place, this clinic.
It's a suite inside a building filled with different suites.
All kinds of offices and different businesses in this
place.
I go into the, I go into the clinic, the lady puts two cups
on the counter.
She goes, the bathrooms down the hall to the left, meaning
the public bathroom.
She wants me to go whack off in the men's, the common men's
room.
No, I thought that was a crime.
First of all, that's what Pee Wee Herman went to jail for.
Yeah.
It's no different being in a men's room.
I guess if you were to blame it on the clinic, they, you
would be in the clear, but that's not cool.
That's not legal.
Let me ask you this.
Even in a stall, it's not legal.
Who's able to whack off in a men's room?
No visual stimulant, no lube.
If I tried to whack off in my own bedroom with no lube or no
stimulant, 90 solid minutes easily.
And your bedroom doesn't reek of a businessman shit.
Businessman shit floor cleaner.
Right.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, I do.
There's not a hand dryer blowing just on repeat.
It just doesn't stop.
Somebody hacking a loogie into the sink.
Yeah, it was insane.
So I brought it home.
I brought the cup home and I, I whacked off into it at home,
but I had to use lube.
So now I'm worried.
I'm going to, my urologist is going to call me and be like,
we got to talk.
Yeah, there's aloe in your jizz.
So you definitely, I don't think should have done that.
Well, I didn't know what to do.
How do you do it?
Can you whack off without the lubricant?
I've never used it, to be honest with you.
I can't do it.
I don't love the direction this podcast is heading, but I don't use it.
Why?
Never have.
No, no.
Why don't you love the direction the podcast is heading?
It's just like, Hey guys.
And then we're talking about whacking off into a cup.
Yeah.
Well, it's what I did this week.
No, I'm sorry.
Is this too low brow for you?
Maybe, maybe it is.
Maybe it is.
I was going to talk about, you know, the work of merchant ivory productions,
room with a view, Howard's end.
Okay.
Nope.
No cup jizzing in those films.
The piano.
I once stayed up to watch.
They made the piano.
Yeah.
I like, I don't think they did, but I love the piano.
They didn't, but Harvey Kitell's penises in that you call that art.
No, definitely not.
All right.
Thank you.
Uh, what was the, I guess it was a room with a view and I used to, uh, stay at my friend's
house and I would stay up even after he went to bed to watch the nudity on cable.
Cause it was my only way to see nudity.
And it said a room with a view starting next, uh, nudity PG 13 for nudity.
And I was like, Oh God, I watched two and a half hours of this thing.
And then I see Daniel Day -Lewis running naked down a hill into, into like a river.
Wait a second.
A room with a view is that's a Hitchcock film.
No.
What room of the view is a Daniel Day -Lewis British version of a view to the kill of you
to a kill you to a kill is a James Bond movie.
Rear view window mirror.
Rear window.
Rear window is what I was thinking of.
Jesus Christ.
Yeah.
Anyway, the point is I'm up at like five in the morning can barely open my eyes
waiting for this nudity.
And then I see Daniel Day -Lewis is bare ass flopping around in a swamp.
How long are you going to take you to finish to DD?
It was like 10 minutes because I don't use lube as we discussed.
All right.
Let's start Hellraiser.
You should be all paused up by now and all set to go.
I'm going to count to three and then say play.
And we all hit three.
We all hit play when I say play one, two, three, play.
Now we're rolling.
Here are your opening graphics.
Do you have any stories about masturbating into cups?
Sadly, I do.
When I first moved LA, I had no money and I decided I was going to donate semen.
I got, I got a trash can here full of liquid gold.
All right.
Because you want to create a life with your semen.
Yeah, exactly.
So this, this jerk off is going to go jerk off to create another jerk off.
Exactly.
So I drive out.
I think it's funny.
It's really a strong joke.
I said it to Pat before we started recording and he didn't like it.
I think it's a funny joke.
I thought you were kind of trying it out to see if it was worthy.
I gave you a firm no and here it comes.
So I drove out to Westwood and I go to this kind of shady looking clinic
and they did have rooms, almost like peep show booths that you'd go in and play a DVD
to jerk off and like made, made very sure you didn't touch anything in there.
And I go in, it's a very attractive Asian nurse and she hands me a cup and a DVD face down.
And I'm thinking, well, it's probably going to be like playboy wet and wild.
Yeah.
Jenny McCarthy.
Right.
And maybe Olivia Newton, John.
Or like they'd give you a sports illustrated swimsuit edition or something.
And I get back in the room and the DVD is called jam it all the way up my ass part two.
Which I was shocked by that in a doctor's office.
This was the material they give you.
And what if I'm not into that, by the way?
Anybody's into that in that situation.
That is a high pressure masturbation situation.
They're giving you filth.
Yeah.
They're trying to get you right to it.
It was really rough stuff.
And I I'm in there and I'm thinking, I don't want to take too long
and ever think I'm perving around.
Well, that's why she gave you a jam it all the way up my ass.
They don't want you slowly making love to a fucking and Nicole Smith video.
Sure.
With a with a soft focus.
Right.
I'm also thinking I don't want to come out too early and have her be like, oh,
this guy in case her and I make love later, I guess is what I'm thinking.
She thinks I come to.
Can I tell you the worst case scenario?
Yeah.
You're in there forever with the jam it up the ass video.
And this she's out there thinking this guy can't this guy's real demented.
You just can't shoot it out for nothing.
You must need something far darker.
But I came out, I handed to her and as I'm leaving, she was Mr.
Walsh, we need the DVD back.
And I had been so nervous that I was just carrying it with me.
I was ashamed.
I brought it back to her.
Can I can I make a joke here?
Yeah.
Were you carrying it or was it stuck?
That's good to your hand.
No, I washed my hand.
That's a jizz joke.
No, I got now we're into the movie.
It started or in Marrakesh or something.
Yeah.
Indiana Jones is sitting behind these people at a table somewhere.
Terrible dubbing.
I watched this last night and especially in that scene.
It's like I think the guy was speaking his native tongue and they dubbed in like
they didn't want to do subtitles or something throughout this movie.
There's many instances where the dubbing is way off.
Yeah, it's a low budget film.
They did what they could.
But we've got I would say our main antagonist, Frank.
Many people think the antagonist of this film is Pinhead.
It's not Pinhead.
It's Frank.
And he is toying with the box.
This is actually exciting for me to watch.
This is the first time in movie history that you ever saw the box happening on film.
They went on made nine sequels to this movie.
I believe it was.
And this is the first time you're actually seeing the box.
They all involved the box.
Yeah, yeah, the what?
How did they never make a hellraiser porno about the box?
Well, now I always thought easy.
Maybe they did.
We don't know.
You call it a ball hell dick razor.
Something like that.
I don't know.
Ball drainer.
Yeah, ball drainer.
I always thought that Pinhead's name was hellraiser when I would see this at the video store.
And saying tell everybody how recently you thought that too.
About a year ago.
I thought his name was like Jackie Hellraiser.
That's embarrassing.
The only thing that worse that would be if you thought the monster in Frankenstein was
still named Frankenstein.
No, I've learned that.
Now, Frank just got hooks in the skin.
He opened the box.
Hooks came out.
Evidently hurt him.
As we're going to see in a moment here that he's been ripped to shreds.
Yeah.
And this poses my one question about the Hellraiser franchise and the workings of the box.
These guys obtain the box to explore the heights or depths, if you will, of pleasure and pain.
I've never seen one person get pleasure in any one Hellraiser movie from the box.
Every time they open it, immediate hooks in the face and they die.
Is what we're supposed to believe that they've chased the erotic eyes for so long.
The only thing that can get them off is true pain.
I don't think it's that.
I think it's that they've sunk to such a depraved, immoralistic level
that they are willing to play with this box.
And then the twist of fate is you die immediately.
There is no winning.
It's a trap.
I know this part where there's this skin all over the floor.
It's really gross.
They're kind of fingering through it as if it's crawfish.
Yeah.
Like they're fishermen that just brought in like a load.
Oh, so that's him.
I didn't even put that together.
God, I'm dumb.
So for those of you not watching, Pinhead just put a face back together on the floor.
That's clearly a clitoris cut type thing he's doing there, right?
When he was supposed to believe that's like a fingering move.
It's how you open the box.
This movie is super sexual.
All right.
But let's just let's just glaze over the dumb thing you just did.
Okay.
We just watched a man get ripped apart by hooks.
And then Pinhead comes in and puts a face back together on a floor,
riddled, littered in ripped up flesh.
Pat didn't know that that was the same guy.
Well, I guess it's because you only see the hooks going into his hands
and then he's just kind of vanishes.
I didn't really connect.
Oh, literal Walsh, we call him.
I am too logical with things.
You have a poster on your wall of Hellraiser, so you must love it.
I love this movie.
I love the second one.
I am a big fan of the fourth one outside of that there.
I'm not too crazy about the the other entries into the franchise,
but that poster up there that I have on my wall is the original poster.
It's not the original meaning.
It's an original.
But that's the original poster before Pinhead became
the sort of mascot of the franchise.
Right.
As you can see, there's a frightening clown on it.
And there's not a clown in this movie.
No, there's no clown in the movie.
It's signed by Doug Bradley who portrayed Pinhead in all the movies,
except one of them.
And I heard that the casting search for a guy with all those pins in his head
just went on and on and on because it's hard to find.
I mean, and this coming from the guy that knocked my jerk off,
making a jerk off routine.
Now, when I got that poster signed, some of the cast was there.
Doug Bradley was there.
But this lady was there that plays Julia, the stepmother, the wicked stepmother.
And it was weird meeting her because she's so mean and evil in this movie.
And she was so charmingly lovely in real life.
She got such a kick out of being the fans.
These like this couple is not in the other ones.
Now, I assume is another is one of the future ones like set in Pinhead's world.
Uh, Hellraiser 2 delves into it.
And we should do Hellraiser 2 at some point,
because Hellraiser 2 is the best entry in the whole.
Really?
Franchise.
Hellraiser 2 is awesome.
OK.
Hellraiser 1 is great.
But Hellraiser 2 is really.
I really wanted to be out of Pinhead's world when I was in there.
I didn't like watching it.
I was watching it before bed.
I didn't like it.
Disturbed me.
I had nightmares.
He, to me, is one of the, I mean, to most people, I would think,
you know, he's definitely one of the great horror icons of all time.
But he, to me, is the coolest of all the famous movie monsters.
And I'm a huge Kruger fan.
Jason's awesome.
Chucky.
Why not?
You know, I like them all.
The alien.
You know, everything's great.
But to me, Pinhead is the coolest because he's so elegant.
There's something.
He's very Darth Vader -esque.
Yeah.
Well, his sidekicks are the freakier ones, in my opinion.
There's that fat one that I despise looking at.
Do you know what his name is?
No joke.
Pudgekins.
Butterball.
Butterball?
Yeah.
Okay.
Look at that.
Maggots.
Real maggots.
It's really gross.
I remember.
You ever have a maggot experience?
Oh, yeah.
You want to hear about it?
I guess.
I had one myself.
I mean, it's not that much of a story.
I flipped over a piece of meat and there was a ton of maggots on it
and I screamed for 25 minutes.
I had a horrible apartment.
Where was the meat?
I came home from the grocery store, set it on the counter,
went about my business, not for a long period of time,
and I came, picked it up, and had maggots all over.
Well, that was bad when you bought it then.
Yeah.
Oh, absolutely.
Well, I used to go to the Vons at Melrose and Vine, my apartment,
which at night they enclose in giant black bars like a prison.
Oh, good.
So they always had the most high -quality meats to choose from.
Welcome to Hollywood, kid.
Yeah.
Close the bars, then go jerk off in that cup for money.
It was a real nightmare.
I had an experience in college.
I lived with two guys.
There you go.
There's your problem.
And one of them was not ever doing any dishes or anything.
So my roommate, Mark, said,
I refuse to clean anything until our other roommate, Jim,
starts doing dishes.
He just refused.
And it got so bad that finally, Mark said,
I'm just going to do the dishes.
Oh, no.
Clean the dishes.
Got to the bottom of the sink, screamed, and ran across the kitchen.
And I said, what?
And he goes, look in there, man.
And I looked in, and there was a half -eaten burrito with maggots in it.
Oh, God, that's disgusting.
Yeah, I started gagging immediately.
Then we yelled it.
Who throws a half -eaten burrito in the sink?
Jim did.
We yelled at him about it.
Jesus Christ.
We yelled at him.
Now, this is Kirsty coming in.
She is our protagonist.
Pat, you know the difference between an antagonist and a protagonist, right?
Yeah, Joe.
I've sold two screenplays to major movie studios.
Oh, look at the big shot.
Now, what is this?
He's fully dressed, having sex with her there?
I didn't quite understand this.
Well, she's looking at pictures of Frank.
She's clearly got a lust.
She had an affair with him.
For this man.
Yeah, well, don't ruin it for the people that I haven't seen yet.
I thought that had already been all right.
No.
Well, nobody's watching this for the first time.
How do you know?
Maybe they are.
But they can't hear the dialogue.
So why would they be watching it for the first time?
Maybe they turn the dialogue up loud.
All right.
Maybe they're doing it.
Let people do it the way they want to do it, Pat.
It's not your decision how they will enjoy this.
Let them enjoy it their own way.
They can, but I can also say that she had an affair.
She was just, yeah, Julia, the stepmother was just looking at pictures of Frank.
And he was weird because it was sex pictures, but he was clothed.
That's why I say it's a sexual film, but I wouldn't call it gratuitous.
There is some butt and a near dick.
Clive Barker just released a book called The Scarlet Gospels, which was.
What he said to be his final installment of the Hellraiser mythology.
OK, and there was a really gross part in it
where a demon made a guy spit into his hand so he could jerk off.
I don't care for it.
I didn't care for it.
I didn't really like the book.
It was too it was too it was it was too like it was too raw or something.
I can't I can't put my finger on it.
Now, here's an interesting piece of movie trivia.
That guy right there, the mover that's moving this mattress up the stair.
Yeah, the swar of the Italian looking guy.
Square is a word we don't really use in this house.
I'm kidding that pin.
But Doug Bradley was offered that part.
He said he said they said you can either play this demon
and it's a cooler part.
The problem is, is nobody will see your face, right?
Or you'll be in full view, but it's just a move.
And a strong decision.
Yeah, he goes, well, I guess I'll just play the demon.
That seems more interesting.
Yeah, of course.
Made his goddamn career.
Well, has he ever done anything else?
Yeah, he's in other stuff.
OK, but once I was in a bar drinking and I looked over
and he was standing next to me and I said,
Hellraiser 2 is the greatest horror movie of all time.
And he said, no, it's not.
No, it's not, mate.
And I said, yes, it is.
He goes, no, Bride of Frankenstein is.
And you can ask Robert England.
He'll agree with me.
OK, I took a swig of my beer and shouted in his face,
take the compliment, Bradley.
And he laughed heartily and took a swig of his beer.
All right.
It was a good time.
This poster you have is a quote from Stephen King.
I have seen the future of horror fiction
and his name is Clive Barker.
I read Ebert's review of this.
Ebert hated this movie and he said,
I guess Stephen King was thinking of a different Clive Barker.
So why did Ebert hate the movie Hellraiser?
He said he can't believe all these people
worked on something so empty and soulless and terrible.
He really hated it.
Really?
Yeah.
And it's weird, too, because he likes really cool
original visuals.
He loved Dark City a lot more than I did, for example.
But I don't know.
He couldn't see the craftsmanship that went into this.
I think they did a really great job with this movie.
My favorite movie review of all time
is his review of Kingdom of the Crystal Skull.
You said that before on one of the podcasts.
I said it on this one?
Yeah.
Well, then all right.
Sorry.
I'm just helping you out.
Jesus.
I didn't know it was with a stenographer.
Get off the weed, Joe.
Or the grass, as Woody Allen would say.
In Irrational Man.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, we both saw.
We talked about that before, right?
Yeah, we both saw Irrational Man this week.
It was Woody Allen's new movie.
And there's a scene where, because it's a good movie.
It's one of his dramas.
I really liked it.
Kind of satirical.
I liked it a lot.
But he's writing for Emma Stone and Parker Posey
and Joaquin Phoenix.
And he's 80 years old.
So at one point, Parker Posey is like,
you should come up to my room.
I've got some terrific grass.
And the whole theater just burst into laughter.
And I can't believe that.
And Woody Allen has said in countless interviews,
he goes, I'm not married to the words.
Yeah.
I just say, get the gist of it.
I don't care.
I can't believe Parker Posey didn't go.
Can I say weed, please?
He was probably scared to be like, hey, old timer.
Then another point, Emma Stone goes,
let me get one of those jazz cigarettes.
Oh, god.
I made that up.
Oh, yeah.
Well, remember the part where Joaquin Phoenix
said, skittily be bought.
And he swung a pocket watch around.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
He was doing that thing where you wag your finger off
to the side.
Yeah, yeah.
This is now Frank is coming into the house here.
We're seeing flashbacks.
This is where the affair for those of you
that don't remember when Pat forgot to say spoiler alert.
I'm going to spoil it if it's going to happen in 30 seconds.
We're showing the movie came out in 1987.
We're showing the flashback here where they meet.
And you can see in Julia's eyes, she
wants to bang brother Frank.
Right.
It's her husband's brother.
I don't go for this spoiler thing at all.
I think if it's last night's episode of Mad Men
and it's Monday morning, you can't walk into the office
and be like, oh, my god.
Can you believe Don Draper kicked that guy in the throat
or whatever?
But if a movie came out in 1987, we're past spoilers.
You can't be upset about it.
I mean, Pat, look, these are your rules.
I'm asking you, what do you think?
It sounds like you're telling me what to think.
No, this started by me saying, what do you think?
I'm telling you what I think, which
if we're not allowed to say what we think,
this podcast is going to really be boring.
No, I think that I think at any time if somebody says,
you know, don't spoil it for me, you got to respect that.
You got to respect it.
But come on.
I agree that if I'm good.
Look, if I, you know, if I if you know,
if I've never seen The Empire Strikes Back, OK,
and then I'm reading a magazine article today
about The Empire Strikes Back, I'm going to expect
that it's going to blow the lid off of some of the stuff for me.
That I get.
But I hate in conversations
because people do this all the time conversation.
They'll go, you know, Top Gun or whatever.
You go, I never saw it.
Don't don't tell me the end.
Yeah.
They'll go, you've had 30 years.
Get over it.
No, that you can't do.
Absolutely.
But you should feel comfortable discussing Top Gun at lunch.
Well, of course.
But if somebody says something, then, you know,
give them the minute to cover their ears and hum,
you know, so they don't hear it.
Goose dies.
This is the part of the movie that I know Goose dies.
I've never seen the film, but I know Goose dies.
I like this move here.
Now, they're about to they're about to consummate their affair.
Uncle Frank and Julia and his his first decision
is to take out a switchblade and cut her nightie off of her.
It's a bold first move.
I mean, but you know, if she stays with you.
Yeah, you're in.
You got to keep her.
But it's a gamble as if she doesn't like the switchblade play.
You might be in some trouble.
Well, she went for it, man.
That's why I look at this.
He's banging her on her wedding dress.
By the way, what's strange to me is he's like he's the kind of guy
who's going to cut your dress off with a switchblade,
but then he's allowing her to just calmly lay down.
It seems like he'd be more of a thrower.
Yeah, he's gently kissing her breasts.
Pick a side.
Oh, this is real gross when he catches hand on this thing.
Spoiler alert.
Yeah.
Well, I like the I like the cross cutting between his wife
getting fucked in the flashback and then trying to move the mattress
and the grunting of the moving.
That's very strange.
The grunting of the sex.
And there's the knife.
Yeah.
And he cuts his hand with the ejaculation, I believe.
This would be the scene where my mom would walk in
if I was watching it as a kid.
And I go, I'm just watching the.
This is a strange thing to admit.
I saw this movie when I was.
Oh, God.
I saw this movie when it came out.
Here you go.
Button near dick, as promised.
With my old tiny bit of dick shot there, just a faint dick shot.
I saw this movie when I was, I think, 12 with my parents.
See, you have a very different relationship with your parents
than I do.
My dad wanted to see it for some reason.
He was like, I want to see that guy with all the nails in his head.
That looks cool.
All right.
And we watched it.
I remember this part made me feel uncomfortable, though.
I couldn't see our movies until I was 17.
And in a PG -13, if there was a couple and they started making out,
if it felt at all like there could be any sex in the future,
I went in and got a drink for maybe five minutes.
I would, like, carefully place cubes in the cup.
I can't do it still.
That's how repressed my family was.
And is.
I can't do it.
I was watching a movie with my mom and dad over Christmas.
And I said, Mom, I'm just going to tell you now,
never admitted this to you, feel very uncomfortable
when anything nude or whatever happens and you're in the room.
So I'm just going to when you see me look away.
Yeah.
It's because I feel weird.
It felt it was such a release to just finally admit that.
And the movie you were watching, Jam It All the Way Up My Ass Part II.
It was Bad Santa.
Oh, sure.
See, that's that's too blue for a family view.
No, it was great.
We had a great time watching it.
I just had to look away during the Fuck Me Santa parts.
Sure.
Show you what.
Gilmore girls that lady now.
I'm not criticizing the film when I ask this question.
What is the rule that the blood now the guy moves the couch,
he cuts his hand or the mattress, he cuts his hand.
He goes up into the room where Frank was killed.
His blood is dripping on the floor and now his blood is going to reanimate Frank.
Yeah.
What is the rule of that?
They don't explain it.
And to me, I thought that was kind of cool.
Like when they when the guy just kind of shows up and you realize he's formed from blood,
I was like, I get it.
I didn't need anymore.
Oh, you know.
Well, excuse me.
Like what are they going to do?
Like have a piece of parchment float up and then like stick to the camera
so you can read about the legend or something.
There's no one here to explain it to us.
So but why?
But then he gets he gets to escape hell through somebody else's.
I guess it's that it's that it's the bartering of souls.
If someone else gives their blood on purpose or by accident, you get to return from hell.
Like but that's what's weird, too.
Now I will think about it.
It has to be in your in the home that you.
You know, like what made his blood bring this guy back because their family
because his heart was under the floorboards.
You just saw it.
How did that happen?
Why was his heart under the floorboards?
I don't know.
But, you know, in horror movies, I'm always just kind of like,
what are we doing now?
You know, I don't care.
Clive Barker has a very different approach than Stephen King,
which is there are questions.
There are more question marks with Clive Barker.
Yeah.
And I like both for different reasons.
Right.
Stock footage of nature, it looks like.
No, that's not stock footage.
That's reverse.
That's reverse claymation.
It just looked really bad.
This was a really awesome effect, I thought.
This is great when his body's coming out of the floor.
And I like this is really cool when his head forms.
It didn't form yet.
This reminds me of the fly.
Yeah.
The Goldblum one.
Or the thing.
And the dog.
The horrifying dog that is possessed by the thing.
It's one of the grossest things I've ever seen.
It's horrible.
Nothing to me is grosser than the fly.
And it's one of my favorite movies ever.
We should do that one next time.
Yeah.
Love it.
It's no, you're grown and big.
Tremendous piece of work.
I like when his head comes on here and forms
and it cries like a baby because he's being reborn.
And I'm trying not to talk over it so we can hear it right now.
But hear the oozing?
No, I want to hear when he cries like the little baby.
Look at this.
So these are great effects.
The slime and the fingers growing out.
This is half their budget.
This had to be half the budget.
Yeah.
Right?
Yeah, it's really great.
Blood coming up off the...
Look at this.
See?
Yeah.
It's pretty cool.
He cries like a baby.
I like it.
Did anyone get when I said, no, you're Cronenberg,
that there was a reference, a lyric from British hip hop artist, The Streets?
I would imagine zero of you.
Not a fan.
I actually love The Streets.
I guess he's done because he hasn't released an album in 10 years, but I love them.
Don't care for it.
Techno beats the rhymes off time with.
Well, you're a very traditional hip hopist and I embrace all kinds.
Hey, can you blame me?
No.
I blame all kinds.
Right into this dinner party scene.
Blame all kinds.
Here's the hard part for me to understand is you got the...
They're at a dinner party now.
Look at these people they hang out with.
They're like the dorkiest fucking Mayberry couple on Planet Earth.
Yet he's married to a woman who fucks with a switchblade.
You know what I mean?
Exactly.
It's odd.
Well, but that's probably what happens out there, you know?
I got a friend back home in Missouri, I won't name any names,
who told me that two different married couples in their cul -de -sac
were having two separate affairs with each other.
And not a planned wife swapping thing.
The wife of one and the husband of another started hooking up.
The other two found out about it, privately discussed it, and then said,
hey, if they're going to do it, we're going to do it, and started having sex as well.
So they both just carry on affairs that they kind of may know about,
but it's not officially wife swapping.
It's not an open marriage.
It's very dark.
Very dark.
Sounds like a good deal.
I guess.
Marriage, man.
Hey.
Some tough shit.
Hey, you know what they say, Patty?
You can't live with them.
You can't live without them.
Wives?
Women.
Oh, well.
Wives.
Marriage.
You know, it's about as big a cliche as you can get, but it is true.
It is true.
I've never lived.
And I'm sure women feel the same about them.
Let's be honest.
We're terrible.
Yeah.
Well, what can I say?
I've never banged a man, so I don't know what annoying things we do.
Well, I could tell you what you do that's annoying.
I don't have to bang you.
I don't see why you would have to do that.
Anyone listening to this podcast can probably name 10 already.
That's that's I mean, I don't even know why you do that sort of thing.
How do you hurt?
Why do you feel the need to hurt?
Hurt people hurt, you know.
It's true.
Jerk offs make jerk offs.
Yeah.
There you go.
All true.
That's a great bumper sticker.
Jerk offs make jerk offs.
Make it make a million dollars.
Million.
Julia now is about to find Frank in the room.
And this part is really creepy.
The way he like scurries up to her.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
He's just like a pile at this point.
It's tremendous makeup.
And it always made me sad that he's the guy that plays.
Frank isn't the guy in the makeup.
It's a different guy with a double.
Really?
Yeah.
Well, that's pretty clear.
I mean, they don't look anything like.
I know, but I don't know.
I want to what is that?
Rats eating puke.
It looks like.
Yeah.
I mean, what?
Here she here he is.
Frank just grabbed her.
And this is very creepy.
Look at.
Oh, look at that.
Look at that.
Oh, it's so creepy.
It's not unlike the sloth guy in Seven, which is a terrifying movie.
Oh, God.
This is just rough stuff.
Don't I love that line.
Don't look.
Don't look at me.
I just grabbed you and chased you across the room.
But don't look at me.
You're a skeleton with a little bit of flesh on your face who just grabbed me.
What do you want me to read the newspaper?
Yeah.
Why don't you just stay in the corner in the shadow and just say, just go.
Excuse me.
And then he says, it's me, Frank, and she believes him.
She just believes him.
Sup, Frank?
We used to get it on.
Watch how quickly she accepts this.
It's me.
It's me, Frank.
Maybe she thinks he just got burned or something, you know?
There's no way.
They don't look much alike.
She already believes him.
How long did that take?
Yeah.
Let's role play this pad.
It's me, Joe.
Pretend I look like him.
Oh, no, I didn't answer because I'm in my car driving home.
You think I'm hanging out with you after that?
It's me, Joe.
You think we're going to go get a hot dog?
No, seriously, it's me.
That's literally what he just did.
Yeah.
It's me.
No, no, no, no, no.
And then he goes, the blood on the floor brought me back.
She's like, yeah, I'll buy that.
Yeah.
All right.
Well, I got to get back to the dinner party.
Yeah.
What else is on your mind, Frank?
Yeah, very, very cool looking makeup here.
I mean, this is this is a horror movie done right.
You got to get a creepy zombie guy coming back to life slowly,
regenerating slowly up in the attic.
That's fucking creepy enough.
Most horror movies that would end there.
But then you got the centibytes coming.
Yeah, they're coming in.
That's yeah, I can't.
I can't imagine that Hellraiser 2 would be better than this because
Hellraiser 2 is awesome.
They go into hell.
Yeah, I don't want to go into hell.
It's awesome.
I had to live my whole life trying to avoid hell.
Hellraiser 2 has arguably the greatest horror movie quotes of all time.
All right.
I'll watch it tonight.
No, I'm not tonight.
It'll be one thirty in the morning.
Want to hear a great quote from Hellraiser 2?
Pinhead goes, but fool us again, child, and your suffering will be legendary even in hell.
Oh, wow.
It's a great quote.
Sounds like some tough suffering, Joe.
Tough suffering.
That was the name of my post hardcore band in college.
We are tough suffering.
One, two, three, four.
Yeah.
This song is called me to do that fake British accent like Billy Joe Armstrong.
You a Green Day fan?
I was, you know.
Yeah, like everybody.
I was in the early days.
Not even the early days.
I stuck with them through all the way up through Nimrod.
Oh, well, that's still the early days.
Nimrod's a really great album.
And I liked warning and I like parts of American Idiot, to be honest with you.
Nah, I thought they were on Sunday is great.
Late Green Day song.
I don't know it.
Now you got this guy, too.
I forgot about this third monster guy in the movie.
This bearded man that's sort of early in it, but it's still it's a third monster to fill
in the gaps between the other monsters.
I like it.
It looks like like if you told me that this was Clive Owen 20 years ago, I'd completely
believe you.
Who her boyfriend?
Yeah.
Kirstie's boy because he looks like Clive Owen like before he became cool.
I'm not getting a Clive Owen.
I'm getting a young Matthew Modine vibe from Jim.
What are you talking about?
I'm getting this man looks exactly like Clive Owen and nothing like Matthew Modine.
I'm saying the wrong guy.
OK.
Who's the guy from Beautiful Girls?
Matt Dillon.
No, the main guy.
Matt Dillon isn't beautiful.
He is.
I'm not saying he's not.
Pat.
Timothy Hutton.
I'm getting a young Timothy Hutton vibe from this guy.
You know, especially when I was an NBC page when I was 23, I used to get on a daily basis.
You look like a young Timothy Hutton.
Look at this.
Now, Julia.
No thoughts on that.
Lying wide awake in bed.
Taken so much by the fact that this guy fucked her so good switchblade style before he died
that she actually wants to go up and visit his goddamn slimy body in the attic.
Yeah, it's insane.
It's nuts.
No sex is this good.
Look, she goes up to see him.
Now.
Oh, yeah.
See, really, this is kind of a similar plot to Little Shop of Horrors where there's this
creepy thing in the basement that needs blood to get bigger and badder.
You know what?
I never put that together before until right now.
And you're absolutely right.
I would have liked to have seen Rick Moranis in the stepmother role here.
Sure.
Rick Moranis being laid down on the bed in a silk nightgown.
Oh, you're gonna have sex with me, eh?
All right.
I guess that's cool.
Are you a fan of Little Shop of Horrors?
It's one of my favorite movies, especially when I was a kid.
I would watch it constantly.
I love the music.
I love Steve Martin in it.
I think he's hilarious.
I love John Candy in it.
Everybody.
Who's John Candy playing in it?
He's just the host of that weird radio show.
Ellen Green.
Everybody in the movie is awesome.
Suddenly Seymour.
What more do you want?
Have you ever seen the original with Jack Nicholson?
I have.
It's not a great movie.
Nicholson's great.
It's not.
Nicholson's great in it.
But Bill Murray in that Nicholson role was tremendous.
It was incredible.
And I think also completely improvised from what I heard.
Really?
Yeah.
Now on Broadway, Gyllenhaal is playing Seymour.
I'll buy it.
I would see it if I lived there, but I don't.
Who's in the Bill Murray role?
That I don't know.
Who's playing the dentist?
Probably Lance Bass or something.
I don't know.
They just did a scary nightmare sequence.
That was freaky.
So he's got a lot of good things.
They keep the freakiness rolling pretty steadily throughout.
For a movie where if you didn't know any better,
you'd think that it was going to be all about Pinhead.
Yeah.
Being like a sort of Freddy guy.
Pinhead's not really in this a lot.
That's probably a total of seven minutes, I would guess.
They do a good job keeping that freaky factor going.
Yeah.
Going strong, which I like quite a bit.
Pinhead scared me.
His associates scared me much more like Pinhead.
I had seen him so many times.
I was kind of like only bothered by the others
that I thought were really, really gross.
Well, The Chatterer is the freakiest one.
Yeah, I didn't.
And then in this, there's that big thing
that runs toward her in that hallway.
That was really freaky as well.
Yeah, yet another monster.
Yeah.
Movies lousy with monsters.
So these are things that are just in hell hanging out?
Are there souls?
Because I didn't get an explanation.
Well, that's what upset me about this book,
The Scarlet Gospels, that just came out.
Before it came out, they were saying
that they were going to really explain the Cenobites are
part of the Order of the Gash, yet another sexual sounding
thing.
But they said they were going to kind of,
or Clyde Barker said he was going to kind of explain
what that was and how they, the history of the Cenobites.
OK.
And it didn't at all.
It's just a story about Pinhead trying to take over hell.
And he's kind of an asshole in it.
And it's not that fun.
Right.
I kind of quit on it halfway through.
Feel bad saying that, but I just wasn't feeling it, man.
Clive, I'm sorry, baby.
I'm sticking with you, but I just wasn't feeling it.
How many?
So none of the movies are, yeah, none of the movies
are adaptations of the books, are they?
This is an adaptation of The Hellbound Heart,
which I have, if you want to read it.
You can borrow it after.
Sure.
Is it faithful, unlike this woman?
Pretty faithful, yes.
Julia's now at a bar trying to find men to bring home
to get their blood so she can rejuvenate Frank.
Right.
Because she needs that dick.
Now, I was thinking as I watched this
and actually laughed to myself.
Now, I put myself in her husband's position.
OK.
So you're a man.
You think you're happily married.
You got a wonderful life.
You're moving into a new home with your lovely wife.
And you find out that she's cheated on you
with your brother, A.
That's like step one, like the most bare bones thing
that she's done.
Sure.
They had hot switchblade style sex together.
Then he dies.
She's so obsessed with him that she continues to go upstairs
and like basically carry on an emotional affair
with his charred remains.
Right.
Then she loves him so much that she starts bringing home
other strange men from bars.
She makes out with them, whatever it takes to get them upstairs.
Then she kills them and feeds them to the corpse
in the hopes of bringing him back so he can fuck her some more.
Imagine finding those things out as the husband.
This is a dedicated woman.
Well, how unsatisfying must their love life be?
I mean, that's the thing.
Is this guy a chump or is she just that rotten?
Who knows?
The way the movie plays it is that she's just pure evil.
She really is.
I don't get why she married the guy to begin with.
I'm confused by it.
Also, by the way, security, she's lured this guy home
from a hopping bar.
It's three o 'clock in the afternoon.
Did you see that bar?
Yeah, it was swinging.
Yeah.
It was swinging.
What bar is hopping like that at 3 p .m.?
I don't know.
Maybe it's a Saturday job.
No, please it's not.
This guy's a businessman that just skipped work.
That was the issue.
You thought strand credibility and hill raiser?
I'm not saying credibility.
I'm just saying, you know, this guy didn't go back to the office.
He's like, I'm just going to go bang this fucking broad at home.
Well, she took him.
She told me not.
Who wouldn't go?
Who among us would you go?
Would you go?
Look at this.
She goes, we don't need a bed.
He's standing in a room where there were rats eating vomit.
He is.
He is drunk.
There's no way that room doesn't smell horrible.
Yeah, there's a slime man sitting in the corner.
But maybe that's a little hidden theme is like guys will do anything
I think that's part of it.
Like the depths you'll sink to for your pleasure.
Yeah.
Plie is part of it.
What is your pleasure, sir?
Plus, I mean, this guy must have thought, hey, I look like Phil Collins.
I'm probably he's probably getting laid all the time.
You know, he's got that weird bald anti bald spot in the middle of his head.
This guy looks like Phil Collins.
This lady looks like she was on ab fab.
Exactly.
I've never seen women in England look like in the 80s and 90s.
This was like this was like England hot back then.
You'd call them all handsome.
Yeah.
Handsome woman.
I'd have sex with this lady.
Look at this big star earring she's got on.
Now, big tall hairdo, too.
Real tall hairdo.
Look at this tidy whitey.
Oh, Christ.
Now, they cut that.
So it looks like he's staring into this man's butthole.
Well, I mean, kind of liking what it is.
It's the room is lit up.
It's three o 'clock in the afternoon.
You got sun.
How is he not seeing the rotting man in the corner?
He's you know, he's drawn to the flesh.
I mean, it just doesn't it doesn't seem likely to me.
He's saying he's got to go pee now.
Too much to drink.
Tend to the old bladder.
The guys.
Oh, this guy, if he could just get out of the room.
Oh, there you go.
Hammer in the head.
Oh, she beats him to death with a hammer.
Christ.
See, they go the terrible way to die.
This movie I've noticed.
They go a little further into grossing you out like any other movie.
It just because she hits him a couple of times with a hammer.
You see his jaw bashed off.
Give it really disgusting.
Give it to me, baby.
Now, she's got this guy's blood on her face.
He could have any kind of blood borne disease.
Sure.
It's in her eye for crying out loud.
Don't look at me, Frank says again.
I just killed a man for you and still I can look at you.
Do me a favor.
Bring me a corpse.
Beat him to death with a hammer, but don't look at me.
Hey, a couple demands and then once you've done them,
I'd also going to continue demanding certain things from you.
The way.
But she loves it.
Whoever played the Frank in the suit crawling around the floor
deserved an Oscar as far as I'm concerned.
It is the most disturbing body movement I've ever seen.
Sure.
What's that thing on the wall?
Oh, I was just wondering that.
Hand dryer?
It looks like the world's largest private bathroom hand dryer.
Yeah.
What is that thing?
I have no idea.
She's looking good, though.
That looks good, though.
That blood splattered on that black lace.
Something sexy about it.
That's a good shot.
Gone Girl did a similar shot.
Uh -oh.
People ripping off Barker, babe.
Although I have mentioned two Fincher movies,
maybe he's a Hellraiser fan.
David Fincher, babe.
I'm doing that's my Dennis Miller.
Yeah, I got.
Yeah, Sarah fan talking over to David Fincher.
Look at it.
She sucked his.
Oh, now she's mortified.
She comes back in and sees that his corpse has been sucked dry
of the blood, and now she's freaked out.
She's going, oh, Jesus Christ.
And they don't really show how he sucks it out.
I mean, is it through the neck vampireish?
In the second movie, they show it.
OK.
They don't show it in this one.
Frank can stand now.
Yeah, this was very cool how this all progressed.
It gets a little more flush on him each time.
Look at this.
That's very good makeup.
Yeah.
And I love that he's constantly dripping, right?
Constantly dripping.
Now, do you think he's in pain?
Yeah, probably all those exposed nerves and everything.
You know what?
Probably one best makeup this year was like The Last Emperor.
Like some movie where they like put like a couple of wrinkles
on a guy to age him over 30 years, you know,
because why would anyone in the Academy watch this?
He the the for those of you not watching, Frank is
he looks like the, you know, the biology book guy.
Yeah, exactly.
No skin.
You see all the organs and he's demanding that Julia come to him
so he can touch her and she let him grab a tit.
Yeah, she let him get a tit grab in even though his skull is showing
because there's no skin on it.
And her husband just came home.
How do you explain this one?
Suck dried corpse on the floor in a in a biology.
Yeah.
Now, imagine he opens this door and she's like, um, so a couple things.
It's not what it looks like.
So I can explain the first.
She's carrying very strange, carrying the suck.
Leave it in the room.
Why?
Yeah, that I didn't get either.
She's taking the corpse into another room.
Leave it in the gross room that nobody goes in.
Yeah.
Oh, hey, could not be sunnier outside.
All of this.
I think she, yeah, she like fakes diarrhea here.
Oh, does she?
The husband, by the way, seems really nice to seems like a great guy.
He's very understanding.
He's in something else.
I can't remember.
He's in another horror movie.
I feel like it's like return to Salem's lot or something.
Okay.
And then she says she's feeling sick.
That's for those of you at home.
If you're ever caught in the midst of a murder, a double bathroom, say you're feeling sick.
Yeah.
Apparently that just gets you right out of it.
And then he's like, oh, I'll get you a sprite, babe.
Like, OK, cool.
And what does she do?
Go out and kill more men for this demon upstairs.
So she can fuck a skinless body.
Yeah.
Does she she fucks him before he's like regular, right?
Um, yeah.
Yeah.
I mean, he's not all the way back.
You got to imagine what does that dog look like?
I'm just exposed.
A big fucking bloody dog, a big bloody old swinging dog.
This guy must be hung like fucking Manowar, man.
But why?
Yeah, you think you could see it, though.
Oh, boy.
Look at you.
I love it.
So she goes into the room to find him, to to read, engage with this fucking abomination.
Abomination.
And he taps her on the shoulder.
She screams.
Right.
When are you going to be done being startled?
Julia, you're in.
You're you're you're waist deep into this.
I would always be startled by the shit dripping up.
Yeah.
How do they make them keep dripping like that?
I suppose right before each take just dumps them onto the top of his head.
God, that had to be a miserable makeup process.
Maybe that's why the guy didn't play the part.
I did commercials.
The first acting gig I ever got was a commercial for Sportsnet New York,
where I played their mascot who was a guy that a TV for a head.
Yeah.
And they actually hollowed out a real TV and bolted it around my head.
How was that?
It was excruciating.
Yeah, horrible.
It was really heavy.
It was really hard to move around and it would burn incessantly after like an hour.
And I'd have to have it on for three hours of a clip.
It was horrible.
But, you know, as bad as that was, I couldn't fucking hold a candle to this, you know?
Well, it's horrible.
We had to do a shot where I had to walk down the street and I couldn't see anything.
And they were like a guy had to walk in front of me and just had to follow his voice.
What was this for?
Sportsnet New York.
OK.
But I was shocked at how many people knew it was me.
They were like, I heard that you in the they knew my voice.
Were you handsomely compensated?
No, it was a buyout.
It was fine.
I mean, at the time, I felt like I made a fortune.
But, you know, right.
What are you going to do now?
We're in a pet store and here's the guy again.
I love this part.
He eats the crickets.
He's standing over the the like lizard tank.
That's oh, yeah, this is really gross.
Yeah.
But then what is this guy?
That's never really addressed.
Oh, yes, it is.
It's absolutely addressed.
OK, then maybe I wasn't paying close enough attention.
Oh, it's so gross.
What are those crickets?
Yeah.
Are those crickets?
They're not crickets.
They're.
And this guy's eating them.
Oh, it's so great.
I love it.
Does she work in this pet store?
Yeah, I believe so.
She just being like a good social person kicking the guy out.
I don't think she was like shopping for a pet.
That'd be an odd.
I think it's odd that she works in the pet store.
Yeah, people have to work in pet stores.
You need jobs.
This is the guy.
This is the sort of he's the sort of a curator of the box.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
At the end, who's I assume is Satan.
Has there ever been a movie with more hand on the shoulder scares?
They've done it now eight times.
They're doing plenty of hand on the shoulder scares tonight.
Hey, what did you do earlier today?
I worked all day.
Some of us work for a living.
What do you ask?
Make a living doing stand up.
I did a audition for The Tonight Show that was so bad.
Valum?
Yeah, the crowd was so bad that halfway through my audition, I said, fuck it, I'm not.
I'm done.
Oh, wow.
And I just started doing other jokes.
Pulled a Larry David.
Oh, they were terrible, terrible audience.
So you were you were supposed to do like a five minute audition set.
Yeah, it's like, I don't need.
I mean, they were not laughing at a goddamn thing.
Yeah, horrible.
Does that matter for the Booker?
I guess it does.
My friend is the Booker.
The tape will never, you know, he'll never show anybody.
Get him a different tape another time.
I'm sorry, my friend, we're the Booker.
I wouldn't have taken that liberty.
Yeah.
But I've known the guy for years.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Well, what are you sorry about?
I wish it had gone well for you.
Pat, we live, we learn, you live, you breathe, we die, we breathe, we conquer, we seduce.
You know what I mean?
I guess it's another day.
That's true.
You're not usually that guy, Joe.
Usually very despairing.
I'm not anymore.
I've been so positive lately with you.
You've been stone drunk every time I've expressed it to you.
So you don't seem to remember it.
I also I haven't had a drink in 12 days.
Oh, well, I also haven't had food.
I'm doing a cleanse.
Get him a medal, everybody.
I'm just simply responding to your accusations.
I know.
I'm kidding.
Come on.
But it is true, though.
Every time I tell you I'm happy, it's when we're in a bar drunk.
Okay.
Well, you're usually, to be honest, saying you're unhappy.
Huh?
You're always saying that you're unhappy.
Never saying that.
When am I saying that?
Joe, we've had this conversation a lot lately.
No, no, no.
I told you I was mad at my friend and then you said you sound like you're unhappy.
That was your saying.
I didn't say that.
Yeah.
No, you do.
All right, fine.
All right.
Are you happy?
I'm not going to scroll through the text.
I'm happy.
Yeah?
Yeah.
All right.
I'm happy, too.
I mean, everybody goes in and out of it, but.
What tech?
What are you talking about?
What text?
Well, I think we should talk about your happiness after the show.
All right.
Joe, you're always like, I'm having a rough time.
I got to cancel tonight.
I'm in a bad place.
I'm not dreaming these things.
But you say the same things.
Not I'm in a bad place.
Occasionally, you know, you have, I can't like not hang out because I'm in a bad place.
I think I just admit to it more than you do.
That's probably true.
I think I'm more in touch with my feelings.
You're a callous Irishman.
Yeah, I mean, that's all.
Shove it all deep down in your soul.
You'd be good at you should get your hands on one of these boxes
from the Hellraiser thing and and go to hell.
That's what you want from me.
I could see you being a guy that's like, oh, fuck it.
I want to see what the pain and the pleasure are the same.
No, that's not going to happen.
I feel like if we were in the Hellraiser movies, I'd be the nice husband.
You'd be frank.
Wow.
You really view us differently than I do.
Somebody would be bleeding you back to life.
Now, I can only orgasm if a homeless man watches.
I don't know if that's weird, but so it's usually like if I pick somebody up,
it's like then I also have to pay a homeless person.
That's a shame.
A lot of times the lady in question is not up for that, you know, and I get that.
That's that's really a shame.
I hate to hear it.
I really hate to hear it.
What I was going to say last night, I saw the man from Uncle.
Oh, I heard it was great.
No, who told you it was great?
The reviews.
It got OK reviews.
It's it's fine.
Well, what were you expecting?
I kind of didn't expect it to be good, but like Henry Cavill,
the most boring actor alive, Army Hammer, the second most boring actor alive.
I like both of those guys.
And I enjoyed the Lone Ranger.
I don't care what anybody says.
I didn't see the Lone Ranger.
You like you like Henry Cavill and Army Hammer.
I said Cavill first.
That didn't feel right.
Cavill also didn't feel right.
I think you're thinking of Caviezel.
No, no, I'm not thinking of Jesus.
I don't think it's Henry Cavill.
I think he's a great I think he's a great Superman.
I enjoy him in Superman.
I enjoy him in Whatever Works, the Woody Allen movie.
Those are the only two things I hated that man of steel.
And what was he in?
He was like a fiance of somebody.
He's the guy that's like in love with Rachel, Evan Rachel Wood,
or whatever name is in Whatever Works.
The guy that's like that lives on the boat.
All right.
And he's quite quite sure he's quite charming.
Sometimes you say somebody's somebody and it's not the somebody that you said that it was.
Pat, here's what I'd like out of you tonight.
One compliment and not a criticism.
Any other criticisms?
Joe, you're unhappy.
You don't have your facts straight.
You talk too much about it.
Masturbation at the top of the podcast.
What have I done?
What have I done to deserve this?
Nothing.
I made an error on the previous podcast where I said that the guy who
molested the kid who directed Powder, Victor Salva,
I said he made a movie called The Fun House produced by Francis Ford Coppola.
It's not true.
The movie, I believe, was called Clown House because I looked it up
and it was like Roman Coppola or another Coppola.
It is Clown House.
And if I'm not mistaken, Sam Rockwell is in Clown House.
That might be.
A young Sam Rockwell.
I got to publish the clarifications now for previous podcasts.
I've been working on a Sam Rockwell impression forever.
I can't get it down, man.
He's not that easy to do.
I can't get it down.
You want to try?
You easily slide into a Giamatti and he seems kind of like a very toned down Giamatti to me.
I slide into a Giamatti?
Yeah, like your voice naturally without much doctoring
works as a Giamatti impression.
A little bit.
Yeah, there's a little.
Jerry Heller.
I have a Giamatti look.
Yeah, true.
I feel like I could maybe take the parts that Giamatti turns down soon.
Sure.
You know, I mean, you look like here's a compliment for you.
Look like a more attractive version of a couple celebs.
Jared Vogel of Subway, Paul Giamatti, you know, a more attractive version.
Pat, I've never said this to a person.
I want you out of my house for the love of Christ.
You fucking cocksucker.
Now, Frank's about to kill this poor bastard.
All he's trying to do is fuck his wife.
I honestly can't believe how terrible this woman is.
And she does stop the killing.
She's trying to stop Frank from killing her husband, though.
She's saying, please don't.
Her husband thinks her.
Look at this.
Now, that's a red open over the bed.
Why does he do that?
To be like to be like, I'm in control here.
That's so gross.
Now, also, her husband thinks she's crying.
Please.
No, don't fuck me.
Yeah.
Now, the guy keeps going.
That's what I don't understand, too.
The guy keeps going and she's going, I can't bear it.
I can't bear it.
The first time I hear I can't bear it, I'm wrapping up the lovemaking.
I don't think that he's ever heard his wife say it.
Well, because here's why, because upstairs she starts jumping.
When they first go upstairs before the scene, she's seducing him
because she's trying to save him from Frank.
Yeah.
And then they go downstairs and then Frank turns out to be in their bedroom.
So now she has to switch gears.
See?
Yes.
It makes perfect sense.
I honestly look.
I don't know what it is with me.
I honestly thought that she brought him up to the room.
I think she did bring up to the room and then she had second thoughts.
Oh, but I just thought they went in there because he's in the room.
I didn't know he could get out of the room.
Why couldn't he get out of the room?
I just assumed there were rules.
You only see him in the room.
Has there been one rule so far in this movie?
And the blood bringing people back to life because I was just like that brings demons
we haven't seen in an hour and a half.
Yeah, that's true.
You know what I mean?
There are no rules.
Since when is there a bed in this upstairs blood drenched attic?
But now I understand.
I heard Clive Barker on set, he would say to people,
hey, when they would ask questions about the script, he would go,
you go, hey, Steve, when would it roll with it, baby?
That didn't happen.
I heard that's what he would say to people.
He just plays it on a boombox.
I told you I haven't eaten in 11 days.
So good.
So anytime I see food, except in this movie, I'm not feeling hungry.
I mean, Pat, listen, you live the life of it's a real healthy routine you have where you
destroy yourself for six months and then not eat anything and drink
vegetable juice for 18 days straight.
Once a year.
Yeah, it works.
I'm sure it's a healthy way to do the thing to do to your body.
I mean, actors do it.
Yeah.
Well, you know, actors, they're healthy people.
Hey, Pat, I'd like to introduce you to my friend.
His name's moderation.
But you do the same job.
I mean, you're a big I'm not drinking and then I let's get drunk.
No, we're those kind of people.
It's a very Catholic thing.
I don't think you're a little break from the booze sometimes.
But like, I never did this cleansing to not eat and to drop weight.
This is Michigan.
I don't know.
It works for me.
I mean, it does their own shit.
Well, I'm just saying when you drop dead, you'll know why.
I'll stand over you saying I told you so.
I would hope your reaction was something different than that.
I feel like if I died right now in front of you,
it would just still be the same stoic.
I, you know, I'm a little more emotional than people think.
I haven't cried in a decade, but.
And when I did, it was at the movie about Schmidt.
No, it's a hundred twenty seven hours.
The other movie I cried.
See, that's the that's the problem.
The last time I cried, I think, was when I saw one hundred twenty seven hours.
Our relationship started with great emotion.
You mean just that we liked each other?
We were.
It was fast friends, but then we had that Christmas text
where you said, Joe, you texted me Merry Christmas.
You were the only person I was going to text that to today.
Yeah, it was very nice.
I felt like we got off on a nice emotional start.
And now I feel like you take me for granted.
Well, this sounds a lot like other relationships I've been in.
I've left town for for a week and a half.
You've texted.
Joe, do you even miss me?
You've texted that to me.
Yeah.
Well, you know, these are kind of jokes, Joe.
I know they're jokes, but the thrill is gone is my point.
It was gone.
All right.
PBBK.
We're sleeping in separate rooms at this point.
Yeah, exactly.
I saw we're both reading separate sections of the newspaper at breakfast.
It's that we're at that scene in singles where they're.
Yeah, yeah.
Hey, you.
Hey, what is it when they read the paper?
She's dating when Kyra Cedric's dating a really awful, like, oh, guy.
Yeah.
Hey, you.
Hi.
So just dead.
The whole relationship.
Second, because we talked about singles as well.
Why wouldn't you talk about singles?
I don't know.
We haven't worked into this one yet.
Child molestation.
No, I did.
I brought the powder guy.
Oh, there you go.
But man from uncle.
So I'm thinking I had a joke about this today.
But like a studio, you come to them and you say,
hey, I got army hammer hot off the Lone Ranger, one of the biggest flops of all time.
I've got Henry Cavill.
Right.
And I want to reboot a 60s TV show that no one knows with the worst title ever.
The man from uncle.
I think it's a great title.
Why on earth was this movie made?
And it cost 100 million dollars.
Actually, I looked it up.
It cost 75 million dollars.
It was a bomb.
I just I don't get it.
How these things get made, how they decide what to throw money at.
You could make.
Not not kidding here.
Seventy five.
One million dollar cool, interesting movies that would all probably some would turn a profit.
You know, that's not their goal.
Yeah, of course.
But what is what is their goal?
They're losing money on man from uncle unless it makes money overseas or something.
And they're like, oh, Superman.
You know, that's not their goal.
I mean, you're talking like you've been in this town for five minutes.
Like you're chewing on a piece of straw.
I'm saying why couldn't they?
Why wouldn't they?
Well, why couldn't they is not the question, Pat.
Like anyone would know.
Like it can't be a shock to them that some of these movies bomb.
It can't be a shock that the man from uncle bombs.
But it's how they've been doing it forever.
They they they put all their chips on one number.
Yeah.
And try to make a windfall of money.
Right.
You know, OK, Fantastic Four completely bombed nobody six years ago.
So what should we do?
Let's make it again.
And let's make this one suck, too.
But that's Sony.
That's Sony, you know, trying to, you know, they're saying, hey, they fucked it up once.
Now Marvel's hot.
Right.
We're going to try to reboot it and do it right this time.
But then that director fucked it all up, apparently.
Who was a cool director made the old Chronicle.
Yeah, Chronicle.
You know, I thought that movie was overrated.
But visually, it was cool.
Yeah, it was.
It did some new things.
It was fine.
Frank is now trying.
By the way, Frank just exposed him, not exposed like genitals,
exposed himself to Kirstie for the first time.
Right.
She also came to terms with this very quickly.
Well, now, why did he expose because these are.
He's a dad, right?
I don't know.
He looks nothing like herself.
No, he's not her dad.
He's he's her uncle.
OK, yeah, yeah.
But he was saying come to daddy.
I don't I think he was just in the.
Oh, because she because she saw
she knew Julia killed somebody upstairs
and then she went upstairs
and then the half dead guy came out like, help me.
And then to the jig was up.
She knew what was going on.
Then Frank came out like, hey, come here and fuck me.
All right.
Your blood or something, you know, like one of those things.
He was also trying to bang her, correct?
Yeah, he's a pervert.
So like and this woman is still interested in him.
Who?
The married woman.
Yeah.
Yeah, Julie is a terrible person.
Crazy.
Look at these three Yankees have.
Who put these three people together?
So they were they were a doo wop group on the corner that came up.
It's like literally the three people that run the food truck
just were used as extras in the film.
This is supposed to be set in London, right?
You know, I've never been able to figure out.
I don't I hope they didn't give that guy Yankees cap.
So we believe this was New York City.
I don't think it's supposed to be set in London
because nobody has English accents except Julia.
That's true.
It feels very British.
It's clear that we'll look at this fucking hospital room.
She's yeah, for Christ's sakes.
You know, you wouldn't see a hospital room like that in the States.
I don't think you'd see one like it in London either, but fine.
Have you ever been to London?
Yeah, I have.
Well, then maybe two years ago.
I didn't go to the hospital while I was there.
Wasn't that kind of a trip?
Look at that guy.
That doctor has some kind of weird makeup on.
You know, I always wonder in both horror movies and in comedies,
like David Lynch always casts completely freaky looking people
like you've never seen before.
Crazy faces.
Everybody looks interesting and it keeps you on your edge.
He doesn't even have to do any work really.
He does.
Everything's amazing that in comedies.
Why wouldn't you cast like funny looking people in these bit parts?
Get some extra laughs.
Look at this weirdo.
I always say they don't want to explain people's physical shortcomings.
I'm not talking deformities.
Jesus Christ.
I'm talking like interesting looking people.
Get a big fat pig in there.
We all laugh at the fatso.
Is that what you want, Pat?
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Not at all what I was saying.
I'm saying get people with some character in their face in these bit parts.
They always have like generic boring looking people in movies.
This movie's doing a good job.
You got some weird looking people.
Right.
I agree.
Let's say interesting looking.
Interesting to judge beauty like under the skin.
There's a great example.
I love that movie.
Kind of a horror movie.
You won't watch it because of that guy.
It upsets me.
And that's an actual deformity.
I know.
I don't say that to be mean.
It looks like the elephant man.
But somehow I can't watch his real life face is more unsettling than the elephant man.
Well, I heard that if you go back and rewatch the elephant man now,
it just looks like bad makeup.
I don't know about that.
I don't know if that's true.
I can't watch it.
I can't watch mask.
I can't watch the elephant man.
I can't.
And it's not out of meanness.
It's out of it.
I find it very upsetting.
All right.
Now you were saying last week on the podcast.
What?
Show me something.
You were like the director didn't want to have Freddy Krueger something
you had to look away from in horror.
But you were like, I want that.
Give me something I have to look away from and make it disturbing.
Well, in horror.
Now you're saying the exact opposite.
No.
In horror, it's Kirsty just opened the box.
Here we go, boy.
Here we go.
The wall just opened up.
That means pinhead's coming.
No, it's it's see that corridor pet.
Yeah, this part really kind of bothered me also.
Why did it bother you?
It's horrifying.
It's hell.
That's what that's the gateway.
Did they have to make hell so horrifying?
Sprinkle a little heaven in for us pussies.
What did you want?
Hello.
Look like Pat.
I don't know.
I thought it would be red.
Maybe more like a bam bam bigelow scene with a painted flames everywhere.
I mean, give me one guy with a fork tail kind of shaking.
You like more of a hot rod race kind of.
Yeah, I got you.
Yeah, I understand.
Like the mascot of this very podcast.
I understand.
This thing that comes at her is disturbing.
And I also wondered if you can see the man's legs who's running it.
I don't think you can.
I pause it and I was like, I think I see this guy's legs, but maybe I didn't.
With horror.
I like gruesome and gross and disturbing and blah, blah, blah.
When it's a real person, it upsets me because I feel terrible for that person.
Sure.
So it's hard for me to watch.
I seemed really at ease and actually does full frontal nudity and under the skin.
God bless him.
Go for it if you're going to do it.
This part always reminds me of like like this big war.
He's big.
Adventure is kind of what the vibe is.
It makes me think of like a Jim Henson kind of thing.
Yeah.
We're noises it's making are really what makes it unsettling.
It makes me think of labyrinth.
Yeah, sure.
You know, because this hallway looks like the labyrinth.
Labyrinth always scared the shit out of me.
Did you ever see the dark crystal?
Of course.
That one is to this day freaks me out.
Yeah, I love it.
It's one of my favorite movies of all time.
It scares the shit out of me still.
I don't feel she's running fast enough.
I would be running much faster.
I think I don't think it's supposed to be like literally look how fast she's you know,
she's running this bad.
I think it's just she's running.
Okay.
She's running.
No pinhead.
I wanted some pinhead there.
We didn't get any pinhead.
He's barely in it.
I know.
I've already said that.
Sorry.
Well, I'm just pointing out I've said it.
There was a time when we used to listen to each other.
I went when I lived in New York, I went down to I believe film forum on Halloween
because I had no friends.
I had lived there for two months and had not.
I don't think I'd said a word about one uplifting story about you moving to a city.
No, you move here.
You're gated into a prison.
You're masturbating for money.
Well, now things are some kind of boogie nights climax.
Yeah, it wasn't like that.
You go to New York, you have no friends.
You're going to movies alone for three months.
I don't think I said one word, but the stories have happy endings
because I wound up with lots of friends and having a good time.
But at first, I didn't know anyone.
So Halloween night, I had nothing to do.
And I went to film form and watched this all night horror festival.
And they showed Donnie Darko by yourself, but by myself.
Donnie Darko, they showed this movie called King of the Ants.
That was terrifying.
You ever see that movie?
It's with William Shatner, is it not?
No.
OK, sorry, Pat.
I think George Went is in it, but it's really, really scary.
King of the was about giant ants.
No, it actually was more of like a very real life
horror kind of thing.
It was Stuart Gordon who did reanimator.
Oh, all right.
I'm in.
I want to see.
Man, it was really freaky.
And then Hellraiser was like the 2 a .m. movie.
And I was like, I don't want to get out of Hellraiser at 4 a .m.
and then have to walk home through the streets of New York.
I couldn't stomach that idea.
Well, so I just went home.
It's a good thing you didn't because in that book,
the Scarlet Gospels, I was told you about there.
These centibites are popping up all over New York.
Yeah.
See, I wouldn't have been good with that.
I do get very scared of things when I watch them alone.
That guy is really gross.
Who, Butterball?
Yeah, he just licked his lips.
Yeah, I saw that.
She's pretty scary.
Why is her throat propped open?
Do you have a problem with it?
It's because it's awesome.
That's why.
All right.
Oh, listener growling.
That's pretty cool.
Just take the pins out and let your throat close up.
Let it heal naturally.
Put a lotion on it.
That's such a great line when he says that.
Oh, no tears, please.
Such a waste of good suffering.
No time for argument.
He's so cool.
He sounds like Darth Vader.
I love him.
I love him so much.
Now, she makes a deal with him here.
She makes a deal with him.
I'll tell you what.
They're not going to take her.
Take that pin out of your nose.
I'm giving more advice to this girl.
Slide it out of your nose.
Then you don't have a pin in your nose anymore.
And sew up the neck hole that you have.
Then you'll be a nice looking gal.
You can get dates.
She doesn't want to sew up the neck hole.
The point is this is who they are.
All right.
The movie is about being yourself is what you're saying.
The whole movie is a metaphor for goth kids.
Let's be honest.
Yeah, for sure.
A lot of black leather and nobody understands me.
I live in a dark box.
I used to drink at this bar in Hollywood called Bordeners.
And it was next to a club.
Alone?
No.
Don't leave the sad part out of the story.
And it was next to this bar that had a goth night every Saturday.
And we would go just so we could watch these people.
And there was a girl yanking her boyfriend around on a chain,
a dog collar and chain.
And he was wearing a shirt that said,
I have a tiny penis.
And she kept like bring him around.
I was like, I want you to meet my boyfriend.
He has a tiny penis.
And we're like, OK.
It was like some weird punishment they were doing.
And that boy was Jason Schwartzman.
Yeah, he later became Rushmore.
My friend at work is reading the or listening to the autobiography of the
Jason Schwartzman.
No, of Rob Lowe.
And tons of ass stories in it.
They said every chapter ends with,
so I was hanging out with this girl and it was no big deal.
I mean, it wasn't like she was anybody famous or anything.
But in just one year's time,
she was Winona Ryder.
And every chapter ends like that.
He doesn't tell you who the person is that he's talking about.
And then he goes.
Does he bang all of them?
I think he bangs most.
He was in the first sex tape scandal.
Poonhound.
I know.
That was when people gave a shit about sex tapes.
Yeah.
He had sex with a 16 year old girl and now we all love him.
But he was 21.
But he didn't even get in trouble for banging the 16.
Nobody even cared about that part.
They were just like, can you believe it's on video?
Yeah.
I don't remember videotaped the degenerate.
It was two girls, I believe.
It was.
Yeah, that girl or that guy.
I'm sure Rob said to the police like, hey, you know, fellas, she was 16 going on 40.
And they high fived him and sent him on his way.
That's probably how that went down.
I love it.
Now, who's banging Julie?
Is this another flashback?
I believe so.
Oh, okay.
She's having a flashback.
Okay, because this is the final.
We're in the final run now.
She's preparing to feed her husband to Frank.
How good must this sex have been?
The sacrifices she's willing to make to get one more taste.
It must be Dick Almighty, man.
Plus then he's proven he's not even going to be faithful to her when it does happen.
He's trying to hit on her niece.
I know.
The guy's like, yeah, I know this woman's murdered 10 men to have another taste of my dong,
but I think I'm going to hit on her step niece.
It's her stepdaughter first.
Stepdaughter.
It's his blood niece.
His step, his blood niece.
He's trying to fuck his blood niece.
Sorry, I wasn't following the family tree of hell raisin.
That'd be a good name for a horror movie.
Blood niece.
Yeah.
She's like your niece, but bloody.
Now this is Frank in the dad's skin now.
If you can't tell by the boils in the bloody seams inside of his head.
How does that work?
How does he slip on the skin?
It's the same thing that bothers me about Mission Impossible.
When they put on the masks and they look exactly like the guy, it's ridiculous.
Do you see the new Mission Impossible?
I loved it.
It was fucking awesome.
I said it was almost Mad Max good.
It was so good.
When he was down in that washing machine thing.
Yeah, it was amazing.
It was tremendous.
The whole plane sequence was out of this world.
Yeah, loved it.
His entrance into the movie, him running over the hill and ducking.
Can you get me on the plane?
They're better than the bonds, I would say.
It was so fucking good.
But it does still bother me that they put on a mask
and then they're suddenly the other person.
Sure.
Well, two really overdid it.
But like same body.
Yeah.
Same everything.
Two was like a dog walks up and then peels off a mask and it's Tom Cruise.
Like two was ridiculous.
That's ridiculous.
That didn't happen.
It didn't happen.
Come on.
John Woo.
You know, real hit or miss that guy.
He didn't do a movie since.
He was the biggest thing that's in sliced bread for a while there.
No, but he made.
You know how big sliced bread is.
He made a pro -crack mountain, didn't he?
No, that's Ang Lee.
Wow.
I guess they all look alike to you, Joe.
Ang Lee and John Woo could not be more different directions.
I thought Ang Lee actually made Mission Impossible two
because I'm thinking of I'm thinking of how he made the Hulk.
Yeah, that's true.
I think he also made Mission Impossible.
How bad was that Hulk when Nick Nolte bites into that electric wire?
It starts OK.
And then they start switching shit around and then it's pretty stupid.
It could have been good.
Well, you know, why wouldn't Edward Norton play the Hulk?
I like the Edward Norton one.
That's the Ang Lee one.
Oh, no, the only one is the Eric Bana one.
Oh, God, the Ed Norton one is good.
The Edward Norton is the one with Tim Roth and he becomes Abomination.
They all run together to me.
But yes, those Hulk movies run together way worse.
The Ang Lee one is the bad one, the way worse.
Yeah, the Norton one's good.
It's like that's part of the official Marvel canon in the Avengers and everything.
Well, that doesn't make it good.
It's a I haven't enjoyed it.
I'm a bad person to talk to about this.
Does she not know?
Does she not see the blood dripping out of her dad's head?
She's clearly blinded by lust for this man.
Who is he doing that?
Wait, who's blinded by lust?
I'm talking about the daughter.
Oh, the daughter.
Yeah, I don't know.
I guess she just didn't look.
Oh, maybe she.
I think we talked through it.
Maybe she does know it's not her dad.
Wait, no, that's is she.
Does anyone come back for Hellraiser two?
Yeah, she comes back.
I don't want to ruin anything, but she's back.
Kirstie's back.
There they are.
I love the thought that someone listening to this movie with us talking over it
could have something spoiled for them.
Well, here's the thing.
Like, hey, he ruined this movie that I can't hear.
They broke.
They broke another rule.
The centibites just appeared and nobody opened the box.
Whatever, though.
Why is Kirstie fighting?
I'm confused.
God damn it.
This is bad for the podcast, Pat.
I don't know what's happening in the movie right now.
I got really lost.
She doesn't know that's her dad yet or she does.
She knows, I believe.
No, that's not her dad.
That's Frank.
OK, she still thinks it's her dad.
She thinks it's her dad.
Why is she not noticing the blood then on the side of his heads?
She probably just like, hey, there's some weird shit going on in this house.
My dad's head's all bloody by the seams of his hair.
She's been through a pretty rough day.
She just got chased by a whole demon.
By the way, how did she get out of the mental institution that she was locked up in?
Look, we've got a lot of questions.
I'm sure she has even more.
All right, now she knows.
OK, she thought her dad killed Frank.
Yeah, when her dad tries to bone her, she's like, oh, OK, I get it.
She thought her dad killed Frank.
She thought that dead body upstairs was Frank.
It's not. It's her dad.
That's why when Pinhead said, we want the man who did this,
she thought she was had to turn her dad over and she said no.
Right.
I mean, and this Julia lady is willing to fuck this guy with skin hanging off of his face,
which is grosser than when he just had like his phone.
She just doesn't care.
Oh, there's the switchblade that he used to bang his.
Yeah, I like.
Why doesn't he have Frank's voice anymore, by the way?
Do you notice that?
Oh, I thought I thought he was getting a more normal voice because he's becoming more normal now.
No, he's got it's just the actor that plays the dad.
It's his voice.
Yeah, yeah, they could have.
They've dubbed everything else.
Why not dub them?
Yeah, oh, there he goes.
Oh, God.
Oh, and he takes he takes Julia's flesh here.
That's the line.
Nothing personal, baby, as he sucks her life out of her.
So that's good makeup.
And I'm so surprised that this guy proved not to be trustworthy.
After all she did for him, his face doesn't look any better
after sucking out Julia's essence.
Right.
Why didn't it heal his wounds up?
Yeah, it should have.
Clive break the rules, Barker.
Clive Breaker.
Of rules, rules left and right in this movie.
Still love the movie.
I'm not shitting on it.
But no, I mean, the unexplained is what the whore is all about.
You know, that'd be a good name for a horror movie.
The unexplained.
What's going on?
I don't know.
The unexplained.
And that's the whole trailer.
Cheech Marin is the unexplained.
Why Cheech Marin?
I don't know.
He needs work.
No, he doesn't.
I haven't seen him in a long time.
Those Cheech and Chug tours.
They're mopping up, man.
Oh, all right. Great.
Well, then let's cast somebody else.
Yeah.
And I can't believe you thought Cheech needed work over Tommy.
Yeah, well, I don't like Tommy.
I think Cheech carried Tommy for 50 years now.
I think Tommy's very funny.
All right.
They're both very funny.
Do you know Tommy?
Not at all.
Did you work with him or something?
No, neither one.
Okay.
Hey, you used to work with Roddy Roddy Piper.
Were you sad when he died?
Of course I was.
I mean, to tell kind of a strange story about it, I was doing the extras for the Always
Sunny DVD and Rob McElhenney called and was like, you guys got to come down here right now.
Roddy Roddy Piper's on fire.
He's been telling stories for like four hours.
You got to get him on tape and we're going to do a DVD extra like Roddy Roddy Piper Tales
and him telling like some of his best stories.
And by the time I got to set, we were interviewing him and he was just like
very much not making sense.
Like his brain had been banged around so much that maybe he got it.
He had a good hour or two of stories, but then eventually it just stopped.
That's really disgusting, but he couldn't have been more charming.
It couldn't have been more nice.
He was funny, but the story is really disgusting.
The stories didn't make sense because it sounds like you're saying Roddy's brain
damage was disgusting.
No, he was a sweet, delightful man.
He was very funny in the show.
I was saying that head full of maggots was disgusting.
Yeah.
Well, you got to describe it to the people that aren't seeing this right now.
A head came out of the darkness and maggots fell out of it.
Yeah, that was really gross.
Roddy Roddy Piper.
Great man.
It is gross.
I'm going to see if there's a way next Halloween that I can do that to you somehow.
Fill a fake head with maggots and throw it at me like a prank.
Well, come into your house and do it.
Let me tell you how that ends.
We never hang out again ever.
And I don't answer your texts or calls you.
So if that's worth it to you, great.
You would never hang out with me again over that.
That's a guarantee.
If you throw if you throw a maggot filled head at me.
No, I didn't say throw it at you.
I would just dip it next to you and freak you out with it.
You'd never talk to me.
Do you do it in your home?
Like you're spilling maggots on the floor of your own home.
That's where it really scared.
Yeah.
So now my floor is covered in maggots and we're not friends anymore.
The maggots.
I wake up November 1st and I delete your number from my phone.
Really?
Yeah.
Jesus.
Sorry.
You're a real fuck.
I don't need friends that I can't trust not to throw maggot filled heads at me.
One time my friend Chip got mad at me because we went down to the Jersey Shore.
We went down to Atlantic City.
It was me, my friend Chip and my friend Scott who you've met.
And I went into the bathroom.
Did you fix your hair up nice?
Stressed yourself up pretty?
Yeah.
For the tables.
For the table.
Spurs, Frank Steen song, Atlantic City.
We went to Atlantic City and I like to reference things.
Scott was in the shower and Chip was on in the bedroom part of the room.
And while he was in there, I went into the bathroom and I shit onto the soap dish.
Oh God, Joe.
And then put it on the sink.
What's the matter with you?
It was one of the funniest things I've ever done in my life.
I was uncontrollably laughing.
I couldn't get my shit together.
I was laughing so hard.
Couldn't get your shit together because it was sitting on a soap dish.
Chip was so offended that he didn't speak to me the rest of the day.
And it was my birthday.
Chip, you and I are kindred spirits because I think I would probably be like,
yeah, you're on your own this week.
Well, you're you're an animal.
I've never liked pranks.
I had for Christ sakes.
Pat, would you get over it?
I don't like them.
I think they're me.
You're a TV comedy writer.
You don't like pranks.
Yeah.
Yeah, you can be both.
The hell are you talking about?
That's really gross.
The centibites are here for Frank.
This is the big climax now.
Oh, look at her hair.
I never noticed that the weird centibite lady has like strands of hair.
Frank, they're going to take her.
Here we go.
See, now this is what they lost with the centibites.
OK, here we just said to Kirstie.
Pinhead bitch.
No, no, no.
What pinhead said.
Oh, it just said to Kirstie.
This isn't for your eyes.
He's telling her leave.
This has nothing to do with you.
He's a rational man.
Yeah.
He's a judge.
He's like, you seem like you could probably have a nice time going with a fella to a movie
and holding hands.
And you don't need to be exposed to this underground world of torture to have sex.
But you know, and that's the thing I didn't like about the new book is that they make
him he's just like a raging asshole.
And you're like, this isn't what pinhead.
This isn't how he rolls.
People change, you know.
Maybe pinhead had some misfortunes in his internal demons change.
I didn't know that.
I thought kind of if you could count on somebody, it'd be a centabyte.
Jesus Christ.
This is really gross.
And then this is the part.
Yeah, I looked away for this when I watched where he goes.
Terrible.
I love this line at the end.
Jesus wept.
Yeah, that's funny.
Why does he say that?
Like I suffered as he did or something.
I think Jesus, I mean, Jesus wept means like this is fucked up basically, right?
I'm not a big Bible.
I don't think so.
I think it's just I think he's saying like this is my crucifixion.
Oh, all right.
Well, he thinks a little highly of himself.
Well, yeah, Frank does think highly of him.
Yeah.
And that's a good little thing.
He fucks women with a switch.
That's true.
Not with us.
There's another rule broken.
Centabyte scraping the wall.
Blood's coming out of it.
Why are they coming after Kirsty now?
They just tried to save her.
They just said they just said this is not for your eyes.
Get out of here.
And now they're coming after her.
Why is that happening?
Maybe because she didn't get the hell out of there when they told her to.
She left, didn't she?
No, she's I don't know.
She watched the guy say as Jesus wept line.
Is that what it is?
Yeah, he never.
I see hook one go into my guy dressed in the skin of my dad.
I leave.
He's telling.
OK, so this is the penalty now.
You got to come with us.
You saw the other side.
OK, I get it.
Now, has there ever been a more warranted?
Oh, shit.
Than that one.
Yeah.
And I and she's now.
Percy closes the box in order to.
I guess trap the centibites again, which they can get out of the box anyway.
We've seen.
And I like the pinhead just goes, don't do that.
Yeah.
Hey, yeah.
Well, they establish in part three that he can't take the box from you.
It has to be given to him.
OK, well, that's how this work.
This is part one.
So but why didn't he fly his chains at her?
A lot of questions here.
Clive, I got a lot of questions.
I'd like to get you on the phone.
I'd like to discuss this with you, please.
I got a lot of questions for Clive.
Break the rules.
Barker and Chrissy is played by Chrissy, the same actress and everything.
And the two.
Yes, that looked out for her getting that part.
She's in two.
She has a tiny cameo in three.
And she turns up again in like five or six or six.
It is actually.
Boy, I can't believe I remember that, but I do.
What?
How lucky are you as like a kind of an OK, generic actor to get like the lead
in one of these eight part things?
You know, what a dream.
I'd love to do movies like this.
Yeah.
Wouldn't this be a fucking ball?
I mean, like saw they're swapping out people every time, but like that
anything where you can like carry it out.
Except the one chick was in a few of them.
That see what I'm.
Who's the broad?
She's a who's the broad that was in a few of the saws?
She was a victim in one and then she's in part two and she falls into like the needle pit.
And then she becomes like his apprentice.
I Tandy, she's got like an interesting name.
She was on Becker.
She played the dumb girl on Becker.
I don't know.
Yeah.
Well, what are you going to do?
I interviewed all of them.
I used to work for Cinematical, which was a great movie website for AOL.
I got to interview all these people from saw.
This thing's back now.
Now this big this this dog thing is back.
And she grabs the box and electrocutes her.
Why did that happen?
Oh, I mean, I hate to.
I just hate to ask so many goddamn questions, Pat, but I'm sorry I am.
Yeah, I mean, I I think honestly, because in writing stuff,
all you have to do is ask yourself these questions and try to make things work.
And it's so exhausting that when I sit down to watch a movie,
I tend to not ask questions and the people who are like, well, why did this?
Why did this, you know, I get it.
I have fun having those conversations, but I'm never doing it myself.
I just let things happen.
Well, you know, that's the world you want to live in.
It is.
I question everything else in my life.
I don't need to question the movies.
You know, I spend
so much time being like, well, I don't know if this is right.
I don't know if it's good.
I don't need to do that when I watch a movie.
Hey, welcome to Obama's America.
That's what I say.
I don't know what that means.
You're kidding.
Well, it's a joke.
It's a joke.
I was making like a political joke.
Sure.
You don't get involved.
No, I don't get involved.
Uh, I have nothing against Obama.
I take that back.
It was just he's a great man.
But it was a funny thing to say.
Who do you think's running our country coming up here?
It's Trump.
Question going to be Trump.
It's it could be.
It's insanity.
It could be time for the pendulum to swing again.
This is how it goes.
Every eight years, it goes back the other way.
I don't think even Republicans trust Trump running the country.
They don't.
But he's leading the polls.
Yeah, he's leading the polls.
All right.
I can't go much further with political talk.
I don't know what I'm talking about.
Neither do I.
OK, look at that shirt.
I'm not even sure I know what leading the polls means.
But that's I read it today or something.
That shirt is the stupidest choice to end a horror movie,
unless it's like it was the year that it, you know, I mean, Joe,
it's of the time.
I don't know that was of the time.
That's like something that kid or play would wear in House Party
three, the pajama jam.
Well, the funny thing is, is every time he looks at that
cross colors rayon shirt that he's wearing, he's going to go,
I thought demons in this shirt.
Oh, I'd be done with that.
This is my demon shirt.
Yeah.
Every time you get it out of the closet.
Do you ever wear it again or is that it?
I probably wouldn't.
I also wouldn't wear it because I would have to beat the shit out
of myself if I saw me in that shirt.
All right.
Here comes the answer to your question about the, you know,
who's the bearded man or whatever.
Yeah.
He's coming back in in a second here.
Give it a second, Pat.
Be patient.
Oh, there he is.
See, I might have been peeing during this part.
Piles of fire, by the way, was this the house?
Is it just a field of homeless people fires?
I guess that.
Very strange.
I think, you know, and I agree with this.
I think somebody like Clyde Barker, even though I don't
think I've seen any of his other movies, I think he just
wanted to create a mood.
I agree.
And I dig that, especially in horror.
I'm not knocking it.
I'm just asking questions.
What's Clyde Barker's like second most successful?
Like he did like Lord of Illusions.
I don't think I've ever seen any of his movies.
Nightbreed, probably.
Yeah, I think I intend to watch Nightbreed.
It's in the queue.
I am not a fan of Nightbreed.
Okay.
Have you seen the director's thing, the director's cut?
Yes.
Okay.
I'm not a fan.
All right.
I'm going to watch it.
I'm not a fan.
He seems to me to be a very creative dude.
He is very creative and I think he's great.
I just, you know.
But he never had another big, like.
Franchise?
Canon movie other than this, right?
This was the biggest.
Yeah.
But I mean, this is to me, despite all my questions, it's masterful.
And right back to the beginning, a new man gets the box.
Great ending.
Can't argue that.
I love anything that starts, ends where it started.
Frank the Monster, in case we weren't clear on that.
Frank the Monster, Oliver Smith.
Oh, now why would you do that?
You think Sean Chapman was like, I'm not sitting for all that makeup.
Now, I just think they probably wanted somebody.
Look at this in the credits.
I love this lead center by Doug Bradley before they had a name.
Wow.
Yeah.
Well, they named him Jackie Hellraiser.
That's another cheesy part in the book that he just put out.
There's this whole thing where if you call Pinhead Pinhead, he gets furious.
Really?
Because it's like, don't call him that.
He hates that nickname.
Yeah.
Do they, when did they refer to him as Pinhead in the movies?
Or is that just what society called him?
It's just kind of what the name he got from the fans, I guess.
Okay.
Caught on or whatever.
Gotcha.
They put this thing in the book where it's like,
you better not call him Pinhead to his face.
He'll get real hot.
Well, they took that from Back of the Future.
Well, whatever.
Ladies and gentlemen, that was Hellraiser.
Yeah, it was a wild ride.
This makes two nights in a row where the last thing I do before I go to bed
is watch Hellraiser.
Well.
Horrific visuals.
Good for you.
And then go to sleep.
And count the minutes till Halloween, Pat,
because a head full of maggots is coming at you.
And you need to treasure these last few months of our friendship, Joe.
I haven't treasured the first few months of the friendship.
I'm not going to treasure the last few.
All right, fair enough.
This has been We'll See You in Hell.
Again, you can follow us on Twitter or send us any questions or comments or requests.
I'm at the Patrick Walsh, P -A -T -R -I -C -K -W -A -L -S -H.
Jodorosa is Jodorosa Comedy.
And tweet us questions, thoughts, movie suggestions, stuff you want us to talk about,
thoughts, criticisms.
Look us up on iTunes.
Review the show.
Give us that five stars.
We'd love it.
Thanks for listening.
We'll be at the Mile High Horror Fest in Colorado.
Littleton, Colorado.
First weekend of October.
We don't know yet which day we're performing.
It'll be Saturday or Sunday.
Or not performing, but we'll be doing a live podcast there.
Details to come, but please come out for that.
It's going to be a lot of fun.
You've been listening to We'll See You in Hell, a presentation of the Fangoria Podcast Network
produced by Thomas DeFeo and executive produced by Ken Hanley of Fangoria Entertainment for press
opportunities, advertising inquiries and information about We'll See You in Hell.
Contact Ken at fangoria .com.
Thanks, everybody.
Thanks, guys.