Welcome to We'll See You in Hell!
This is the second Patreon episode.
For the month of June, today, we'll be talking about The Outsider,
because this is the podcast you come to, to hear about stuff like that.
Park, sci -fi, action, fantasy, genre, drama, comedy, whatever
the fuck you're into, you sicko.
Right?
Even though we're talking about The Outsider, uh, we're all insiders right
now, uh, because of the pandemic, we're living inside our homes.
Now, be honest, how long have you been sitting on that?
I really would be honest.
It honestly just came to me while you were talking.
I would, I would tell you if I had that one in the chamber.
Uh, I remember once I was on Red Eye on Fox and, uh, with Michael
Lee and Black, we were the two guests.
And I made a joke about the show where I called it Brown Eye, uh, which
my friend Chip told me to do.
And you'd go on the show with notes because you had to write stuff
like that day about the stories.
So I finally, after months of him begging me to call it Brown Eye on
air, I wrote it into one of the jokes and had to, uh, and I was reading
the joke off the paper and then was incessantly made fun of by Michael
Lee and Black, like, did he grab it and show it and no, but just was like,
you had to read Brown Eye off paper.
Like you couldn't just, you know, like it, so I'm not quite as sharp
as you was when I'm getting it.
I wouldn't have had the insider bit in my head for three days.
Sure, sure.
Well, I'm very quick.
It's my, uh, groundlings training.
I was a groundling, uh, for 12 years, I spent $180 ,000 on it.
Yeah, that's well, that's good stuff.
Um, no, look, no offense to groundlings.
A lot of funny groundlings have come out of it.
Chris Catan, for example, read the man's autobiography.
Baby, don't hurt me.
Was he one of the groundlings?
He was a groundling with Farrell and Jennifer Coolidge, whom he dated.
I need to ask Jennifer about that.
How did that happen?
Um, but yeah, there's a lot of funny groundlings.
A lot of SNL people come out of there.
Uh, I was sitting in on the bonfire radio show for about two months with
big Jay Okerson and Dan Soder for Sirius.
Yeah.
And we did a deep, deep dive into improv.
And improv as a construct.
Yes.
And watched a lot of improv stuff.
And I will say, and I can admit, I can admit when I'm wrong, we made a lot of
fun of the middle ditch and Swartz trailer and then started watching about
five minutes of it to see how bad we would think it was.
Yeah.
And I laughed and we all kind of said, they're, they're really good at this.
It's
maybe I'll give it a try.
It's worth watching.
Um, I mean, that's all I watched, but I would say it was enough.
We watched like some ass cat.
We watched a bunch of different impressive and we also the same thing.
Every one of these people has made us laugh in another context.
It's just improv that we don't like.
Yeah.
But the middle ditch and Swartz one, I was like, they're clearly much, much
better at this than anybody I've ever seen do it because they actually did
make it like kind of funny.
I have heard that middle ditch was an incredible improviser and, and
sure, I I've never, I don't know.
I, it's not my thing, but I saw him do the improvised Shakespeare company
show and that made me want to hang myself.
So boy, I mean, it was a group outing from a job I had that I kind of felt
obliged to go on, but, uh, that was, I turned to the guy who brought us who,
you know, and I was just like, not for me, you know, like right away, I just
knew it was not for me, but, um, by the way, everybody, I feel the need to say
upfront here, uh, Pete Holmes announced a new lineup of not feeling it.
Chicken t -shirts.
And as I talked about on this podcast once, probably whilst drunk, uh, he
asked me before making these shirts.
Hey, can I split the money with you for doing these?
Cause it was kind of a character that we came up with together.
Uh, and saying not feeling it.
Correct.
Right.
And there was a whole bit attached to it and people liked it and one of the
t -shirts.
So, and as I talked about on the show, he never gave me this money and he
sold a lot of the teachers, but I thought that was going to be kind of our little
secret, but then I realized that everyone he announced over the pandemic.
He said, a lot of people have been saying, I'm not feeling this pandemic
and they wanted the t -shirts.
So I'm announcing a new line of these shirts and they went up for sale.
And I noticed on Instagram and on Twitter, a lot of Hellions saying, and
I assume Pat Walsh will be getting a cut of this money and tagging me and
tagging Pete and whatever.
Now I appreciate it.
Please don't do that again.
It made for an awkward situation.
But, um, as is very common in our friendship, we didn't, we didn't bring
up the, uh, we didn't even bring this up.
He just texted me and he was like, Patty, I'm, uh, selling this shirt.
I'd love to give you your cut.
And I was like, I'll take my cut.
Thank you.
So you did lead to me getting paid.
You never have to go after him again.
All I wanted was a little taste to get paid.
What about laid and in the shade?
Uh, neither at this point, they're just paid.
All right.
Well, um, thank you for doing it, but please, you don't have to do it again.
And, and also please, not that you've done this to my knowledge, but if I
should talk somebody on here, please don't ever at them.
I'm never talking to someone with the hopes it gets back to them.
Um, you know, so keep, keep it between us, even though this is
a wide open available podcast, you just assume that the people I'm
talking about aren't listening.
But I did, he did, uh, pay me odds are with Pete.
He's a busy guy.
He just, uh, forgot, but I got, I got my money.
Thank you.
Uh, let's move on with our lives.
All right.
Fair enough.
Now, Hellions, if you want to go after Pete for him to give me some money,
I'm fine with it.
That would be fun.
Yeah.
He owes me nothing.
I just, uh, you know, it never hurts to have a little extra cash.
You know what I mean?
By the way, and I, here I am just taking the blame.
Look, a lot of it's Pete's fault, but if I had been a man, I would have
called him up and been like Maury and Goodfellas and said like, I want my
money, but I didn't, you know, I just kind of like, let it be this awkward
thing between us and I got to stop doing that.
And maybe that would have led to me having to whack you in a car.
Yeah, exactly.
It's probably better that you didn't do that.
He got an ice pick through the back of the neck, right?
Yes.
Yeah.
I thought he'd never shut the fuck up.
There's like a 20 minute period where like he's going to be killed, then he's
not, then he's going to, then he's not.
And then he gets killed.
Well, what was always so sinister about that scene to me, that sequence
rather was De Niro, he leans over to Ray Liotta during the card game.
And he goes, nevermind about that.
Nevermind.
Yeah.
And then, uh, you feel kind of relieved watching it.
And Liotta says it was like a load off my mind or whatever.
And, uh, and then they still kill him right after that.
That's just, that's just De Niro being like, we got to get Ray Liotta out of
this because it's going to be a problem.
Not the most, uh, well -rounded, uh, Jewish character, Maury, a man, a Jewish
character who they have literally say the line, I want my money 50 ,000 times.
Um, you know, not the most progressive, but Scorsese, you know, he's an old man.
It's a great, uh, and honestly, he's making, you know, uh, he's having the
gangsters talk like gangsters would talk.
So, uh, a dear Jewish friend of mine just had a baby and, uh, a new baby.
And I told her that she should, the baby's middle name should be media.
Okay.
But she laughed very, we laughed heartily.
She wasn't offended or else I wouldn't, I'd be an asshole then, but, uh,
it was funny.
Um, uh, let's do a, uh, let's do a new psychopath because
something has come up in the news.
Just in the hour between doing these podcasts, just in the hour between these
podcasts, and then there's another thing that I want to get to that we're going
to probably really disagree on, but, uh, I'm very excited about it.
Um, so in between recording today, you went off to the bathroom to pee and I
went off to get a coffee.
And while I was getting a coffee, I looked at my phone and checked out
movieweb .com, which I do on most days to see what's happening in movie news.
And also thinking, well, we're doing another episode, maybe something
else will pop up worth discussing.
And sure enough, I see the story.
Labyrinth fans want Tilda Swinton to replace David Bowie as
Jareth in Labyrinth 2.
Um, now, first of all, this is the first time I knew it was Jareth.
I thought it was Jared this entire fucking time.
My whole life I thought it was Jared.
Uh -huh.
The Goblin King.
Uh, she does fit the part and they're both sort of known for being like androgynous.
Uh, so I mean, it's a great casting choice, but I would really hope they're
not having her play the same character.
Why?
You can do whatever you want.
Well, maybe she could be the Goblin Queen or his sister or whatever.
Yeah.
His sister, the Goblin Queen.
I think Swinton fits right into this universe for sure.
Yeah.
I mean, Swinton gives me the fucking heebie -jeebies.
If I saw her in a 7 -Eleven, it would freak me out.
I mean, get her right in there with the goblins.
Yeah.
I mean, Swinton, they could show like five minutes of footage of her
interacting with goblins, two investors, and then be like, man, how did you guys
shoot this and they're like, oh no, she didn't know she was on camera.
We were just over at her house.
She actually lives with a small army of goblins and that wouldn't
surprise me in the slightest.
Yeah.
We just, we just shot a footage without her knowing, just talking to the air
and we just put the goblins in.
We dropped in the goblins.
But she's wearing a star covered cloak.
Yeah, that's right.
That's what she had on and the, uh, the wizard's hat as well.
Yeah.
She had that on when we went over to her.
And she's always playing with this crystal ball.
Yeah.
Why didn't they never release those balls as merch?
I guess it wasn't a merch movie, but like I always, as a kid was like, man,
I wish I had some of those crystal balls.
They're, they're, they're a real thing.
Okay.
I just need to go to a magic shop.
Yeah.
They're just, they're a real thing.
Like that's a real thing that people do.
Like he is actually doing that.
Oh yeah.
I've seen people on like Molly do that at, at, uh, Coachella and shit.
It's fucking crazy.
They get up to your face.
If they can tell you're high or whatever, and they do like glow balls in your
face, it's pretty cool.
Maybe I'll get a pair.
Smash cut pets in a porta potty with a man standing over him.
Yeah.
In, in my mind, I'm watching him play with these orbs, but he's actually
just bringing himself to orgasm.
In front of, I'm looking at his actual balls dangling over my face.
Here's the other, uh, news psycho story I want to talk about and the thing that
we're going to disagree on, I would assume, but I am immensely, immensely,
immensely excited about this and how can we not talk about it on this podcast?
After all, I've run my mouth about Batman versus Superman.
Oh yeah.
They have officially announced the Zack Snyder cut of justice league, which will
be apparently like 75 % different from what was released in theaters.
It looks like it is a much darker film.
It looks like it is the true sequel to Batman versus Superman.
It looks like it's going to be the movie.
I wanted justice league to be, uh, different characters.
Dark side is in it, everything.
It's coming to HBO max in 2021.
They're spending, I think everybody thought it was like in a vault, but
either he's putting a ton of money into it.
Yeah.
They have to spend like, I think $30 million to finish it or something like that.
Um, but the actors are not coming back for reshoots or anything like that.
So I guess they have the footage.
It's just completing the footage now.
Um, I'm sure they asked him like, what would you need to do this?
And he's like, uh, 30 million.
The number's probably closer to about $500.
He's going to get catering each day while he edits the footage
that's already been shot.
Right, right, right.
Yeah.
I don't blame it.
Uh, I, I, I just couldn't be more excited and what, what,
because I want to see this.
I wanted to see his vision through.
They also announced this week that Henry Cavill is coming back as Superman.
Uh, so I'm glad, I'm glad that DC as a fan of DC, I'm glad that they're
staying the course with their content.
I'm glad they're not jumping ship and just redoing everything from scratch again.
Um, you know, the new Batman obviously has not been half like it's
going to be Robert Pattinson.
I'm very excited for that.
And I think DC is just kind of finding a way to make that work within this
universe, I would assume.
But Snyder also said too, that, um, this will not lead to anything else.
Like this is the end of the line for the justice league movie.
Like this is where it was supposed to end.
So I'm curious to see what happens.
Another DC news swamp thing, which was a great show is going to the, the, the, uh,
CW is it the CW now or the UPN CW?
Um, which I think is very cool.
Um, that was the WB, the WWW.
Yeah.
Um, hang on.
We can't just move on because I, I'd like to speak about this Snyder cut
as well.
Why now you were very upset when they redid Sonic the Hedgehog because of fan
outcry in what way is this different to you?
I think that's a bad precedent of like, we didn't like the movie.
We want our version.
There's there are people who like the fans deserve it and then they get it.
I'm like, here's, here's, here's what I would say is different.
The, the, the, the, the studio vision of this was seen through.
It was, you know, they saw it and they released it out there.
Snyder had to leave this projects.
His daughter committed suicide, I believe was what happened, or she OD'd
something very horribly tragic.
So it wasn't like, it wasn't like he was on it the whole time.
And then people said, this is bullshit.
And now he's going, oh, well, I actually, maybe I could change some
stuff if you gave me some money.
He's saying, the fans are saying, I want to see what he was supposed to do with
this because this other version we didn't really like.
So that's finished a movie.
Do you know, or the studio finished?
Josh Whedon finished.
And apparently it is an entirely different movie than what it was supposed to be.
So that to me is why it's different.
Also, but more importantly, the thing of the idea of releasing the director's
version or the original version, I've never been against that.
I love that they eventually put out the Donner version of Superman two.
I love that Exorcist three, the screen factory version has the original bladdy
cut on it with all the deleted footage and the positive, I think that this
would be for fans is not changing the product as it's being made and being
put out there, but for instance, you as a fan of planes, trains and automobiles
and this missing cut that has lost cut.
It's like, yeah, that's a great.
There's, I just read on bloody disgusting.
They did 10 horror movies that we want to see the original cuts up.
And it was like hellraiser four, which is a solid entry into that franchise, but
they're saying apparently the original cut is so much better and makes so much
more sense and it's like, that's out there.
There's the David air cut of suicide squad.
Now it looks like it's going to be released where he's saying like, yeah,
my cut actually makes sense.
You know, like I would like to see that stuff.
I would like to see that stuff because it would have, and apparently errors
cut of suicide squad leads directly into justice league and it all, I I'm curious
to know what happened and why, you know, it was changed.
I, yes, I always enjoy a director's cut.
There's, there's less and less of that stuff going on now as blue rays are
essentially a dead industry, but you used to always get really cool.
Like the, the alien quadrilogy was one of the early, uh, massive DVD box
sets I got for Christmas one year.
He had the first four movies, which were the only four at the time.
But, um, I mean, each movie has such an abundance of stuff.
They have the Finch Fincher's cut of alien three, which they've done, including
like drawings and stuff.
So, um, I'm always all for that.
I guess I'm just annoyed that it's movies.
I couldn't give less of a shit about it.
I mean, I, I hated all of these movies, so I have no interest in them, but I'm
glad that it's happening.
I just wish it was movies.
I like plants, trains, for example, three, there's, there's a few other movies in
the bloody disgusting article that I think would interest you.
Yeah.
Um, it's nine different movies.
Uh, so Hellraiser bloodliner already said, uh, I'm just going to try to pick,
Oh, something wicked this way comes.
Apparently there's a much worse version out there of it.
You're it's a great movie, but apparently there's an even darker version.
Uh, the thing 2011, apparently there's an original cut of that with no CGI
and all practical effects.
Wow.
And they just threw it out.
They didn't think it was real.
No came in and insisted on CG putting CGI over the practical effects.
So I'd love to see that there's apparently a director's cut of event
horizon that's much darker.
I've read all about that when I rewatched that movie.
Yeah.
You know, so these are things I'd love to see hopefully via scream factory.
Uh, yeah, scream factory in terms of like alternate versions, they're
about the only people doing it.
Even arrow doesn't really do that.
They are, they're a great company and they make great products, but
they don't really do that.
Uh, so yeah, so we'll see what happens, uh, in the meantime.
Yeah.
Let me take you over to Pat's movie corner.
Um, I saw, I've watched a ton of movies by the way, in case you don't know,
and you probably do, if you're on Patreon, you get them.
I do two 45 minute to an hour long episodes a month where I just kind of go
through what I've been watching because I watch a ton of movies these days.
So those are a bonus for you, Patreon subscribers.
If you haven't listened, give them a listen.
Um, I saw a picture called, you know what I'm going to do?
I'm going to do a new Netflix show called an Orthodox, uh, which is
about Orthodox Jews in Brooklyn, but then eventually it becomes kind
of a more international story.
Uh, four episodes.
So, you know, four hours, much, much less of a commitment than most shows.
I think it's a closed ended thing.
It basically plays like a really, really great movie.
And if you have any interest in the lives of Orthodox Jews, uh, it
plays almost like documentary.
There's so much information in it, but the story itself is also
fascinating, well acted, very well done.
And a great leading performance from an actress that I had never seen
before who is called Shira Haas.
I think it's a really, really good show.
Uh, I urge you to check it out.
I'm going to do three comedy specials here.
Okay.
To on, on the movie, not all at once, just to, for my movie corner today.
Uh, I'm going to start with Seinfeld.
Okay.
24 hours to 23 hours to kill.
So I, um, I watched it.
I was very excited for it.
I'm a big Seinfeld fan.
Hated almost every minute of the special.
Uh, I just don't, I don't know why he's screaming so much now on stage.
He's screaming every joke.
He's running back and forth and like rolling around on the ground.
I'm like, just be Seinfeld.
And the analogy I keep using is it would be like seeing Sinatra rap.
Don't do that.
Just do the Sinatra thing.
I don't know where that came from with, he was much more physical and running
around and he was constantly doing a voice that's like, ah, like a really
exaggerated version of people's Seinfeld impressions, really.
Yeah.
I didn't understand that.
Uh, I'll grant you, but, um, I thought the special was very funny at once you
got past the first 10 minutes or so, basically from the pop tarts joke on, I
thought was funny pop tarts segment should have been snipped.
Uh, I I've seen the, I bring, I decided to do these today too, because
you'd mentioned Pete Holmes.
Pete reached out to me to ask me if I saw the special and I expressed the same
opinion and he couldn't believe I didn't like it.
He loved it.
And he was like, but he was like, but roses, this is so you, a man just
furious about things he shouldn't be furious about.
And I was like, yeah, I understand.
But it's just not what I go to Seinfeld for, I guess.
I feel like it feels like a very, a guy that I look at as a very
classic comedian who I like a lot.
And you go and he's not doing, I mean, Sinatra did do it.
Like if you listen to LA as my lady, it's like a disco song with
Sinatra, it's terrible.
You don't want it.
You want the classic stuff.
And like, I felt like that's what was happening here.
It had some well -written material.
Um, it had some.
Sort of rather trite material in it had some material that was taken to
apparently I have seen comparisons, but I've seen a lot of people coming
out and accusing, I can't imagine anybody be that stupid in this day
and age, let alone somebody with his power.
I just can't imagine it, but maybe.
I don't think he took anything purposefully from anybody.
I think he's just at a point with being, you know, he's, he's an older
guy who's a little out of step with everybody and he's just a sponge.
Um, and I still don't understand what the title means.
I guess it means he has 23 hours to kill in a day because
he's on stage for one hour, but it opens with this goofy fucking
like James Bond thing where like he drops out of a helicopter and they
go out of their way to show you it's really him jumping from the helicopter
into the Hudson river that was swimming, but then there's no carrying on of
that theme for the rest of it.
It makes no fucking sense.
I'm just like, what is it was the whole thing made very little sense to me.
I was scratching my head through a lot of it and I've seen Seinfeld
several times live in the last few years, uh, and several times live.
I was very thrilled and enjoyed every minute of it.
And he left out a lot of that material that I saw him do that I thought
was superior to a lot of the stuff that made it into the special.
And when I saw him live, he did not crank up this performance part of
it, where it was like he was using the volume and the anger.
Very tact tactfully or tactically even throughout the act where it was
used for emphasis on things.
And I was like, Oh, that's funny.
Like that's kind of a new side to him.
This thing, it's like he hits the stage.
Somebody said to me, maybe he's hanging out with Sebastian
Maniscalco too much because they're good friends.
Like, cause it seems like he's trying to almost do a Sebastian
type thing now, which I do kind of agree with.
Like it was, it was a strange choice.
So sad to say I was disappointed.
I thought the, the, uh, the screaming, the physical, I never like a physical
comedian who's like prowling the stage or whatever, but the new voice I
enjoyed and like I said, had a lot of good laughs.
I thought the half hour of marriage material was really funny.
Um, I don't know.
I dug it.
I liked it probably more than his last couple of specials, to be honest.
I get turned off.
I liked Jerry before Seinfeld a lot.
Um, yeah, I get turned off by like his arrogance has always turned me off of it.
It doesn't ruin it for me, but like even in the marriage stuff, it
annoys me when he's like, if you're not married, I'm not friends with you.
You don't know what you do.
Oh, the only American it's like, can anything just be not that your
thing is the only way, you know what I mean?
Like it's, but it doesn't matter.
I'm still a fan of the guy.
I admire him greatly.
I look up to him greatly.
I just didn't like the special.
Fair enough.
Uh, I'm going to, since you're doing a theme, I'll do a theme as well and do
entire shows that I have watched in this quarantine.
Um, the other on Netflix is Hollywood, which was Ryan Murphy's, uh, look at
Hollywood in the forties, fifties, whatever.
Um, he mentioned this to me as well.
This is strange synergy.
Yeah.
Did he like the show?
He said to me, he, he said he was working on a bit about when people recommend TV
shows to you and he goes, you're telling me to watch Hollywood.
What is it you think of me?
It was really funny.
Like the impression somebody has of you, given the show, they're
telling you, they think you'd enjoy.
Sure.
Yeah.
Uh, it's like, Hey, you should, you should date my friend.
And then you meet the friend and you're like, really?
This is how low I fall in your eyes.
Um, Hollywood is extremely bad, but it was bad in a way that propelled me to the
finish line because like studio 60 or something, you just gotta keep watching.
Um, Ryan Murphy shows are, I mean, they, a wide hit and miss, um, you know, he has
a huge spectrum of between the good stuff and the bad stuff, but this is really,
really bad.
It seemed based on this book I read called full service, which is the story
of an actor named Scotty Bowers.
And I saw the documentary about it as well, which is nowhere near as good as
the book, but he worked at a filling station, you know, pun intended in
Hollywood in the fifties, where he would, uh, hook up with actors, male actors.
And nine times out of 10, it was people, you'd know Spencer Tracy and stuff.
So the book was very like, you know, naming big Hollywood names that he had
fucked essentially, and it was very literal filling station, you know, as a
filling station where he was also filling people that I get, I get the pun.
I mean, what is a filling?
What is an actual filling station?
Oh, it's a gas station.
Oh, a gas station.
Oh, okay.
And especially in those days, they were always called filling stations.
But, um, the book is fascinating.
If you like a real gossipy old Hollywood rag, the documentary is fine.
If you want to see the man who's a real character and this, it's like they're
doing that story, but they're also not, it's just a small aspect of it.
The other aspect of it is there's a black writer who's trying to get his story
made and the, they're basically doing this alternate version of fifties
Hollywood, uh, like post gone with the wind Hollywood, where this movie has
the power to like change and stop racism.
And it was so, if we look at how horribly racist Hollywood was at this time, it's
a revisionist history that I just found insane.
I guess they're kind of trying to do the Tarantino thing of, uh, showing you
an alternate timeline or whatever, but it could have been, yeah, it did not work.
They, it's kind of funny was Jim Parsons, who's the guy from, uh, big bang
theory, Sheldon, he just plays this complete asshole agent who's always like,
like basically if you want to be his client, you got to let him suck you.
And, uh, that character was filthy and often amusing, but the
show at large is a disaster.
All right.
That's it.
That's all I got.
Don't watch it.
Good stuff.
Uh, I watched Patton Oswald's new special.
Yes.
I love everything.
Um, Patton's a friend.
Uh, I'm a fan of his comedy.
I used to tour with him.
Um, it's a pretty good special.
Uh, it's not, you know, certainly none of it's bad.
Um, it's got some classic, uh, Patton Oswald type bits in it.
There's a very funny thing about Denny's at the very end of it.
Yeah.
Um, that he closes with, uh, there's a very funny thing about middle
age breakfast cereal at the beginning.
Right.
Uh, that he opens with, um, the stuff in the middle, uh, was, was a little out
of my taste because big chunk on like, I bought a house and we're tiling the
fireplace and you have to get a subcontractor, you know, you kind of start
to go here, you're losing me here, buddy.
But that being said, um, uh, it's worth a watch.
If you're a fan of his, uh, the, the, the, the, the sort of, like I said,
classic Patton Oswald style bits were enjoyable, uh, and the ones that were a
little more about his life these days and his home and whatever were, were
less enjoyable, um, but that happens.
People get, you know, more established, more famous, more wealthy and, you
know, wealthier and, and, you know, eventually there's going to be
some sort of disconnect, uh, you know, so, uh, you know, that's just kind
of the par for the course, but, uh, but it's an enjoyable special I'd say, uh,
Yeah, I thought it was, I love Patton.
I thought it was funny.
I think, uh, he's very happy and happiness can often be death for a stand
up, but you know, when I saw the title was, I love everything, I was like,
oh boy, but, um, yeah, I had some laughs.
It's a funny special.
Um, I'm going to hop over to the Hulu network and talk to you about a show
called little fires everywhere, which I watched, uh, in its entirety.
This was directed by, uh, Lynn Ramsey, at least at the pilot who just passed
away, um, uh, a very interesting indie director, sorry to see her go, but,
uh, little fires everywhere is Reese Witherspoon, Carrie Washington, um,
Carrie Washington basically takes a job as a cleaning lady and Reese Witherspoon's
home Reese Witherspoon is kind of the same snobby, uh, mother, you know,
where he closed off that she'd been playing a lot lately, the same, basically
the same type of character she played in big little lies, um, I watched this.
I probably never would have crossed my path except for the talent involved.
I liked Reese Witherspoon and I just thought if this is like big little lies,
I'm going to love it.
Cause I fucking love big little ones.
It's great show.
You seen it Joe?
No, it's, it's really entertaining.
This is the bad version of big little lies.
You know, big little lies is a genre I normally wouldn't care about done so
well and so fun that I'm like completely on board and then this is the genre.
I don't care about done in a way that I don't care about.
Um, it was, it's almost like when you watch American beauty, like when I saw
that movie, when I was 18, I was like, whoa, like this is so deep or whatever.
Cause I didn't know shit.
I was an idiot teenager and you watch this and anyone who's having revelations
about race watching this show must just be a complete idiot who doesn't know
anything about the world because it is the most thuddingly obvious, uh, racial
material, everyone is accusing everyone of, you know, like the daughter.
I saw this, uh, I believe it was Mary Hulahan.
It was a very funny comic.
On Twitter did this, like, this is what a clip from, uh, this is what every
scene from little fires everywhere is like, and she was like, um, we're
white, we don't really have dinner.
You know, like it's all that stuff.
We're like, there's no truth to it at all, but every line of dialogue
is about your white, your black.
I'm white.
So I think this I'm black.
So I think this, and it just became exhausting.
It's it's preachy to the point of like insulting, I thought.
And it's gotten very good reviews.
Um, so maybe I'm wrong, but I
crash kind of thing.
Exactly.
It's, and everybody hates on crash.
You know, I granted, I haven't seen it since the theater, but I
liked it when I first saw it.
It's a very simplistic movie, but you know, it pushed my
buttons and was entertaining.
But like, yeah, it's got that feel to it.
Just like, you know, it's, it's meant for like a woman who's never interacted
with a black woman to watch and be like, Oh, interesting.
You know, like that's, and then, and then not change anything about her behavior
and still never hang out with a black woman, but just feel like she learned
something, you know, it's, it's that shallow and I didn't care for it.
Fair enough.
Yes.
Pat, to close us out here with the third special, how could I not talk about
our finest living comedian, Hannah Gatsby?
Yeah, Douglas, the new specialist hit Netflix.
Um, this is a special, according to reviews that has continued
to redefine the comedy genre.
Uh, is it getting the same good reviews?
Oh yeah.
Certainly redefining the comedy genre into something quite different.
Uh, I was always somebody that, uh, defended, uh, Nanette.
Yes.
From the standpoint of, Hey man, there's plenty of room for all of us.
I don't care if she's doing a thing that I don't do.
I don't care if she's doing a thing.
I'm not even into, uh, good for her.
It's working.
She's having success.
You know, that's great.
Uh, and it was a powerful piece of material while in my eyes was a one woman
show and not a standup set, but at the end of the day, who gives a shit?
It is what it is.
Uh, she would have a problem with you saying that pet as she makes
clear in this new special.
Uh, uh, she's a lot of things clear in this new special.
My, my, my, uh, uh, issue started to arise with Hannah when she started
saying things like, if you're not using your comedy to, I'm paraphrasing,
but if you're not using your comedy to say something important, then you
tie or get out of the game, you know, whatever, as if throw Brian Regan
out the window or, you know, it's like, yeah.
And I'm a comic who has made a living off of doing social commentary comedy.
Like I'm not against, you know, talking about issues in comedy or store or
having a point or specific perspective.
That's a little beyond observational or what have you, but like, uh, you
know, or not even beyond, but you know, different than, um, but man,
she is so, so I started to take issue with her when she started
saying stuff like that, that bothered me.
Uh, and then going into this new special, I, you know, I was like,
can I keep an open mind?
And maybe, you know, and maybe she's not who we all think we, we not all,
but a lot of us are thinking she is now.
And my God almighty, man, just like right out of the fucking gate.
It's like, you know, it's just how great she is, how insightful she is, how
candidness about how shitty some of the jokes you're going to hear are going to
be and saying what kind of like, does devil may care attitude, which sucks.
Cause it's a special nerd.
Shouldn't be any shitty jokes.
Then self, uh, uh, appreciation of how great some of the jokes are going to be.
And those jokes are not great.
Um, it's, it's all done.
You know, she does this and these critics keep applauding this like, Oh,
what a deconstruction at the top of the show.
She, she lays out exactly everything she's going to do.
It's like, that's not a deconstruction.
That's a cheap parlor trick in comedy to be able to wink at the audience.
Because I remember when I said this 20 minutes ago, now I'm saying it.
Remember I told you this was coming here.
It is.
Um,
I mean, it's like the audience that, that
applauds, uh, about a callback at the end of a set, I would say 95 % of
comedians use callbacks, but it's like just hearing a word that they heard 20
minutes ago causes most audiences in these specials to go completely insane.
And to me it's all, it always seems cheap and pointless.
And why is that cool that somebody cites something cites a joke they already made?
Um, so I, I hate it even in comedians.
I love, but I understand that it always kills and why they do it,
but it drives me nuts.
I think, uh, you know, man, she, she's just, she's just real proud of herself.
And I'm not saying you shouldn't be proud of yourself when you achieve something.
I'm not saying you shouldn't be happy in your life, but to get on stage and
lay it out there that I know I'm good.
I know that I'm, there's an air to the whole thing of I'm a better person than
you are get on my level and it's like, fuck you.
Number one, number two, for somebody who's so fucking enlightened, you end
the show without even saying thank you to the audience.
So go fuck yourself because this is kind of all about you.
Isn't it?
And the applause that are being thrown at you.
Uh, she brags at the top of the show that she's going to close it out with a
U E C K joke that is so good.
It deserves a mic drop.
Um, but she's not going to drop the mic because she's autistic and loud bangs,
uh, upset her.
She also reveals during the special, she was diagnosed with autism four years ago.
Maybe she's autistic.
Maybe it's just the next thing to do for the next new special.
I don't know either way.
It bothered me that she said I was a diagnosed with autism four years ago.
My loud noises bang me.
Cause it reminded me of when Brian Cranston converts to Judy ism in
Seinfeld and immediately starts going.
Sure.
Our people use humor.
Um, the Louie CK joke at the end,
quits drinking and then is immediately like, dude, you really need to quit
drinking.
Yeah, exactly.
Uh, the Louie CK joke is lazy at best.
I mean, it's, it's the, it's the, it's the Louie CK joke.
Anybody would think of immediately.
Yeah.
Given the task of thinking of the joke.
I didn't make it.
She's looking at a painting, which I'll get into as well, but she's looking at a
painting, an old paint, you know, renaissance period.
I don't know what period it's from.
I don't know art, but, uh, it's an old painting and there's a baby in the
painting touching its Dick.
And she's making fun of that and going, this is a choice.
Why would the painter paint this?
Whatever.
And then she goes, also, that is the first known photo of Louie CK.
The easy, it's like the easiest, most obvious joke you could ever make.
So she's still doing jokes about classic paintings as well.
Oh, still.
I mean, this is, this is 40 % of the special is her pulling up paintings on
monitor on a monitor on stair screen.
And, uh, and, uh, you know, uh, and then, and then she sets the mic down.
Like, there you go.
There's she, she says on top of the special, this joke was so good that the
day she wrote it, she put the pen down.
Writing was done for the day.
It's just a gross level of self involvement.
It's gross.
And I'll say this, and I'm going to alienate certain people when I say this,
Hey, hate Louie CK for all I care.
I don't give a shit.
I don't care what your opinion on the guy is.
At least he's fucking funny.
At least he wrote, he writes good jokes.
Can that stand for anything when it comes to stand up comedy for God's sakes?
Like, you know, so anyway, sorry, go ahead.
Uh, no, I, I, I actually said to Joe, we should both watch this and discuss, and
then had to eat my own medicine because I just couldn't do it.
And, um, my issues are not guys start rolling.
Oh, I know who you are.
I know everything about you.
No, that has nothing to do with it.
And I, as I said, I thought our first special was interesting, but it was
in its of it completely devoid of even joke attempts.
So I don't know how that entered the standup comedy discussion.
It's like when they put dramas up for comedies at the Emmys, you know, uh, it
makes no sense and it seems a little cheap, a little cheating.
Of course, that's a more powerful special than say Jerry Seinfeld because
she's talking about her sexual assault.
Um, when I watched the first 10 minutes of this, I had your exact same
critique, it wasn't even about the material.
I, I didn't get to any material because all she was saying was, you're not
going to believe how naughty I'm going to be.
Um, Oh, just everything you loved about last time, I'm going to do so much
more, I used up all my trauma on the last one, so I don't know what I'm
going to talk about, but the jokes I do have are probably going to be bad.
Um, we're going to close with one good joke, but you know, some of the
jokes just aren't good.
I, I hated her whole vibe and it was so condescending, you know, it's like
almost more important than great jokes.
If you want to be a passable standup comic is like ability.
So many comedians, you're like, I don't see why this is funny, but
their likeability pulls them through.
Of course, I don't have to name names.
You know, I'm talking about, but she has neither.
She doesn't have jokes and the likeability factor is completely gone.
It's just someone sternly lecturing you, assuming she knows what you think.
Yes.
Um, and then telling you you're wrong for thinking it when, how the
hell do you know what I'm thinking?
It was this whole thing where she's like, I understand you better
than you understand yourself.
I understand the world better than anyone else.
I understand relationships and men and women and so forth.
And I'm just going to keep killing it.
Like I always do.
And after she got to the 10th minute of this, I was like, well, fuck this.
There hasn't even been a joke.
The audience was laughing for some reason, but I don't know why.
And let's call, let's call spades spades here.
This is somebody who was acting as if she had no idea the, the, uh, the, the
praise and success that her first special would have brought her.
Uh, that she's just, you know, now I don't know what to do.
I was going to retire, but I guess I don't have bullshit.
Okay.
I was in Australia two years, at least before that fucking Netflix special came
out, she was winning, she was sweeping the awards at the Melbourne
comedy festival that year.
Yeah.
She's been winning and getting awards and getting accolades for this, for
Nanette far before it ever hit the television screen, right?
She knew damn well that she wasn't going to retire.
I don't care.
You know, she wants to tell me what I think.
I'll tell her what, I'll tell her what I think she thinks.
She knew she wasn't going to retire.
Uh, it was bullshit.
And, uh, and it's sad to me that somebody took a very tragic event in a very
poignant moment in their life and did turn it somewhat into a publicity stunt.
I think that's gross.
Um, and I'm also quite frankly, a little tired of somebody bitching to me about
the privilege class and all this, who has done an art related tour with the
national gallery of Victoria, talking about paintings on stage, which she
also does in this and Dada is a modernism impressionism, whatever you
are, the epitome of higher education and white privilege, that your references
alone put you in the class of Woody Allen, your references alone.
And I don't mean because you married your almost daughter.
I mean, because it's, it's that classic thing that Woody Allen gets
criticized for where he goes, uh, it was almost as if Ruben himself was, you
know, and people go, who the fuck is this reference for, you know, you're
writing jokes about, uh, about artists and, you know, esoteric artists.
And I mean, and, you know, look, I know in the art world, that artist
probably isn't that esoteric, but to the common person, yeah, it's pretty
fucking off the beaten path.
Okay.
So it bothers me that the whole, uh, swing from her is that, uh, you
know, that she's not part of this, uh, you know, higher hierarchy, uh, you
know, class, whatever you want to call it.
She is part of it.
Stop it.
You're part of it.
You're a lady, you, you've had some privileged experiences.
Stop acting like you have it, man.
It doesn't mean you can't have a bad, uh, uh, time in life.
It doesn't mean that you can't have something terrible happen to you.
It doesn't mean that you can't, I can't feel bad for you for your tragedy.
Of course I'm a human that relates to all that stuff.
That's terrible.
The terrible things happen to you or to anybody else, but don't fucking
aspect of your life.
That's, that's the, uh, that's the other side of, uh, of, of utter tragedy.
It's just not true.
So I don't know.
It just, it, it, it annoys me.
Anyway, I'm going off on a tangent here.
You know, I don't like getting smokescreened by people and it bothers me.
I feel like she's doing that classic pseudo intellectual thing of, you know,
I'm going to talk down to you.
I'm going to talk about you.
I'm going to tell you, as you said, what you think, uh, but I'm not going to
relate to you because relating to you would then expose my own flaws.
And I can't have that.
I have to be holier than thou.
And I don't, I don't like that.
I don't like that.
And I think that she's proving to be everything that her most unfair critics
assume she was when Nanette came out.
And I think it's a bummer because I really gave her the benefit of the doubt.
And she was somebody I was like, you know what?
Let, let her, let it all be different.
Let's diversify this thing.
Sure.
But it's like, you know, like, I don't know.
It's just, it just, it just sucks.
Yeah.
I mean, uh, again, I can only speak of the first 10 minutes and then the
attitude put me off, but I think Nanette is a very interesting piece of work.
Uh, sure.
And by diversify this thing, I just meant different styles of comedy.
Sure.
You know, I mean, keep it white, but just with difference.
That's what I was trying to say.
Uh, anyway, let's get onto the, uh, uh, review at hand or the day.
Let's do it.
And we both say, um, and unison, that's usually time to move on.
Uh, we are talking about Stephen King's, the outsider, which was, uh, a book that I
read so I can offer a little help and what the differences are and a mini series, a 10
part HBO thing that now they're actually saying could lead to a second season
because the ratings were through the roof and even pre pandemic through the roof.
Um, so that would certainly go beyond the realms of the book, but I'd be, I'd be all for it.
The outsider is basically a story about a baseball coach, a little league baseball
coach played by Jason Bateman, who also directed the pilot and a few other episodes
and did an excellent job.
Um, he is falsely accused of the, uh, sexual assault and murder of a kid on the team.
And basically they have witnesses, they have footage of Bateman doing these things,
but if you were, I mean, this is going to obviously be spoilers if you haven't seen
the outside, but basically they, um, come to find that this is some sort of alien force,
um, who is able to replicate people and do bad things and get them in trouble for them.
Because basically the thrust of the conflict is Ben Mendelson, who's the cop,
who's investigating also excellent in this.
Um, he says, okay, it doesn't quite make sense that this guy that we all know and love would
do this, but we have footage, but it also says he was at this book convention.
How could he be in two places at the same time?
And, and it's really in a very good way because it's, it's a mistake of the book.
The book is the, as with a lot of the Stephen King stuff, the supernatural stuff just kind
of doesn't work.
So what they do here is have Mendelson be his character.
Who's like, I'm not willing to believe this, just like your viewer.
And then little by little, just like you, the viewer, he warms up to the theory that,
okay, there's no other explanation.
I've scientifically eliminated everything else.
It's got to be this.
And the book is not in the book.
The character is, doesn't do that.
The character does it.
The issue in the book, the book, if Stephen King had written it as a novella,
short story, put it in this new collection he has out, I think it would have been one
of his classics, but like a lot of his later books, unfortunately he's still the best idea
man alive and one of the best in history.
His execution sometimes suffers a bit.
And having just done the stand, the full 48 hour uncut version of the stand audio book
and done the outsider back to back.
I mean, this guy has an issue.
It's a very valid criticism.
I did it to myself going with the uncut stand, but they take you through the interrogations
in the book.
Stephen King takes you through the interrogations of like 50 people who are not the person.
And these investigations are like, I believe I did see him go to the general store at 4 PM.
Really?
Because earlier you said 418.
And some of them are done in like play style where the guy reading the audio book has to
tell you who the character's name is before each sentence until you eventually just go insane.
So that's the first third of the book is chasing down leads that don't come to pass.
Thankfully they do none of that.
It opens with them just going to get Jason Bateman.
So this was a mini series where the differences they made were all superior.
The character of the psychic lady played by Cynthia Ervo from Harriet.
The psychic lady is such an annoying character in the book.
It was read the audio book by Will Patton, who's in like the green mile on a bunch of stuff.
And he does a terrible job.
He does voices for everybody.
And like the voice he did for that annoying already annoying character.
In the book, she's like a real OCD.
She's way worse than in the movie version.
She's just really annoying and irritating.
And he does this voice for her that drives you insane, amplifying her annoyingness.
And the book eventually drove me nuts.
I couldn't stand it.
The stand was a much better experience.
But there is a point where you're like, what the fuck is going on, Steven?
Not because you're dying to know, but because you're so sick of listening to it.
And by the time it comes, you're disappointed.
You're angry at wasting all this time, blah, blah, blah.
So the mini series made very smart changes.
It was shot really well.
I don't think the mini series needed to be 10 episodes.
You could almost drop two out and not lose anything.
But I agree with that 10.
This this standard of 10, one hour episodes, one hour plus up is too much.
I agree.
It's too much Christ.
You get to you get to the now I enjoyed the outsider,
but you get to the middle of this thing.
You're like, by the end of episode four, you're like, I got to get to 10.
Yeah, exactly.
You know, so like through five, six, seven and a half of eight, you're just like, all right.
And then finally it picks back up.
And as you judge, you charge towards a resolution.
But I enjoyed the show.
I think King as a writer, you're you're you're obviously you're correct.
But I mean, he must just have a deal at this point where it's like, guys,
I hand you the book and you put it out.
I think there's no like, you know what I mean?
Like there's not an editing process, right?
Yeah, but he, you know, I did enjoy the show for the most part.
It was too long.
I mean, you want to talk about but my pet peeve
and I've bitched about it time and time again on here.
The the you know, they did the thing again with like the mystical black person,
like the person who knows what El Coco is and everything.
It's the black lady.
She's not I asked a friend.
She's not black in the book.
She is white, noticeably white in the book.
Yeah, it's it's insane to me.
Yeah, it's insane.
How fucking many times are they going to do this goddamn stereotype
and it's in one of these horror shows?
That bothered me.
I will say he was great in it, though.
The person, the actress who played her was wonderful.
But I just it just bothers me.
And they did, I think, do a commendable job of fleshing out that character
and making her more well rounded and certainly less annoying than she is in the book.
So yeah, I didn't think of her as being like the voodoo priestess stereotype you normally find.
She was just kind of an expert.
But I hear you.
Yes, I would.
I would disagree with you because now I did think she was a fleshed out character.
I enjoyed the character.
Right.
Certainly more better rounded than you would usually see.
But also this was 10 episodes versus two hours.
Yeah.
But I would disagree with that.
She wasn't still just cut from that same cloth because the explanation of her knowledge was just.
I don't know.
I've been like this since I was a kid and they ran tests on me
and they don't know what is wrong with me.
Right.
Like, I don't know why I can remember every single detail of everything I've ever experienced.
Like, yeah, it's kind of just like, what is this?
She just has like this weird superpower.
Right.
Which, you know, Stephen King also gave to Michael Clarke Duncan in the green mile,
who was one of the sort of prime examples when discussing that stereotype.
And this the lady in the stand.
Whoopi Goldberg will be playing.
I know.
They offered it to her first time around.
We'll do a whole stand.
We'll do a stand where we do the mini series, which I just watched and hopefully Joe will watch.
I've seen it.
Okay.
I just read the book and then we'll also definitely watch the new CBS.
All Access version.
Yeah.
Who knows if they're done with it or not.
But that lady in the stand, when you're hearing this clearly very white dad like guy read the stand
and when he goes into that chapter where it's like 50 N words and he hits every one hard.
Whoa.
I mean, I was out for a walk and I was like, good Lord.
I had to like take a break.
It's like listening to a hate crime.
Who reads it?
That one is just a very famous book reader.
It's like his job, but I don't know what his name is.
He's like the guy who does in a world in the trailers.
He's known for it.
I love Will Patton.
He's a bad reader.
He's it's I made the joke to you the other day.
I go, he reads the first and I think third story in the, if it bleeds book.
Yeah.
And he said to you, the guy sounds like he's holding a fucking straight razor.
Like the entire tennis is he going to kill himself.
Weber does a much better job with the final story in it, which is the most enjoyable and if it bleeds.
Yeah.
But yeah, Patton, it's like that it's just like, and then she went to his head.
She hated her brother.
She couldn't stand.
I'm like, Jesus Christ, man.
You would, you would not believe the read on this outsider.
I mean, I was punching my steering wheel.
I hated it so much.
So maybe unfair, but the, the mini series it's, it's top notch.
I mean, these HBO shows always look better than other networks.
They, you know, they get every it's like a feature film every week.
It's a great, it's a great show for the most part.
I would have liked a better resolution.
I didn't mind the explanation of what was going on, but the final episode in this thing kind
of plays like the end of a lazy heist movie where they're just like, you're going to say
this and I'll say this and we'll say we were out getting chicken.
And then everybody just believes them.
So they can cover up that a monster existed.
Right.
There's 10 endings, including like a post credits ending.
Like it just keeps ending and ending and ending.
Yeah.
Performance is great across the board.
Very well cast, very well acted.
Mayor Winningham, great to see her again.
And she was great as Mendelssohn's wife.
I liked her performance.
She's wonderful.
One strange choice in this thing is the
uh, decision to give like couples in their sixties, young children.
It's so weird because Mendelssohn and his wife the whole time are going through this thing,
but they lost their child.
Yeah.
And it's recent.
62 years old.
Agreed, agreed.
So it's, it, you know what?
It's, it's not even that it's strange.
It just reminded me of what it was like when I was growing up.
I was like, oh yeah, this is what parents looked like when I was growing up.
Your parents looked like old people.
Right.
Um, you know, so I guess there was something sort of endearing about that, but, uh,
but that's the, those are my only real criticisms of this thing.
I, I enjoyed it.
I, I would have liked to have seen a little more of the supernatural stuff,
but I've noticed with Stephen King as he gets older in the last, I'd say 10 years or so,
maybe even longer, he seems to really have taken a turn from a horror writer
to a crime procedural writer that incorporates sometimes horror elements into the stories.
Like, he hasn't written just a straight up and down, like, like it, you know what I mean?
Like, I don't think he written anything like that in a long time.
And I really wanted from him.
I mean, the, the most annoying parts of the outsider are the procedural parts
because I don't think he's good at it.
He, he talks about being inspired by Harlan Coban, who's another crime fiction writer.
Um, and Harlan Coban's even mentioned in the outsider, like they're,
I think they're going to see him at that conference in the book version.
Okay.
So he's clearly very influenced and he loves this guy, but it's like,
that's not what people think of at all when they think of Stephen King.
And you might be having fun writing this, but like you basically writing down the minutes
of a town hall meeting, um, is not entertaining anyone.
It's not advancing the plot in any way.
He doesn't understand too, which is largely considered his masterpiece.
I mean, the audio book, you're listening to town hall meetings for 200 pages,
like about the details of the new city.
I was pulling my hair out.
Well, it's, you know, look, I think a lot of it has to do with sobriety.
Yeah, absolutely.
When King got sober, needful things came.
Which was supposed to be the last castle rock book.
And it wasn't her story.
And it wasn't, um, it was needful things.
And then I think Gerald's game.
And then I think Dolores clayborn, which already by Dolores clayborn,
you're starting to lose me.
You know what I mean?
I never read that, but I love the movie with Kathy Bates.
I never read the book.
I want to see the movie because I just rewatched misery.
Oh, classic.
Classic.
And I will go on record now saying it is the best adaptation.
I know I'm in the past.
I've said it's either that or the mist.
I have to give it to misery.
It's just fucking masterpiece.
Yes.
But, uh, um, but my point is, is like, he's three books out from sobriety
and then it starts to become like, and then the final three dark tower novels.
And, you know, and then like, and then, then it's a lot of titles with the,
it's like the outsider, the Institute, the inside man, the Buick guy.
Well, it reminds me of, I saw a John Grisham book the other day and the title was the
Whistler and I laughed for five minutes.
I was like, he's, he's giving up the Whistler.
Like nothing sounds interesting about that.
There's a really funny joke.
What was that?
Go ahead.
Oh, there's a really funny joke.
And the thing about my folks, the Peter Falk, uh, Paul Reiser movie,
it's Paul Reiser is like a struggling writer and Peter Falk plays his dad.
He's like, I went to the bookstore to see if they had your book.
They didn't have it.
But that John Grisham.
Oh my God.
And Paul Reiser just goes, yes, he's very, uh, he's, yeah, he's very productive.
It's just a very funny telling scene of a writer.
Just being like, if one more fucking person points out to me that John Grisham gets to write.
Oh, you're a writer like John Grisham.
Yeah.
The, um, it, it, he's almost followed.
And I know you liked the prequels Joe, but he almost followed the trajectory of George
Lucas.
He was writing these pulpy fun, you know, like the three Star Wars movies.
And then when he comes back, it's like long talkie scenes of government bullshit.
Yeah, yeah.
You know, and, uh, King can still write.
I, there's always still even, even the non -horror sections of his books.
I'm always like, he's a good observer of, of human nature, you know, sometimes,
especially now when he's trying to write younger characters or black characters or anything
like that, it makes you cringe your, your head off, but by and large, he's a good writer
and he's trying to improve his worldview because you read some of those other books
and it's like, okay, buddy.
He also like, like you can tell he gets like references to plug in.
But like, I learned that's what he did with the stand.
So when I'm listening to this, this audio book, they're referencing things and I'm
like, well, wait a minute.
This book was written in 1978 and he just referenced lethal weapon or something.
And I looked into it and it turns out when he did the new version of the stand, he just
plugged in newer references all throughout the book, like mad libs.
Yeah, that's weird.
He does like, like he'll do references, but then like, he doesn't get all the references.
So half of it is in his old man voice and then have, so it'll be like, it'll be like,
you know, they, the, you know, the kids used to go up to Hunter's point to listen to
little Wayne and neck, you know, it's like, yeah, he wrote disjointed.
He always starts the chapters with, with two song lyrics.
So it'll always be like, I'm a gonna raise a fuss.
I'm a gonna raise a holler.
Dwayne Eddie summertime blues or Eddie Cochran summertime blues.
And the next one will be like, you know, smack my bitch up prodigy or something.
It's like, no, wait a minute, wait a minute.
Or like a run the jewels quote.
And I'm like, all right, you're just Googling modern day music quotes
and plugging them into this.
You don't listen to run the jewels.
Yeah.
So I, the first story in this, if it bleeds, it's called like so and so's cell phone or
something.
Yeah.
And he's telling the story of a little kid who works for an old man that lives up on
the hill in the neighborhood.
It was like the rich guy in their neighborhood.
And at one point he's like talking about the kid's dad, giving him a hard time about
how cheap his boss, the old man, boss is for the kid.
Cause the kid only gives him like five bucks an hour or something.
You're like, I was like, the whole time I'm listening to this thing, I think it's like
taking place in like 1985.
And then it's like, it was 2012 and there was the hottest, like, did he look into this
at all?
Like, that's absurd.
I opened the door and naturally found a full bottle of cold milk there that had been
delivered.
Like, no, Steven, no.
Yeah, for sure.
That, that is an issue of his.
Anyway, uh, check out the outsider.
We make jokes, but it is a fun show and it's enjoyable, uh, a little slow in the
middle, but overall hogs up, I would say.
Right?
Yes.
My hog is up.
We just, we just shat on the man and the mini series for 20 minutes.
But I mean, there are, there are funny things about them.
Like, and it, and by the way, and I know I've said this during the pet cemetery
episode, the worst rider of sex scenes in the history of fiction.
Yeah.
There has never been a worst rider.
The of sex, the, I wrote something down.
I'm not going to go get it, but I wrote down a sex scene from the stand, a phrase
from it that does remind me on the next podcast.
I'll have it.
But, um, Jesus Christ, I played that pet cemetery one for you read by Dexter in
the car and it was like, man, it's as though, it's as though he's an alien,
like learning about sex.
It's like how, when I saw that the, one of the latest Woody Allen's irrational
man with Joaquin Phoenix, and I always reference this when Parker Posey says,
you want to come up and have some grass, smoke some grass.
It's like someone has to step in and tell these people.
And I guarantee you they go, oh God, thank you.
I didn't know that.
Well, it's that classic thing too.
Like from like, like Woody Allen does it in Hollywood ending where like he has
to show that his, he's the, that his character in the movie is out of touch
with his son.
And then it shows the son and the son has like a bone through his nose and green
spiked hair.
You're like, nobody has done this in 20 years.
Yeah.
Like this is, you know what I mean?
It doesn't like, this doesn't match like the, what a modern day rebel would
look like for this time period.
Anyway, Joe DeRosa comedy on Instagram and Twitter, Joe DeRosa comedian on
TikTok and Facebook.
Check out without a country, Corinne Fisher and myself bringing you the gray
area of news available wherever you get your podcasts on guest digital.
Pat, it was good to see you.
Thank you again to the fans for sticking with us through this.
We appreciate it.
It was great.
Great to see you as well, Joe.
Um, and thank you all so much because it's your Patrons that is keeping
this show going.
Uh, I, I just can't thank you enough for your contributions, for listening,
for your positive comments, et cetera.
Thanks to Emily Simpson for helping keep things afloat and keep the, uh, the
conversation lines open betwixt us.
And thank you, Emily, I, between us, I mean, uh, the fans and us, I am the
Patrick Walsh on Instagram and Twitter.
I have guested on three podcasts recently.
My friend, Lizzie Cooperman's podcast Home Alone, uh, where she just basically
talks to people over the phone while in quarantine.
I did, I said no gifts with my buddy Bridger and I did punch up the jam with
my friend Miel.
Thank you all again for listening.
We'll be back next time and we'll see you didn't do it right in hell.