Thanks for joining us on We'll see you in hell folks, we're here to talk movies.
That's Patti Walsh over there. How's it going Joey? Good buddy. Good to hear. I'm going to bring
shit down for one second. I'm sure you'll join me here as well and then we'll get right
into the fun. But I got to say a dear friend of mine and Joe's passed away this past week.
I debated mentioning it and I'm like, of course, I'm going to fucking mention it. Trevor Moore
I'm at Trevor when I was an NBC page in 2004. So, you know, 15 plus years ago at this point
we were pages together. I loved him. He was a little bit of a dick to me because I was coming
into the program. He was the senior page, but he was always funny about it and like we had
like a nice rapport. Then he immediately formed the widest kids you know, which is a really,
really hilarious sketch group that I used to see live and who made it to their own like five
season IFC show. There's some brilliant sketches on there. Trevor was also a brilliant
performer and we stayed in touch. He lives in my neighborhood with his wife Amy and their
son. This is very sad. Of course. But a great man wanted to give him a shout out. I mean,
many nights me, Joe and Trevor have drank. The most memorable was probably that night. I bet
your DFW hole there, Joe, which was just like a blast. That was my first time there. And you
know, just want to one of the truly funny people of the world, but also no one has anything bad
to say about him. And that's not true of anyone else in comedy, really. He was like he was so
genuinely nice to everybody. And genuinely funny. A great dude. All right. Yeah. I'm still in
disbelief. Trevor is a guy that I met for the first time at the cluster fest in San Francisco was
a comedy and music festival that comedy central produced. We did a show together that I hosted
that was about drinking stories. And he came on and it was the first time I ever met him and I was
happy to meet him and his story was really funny. And then that night I saw him at the bar at the party.
And we drank for a while together. And at the end of it, we exchanged numbers and I was like,
we should hang out. And he's like, yeah, we should. And I was like, I don't mean this like in the Hollywood
bullshit way. Like I really feel like we could be friends. And he's like, no, no, that's what I'm
saying to you, man. Like, let's be friends. And we're very fast friends from there on out. Like every
project he ever worked on, he would pull me in. He's one of the only people that ever pulled me into
things without putting me through some kind of, you know what I mean? Because he was able to because
he was at the lead of a lot of these things. But that's irrelevant to how I thought about him on a
personal level. I just loved the guy. I just loved hanging out with him. I loved, I just got him.
Like we were Star Wars prequel defenders. We had the same interest. We just had a lot of the
same interests. We were politically very aligned. We were irreverent in a lot of the same ways.
And he was a guy that I just really clicked with. And when I got the news on Saturday,
Sam Brown, who's also a great dude and was in the whiteest kid you know, and was Trevor's best friend
called me and told me I was like, this is the only time I've ever actually said this is somebody.
I said, I said, come on, tell me you're kidding. Like, this is like a joke, right? Because they,
that's a joke Trevor would do. Yeah, they're not a, they're not above, they're, they're
pranky sort of guy a little bit in their own way. And I just couldn't believe it. I couldn't
wrap my head around it, man. And then Johnny Pemberton called me. Who's another great dude?
Yeah, these are all great people. And was like, dude, Trevor more died, man. Can you believe it?
And I was like, what? And then I called Vince Avril, another great dude. Yeah.
So to tell him, but Jesus Christ, yeah, it's wild. It's wild. And it's sad that he succumbed to just an
accident, a freak thing like it's just, it's just a real, real bummer. He will be missed. He is very
loved. And you know, I hope that he, his legacy lives on in the strongest way possible.
Yeah, I had literally met with his wife, Amy, who was also a page with me and met Trevor in the
page program. But I had a meeting with her five days ago. So extremely recently and we had a great
talk at her place of business. And, um, you know, she, she has a five year old kid,
Oggy, who will carry on Trevor's name. You know, but it's, it's very sad.
RIP, uh, he lives on in his work. There's so much great stuff. You probably have better luck
on YouTube finding their really great stuff because IFC doesn't release their, you know,
whitest kids, you know, stuff I doubt. I don't know where you'd be able to find it. But I could be
wrong. I will say this. I'm very funny, dude. I'm very grateful that the last time I talked to him
was his podcast that he had on the Twitch channel. Yeah. And it was on a Friday night, but it was like
during lockdown, but even during lockdown, Friday nights are still weird. Like you still feel like,
do I want to be on a zoom because I feel like I'm doing that all week and it's working in its own
way. Uh, but that was, it was him. So I was like, yeah, dude, let's do it, man. And, and we did,
and we drank on the zoom together and we just reminisced and talked and laughed. And I'm so happy
that that was like, I got to spend like two hours with him or however long I was just talking.
Pretty cool, you know, so RIP, Trev. Uh, yeah. My last time was that night with YouTube at the VW.
And then I took a, a, a sauce step, uh, Uber ride with him back to, back to his house. And then
I was like, oh, you live 10 feet from my house, which we did not know. Um, anyway, ride that Uber.
I think I stayed behind like, what do you mean you're going? Oh, yeah, you stayed. I was like,
it's 330 Joe. Uh, anyway, yes, great man. RIP loved his family and loved his friends. Uh,
let's get on as difficult as it will be with the laughs and the show. Uh, Joe, what's new with you,
what's happening in your world? Has the temp gone down? Has your core temp cooled?
I've cooled off since the last app. What are you drinking, by the way?
Water. What were you drinking before, though? Coconut water. Oh, that's why I was all
clever. I think I got a cocktail. So I'm coming. No. Oh, that was, uh, come.
Gathered from my gentleman friends. Uh, our movie today has a come shot in it, which is unnecessary.
Wow, it sure does. We'll get to that later. What's new? My core temp has gone down. I have two
shows tonight here in the great Big Apple, New York City. I'm very happy with my stand -up lately.
I'm only doing it in New York right now, but I'm discovering, discovering new things and, um,
kind of writing props, right? From what I've heard a lot of props you've been discovered. Yeah, props
and the props give me bops. And I get and pops from the audience. So yeah, it'll work out. But, uh,
all right, I'm happy about that. I'm, you know, doing stand -up like this now on my own terms versus
doing it because I have to pay my bills, right? It's it's such a different experience. It's just like
enjoyable again. Like who, who thought it could be enjoyable again? Jody, ever go outside of your
apartment and look up and portal around and go, I love you, Big Apple, and I want to take a bite.
Yeah, I do. And then usually somebody from above spits on me into your open mouth as you're taking the
bite of the big apple. The, uh, then he yells down after I have a disease. As you swallow a spit.
I'll do that. Sometimes I'll come in very excited from a long day out in the city. And I'll
put my back against the wall and just sort of slide down as I smile, giggle, and then kind of a sigh.
And then maybe a wistful tear because you're alone too. Yeah. Yeah. You know, you've got the city,
but you don't have that other thing. Love. Yeah. I don't need it. I love the stage.
I'm glad to hear you doing the stand -up. I'm excited to come out and enjoy one of these delicious
sandwiches. Uh, do you have a liquor license? Yeah, liquor license. I promote this dance.
Dance. Yeah, I know. We just sort of an opening date yet, but I did receive the liquor license
on my birthday. It seemed like Kismit. Uh, so Joey Rose's brick and mortar is coming very soon.
It will be a fun neighborhood bar that also has a great selection of these sandwiches. It's going to be
a place where you can affordably drink and eat and have a great fucking time. Uh, that's, that's
as best as I can put it right now. I think you're all going to really enjoy this place.
All of you that live within blocks of it, they can come to it. The rest of you are going to, you know,
this is going to be an open till four joint. Uh, two, two. Yeah, two sandwiches right up till two.
Are we cutting them off? That's what we're planning on doing. A couple nights a week, we're only open
till 12 because we're a new spot. So you, you know, they kind of easy. But we, uh, you know, the nights
that count were open till two Thursday, Friday, Saturday. Um, you know, so it's, it's going
to be a good time. It's going to be a good time. And yeah, the plan is just to serve right up until close.
Okay. So there you go. Uh, you ever think about calling it sand witchcraft?
There is a place called, did you know that there's a place called a witchcraft that's like sand,
which is a something I forget what they have. That's a good, it's good name. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
So, uh, I was going to call it sand, sandy witchway, but loose.
Uh, Joe again with these weird connections between us as we were having on the last podcast,
my first up in my, uh, movie reviews is any which way, but loose, which I watch for the first time.
Give it to me right now. Give it to me. Well, let me make sure that's the one I saw and not every
which way you can. What's what's the difference? The difference is, is every which way you can,
sounds like a movie about a man that will fuck a monkey because he's horny enough.
The first one sounds a little more like a screw ball, paper. No, actually, every which way, but loose
sounds like if any part of you's loose, I'm not fucking it. I'll only fuck the parts that are tight.
Or this, this orangutan is getting any which way, but loose from my
clutches. Yeah, because I'm fucking it. Uh, maybe that's what I watched was indeed because I
get them mixed up. Obviously, uh, pulled out my old Clint collection, which if it's, I mean,
I got this on Amazon years ago for like $20 and it has 80 Clint Eastwood movies. Yeah. Uh, I'm pumped
about cry macho by the way. Eastwood and, uh, yo, I was a trailer. I haven't watched it yet. It's,
you know, there's, it's basically him going, you get a cray macho, you know, like that's basically
the whole trailer. Uh, I think I could tell this story on here. I don't think this is out of line.
And I don't think I'm talking out of school, but oh, I told you that I had an idea for a dirty Harry
reboot. Yeah. I told the idea to, uh, this is how I'll keep it discrete. I told it to a friend of mine
who's way up the ladder in the business. He said, why don't you add his son to it and it's about
his son taking up the mantle. We developed a whole idea. He gets in touch with Scott Eastwood and
pitches it to Scott Eastwood. Okay. And we got about as far as, you know, guys,
uh, my dad does been here in this for years, man. Oh, no. Oh, no. But he did say I like the idea.
I like this take on the idea. And I'll take it to my dad. So there's a chance Clint Eastwood has heard
my dirty Harry pitch. I don't think anything's going to come out of it. Right. But it was just one of
those like son of a bitch, man. I remember pitching the Ralph Wachio and saying, we have this comedy show
idea. You're where these agents. Right. It was me and Robert Kelly. We play these agents who get
booted from William Morris. And then all we can do is, is, is, is represent like retired
sealist actors and you're our top client. This is the way before Cobra Kai. Yeah. And, uh,
and the first episode is we get you a gig hosting Williams Botca's Super Bowl party. And we leave
you there. And then he actually beats you up for real. Like, uh, and he goes, guys, people have been
trying to get me and Billy back on screen for years. And I was like, you're just like, God,
damn it. Yeah. Little did I know. And I just said, we want to do a sequel to the karate kid. He
would have been like, sure. Well, I think they had been approached about doing that too. I think it was
my, my buddy's take it. Right. I've said I'm good friends with all three of those guys. I think it was
their genius take that they've been telling me for 10 years that made them go, this is worth doing.
And they were right. I don't think it was a particularly fresh pitch, but they just had a great
take on it. Um, but yeah, um, I was talking about every which way. Sorry, Clint Eastwood. Clint,
I can't close now. But, uh, Clint, did you didn't speak to him, right? No. Yeah. No. Scott's son,
I apparently took the, I don't know who was great in Wrath of Man. He's amazing. I was watching
McCartney 321 or whatever on Hulu. It's one of the lamest documentaries I've ever seen.
His Rick Rubin nodding his head and playing on a, on a mixing board, isolated like bass tracks from
Beatles songs and then McCartney chewing gum and nodding his head and then going like, yeah, remember when
we wrote this one, you know, John turned to me and he says, Paul, I think I've got a melody that I can
lay on top of it. And they cut to Rick Rubin. He's like, yeah, yeah. Then he comes in with the melody.
And at some point, you're like, you're describing writing a song. And you've done it now for six hours.
And I've watched it all. God damn it. Yeah. It's just it was so fucking boring. And then at, at
different parts of it, Rubin is sitting like meditation style on the floor. Yeah. Yeah.
Front of McCartney. And then it's like, oh, yeah. Oh, God, it fucking sucked. It was so boring.
Not one story I hadn't heard five billion times. And then he doesn't tell the story you want to hear,
which is about him and John Lennon jacking off together when they were kids. That's the story we want.
Yeah. Get into how much you hate Yoko. Yes. But he's too nice to really get like the meat of the
stories that you want. But my really, I don't know why I'll wait. I got a Kevin. We got to
pull McCartney story. Well, I mean, this will just be a real sloppy one. It's right. We'll get back to
any which way of it. Because I got to I'm not going to go there. I'm going to go. The reason I'm saying
all this and I'll count that as one of my reviews is that you don't know until you pitch an idea
if it's genius. Like he talks about the song yesterday. And he was like, it was so simple. I was like,
this song's probably been, you know, 50 times. We've been around for 50 years. And I just am
using an old melody. It's too simple. There's no way I thought of something that's good. And then
turns out it was yesterday. You don't know until you do it out loud. It's a shit song.
Yesterday, it's a little one note. My favorites. It's up there with a magic. I mean, it's just a
shit. I've become friends with Kevin Farley over the years who was brothers with Chris Farley
and an actor in his own, right? Yes. Yeah. Yeah. But the point of this story is you remember to
gather the short live boy band spoof on MTV. Yes. He played one of them. I do. But I only
mentioned his relationship to Chris because it relates directly to the story. In the David Spade
audio book, he tells a story, David Spade tells a story about Farley having his brother's backstage
at SNL. And he's like, and he's like, Farley's got his brother's back there who should never speak.
And he goes, Paul McCartney comes walking through and one of them drunkenly yells, hey, Paul,
you're getting a little gray, like right before Paul goes on stage. And then Spade goes,
a spade. I don't know. David Spade goes, there's big goes, like it was funny. And then he goes,
all right, it was kind of funny, right? So I see Kevin Farley recently at a friend's birthday party.
I'm like, dude, I'm sorry. I don't mean to ask you David Spade questions because Kevin
dictored with David Spade for a long time. I'm like, I'm not trying to be the guy asking about
the other guy. I got to know is this story true? And he's like, oh, yeah. And he told me the whole story.
And he we were laughing hysterically. And he goes, it's my brother, forget which brother it was.
But he goes, dude, he showed up that night to the taping shit faced. And we were like, what are you
doing, man? Uh huh. And he goes, we were back backstage watching Paul McCartney go on drinking out
of red solo cups. And he said every bit of it is true. Every bit of the story is true. And I was like,
that's great tale. Fucking incredible, man. Well, I love those spade audio books. I remember
that story from there. I lost it. They're just fun like light reads. There's also the stories. There's
that really long chapter about the plus one where Spade talks about that friend to his.
Right. Yeah. Yeah. Who's like so insane. And like such a month, like just an animal.
Like a guy. I said, do you do you know who that is? He goes, oh, yeah. His name was such
that I go, are those stories true? He goes, 100 % everyone is just real. And then he started telling
me the stories. He's like, does he talk about when he went to just shoot me? And the guy came in
all fucked up from hanging out with Mick Jagger. I was like, yes, it's all in the book.
Yeah. So anyway, all right. Yeah. I once pitched a movie called plus one
about a bringing a crazy plus one to a wedding. I pitched it to Isla Fisher and her husband,
Sasha Berko and sat in the room looking very angry from the jump.
But there was like one scene where she had a conflict with another woman. And she stopped me and
was like, does every movie have to be about fighting between women? Does every comedy have to be
about fighting between women? And I was like, what happened? And the whole vibe went south. And
box office gold. You know what I mean? She's not, you know what I mean? It's like, yeah,
not I do put the brakes a little bit here. She's a Rob Schneider. You know what I mean? It's like,
yeah, come on. And this by the way, this was a decade ago. This wasn't like now where you'd be like,
now naturally, these women are respectful of each, you know, it was like back when every movie was
like involved Ryan Reynolds eating dog come. Speaking of. Oh, that freaky comedy. Oh,
guy, I can't anymore. I can't. It's I'm getting pop ups on every website. This is the free guy.
The free. Come on, free guy. What are you about free guy? Tell us what you're about. I know what it's
about. It's about a guy in like a grand theft auto video game, but like one of the background people
that has like no part in the story who realizes he's in a video game and then does like a matrix
thing where he's like, I can do whatever I want. I live in a video game and I can become the here.
It's one of the dumbest fucking premises I've ever heard. I, who gives a rat's ass? This is up
there with pixels, which that where Evan James plays the president of the United States by the way.
I don't know if you knew that because I watched pixels. I watched. Jesus Christ.
Speaking of movies that make little to no sense. Yeah, I watched cops and robbersons.
Oh, no, I saw that. That's how that theatrically. That's the biggest left yet on a title that someone
watched. I haven't thought about that movie since I saw it in theaters in 1994. I was in a
space. I believe with pulp fiction in the next theater and I was like, why can't I see good movies yet?
Oh, my God. That's great. I was in a space last week where I was just like, please just take
Calgon, take me away. Get me out of this headset headspace. I was like, there's got to be funny parts
in this. There's got to be because it's like right on the edge of Chevy Chase starting to make the bad
movies. It's Chase and Palin's, right? Yeah. And Palin's is actually very funny in it. Palin's
is very funny in it. He's got that thing where Diane Whiske who plays Chevy Chase's wife in the
matriarch. Yeah. Where she's trying to like powerhouse cast. Yeah. She's trying to con Palin's into
cutting the lawn. Yeah. And he goes, he goes, let me, let me, let me be clear about something,
Missy. I don't cut grass. I never cut grass. I never had a lawn. And if I had one, I'd kill it.
Okay. All right. Funny. I'm funny. Chase has his moments, you know, the scene that everybody knows
from the movie that knows any other movie is when Chase is trying to prove that he's a smoker
and that he with Robert Davie playing the criminal. Right. And he rolls that cigarette and it's like,
it's all stuck, it's all stuck in his mouth and his teeth. That's a pretty funny Chevy Chase thing.
The terrible movie, there's a funny gag where the kid thinks he's Dracula and and it attacks Jack
Palin's and then it cuts the Chevy Chase going, I'm sorry, my son bit your neck and tried
to suck your blood out of it. Like, you know, there's some moments that are like kind of funny.
What is the plot of it? I don't even remember. The plot of it is that is the family's name,
really, the robbersons. Yeah, they're called the robbersons. Jesus Christ, that's bad. The plot is,
it's that I bet this sold on like one sentence. I bet this is like a one sentence pitch.
They're bringing out the prices right style novelty check as you're finishing the time to sign over to
you. Yeah, so the they're called the robbersons. Chevy Chase is a dad who has no control or connection with
his family. He's losing touch with his kids and he's obsessed with TV cop shows.
A boot a counterfeiter played by Robert Davie is living next door to him and Jack Palin's the
hard -boiled cop decides they have to set up the stakeout in Chevy Chase's house. There it is. Chevy
Chase gets excited because it's cop stuff. Right. He gets to involved. He helps. It's not a bad premise.
Not a bad premise. Not a terrible premise. And then Jack Palin's who's never loved anybody in his
life eventually becomes endeared to the family and they start to fall in Uncle Jack and all that
stuff. It's actually kind of sweet in places. It's a terrible terrible movie. But I watched it. Okay.
I'll count that McCartney rant as one of mine. I watched every which way but loose, which I started
I think 30 minutes ago. And I bought it because I've been going into these new Beverly double features
to kind of get out of the house, clear my head a little bit. And I bought tickets to any which way
you can. And then I was like, well, shit, I'll be lost. I've never seen the original. So I mean,
this movie, my guess, and it looks like when did smoking the band it come out? 77 Star Wars year?
Yeah. 70. So second highest -grossing movie that year. It seems crazy to me that Clint would
need to do this, but it seems very clearly to be like, get me my smoky. Yeah. Bring me my smoky
independent. And they're like, okay, but how about this time with a monkey? And he's just like sold.
I think he was in a little bit of a slump because the dirty Harry movies had sort of tarnished him,
but they were also very successful. Yeah. And they were pushing him to do the more those. And he was like,
I'm not doing it. And it was kind of like, okay, well, then you do this monkey movie. I think that's
what happened. They were, they were huge hits. I mean, this movie is very stupid. It is
incompetent, really. The monkey and Clint, like, their relationship, I guess, is kind of sweet.
The story is, you know, it's just kind of a bunch of random incidents. I'm not thrilled now about
going to see the sequel. I might set this one out, but have you seen these pictures?
I saw the first one when I was very young. And, you know, it's a monkey and or you're
angiting. And so I, of course, I thought it was funny, but like, I wouldn't watch it now.
I mean, it's really like designed towards kids and and stupids. Yeah. I think it's a kids movie.
Yeah. All right. Uh, the reason I watched cops and robbersons, because I was led into it from funny
farm. Uh, I rewatched it. I wanted to rewatch it after we talked about that. The, the, the hats off
review, whatever the YouTube channel was. I was talking about that, that said, it was in their
almost cult classics thing or whatever. I, um, and Tarantino discussed it at length on his podcast.
Yeah. Um, I saw this in the theater. I didn't like it when I saw it in the theater.
I was, uh, and after hearing this review, I was like, I was probably too young to get it.
Rewatched it here. Didn't really like it again. I got to be honest like it had some moments that are
funny, but like overall, it's a very, it's in the vein. There, there were, this was a type of
comedy that was coming out at this time period where they, they, they, it was very dry in places,
but then there would be gags. Right. And they also, because, but they were trying to make like a more
high brow. You know, I honestly, this is, and we've disagreed on it, but this is like right when,
this is right in there with like crocodile dundee. This is right in there with what about Bob. Yeah.
This is when these types of comedies were coming out of the house sitter with Steve Martin Golding on.
Yeah. And I felt like they never committed hard enough in any one direction. This movie is also like
that for me. We're like, it's funny to watch JVJ's get hit in the balls with a doorknob and funny when
he pulls a snake out of the lake. Right. But then a while, man, the crazy male man throwing the
male out was pretty funny. It's pretty funny. Like the first two times they do it like five times,
man. You know, the Chris for me, that's just fun. But yeah. Yeah. For me, that's a lot of just when
I saw it, you know, when I was a kid and anything with Chevy or Martin short or Steve Martin or John
Candy, I'll love them forever, even though, you know, they don't not all of them hold up. I saw this
in the movies. I think the same week I saw the great outdoors. The great outdoors is another one of
these movies. We've discussed the funny parts in the great outdoors. Yeah. The great outdoors is not
in my opinion a solid comedy. It just has some really funny moments. The teen romance shoehorned into
that is one of the most embarrassing subplots in movie history. I can't believe they they allowed it.
Yeah. It was it was so boring. And then Dan Acroix and John Candy and a net -bending, you know,
like these amazing characters. And we're going back to like two teenagers like, is this your first summer
at the lake? Yeah. She's unacceptable. It's unacceptable. But I'd I'd put summer rental in there too.
You know, big laughs. But between you're basically watching an episode of Full House, you know,
there are a lot of comedies like that through the years. Dan Acroix's funniest monologue ever is
in great outdoors with the with the mental patients that escaped. They dismember their their victims
and eat them. And then him and he get with so no more scary things. Yeah. No, I think I think the
movies of a solid B plus a minus. But that again is probably the age I saw it. Well, I watched Joe,
a movie you just did on here. What happened was, which I thought I had seen, but never had seen,
the one basically one night after our style movie with Tom Noon and Karen Silas having a very
awkward first date. Joe raved about it. I heard somebody on a podcast rave about it. It's up on
criterion channel right now. And you know, it's really good. I liked it a lot. I love the vibe. It's
it's certainly not a very satisfying movie. It just kind of leaves you uncomfortable. When I read
up about it, dark stuff. It is very dark. The story she tells, like when she reads her book, I was like,
I was laughing. And then I was like deeply disturbed. And I love where it goes. It keeps you kind of
on the edge of your seat, which is very strange for like a two character romantic movie. But
I dug it quite a bit. And I learned that it is the favorite or at least one of the very favorite films
of Charlie Kaufman who did being on Malcolm's adaptation. And that makes a lot of sense. It feels like a
very big influence on some of his recent movies, especially, which made me when I read that,
I heard that too about Charlie Kaufman and like Tom Noonan is at no loss for work. He's in everything
that's ever happened. Yeah. But you hear that. You're Tom Noonan and you hear that.
Well, no, he put him in that animal Lisa. Like he did the voice of the lead guy. And he's
in the lead. Oh, okay. All right. Well, then he tosses him a bone here and there. Okay.
My last one is, and I watched this also because of funny farm, the money pit. Oh, love it.
Uh, but again, some sitcom shit in there too. It's, it's, it's enjoyable enough.
How about when, how about Hanks's laugh when the bathtub falls through the floor? Yeah, amazing
moment. Amazing. Yeah. How about Luna and his Tom Hanks? Like he doesn't do that anymore.
When he hits himself in the thumb with the hammer. How about his reaction to that?
His reaction to that. Him in the, him in the, uh, floor stuck. Great stuff.
I've been here. You know, he's like, he's trying to do a gene wilder or something in his early movies.
And he's great at it. And the, the, it's an enjoyable film. Um, it's ridiculous. I mean,
they buy this house and the house turns out to be a money pit. It's a, it's a bad investment.
But like directed by Dick Donner, RIP recently passed RIP Dick. It's falling apart in a way where you're like,
they couldn't have faked the sale. Like it's like literally the first day they're in there,
the bathtub falls before the staircase collapses. Like it's so insane. And you're like,
all right, guys. But, uh, so, so it's a little much, but hey, I guess if I'm complaining about
movies taking it, taking a stance and leaning hard in one direction, this certainly does that.
Uh, it gets a little depressing towards the end because they him and Shelley Long are going to get
to where Shelley Long's great. And then I forgot how much I enjoyed watching Shelley Long, because
you don't see her in a ton of stuff. No, I think it's modern families, but not much else. By the way,
Richard Benjamin directed the money pit. I was wrong. Normally, I would just let that go, but I looked
it up and you said Donner, I knew that was wrong, but I didn't know who directed it.
Richard, yeah, it's not Richard Donner, it's Richard Benjamin, but I do love Richard Donner.
And he did recently pass an RIP, Dick Donner. And Richard Benjamin's no slouch, you know, from West
World. No, he isn't. Oh, yeah, that's right. Yeah. But, uh, but all in all, you know, you're getting
that you get a Tom, so Tom Hanks box set for yourself and that's in there. It's worth a watch.
I have a Tom Hanks box set with drag net, which is not a good film.
I'm enjoyable at times though. At times. It's another one of these things where you're like,
they're really funny. Well, the, the milk factory thing. Yeah, milk,
all sort of new trenches, but I'm sure you wouldn't know anything about that. Would you?
Acroid in that does have some moments for sure. Yeah. Uh, Andy Coleman is great. You're right.
And don't watch the rap video of Tom Hanks and Dan Acroid rapping. If you ever want to respect
either one of them again. Yeah. No. And in fact, Dabney Coleman and drag net playing the porn
king with the list. Yeah. I'm convinced Philip Baker Hall. That was what he took from for boogie nights.
It's like they're doing like the same voice. Yeah. You know, they're doing our wrong.
The same fucking voice. It's crazy. Yeah. Anyway, let's get to our film for today. That's three and three.
The Green Knight. Green Knight. This is the, the sequel to Green Day. The beloved band that
broke big with dookie on the pop punk charts back in 1994. And a prequel to the green giant,
the upcoming string beans. String beans, bio pick. They would do it too. That, that,
that deadline announcement is going to happen by a year's end. They, you know,
they got a Chester Cheetah, Flamin' Hot Cheetos movie coming out. You got a Chrissy Teague
and documentary about French fries. Yes. Yes. That, here's what it'll be. It'll be like, uh,
you know, a beautiful like New Zealand, Lord of the Rings type thing. And then there's a giant
like Lake. And then you hear this. And the lake like vibrates and all the trees sway around. And then it
it's like this fall. It just, that's where the teas are in. It's coming 2023. Yeah. Yeah.
And then maybe like a pee, a pee, the size of a watermelon like falls to the ground to kind of give
you a little taste. Yes. Uh, I will say this about the Green Knight. It's a, it's a,
based on our, our, our, our Thorian legend, lure. Is that how you say that King Arthur lure? Yeah.
It's an old poem. I, I knew I was in trouble. The fucking second. They were like, if you're familiar
with the, with the, you know, the full length poem, you're going to enjoy the movie a lot more.
And I was like, I'm not, and I'm not going to get familiar with it. Um, this is the movie
produced by a 24. This is the movie. It finally happened, folks. It finally happened. I hate a 24 now.
It took about four flicks, but I do not like this company anymore, man. Like this is such,
oh, for Christ's sakes, what a just masturbatory boring, literally masturbative bullshit,
fucking movie that didn't deliver on anything. They made it look like it would in the trailer.
Just a pointless fucking film point. Yeah. It's like their, their thing is vibes.
You know, and they all are starting to have the same vibe and feel like it, it feels like it's
like a factory that is shooting all of these movies regardless of genre in the exact same way.
And moment to moment, that can be beautiful. There's lots of like really great images and those
don't get me wrong, but you're just like, it's becoming a cliche. You're not, you can't call this like
art anymore when you're doing it the exact same way every time. Something like the lighthouse mixes
it up by going black and white or something like that. But by and large, the 824 aesthetic is becoming
you know, too much of what they are. It's not, it's almost feels like they're a studio that's
imposing what they want on filmmakers. I don't know if that's true, but it's just they all have the
same look and vibe to me. I think I know we disagreed harshly on midsummer, but to me, this was a
fairy tale version of midsummer. It was the same fucking thing. It was a lot of nothing,
it was a lot of despicable characters I didn't really care about. It was a lot of, not a lot of,
but in this, but the shock value when you needed, when they needed to shock you, you know, I didn't
need to see the guys to scene where Joe Edgerton comes into this thing 90 minutes in or something to
play some prints. Well, okay, let's start at the beginning. Swinger prints. Yeah, I don't even know.
So he, so the movie starts awesome. It starts awesome. It starts on Christmas morning.
Our hero is in a whorehouse. He's in love with one of the prostitutes. I think I just said two words
you're not supposed to say anymore, but yeah, sex worker. Yeah. Believe it or not, the nights of
the round didn't call them sex workers. But anyway, they, they, and he's going to become knighted on
this day, right? And he goes to the king. And you know, he says, I'm not worthy to be knighted. I'm not
honorable enough. They're more honorable men. I'm okay. I'm listening. And income is the
green night voiced by the man from the witch. The man with the scariest voice of all time. Right.
Played the dad and the witch. And he challenges the night, which one of you nights will come up and strike
me. And if you strike me a year from today, I'll strike you back. And what it's this really,
when the green night is clearly otherworldly. Yeah. Do you know that guy also plays on the British
office? His like super sleazy friend? Yeah. Isn't that hilarious? Yeah. I always love that carrot finchie.
Yeah. So he, he goes, I'll do it. I'll, you know, and then because he wants to show off, he cuts the
green nights head off and then the green night lives and picks up his head and says, one year thus
or whatever and rides off. And you're like, and then you realize a year later, this guy's got to go
face this guy again. And he's going to go on this big adventure and journey to get to him. And I'm,
I'm excited at this point. I'm excited because now I'm not taking your note from you, Pat. But I'll say
at this point in the, in the theater, I'm going, this feels like early Terry Gilliam. This feels like
we're going on a really fun like time bandits kind of adventure. I know from the trailer, he encounters
giants at one point. Like, this is going to be really cool. There's a talking fox at one point.
Like, they showed that much in the trailer. I'll grant you first 15, 20 minutes. I'm like, this,
this looks awesome. This is beautiful. I, I'm into the story enough. And now we're going to go
meet all these fun characters on an Odyssey. And then he leaves the town a year later.
One year hence. That's what he says. He leaves the town one year hence.
And from this point on, it's basically a man riding on a horse.
Nothing really happens. He meets, he meets a thief at one point who's very sinister. That seems
like it's going to be interesting. But then it just isn't. Every time he loses something he needs
for his journey, like the acts that the Green Knight gives him and says protect it well and all
that. It just magically appears again. There's a kind of cool sequence where he finds a woman that says,
I need you to go into the lake and find my head, which is sort of a Tim Burtony vibe for a second.
Right. But that kind of goes nowhere.
And then if it religiously follows the poem, and I don't know if it does or if it doesn't.
But it's not a very good poem. It certainly doesn't translate well to a film story. But
if this is just the guy, what the guy wanted to do, then I don't know how he goes in and pitches
the story and doesn't have them go, well, what, what? Like that's the thing. You can let people
indulge too much. And people are raving about it, but they're raving about the visual aspects of it.
Like this is just, it feels like a big missed opportunity. Like you've got this, this budget and
these amazing sets and costumes and all this, but it's like to what end and nothing really pays off
in it. And everything is used as a symbol of how this guy is actually not a very good knight,
especially when he comes on the thing. Then it's like now he's, he's not a pure knight or whatever.
Like it's very boring. It's, it's what they call episodic where you're just going from thing to
thing to thing and it has no real impact on anything. And that's, you know, generally what they
consider bad storytelling, episodic. And that's just how it feels. Yeah. It comes one thing to the
next with no through line. Joe Edgerton comes into this late in the game and he's got a beautiful wife
that lives with him. And he says, whatever is mine by Alicia DeCanter. Yeah. Whatever is mine in my
castle is yours. And you must tell me as long as you tell me what you receive while you were here.
Yeah. And what he ends up receiving is he grinds Alicia DeCanter till he comes.
And then she gives him a belt that will bring him no harm. That also was the same belt that he
loses along the journey at the beginning that his mother gives him the girdle. He comes on the girdle.
Yeah, he comes on the belt and they show the cum, which again, I don't need to see, but
but also his mother gives him the same girdle and he loses it. Then he gets it back. He's losing
everything through the journey and then getting it back through these little encounters, which I get
that that's a device and whatever. But it also strikes up a sort of strange thing where you're like,
is he fucking his mom like what is going on? I kind of didn't quite get the correlation.
Yeah. But I guess it was just that he didn't appreciate any women in his life.
And anyway, then he takes the girdle. He gets to the green night. His penance is he must be
beheaded because he beheaded the night. So he needs blow for a blow. So he gets to the night.
The night goes to behead him and he says, I can't do it and he runs home. And then he lives a life
where of a lie where he says he's done his deed and he becomes the worst human being ever.
The prostitute that he's in love with has his baby. He gives her money and disowns her and no
one can ever know because she's a prostitute. Sex worker. Sex worker. He what's it called?
He then rules his kingdom but isn't I guess I think it's like he's not really respected by his
subjects. And then his son grows up and dies in battle. And finally he's going to be overthrown
from the throne in his old age. And it's just thing after thing after thing tragedy if tragedy happens.
And you realize this man has no honor. He had no honor in keeping the vow with the night.
And he had no and then that that lack of honor polluted the rest of his life. And then right at the end of
much like, well, I don't want to say it's much like another movie though. He comes to and realizes
none of this has happened. This was all in his head. It was a fantasy of things that could come.
And with honor, he lays down in front of the night and says, do do it. Kill me. And he says, but wait.
And he takes off the belt that will never that'll protect him from ever being harmed.
And the night goes to kill him. And then the night stops short of his neck and says, you've done well
soldier. Now go home. And you realize he's he's faced the challenge properly. He is a man of honor.
And being a man of honor, he doesn't get killed. And then the last line of the movie is the evil green
night smiling at him and saying, now off with your head, a pun. Meaning you get your ass out of here.
That's the last line of the movie. There you go. That's the green night.
Is that for sure a pun? Yeah, he looks at him and smiles and he goes now off and he nods like, go home.
He goes now off with your head and he smiles like, he's wanting to make sure I had read it correctly. Yeah, it's
it's just super unsatisfying, you know, it's I saw it at the theater. It was a fairly crowded theater.
And there was just a collective sort of grunt and shrug that has come from I felt that it's so many
movies throughout the last 40 years where just the whole theater at the end is like, God damn it.
And then you get online and every review is fucking jizzing about this movie just like dev Patel
jizzed on his fucking green girdle. I mean, what are these fucking critics talking about? I mean,
how much payola is going on at this point? This is a masterpiece, masterpiece,
masterpiece. It's like, okay, and the guy, David Lowry who I've read interviews with him seems
like a very cool guy, but like he did the Pete's Dragon reboot, which I didn't see and he did a ghost
story, which is like it contains a 12 -minute scene of the lead actress eating a pie. An unbroken 12 -minute
scene of the actually eating a pie. Now, this one had a very controversial and highly discussed
scene, but like to me, that's a director I don't trust. He did it in this, the riding the horse out
of the kingdom. Yeah. Yeah. He hung on that for like five minutes. And at first, I was like, oh,
that's pretty cool. Like he's showing you how long this would take. Like this is a slow real -time
journey. And I was like, all right, that's kind of cool, but then later you're just like, oh,
fuck you, dude. By the way, the thing with the giants, it turns out in the movie to be a hallucination.
He eats mushrooms. And he holed another mid -summer fucking connection. But I do want to go on record
as saying I really love the film mid -summer. Have you seen it again since you saw it in the theater?
No, I want to watch the director's cut. Maybe I'll do it tonight. God damn it.
I have a feeling your opinion is going to change a bit. But we'll see. We'll see.
But I hate this shit. I hate these kinds of movies. I can't stand it. It's stupid. It's fucking dumb.
Like I just hate it. I'm not a sword and sorcery guy at all. Not really my thing. I was very excited
about this. And the trailer looks awesome. And that kind of is what a lot of these movies wind up being
is it's almost like they make the trailer first. And then once people get excited about they're like,
you know, throw whatever you want up there. And the movies are not they're not ending properly.
They're not making sense sometimes. I don't know. I found this
to be beautiful. I'll give credit where it's due. And I like some of the camera work and the shots.
And like you said, the beginning is cool. But when you look back at it, like I felt like
everybody else in the audience just like, you know, like don't make me leave my home in a God
damn pandemic for this. It's this thing that's happening with all the genres that we talk about a lot.
Now it's now it's infected sword and sorcery. Now. Oh, now let's start making sword and sorcery
movies that don't have any sword or sorcery in them. Right. It's not cool to have to have a story.
Hey, but it's also it's like it's not cool to have the elements that make it a genre film.
You're doing the genre without doing the genre. And that's maybe that's cool for like one movie
as an experiment. But when it's your whole aesthetic, it starts to get very predictable.
It's getting very frustrating. It's no monster horror movies, no scary horror movies, no joke,
no comedy comedies. Now it's going to be no fantasy fantasy films. What a fucking snooze, man.
What a fucking sound. I like sword and sorcery stuff. But I hate these kinds of movies that give
you nothing that don't deliver on any front. And God damn it. I'm going to say it. You can't
fuck you with the main actor is I believe Indian. Yeah. And right away they have a the widest
king I have ever seen in my life, the most English widest, you know what I mean?
Arian looking man I've ever seen. And then he goes, I protect you because you are my sister's child.
And it's like these men are not blood related. Can't you make the king look like the nephew?
Like, can't you put two actors of this non -white persuasion into this part? What fuck you with this
hole? Like we don't have to explain it. It doesn't have to make sense. Whatever. And then you're going
and then they're going, well maybe it was, you know, maybe, maybe, maybe his father was. And then
they show the mom. And it's like, no, the mom is also like, this is not this man's blood sister.
This is absurd. I can't disagree. You know, the entire fucking movie is white people. You can't
put a couple extra non -white actors in. So this guy's heritage makes sense as your main character.
It's ridiculous. I won't disagree. Thank you. But yeah, it's it's a it's a frustrating experience as
you can as you can planly hear in Joe's voice. It's it goes nowhere and it takes a while to get there.
Is it something you need to see as a film fan? You know, it's something visually striking that is
out there now, but it's it's also just it really winds up feeling like a waste of time.
It winds up feeling like late Terry Gilliam. It starts feeling like great early Terry Gilliam. Yeah.
It ends feeling like horrible get me out of your recent Terry Gilliam. That's why I said I wasn't
trying to steal your note because yeah, it's text to me while you're watching it. This feels like
late Terry Gilliam. Yeah, you're absolutely right. It starts as early and then ends as late and you're
right. Yeah, but the end of this thing, you're like, you're watching that fucking Dr.
Parniseepist movie or whatever that fucking thing is. The imaginary of Dr. Parnassus. Yeah, it's like
and everybody fucking hated that movie, by the way. You go look up the reviews of that. It's got
like a 4 % or the brother's grim with Matt Damon. They gave that a 5%. I mean, they everybody hated
those movies, but then this comes out and it's it's masterpiece season. I don't know. I'm all for
people's visions. I'm all for weird shit, to be honest with you. I'm all for things not making sense,
but this just did not put them together in any sort of compelling way. I just that's all I
can say. Two hogs down. Two hogs down for the green night. And that's our show folks. We'll
be back next month with four episodes as usual. I don't know what we're going to do yet. You don't
know what we're going to do yet, but we haven't discussed it, but I will guarantee that we will do
don't breathe too, which comes out this weekend. I want to see it badly. So I hear it's awesome.
I only want to see it because of the reviews. I did. I was not a big fan of don't breathe one,
but I love Stephen Lang and I do want to see this. And so I will be doing that at some point. We'll
probably do pig at some point and he still need to see pig. Yeah, those will probably be two of the four.
Stuff's coming up. But anyway, folks, thanks for listening. Thank you for your support. Thank you
Emily for all she does. Thank you, Will Potter, if keeps coming out with the artwork. Appreciate it.
And thanks for sticking with us here on Patreon. We'll see you next time. And we'll see you in hell.