I'm here for Bet Rivers online casino and sportsbook with poker icon Phil Helmuth.
And now thanks to the excitement of Bet Rivers, I'm also a slots icon.
That's great! And a same -game parlay icon. Cool, cool. A blackjack icon,
a money -line icon, a roulette. Take it from Phil Helmuth. If you love games,
Bet Rivers is the place to play in Bet. Bet Rivers. Games on.
Must be 21 plus in present in West Virginia. Void were prohibited. Terms in conditions apply.
gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamberland.
Firestone Complete Auto Care's epic savings advantage is the sign you need to stop putting
off your car's maintenance, and you can save up to $100 on tires and services while you're
at it.
Don't wait, call Firestone Complete Auto Care for an appointment.
This is a headgun podcast.
Hello everybody and welcome to we'll see you in hell on our new home the head
gum podcast network. This is season four of the show. Has it been so long, Joe? It
feels like it was only yesterday. You turned to me and said let's change the
world, baby. And we stood back to back and played dueling guitar riffs and changed
that world for good. And then I changed my pants because they had shittin' them. Oh,
oh, I thought you were going to go with com folks. This is, we'll see you in hell. It's
a weekly podcast. We talk about horror or sci -fi movie, but really, at the conversation,
you can go anywhere or fantasy or fantasy. That's not really fantasy out.
Fantasy as Gene Simmons would say. Fantasy action. That's what Logan was, right? Or, yes,
some action, whatever. Anyway, folks, without further ado, on with the show, and on with
the Joe. Thank you, Pat. You're welcome. That was the most committed you ever worded
doing that committed. It wasn't my favorite, but I've always committed, been quite committed
to it, but that was very committed. I should be committed. That's like a Vegas billboard.
He's a committed comedian dot, dot, dot. And then it's him in a straight jacket. And
he should be committed. Come check out many papots. Uh, the moron. I remember seeing the
billboards in New York for my mother's Jewish, my father's Italian and I'm in therapy. Oh,
Oh, God boy, did I love seeing those billboards?
And I remember my dad saying to me,
have you heard of this show?
It sounds very funny.
And I said, Dad, shut the fuck up, you asshole.
Yeah.
What are you talking about?
It's like that Tony and Tina's wedding,
where you're a part of the action.
I was in a ripoff of Tony and Tina's wedding,
not the actual Tony and Tina's.
You acted in it?
Yeah, I was in a show called the So Prano's dinner theater show
about the, when was this?
Yes.
When I first started doing comedy, 15 long years ago.
The so pranos, it doesn't even make sense.
Look, Pat, I didn't write the goddamn show.
I don't know, I just did it for the money.
What is that mean?
You were in the show and you don't know
what the so pranos, it was called this,
it was just their way of saying,
like we're doing a variation on the name so pranos.
Was it so dot dot dot pranos?
I can't remember.
It's a great question, I can't remember.
Or was it SEW?
No, it was like the so pranos.
Okay, I don't know.
I played PD the gay cousin who's not a part of the show.
They invented him for the stage.
Now, one to ten.
How flamboyant did you play it?
Ten, baby.
Ten, I'd say 11.
They should have said 11.
That would have been the right answer.
Yeah.
And my favorite thing that ever happened at the show was
Was a I'd a buddy Lev
Who was kind of like a tough kid or whatever and he had to play the PD part one night
Because I wasn't there or something like that so he stepped in and
He was you had to do table work yet to go table to table and talk to people as they ate their palm is John
So they were in Northeast Philadelphia and this
This, this burly man was really prodding him and being like, look at this kid, look at
this little pussy, look at this little, little fruit cup, you know what doing all that
shit?
And when, when love was at the table and love like work the table and walked around and lean
down into the guy's ear and said, hey buddy, this is just a fucking show, I'll beat the shit
out of you right now.
And the tough guy, Tattletail, on him, and Lev was fired immediately, was asked to leave.
Wow.
That's like that, that curve episode where he doesn't know if it's real or the bit.
It was, if you see him, though, when he runs another guy in the bathroom who's doing
talking to him.
And it was after I had done this.
Okay.
So that was magic to me, seeing Larry David be like, let's, let's just stop, I get what
we're doing.
Yeah.
Let him stop it right now.
How long did you do that and what did you make?
I made $150 a show, I believe.
Not bad.
And they took about two and a half, three hours.
That's pretty good.
It gave me great, great.
It was a great workshop for crowd work.
It taught you how to do crowd because you had to go table to table
and you had to really think on your feet.
As somebody else.
Let's not overstate what you're doing.
This isn't inside the actor studio here, Joe, you were doing the so pranos, you know,
in Philadelphia, getting into the nuance of the character, yeah, took time.
I'd sit out in the parking lot and I'd stare into my rear view mirror.
Let me ask you this, what is your favorite sound on noise?
I don't think I ever told this on the show.
I was telling this to somebody the other day.
When I was at Conan O 'Brien, I was the page and I would bring up the guests.
And very often we would have guests that would be there just for the sketches, and that
was a little awkward because they didn't get a dressing room.
But like James Lipton used to be in these sketches all the time when Conan was on a 12 -30 in
the morning.
So I picked James Lipton up, he's being very annoying.
He was always extremely annoying, had a lot of demands, he just wanted to talk, tell stories.
So like when it was revealed that he was a Pimp in France in his autobiography, wait, what?
I knew that because I had heard that story. Wait, he was an actual James Limson was a French Pimp
prior to what he does now, which I'm sure that shows over. Just, of course it was the most polite
of all Pimps. Yeah, exact. French Pimp. So he comes up and he's being really annoying and he goes,
Patrick, who are the guests today on the show? I was like, oh, it's a big one. It's Cameron Diaz.
who's, oh, Cammy's here. Cammy. I said, well, no, not yet, but she's going to be here shortly
and he's like, oh, I adore Cammy. Would it be all right if I said hello to her?
That's a weird area. I'm certainly not supposed to let anyone talk to the guest, but James
Lipton is sort of a celebrity. And that's also, that's a weird area. That's also what you said
to him on the drive over. He put his hand on you. Yeah. So I'm getting a little stressed out,
because I'm 22 and I could have them have these very tense encounters.
I think I did talk about the show when Peter Gallagher and Val Kilmer were at Conan and
they circled each other like dogs because Kilmer had stolen Gallagher's girlfriend 30 years
prior.
Like I've got some amazing stories that took place.
Kilmer, I would give, I'd give, I'm going to say this 10 years off my life for the privilege
to sit with Kilmer and get all the stories.
Yeah, he's not because that guy, him and Keith or Sutherland, I just, oh, God, I want
to sit down with the two of them and see what went on.
He was telling stories all day and today on Twitter, Kilmer was about how obsessed he is
with Kate Blanchett, and they were all fascinating stories.
God, damn it.
He's running around the country playing Mark Twain in these theater shows.
He's a loose cannon this guy.
No, I would go to that Mark Twain show if he comes here.
When I met Will McGrubber, Will Forte. When I met Will Forte, I told him how much I
loved McGrubber and he told me it was a great time. He said, and I go, I can't believe
how much you got away with in the movie. And he said the only thing we didn't get away
with was we actually wanted to have Val Kilmer's character eat his own dick. We wanted to
castrate the character and feed and Valkymer said I won't do that and we were like, but it's
just a prosthetic dick or whatever and Valkymer was like, I won't do it. And then I said,
Will, if you promised to put me in a grubber too, you can cut off my dick and feed it to me.
All right. And he said, you're actual dick and I said, yes, but you have to feed it to a prosthetic
man. And he laughed and it felt damn good while. Yeah. I made, I made forte laugh.
Um, he's a great dude when he was on, he was on SNL when I was there and he wasn't only the nicest of the cast
But he was like the nicest person I had ever met in my life. Very sweet man. Very nice. But anyway, good man
Good man, that will afford to. Here's Kilmer's tweet from today, which I thought was actually kind of beautiful. I
Fuck James Lipton in the room, sorry. Okay. Here's Kilmer's tweet from today. Yeah once I flew all the way to Australia
you just to talk to Kate Blanchett, her husband met me first, or instead, I guess, to be
more accurate.
This guy's going, I mean, she's just off the rails.
Yeah.
I mean, the husband comes out like, you're not going to be meeting with Kate Blanchett
today, you creep.
Yeah.
That's what that story means.
He is the character from Willow.
He's a man that's been living out in a wilderness cage for too long.
And he doesn't know how to interact properly with society anymore.
Yeah.
So there you go.
was, I'm sorry, I don't know why I'm drawing a blank, was it going to weaver the villain
in Willow? She wasn't. No, the villain in Willow, Mad Martin. That was, no, Mad Martin
was Val Kilmer, uh, Warwick Davis, I know that's Willow, of course. No, no, no, Willow's
the baby. Willow's the magic baby. Uh, I mean, you want to take cheap shots at Warwick Davis
for being short. I mean, you know, that's, that's on you, but I'm not going to do that.
I thought he was a baby if I'm not going to joke them.
Just because you carried a rattle around for the whole film, I don't understand.
The bad guy, or the bad lady, it was a woman, right?
It was a witch.
It was the...
I can't remember.
She's in some...
She's in other shit.
I just can't remember where she is.
But then the good witch sort of part was played by the old woman that was in the never -ending
story that eats the worms.
Right.
the one that's like drink this, right?
She doesn't look at that mountain.
And you see her sort of naked in it?
Like not.
Yeah, I remember that for sure.
Like they don't show like nips or bush or anything,
but like you see her like naked.
Cause she like, like a bird transforms into the woman
or something like, you know, she does some wizardy thing.
Well, the, okay, the witch was Joanne Whaley,
who became Joanne Whaley Kilmer, bell comers wife.
Really?
Yeah.
And uh...
She's got a BB new worth vibe if I'm not mistaken.
Rick Overton's in Willow.
Rick Overton?
Comedy's Rick Overton.
Yeah.
Yes he is, isn't he?
Now were you a Rick Overton man or a Rick Dukeamon man?
And I feel like this is like when you ask somebody beetles or stones.
I preferred a Dukeamon but I have met Overton and he could not have been a sweeter person.
Never met Overton, never met Dukeamon.
Overton's...
I mean I haven't done comedy in a while but every time I ever did comedy it seemed like
Overton was there.
I would love to meet over to Duke and it's crazy you have yes, I know. But I was a Duke and man because of the burbs because of the burbs
We see a stand -up to Duke and them probably
Yeah, yeah, he totally was
Let me finish my story so 20 minutes later
Which is probably my own fault James Lipton James Lipton what would I be permitted to see Kami when she arrives?
I was like how about I'll ask her, okay? I'll let her know and he goes actually I won't even bother her
He goes, would you mind if I just run a gift
into her real quick?
And he just found out she's on the fucking show,
but now he has a gift for her.
So I go, yeah, but I'm going down to pick her up now.
So just, you know, kind of in and out.
I get to get to talk to him like a kid.
And he's like, okay.
So he runs over to the makeup department.
And he's like, I'm just gonna try to find something
to give her as a gift, I guess.
But I get the call.
This is a good pimp.
I mean, this goes how to do it.
I get the call.
Cameron Diaz, the 50th Street side,
you gotta go pick her up.
I run downstairs, I pick her up.
But it could not have been nicer.
And we get up there and I'm like, God damn it, her dressing room door is shut, so I'm
like, he's going to be in there like some sort of fucking creep now.
So I knock, I don't hear anything, I open the door, he's not in there, I'm relieved.
And then she goes, what the fuck?
And I look over and her entire mirror, every available surface of the mirror has been
written on with lipstick. And it says, welcome, Cammy. Love exo exo James. Come see me down
the hall when you get a minute love. Thanks, Cammy. Like he's written an endless paragraph.
She cannot see herself in the mirror. This is an actress, by the way, a very beautiful actress.
And she's like kind of angry and we start I start crying a robot off and it's not coming
off. It's just mirroring. I'm not. It's worse than now. Here's the thing. Yeah. Two things.
It's worse than you busted it and James Lipton is wearing the lipstick, which is what I thought you
were going to say. Dick Tuck between his legs. Yeah. Secondly, the only other road on the mirror
and lipstick story I've ever heard is that urban legend about the woman that wrote Welcome to
the Wonderful World of AIDS. Yes. That's right. That's right. So I feel that anytime somebody sees
lipstick on a mirror. They're going something bad has happened. And if you don't know that story,
that's an urban legend that a woman fucks some guy and then when he woke up to go to the bathroom,
she had written welcome to the wonderful world of AIDS on his mirror. I don't even remember how that
originated. That's a rough. That's a rough cut. That one. That's a good like cold open to something.
Like maybe a sitcom. CSI. Yeah. Or do you know, I would like to see a dookie house or open like that?
Yeah. It starts typing about it. Anyway, folks, she's, she's annoyed, but like, you know,
No, she's still, you know, she's not a bitch.
She was just kind of like, this is really obnoxious or whatever.
So I'm trying to wipe it off and I go,
we'll get somebody in here to clean this up.
I'm really sorry.
And she goes, but who did it?
She was like, who is James?
I go, oh, it's James Lipton, he was in a sketch earlier.
She was, who's James Lipton?
And I go, oh, the actor studio guy.
She goes, I never even did that show.
So I go, he actually said that you had done the show.
You've never met James Lipton.
She goes, I don't even really know who he is.
How horrifying is that?
And then she pulled off her wig and it was James Lipton.
She thought that just Camerendia's would know
and love a message from James Lipton.
And then he could call her Cammy.
One of my favorite jokes ever about James Lipton
was Panos wanted a joke where he said,
he said the stench of failure is wafting off of that man
so severely that if you stood behind him,
you'd get that wavy fog desert effect.
That's very true.
Did he have a stand -up special name, the stench of failure or who was that?
That was already.
I already am.
Boy, I gotta tell you, he was a creepy odd dude James Lipton.
Yeah.
Not already lagged.
No.
I love already lagged.
Of course, and we wish him the best.
But yeah, Lipton was a true maniac.
And I guess they don't do that show anymore, but I did use it on and got canceled come on come on
Yeah, I'm having fun here. Yeah, this is where riffin. This is radio, baby
Do you have any I'm gonna actually do my movie corner because I remember the movie I watched last night
I've got a bunch for this one all right we might not start and I'll chime in
Actually, I've got three it's not that many
Okay, I went to the store the and we got to do Joe's scary stuff
I keep forgetting to fucking do it every week. I'm not stopping you. I know you're not
I'm just saying how we remember that again
I also don't feel it's a huge loss if we don't do it
There's no need for that
I've got the wound. You don't need to roll me. It's still don't quite know what it is. It's we know what it is all right. I was in Best Buy the other day. I bought not to brag a film. I saw the Blu -ray. It was $5 .99. It's a film I've never seen. It is a film from a genre that I am a fan of. The superhero horror sci -fi genre. Are they doing sick deals at Best Buy? They know that the juice is up and they're almost done. There's some great deals. All right. I'll know. This was $5 .99. It's $5 .99. It's a film I've never seen. It is a film from a genre that I am a fan of. The superhero horror sci -fi genre. Are they doing sick deals at Best Buy? They know that the juice is up and they're almost done. There's some great deals. All right. I'll know. This was $5 .99.
better than Amazon.
Ah, it's comparable.
All right, fine.
This was the 599 for the brand new version
of the Blu -ray of the director's cut.
What is the movie, Joe?
Spawn.
OK.
Movie I've never seen.
I saw it in theaters 1997, the Regency AMC 8.
I remember I hated it.
Looked up, looked up on my phone.
I said, you know, I never had an urge to see this movie.
The John Lenguizamo clown character always looked pretty cool to me morbidly obese clown, right?
Yeah, how much time was he in makeup? Did you watch the extras? I did watch the extras a long time
Yeah, I'm sure it was a long time. I don't remember the details, but a long time
But I bet he kept him laughing with his colorful characters
They both both he and Michael J. White said that the makeup
Process was one thing, but once they were in it. It was a torturous experience. They said people would
Consistently come to them on set and make jokes and they wanted to punch them in the face
Yeah, that it was just fucking miserable. They said it was miserable. It was hot. It was not fun
But after all that torture you go to the premiere and the movie you have made is spawned. Yeah
Now here's why I bought it. Can I say this? Here's why I bought it. You don't have to ask. I know
I don't know why I'm gonna have it a saying that these days
Here's why I bought it. I look up on my phone. I go, you know, let me look it
I feel like this movie might have been overlooked. I feel like maybe it bombed when it came out, but it was better than they then everybody thought it was
Where I look up the movie
Roger Ebert
Three in a half out of four stars. Can I tell you I was obsessed with Ebert particularly at that time
And that is why I went to the movie opening. That's why I bought the damn thing. Yep. Roger Ebert three point five out of four
That's why I was there this fucking he likes a visual world. He loved he gave dark city four stars dark cities a great flick
I have to say it again this movie spawn. It's not even a visual thing. It's dog shit
It's the worst CGI I've ever seen in my life the CGI looks like you're you're you're playing some hell video game on a tandy
2000 computer from radio shit Jessica 10 is Jessica tandy. Wow. Yeah, like a cyborg
Not just a tandy, a Jessica tandy.
That's how old the system was.
Yeah, Google Chrome, how about Google Hume Chrome?
All right, that's good.
It, the movie sucks, it's fucking terrible.
What is, how does spawn, I guess he's spawned by the devil?
Is that what it is?
Hell spawn is why he's called spawn.
Okay.
The movie opens with Martin Sheen playing a,
Some sort of a man, a big US military, again,
and I said this about some of the dialogue and drive.
It's written the way, when I was 14,
if somebody was like, can you write me a movie
where a military big wig is trying to pull some stuff?
It's written the way I was like,
we need to take over Fallujah.
Can your armies help us do that?
And like, it's a shadowed John Languizambo.
Yeah.
And the military general is calling no attention
of the fact that he's talking about that supernatural clown right now and then it's in the spawn world
it's just a common place spawn die the main guy dies he gets set up by Martin Sheen and then
his second chance is when he goes to hell they say you can avenge your death and and see your
wife that you love so much again if you lead our armies and he says I'll do it but then they reveal
that he didn't know what he was doing when he did that he was like a black blacked out yeah like
like almost like a blackout drunk or something.
It just doesn't make any fucking sense to me.
And then like, and then you got this demon using guns.
He's using guns, right?
And then like he learns his powers in like two seconds
from some old man that looks like a Van Helsing ripoff
who they never really explain fully what his thing is
and why he looks normal but spawn doesn't
and it's a mess of a fucking movie.
And then at one point John Ling was almost turns into this big demon and is running through the street
By the way, everybody can see them right. It's not like Dr. Strange, which I also hated
Where they where they
Build like some sort of like a wall that they can exist behind in a parallel world. Everybody can see them
So people are seeing like this these demons fighting in the street. Yeah, they're just like oh lord. That's crazy
Yeah, yeah, but I guess you're supposed to be like hey, it's New York. We've seen it folks
You know what I mean? It's a terrible fucking movie. It's terrible. That's that's a standard joke in any New York
Movie is like something crazy happens and then the old guy just bites into his bagel like he's a
Typical New York. Yeah, 800 cities into big apple. That's just what up. Oh, baby. Yeah. All right. Anyway
Well, thank you for taking me back to spawn. I don't remember one minute of it except I can visualize
was, what leg Wasama looked like, but I know I saw it opening
night. Leg Wasama looks really cool. And he's really creepy.
Yeah. Until he starts farting green smoke. And then you're like,
that was a studio note. I probably was probably in the comic.
I don't know if it was, but you're just like, this could have been like the scariest,
creepiest character ever. And he's literally farting green smoke.
Dude, he's a big creepy like clown demon. It's creepy. Yeah.
All right. But then he farts green smoke. And he's eating like donuts all the
time. We've got to stay fat.
Diculous. We've got to stay fat.
Last night, um, due to my busy schedule, my, my lovely lady said to me, Hey, we
should watch a movie. I've watched a movie in a month. And I was like, great, for
some reason, the words that came out of my mouth were true and lost. Okay. She'd
never seen it. Folks, I know Joe, you're, you're a big camera and hate her James
camera. True lies is a fucking blast. It's so funny, Arnie, Tom, everybody in its
funny. Jamie Lee Curtis gives a masterful performance I would say. I love
Jamie Lee. Her strip tease had me boned up when I was 14 and it had me
boned up at 36 ladies and gentlemen. Well, she's a beautiful woman. The movie is
hilarious and I could not believe how fucking dark it was. The great
The late great Bill Paxton, giving one of my favorite performances at his, he's a guy
who pretends to be a spy.
The plot is a little ridiculous.
Pretends to be a spy to fuck like housewives and he's trying to fuck Jamie Lee Curtis.
So Schwarzenegger takes him out on a ride to use car salesman, of course, and this guy's
talking about how excited he is to fuck Arnold's wife, Jamie Lee Curtis to him.
And Arnold's getting angry and angry, of course.
then they bust in on them and they're like kind of like fake having sex in the way like it was
almost a threes company bit it really was like they're there he's like well we should pretend in
case on my next mission I need to pretend that we're having sex right and that's when Arnold comes in
it's to protect our characters you don't hate her for fucking bill packs but she's had it with Arnold
and she's ready to cheat I mean these are like threes company style yeah yeah and I could not believe
that out what I was seeing then Arnold kidnaps her to punish her for cheating so they're
running her out and then this guy hits her in the head at one of the SWAT team members
not Tom Arnold or Bill Paxon or or Pax hits her in the head and then Arnold beats the
shit out of him for doing that because they're all wearing masks.
They take her to this room like a zero dark 30 interrogation room and Arnold and Tom Arnold
I'll be behind Arnold and Tom Arnold.
Behind the glass and interrogate her.
Until she's so angry,
she's trying to shatter the two -way glass
with a stool and I was like,
they are torturing this woman.
Did this play as comedy in the theater?
Because I loved how crazily dark it was in this movie.
I couldn't believe it.
I know James Cameron has been divorced like 25 times.
He's probably working out some issues.
Isn't he still married to Linda Hamilton right now?
And I'll think so.
know this movie would never get made today and if it did there would be think pieces out
the ass about this thing. He then has her pretend to be a prostitute. She's promised
that she won't have to fuck the mystery man. Yes. Just dance for him. I remember that part.
She does a strip tease for him. Then he says lay down on the bed and you're underwear.
She does it with her eyes closed and then he reveals that it's him. And she's like what
the fuck? This movie takes some of the darkest turns I've ever seen. Yeah. It's an elaborate
I'm not a big fan of the film, but we were riveted because the action is incredible.
It's still, and honestly, this movie had an aged, in terms of CGI, Cameron always kills
it with that.
I mean, this movie could be made today, and you'd still be gasping at this shit.
When he pulls her out of the car at the end, from the helicopter, it's got some amazing
action sequences.
You're fired as I've always thought was bad.
Especially now that he's the host of the fucking apprentice it sucked. Well, he's not anymore. But you know what always bother me about true
Eyes. No the poster for the movie that covered them VHS the cover the DVD. Yeah, this is why I didn't want to see when I was young
It's just a head shot of with a gun. It looks like a bed. It's not even there's a gun. I think it's just his face
I think he is holding a gun up, but yeah, but I'm just like this literally looks like a promo shot for Arnold that his publicist had taken
Well, I mean, he was coming off T2 you just at that time you were just like
Put the star up. We paid 20 million for him. I know put him in a scenario. Yeah. No last action hero followed T2
Yeah, right. I believe and this was kind of his comeback. So anyway, but good lord and it's you know like
In a way that
Didn't demand of him
He realizes he's playing with like
Terrorists and they're they're talking about the issues that are still you're gonna kill our women and children and
Now we're gonna kill you. Like it's all kind of eerily relevant and
Cameron gives them a really funny intelligent
Indian sidekick on their SWAT team with Tom Arnold and I was like that's pretty progressive for 1994
Sure, he knew he was dealing in murky waters. Sure, and Tom Arnold
You know, he's never been good in anything except he was fucking hilarious in this movie
I mean, I would disagree that I think time Arnold strangely, he's, he is the male counterpart
to Roseanne.
Yeah.
They're both nuts and they always strangely deliver.
I can't explain it, but they do.
I shouldn't have shatted him.
I do always like Tom Moore.
They do.
They always deliver somehow.
I don't know.
And a role that I guarantee the studio was like, we don't want Tom Arnold to be your partner
in this movie.
That's ridiculous.
But he kills it and Paxton kills it and Curtis kills it and it's about as likable
Arnold's ever been. And then at the end of this fucking movie, the climax you're done
and I was like, boy, that's great. You're at the two -hour mark. Then there's a second
climax where he shoots the guy, he's got his daughter, Alisha Dusku on the, on the
hood of the airplane. Right. Amazing action. Where's she been? Oh, she's, what's she's doing
a show? I miss her. Where is she? Gorgeous woman. Doing what show? We used to, when I worked
it always sunny, we used to watch her stretch every day, which I probably shouldn't be
She was on that show like dark angel or whatever that show where were she stretching they shot right outside her offices
So she'd come out stretch before her action sequences and we'd all be like
Oh my god gathering around like the fat guys in fat
So when they start talking about filling the donuts up with chocolate ice cream
Yeah, it was not not a great thing to do, but you know, I'm glad I did it
uh so then that action sequence ends and then they still cut to Jamie Lee Curtis and Arnold
and their co -spice she gets a call and she's like oh that's my code name and then Arnold and
Jamie Lee are spies together and they do an elaborate she gets hired based on this whole thing right
they do a tango because at the beginning Arnold does a tango with T for air yeah that's the beautiful
team and they're doing this and even now knowing that we're 22 years down the line i was like
What a beautiful seamless setup for true lies to but we're not getting it. Yeah, that movie should have been
Five movies with us getting it. We are getting a big terminator announcement in the next few days apparently, but
Another one is to
Apparently they killed the genesis thing or whatever
Uh, and Cameron is coming back. All right. Some huge there's some huge terminator announcement coming. All right. Nobody knows Eddie furlons back. Oh
Well, yeah, it's it's uh, it's called uh, it's called Terminator
Sweating to the oldies
It's Eddie for a long trying to just shave off those that last 35 pounds
For me my honestly, it might be my pick and I I always was very excited that they were talking about Ferris
Bullard too when he's taking a doubtful work. I'm sad they couldn't come to pass because John Hughes passed away
That was gonna happen. I still think they could do it though. They could but it would be terrible
You had to be real careful who you got.
You're telling me if I said it, we got broadrick.
We got the guy from Spin City that played Cameron Alonrock.
We got Sloan.
Look, you know I'd go.
You're telling me you're not there?
You know, I would go.
But the guys that wrote Kingpin wrote it, I mean, you know, they haven't written a movie
since boat trip.
They're follow up to Kingpin.
Oh, and I think the fellow brothers did a lot of work on Kingpin because they had their
credit it.
Oh, mommy.
Oh, mommy, burger.
But Joe, I wanna ask you, I think it's an interesting question.
I would say true lies delivers the best ever,
most seamless, least desperate set up for a franchise,
maybe ever that didn't deliver,
that didn't come through with the other.
It is surprising that they say it's yours.
Cause those could have been the new James Bond.
What is my pick for most seamless delivery?
No, no, no, franchise.
What is your pick for a movie you saw where you're like, oh, what a beautiful set up for a sequel and you never got it?
That's a great question. I don't know that I can that I can think of one
I have her while you're thinking I have heard rumors about true lies two for years, but it's just too late now
I mean that they could do it, but I don't even know if people today would even give a ship. You know, man, I thought that
But I thought that Tales from the Crypt Demon Knight was very promising.
It did sort of have an open end with the new, with the new Demon Lord or whatever following
the bus and whistling the Tales from the Crypt theme as Jada Pinkin became the new Demon
Knight or whatever.
I thought that was something where I was like, okay, we're going to get into something
else here and then never revisited it.
I also thought that but that was a movie that lost money and true lies the movie that made a tremendous amount of money
I honestly I'm so laughable. I'm gonna I'm gonna stall us here trying to think I can't really think of you know what predator
Well predator had plenty of sequels. Oh
Yeah, you're right
Predator two predators alien versus predator. I guess I guess what I mean by predator though was I thought that predator was gonna be a
a Schwarzenegger franchise.
Oh yeah.
And it wasn't.
I should have, I mean, I just watched,
which led me to true lies.
I just watched Predator 3D at my house.
And one of my best investments,
especially as a guy who enjoys the occasional puff
of marijuana, was the 3D compatible TV
and Blu -ray player.
I love watching a 3D movie.
And when they only do it once a year or so,
but they went back and redid Predator for 3D,
it looks incredible.
Oh, I gotta do that.
It's not shitty or cheap or anything like it looks like you're watching a current day 3d movie
But the predator especially before you see the predator when he's that like weird hologram thing. It looks incredible when he goes
Paddy look let's move here because we're at let's talk Christopher half hour mark really quick
Joe scary stuff for you hard fans out there best by currently right now
Has for sale
Friday the 13th the complete series
For a cool $35 three seasons for $35 if you don't remember the series it was a show called
Friday the 13th that had nothing to do with Jason Voorhees oh this doesn't have the movies
no it is the TV series it was a TV series about a pair of cousins that inherent and antique shop
that had a bunch of cursed items that were sold out to people these items make people murder
for power and supernatural power.
Beautiful things whatever it sort of is rip that off.
So, anyway, the complete series is available now at, again,
Best Buy for 35 bucks.
Really nice hard work.
Very well done.
You should go get it.
It's just Jason killing people week after week.
No, no, Pat, the, the needful, but I know you said the shop,
but I can't imagine a Friday 13 show doesn't have Jason.
Jason's not in it.
That's, I don't understand that at all.
That makes no sense.
Uh, they had the license for the title Friday the 13th, so they used it.
Does the intro at Cripkeeper style?
No, because he doesn't talk.
No.
That is the stupidest thing I've ever heard.
It's not, it's a good show though.
It's the point.
All right.
There was a rumor going around that the finale was going to be them
them finding the Jason mask and that was going to be the final item.
But they, you know, the craters of the show have said, like, look, had we had the license
to use Halloween, we would call it a Halloween the series, right?
That was just a selling point.
Given what you know and what you're hearing now, this is actually good.
It's a good show.
That's the surprise.
All right.
Because you'd think it'd be terrible.
David Cronenberg directed an episode.
Okay.
Yeah.
There's some, there's some good stuff in the show.
I highly recommend it for serial horror fans.
If you like that sort of thing, like Frank and Barry, Boo, Barry, count, yeah, count,
chocula.
Yeah.
Exactly.
Ghostbusters, slime or cereal, yeah.
If you're a serial horror fan, you enjoy this kind of thing.
I would really recommend it.
It's very much in the, in the, in the spirit of Kojak the night stocker and that sort of thing.
And for $35 you can't beat that. It's three seasons. It's every episode. It's, God knows how many it's a lot and I've been enjoying it thoroughly in the great episodes you're
riveted by in the bad episode. You kind of take a little nap too, but it's a win -win. So go out and get that.
And that's show's scary stuff onto the main talk tonight, our film is Christina.
Nope.
Christine.
Christina was.
I felt that I had a splash.
Christina was the sequel.
So yeah, this is John Carpenter's Christine, which as I mentioned on the last podcast, I was
baffled by it.
It should be Stephen King's Christine.
It's his fucking book and idea and vision.
but, Christine, really, here's the plot, it's about a killer car. It's about a car who kills.
There's a nerd in high school very well played by Keith Gordon who sees a car and a junkyard
and he's got to have it. Who it now is a director? Yep. And Keith Gordon, if you ever watched
a little fun fact, you ever watched the show Night Visions, which was in horror, was a
never saw strangely enough. Keith Gordon directed patterns, which was the episode that started
Malcolm McDowell. Malcolm McDowell was, it was an Emmy nominated episode. It's the best
episode of the show. Okay. So very cool. I like Keith Gordon also started back to school, which
is correct. You know, many would say Rodney Dangerfield's Sergeant Peppers. Yeah, I would, if you will.
Yeah, I like Keith Gordon. I hadn't seen Christine maybe since I was a kid. I read the book.
I remember but the book paled to Kujo. They came out around the same time. The movie
Christine pales to the movie Kujo. I'm going to say this folks. I don't know that I've ever seen
a less scary horror movie than Christine. It packs zero scares. It's a car that kills people.
I'm going to say this. Instantly, one of my favorite John Carpenter movies.
real instantly holy shit. I saw it for the first time this week. I mean, bearers to say. I'd never seen it when I was a kid because I also had the very stunted
Perspective that you have of it's just the part of the kills people. I don't care
I was at Best Buy once again. They had the steel box blu -ray for $10. I said, let me take a chance
I called my good buddy Jim Pinkstone, your friend and ours. I said, is this worth it? He said buy it
I'm telling you, you're gonna love it.
I bought it, I watched it, I fucking loved it.
I thought it was phenomenal.
I thought it was a phenomenal film.
I thought it was a great take on the idea of machismo,
of the idea of men that love their car,
of this obsession that men have with their devices
and their technology and their...
So you're not willing to explore the themes of the Neon Damon,
but you're doubling down and finding the themes of Christine.
I am willing to explore the themes of the Neon Damon.
They weren't executed very well.
The themes of Christine were.
Now I will say him caressing the V,
the vagina part of the V at the end as Christine does
was an interesting choice.
It's a great flick.
It feeds off the love of the owner.
the mileage goes down, the more the owner loves it,
it's a really, really cool fucking idea
that came out, now mind you,
where you gotta remember this.
This book was written in 1978.
This was written at a time where men were absolute,
every guy had a muscle car
and men were absolutely obsessed with their cars.
It's a very, very cool social commentary, very cool.
I don't think it's that cool.
I enjoyed it sort of for like it's it's kind of 80s catch factor
But like when I'm watching a a driverless car
Chase some guy down a street. I was like this. I've never felt less
Excited I've never felt less suspense. You didn't like when it was engulfed in flames like chasing that bully
I loved it. I liked the music. I liked certain aspects of it. I like Keith Gordon in it
But like I was kind of thrown by the whole thing and it starts okay, so it's like 1957 is that with the title card says right then the cars and an assembly line and they start playing bad to the bone which came out in 1982.
Then they start playing a 50's song in the car right and then kill so you watch the car like literally eat a guy's hand.
It doesn't eat his hand the hood closes on it eats his hand
It doesn't eat it doesn't eat his hand then we're like now. We're gonna cut ahead to 1978 or whatever and
It just seemed so so much
Ridiculous overplotting for a movie about a car that kills people
It's not just a car that kills people. It's a car that the owner falls in obsessive love with
Yeah, that's speech that Keith Gordon gives it the anewars going and if you work hard
And if you try you can have that love and then his friend goes
I don't know you thought this way about your girlfriend and he goes I'm talking about Christine
Man like it's the idea of this obsession with with the machine
Which I think is a really great social commentary. I got it Joe, but did you though, Pat? No
It's just I mean are we really saying that some sort of great social commentary?
I think it is a great social guy loves it.
It's not a great book and it's not a great movie.
It's been a great social comedy since the beginning
of filmmaking.
If you watch any of, you know,
what's that, what's that famous silent film?
Jesus Christ.
You know, Metropolis or the other one the guy did.
God dammit.
The same guy that did Metropolis.
You know what I mean?
My point is, for the beginning of filmmaking,
there has been this interest in commentating
on man's obsession with machinery
and what it means to him over the importance
of another human being.
I just was kind of like the movie itself,
in terms of scare.
Were you ever scared during Christine?
Uh, I was freaked out by the main character, the kid.
I actually loved the scene of him being bullied.
One of my favorite things about Stephen King
is that...
He writes great bullies.
When people get bullied in his movies,
it's like a knife to their stomach.
Yeah.
And that's great bullies.
He writes great bullies.
Much more realistic than like the bully
who's like kind of fucks with you a little bit.
The bully pulls a noxial one shot of your hand.
The main character's name is Cunningham.
Yeah.
And the first scene where you see him getting bullied
is a guy with leather jacket in the long hair with a switch blade.
He was also 46 years old.
Yes.
Going, why doesn't your lunch say cunting ham?
It's classic bullshit.
The teacher comes out on their exact same age
and they have like an altercation with each other.
Yeah, I think the student's actually older than the teacher.
The student sends the teacher to detention folks.
I hadn't seen it in forever.
The bullying stuff I liked, I really liked the first half hour.
And then I was still sort of entertained throughout.
I can admit, but like, I found myself on the Wikipedia page
for it at one point in Carpenter was like,
look, in my early career there's a lot of movies
I did out of passion.
When the thing made no money, he's like,
I had to do a movie for money and that's Christine.
He's like, I had no real interest or passion in it.
It was a serviceable job.
And I feel like that's what we got.
I mean, he directs it really well.
but at the end of the day, it's a car that can't be killed.
I know I can tell you this, you know, this is what upsets me so much about so many
hard directors. Carpenter, you know, was Goddamn as far as I know,
Gung Ho about remaking children of the damned or whatever village of the damned
or village and then, and it's fucking terrible.
Yeah, it is.
And then this one he goes, ah, kind of half -asseted, I didn't really care.
And to me, it's brilliant.
It's brilliant.
It's like when George Romero goes, we weren't trying to make a statement with the mall and
dawn of the dead.
It was just a big place that we could shoot it.
And it was like, dude, the whole thing is the zombies walking the mindless culture that's
the whole thing.
Yeah.
I mean, you're giving this thing way too much credit with
brilliant, but I thought it was brilliant. Anything brilliant you're getting from it came from Stephen King's book
It did not come from this interpretation of it
Well, I don't agree with them. He's they cut a lot of cool shit out from the book
In the book the former owner is in the back seat as a ghost decaying which they cut out
Yeah, I remember that because they said it was too similar to American Werewolf and London which has just been released
but um
But I will I will say this and I swear to you
I swear to you, I don't say it to be provocative.
Favorite Carpenter movies?
I'm gonna go thing in the mouth of Manus and Christine.
I really love the film.
Halloween's not up there for you.
Halloween.
Now I like Halloween too better than Halloween.
Holy shit.
Because I find Halloween one, here's the thing.
Halloween one's the origin story.
It's interesting, it's fun.
There's great moments.
And you're putting in the mouth of madness above them.
Yeah, I've watched that recently, that's not a good move.
Oh, it's a great flick. It is not a good movie. Halloween is a great movie. I'm not saying
it's not, but it's an origin story to me and then maybe big trouble little China.
Well, it gets exciting in Halloween too is as all the reveals and I know he hates it. He's
like, I hate that they had to be brother and sister, but that to me is where it starts to get
really interesting. And I like that. I think it's cool. I think that Halloween too is a better
sequel than it had to be, but Halloween is fucking killer from start. Right. If you said
to me right now, if I wanted John Carpenter to review, I would go thing. We're in the
mouth of madness or Christine. All right, trouble alone, China is fine. Best
description I've ever heard of it. And Pinkstone told me this. He said they were
taught. There was a form about it on Facebook and somebody said, somebody goes,
I've never seen big trouble in China and somebody responded, you've never seen
it. It's like a Sega Genesis game. And I was like, that is, yeah, we were both
Laughing, I was like that's perfect like are you a you have the fog fan? Yeah, yeah, I like the funk
I like most of what he's done
Did did he do her to West? I think West Craven to deadly friend. Do you remember that one?
That's West Craven. That's not a great one. That's a West Craven had some terrible years and so did Carpenter
Look Carpenter's still kind of not being able to figure it out escape from LA. I don't know if that's gonna hold up either but
Escape from LA or New York's great, but L .A., I remember being
pretty ridiculous. It wasn't good ever.
No, it wasn't, but I didn't know if it would be even more dated now.
Robert, it is absolutely is.
Robert, I agree you guys directing the Escape from New York remake.
Okay. So I think that'll be cool.
Who's playing Snake Pilskin?
I don't know.
But to me, you get Kurt Russell in there at 70 years old.
That's what you do.
I bet it's like Indiana Jones.
So like I don't care if he's 90 getting in there. They're doing they're doing big trouble with the rock, right?
It's rumors. I don't know if it's true though
And I'm very excited about this dynamic bride
Halloween. I'm very excited. Very excited. Those are some of my favorite guys in all the film dynamic bride and Jody Hill
Very excited. Well folks. That's our show Christine
That's our show we talked about a Pat Thumbs Down Joe Thumbs up
You know, an affectionate thumbs down. I didn't hate the movie, but it is pretty stupid.
How about at the end when she goes, God, I hate rock and roll.
Oh, come on. You're gonna shit on the movie for that.
I mean, that's fucking terrible.
You've shot on movies for significantly less.
You can, God, you're just a bitch tonight.
You can follow me on Joderos Accomedy on Twitter and Instagram at Joderos Accomedy.
And as always, go get my albums in five star reviews.
Please, balance out these trolls.
Go get my albums.
Where's that from?
That I got.
Go get my album.
Jerky Boys.
Nope.
I don't know.
Hey, Missy!
That helped?
I have no idea, Pat.
It's from Missy L .A.
It's under construction.
One of the greatest rap albums ever met.
All right.
Well, listen.
The sketch that kicks it off.
Give your goddamn plug.
Hey, go buy my album.
My plug is I'm at the Patrick Walsh on Twitter and Instagram. I don't have anything I can show you right now
I don't have anything I can tell you. I hope you're doing well. Thanks for your comments. Thanks for your
your love and
We'd back next week. I'm not sure what it'll be. What you have a guess. No, no, no, let's not guess
We don't know we don't know all right, but watch all the movies in advance of that podcast
Good night you guys next week, but that was a hit down podcast