🎵 I'll see you in hell. I'll see you in hell. And when the sound of your screams becomes a thing of my dreams, you know I'll say. I'll see you in hell. You know I will. I'll see you in hell. You know I will. 🎵
My name is Patrick Walsh. I forgot for a moment, oftentimes when we do this podcast it's the first words I've said of the day and that's scary sometimes. You don't know if it's going to come out squeaky or that 7th grade voice changing kind of thing. But I'm doing all right. Joe, how are you?
I'm well. I would dare to say sometimes we do this podcast. It's not just the first words of the day for either of us. Sometimes it's also the first person we've spoken to in a day or two. Sometimes. True. True. I'm well, Patrick. Yeah, I've been. Go ahead. Go ahead. You were going to say it's a beautiful day in the neighborhood? The rhythm's off. We haven't interacted with humans. Yeah, it's a beautiful day here in New York City. I actually have to take a
trip out to Williamsburg this afternoon after we record this to do my friend Ian Fydance his podcast and it's so beautiful. I think I might walk over the Williamsburg Bridge.
I've done it. I love it. You're probably going to show up to his podcast sweaty, but hopefully he won't mind. I don't know that guy, but I see him pop up on social media and he seems very funny. Mustache.
Looks like he's up to something no good. He's just got that look. Yeah, for sure. Yeah, I used to walk across the Brooklyn. Listen to us. I'm sorry. The rhythm has gotten us just as Gloria Estefan warned us.
Let's take a breath. Today we're going to be talking about the Boogeyman, an adaptation of the Stephen King short story. As I was texting Joe while he was sitting in the theater, maybe not all short stories need to be adapted. This story is four pages long.
I was like, you know what? I'm going to really do my research this week and read the story and see the movie. I read the story in literally two minutes and I was like, all right. But I felt such a sense of accomplishment that I grossed myself out because of how little I read these days.
It's a movie. We'll get to it. It's a movie. We'll get to it. What I was going to say is, I said you wait walking in finance. Oh, oh, Ian finance. If you look up a picture of my favorite joke to make to him.
Mid discussion will always be. Now when you were shooting stir crazy with Richard Pryor, what was he like? Because he does kind of look like Gene Wilder. He's got Gene Wilder hair, undoubtedly.
Yeah, the Jeremy Allen White, the star of the bear and previously shameless, looks to me exactly like Gene Wilder. Kind of a buff Gene Wilder.
The main guy. Yeah, OK. Something in his eyes and he's got kind of the poofy hair as well. I feel like if he didn't cut it, it would go out of control.
We got to watch this damn bear. I pet. I had a I just want to give a shout out real quick to.
The good people over at the too many games expo. Yeah, in Oaks, Pennsylvania. Oaks is right near where I grew up in Collegeville and there's a expo center there.
Called the Greater Philadelphia Expo Center.
And I guess once a year.
They do this. Well, it is once a year, but it's just my memory of it is a bit off because of covid.
But anyway, at this expo center right near where I grew up once a year, they do a fest convention called too many games.
I finally went as a collector. I never I'd never been.
Pat country, the NES punk who's become a good friend was there. I went and hung out with him at his booth for a lot of time.
I also went and met Tony from hacked the movies on YouTube, who the co -host his co -host is my friend Crystal, who I've known for years through the comedy scene.
But it was really fun going and hanging out with everybody and I shopped and bought video games and Pat, I will tell you, I spent.
Some of the most money I've ever spent on single video games in my life.
OK, it is like out of print, hard to find. Yeah, they're all retro games, so none of them are in print anymore, and they're games I was looking for for a while, and it wasn't anything crazy.
It wasn't like I spent $600 on a game or something like that, but.
But I will tell you, it is re the investment has re sparked my love of of gaming.
I kind of thought I was falling out of it for a while. I wasn't feeling the spark anymore.
And I've been I've been really rejuvenated here, and it's a very nice feeling, so shout outs to too many games.
I've met some really nice vendors there. Guy that has a shop down in Asbury Park.
I believe his shop is called Kill Screen Games.
You see Bruce and that too many games are kill screen games.
Bruce Bruce Springsteen, it is Bruce Springsteen who does a retro game shop.
Little little extra side hustle for Bruce.
Yeah, he came up to me, he goes, I just wasn't making enough money.
As you know, I work in a factory and I have for 50 years.
Rock and roll ain't what it used to be, man.
And my dad's really got me down, even though he's been dead for 30 years.
You know, he still gets to me and here's a song I wrote about that.
In the meantime, can I just share in this limited edition Sonic the Hedgehog?
It's it's it's expensive, I know, but it's only because Knuckles has his dick out the whole time.
They made a game where Knuckles has no pants and he's got a big old dick.
Can I play Thunder Road for your acoustic while you play?
Yeah, speaking of Knuckles, I grew up in a tough neighborhood.
The whites and the blacks, you know, we lived right on the same street.
You know, it was wild. Nobody else had that experience except me, Bruce Springsteen.
Here's a little song about it called The Blacks and the Whites on My Street.
Perhaps Billy Joel.
Only a true man of the New York streets like Bill Joel.
We did a thing.
Joining me tonight on my next song.
We did a thing once on Opie and Anthony where we just talked about all of the
It was Billy Joel, Bruce Springsteen, John Mellencamp, these guys that are are just,
you know, they they like live out in the Hamptons or whatever.
But then it's time to go to work.
And it's like Billy and Bobby used to sing on the corner and fight with the chains and the bricks.
Did they?
No, Billy Joel, you're thinking of Happy Days.
You're describing the plot of an episode of Happy Days you watched from the mansion you lived in.
One of my favorite jokes ever from It's Always Sunny when they're making the
they're trying to make the band and DeVito comes out in the leather jacket and he's like,
we got to freak the parents out because their kids want to bop with us.
Yeah, yeah. Funny show.
Still funny.
I this is this is interesting.
So one of the things I enjoy about talking to the vendors at these cons
is the game cons is is, you know, like now that I've opened this bar,
it's like it's a relatable conversation.
Like, oh, well, you have like a game shop.
That's a pretty niche thing.
And like, that's interesting.
And, you know, I have a bar and like, wow.
So I went to a I went into a vendor.
They were called Cartridges Galore.
They're very nice.
And the young woman that was working there came up to me and she goes,
are you Joe DeRose?
I said, yeah, she goes, I'm a huge fan.
I was like, oh, wow, that's really great.
I said, you have a great selection of stuff here.
I'm going to buy some games from you.
And she said, great.
We talked for a moment.
I was like, this is really cool.
So how's your shop doing?
Trying to do a little like, I know the ups and downs, miss.
Let's discuss them.
How's your shop doing?
She goes, well, we have eight.
I was like, I'll go fuck myself over here with my one bar.
I'm trying to keep open every day.
Yeah, she's the chain, the Walmart of games.
But Cartridges Galore, very nice people, very helpful, very cool.
It was awesome.
It was, I had an awesome time at this thing.
You know, I've been a while since I'd gotten out into a big public event,
talked to people just to talk to them.
You know what I mean?
Like, right.
Interacted, just made small talk with people, met new people.
It was good, man.
I need to do more of that.
Felt good.
Felt like there was still like a human race out there.
You've kind of forget sometimes, you know?
Yeah, I'm, you know, was seeking sort of a way away from my loneliness by dating.
And it was making me much, much more lonely.
So I started setting up a daily lunch with a friend and maybe an activity.
And it's been great.
I'm going to see our dear friend, Vince Avril today.
After this, we're going to Amoeba.
It's a classic Joe Pate, I got to tell you, but you don't live here.
We're doing Amoeba and lunch.
God damn it.
And, and you're still on the sober train too,
because that day usually would lead up to heavy drinking.
Yeah.
Start the day at 11 a .m. and be drunk by two.
I'm about to hit the 30 day mark of complete sobriety and no sugar or carbs as well.
So yeah, I'm just kind of low energy, but hanging in there, hanging in there.
Brett, what else?
Well, I went to Costco yesterday.
This place needs to be shut down.
The carts are bigger than the aisles there.
Whatever the fire limit of people is, they're tripling it.
Whether you go at 9 a .m. or 10 p .m., it's the same level of pack.
And I walked in, I was texting my friend, like, how are people not
brutally murdered at Costco every day?
I mean, the fights, the irritating people.
And then as I was walking into the aisles,
like I'm getting ready to start my shopping experience, taking a deep breath, et cetera.
I get rear -ended, by which I mean an old Asian woman
ran her oversized cart into my lower back at the highest speed she could give it.
I turn around and look at her.
She's wearing a mask, which I can't believe I'm becoming the kind of guy
who wants to rip a mask off your face, but it's over, guys.
It is irritating, isn't it?
I look behind expecting her to be like wide -eyed and like I'm so sorry or something.
She looks at me and I realize it took me about 10 seconds,
but finally I had the slow realization that she had hit me on purpose.
That I was not moving quickly enough for her in the Costco.
And I, you know, what am I going to do?
Scream at a 90 -year -old woman?
I wanted to.
Deep in my bones, I wanted to.
But people are just losing their fucking minds.
Hey, should I go with an excuse me or ram his spine?
Yeah, you forget that.
And I have a certain empathy for old people.
It's certain, you know, you're getting towards the end.
I get it.
But you do forget that old people can be assholes too.
It's like you forget that you're like, you're like, you think old people are like children
where you just assume like, oh, they're all precious.
And it's like, no, no, no, they're not.
Like there's that guy, you know, that's a dick right now.
He's going to become an old man and he's going to be a dick then too.
You know, like I find generally people get meaner as they get older.
If you start mean, I mean, you either, you go one of two ways.
You mellow out and that's like the old man who never went to therapy or something.
But he's way better with his grandkids than he is with his kids, that type of guy.
But for the most part, you just get older and bitter and angrier.
I mean, that's, that's what I've experienced certainly in my family.
That's how it's been.
I mean, I quote Dennis Miller jokes all the time, but a great one when you, when you talked about
Costco, he's had a joke about Walmart.
It was like interesting, interesting clientele at Walmart.
I'm pretty sure anything under 350 pounds doesn't even trip the automatic door anymore.
That's fun.
Is it from his special, which I actually saw at Amoeba last time I was there.
They were selling a copy of it.
Fake news, real jokes.
No, no, no.
No.
No, I, that's not a good title.
That's the last special.
It's weird too, because he went like, like, like as far as like distribution of the special,
in like availability, he went real hard on that one and like he, the company, whoever,
but like the classic ones aren't available.
Like that's one of the only ones you can get.
It's just a bummer.
Like I'd kill to have some of those.
I mean, I own them on DVD, but like those original HBO specials are like the first,
well, the first one, he's still a little too like weekend updated, but like
number two, three, four, you're like, holy shit, man.
The one where he comes up doing the Michael Jackson thing with the hat and like that special
is insane.
It's so good.
And that's when he was like the coolest version.
Yeah, it's like, it's like right when he was about to get the HBO talk show.
Right.
Like he was like right in the perfect pocket of like, he was kind of shitting on everybody.
He didn't do too much political stuff.
It was still a lot of, you know, just, just really funny, funny shit, but it had bite to it.
It was a good, good, good period.
That's a good, good year for Miller.
Yeah.
Three, you know, 92.
I thought I had, oh, tomorrow's a big day.
Indy Jones.
I got a solo ticket 3 PM in my neighborhood.
I'm going to see it alone first, I think.
And then I'm going to see it with my buddy Brian on Friday.
I'm going solo IMAX.
Uh, I got the perfect seat Friday morning, morning, 11 30.
So I don't, I don't want a single word from you until I have seen it.
I don't want to, uh, it's well, you're going to be let down.
I don't want anything.
I won't.
We'll talk.
Do you want me, if I love it, do you want me to say, Hey, I loved it.
Oh, and now that now that's okay.
I won't because now if I don't do that, then you'll know I didn't love it.
I don't want to work.
I won't say it.
All right.
Um, I'm really excited.
Uh, I actually got asked to do a work thing tomorrow and I said, I can't.
And they said, really?
There's no time.
I said, no.
They said, why?
I said, Thursday and Friday are out.
And they said, why?
And I said, because Indiana Jones is coming out and I'm going to see it multiple times.
And I'm not, I'm sorry.
I'm out.
Like this is a, this is, this is it.
This is probably the last biggest thing ever from my childhood.
I'll ever get to experience.
That's one of the reasons I'm going to see it alone first on Thursday.
I feel like I need to have a viewing.
As much as I want to see it with a friend first, I think I need to have my, I mean,
they played the trailer up for it before the boogeyman this week.
And it was the first time I'd seen the trailer in a theater.
And I started crying during the trailer.
I'm like, I think I need to just kind of deal with my emotions alone.
I've been watching.
I'm not going to get into the movie, the old movies,
because we're going to do a whole indie episode,
but like I've been watching the old movies this week and it's been a journey.
It's been a journey.
Like I'm very much curious to see how it all ends for this guy.
Well, tell them how you're watching the films.
I was going to save it.
Let me save that for, for when we do the episode, but, but I'm watching them chrono.
I'll get into why I enjoyed this, but I watched them chronologically this time.
And I have tonight to tackle last crusade between tonight and tomorrow at 3 PM.
I got to do last crusade and crystal skull.
I'm tempted to jump to crystal skull after Raiders to see the connective tissue between
Marion and him from that movie to the next.
And then go back to crusade.
But I think I'm, I think I'm just going to go chronological.
That's all I should watch the entirety of the young Indiana Jones chronicles as well
before starting the franchise.
I think you've already fucked up, but that's just me.
I've tried many times with that show and it's got its moments.
Yeah.
But it just feels too much like, you know, like any of the shows at that time, like when
they did Robocop, the series or whatever, they just, they're not bad.
They just feel like made for TV.
There was a real disparity at that time period between a movie and made for TV.
Even back then it was like, remember when it was like an actor would do made for HBO
movies and you'd be like, Oh, this poor bastard.
It's come to this.
That was like, that was like sad.
Like it was a step down, you know, it's definitely switched.
Uh, it switched five years ago and kind of never went back, but I hope it does at some
point, uh, Joe and I were discussing in writers guild strike news and maybe screen
actors guild, upcoming strike news that, uh, during all this Netflix changed what
constitutes a view during this, during the strike, we're all waiting for them to answer
these very real demands we have.
And they released this information at midnight, which is always a sign that maybe it's a
little, little shady, but, um, they're changing what constitutes a view.
And Joe was informing me that YouTube does the same thing to fuck over their creators.
Basically, I mean, if somebody doesn't watch the entire episode of a show, it doesn't
count.
They're doing this so that when the strike ends, um, they'll be able to say to their
writers, Hey, sorry, nobody's watching your fucking show.
So we can't pay you.
Meanwhile, they're also lying to their investors and trumping up the numbers of how
many views they get and no one is checking their books.
They're allowed to lie to all these people for some reason at this moment in time.
And, uh, I would think anyone would understand that that needs to change, but we'll
see what happens.
Netflix is on a real tear.
Uh, they also just re added, uh, Titanic.
Yeah, a lot of people are talking about that boat.
So they were already getting blowback.
I believe it was Netflix was already getting blowback because they put up some
documentary or, or, or, or featured some documentary about deep sea exploration.
And people were like, guys, are you doing this just because of the sea, the Titanic
vessel story that's happening?
What are you doing?
Yeah.
And then they repush or re feature or re add whatever it was, uh, Titanic.
I, and I guess there's a world in which, where you could say, well, you know, people
are want to see Titanic stuff right now.
So we're going to let them have it.
But there's also like, are you capitalizing on this?
Like it's just so gross.
I've always said, look, if Netflix offered me money to do something, I'd probably take
it.
I've always said you'd be a fool to not take the money from these big, these big
budget corporate, whatever, you know, uh, if they're offering you money, take their
money, but you don't need to pursue them or feel defined by them or think they have
any value.
You know, um, it's, it's, it's just really gross.
It's very disheartening.
It's very gross.
Um, you know, it's a, it's a fire sale.
It's like Paramount plus, and this affects you, Joe, they announced last night that,
they're pulling all of inside Amy Schumer off of Paramount plus, uh, you've been on
that show.
So that fucks your money.
And they know that they're dumping it because they don't want to keep paying
residuals on it, but they're even dumping the latest season, which is up for any
consideration.
So it's like anyone that wanted to go watch the episodes to maybe vote for it.
It's own network isn't giving them that chance.
It's pulling the show and then comedy central was like, yeah, we're not going
to show the new season either.
We're just not going to show it.
It'd be too expensive.
So they made the episodes and now they're just not that you really are not going to
be able to find inside Amy Schumer, which, you know, whether you consider it one
of the great shows or not, it was unquestionably always a very funny sketch
show and up for Emmys.
I think one Emmys, you know, but, um, they pulled the plug on a bunch of shit
that grease rise of the pink ladies showed is, is now never going to be seen
again.
And, you know, I didn't watch the show.
I did see a clip where apparently they fired one of the elite actors.
So they only shot him from behind for the final episodes.
I'll send you this clip, Joe, you can find easily online.
They only shot the actor from behind and when they shoot him from the front, they
superimpose a still picture of his face on his stand -ins body.
So his face has no movement.
It's like they truly don't care.
And it looks like shit.
It looks like they did it like, you know, with Microsoft paint.
It looks terrible.
So Paramount Plus is clearly going under.
It's just like, Hey, we got to lose shit.
Netflix or HBO Max is selling HBO shows to Netflix.
And then the HBO executives who've been there since the beginning are like,
guys, we've worked for 40 years to make this a brand of quality that people
respect.
What are you doing?
And they're like, yeah, sorry.
It's not going to be special anymore.
We need cash.
It's awful.
It's all awful.
Yeah.
It's an, unfortunately, it's a, it's just a reflection of where the country's at.
You know, it's, you know, it's, it's, it's odd.
Things are, things have been a little strangely slow the last two weeks at the bar.
And I was talking to my partner today about it and it's weird that you seriously,
like we actually said at one point, like, is this, is this due to what's happening
everywhere right now?
Is this due to business just being slow or is this actually in part because of,
you know, oversaturation, crashing economy, all these, you know what I mean?
Like, and it's, it's just, it's just strange.
I mean, look, it's never strange to have to think you consider the crashing economy
to be something that might affect your business, but.
It's because no one's talking about it.
It's because like, no one is saying the words recession and economy crash and stuff.
You almost have to seek that information out, but it's unquestionably happening.
Of course, June and July, at least when I lived in New York was when the bars became packed
and everyone, you know, the ladies showing off some cleavage and so forth.
And everybody was horny and ready to go.
And I feel that too.
It's like restaurants seem to be dead and the streets seem to be a little dead.
And I don't know.
Do you think it's cause the president is one of the Stepford wives that might have
something to do with why we're not discussing any of this right now?
I, I mean, sure.
I think, you know, the fact that they're running him again, probably has people more scared.
You know, I, I don't, I don't know.
I, I, there doesn't seem to be a lot of hope at the moment.
And I think for a while we were like, I guess everything's okay because no one's saying
the sky's falling with the economy yet, but I don't think we are.
I think something's wrong.
I watched a comp of Biden, like dodging questions on YouTube and
you're like this poor bastard.
Like they got this old place.
It's like you throw your granddad out there, you know, like, and he's saying these
I feel nothing but, but sympathy.
You know, I don't, I, it's not like I'm mad at the guy or something because I,
I've always liked him politically to some extent.
But yeah, it's, it's sad that he's, he's up there and it's like,
it's almost like he's living the dream of, of its opening night.
You don't know your lines every day.
Or the night because he'll use these phrases, dude, that thing where he said,
God bless the queen at the end of this, like that's wild.
Like I watched another one where they, some guy was like, what about your son's,
you know, laptop, whatever the fuck it is.
And he was like, you're a one show pony, Jack.
It's like, I don't know what that means.
Yep.
That's a weird thing to say.
Anyway, it's a, it's a time.
Well, shall we go to this movie corner?
We have movies.
Oh, sorry.
Yes.
There you go.
We were saying the same thing.
I on the, on the solo corner was running the Mission Impossible titles.
I've been watching those in anticipation of the new one.
And I do think that that is the most consistent action franchise, maybe of all time.
And Indiana Jones, if the new one's great, I'm willing to say,
okay, Indy's better, but for just pure straight action,
it's hard to argue this Mission Impossible for how long it's been going anyway.
Agreed.
And I, what have I seen?
I saw Past Lives, which is the new A24 film, but it is not a horror film.
It doesn't feel like their usual fare.
Um, and I gotta tell you, this thing had been pumped up to me a lot of rave reviews.
And I'm like, all right, it's, it's a slow romance, you know,
let's see how, you know, how's this going to be?
What do we think?
And it wrecked me as, as they kind of promised it would, you know,
usually when they're like, you're going to cry, dude, you're going to cry.
I'm like, no, probably not.
It got me.
It is a story of two kids in Korea, a boy and a girl who are the best of friends.
Um, the boy kind of has more a crush on her than she does on him,
but they definitely love each other.
She's way more ambitious.
She wants to go to the States.
She wants to make a name for herself.
So she does, and he stays behind in Korea.
And, and it just kind of tracks their life.
It's one of those where it's like 12 years later, another 12 years later.
Um, the first half is kind of too slow.
And then it just starts picking up steam because when, when she finds him in New York
and it looked to me, Joe, like they kind of live in your neighborhood.
I saw all the same sites I saw when I was out there to visit you, but, um,
he, he, he finds her online and they start kind of talking over zoom, just like Joe and I are.
And they develop, you know, it's like they picked up with, with no time.
Uh, no, I'm Joe Biden.
They picked up, like, there's like no time has passed.
They start kind of flirting and getting into each other again,
but ultimately he won't come visit.
He's shy and she's like, look, I can't sit here talking to you over zoom all day.
I gotta make my life happen for myself.
Sorry, I need to stop seeing you.
And she kind of breaks it off with him a second time and he's devastated by this.
And then he comes to New York to visit and she is married to,
and here's where the movie really shines to a very nice understanding dude, a white dude too.
He's not the villain.
As soon as I saw she married a white guy, I was like, this guy's going to be a piece of shit
and you're going to wish she got back together with her dude.
But the truth is, um, it's a genuine true love triangle where she is happily married to this
great guy who gets her and understands her.
But then the true love of her life shows up.
And man, it just gets more and more kind of interesting and powerful as it goes.
It all built to the scene in a bar where the three of them beat up for drinks
and she keeps talking to him in Korean, which is really alienating and isolating her husband.
And, um, it's, it's an emotional movie, man.
It, uh, it really got to me when I, I mean, I was crying by the end for sure,
but I didn't feel bad because when the lights came up, everybody looked like,
you know, mascara running down their faces.
Um, it's just a classic, you know, in the style of the notebook or whatever, it's a classic, like,
very complex adult love story that gives you no easy way out and is just like life.
It's really painful and well done.
I recommend it.
The writer director is Celine's song.
Um, check it out.
I really enjoyed past lives, Joseph.
Uh, well, speaking of Netflix, uh, I watched this season of most of the season of black mirror
and what a steaming pile of shit this show has become.
Netflix now has taken to making fun of how awful they are through episodes of black mirror
as if that excuses the behavior.
Oh, we'll just call ourselves are out on it.
It's this, it's this.
Shoulder shrugging, sorry, I'm a bitch approach to being a bitch.
And suddenly that's supposed to make it okay.
Um, most seems to be most people's approach to being a bitch these days.
Yeah.
So I love myself.
So deal with it.
Yeah, fuck off.
Uh, so, uh, you know, I don't really want to get too into each episode and whatever,
but you know, the, the, the most frightening of which, uh, or appalling of which is the
Joan is awful episode that everybody's talking about, which is about a woman who's kind of
awful, but, but in her, but in her, in her own way, it's justifiable.
She one night sees there is a show on stream Barry, which is what they're calling it instead
of Netflix, but it's the same logo with an S it makes the same noise.
It's not even a cute wink.
It's like, just call it fucking Netflix guys, like get meta or don't.
And the show is called Joan is awful.
It's Selma Hayek playing her and she watches the episode with her fiance and it shows
everything she did that day.
And it reveals all of her dirty doings or whatever.
She's obviously incensed her life gets slowly ruined because of the show.
And she finds out that Netflix is allowed to do this because
she signed the terms and conditions thing agreement.
Interesting premise, cool premise.
Um, and you're like, great, where is this going?
Well, Pat, the answer to that is absolutely nowhere.
Uh, they eventually bring actual Selma Hayek into it playing herself.
They try to make that funny.
Pat, would you believe if I told you that Selma Hayek is not funny at all?
Would you believe such a thing?
I would, I like Selma Hayek, but I would believe that.
I like her too.
And she like, they even put jokes in where she makes fun of herself
and it's too meta and it's stupid.
And she's like, I am, she goes, I am a dyslexic with questionable English at best.
Like, like that's like a thing.
She screams at her lawyer.
It's like, it's just bad.
It's just bad.
And you're also like, guys, these are jokes that belong in Anchorman.
Not in the middle of a fucking black mirror episode.
Like it's stupid.
I've heard nothing but bad things.
And if I remember correctly, the last season was pretty good.
I think that was the one with the Anthony Mackie video game.
Yeah.
Gay love story thing, which I actually thought was incredible.
But yeah, I've heard nothing but shit about this new one.
This episode continually goes up its own ass.
And the ending is just, she goes to Netflix and destroys the computer
that's creating these virtual universes about her life.
And like, who cares?
That's not a commentary.
This started sort of as a commentary.
It didn't.
But what's really appalling now is Netflix puts out this website
where you can make yourself awful.
You can have your own face put into the episodes.
You can watch yourself be awful.
And as Yahoo News pointed out in a news article,
if you read the terms and conditions you have to sign to do that,
they are eerily and frighteningly similar to the terms and conditions
in the episode itself that get this woman in trouble and ruin her life.
And every fucking self -indulgent obsessed with the lexicon,
social media, pie -eyed moron is going to run and do this and go,
I don't care if Netflix exploits my image and puts me on a billboard
and doesn't give me a dime and does whatever the fuck they want to do with my face.
I get to be part of the whole thing.
And this is how it happens.
This is exactly how it happens.
Everybody thinks it's going to be Gestapo tactics
and you don't need to worry until you see machine guns on the street
and all that stuff, which we have seen, by the way.
We've seen that side of it.
And people think that that's the only problem.
No, this is the other side of the problem, people.
These are twofold or multifold things that happen that destroy us as a society and whatever.
And people are going to just willingly sign over for that.
It's just pathetic.
Shame on Netflix for doing it.
And again, they think because they're calling themselves out on it
makes it OK or excusable.
And then but the biggest offense of all, the episode sucks.
It's a thing that could be good and it sucks.
There's two episodes in this season that
one of them is marginally intriguing that are just horror episodes.
You're like there's no what is the commentary?
Black Mirror is supposed to be future technology.
Chilling take on where we're going and how it's happening, blah, blah, blah.
You're doing two episodes.
By the way, two of the episodes this season take place in 1969 and 1979.
The finale is called Demon 79.
It takes place in the 70s and it's about a woman who finds an idol
and accidentally conjures, get this, a funny demon.
Oh, great.
Great.
A funny demon.
And she has to kill three people, not that far off.
OK.
Who plays the funny demon?
Josh Gad.
I don't know who he is.
He's an English guy.
OK.
But he's like like when the idol starts talking to her, she gets scared
and throws it across the room and it lands upside down.
And from across the room, you hear the demon's muffled voice going,
oh, for the love of God, don't throw me across the room.
I'm trying to bloody help you.
I it's it's fucking pathetic.
It's pathetic.
OK.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
I'm getting really worked up right now.
It's I mean, I would advise pulling the plug on on Netflix.
I haven't looked back once and I saved twenty dollars a month.
Very easy to do.
I've got my my parents log in.
Oh, OK.
So until they come for us in the night.
They're supposed to have already done that, I thought, but maybe not.
You know, I'll keep it for now and, you know,
and watch Arrested Development or whatever.
But I mean, it's just it's just terrible.
It's shit.
It's it's not the brand.
And again, like it seems to now be this weird meta method
for Netflix to excuse themselves over their own sins.
That's not brilliant.
That's sick.
It's crazy.
It's yeah, I'm just seeing the Martin short Arrested Development.
No, I'm way behind on Arrested Development.
I got sidetracked.
But by the way, Arrested Development, let me say a positive thing.
Jessica Walter, my God, she is the I would go as far as to say she's the
best person on the show.
She's a hard choice.
But yeah, she's hilarious on that show.
They write her very, very well.
God, she's incredible on it.
Yeah.
Anyway, that's black and apparently took abuse
the entire time she was on the show from Tambor and everybody else.
No, no, no, not everybody.
No, no, no.
Let's not smear.
She said Tambor yelled at her.
And she said he but he apologized.
She said in front of him, because I've read up on this a lot,
she said she said Tambor was verbally abusive.
The other cast members defended him.
She then said in front of Tambor, nobody's ever yelled at me like that on a set ever,
but he apologized and I'd work with him again in a heartbeat.
That's the part they always leave out.
Yeah, yeah, I didn't know.
Sorry.
Go ahead.
Got way too worked up about Black Mirror.
I'm sorry.
It was look, it was a good show for a while.
Look at it like it's season seven of a great show,
and usually that's going to have problems, unfortunately.
Although when you're waiting five years between seasons,
you think the quality would be a little better, but who knows?
I wish.
Can I just say something real quick?
I long for the days when somebody sucked at their job,
the boss was able to stand there and go,
why are you still in front of me right now?
Are we not speaking the same language?
I asked you to do something.
You didn't do it.
So you're either stupid or you like,
I missed the days of a boss being able to be like that
because that got you quality.
It's gone.
It was murder.
I experienced it.
It sucked, but it made you do your job the right way.
You can deliver a quality product.
There was something too shaming.
There's an argument to be made for slapping your kids around
and everything.
They get results.
It's just not necessarily the side effects that you want.
I saw the return of comedy to cinemas.
No hard feelings.
The amount of discussion about this movie
and how the fate of comedy rested on it I thought was insane
because the movie is like a 15 million budget comedy.
Jennifer Lawrence is 10 million of that.
She earns beyond every penny.
But look, guys, it's a really funny comedy,
the likes of which might have come out in the late 90s or early 2000s.
It feels like a revelation because it's been missing for so long,
but the truth is it's just a really solid down the middle comedy.
It's written or directed by Gene Stupnitsky
and written by Gene Stupnitsky who was an office guy,
wrote many of the kind of most famous best episodes
of the American office or co -wrote or as we all know,
written probably by a group and he got the credit.
But done a lot of funny stuff and this is no exception.
It's for like a lot of big comedies.
It loses its way by the end.
The third act kind of meanders.
Wedding Crashers to me is kind of the big example of that,
of a movie where suddenly you're on a beach
with Rachel McAdams and Owen Wilson for 30 minutes
talking sincerely about how much they love each other and it's like,
what is happening guys?
What are you doing?
And this goes kind of that way too.
It has such a simple premise that it struggles to resolve
and I think that is because the premise is just in nature a little icky for people
and they probably had to go through hundreds of rewrites
until they got it to a place that everybody felt was okay.
But the movie is about two parents,
Matthew Broderick who is very funny in this
as like a total douche with like a long gray ponytail and like white sweaters.
He's really funny.
His get up like visually alone, I was like, man, it's perfect.
Yeah, yeah.
He's like a Long Island, you know, or whatever the rich part of Long Island,
that beach community kind of vibe and his wife, Laura Benanti,
who's a big Broadway actress.
They're really funny as the parents,
they take out an ad.
This is based on a true story.
Actually, the ad says, hey, our son is 19.
To me already, you're taking the teeth out of the premise by making the son 19.
But I understand they probably would never have released it if he was younger,
but they're saying our kid is about to go to college.
I mean, generally a kid in 19 would be at college, but
he's never drank.
He's never had sex.
He's too sheltered.
He's a nerd.
We want a woman to come over and fuck him basically,
and date him and get his confidence up before he goes to college.
And they're looking for somebody in their 20s.
Jennifer Lawrence is 32, but very, very game to make a lot of jokes about her age.
People are calling her old throughout the whole movie and it's really funny.
But she takes the ad.
She's broke.
She's had her car towed.
She's about to lose the family house right there.
When she's about to lose her grandma's house.
I was like, yes, guys.
The premise of every comedy from like 1985 to 1999.
Thank you.
Just give us a simple.
They're going to sell my grandma's house.
Happy Gilmore.
You know, they've done it a million times, but you get it immediately.
She needs money.
That's all you need to know.
We don't get any deeper than that.
She shows up at the house and she agrees to fuck this kid by the end of the summer.
And the kid is great.
He's wild.
I had never seen him in anything.
My date told me that he was in.
What's the big Dear Evan Hansen on Broadway or something.
But other than that, I've never seen him act, but he's super funny.
I see why he got the part.
He plays a great nerd, a very realistic nerd, and they have great chemistry.
It's like a really sweet, funny, romantic comedy between the two of them.
I won't tell you if they wind up fucking or not, but I really enjoyed it.
Even when it does go off the rails a bit at the end, the only reason I was annoyed is
because it kept it from being a really great comedy and made it just a pretty good comedy.
But the one thing I got to say is, as much as I talk about how sex and nudity is missing
from the movies these days, Jennifer Lawrence has a scene in this where she takes her clothes
off in front of him on the beach.
They're going to skinny dip.
She takes her shirt off and they do it from behind.
You only see the upper part of her shoulders.
They don't even go below that.
Then she takes her shorts off, off camera.
Like they just, you see, you know what's happening, but that's it.
No butt shot, no nothing.
It was the most chaste thing I've ever seen.
Like she might as well have worn a towel up to her neck.
And I was like, okay, got it.
This is what this is going to be.
It's the hard R rated comedy, but you know, this is what we're doing.
Okay, fine.
They go out.
They're swimming naked in the ocean.
The kid joins her.
And then some neighborhood kids come and steal their clothes.
And I was like, okay, this classic bit.
Here we go.
At that point, Jennifer Lawrence rises from the ocean and walks towards the camera in
a long shot that lasts about a minute, full frontally naked.
One of our biggest stars walk into the camera, full frontally naked, and then a lengthy,
completely nude fight scene.
She gets punched in the vagina.
She's like doing kicks and punches and everything.
It's very funny, but it's also very, very sexy.
I commend her for doing it.
I looked it up and sure enough, there's a huge discourse on Twitter of people who are
disappointed in Jennifer.
There's people saying, well, I hope it was a deep fake or something.
I certainly hope that she, they, they used AI and she didn't exploit herself like that.
And she's like, no, I got naked.
My, my body looks good.
I got naked.
I wanted to do it for the movie.
It's like, but what are they disappointed in her for?
I don't understand.
We're supposed to be like, that's supposed to be like empowering and stuff.
It made me ecstatic to not be on Twitter anymore, honestly.
Um, if it was Gabor Sibide, you'd all call her brave.
You know, it's, it's Jennifer Lawrence who looks incredible.
She's wanting to show that off in a comedy and you could,
you could just feel it in the audience.
I mean, obviously the guys were into it, but the women too.
It's like these comedies used to show you something you'd never seen before.
And something about Mary, it was the come in the hair or whatever, you know,
the, those shocking moments are what make these movies last.
And I just commend her and she is excellent in this movie.
And if they were smart, they would try to get to steer her career more Cameron Diaz
than the like story of the woman who created the mop that she's been doing
or the hunger games or whatever else.
This, this is a woman who should not be trapped in these big,
slow action sci -fi franchises anymore.
She's super funny and just like radiates off the screen.
And it's not just because she showed me or who I thought she was great in the movie.
All right.
I just masturbated to that while you were talking.
I kid people, I'm only going to do one more just because I like staying on theme
and it'll be something I'm praising a TV show that's been running for quite some time,
opposite of what black mirror did and not delivering this season.
Much to my surprise, it's always sunny is delivering in spades this season.
I thought they were going to reel it in.
I thought they were going to make it PC.
I thought they were going to, not only are they delivering the classic sunny
uncouth irreverent humor that they've always delivered,
they're undoing the precious things they did in prior seasons.
I always said, I felt like the show might've jumped the shark when Mack does the dance
to like express why he's gay or whatever.
Not that I didn't like the sentiment of it.
I just was like, this isn't that kind of show.
Like it's like, you can't get that serious on a show like this.
They make a joke about that in this season.
That is a very ballsy joke for them to make.
And I'm like, man, they are fucking going for it.
The uncle that molested Charlie keeps turning up.
They're going hard with him.
What was the joke about the dance?
I've been watching.
I don't remember that.
There's an episode where Mack is having an online flirtation with a guy
and the guy is saying this has told him to put anal beads up his ass.
Where else are you going to put them?
To insert anal beads, keep them inserted.
And the guy can control the vibration of anal beads from his phone.
He's never met the guy, but whenever the guy makes the beads vibrate,
it means Mack has to go to a motel and wait for him, but the guy never shows up.
So Mack's having a crisis of like, I think I'm in love with this man,
but he keeps stiffing me.
He's not showing up.
They're in the bar.
He's asking for Dennis's advice on how to deal with this.
Danny DeVito is there.
Danny DeVito says something about like, I love the gaze or something like that.
And Dee goes, you're the most homophobic man I know.
And Danny DeVito goes, no, no, I get it now.
Mack's dance after I saw Mack's dance.
Now I get it.
And Mack goes, see, I know Frank's an ally.
He gets it anyway.
Johnny told me to insert these anal beads and he's controlling them from his phone.
And then Frank goes, what?
What?
And he's so disgusted and he goes, I take it back.
I don't get it.
I'll never get it.
I was like, dear God, they are going for this.
And look, that doesn't elate me because it's a gay joke.
It elates me because it's a nothing is sacred joke.
And they're back doing that again.
My hats off to Rob Rozelle, Megan Gantz.
They're writing great episodes.
I know there's other writers on there, but those are the two names of the people that
I recognized and remembered.
They're just doing a good show.
It's really, really fucking funny.
I just didn't think there was any way that was going to happen with all of the other
mainstream stuff they're all doing now.
So there you go.
There you go.
Yeah.
I mean, Rob is literally buying sports teams and like he's doing,
now he's doing NASCAR racing and all kinds of shit.
Well, they also were like, they were like kind of apologizing
on the podcast for things.
And I was like, this is it, we're done.
I don't know what happened.
I mean, dude, in the second episode, they say cunt, no, the third episode,
they say cunt like five times.
I'm like, the breaks are off.
They're doing it.
This is the classic show.
I've been enjoying it for sure.
And it's season 16 or whatever.
I saw the blackening.
I was just going to say, and of course, howerton is always, yeah, just the best.
Anyway, I saw the blackening.
I did not really know what to expect on this one.
It's got the tagline.
We can't all die first, which is pretty funny, you know,
but that's about as far as the jokes go in this movie.
Um, I, you know, it's, it's a part of the reason, and usually I have a pretty good
sense of humor about this, but half the jokes are about how much white people suck.
Three fourths of the audience was white people.
So it's kind of like, okay, you know, after a certain point, it's like,
all right, guys, we suck, you know, like let's find another angle.
Um, it's a horror spoof in the vein of scary movie,
but it's also nowhere near, uh, as funny or, or interesting.
It's a bunch of people in a cabin.
Um, there is a game with like a, uh, uh, one of the old, you know,
like in ghost world when Steve Buscemi has that black face figure
and they're very offended by it.
Um, it's one of those, one of the old, like mammy blackface things,
they find this game in the house and the game starts giving them like black trivia.
Uh, and it's like who will survive the weekend or whatever.
It's also one of those where somebody in the house is the killer.
You don't know who, um, the biggest name in the cast is probably Jermaine Fowler,
who is terrible.
He's doing an impression of Eddie Murphy and both finger to, I would call it a steal
more than I would call it an impression.
He's doing the exact same face, um, clothes, glasses, voice, et cetera.
The problem is Jermaine Fowler is nowhere near as talented as Eddie Murphy.
So the character is just grading and annoying.
Um, that's a bummer.
I'm friends with Jermaine and I think he is very talented, but
somebody else was saying to me that they were like, he's doing like an Urkel.
And I said, is that because it's both finger?
Yeah.
And I, I asked, I go, is that because he's playing like a trope?
Is it like a meta thing?
And they were like, I don't think so.
It's just, he's just doing it.
Everybody else is playing it fairly real.
And then he's playing it like beyond broader than like a scary movie movie.
So no idea what he was doing, but I did.
I certainly wasn't funny.
Um, to me, it was very, very obvious who the killer was.
There was no suspense, certainly none of the scares work, although that wouldn't
be a complaint of scary movie.
It's not like I, I was mad that scary movies mystery didn't work better.
Um, it's just that the laughs weren't there either.
So it didn't work on any of these fronts.
It opens like the cold open of the movie is Jay Farrow from SNL used to be on SNL
and Yvonne Orchi or Orly from insecure.
And they're in the house and they start talking.
The game asked them who, um, are some black people or who is a black person in, in
scary movie history who survived till the end of the movie and they can't think of one.
And then he's like, Oh, uh, Jada Pinkett and Omar Epps and scream too.
And Yvonne goes, no, they died right away.
They died right away.
And she goes, and I think it's because they were so famous that the studio couldn't
afford to pay their salaries.
And then these two look at each other for a meta joke, like, uh, oh, as if they're
super famous, Jay Farrow and Yvonne Orchi, and it got silenced in the theater.
But I'm like, guys, that doesn't work when the people are not super famous.
It was, it was just weird.
You know, I didn't like it in any way.
I really thought it was a bad film and I wish I liked it more.
I don't know what else to tell you.
I went in with I hopes, um, but it's bad.
All right.
There you go.
Speaking of bad, speaking of bad, here's a real straight down the middle horror film
called the boogeyman.
Uh, I'll give you a joke.
I've been sitting on since last night, Pat.
Yes.
They want me to think BM stands for boogeyman.
I can think of something else it stands for with this picture.
Here's a movie.
I texted Pinkstone after I got out of the movie because he texted me when I was in
the movie.
I got out.
I said, Hey man, sorry.
I was in the movies.
I saw the boogeyman.
This is a movie that starts great, then becomes boring.
Then becomes bad, then becomes lazily, utterly dog shitty.
Like, like, like it's crazy.
This thing starts.
So, so it's based on the Stephen King story and they actually do do the story in the
movie and they use the four, the four page Stephen King story is about a guy that goes
to a psychiatrist and says, I killed my children and the guy says, what do you mean?
And he says, well, I had three children.
They were all murdered by the boogeyman and I couldn't stop the boogeyman.
So I essentially have the blood on my hands and the boogeyman's real.
And then at the end of the story, the boogeyman comes out of the closet and the
psychiatrist office or whatever and kills the guy.
That's the basic story, uh, was adapted very well in the, um, what is it called?
I got it.
I got it over there.
Stephen King's, uh, night shift collection, which were two VHS videos released in the
eighties, uh, uh, when Stephen King was licensing his stories out for a dollar each to college
filmmakers, uh, he picked three that he thought were the best and they released them on VHS.
One of them was an adaptation of the boogeyman and, and I own it and it's very good.
Um, but it's just an annotation of that story.
This movie opens with.
First of all, they kill a baby in the, in the cold open.
I was like, Oh, they're, they're going for this.
All right.
Here we go.
Boogeyman, uh, that's disturbing.
Uh, it then starts with the psychiatrist and his first patient in the movie.
Basically is the guy coming in saying, you know, you realize, oh, that baby was this guy's
and you're like, okay, this is the Stephen King story.
And it transpires exactly as it does in that story.
Except the guy doesn't say the N word 20 times, which is really weird in the book.
It's like Stephen King makes him a racist for no reason.
It's really strange.
Yeah.
I always wondered why that was.
If that was supposed to be like, look, you're supposed to find him unlikable.
Yeah.
Like, or something about him is indicating he could have done this.
I don't know.
I'm never quite sure.
You know, that's the argument with Tarantino Scorsese.
And I guess probably sometimes Stephen King is like, you got these people in here saying
this stuff.
Are you doing that to get away with it?
Or are you doing it because you think it serves a purpose?
Anyway, um, so that all transpires in the movie.
And then you've got another 90 minutes to get through.
So it then takes you on the journey of this single father slash psychiatrist,
psychologist, whatever it is, and his two daughters, and they have lost their mother
in an accident and car accident.
And they're recouping from that recovering from that.
And the premise here is, is basically now, and it's painfully fucking obvious.
Now the boogeyman has attached itself to their family, which Pat had texted me
while I was in the theater saying, enjoy that movie.
Enjoy the horror movie about somebody dealing with trauma.
Cause we haven't seen that 400 times in the last year.
And I was like, I know, I agree.
And I said, and also enough of this.
It needs a host bullshit guys.
It follows was the, was the be all end all enough.
That's enough.
This was what insidious is.
There's a new insidious coming out.
This was, it follows.
This was sinister.
It just goes on and fucking on enough.
Anyway, it feels like, looks like, smells like almost every other horror movie.
Like you realize that there's a whole new set of cliches now in horror.
Everybody complained about all the cliches in the slasher movies.
And the same cliches, we're still trying to parody with the blackening, but now
there's a whole new list of cliches that all these movies have to be about grief.
Trauma, they're shot the same, like we've watched so many of these in this fucking
show, uh, antlers and all these kinds of movies that came out of the pike stuff.
You forget about the minute they're gone, the lake house and all that.
But I mean, this, this is really just a jump scare delivery machine.
And everyone's really sad because somebody died, usually the mother of a family.
It's like, we don't need this same story told again and again and again.
It makes your horror movie not fun.
Smile did the same thing.
It did a metaphor of trauma.
But it did it really well.
And it followed it to the end.
It like really had something to say.
And it tried to do new things within this formula.
But I am done with this shit, like just done with it.
It's so boring to me.
It's very boring.
And this also, there are no real stakes.
There are no real motivations for characters.
Everything is very, is justified with such simplicity.
Well, the little girl sees the boogeyman first and nobody believes her.
Why?
Because she's little and she's afraid of the dark.
She's just being a kid.
It's a boring fucking premise.
It's a boring justification.
They're able to defeat the boogeyman at the end.
How?
Because somehow the mom spiritually helps them.
It's fucking terrible.
This ancient creature that's existed before man is defeated.
How?
Because they burn it to death.
What?
It's physical?
Joe, what did you do when Elvis's burning love started over the end credits?
Pat, I'm going to tell you something.
I was out the door already.
I watched it up until they burned the thing to death.
I was furious.
I looked at Wikipedia.
Wikipedia said in the premise.
The final scene is she goes to a therapist and the door is open insinuating that the
I don't need to stay for another four minutes to see that scene.
I'm out.
This movie sucks.
And I walked out.
Well, believe it or not, there was an ironic upbeat song over the end credits.
Yet another cliche.
Burning love.
It's a fucking bummer.
It really is.
And what's curious about it to me is that it was written by the guys who did Quiet Place,
which I know I liked a lot more than you.
That okay, go ahead.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
And then directed by the guy who did host the very, very clever and creative and fun zoom
horror movie that that premiered during the pandemic on shutter.
Then he followed that up with dash cam, which while not perfect either,
just had a lot of energy to it.
This is a guy who has been trying to make innovative, low budget, very, very low budget
horror.
And now he gets his chance to do a big Hollywood thing.
And whether it's his fault or not, he just starts doing exactly what everybody else does.
What we need is people like Sam Raimi, who at least early on in his career,
tried to bring his insane low budget energy to all these big budget films.
That's what we need.
The boogeyman could have been directed by anybody.
So why do you get some?
It's the same thing Marvel does.
Why do you get some exciting up and coming new director and then handcuff them and make
them do something like this?
Does Joe Dante is just said, you know, because they're controllable, you know,
Yeah, that's true.
I was a skill set is going to be a problem who established is going to be a problem for them.
And then a younger guy with a skill set that they'll just toss the skill set out.
And if that skill set becomes a problem or the director and pushback become a problem,
they'll replace the director.
They don't give a crap.
All they're looking at is is this guy has enough buzz to make us some money.
We don't give a fuck about his original stamp being put on this at all.
So I'm glad I did not know the Quiet Place guys wrote this.
But it makes sense because I wrote to you and said,
Why does this monster look like something from a quiet place?
This is stupid.
You were hint.
And this is the most egregious aspect of the movie to me.
You are given a chance to make a movie called the Boogeyman.
It's based on a cool Stephen King story called the Boogeyman.
What's it about?
The Boogeyman, literally about the Boogeyman.
It's not about some meta.
It's not some other thing.
And it's called the Boogeyman because that's a metaphor for this.
It's literally about the scariest, coolest, oldest monster ever that we've all been afraid
of since we were kids.
To my knowledge, we've never seen on screen.
So you have a wide open palette to do whatever you want with it.
And you make this thing an asexual quad ped, whatever the fuck it's called,
or four legs beast.
Make it the goddamn Boogeyman.
Make it scary.
Like this thing, it looks like a fucking alien from a quiet place.
It's stupid.
It's not scary.
The only scares this movie has are jumps.
Any promise it sets up or establishes in the beginning that where it could be suspenseful,
it's lost by halfway through.
And I saw they had this David Dalmashian, Desmouchian, the guy who's kind of like,
he does a lot of these type of weird characters now.
He's in Prisoners and stuff.
When I saw that he was going to be the guy that comes in and he's like,
I want to kill myself, and he's telling the story of the Boogeyman.
I thought, okay, we've got this great, weird, creepy character actor.
He's going to be playing the Boogeyman later in the film.
I thought that was going to be the turn.
So I was in the exact same boat as you, Joe.
When they're showing us this creature that looks exactly like the things in Quiet Place
or any number of other movies, I'm like, why not cast this guy as the Boogeyman?
He's the best performer in the movie and you give him one scene and then he kills himself.
There's so many questions I have.
I think in this day and age, they're like, a man doesn't scare anybody.
It's got to be a monster.
Men aren't scared.
Dumb. Dumb.
It's just, it sucks.
The movie just sucks.
Again, it starts with -
It felt like the Hulu original that it was.
They just released it in theaters.
Yeah, it starts with great, great promise and it goes absolutely nowhere,
except in cliched directions, including, of course,
the young heroine going to the house of whatever that guy's name is that you just mentioned,
his character's remaining wife.
She's the only one that's still alive from the family
and getting all the information she needs from a perfectly available source,
which is such a lazy form of writing.
And then also, too, that lady's terrible, too,
when she's trying to play a badass and you're like, this sucks.
Oh, God.
Locks her up to use her as bait.
Fuck this movie.
I'm actually aggravated about it.
My hog is way down with the boogeyman.
Don't waste your time.
My hog's down, too.
Yeah, if you just judge it on its surface, on what it is, it's bad,
but if you look at the potential,
then that's when it starts to get kind of upsetting,
because they just did nothing with this.
Save your time.
Save your money.
Save 90 minutes and read a quick, effective four -page short story by Stephen King.
Or watch the student film if you can get your hands on one of those.
I think you can actually watch it on YouTube.
It's just on there.
Anyway, folks, we will be back with a major Indiana Jones episode in early July.
That's next up.
Yeah, get out there.
See that one.
That's the next one we'll be doing.
Also in July is the new Mission Impossible,
which I have to imagine we will tackle as well.
I am on Instagram at the Patrick Walsh.
I did my dear friend Kevin Porter's podcast Good Christian Fun yesterday,
where we discussed the movie Contact with Jodie Foster,
and that should be dropping this week.
Give that a listen as well.
I have a major, major plug.
So a couple things.
Number one, I've got shows on sale now.
I'm embarking on some new types of a new venture,
as far as the venues that I'm playing are going.
And we've announced a few shows here.
I've got Avenal New Jersey at the Performing Arts Center September 16th.
Toronto, Ontario for the Just for Laughs Festival,
Thursday, Friday, Saturday, September 21st, 22nd, 23rd.
And November 11th, Philadelphia, PA, the Theater of the Living Arts.
These are all really big shows for me.
These are new venues, types of venues that I'm doing.
I'm moving into the small theater space.
Please, please buy your tickets.
Come out and see the show.
I'm doing the I never promised you a Rose Garden hour.
Jodorosa .com.
Simple.
Hope to see you out there.
Also, fans of this podcast and fans of my other podcast taste buds
have been asking me about my old band Salsa Windfall.
You have shown interest and support in seeing us potentially doing something again.
Finally, this album we've had on the shelf
is being released in August.
It is called Artificial Birth.
And on July 7th, which is next.
Well, yeah, next Friday for whenever you hear this.
Or this coming Friday, whenever the hell you listen to this, you get it though.
It's a Friday coming up real soon in July on July 7th.
The first single from the album will be made available on digital platforms everywhere.
The song is called Mouth on My Money.
We're really, really excited for this to be finally coming out.
Again, digital platforms everywhere.
Salsa Windfall.
Mouth on My Money.
July 7th.
And the announcement that the album Artificial Birth will be coming on August 4th.
That's it for me, folks.
Love y 'all.
If you're in town, hit Joey Roses up.
JoeyRosesNYC .com.
Until then, we'll see you next time.
And we'll see you in hell.