I'll see you in hell.
Folks, it's we'll see you in hell, the podcast where we talk about movies
sometimes twice because somebody lost an episode that we recorded already
yesterday of this exact same movie. It was Joe. It was like a long episode
too. Really gave it a roll. I felt like you were sort of keeping me on the line
out of loneliness after a while. It was very long because the first 40 minutes of
it was a dive into dark territory for you and I probably it might be best that
it was lost. There was it hit moments where I was like people people aren't
about our emotional states, various weeping incidents, bad customer service,
a lot of bad customer service stories. Yeah. Yeah. I had a door dash incident,
Pat had a thing at the deli. Yeah. Yeah. And that's probably not a good
sign either two grown men and their biggest gripes were food related. It was,
you know, it's very, it's very old man -ish deli problems. That'll be our podcast
when we're 75 years old living in a two -bedroom apartment. Or let's be honest,
maybe a one -bedroom apartment. At that point, we'll just have admitted it to ourselves.
We'll see you in deli. Folks, we are talking today about a
Christmas story Christmas, the fourth sequel to the classic Bob Clark original.
And the fourth official sequel has Joe pointed out yesterday. Yeah. It's the third time
they've called it an official sequel after my summer story, after a Christmas
story too, and now a Christmas story Christmas, who would have thought that of
all the legacy franchises that get the we're going to fix it with the new sequel thing.
A Christmas story would be one of those that gets the Jamie Lee Curtis Halloween
treatment. Yeah. We're going to ignore the other two. We'll see that that's the version
I would have liked is them coming back and him like getting revenge on the bullies.
You know, and it's it's Billingsley on a mask or something. So we don't have to look at
Peter Billingsley for 90 minutes. You know, and I don't mean he's a bellic
guy. I mean, he's a reminder of times inevitable March because the last time we saw
him, he was a fresh face eight -year -old. And then when you see him in HD and everything
now, you're like, whoa, but of course we've all aged like that. We've all aged.
No criticism of him. I'm just saying I know what you're saying. He comes back and
takes revenge on the bullies. That's what I want to see. And then Halloween can go
the comedy route and we see them as kids and the traumatic but amusing adventures that
made him Michael Myers. I agree. I agree. You know, I'd like to see a six -year -old
Michael Myers blowing up a frog. Yeah. Yeah. Firecracker and beating every cat.
Yeah. Christmas story Christmas. Here we go. And who would have thought a Christmas
story would be a franchise with different timelines. But here we are. We've got three
different Christmas story timelines. True. The multiverse. And when Dr.
Strange popped up at the end of this latest Christmas story, I couldn't believe. Yes.
Did you see the new Rami multiverse? No. No, that's really as we've said, I think
one of the only Marvel movies I really liked was Dr. Strange. And I love Sam Rami.
So I'm excited to see it, but I also couldn't care less or could care less.
It's at a point where this, you know, so should we get this avatar?
Three cool coming out three way of water. Yeah.
Cameron, I just read an interview with him and I agreed with him.
And you know, I'm not a Cameron fan. So this is saying a lot. He, he was responding
to people saying that Avatar had no cultural impact. And he basically, I'm paraphrasing.
He didn't curse. And he wasn't rude. But my interpretation of what he was saying was like,
what the fuck are you talking about? I made the highest grossing movie of all time.
Sorry, I don't put a movie out every week like Marvel does. And how dare you say that
that's what cultural impact has to be is a barrage of cinema that you can't escape from.
You can't go see a new movie now without seeing a trailer for a Marvel movie.
It's crazy. It's sick. Well, even ones that start off not being Marvel movies,
like the trailer and halfway through it and you realize it's Marvel now.
I was watching the new Ant Man trailer and I turned to my friend and I'm like,
isn't this the comedy one? Like it was just another serious Marvel movie.
The comedy's gone from Ant Man. Then some guy takes his super, you know, villain mask off.
It's Bill Murray.
Wait, and that's supposed to be funny though, right? No, no.
But I was also sort of hardened that he's not canceled. I mean, they didn't give him a line in the trailer.
You just saw him take a mask off dramatically, but I don't need to see Bill Murray's nobody.
Like I don't need to see Bill Murray kicking ass. I don't I love Bill Murray.
You know, I don't he's funny. I don't need to see that. He's a guy. I don't need to see do that.
I hated. I have hated the last.
I was so relief. Like ghost prostras after life. We gave it a good review.
It's not a great movie, but it's it was serviceable.
But if I had to watch that ending a second time, I'd probably be pretty alarmed at how bad that looked with the four of them in front of the Universal Studios theme park backdrop.
Yeah, I saw that movie after a day where con Edison for no reason shut down the electricity to the bar.
We were building at the time still. So construction workers were on the clock.
We're not working. They were just getting paid. Right.
I had the one of the biggest blowouts I had ever with my business partner.
And I went to the theater and drank four whiskeys before I went into the movie.
So I was in pretty good, just relieved spirits to be watching ghost busters after life.
Right. I agree. I think on a rewatch with a clear set of state of mind.
I might not be as swept away. But my point is I was happy to see Bill Murray do something like that.
Because I much like Tom Hanks. I had hit my limit with Bill Murray serious movies.
Like it was enough. I was like enough with the indie brooding enough bill. I've had enough.
What when he played Roosevelt in that one movie with the with the never even sawing low the cigarette. I never even saw him.
I looked at that picture of him with that cigarette and I said no.
Unless this is monopoly the movie, then I'll go see it. If it's not, then no.
I do that with more movies each year. But I remember I used to see everything in them one year.
I was like, I'm not going to see this Mrs. Potter's the one with what's her face from Jerry McGuire.
It was, I believe it was about AA Milm, a movie of life of the person who wrote Winnie the Pooh.
Wait, Rachel's Renee Zellweger. Renee Zellweger. Yeah, Mrs. Potter.
It was, I believe it was the story of the author of Winnie the Pooh.
And I was like, all right, one year I get to pick one that I'm not going to see.
And, you know, usually now the only screeners I get the only one I currently have is the one about the 13 miners that we already made fun of.
Right.
And then a movie where I got to watch Emmett Till get hung for a crime he didn't commit on a Friday night.
The, the, the, the Till one, the Till, Till seems to me to be quite an important movie and a story that should be told in a very relevant movie.
Oh, absolutely.
But it's not a movie. Yeah, it's not, it's, it's, it's up there with, well, it's, it's a movie you just bought on 4k.
It's a, it's a Schindler's list. It's a precious. It's not a movie.
You're talking and for both of those movies, right?
I'm, they're wonderful movies. I'm sure Till is great too, but I'm saying you've got to be in a certain place to watch something.
It's heavy stuff, man. Yeah.
Yeah.
Uh, these two I got in the mail today. I've never even heard of these.
The sun, the sun and the sun is like a sequel to the father that Anthony Hopkins one.
Are you kidding?
Super depressing and about Alzheimer's.
But the sun has Hugh Jackman as I believe the son of the Anthony Hopkins character.
I'm serious.
I don't know if you have to see the father to get the son.
Who plays the son in the first one.
There's no son. It's a daughter.
So now he, now the son comes in his Hopkins in this one.
I'm going to look up.
Let me look up the son. Now we got enough.
Jesus Christ.
Uh, the son centers on.
Oh God.
No, I don't want to watch the trailer.
It's already out. It's been out.
Um, no, maybe maybe it's not connected.
It's not connected.
That is madness. If it is.
The same director.
Oh God.
He did the father.
He did the song.
Oh, that's right. The, the father was.
Um, peep show.
What's her name? Olivia.
Yeah. Right. Right.
Uh, multi jet. No, no, a multi -generation.
No epic telling of the story of America's birth as a superpower.
Oh, wait. No, that's a mini series that came out to us.
Like, what the fuck?
We got to abandon this.
We got to abandon this line.
Oh, it serves as a prequel to the father.
Maybe he's the young version of the father.
No, Hopkins is in it.
Hopkins is in it.
And it's Laura Dern.
It was the father.
I don't think so. No, she wasn't.
So yeah, it's a prequel.
To a story about a man slowly dying of Alzheimer's in an apartment building.
We, we see the prequel to it.
How do you?
I don't understand.
There's another.
Oh, this is the TV series.
This was a great movie.
It was, it was.
Unbelievably depressing, but it was great.
The son, the TV series is a miniseries starring Pierce Broston.
It's like a prairie cowboy.
Uh, which the title makes a little more sense for that, in my opinion.
But, yeah.
Um, and then living.
What the hell is living?
Living is a very bad title.
I got, yeah, it's like, I used to really enjoy getting these screeners.
Now I'm not getting any, and I also don't even know what some of them are.
It stars Bill Nahi.
You want it?
Can I read you the definition of this one?
I was just about to go ahead.
So now I'm just a veteran civil servant receives a medical diagnosis that inspires him to move to the South.
The South Coast and cram some fun into his remaining days.
Jesus Christ.
When there's more, he meets a sunny young female colleague who seems to have the pep that had previously escaped him.
Grime.
I guess it's going to be like blam it on Rio.
It's just going to be Bill Nahi fucking a 20 year old girl.
Full drama.
No comedy either.
Oh my god.
Alrighty.
Joe, did you see the indie Jones trailer?
Yeah.
New psycho.
That's the real lead today.
I did see it.
The trailer.
Do the slow.
I didn't even notice if it did though.
It did.
Yeah.
But it did when it hits the.
Bam.
When it hits the slow part of that, I got it.
I got.
I got some chills.
Yeah.
Trailer's great.
It looks awesome.
The title sucks.
But we'll all get used to it.
I'm sure when they announced Temple of Doom, people were like, we're like, what the fuck are you talking about?
So, you know, I'm sure the title will.
I will say Temple of Doom is a badass title for a badass film.
The style of destiny.
I think so too.
But do we think Temple of Doom is a great title because we were five.
We're never going to problem.
Perhaps.
Look, you know, I remember when they said Star Wars 2 was going to be called Attack of the Clones.
And I was like, that is insane.
Like, and now I'm like, yeah, it's Attack of the Clones.
Anyway.
The trailers writing a letter to George Lucas with a quill pen.
Angerly.
The trailer is great, but trailers are often great.
They're heavy, heavy, heavy, heavy, heavy.
Internet rumors, which sadly are usually true these days.
Trumers I call them.
Trumer.
There you go.
That the news equal to trimmers.
This is the, uh, the, uh, the gravity infiltrate Fox News.
And I always say pat that rumors are like tumors.
Hmm.
Cancerous.
Yeah.
And last we're talking about Fleetwood Max rumors.
And good night to the great Christine McVee.
any of my favorite Fleetwood Macsons and her solo single Output got a hold on me that
was in my top 100 Spotify rap list. It's an amazing song. Anyway, carry on. No, it's
a great trailer, but I'm worried about the rumors. There's rumors that there's going to
be time travel in the movie. The dial of Destiny sort of speaks to that to me. In a world
where we're ripping hearts out of rib cages, you're bothered by what? The that it's not grounded
in reality, traveling through time or what? No, the thing that makes Indiana, I like all four.
I even like Crystal Skull, even though there are abominable parts in it. I like it. I like the movie.
It's got parts that I hate, but I make me cringe and wins, but I like the movie. But
Indiana Jones, when it's at his best, is like a last crusade kind of thing where it's all
very grounded and then something miraculous happens in the final moments. That's that's sort of
inexplicable in its own way, but maybe could be explained away, you know, like for instance,
when he in class crusade, when he walks across the precipice and it's supposed to be like he's
walking on air, but then you see that the stone is painted to look visible. And then like the guy
in their tomb is supposedly the night of whatever crusade and the last, you know, last crusade, but you
could say, well, we don't know that for certain. It could just be a guy that's just in there saying
that, you know, all of it is sort of you could explain the magic away in some way, shape or form.
But yeah, in Temple of Doom, you can't, Temple of Doom gets a little nutty, you know, with like
the voodoo possession stuff and all that. Crystal Skull gets a little nutty with like the,
I never, the alien thing never really bothered me. It's just kind of the idea that the device
can hypnotize you in whatever. I really remember his prairie dog reaction shots.
Yeah, those weren't great. And Shia LaBuff in the vines.
That's, yeah, those are two of the things that I didn't care for. But, and that's what sticks with
me sadly. Look, it was cool. I just hope that, you know, Star Wars has become very hit and miss.
You know, they're, they, they, they, they do certain things with it that make it suck. And I
don't mean like, you know, I'm not complaining about diversity or anything like that. I'm complaining
about like they, they, they like, they, they do bad storytelling. This willow show for him is a great
example of a Lucasfilm. This thing looks like, I mean, I'm not a huge fan of the movie Willow. I love
that as a kid, but it's a movie. It's a well put together film. It's a fantasy film. This
fucking show, dude, I turned it on last night. It looks like I'm not kidding. It looks, I tweeted about
it. I said, I said, I knew the new Willow was a legacy sequel series. I just didn't realize it was
to Kevin Sorbo's Hercules. Like, it looks like, it looks like cheap. Yeah, it looks like Xena warrior
princess. And it's cast completely with contemporary teens who say the word like every other word in
Willow and are having like sex with each other. Like, like, it's, it's terrible. And Warwick Davis is
there jerking off for what? Warwick Davis comes in to lead them on a journey. But like the, the
almost entire first episode is all about like the romantic relationships between all the teen
characters. It's terrible. It's terrible. I watched the pilot. And then I, I, it ends with a
contemporary rock song. Okay. It's terrible. It's the magic dragons. No, it's like it's like it's
like it's like one of those like, like a, like a female pop singer, like, like it ends literally
talking terrible, unfathomably terrible, inexplicably terrible. So my worry is with Indiana Jones that
they're going to do it all, you know, Kathleen Kennedy gets blamed a lot for it. I don't know if it's
her or not, but here's the sad part. These rumors come out. The creators deny, deny, deny, deny.
And then the rumors are all true. That's happened over and over again in recent years with these
big legacy projects. And, you know, there were, there were a lot of rumors about this one, the
test greetings went bad and all this stuff. And James Mangold came out and said, none of it's true.
But I've heard this before. Kevin Smith did this with, with the Masters of the Universe thing,
where he was like, this show is 100 % about him and all these rumors are wrong. It's not
what, and it wasn't. It was all everything that they said. And it's like, I don't know, dude,
it just sucks. Yeah, sucks. You're just the bummer. It's like, why, you know, if you're just using
an old property to launch a new thing that you have whatever the agenda may be behind it, it's like
just create some new shit for God's sakes. Like don't, yeah, don't tease me with,
you know, as corny as it sounds for a 45 year old man to be sitting here going, I didn't get enough
he -man. I mean, you know, you're teasing me with him. I got excited. I wanted to see a he -man
versus Skeletor show. I know that's not what it was. So I just hope that that's not the case with this.
And time travel as a concept, of course, it's not that absurd in the scope of Indiana Jones,
but I feel like the way they would do it could be absurd. But I don't know, dude, the trailers
great, but what does that mean anymore? I don't, you know, look, the last time mangled
tackle time travel, I think we're talking about a little movie called Kate and Leopold starring Hugh
Jack when a Meg Ryan. Really his only shit movie. So that is a little scary, but I don't mind Indiana Jones
traveling through time. I don't mind it. I'm excited of a young Indiana Jones type thing to do,
but I'll buy it either way. I'm excited about Harrison being back. I'm excited about Phoebe
bridge bridge. Is it bridges or bridge is or just bridge. Bridges is the singer and Phoebe
Waller bridge is the bridge. I always get it confused. I think she's awesome. I think she'll be
sad to say. Oh, okay. Yeah, she's very classical, classically beautiful. And I'm not putting
her beauty as a qualification. I'm just saying she looks like a leading woman from that time period.
Right. Much like Harrison Ford all reminded us of like a bow guard or whatever. I'm happy to see
Salah back in the trailer. That lit me up. Mads Michelson. You can really not go wrong with that guy.
And he's the main villain. Uh, you know, you got bandara's in there in a little part.
Antonia. Oh, yeah. Didn't see him. They also, you barely saw a wall or bridge, but
you know, maybe they're saving some stuff. I don't know. Got D .A. Jindy. I'm into that little flash.
And it actually looked pretty good. Got to say. Yeah, looks pretty good. So I think it'll be a fitting.
I hope they just give him a fitting close. And it's by the way, it's a perfect
rhythmically in the series. It's perfect. Every other movie deals with Nazis and every other movie
features Salah and has the connective tissue. The one two and five are the ones that are sorry,
two and four are the ones that are sort of standalone and get crazy and go way more out there with
the concepts and all that stuff. One, three, four Nazis, characters tying everything together.
And then usually something religious based. But this one's about the space race. So I don't know
that any, you're going to get any Jesus biblical stuff in there. But we'll see.
I'm pumped. And folks, Joe's being modest. He doesn't want to tell you so I'm going to tell you
he did join the very small select team of advisors for Mr. Yay West this week.
Also known as Kanye, but Joe decided this week to kind of get on the bandwagon. And then you know,
I think we're getting a lot of Joe's beliefs sort of through Kanye, which has been exciting. Yeah,
to see. Did you, did you watch the question? I can't believe you didn't ask that. I like that you
did a headier version of it. But sure, I mean, look, we've been together a long time. We got to keep
it spicy. Did you watch the Alex Jones interview with Kanye in the zip up mask, talking about how he
loves Nazis and Hitler and thought that they not only made a lot of great points, but like we're
pretty good people. You told me about it on the show yesterday. As you were telling me, I was like,
there's no way this is what he actually said. That's got to be exaggerating for a humorous effect.
I get off the thing. I Google it every headline. Kanye praises Hitler. Yeah, Jesus Christ. Yeah,
I mean, you can just watch clip after clip. Craziest was him with a net, a net, like a butterfly
in that and a you who bottle, like he was talking to Benjamin not Yahoo. And he was going, hi,
talking to them like how do you do to your whatever. So I don't know. I don't know if they're pushing him
to act really crazy so that he can blame it on. I don't know. I don't know what he's doing. I don't
know. I don't know what's real anymore. Having a complete mental collapse. I believe he's
having a mental collapse and he's being taken advantage of by right wing thugs, but I don't I don't
know. Yeah, it looks like those guys have got him kind of propped up and it's bad news. He's he's
having a mental collapse. He's too rich and isolated for anybody to force him to do anything to help
himself. And you know, my take on this will always be the same. It's my take with Ezra Miller.
It's my take with Kanye. It's my take with anybody. It's my take with Will Smith. And obviously the
the the actions of these people are in varying degrees of problematic or whatever you want to call
it. But you know, I don't agree or can with or condone anything that any of these guys have done.
I'm not saying that they're not causing harm. I'm not saying that they're not even potentially
acting out of their own just shitty nature. But you got people who are having a mental breakdown.
They're sick. We're not supposed to be crazy shaming. We're supposed to be trying to help people
in these positions. And yet it seems like the anti crazy shaming thing goes out the window. The second
we can make a big news story out of it. I don't understand. You know, David Cross had a bit about like
you know, they blamed Columbine on violence on violence on TV. And he was like the coverage of that
was violence on TV. How many times they show them lifting the the corpse out of the window of the
school? He's like, that's violence on TV. And yet that's what's their that's the very stuff that
they're blaming the incident on like other. It's like, this is crazy shaming. This guy is
damaged. Like he's got a problem. And I wish some of the coverage. It may be this the truth. I
don't know. I wish some of the coverage would say, I hope this guy can get some help. Like he's
fucked up. You know, I don't think this is like Kanye West was always secretly a wild Hitler lover.
I think he's had a fucking mental breakdown. True, but you know, yeah, there's not a mental illness
that makes you start saying that if it's not present and something. Well, that's not true. There's
mental illness that'll make you say, I'm Eleanor Roosevelt. You know, I don't think at this length.
I mean, this is a guy with just hated his heart is what I feel. I've given him too many passes at
this point. And I know you had issue with him from the jump. Oh, yeah. I was a fan. I got off the
train relatively early. I knew where this was headed. I might not have known this. And I'm sure
we've got even further to go and perhaps something even more horrible will happen, but they're just
letting him go. It's terrible. It's terrible. And again, I'm not placing to your point, Pat.
I'm not placing zero blame on him. Maybe he does have that inside of him. And maybe it's been
in there the whole time. I don't know. But like, my point is is like, he's fucked up. Like Jesus,
great. Like also, okay, how about this to bring it back to entertainment and out of the world of
mental, whatever? When are they going to learn that like to stop doing this to people? Like, when
is that going to stop? When are they going to stop allowing people to reach these levels of insane,
insane star? That will never happen. How many Britney Spears have to fucking collapse on the floor
as the press are following her around? And you know what I mean? It's like how many times does this
sort of thing have to happen on camera before people go, you're right. It'll never stop. It's gross.
It's gross, man. Because we love it.
Media in this country, man. Kanye is fucked up. I'm not saying he's not. But the media in this country
is fucked up. There needs to really be, you know, I don't know. I don't know how you maintain free
pet press, but also have regulations. But like, the fact that the press can just run wild with anything,
it's so crazy to me. It creates the whole Elon through Kanye off of Twitter.
He did? Yeah. And all he does is talk about free speech. Yeah. And it's like, dude, you've dug,
you immediately have dug yourself this whole because now you have to publicly deny this man his
horrific, but admittedly free speech. Right. It's just a, it's just a goddamn mess. It's just a
goddamn mess. World's crumbling, buddy. Yeah. And it's said that we're using Kanye West as a bro.
I know. To bring it over to movies. Yesterday, the sight and sound poll was released,
which is a British magazine. And, you know, generally pretty high pollutant. But when I first started out
watching like the great films, when I was like, what, you know, what are the thought of as the great
movies? I thought I started that very young. And I would use the sight and sound poll.
So, Ebert would vote so he could he'd put his picks and stuff like that. All the critics vote
and they tabulate them up. Directors all get to say, so for long, long time, the number one movie
has been Citizen Kane. And people were like, maybe it'll get shook, shook up this year or whatever.
Things got real shook up on the greatest movies of all time list. So, I watched number one,
yesterday. I was like, how have I not heard of the number one movie when I feel like I've seen
pretty much all the great films? With the film school, that was, you know, that was my life for many
years. I'm like, all right. It's called Gene Deelman, comma, 23, comma, quadrucomers, comma,
1080 brook sales. Who the fuck fuck you? Fuck you and fuck that movie. And who the fuck voted that
is number one? Who determined that? It was the pooled result. So like, what? And this is
Chantal Ackerman, who's a name I've heard, but I have not seen her movies. I thought I was like,
you know, these are experimental movies or whatever. Okay. So, I'm like, all right, not, you know,
not going to be pissed about it. I'm going to have an open mind and I'm going to watch this movie
knowing nothing about it. And I bet I'll have my life changed. Let's do it because since I have the
criteria in collection, I owned this movie. I didn't even know. Okay. So I opened it up, I threw it on.
I'm watching and this is not not an exaggeration. A woman go about her day, you know, pretty good looking
40 -year -old lady in Brussels. So there's subtitles as well. But she would like wash dishes,
but fully washed dishes in a static unbroken shot. Five minutes. Then she'll go into the
living room and sit down and start knitting two minutes. Then she'll say, I'm almost out of yarn.
Keep knitting. Sun comes home. They sit at the kitchen table.
They have dinner and complete silence that goes on for 10 minutes. Just spoons hitting plates.
I'm getting angry, but I'm like, all right, fine. Let's see where this is going. Right.
A John shows up. You see this guy leaving any pace or so, like, he clearly gets implied that he
fucked her for money. Okay. She's like, okay. So she's like a housewife with a son or a husband's
dad turns tricks to make money. Okay. So at that point, you're like, well, something interesting is
happening. All right. I hit pause. I'm like, where are we in the movie? We're at like 50 minutes.
So when something that wasn't just a static shot of somebody doing a chore happened. So you're like,
okay, she goes into town. You're like, oh, finally, a change. It's set over three days.
She fully runs errands and you watch the errands. Come to home peels potatoes slowly. She's making a
meatloaf slowly. I finally look it up. The running time is three hours and 21 minutes.
And I'm like, no, fuck it. I'm going to sit here and finish this. The number one movie of all time
keeps going. I'm not going to tell you the ending because if you want to watch it yourself,
that's the only thing you're waiting for is the ending. You're not going to be happy with the ending.
I'm never going to watch it. Tell me the ending. No, I'm talking to it to our listeners. I'll tell you
because look, people are going to be interested in this now. It's number one movie. But when I'm
what I'm telling you is so it's so an under reporting of what was happening. I'm so not exaggerating enough
to tell you how long these scenes are. The one scene that's at least entertaining for sexy reasons is
this woman gives herself a bath that goes on for 12 minutes and you're at least there's nudity in
the frame. So you're like, okay, but for the most part, it's a lady doing dishes. So about
two and a half hours in, I'm like, I think this movie is showing me the boredom of everyday life and
how boring it is to be a housewife in the patriarchy to use the word of the times. This movie was like
1975. And does anyone know how boring the life of a housewife actually is? We're going to show you.
That's how I took it. So as the movie goes, then of course, her routine starts unraveling,
which they show in like a four -minute scene of her cutting potatoes, but then she like cooks it too
long and she's shining a shoe, but she drops the shoe brush on the floor. You're like, oh, she's
cracking, but these scenes are all still five minutes a piece. Slowly, slowly, slowly, you see that she's
kind of unraveling. Folks, this is where we're at. I wrote a little thing about it on Letterbox.
I was so pissed because I was like, the 10 -year -old kid today, my cousin or something excited about
film is like, oh, great. I'm going to watch the 100. They just picked the 100 greatest movies of all time.
If they start with that, they're probably going to turn their back on movies altogether. Ridiculous.
Great. What a coincidence. What a coincidence that right now, sight and sound, the AV Club,
has realized that the greatest movie of all time just happens to be a movie about a woman
made by a woman that nobody has ever heard of. That can't just be a coincidence. That's amazing.
What an amazing coincidence that happened this year. There are so many great female filmmakers who have
made so many great films. Exactly. To pick this one at random, I really don't understand.
I really don't understand. Because the AV Club wants to go look at us, we're going to give a nod
to a film that deserves more, and maybe this film does deserve more. But it's just such
transparent nonsense. You hit it right on the head. There are a million dynamo, female filmmakers out
there that have busted their ass and made fantastic art. And that's not enough. AV Club has to pick
the rarest, most boring, most jack myself off to show you that I'm a fucking artist and I get it
bullshit fucking pick. Oh, give me a break, man. Give me a fucking break. It's tough. And like,
you know, Raging Bull fell off the list. Lawrence of Arabia fell off the list of classics.
But it's an interesting, like I'll just do the top 10 real quick. Number two, Vertigo. Vertigo's
always up at the top. Citizen Kane 3. Number four, Tokyo Story, which is great. Five in the mood for
love, which is great. Six, 2001. Seven Boat Reveil, which is a movie I love, but I'm surprised to see
it that high. Eight Mulholland Drive, which is a movie I love, but that's crazy.
Nine man with a movie camera. So I guess they're kind of just, that's like the historic 1929
bullshit that I watched at film school and then 10 singing in the rain. Who votes on this?
This is a collection of film critics. And then also they publish. I'm going to get the magazine
because it seems interesting. They publish like 400 directors top 10 lists that they picked,
which I'd like to look at myself. But I think they film critics decide the sight and sound list and
they pull the results. There's a bunch of ties on the list. You know, it's a weird list.
Here's an interesting response to the article. Get out on there, which had people like, can you put
on a movie from three years ago and in the top 100 of all time? That kind of stuff.
Here's an interesting comment on the thread on the AV site. This guy says, I will say three things. I've
issued. Fair. Yes. I really wish lists like this would stop saying best of all time and change
it to most important or most influential. Great point. Great point. Maybe this, that's what they're,
you know, and on that note, I'm glad to see Citizen Kane slipping a little bit because again,
it is not the best film of all time. It may very well be the most important or influential,
but it's not the best. These are great points. Are you running your own comment?
Let's talk it away. So joderosa .com, I just, you know,
it's, you can look at the list. Look, if you watch these movies, you're going to see a lot of great
and interesting films. Don't get it going. But it's like, you know, to see something like that was just
kind of a bummer to me because even like my mom, let's say, we'll go, oh, I want to see the number
one movie. Like you're just furthering that divide between regular folks and like your little film
snob community. And why do that? Why not put as your number one a movie that's influential and important
and entertaining and accessible to the general audience? Because people won't finish this movie.
That doesn't score any points. You don't get points like that. You get points further dividing
everything you can possibly divide down to a fucking movie list at this point where it's just like,
yeah, it's, again, I don't care if you came to me and said to me, hey man,
this movie, 23, quad, do commerce with six commas in the title and 1080p,
THX 1138, whatever the fuck it's called. You came to me and you said very sincerely.
Like, hey, dude, that's my favorite movie. I'd be like, oh, cool. The great. You know, the filmmaker,
she didn't, you know, they deserved a lot more than they ever got. But okay, cool. Like, all right,
I want to, I want to learn about this. I want to hear about this. If you said, you know,
that movie should be on more lists. Cool. Yeah. You know, hey, that's great. That movie's on more
lists. But when you do it like this, I'm sorry. I'm not trying to undercut anybody because of
gender or anything like that. It's a transparent signal. It just is. It just fucking is.
It is. That's it. Like, you know, you can't tell me that, that
who did a, oh, for Christ sakes. You know, cat, a big low, where's where's she? She on the list?
No, who's one Oscars and made dynamic fucking picture after dynamic fucking picture?
It's, you know what I mean? Like, it's like, I have a fucking picture.
It just drives me fucking crazy. You know what I mean? Yeah. The obel code who's done tons of shit.
You know, like, like, for Christ sakes, Lena Dunham, for Christ sakes. I'm not a huge Lena
Dunham fan. But you wouldn't put one of her films on this list. Maybe, maybe tiny, maybe a tiny
furniture. Okay. That would have had people riding in the street. But I'm just saying, it's just
like, it's like, it's like, it's like, we're going to go as obscure as possible. So we can look like,
oh, like, we get it. You know, and it's like, okay. All right. You get it. But the rest of us don't
want to watch a woman watch, or a man watch dishes for three hours. All right, 21 minutes.
I can't, I yesterday, the make a point that the patriarchy is bad. I know that.
I'm going to now piss everybody off with my first review.
So as I, as I condemn this art house film, being caught as put as number one, I watched
Billingsley is in this movie. So I'm going to go with it for Christmases.
Starring Vince Vaughn and Dwight Yohkum, Dwight Yohkum and Reese Witherspoon, of course,
John Favreau. Terry Bradshaw, I want to say in there. No, but you do got a Sissy Spasek. You got
a Robert DuVale. Oh, wow. Okay. Mary Steen Burge, Christine Chenoworth. Uh -huh, Chenoweth.
Or Chenoweth. It was on in my hotel room. I watched it. It's a plenty serviceable Christmas movie.
It's got some, it's got some funny classic Vince Vaughn in it, like, you know, Vince Vaughn,
being Vince Vaughn. Favreau is really funny in it. He plays the UFC Meathead brother who physically
attacks Vince Vaughn every time he sees him. It's a weird gag, but it's a funny one.
Is the movie good? It's okay. Not great. But it's a fun little Christmas movie. It's a sweet movie.
Vince Vaughn almost puking when he sees the baby puke will always make me laugh. That was a big
part of the trailers. I don't really have much more to say. It's, it's, it's, it's an okay Christmas
movie. It's okay. I saw it theatrically. Remember nothing about it except that the cast was stacked
and they weren't making daddy laugh. Well, you put it up against anything being released now.
You're like, you know, it's a shining example of how, of how cinema should be made. But back then
it was, it was a dime a dozen. You were like, who cared? Another Vince Vaughn and Reese Witherspoon
movie. Here we go again. Yeah. I do. Yeah. I watched Booty Call to flip it up a little bit. I had
never seen the film or if I had seen it, I did not recall it. Starring Jamie Foxx and Tommy Davidson.
Vivica A. Foxx. And Tamala Jones, who I haven't seen since, but I'm sure she's a word. Yeah,
she's been in a bunch of stuff. But a very likable cast and unfortunately a pretty dumb movie,
but not terrible. I learned that Bill Cosby came out in a vocal opposition to Booty Call and
thought it was denigrating to black people, which is very ironic. But it's interesting too,
because the movie is promoting safe sex. It's like these really hot young people desperately want
to fuck, but they're all in agreement, not until we get a condom. Like, why is that a bad message
bill? I don't understand. Probably never saw the film. But yeah, it's all about the cast. It's like a
young, hungry Jamie Foxx. And everybody's really funny. Vivica Foxx is great in it. The jokes
are pretty stupid. There's a lot of scenes with like, you know, at this point, maybe at that point,
too, some real racist kind of 7 -11 worker caricatures. But they're funny. The guys get a lot of jokes
in, you know, but you know, not a great portrayal. And then you have a real rough scene from Getty
Wedenabe from 16 candles. You know, it was one of those kind of shocking things where you see that
just from 25 years ago, you know, we let a lot of stuff slide in movies. That wasn't great. But
all in all, a decent entertaining comedy. Another one in the Billingsley Vaughn family.
Watch this with my dad on Thanksgiving morning. Fred Claus. Oh, perfect movie to watch with your dad.
Again, is it a good movie? Not really. Is it a serviceable Christmas movie? Sure. But it's a perfect,
you watch it with your dad movie. It's Vince Vaughn is Santa Claus's brother,
Giamatti play Santa Claus. It's a very funny concept. Like, what if Santa Claus had a loser,
like sort of scam, scammy kind of brother that was the opposite of everything Santa Claus is.
And it's perfectly class. Cass was Vince Vaughn. Rachel Weiss, lovely.
Kathy Bates, charming. A waste, no, no, I'm getting this mixed up with elf now. I was going to say
Bob Newhart, that's elf. Is Kremholtz in this one? No, Kremholtz is in elf. No, which one is in?
What is Kremholtz? Santa Claus. Santa Claus. That's right. The guy is in the new show apparently.
Yeah. The guy from what's it called plays the main elf in this one. The guy from Best in Show.
John Michael Higgins. Yes. Yeah. So, again, not much to say here. These are the first
handful of Christmas movies that I will be watching and reviewing as we move through the month of
December. But, you know, I also saw that one theatrically, never again. I just didn't, I didn't like it.
I was really bummed out by Vince Vaughn. Like, he seemed to get, his movies got less funny each time
at the plate. It seemed like for like 10 years. And now I'm glad to see him back in action.
It's funny when the three secret service elves attack him and he's really mad and he's like
huffing his chest at the elves. There's moments like that in it that are really funny. But,
you know, it's Christmas movie, you know, sure. I saw woodlands dark and days bewitched. Great
story of Folkora. So, your set finally came in and you're finally watching it.
I said, Kim, did you watch this documentary? Yeah, it's awesome. It is. So, yeah, directed by
Keir Lodge and East 194 minutes. So, I'm complaining about length in one movie, but embracing it
in another. Why? Because this one is very, very entertaining. This is a history, as it says,
of Folkora in film. They dabble into like its history in terms of like oral tradition and how
stories get passed along culturally and that kind of stuff. It's a big part of it, the background of
it. But mostly it centers on films. They talk to a lot of great directors. It's not the usual
thing where they have, you know, all of a sudden some delist stand a comedian. It'll be on,
riffing on the stuff. It's a pretty serious scholarly affair. Everybody's got really interesting
insights. I watched it in two parts, which I think is the way to do it. It's divided into eight parts
itself. And you get the feeling that it was intended to be like almost like a class. And I
felt smart watching it. I felt like I learned a lot and it gave me a bunch of movies to seek out.
And then the set comes with a lot of these movies, 20 of these movies, which I am excited to watch.
And I own The Wicker Man, which they talk about at great length, but is not included in the set.
But I'm excited to go down this road. I don't know if I want to do a Folkora holiday season,
but I want to watch a lot of these films. I love the documentary. Check it out.
I still be on a shredder. I don't know. I think it is.
It's a great doc. It's a great way to start that box that it's just, it's just great.
All right. Last for me.
Christ, I guess I'll do another, I guess it's, I don't have a third Christmas one, unfortunately.
I feel bad that I don't. But I will say I watched something family oriented.
Martin Scorsese Italian American, which I, you know, it's, I was scrolling through HBO.
You know what? I'm not going to do this one now. I'm going to save that because I also
watched the Nora Efron doc and I want to do those together. But this one fits into comedies.
Analyze this. I watched it, Pat, based on the fact that you said you had just watched it.
Yes. Loved it.
Let's just great. Yeah.
Great movie. I just love it. It makes me laugh. Simple, approachable, enjoyable.
You know, Crystal is top of his game, De Niro's top of his game.
The Pudgy Face Gangster, whoever plays that guy, does steal the show.
Kudro at her best playing like the, like, when Kudro is playing tense, Kudro,
where she's constantly blinking because she's so tense, you better watch that come back at that.
That's Kudro at her best. Oh, yeah, I got to get into that. I've been, I've been throwing
on Mad about you at dinner time and she plays like the Ditsy waitress and she's, it's very similar
because she's, she's been, sub in the comeback, sub in the, all the best shows ever.
All right. I like to laugh track during dinner. Just, it's comforting. I hear, I hear.
It's, you know, it's a great, it's a great, and again, one you can watch with your, with your folks
and without too much awkwardness, I'd say, around the holidays. A lot of fucks.
But, but not, you know, not anything to, you know, even the one sex scene is pretty,
is pretty tame. So, maybe for your family, would you feel awkward watching analyze this with your mom?
Not with my mom. My dad, I would leave the room for that, for that brief fuck saying with
the narrow and that woman. Go crank one out, come back. No, just when anybody kisses, and since I was
little, if anybody kisses in a movie, I just would leave the room.
In, you know, in a movie, you mean, not in, oh yeah, yeah, we watched tons of movies and any time
that would happen, I would just leave until like the sexy music would end. Now, I asked you this,
when you talked about it last time, and I don't remember what you said, did this, wait, who wrote
this again? I can't remember it to save my god damn life. You've told me what? The analyze this,
who wrote the story again? The series. Kenneth Lonergan. Kenneth Lonergan. You can count on
me and Manchester by the sea. Did he also write the analyze that story? Or no? Well, he gets credit
because he came up with the characters in the original basis. So, I doubt he had worked on the movie,
but I don't know. I always thought there should have been a third one called analyze me where
Danero, where Billy Crystal needs counseling from the mob guy through some situation.
Okay. Never have never. I mean, I, you mean like a therapy from Danero? Not so much therapy,
like like like street smarts therapy, like like almost like a hitch style movie, where it's like,
he now has to be coached by Danero because he's navigating some life situation where he needs street
smarts and he knows how to, you know, maybe it's a business thing that he's going, I don't know
what it would be, but you're going to say analyze the other, isn't it this bad or the other?
No. Well, yeah, but I mean with the hell would analyze the other big. I'm trying to keep it a
muddy murky. Yeah, comes in record scratch question mark. Isn't triplets now Tracy Morgan,
it's not even any Murphy anymore or is it like, or Tracy Morgan's also in it now? Yeah, it's
Tracy Morgan as the other one. Yeah, it's not anywhere for anyone. I believe that's correct. Yes,
but I thought that might have been directed by Ivan Reitman who is dead. So, I don't know what,
where that project is that currently? Yeah, it's Tracy Morgan now. It seems like a horrible idea.
Let's just be real, but Eddie just, man, Eddie just does what Eddie do. He just drops out of shit,
man. Yeah. I remember, remember like two years ago when he was like, I'm going to do a, I signed a
$70 million deal with Netflix to do a special. He just never did it.
End of tour was supposed to be imminent. When over to Amazon Prime did
Jesus Christ. Let's get to the movie at hand because my third pick I'm going to make
Jeannie Eiligman of of 44 Ducex Avenue Street, colon, comma, apparatus, place. I
and Joe watched on HBO Max, a Christmas story Christmas. Yes, this is
the sequel set in the 70s to the beloved Christmas classic. Ralfy is now about 50 years old, probably
playing a little younger. He is married to Aaron Hayes, the actress from, you know, Kevin
can fuck himself and many, many sitcoms. No, well, Kevin, Kevin, you did that too, though. Wait,
she's in both. Oh, well, that show was based on her experience. So they think they brought her
into that show. Yes. Because that show was based on her getting fired off that show because Kevin
James hated her. It was. Yeah, I didn't know that. I thought it was just called Kevin can fuck
himself. Is she the main person in Kevin can fuck himself? Yeah, well, no, no, no. But the lady
from Shits Creek is basically playing her as how I took it. Oh, she like created it or something.
No, but I think she guessed start on it. And it's just sort of based on her experience without
paying her, really, which is probably why they brought her into the fold. And I don't even,
I'm not even confirmed she was on that show. But yeah, this, this, this really diluted as you told
I'm looking it up. I'm looking it up. You don't need to.
Aaron Hayes, but she was on Kevin can wait. Yeah. And her, they did not bring her into
apparently. Yeah, Kevin can fuck himself. I'm going to get a title that always bothered me. I'm
such a Kevin James. I just got a song about Kevin James. She was on it. Okay. That was right. She was
on it. Um, so yeah, it's basically based on her experience. Anyway, that's a little side D tour.
But um, and I did not see Kevin can fuck himself actually. Aaron Hayes was great. Yeah, I heard it was
interesting. Aaron Hayes plays, uh, his wife, he has two little kids who are kind of zeroes really in
the, in the context of the movie. The plot of the film is at the very beginning, the sort of
inciting incident is that Ralphie's father, the old man from the original Christmas story has died.
Uh, so he gets the call and he has to go back home. His mother is now played by Julie Haggerty
from Airplane and what about Bob? Mm hmm. Who is great, but a very different style of performer from
Melinda Dylan, who has retired from acting, but she played the mom in the original. Yes.
Uh, he gets home. Yeah. Then, or go ahead. I'm sorry. No, go ahead. Go ahead. That's it.
Basically. I mean, he's home and then high jinks ensue. He's got to write a, uh,
obituary for his father. He struggles with that. He goes home for Christmas or for the funeral.
It's also happens to be Christmas. He's already going home. His mom says, we're not going to be bogged
down with sadness. We're going to have the best Christmas ever. That's what your father would have
wanted. And the movie goes from there. The only mention again of the dad's death, uh,
is like Pat just said, he's tasked with, as a struggling writer, having to write an obituary for his
father, which he struggles with writing for the entire movie, because he can't put it into words.
How great his father was. Um, you know, I, my, my first issue with this was that
you got a guy going home for his dad funeral and then they don't ever have the funeral.
And you're going, well, Christ almighty half a week just went by where the hell is this body?
Like they're, they don't even mention it. Right. Which is odd. I actually thought
that the funeral gave them an opportunity to do this fantastic comedic Christmas set piece
in the finale of the film, but they don't go back to it. They just ignore it. Um,
this movie does that a lot. Like it is a comedy through and through 100%. Um, but
it does bring in a lot of, uh, issues that a parent might face when dealing with Christmas and
putting a Christmas together for their children, as in the death in the family. Uh, they don't have,
their presence gets stolen. They don't have money to buy new presents for the kids. Um,
uh, the existence of Santa Claus, all these things are just part of it. Like, and it's clear
that the movie is supposed to be more along the lines of the first ones about the wonder of it being
a kid at Christmas and this new one is about the, I guess the challenge of being a parent at Christmas.
Which is interesting, but that therein lies the problem. There's nothing fun or really wondrous about
that. It's all very technical. It's all very, uh, almost clinical in a way. Like, you know,
it like in, and it feels a little paint by numbers. It feels like they're just kind of ticking the boxes.
The dad spends a lot of time at the bar because it gets tense at home. So he goes and drinks and his old
buddies from home are there. Uh, yeah, they bring back all the old, uh, friends from the original Christmas
story and pretty much all the old bullies and everybody gets, you know, a few scenes, but it's kind of like,
I don't think anybody was coming to this dying to see the, how everyone turned out in the original
Christmas story. Maybe I'm wrong, but we spend a lot of time with these guys who were child actors who
haven't been in anything else. So they're not, while they're perfectly likable people, they're not
exactly compelling performers to be carrying a story in my opinion. I had no, I, I liked that they
brought everybody back. I didn't like that they gave them all nothing to do. I don't understand why
in every, and I'm not trying to pick on this movie. I like, I've met and spent time with Peter
Billings Lee and he's always been very cool. I like him quite a bit and I like Wild West picture show
and I'm a big fan of all the stuff. Not, not everything they do, but I'm a fan of what they do.
I'm like, like rooting for this. I was excited for this. And I just don't understand why when they
make these legacy sequels, they don't give these characters anything to do. Like it's like here are his
two best friends from childhood. And all they do is is Schwartz owns the bar and Flick is a guy that
drinks there all the time that can't pay his tab. And then they add all these new zany bar
characters that you don't need and you don't want and you don't care about everything. Yeah. And it's
like give them something to do like make them instrumental as a part of this story. They actually
do make Farkis, Scott Farkis when he comes back sort of important in that he plays a cop in the
climax of the movie, the big climax is Ralphie needs to get a star for the top of the tree because the
star gets broken and he says at the beginning in this neighborhood, if you don't have a star on
the top of your tree, you're, you know, you're done. That's not Christmas. So he breaks into Schwartz's
bar. And what am I in there? It was like, why not grab a paper plate and cut it into a star? I
didn't get the urgency to break into a bar at that point. Why not call Schwartz? Yeah. Hey,
buddy. I'm gonna be heading over to your bar. Yeah. It's like so crazy. It's like, you know, like
we're just don't have them have them break in somewhere. But have it be have it be the display at
the, at the, they make such a big deal of the window display at this department store in both
movies. Have him break that. Yeah. But instead they just go now, he'll break into his buddy's bar.
It doesn't really make sense. And then he won't get in trouble. And then it's just it's easy fix.
And anyway, Scott from the writer of Grand Torino, which I found very interesting, not exactly
I guess it had comedic moments, but a strange departure for him. And the director of
Santa's Kurt Russell's badass gold Christmas. Yeah. I had it right, Joe.
You know, Scott Farkis, it's like he plays the cop that catches Ralphie. And like that provides
a bit of tension. Like, oh, shit. Now he's a cop. And now and where he hates Ralphie probably
from when they were kids. And he's gonna ruin Christmas by putting Ralphie and jail. And then
Scott actually does the right thing and says, like, hey, man, I was actually a jerk when we were
kids. Sorry about that. Things can change. I'm one of the good guys now, whatever. And
and that's the only really like functional cameo in it. Like that has a, that gives you a plot
point of some kind or or a device, something. But, um,
you know, they scuts kids are the new bullies. They don't call attention to that or they don't reveal
that until the third act. But it's very obvious. As soon as you see them, that that's going to be
the big reveal. The bullies have no real place in it. They just drive a snowmobile onto Ralphie's mom's
property and screw with his kids. Yeah. And that's not like a interesting or really relatable bully
thing. Like, you know, like, like, sure, like when I was growing up, there was like bullies in my
neighbor that wrote dirt bikes, but it's like, but you, the thing is, if you don't have to encounter
the bullies, it's not that scary. Having them come onto your lawn when you could just call the cops
on them because it's the 70s. Right. And that's a pretty fixed, by the way, it's the 70s,
you could hit one of them. Yeah. You could hit a guy's kid in the 70s and it was kind of like, okay.
Like, well, that's, that's the big difference is the original movie has like 100 moments,
one a minute that reminds you of your childhood, something recognizable. You're like, oh, that's
exactly like something that happened to me or friend of mine or whatever. That's the whole movie.
And this movie is trying to create those moments out of thin air, but they're not a person's,
like, lived in treasured memories. They feel like just fabricated made up Hollywood shit.
So nothing's really interesting and nothing connects. Like, so what Joe's saying about these bullies,
doesn't, it doesn't, no one can relate to it. It's not like anybody's like, oh, yeah, I remember when
a bully drove a snowblower onto my lawn because it doesn't happen. Well, yeah. And you're also too,
I think, I think what you start to see is the budget on screen. You're like, yeah, how do we get
the bullies onto their property? Oh, they'll drive a snowmobile around the neighborhood.
Forget that this could logically be rectified in 10 seconds and provide zero tension.
That's how we'll do it. The beauty of the bullies in the first movie is they have to encounter them
because they have to walk to school. They have no choice. It's a great problem. It's a great problem
for these kids to have in the movie. They do the fantasy sequences in this one. I got a few
laughs here and there out of it, but they're just not Bob Clark, just as such a great job as a director
in the original. And when he tackles those sequences, they feel like little vignettes and they don't
feel like that in this. They just feel like everybody puts a costume on for three minutes and acts out a
weird sketch. Yeah. Yeah. It felt like something that was made quickly, cheaply.
And I'll say in the home stretch that I had a really rough first half hour, in the home stretch,
a few moments kind of hit. You get a little of the old holiday magic here and there, but for the
most part, it feels like you're watching just any generic hallmark movie. It doesn't feel like
you're watching something in the vein of Christmas story to me. There was enough connective
tissue there for me that it felt like a sequel. It just didn't feel like a great sequel. It's got
really good reviews. So I was like, maybe I'm just expecting too much. Maybe I'm missing something.
I don't know. It just, but I will say this, I got Terry at the beginning when they talked about the
dad dying. That was very sad to me. And at the end, the big resolve, the whole thing is that
Ralphie writes a story about his dad, unbeknownst to him, his wife submits the story to the paper.
The paper prints the story. The neighborhood all sees the story and then they come to Ralphie's
mom's house on Christmas day to pay tribute to his father. And the end of the movie is they ask
Ralphie to read the story to everybody and he starts reading it and you realize as he's reading it,
oh, this is the original Jean Shepherd story that the first movie was actually based on.
And as he's reading it, it dissolves from Ralphie's voice into Jean Shepherd's voice when he actually
read it. And it's a clip from the radio show when he read it on the air on air. And it shows a
flashback of footage of the first movie. And it's a really beautiful little ending to the whole thing.
So like, I guess somewhere in some way, it gives you closure with the character or characters of
the first movie. And it's nice to know where they landed. You know, we could argue that it's just
fan fiction because Jean Shepherd is dead. And it's I don't think it's really based on anything.
I mean, maybe well, it says at the end, it is based on the book in God we trust all others pay cash,
which is what the first one's based on. So, so maybe there's elements from that book that are in
here that I'm not aware of. But maybe, yeah, I don't know. You know, so I mean, look, it's,
it's it's probably more of a true sequel than any of the Lucasfilm stuff is at this point. You know,
so, um, but that's the way of these legacy things. They're, they're sort of glorified fan fiction,
whether this one is or not or to what extent it is or not. I don't know. But yeah, it didn't hit me on
any sort of emotional or or comedic level. But I feel like it's hard was in the right place. Yeah,
disaster. It just didn't click for me really. Yeah, hog is sadly down for me. But I'm not mad at it.
I just was kind of like, man, that's a shame. I wish I wanted more.
Same. Agreed. Folks, we are going to be in St. Petersburg, Florida, which I'm told is near Tampa,
hopefully near Tampa, because that's where I'm flying into. Yeah, I'm flying. It is very close to
Tampa. We are there Thursday, December 8th at Coastal Creative. Get tickets on Joe's website.
I'm on the Patrick Wall should Twitter, Instagram.
Joe to Rosa info .com for tickets to we'll see you at Hell live in St. Petersburg. The great Mike
Calta morning radio's Mike Calta of that region. And one of one of the best guys I know in
comedy is as our guest. He's coming in as a special guest for the show. It's going to be a lot of fun.
We're going to fun with Mike. Uh, we may or may not announce whatever movie we're doing
beforehand. I know on this version of the show, we're going to do Silent Night Deadly Night 4
as one of our holiday picks. Uh, yeah, Florida. I don't know what we'll do. We'll have to figure it out.
But anyway, it'll probably be something Christmasy. Um, uh, Joe again,
Joe to Rosa info .com for ticks to that. And then on the ninth and 10th, the next two consecutive
nights, I'll be doing my new show. I never promised to a Rose Garden. Come out to that if you can,
too. Uh, and I'm doing that all over the place. Go to Joe to Rosa info .com for tickets and info to
upcoming shows. I'm coming to Austin doing the crane theater in New York. Uh, governors on Long Island,
New York got a bunch of Midwestern dates coming up and, uh, down south in Lafayette, New Orleans dates
are coming up to. So I hope to see you out there. Uh, come to Joey Roses if you can.
Joey Roses NYC .com, seven days a week, open every morning at 11 .30 a .m. We'll see you next time.
And we'll see you in hell.