I'll see you in hell.
Folks, it's, we'll see you in hell, a very special edition today.
Why do I say special edition? Because we'll be discussing a film called The Northman.
Did I have a feeling some fireworks might fly over?
I just have a feeling.
Well, they certainly flew on screen in the film The Northman.
Joe, you're already sort of freezing.
Which is not, I can hear you fine, but I'm concerned about the future of this record.
The integrity of this record.
Now you're basically fine, but you were a little patchy, choppy.
Alright, well, as long as it sounds fine, we can keep going.
My internet is fine. Nothing's turned on.
You look right. We both look great.
It's Monday morning. You were out getting a.
COVID test.
Yeah, it's, uh, we have had.
You get an email at work. It's, it's insane down down here in Atlanta.
You go into any store, anywhere, any grocery, anything.
No one, no one is wearing a mask. Nobody.
And fine.
But then at work, everyone has to be a militant about masks because TV is more important than every other industry.
And we get tested on the way in where they put the gun to your temple that's how I start every morning.
Then you walk in and do the nose penetrates where they jam it into your bin to both nostrils.
And now we got three emails last week, positive, positive case memos.
And when those go out, everyone has to take a break for a week.
So currently we're on at least a week off of work.
And yet I have to go up each morning and get a COVID test.
And this morning I tried to ask somebody what the point of this is.
Why not get a COVID test the day before you come back to work?
Why am I doing it every day for no reason?
And the nurses didn't have an answer.
It's absurd at this point.
I've said my alarm on a rare day off work.
And in the rain, I'm driving up to get a COVID test that I'm going to have to get tomorrow.
And first, if I wanted to be a real bitch, I could make somebody come to my home to do it because I'm a producer.
But that I would immediately be branded a premodana, you know, and rightfully so.
No, I'm saying you can't do a self -administered.
You can't, I mean, these tests are, you know, they sound like like orbit's gum at the register anymore.
It's like, why can't, isn't that the point of you asked if you could sneak in a paid advertisement for orbit's gum?
And I told you no.
And yet, here we are.
Now, you know, it's, it is what it is.
I just follow blindly, whatever people say, it's fine.
And that's the problem with this scam.
Wherever you need me to go, you know, I just, at this point, I almost, I almost prefer being told where to go and what to do so I can just not have to think.
Well, Pat, and that brings me to the staple in this country.
I gotta tell you, if you're better for worse, Walsh, I know you're not a fan of the guy.
In particular, talking about God, God, yeah, the vengeful God who has wrecked my life.
I just need to say this out loud.
I've been watching Bill Marr.
I just agree with him 100 % on almost everything I hear him say.
I finally found somebody out there that I'm like, I agree with what you're saying.
Let me ask you this.
Are you laughing?
No, I don't find, I don't find that you're still okay. You're still okay.
Yeah, I just agree.
He's a rare voice of somebody who's between these two poles, these two extreme poles, and that's refreshing.
I think the comedy is, you know, expired by about 30 years.
It's that, you know, it's newsroom comedy.
It's like they do it on like like my buddy Greg Gutfeld, you know, he has his own show on Fox and people love the show.
But it's that style of, I'm not shitting on Greg or anything, but there's a style, there's like a news show style of comedy monologue.
That's, that's it. Mar does it.
John Stewart does it.
But here's the thing.
As annoying as I find a modern day, John Stewart, as annoying as I often find John Oliver, even while watching his show every week, there are jokes.
There are recognizable punchlines, jokes, laughs.
There's an attempt to stay relevant both in terms of what they're talking about and the humor, you know, Mar.
I was talking about Mar at a wedding a couple of weeks back with some guy and he had a great point.
He was like, well, you know, Mar came up at a time where there were three channels.
If you were on one of those three channels, you were immediately famous and you can be famous until the day you die. And it's basically true.
Bill Mar comes along now.
He would, he would be a zero. He'd never be on television.
Well, he'd get, he'd be a podcaster.
He'd be a podcaster right or he'd have an MSNBC show or whatever it is.
My friends and I had a blast for a long time doing group chats, making fun of real time.
But then we all were just like, this isn't funny anymore.
We couldn't get to the end of the episode. His guests are people he finds on the street, seemingly.
There he has no, there's no star power on the show.
It's like, let's bring on our first guest.
It's Bill Kleinhauser and he comes out. He talks for 20 minutes.
He looks terrible.
He's a patty there for build, he's a paper tiger for build to beat, usually.
But now he has on people who agree with him most of the time. It's an echo chamber.
It's a new, it's a news show. It's, it's, it's, it's an entertainment news show. That's, that's, that's a format now.
You know, it's the same, you know, who else used to do it like that was.
You know, John Fugel saying did it.
Kurt, the guy that was on ESPN.
And then became a news guy. They got the glasses.
That got in trouble because he said he talked about evil ESPN was when he left or whatever.
Okay.
He was friends with Craig Kilborn and, and, but he went into news and Kilborn didn't put.
Anyway, it's a style of, and the problem is is with the, if you're looking at it for strictly comedy, it's, first of all, that's not, it's not there to service that.
I don't think, but he does a comedic monologue and comedic sketches.
Well, there's new rules.
No, no, no, new rules that new rules is exactly what I'm talking about though.
That's the problem. It's not a problem. It's just the style.
It's like, if the whole thing is, is that you have to make points.
Uh -huh.
You're in a different, forget it.
You're looking for, you're looking for, for Claptor as Tina Fey calls it, where you're, you're clapping instead of laughing.
John Oliver will,
John Oliver's still desperately wants the audience to like him, which is why he is screaming at the top of his lungs.
Yeah.
He obviously, he did a more subtle performance as the, uh, bird in the lion, the live action lion king.
You know, like, he gets on there every week and he's like,
whoo, whoo, how much?
It's like every week I start by turning the volume way, way down.
There's too much.
I don't know how you watch it.
I can't.
I don't know why I watch it.
I don't know why I watch anything.
I don't like anything.
Uh -huh.
As much as I agree with Mars perspective, I still couldn't watch the whole show.
I just, you know, I, I, I agree with what, I agree with his premise of, of every new rule thing.
I, um, I was like, yeah, that makes a lot of sense.
Uh -huh.
No rule vegans.
You have to start eating meat.
You're like, what?
Everything's like that.
Well, that makes me sound like an asshole now.
I don't know.
The man, I should have you tried watching, uh, hashtag adulting the latest stamp up special.
I got about two minutes into it.
I couldn't do it.
Whoo.
It's, it's, it's an hour of that though.
It's an hour of, I have points to make smirking.
Yeah.
You know, I look, some of the lines are very clever.
You know, like some, I'm like, oh, that's a very good one.
But I mean, look, I can't, I also can't completely not get because George Carlin is my idol.
And Carlin did that in his own way too, you know?
So, you know, when Carlin's making a point about something, you know, it's there,
there aren't a lot of joky jokes in there.
But that's fine.
You know, like it, it's a style.
He's also, I mean, I watched a lot of crowd on the last week because I had never really seen his specials.
My dad loved him, but also wouldn't let me watch him.
Uh, but anything my dad loved, I didn't like.
And I thought I'd watch a few of his specials before.
Or the new documentary.
And he's very funny throughout Carlin.
And, but I mean, he's also making points that seem ahead of the time when you watch them now.
Yours, you know, Mars usually making points.
Like his movie references, like, like, they go, they predate GI Jane, you know, like,
you always know what, what was on showtime.
Um, uh, our stars as Bill Maher was going to bed the night before because his movie references are all from like 1984.
He's got the gray in the front, the brown hair in the back.
He's just a hot duck.
He's got that podcast now where he talks to stars while he's high.
And he still thinks getting high is really shocking, which is really.
Wait, is that like, that's his podcast as he gets high?
Yeah, it's called the, um, it's got a really bad name.
It's called like the shakedown or something like that, isn't it?
It's, it's worse than that.
Um, we're rumors.
It's worse than that.
It is called club random.
Oh.
I go on it in love with that.
And that says I make fun of it here.
Yeah.
Oh, no, you, you, you, of course, I'd go on it as well.
And I'd be able to hold my smoke better than fucking Bill.
Jesus Christ.
He's been talking for 40 years about how much he loves.
We just opened a pot store in West Hollywood with Woody Harrelson.
And you see him on there, he takes a hit of a joint and he's like,
girls are sexy.
I wonder if I align with Woody Harrel's in politically.
You probably do from what I've heard.
Well, on curb they made him look like insane,
but I know that was for comedy sake,
but I also didn't know how much of it was based in truth.
He's pretty extreme with all the hemp stuff and all that from things.
I've actually have several friends who have spent a large amount of time
with Woody Harrel's and oddly enough.
And across the board, everyone likes him.
You know, he's a man who's always stoned, which is usually good.
I got my classic kingpin story that it'll serve me till the day I die.
I want to.
There we are.
I wish I liked weed.
Seems so good to just be high all the time.
You know, you know, I love it, but it does as my therapist always said.
It.
It'll hit an end point for you.
And it's hit that end point for me.
It doesn't.
Doesn't save my life like it did for many years.
It just kind of.
Nums things a little bit, which is helpful.
Don't get me wrong.
I have to before getting on this podcast and trying to be entertaining.
I literally do the full all that jazz and the bathroom mirror.
You know, like just cold water on the face and like.
Showtime.
You know, wipe away tears.
No, that's.
That's.
That's every morning, man.
Just just.
And not even from hangover just just the horror of life.
Yeah, no, I've stopped drinking.
It was taking me to two darker plays.
Doesn't mean I.
I wouldn't have a drink of someone handed to me right now, but.
I pretty much stopped.
And I still wake up feeling like groggy and.
It's just a.
It's a time.
You know, it's a time.
Yeah.
Should we go to the movie corner?
I mean, what's happening in the world?
Well, I was going to give an update on the amber herd.
Oh, thank you.
Uh, so now several celebrities are coming out publicly to defend Johnny Depp.
Amber herds assistant or other people now from Amber herds past have come out and said.
There's one girl came out and goes.
No, Amber.
You threw me down the stairs.
He was just there.
Uh, okay.
Interesting.
She was threatened with perjury the other day.
Uh,
And I don't know.
I just find it all fascinating.
I look.
I get it.
Men have done awful things since the beginning of the movie.
I don't know, I don't know.
I don't know what time I'm not saying we haven't.
I'm not going to go on some.
You know,
Uh,
We need justice for the guy's thing.
Um,
Because it's sort of like when I see, you know, my friend Dante.
Who is black.
He said something very poignant to me once and it really stuck with me.
Like when I said to him a thing about like, you know,
Like I think it's fucked up.
I think racism in any form is fucked up and.
You know, like I don't think it's cool that everybody's just bashing white guys now.
So like loosely.
And he said,
That's nothing new.
It's just happening to white people for the first time.
So now everybody thinks it's like this new thing.
So.
That resonated with me and I was like, you know what?
That kind of took me off the, like when I see.
A white guy on Instagram being like this racism needs to stop.
It's like.
Well, where were you yelling that for other people that were being persecuted?
It just seems sort of self serving.
So in that same vein, I'm not going to go on some.
You know, the poor men thing because I know men have done awful things forever.
I know plenty of men have been abusers.
But with that said.
With everything that's happened in this trial,
the people that are still somehow spinning Amber herd into, you know,
a justice for women thing.
It's just nuts to me at this point.
It's, it's crazy.
I see people on Twitter being like, OK, so maybe she did lie.
But what about all the women that didn't?
And it's like, guys.
You don't have to like Johnny Depp.
You don't have to say poor Johnny Depp.
You don't have to say poor guys.
What you should say though is is this woman is hurting the cause.
She's making a fucking mockery out of it.
Another woman came out and said, Amber, her stole my abuse story and made it her own.
And like, like one of the stories of abuse she's telling is belongs to another woman that she knew.
So like, it's bad.
It's just a bad thing for.
There's literally a lot going on there.
I haven't followed it much aside from the big headlines.
It all seems sort of gross if there is actual abuse on the line.
And it seems to me like both of them were abusive in various ways over the course of this relationship.
It sounds like a relationship tainted by heavy, heavy drug and alcohol use.
Seems like both narrators might not be totally reliable.
Um, you know, I think I think it's a hundred percent of toxic relationship.
And I think it was absolutely emotionally abusive in two directions.
But I think it's becoming apparent that the physical stuff she's claiming is not real.
And that she in fact might have been physically abusive to him, which is nuts.
Well, I think both are true, but it wasn't he proven as having hit her at at least one occasion or am I crazy?
I don't think so. I think it's all.
I think they're gold. I think his defense is gold.
Now, maybe I'm mistaken, but as far as I can tell, his defense is gold is to say he never was physically abusive to her.
And I got to tell you, they're looking pretty fucking good at this point.
I mean, it is bad.
And then if you watch the footage of her on the stand, she sounds like some.
I watched a thing where a female.
A female.
I don't know what the term is.
I want to say pathologist or something, but a doctor that is an expert in detecting lies and like inconsistencies and people like enduring interrogations and things like that.
A female doctor that does that.
I watched a clip of her on a very liberal, very liberal morning show that my friend Al Jackson is, is a panel host on.
And even on that, that woman was like, she's lying.
And like was going through the footage and being like, see that. That's the indicator of a liar. See how she's changing tenses. That's what liars do.
And even the panel of mostly women on the liberal talk show were like, wow, yeah, that sucks. That's, you know, I'm so my point is is like.
At this point looks as if she, the other thing they got her with was.
She said she was going to, I mean, this is just her being shitty, but.
She said she was going to donate her entire divorce settlement to charity because she didn't need it because she lives independently from Johnny Depp and it wasn't in any way a maneuver to get money out of him.
Right. And she kept it.
And on the stand, she kept saying, I did donate it. I did. And they were like, you didn't.
You pledged it and didn't donate it. And she was, it was pledged. I donated it. And they're like, you didn't donate it.
Right. You still have the money.
Like we called the stand, the people who were supposed to get the money, bringing like a hundred people.
Yeah, we don't have the money.
So my point is is I think it was absolutely a toxic relationship. I think he actually might be a shitty guy like, but I don't think he's a wife beer.
And, and I don't.
You know, I, I don't know, man, it's wild. It's just wild. So, so I just think it's hurting a cause that.
It should hurt.
You know, it's, it's, this is something we all need to be discussing and taking seriously. And the fact that this, unfortunately, at the hands of Johnny Depp has become a national spectacle, because he, I guess he was the one that said, like televised the trial.
But yeah, I got no allegiance to the man. Personally, I've always enjoyed him as an actor, but in, and he's not like a guy where I like.
Oh, I bet I'd love hanging out with him or something. I always thought he seemed very odd and, and especially his later Burton.
He started doing the cage thing. He became a parody of himself.
So, you know, I look at it as a passive bystander. I, I, when, when is this ending? Does it have any end date this drop?
Who knows?
Who the hell knows?
I mean, imagine what they're dropping money wise into these law defenses.
I don't even know like, I don't really understand how any of this works.
Yeah.
I don't understand how you're allowed to have TV cameras in a courtroom, but then like any other trial, I'm only allowed to see drawings.
Right.
And then how would they assemble a jury?
People who have never heard of Johnny Depp, what are you talking about?
I don't think it's a jury trial.
I think it's a, well, maybe I'm wrong.
No, maybe there's a jury because she looks over a lot.
Yeah.
Like to, to not her defense to somebody. Maybe she's looking at the jury. I don't know.
Anyway, it's just, it just becomes crazier and crazier.
But the bigger takeaway for me here is it's yet another thing that convinces me we're living in some sort of simulation because it is.
I mean, this thing is the cable guy. It's like, it's like something out of, it's like the trial out of the cable guy movie.
Yeah.
It's like, it's so.
It's so.
Like, it just, it's so fitting for these times in such a satirical way.
It's crazy.
Like, it's just nuts.
Like, I'm just like, how is this like when OJ happened and it's now in very infamous trial, obviously.
But when it happened, I guess there were people saying this sort of thing then too.
But I feel like when OJ happened, that was a first.
That was like, this is never.
And that was at least a murder involved.
Right.
Yeah. And also too, but there was this era that I wish there was a murder involved with the depth.
Well, that's the other weird thing too with, with the I stand with Amber things.
It's like, I sort of bit my act about this.
It's like, you know, it's like, what are you saying?
I swear to God, she better have been beaten.
She better have been beaten.
It's like, you're mad that she wasn't beaten.
What's your goal here?
What's your end game?
But I was going to say with OJ, I feel like there was an era of guys.
We've never really done anything like this with trial.
This might not be good.
Right.
But the era around this right now is not that the era on this is like,
part for the course and look how crazy it is.
And it's just so reflective of the culture and.
The insanity we're living in.
I mean, down, down to the fact that the two most beautiful people on earth look like utter dog shit, like the rest of us because of COVID and everything.
Every aspect of this is so directly reflective of the awfulness of our culture right now.
And the fact that it's that America is into this while everything is collapsing around.
Yeah, it's just, it's too perfect.
And I'm like, there's a kid in his living room right now.
And I'm inside of his Xbox.
What?
Oh, it's in my subconscious.
Yeah, yeah.
I was like, wait, where did you go there, Joe?
What the hell is wrong with you?
I hear you.
It's, um, I have not felt like I'm living in any sort of world I recognize for a while.
I feel not like myself every day when I wake up.
I go to bed, not feeling like myself.
And I keep thinking it will stop and it doesn't.
Not a good feeling.
I was at the movies yesterday.
And as I told Joe and then it's like I never do Twitter anymore, but I texted Joe.
Like there's some guy here having a full FaceTime speaker phone conversation mid movie while I'm watching today's movie, The Northman.
And so I threw it up there on Twitter.
It's, it's a massive viral hit.
And I thought I didn't care, but I was like, my, my dick's getting hard again.
Is this what I've been missing?
Is a tension from the public?
It's, it's, I was, I was thrilled that I don't really tweet anymore, but that I had this big tweet.
And I was disgusted that it still meant something to me that everyone was liking this tweet.
It's sick.
It's an addiction.
It's, uh, it's bad and it feeds all the wrong stuff.
And there you go.
It's, it's, it's, you know, it's saying it's recognizing the awfulness of the, of the bully table and the, and the cool kids table in the cafeteria.
And then as soon as they ask you to set with them, you're, you're floating, you know.
For sure.
I, I definitely had an unhealthy relationship with it when I was like big into Twitter for a while.
But then, you know, now it's like you wake up one day and you're, your minus a thousand followers with no explanation and it's like, all right.
You know, once, once Elon Musk buys it, you know, I think that'll probably be it.
I don't know what's going on there.
He bought it.
Well, he bought it, but he keeps saying, I don't know if I'll take it because now Tesla stocks have gone down by half or so.
Part of that is because the car's brought up every fucking day.
Who cares?
Why, why doesn't anybody even care that he's buying it?
Was he buying it from, from, from, from, from a Peace Corps nuns in the South Pacific for Christchurch?
He's buying it from another group of evil fucking whatever that, who gives a shit?
Well, they're like, he'll put Trump back yet.
Trump, Trump was the most entertaining Twitter of the last four years and hands down.
So that, that would be fun.
And I got news for you.
Elon Musk has his, has his bad qualities or controversial qualities, depending on where you stand.
He's tied to herd somehow.
But I'll tell you this.
At least the guys done some good shit with his money.
You know, I can't say that about a lot of these other corporate.
I can't say that about Apple.
I can't go.
Well, at least Apple did X, Y and Z.
They didn't, you know, who always gets a pass is fucking celebrities.
It's like, have you ever, and maybe he has, I don't fucking know.
But let's pick one at random, who's been in the news a lot lately.
Will Smith.
You ever heard of Will Smith donating a dollar to charity?
He has five new shows every week.
They produce Cobra Kai.
You know, they, they, Will Smith has never been to the set of Cobra Kai has no involvement.
But they get their name on these shows because there's celebrities and they run forever.
They don't donate money.
Conan, who is a hero of mine.
One of my top five influences of all time.
I love the man.
And to me, he's never made a misstep.
But him selling his podcast to Spotify for $150 million.
Part of me is like, it makes for him.
No, the other part is like, fuck him.
That's kind of gross, Conan, because you align yourself with all these causes.
It makes me sick.
How much of that money is going to charity?
It's actually going to be the subject of my first ever YouTube videos.
I'm going to launch a YouTube channel soon.
All right.
It's celebrities podcasting.
Fuck Conan.
Fuck Jason Bateman.
It's right.
They all these guys.
Rogan.
They all have one.
It's.
Rogan.
No, no, no, no, no.
Rogan doesn't.
Rogan gets a full pass.
And here's why.
Rogan built his podcast from the ground up when nobody gave a shit about Joe Rogan.
I'm not Seth.
Oh, oh, oh, yeah.
No, fuck Seth.
Oh, yes.
Okay.
Yes.
No, no, no, no.
I mean, look, I, I'm no fan of Joe Rogan.
The man you, the man when people are mad at him.
I'm like, look, he has, he has made an empire from just talking and having on people he finds interesting.
That is the dream of the podcaster.
What, what is your issue?
It's, it's people for some time.
He's not as smart as you want, but I bet people listen to this show.
It's like bad and Joe aren't as smart as I want.
You're only as smart as you are.
But if people want to hear what you got to say, you know, Joe Rogan started that podcast
when he had been ostracized for entertainment for 10.
Colleo Carlos Mencia.
Yes.
Being a thief.
Jordan was, was nowhere near the, in the spotlight when he started that thing.
And he built it up to be the biggest podcast all the time.
But these other guys.
And that's what pisses me off, man.
These other guys like Seth Rogan and Conan and whatever.
They come along.
And what they're doing right now is they're saying, oh, wait a minute.
There's money being made that I'm not getting a piece of.
Exactly.
Yes.
And they have, and as a podcaster with two shows that I'm very grateful to have that are successful in their own right.
And I'm very grateful for that.
I pay a lot of bills with my podcasts.
I'm very, very thankful for that.
I'm very lucky.
But the fact that either of my shows essentially has no hope of ever entering the top 10 in the comedy podcast in world.
Because it has now been locked down by 10 celebrities that couldn't fucking leave $2 on the table.
Yeah.
It just sickens me.
And it really disappoints me.
My language is being a bit harsh.
I shouldn't say fuck Conan and fuck this guy and fuck that guy.
But it really bothers me.
It disappoints me that these guys that have so much and have done so much.
And so many opportunities to do so many other things have to dip their toe into this too.
It drives me fucking crazy.
You know, I completely agree.
And then they had they have no.
They just hire a team to do it for them.
So it's like literally roll out of bed.
Talk for an hour.
You're done.
And, and they pay.
I guarantee they pay the people who do the legwork for them a pittance.
And it is gross.
And then they have each other on each other shows they can get good celebrity guests because they are celebrities.
And it's like when Twitter started or when I first joined Twitter 10 years ago, it was people.
Here's people you should follow and it would be Ellen DeGeneres, Kevin Hart, whatever.
And it's it's frustrating.
It's like, why not recommend people I might find funny or ask me what I'm interested in.
It's just you like celebrities.
And that's what Apple does with their podcasts is what everybody does.
It's like look here.
Here are the notable ones you'll want to check out.
It's never shining a spotlight on some underdog.
It's just here's the biggest name.
Here's fucking Reese Witherspoon's podcast or whatever else.
It's the television production that really drives me nuts.
Like it used to be.
You know, Mel, you know, Mel Brooks, okay.
He's a director.
And then he decides he wants to produce films.
He produces elephant man.
And he's like a hands -on craftsman and helping David Lynch kind of rain in his.
More surreal impulses in favor of a movie that everyone can see and enjoy.
And I don't know why I'm thinking of Mel Brooks, but.
That used to used to mean something.
And now that will Smith thing or Reese Witherspoon or whatever else.
I check deadline every day just to see how far out of the business I am.
And every day on deadline, it is celebrities selling show after show after show after show.
And they're not involved.
And you know they're not involved.
Reese Witherspoon does two shows.
She's a star of two shows.
These stars don't go on the pitches.
Another of a mother of three or whatever it is.
You know what I mean?
It's like you're not a mom.
Or a dad.
Unless you're a deadbeat.
Yeah.
And starring in two shows.
And then also grinding out.
Pitches.
You're just not.
You're not on the pitch.
You know, look from my experience working with stars.
I did a show with the leaky.
He was very involved.
You know, I, I'm not saying it can't happen.
But generally the most a star will do is pop into the zoom.
Say hello at the start of the pitch and leave.
And generally that doesn't even happen.
Leaky.
But that's sharing in the profits of these shows.
The leaky hands on to the point that I did during our big celebration party.
I had to leave four times.
Change.
Try out new costumes.
Yeah.
Because he was sending.
And he was like laughing when I got back.
Because I was like.
Mother fucker, man.
I'm trying to enjoy the party.
They keep making me go back and change my costume.
And he was like, sorry, dude.
That's my fault.
I've been sending them notes on what I want.
But it's like, how hands on is that?
You got a guy that's making a million an episode on a sitcom.
And he's sitting there.
Correct.
It do it a bar.
Yeah.
During a party texting notes about a third string characters.
Costume.
Yes.
Fourth string.
But yeah.
Oh boy.
No.
It's.
It's really something.
You know, because they.
It's like.
I don't know.
Let's.
Let's pick on Reese Witherspoon.
Because she's in hot water now for telling moms everywhere to buy NFTs the week before they crashed.
So she's responsible for lots of moms losing their family a lot of money and hasn't spoken out on it.
But she's got to be an NFT.
She's got to be in this.
She's got to be in that.
Her producing these shows.
She has a team that is paid who finds material, homes material, shapes material with the rider.
But who is getting.
50 % minimum of the money.
Maybe 90 % Reese Witherspoon.
Why do these shows sell?
Because they're like, oh, well, Reese Witherspoon is attached.
Has that ever mattered to anyone?
If a TV show is coming on and they go, it's produced by Reese Witherspoon.
By the way, you never.
You never even see it.
It's.
You don't see it.
It's so buried in the credits.
Yeah.
And you're.
When you're busy.
You know, getting your first slice of pizza prepared or cutting whatever food is in front of you or.
Right.
Drink.
Nobody ever sees the celebrity name in the credits.
It's not like it pops up at the head as a heading and overseen three or something.
You don't even know.
No.
I couldn't tell you who produces any of the shows I enjoy.
It just bothers me, man.
You know, and it was bad enough when these celebrities were all sucking up every commercial endorsement they could and like, look, I can't control that.
It's not my fault of AT &T or it's not I have.
I have no control over the fact that AT &T wants to go after Mark Wahlberg, the highest paid movie star in the world.
To.
To hack their product because they're willing to pay that money.
And their dead set on a celebrity.
And that's what they're going to do.
That's a corporate decision.
I think it sucks that celebrities are so willing to do it, because those gigs used to go to somebody.
for instance, like Flow, you know, who's made a career out of being the insurance lady,
or the AT &T girl. Why couldn't they cast Flow's family? Why did Flow have to play all the
parts? That's my next question. So now Flow has become the Mark Walper. So put that door behind her.
But this is corporate American. You know, none of us have any control over that.
What bothers me is now, like I said, the celebs have now stepped into the, this is exactly what
happened with Indy cinema when there was the Indy cinema boom in the 90s. And it was truly
artists making their art for hundreds of thousands of dollars if you were lucky.
You had guys out there like Kevin Smith doing movies for 10 grand or whatever it was.
And then now if you ask a hundred teenagers what Indy film is there, they would all say a 24.
Yeah. And that's just as becoming as big a studio as Warner Brothers.
The studio's vacuumed up every small thing and it just became another corporate thing. And now,
you know, it's just this is this is this is like when fucking John Mayer
would drop in at the comedy seller to do time and everybody and all the comedians that are like
sweating it out for their midnight spots have to now wait an hour in their job as harder
because this guy has to drop in. I'm just so tired of it, man. Don't you fucking pigs ever get
enough to eat Jesus Christ almighty. Stole a tweet of mine too. Right right from my mouth.
Oh, oh, I thought you were saying you tweeted don't you pigs ever get in the
way. Yeah, I was like, no, it's not my fault. It's all a tweet verbatim of mine.
Anyway, all right, let's go there. But I wanted to ask though have you seen the trailer
for this new movie with James McAvoy where the trailer is him driving. And then at some point,
he gets out of the car and is like, no. And they go, they keep putting up words on the screen
telling you what's going on. Because I'm like, what is this movie even about? What's happening?
The trailers are so boring. And then they go, the first movie in history where the star will be
figuring out the plot at the same time as the audience. Is it a comedy? No, no, although that was
that Will Arnett show. And that was the same thing. But what a coincidence. These two things come
out at the same time. It's apparently a heavily plotted mystery and he's playing like a cop and he's
getting clues as we do. That's what our next thing was except it was comedy. I know, I know.
But the presentation of this is that this is the next boyhood. That this is a transitional shift in
cinema. Yeah, sure, it's going to boom. It's going to be a big boom. Let's get to the movie corn.
I'm going to stop as I fill my coffee, please. And then when you go, I'll fill my coffee
because I've been needing a refill my damn self. I'd like to start this week as my letterbox slowly
opens with let's start with the George Crawlin doc because why not? I watched four specials of George
Crawlin throughout the week. I sent Joe a list and was like, hey, this is a pretty good list right
of the best George Carlin specials ranked. And Joe was like, no, that list is completely wrong. Here are
the ones you should watch. So I watched four or five. And it made me into a huge fan. I mean, I knew him
from Bill and Ted. I knew him from a few things. I'd seen clips, of course, whenever they make the
Twitter rounds. But really, you know, masterful next level standup comedy. And in his later live,
I watch a few of his like specials where he looks like he's close to death, really not missing a beat.
Just just a guy whose whose voice is sorely missed, I think, in the world. And George Crawlin's American
dream is about as good a place as you could start. It's it's as great a documentary as the Gary
Shanling one was in typical appital fashion. It is four hours long. It basically when he dies, spoiler
alert in this movie, I click pause to see how much longer I had in the documentary. And there was 45
minutes to go after his death. That to me is where the documentary takes an unfortunate turn. It goes
almost into a what's his name, bowling for Columbine, Michael Moore kind of vibe, where it's showing
you like the events of the last 30 years with Carlin's voice over them. And I get it. And it's
effective. And I bet a lot of people watching it thought that that was really cool. But for me, I'm like,
you're really told a beautiful story of the man. And then at the end here, it just felt a little
because it's it's choosing all like the left moments. And it's politicizing his words in a way
that Carlin never really did. Yes, he was liberal for sure. But he also hated both sides. And
appital or whoever him and his co -director, they make political choices with what they're showing.
You know, the impression watch it. This is why I didn't watch it because he because Carlin on his
second to last special said. And he and this wasn't the first time, but he made fun of conservatives.
And then he said, and don't forget these campus liberal assholes. They're just as bad except from
the other fucking direction. Talk a lot of shit about the liberals. Yeah. And he he trashed liberal
class America all the time. Guilty white liberals have invented a language to conceal their sins.
It's as simple as that. That's all political correctness is. He was staunchly against voting. He
thought it didn't matter. He thought involvement in society and culture was pointless. That his his
role was to observe and report. And that was it. And this is why I've avoided this documentary.
Because as much as I think I might enjoy parts of it, I have a problem with the fact that a group
of very liberal minded Hollywood people that often have an agenda have taken it upon themselves to
tell his story. I especially when appital is a guy who speaks out about against certain types of
jokes and doing certain things and blah, blah, blah. And it's like Carlin as a guy that says they
say, you can't joke about rape. I say, fuck you. I think it's hilarious. You can joke about anything
as long as it depends on how you construct the joke. Well, like appital is an interesting case because
he talks a lot of shit about what you can and can't joke about. And he also talks a lot of
shit about cancel culture. And you can't have it both ways. Like he's basically saying why are they
canceling, you know, he was he was pro Louis CK and these people and whatever he wants to think is
fine, but he's always kind of talking out of the way. Oh, appital is pro Louis. I didn't know that
far as I know. He I think he's pro a lot of people in comedy and they can can comedian should be
whatever they want. But then like you're saying, he also is weirdly liberal and censoring as well.
And I don't know, it's just they they politicize Carlin at the end of this. It's a well -done video
piece. I just don't know that I would have put it at the tail end of this documentary. He's the
stuff about him, you know, the more traditional biography stuff of him. He's got a way more interesting
trajectory than most comedians. It's not that old. Once I started talking about myself than
everything, you know, which is the story of it, you know, every single standup commute comic.
Carlin's whole thing is like he tried to be the suit and tie square telling jokes guy and then
little by little as he found drugs and he found the counter culture. He went off on truly his own
thing. He's a true original. This what got me the most emotionally is the stuff about his wife
who was an alcoholic to an extreme degree. They got sober together and then, you know, Carlin,
I think had big patches of anti -surbreity. But their love story had me crying by the end of the thing.
I thought it was really, really beautiful. And it's it's great, you know, it's it's a big messy
documentary. And if you're a fan of the guy, of course, you got to check it out. How much is Kelly?
It might annoy you. How much is Kelly in it? The daughter.
Too much, I'd say, you know, I she her her remembrances of her dad are not that interesting.
They're anybody's reminiscent of their dad, you know, like, but she's she's cool, you know,
I like her being in it. I was telling Joe, like, why are the fuck are they interviewing Alex
Winter? And then I forgot about Bill and Ted. But it's like, they're not asking Alex Winter. They do
a little bit about Bill and Ted, which takes up maybe 15 seconds of a four hour documentary.
But there's also big chunks of time where Alex Winter is talking about Carlin's comedy. And there
are a few of the talking heads chosen where you're like, why is this person speaking on it? But for the
most part, everybody, as I told Joe, even comedians that I don't like or respect, everybody has really
interesting thoughts to say about George Carlin. How we affected them in the world and it's it's well done.
Please tell me Louis Black is heavily in it.
I don't know if he isn't it, but because I think I'm getting him mixed up with the kids in the
whole documentary because he's in that quite a bit. He's not in the Carlin documentary.
He was Carlin's favorite comedian in his later years. Is that right? Yes. So that's
what that's the other thing that bothered me. It's like, it's like, look, nothing against Patton or
any of these people. But it's like every talk or Kamau Bell or whatever. But every talking head I saw
in the trailer, I was like, this person didn't know him. I want to hear from people that knew him.
I hear more pontification on why Carlin was brilliant. I have enough of that going on in my own
brain. Give me something I don't know. Like I want to hear from his daughter. She has inside
information that I don't have. Right. You know, like I let me hear from some of his peers.
You know, like I guess maybe I'm a lot of them are dead. But you know, like I'll tell you
guy, what I love to have heard from my friend Danny, who had a fucking public air radio show.
And he did for free from a college campus in his 30s that Carlin went on regularly because he met him
and he liked him. Yeah. And he would go, that's how I met George Carlin with my buddy Danny's goofy
fucking radio show that he made no money on. The Carlin just took a shine to Liz Maley, who's a
comedian and a friend of mine. She had lunch with him several times. Why? Because she met him and he
just took a liking to her. And she had stories of eating lunch with him as he showed her all of his
new material and said like, is it those are the stories I want to hear. I don't I'm sorry. I don't
care if Sarah Silverman has an opinion. You know, and it's nothing against her. It's just they don't
talk to Sarah Silverman. I mean, or whoever. I'm just there's there's there's enough of those
people. I think I think honestly, you'll be pleasantly surprised, Joe. That's a guy who's obsessed.
You're going to have a really good time with the documentary. But one one story I do want to share
from it. Very brief is Paul Reiser is great in it. And he said he's talking about how just like
what you're saying, his little sister was doing a radio interview show at the college and Paul Reiser
who was obsessed with comedy comes home one day. And his sister was like, can you just stay
back here? George Carlin is here. And I'm interviewing him for him interviewing him for this college
paper or something. And Paul Reiser was freaking out because she didn't even know how cool it was.
And he was talking how he heard George Carlin taking a piss. And he was like, George Carlin is
taking a piss in my house. It's a great story. I love Paul Reiser. But then the the cap, the cap
of it is his dad comes home. It's like nerdy dad. And they're both like, oh, fuck, you know, he's
going to he's going to embarrass us. And Carlin's like, all right, well, I'm heading out and the dad's
like, oh, no, no, I've got to drive you. I'll drive you. It's fine. Let's go down and I'll drive you.
And he's going, no, no, I'm good. I'm good. I got some errands to run. Well, what do you got to do?
I'll drive you to the errands. We never get a celebrity here. And he goes, well, I'm going to buy
a camera. I want to take some photographs of New York. And it'll be too much of a hassle. No, no,
no, where are you getting the camera? And he tells them and he goes, no, you got to go to my friend
Mori. You got to talk to my friend Mori. He'll get you a deal on the camera. And they go up
to the camera shop. And then Paul Reiser tells a story about running into George Carlin years later.
And he goes, I know you probably don't remember this. And Carl goes, I remember it very well. I was
going to score some Coke. I realized I couldn't tell that to your dad and your little sister.
So I went on a whole day journey to buy a fucking camera because I was too embarrassed to say what
I was really doing. Great, great story. Very funny. It's really funny. I mean, you're going to love
the documentary. It's all I can say. You just got to separate yourself from the issues you might have.
Joe, I'm going to get a coffee. That's by the way, streaming on HBO Max.
I only have two for today. I'll do my rewatch now. You know what, I do have three.
Well, I watched grandma's boy last night. You know, I never saw it. I remember when it came out,
people that I knew that were fans of the Sandler camp were like, it's really funny. You got to see
it. And I just had never watched it. And last night, I'm sort of flipping around on Amazon Prime
or the stars plug in or whatever the hell it was. And I see it. And I open up the
you know, the description or the details. And I'm like, all right, it's really Jones.
You know, the mom from, I forget her name from everybody loves Raymond.
And Nick Schwarzen. All right, I'm going to give this a watch. Oh, Linda, I want to say
Tortillini. You know, the she was in a bloodline. And you know, anyway, I'm a fan of hers.
Anyway, I turn it. Cartillini, that's it. It's just not a good movie. It's got a couple laughs in it.
And I just, I guess they made a lot of money, man, but I was like, my God.
Has any film company made more bad movies than happy Madison? And I'm a fan of Adam Sandler.
But I went on the Wikipedia page. It is a laundry list.
I mean, my God, it's just one after the next. We are like every one of the, I don't think there's
a certified freshman, the entire list. I, as I told you, Joe, got an email asking if I wanted to
perhaps meet about a happy Madison reboot of Artless. Artless. I mean, the instincts aren't great
over there. Let's be real. But I'm watching it. And there's this guy on there. Something Dante is his
last name. And he plays the weed dealer. And he's very funny in the movie. And I, you know,
or for his funny as you can be in this movie. But he has a charisma. And I was like, you know what?
It's guys interesting. Who is he? So I look him up. And it's, you know, he's part of that Sandler
camp and covert, right? Covert on covert? No, no, no, his last name is Dante, something Dante.
And I was like, no, covert's the main guy. Yeah, I saw a ground. I saw it in the theater. I don't
remember it. I remember finding it amusing. Sorry, I look this guy up. And I'm like, okay, he's part
of the Sandler camp. And I do it a bit of a deep dive on him because his Sandler involvement falls
off suddenly. Yeah. Five years ago or something. This Dante guy. And he always plays a guy named Dante
in the movies, which is funny to me because I'm like, this is clearly like their boy that they
were just like, he's so funny. Just put him in stuff and just make him be Dante. Yeah. So anyway,
I look him up and his Sandler involvement falls off a few years back. And I'm like, that's weird
because covert, the main guy, he's in every, like Sandler doesn't cut anybody loose, you know,
you get to keep going. What happened? And I find a string of videos of him on TMZ saying horribly
racist things to the public. I think covert did some of the same shit on Twitter. Well, this
don't really went after people on Twitter. And I'm pretty, I would say, racially kind of wild
way a few years back. This was, he's like at a, this guy's at a, there's footage of him. He's at a
sushi restaurant in the woman's like, you have to wear a mask and it's outside of the mask mandate.
And he's like, you know, you're garbage, right? You know, you're garbage. And then he starts,
she starts with like, you need to go back to wherever you came from like all that shit. Do you know
who I am? I'm famous. Oh, that shit. Yeah, yeah, yeah. So I'm like, okay, this guy kind of dug his
own gray. And then I can't, apparently there was another thing that he got caught with a black racial
thing. And the TMZ has an interview with him in the street being like, I'm not racist. One of my best
friends is Nelly. And you're like, Oh, Jesus. Holy crap. Peter Dante, the gentleman. Peter Dante.
So anyway, that was my takeaway from Grandma's boy. He was about it. Looks like he threatened to kill
his neighbor as well as his children and wife. Not great. That was the latest thing over construction
that started at 9 .30 a .m. Oh boy. Yeah, call the waitress to see where to have to make him wear a mask.
Okay. Yeah, that's the Asian. Yeah, I believe. Anyway, there you go.
All right, well, I won't rewatch it. It's not when I ever thought I should. I remember finding a
couple of laughs and Bucky Larson. I mean, Swarzan makes me laugh occasionally. It's just, he's got
laughs in this because he's just a naturally funny guy, but he's taking nothing in making it sort
of funny. Right. You know, but I mean, it's, look, it's very of the time. It's like, he plays a 30 -year -old
man who sleeps in a race car bed and wears onesie pajamas. You know, like, guys,
at the show that he's stunted a little bit without having him literally wear footy pajamas. Yeah,
it was, you know, it was, it was, it was weed humor back then. It was like going to this thing blazed
and you'll just laugh because it's so idiotic. But, you know, I saw, I've been alternating between
the dumbest, most mindless shit to try to snap my depression and then also really
wallowing in it with really depressing movies. I only do one or the other, so you might notice
these being a little schizophrenic. But I rewatched Weekend at Bernie's. You know, that would definitely
fall into the, the latter, the earlier category, the dumb ones. But it also, I listened to, I love
the podcast Double Threat with Tom Sharpling and Julie Klausner. And their engineer, Brett,
has this new podcast that I thought was really good idea, which is each week they watch a dumb movie
and then one of the great canon movies. And the name of the podcast is Weekend at Bergman's. I have
not heard it, but the first week they do the seventh seal and Weekend at Bernie's. They played a clip
from it and he was talking about how it was kind of a brilliant movie Weekend at Bernie's as much as
Bergman's movies were about death. You could look at this as a movie about how death is all around
this and we're just completely ignoring it. Now, I think that's reading a bit too much into Weekend
at Bernie's for sure. I would agree. But there is some sort of, there's an interesting thematic
element to it. And the guy who did it, and this really blew my mind, Joe, wrote, Where's Papa?
The movie I talked about on this show with the insane gang rape sequence. So I think he is a man who
obviously loves pushing boundaries, but he also does really depraved shit with purpose. So even though
most people watching Weekend at Bernie's are not making that connection, sometimes hearing somebody
talk passionately about a movie can make me give a shit about it. And I really enjoy with this guy
had to say about Weekend at Bernie's. I watched it. Look, it's not a classic film. John Cryer, I learned
really wanted both parts, but didn't get it. It went to Silverman and... What's the other guy?
Andrew and Carthy. Always charming the two of them. I find them very charming. Always charming.
I like them together. I've liked them and think separately. But I gotta say, I do wonder if this wouldn't
have been a real classic if we had like a Vaughan Wilson or something. You know, these are pretty
lightweight comedic performers, McCarthy and Silverman, even though I like them. Silverman,
I saw at the arc light once, making out with a girl who looked 13. So that kind of clouds,
that's come on. Stop, that's not. I'm telling you what I saw. She didn't look 13. She looked like a
child. I assume she was 18. I assume he's a respectable man, but he had gray hair and it made things look
dramatic. Yeah, you gotta be careful what you throw around these days. This was years ago.
I'm not, I'm not testifying. He was making out with a young woman. It's not a shocker in Hollywood,
though. Even at the arc light, you can always see an old guy with a ponytail making out with a child.
But... I met him at a stand -up show once and he really liked my comedy.
Well, that's it. That's why you're standing up for him. No, no. I immediately said to him,
dude, I'm a big week in a Bernie's fan. I love odd couple two. He looked at me like I was
a little crazy, but I was like, I'm serious. I like those movies. Yeah, no. I actually, if I saw
Weekend at Bernie's two, I don't remember it and I don't think I did. I know that's supposed to be
the really bad one, but terrible. You know, the original, in my opinion, the slapstick in it,
it's a lot of slapstick, of course, with the corpse. It's very well done. There's good and bad
slapstick. Everyone, comedy has become... There is no comedy. Let's put it that way, but
it used to be slapstick was just lumped into this thing of a lesser style of comedy, but for true comedy
heads, there are degrees of slapstick. And Weekend at Bernie's is well executed carefully timed,
sort of pitch -perfect slapstick. And it works really well. The leads are likable. The stories kind
of fun. I do think it needed to go to like a crazier place, a phrasier style farce I would
love to see break out at the end of this. And they're not quite equipped to give you that level of
entertainment, but it's a funny movie. I've already talked too long about Weekend at Bernie's.
I will only do two. I was going to do three, but only do two. I watched a film I'd never heard of it
called Into the Labyrinth. Dustin Hoffman's latest picture came out in 2020. Never heard of it.
May neither. A lot of these guys, whether it's because they got in trouble here or because their fame
is waning here, kind of go overseas and do these movies that you never really hear of here. This
was an Italian film made by an Italian film director. And in all Italian cast, the entire
things and subtitles except for the Dustin Hoffman scenes. Okay. He plays a psychoanalyst who is hired
to interview a kidnapy who has returned 15 years after being kidnapped.
She turns up in the wilderness. She's got a broken leg. Nobody knows how she got there. They're trying
to find her a doctor. And Hoffman plays the doctor assigned to her to figure it all out.
Meanwhile, there's a B plot or an A plot. I should say that's more the B plot. The A plot is
there's a guy who is his entire career was basically debt collecting. And he's given a diagnosis
where he's going to die in two basically two months. He realizes that for his life to have purpose,
what he needs to do is solve this mystery of who abducted this woman. So his investigation is basically
the A plot. The cops don't want him around. He's in the way, but he's actually doing all the real
work, that kind of thing. And intercut is the flashback sequences of her time in being kidnapped
that are told through the interviews she's doing with Dustin Hoffman. Lots of twists and turns,
a little too long, but I enjoyed it overall. It was pretty sinister. There are moments where you're
wondering if it's going to have a supernatural edge to it. There are some legitimately creepy parts.
I don't know any of the cast because they're all Italian actors. Quality wise, it's a decent film.
It's got a little bit again of that. I'm trying to think of another example of like
you know, like Travolta's a guy that'll do these things now where it's like you see these movies
in there. Bruce Willis. Bruce Willis. There's like a cookie cutter quality to them.
Cigol. Yeah. Well, Cigol is even, I mean, that's way low. You know what I mean? These are like
movies that I feel like get releases of like Europe. They just come out over here.
Well, that's what they said. Willis was doing for the last several years just popping up on set.
They prop them up because they know they can put them on the poster and sell more tickets. Yeah, so
you know, it's it was an interesting movie. I enjoyed it enough that I stuck with it till the end
and I wanted to see what would it finally how it would play out. I wouldn't tell you to rush out
to see it, but it was definitely a better version of something like the snowman or or a not as good
prisoners. You know, it's sort of like lie somewhere in there. It's a big gap between those two
movies. Yeah, it is a pretty big. Well, these movies, I feel like are always sort of a big
they're all over the place, man. You know, a mystery thriller is that's a tough one to pull off.
You know, that's a real tough one to pull off. Unless, evidently, you're Adam Sandler and Jennifer
Aniston because murder mystery too is on the horizon. Well, you know, the original murder mystery
was written by the guy who wrote Zodiac. So I didn't like it much, but that's that's what's happening.
So in my last one, I'll be brief. I saw Jack asked 4 .5, which is somehow streaming on Netflix,
even though it's owned by Paramount. I hope it's also streaming on Paramount Plus or else how big
a fuck up was that? The whole point of this was that you owned your own content. Anyway, Jack asked 4 .5
in a lot of ways as just as funny as as the movie. And in many cases, there are stunts, bits,
whatever you want to call them that far exceed what was in the original Jackass. So I don't know if
it's, you know, honestly, Jack asked 2 .5 is better than Jackass 4. It seems to me and I'm appreciative
that they did this. It seems to me they decided let's make two really, really strong movies as opposed
to doing one really funny one and then one kind of odds and ends pile of shit. I was very surprised at
how consistent Jackass 4 .5 was. So if you liked 4, I know Joe and I kind of split on it, but I had
enough laughs to make it worthwhile for sure. This is on an equal level. Check it out.
Do we get any bam? Do we get any bam in this thing? No, no, they dedicated to Ryan Dunn, but no bam.
You get, I mean, look, they basically this star of the thing is practically Steve. They do all kinds of
shit to him. Painful, horrible shit. The one guy's got to have testicular torsion or something,
the guy who they keep kicking in the nut. There's a softball girl who is nailing them all in the
balls and that was in the movie. Then maybe this is an extended sequence. I don't know, but
oh, this was tennis. So this was a famed female tennis player. It's just nailing each of them
right in the balls. But look, there's lots of great stuff. I never like spoil on the stunts and
Jackass. Part of the fun is not knowing what's coming up around the bend. So I recommend it. And let's
go now to the movie of the week, the Northman, which I thought was a 24, but it was not. They decided
the guy, which I found very interesting, the director of the Northman, who also we should say did the
lighthouse, which I absolutely loved, and the witch, which I should probably rewatch, but did not
love. You hated the witch. Yeah, you did not like the witch, but Robert Eggers, I don't ask this
to push buttons. Yes, maybe a little hyperbole here. You absolutely love the lighthouse. Now keep in
mind, absolutely love is a space you need to reserve for your favorite movies of all time. You like
no, not true. Not true. I love all kinds of movies that don't fit into my favorite of all time,
but at lighthouse would not. I watched it once in the theater. I thought I was just annoyed by the
gimmick of it the way it looked, whatever. And I couldn't understand what anybody was saying. And I
thought this is beautiful, but whatever it is, what it is, and it's over. When I watched it at home
with subtitles, I loved it. I don't know what else to say. I love the movie. But Eggers, when
interviewed, he did both the witch and the lighthouse with a 24, and he said he split away from them,
A, because he needed a lot more money for the Northman, but B, because he wanted more creative
freedom, which is very interesting, considering a 24 really broadcast that they give you creative
freedom. But then again, when you watch all their movies, they look and feel identical.
So I thought that was sort of interesting. I also, a 24 clearly put their night movie
Are there their historical epic money into the really bad green night, which we also talked about
on the show. And not the Northman, but in my opinion, the Northman is by far the superior movie,
even though they feel similar in a lot of ways. The Northman is better than green night,
but you know, to me, that green book. Yeah, to me, that's like saying, well, at least I didn't step in
the wet shit. I found this movie to be visually stunning. And it really hit the ground running.
And from there on out, it was just a pretentious slog. I find Robert Eggers at this point to be
pretentious. It's a lot of look at what I can do. I'm going to explore languages and dialects and
lifestyles that you're completely unfamiliar with to show you that I can pull off this feat.
It seems to be more about challenging himself. Unless about challenging the audience. And
this thing was an hour too long. And it is it is 220. You know, and you know, just the basic plot
is hamlet essentially. Yes. A man's uncle murders his father and take and kidnaps his mother and
tries to murder him, the boy who's supposed to inherit the kingdom. The boy flees manages to escape
with his life. Cut two years later, you find out the uncle did not succeed with the kingdom and has
just become a quiet farmer on an island somewhere. The boy still is intent on saving his mother
and getting his revenge. And that's the plot of the movie. The reason that it's an hour too long is
the kid has the kid keep in mind who is a killing machine from almost birth. Alexander Skarsgard
goes up to be him. Yes. Has the opportunity to carry out his task and easy four times in this movie.
But Robert Egger's inexplicably prevents him from doing so for no apparent reason.
And so this can just keep going on and on and on where he's got the guy in his grasp and then he
doesn't and then he's near the guy and then he's not and then he goes away for no reason and then he
goes back. I mean, for Christ's sake, man, it's just like, what do we, what is the point here? I just don't,
you know, again, this is music video directing to me. Go paint a painting, go do an art installation in
a museum where music plays and we look at your visuals, but this is not good storytelling in my opinion.
And as is often the theme on the show going way back, expert storytelling is not always my top
priority. If the visuals, the vibe, the feel can sweep you along. Like Neon Demon is a great example
where Joe and I really differed, but like the feel of it was enough. I love being in that world for a while.
Northman, I texted Joe about a half hour in and I was like, I got to tell you Joe, this movie is
fucking awesome. And Joe said, oh, I can't wait to hear, you know, he said, I thought the same thing
for the first half hour, I can't wait to hear you change your tune. And I got to be real, the tune
didn't change. The tune didn't change for me. It was, it, a historical epic, you know, which is not my
thing. I don't like Excalibur very much. I find it very boring. Even the classics of the genre
are not really my thing. But this, from scene to scene, even though the story was your basic quest
story, which is a type of story. And a lot of times even like the Odyssey or something, you're like,
come on guys, yeah, at any point you could wrap this up. But part of it is the story sort of like,
you know, like if somebody's telling an old folklore tale or whatever they would say,
then he came up against a giant and then he came up against a midget or a little person or he came
up against a fat guy or whatever. And that's kind of the fun of a quest is just they bump into all these
people. It's the Lord of the Rings movies. They kept it up for 12 hours, those movies of just people
going from place to place, fighting a new thing. My question is, are the things that he is fighting
and the landscape he is fighting in, exciting, entertaining, visually spectacular? And the answer
to all of the above was yes, I was not bored at all in a two hour 20 minute movie. I'll tell you the
difference, even me. I'll tell you the difference. In Lord of the Rings, he doesn't go to
more door in hour one. And then for no reason, leave more door. There's this entirely complicated
plot, meaning not plot of the movie, but plot, they're plotting in the movie to drug all of the
soldiers in this camp with with mushrooms. Right. For some reason, psychedelics keep turning up in
these old Viking films. I don't understand why all of a sudden that's a thing, but it ain't. He does
it. He pulls it off. He drugs the camp. They're all literally on the ground because they don't know what's
happening. He then can, he then finally goes to his mother. And for the first time reveals his identity,
the way he gets into the camp is he pretends to be a slave. And he gets in. He then goes to Nicole
Kidman and says, it's me, I'm your son. And she reveals that not only does she not want to be rescued,
that she never loved his father. And then she tries to seduce her own son.
Yes. And with all the rage that has driven this man, his entire life, this bloodlust to get to this point,
he doesn't kill his mother. He doesn't, he just lets it go. He just lets it slide and walks out.
And then doesn't kill the father as the entire camp has its guard down. The next morning,
when you think that the father goes, where is he who did this to my man? Somebody cut the heart out
of my best man. He descends from the hills holding the heart of the greatest warrior in the camp. And
you think, Oh, now it's on. Now it's on. And no, it's not on because all of the soldiers who are fat and
old and not as in shape as him, managed to tackle him to the ground, even with a mushroom hangover.
This is a guy that we've seen in previous scenes in the movie. Take down an entire army single
handedly in the opening sequence when he, when they storm the village. Awesome. It should be said.
Awesome sequence. That's an awesome sequence. But that's not writing. That's not storytelling.
Make a real obstacle that prevents him from completing his goal. Don't just say, well,
it's too early to end this. So we're going to not have him ended here. And we're just going to write a
lazy thing in as to why he doesn't end it. I don't get it. I think it is entirely dissatisfying in the end
that he dies in the killing of his uncle that they kill one another at the same time. I get the point
of it that he's supposed to die in battle. And that's his honor and all that bullshit. I found it very
dissatisfying, but it's a tragedy, whatever. That's besides the point. I just found over and over again
his goal was in his grasp. And he has taken out of it for no good reason other than to elongate
the plot. And I guess I can kind of hear that. And yet it's just to me, it was the same with the
Green Knight and all these other type of movies. The quest movie to me is just to kind of showcase
battle scenes. There's a snow world. It's almost like a video game in a lot of ways. But all I can say
is they work on me or they don't this type of thing. This movie, I also texted Joe. I said, it feels
like a movie that would have accompanied a Led Zeppelin album in the 70s. Like song remains the same
or something where it's like just something they're they're playing the music over it. If this
thing had like a metal soundtrack or like a Led Zeppelin soundtrack, I think it would be absolutely
fucking awesome. And it's that kind of a thing. It's that kind of a thing of just like, and I was
stone, don't get me wrong. But that's kind of what it's for. It's like a metal, just awesome visuals
and violence and buff dudes screaming. And I felt a little bit like 300, which is a movie I didn't
really love either. But I think it needed a little more of that. I think it didn't have enough of
the 300 thing in it. And it was it was too much there was too much of Robert Egger's jerking himself off.
Get that. I mean, like so when you when he's like flying into Evan or whatever and at the end of
the movie, where you like, as guys jerking himself off, because I was like fucking awesome. What an awesome
ending. Not satisfying necessarily because I don't know. I never care about anybody in these movies.
Have have have him have him. Okay. So the big face off at the end, right? Yeah. Fighting in the volcano
world or whatever. Yeah. Fighting atop of volcano. It was marketed as a naked fight. But I believe
they're both wearing underwear. Yeah. But anyway, they meet up there, right? Yes. Have there be a
purpose for that? Sure. It's not enough for me that you just go, well, in Viking times, that's
just how they did. I don't care. Have it be a purpose. Have it be the next morning after the
mushroom incident. The uncle has fled. And now he has to track him to the volcano world. That's the
part that bothered me. It's literally he runs off somehow with his tail between his legs. Then
finds out his love of his life is pregnant. And then he says, well, fuck you. I'm going to go back
and kill my uncle. Why don't you stay and kill him the first time? I don't understand. Yeah.
Well, it's it's that Anna Taylor joy from Queens Gambit. I never really loved Scars Garb. Like I love
them together. I thought that the movie was sexy. I thought the movie was fun. And I guess we just
really differed. I mean, one of the greatest writing tips that I ever got came from the South Park
documentary on it's on HBO Max right now. It's called like eight hours till showtime or something
like that. Yeah, I like that movie. Trey Parker talks about his process, which is like
you're looking at at cards saying this is the story. But what you need to do is not say this happens
and this happens and this happens and this happens. Good writing to me is when you can say this happens
because of that. This happens because of that. This happens. And that is what I think I'm hearing you as
saying the Northman did not provide for you. It was just a collection of scenes. And often
if he had put a little more work in, I'll grant you. This thing could have been an all -time classic.
Certainly of this sword and sorcery genre, which I think is a lot of great movies. If he had put
the time in to make it a more satisfying script, but that's not really what this guy does. So I came
in expecting like crazy action metal vibes. And that's what I got. And I loved it. I just,
that really just what you just said is also my problem with with the Trey Parker point is also my
problem with Ariastra. I feel like it's the same thing. I feel like he gets a series of ideas into his
head and then connects them as best he can. John Carpenter does that. John Carpenter said he did that
with Halloween. Look, sometimes it works. And sometimes it doesn't. Robert Edgar's look, he does just
like the witch I loved on first viewing on second viewing. I was bored to tears and I hated it.
The lighthouse I found interesting enough, but overall I would never rewatch it. This I loved half of it
and I found the other half a slog. Eggers keeps me hooked in just enough that I want to see what he's
going to do next. But I personally think he's a guy that could do with a little less creative freedom.
He's got the goods. I want to see him team up with an excellent writer who really knows.
I always say this about Shyamalan. You know, I hear you. I always say this about Shyamalan.
Who was a great writer at one time? But it's like why doesn't Shyamalan take his
literally Spielberg level filmmaking skills and serve a great script? Why doesn't he become a director
for hire? It makes no sense. I got to tell you this too. And then we can wrap it up. But, you know,
because I know we're we're we're talking a lot here. But like I'm sorry, man. Nicole Kidman
only cast her in things that take place in present day. I can't look at Nicole Kidman
with with major plastic surgery playing in a Viking movie. It's absurd. It's fucking absurd. I
would I've said this about everything I've seen her in and she's in everything these days,
everything. Ricardo's I was like, what is this? For some reason in this because she always seemed
to be in black and white somehow, even though she wasn't. And it wasn't wearing makeup or whatever.
She looked ghostly and she looked awesome to me. Even though it's not a real face,
she looked like a weird ghost to me and I dug it. I don't know why. And then Defoe creeping
around the corners, you know, I thought the cast was great. I don't know. I was awesome. The the
summoning of Defoe's ghost was really cool. Yeah. I thought it had element. Look, I'll leave it at
this. I'll give it the North Menor rewatch, not in the theater, but I'll rewatch it. Maybe I was
a little too harsh on it because I went in expecting a little more spectacle than I got. I'll give it a
sideways hog. I won't go hogged down on this as I thought I would entering in my hog. I mean,
literally, I might as well have jumped out of my seat. Dick high fists in the air for the final
scene of what happened at the end of this movie. I was like, I really had a great time and I admired
how nuts it was. And my hogs just rock hard full of blood for the North Men. I say this as someone who
hasn't even enjoyed a movie in 2022. I don't think that I can recall, but it's my favorite movie
the year so far. I can't say that, but I also haven't seen any other movies. So it hasn't been a
great lineup. Up next, folks, I guess we'll do let's do firestarter. Yeah, we're also going to do kids
in the hall, the reboot series, but let's do that later in the month. It'll give us a little more
space between the brain candy review and the reboot review. So next episode will give people a time to
watch it since Amazon has decided not to advertise it anyway, which is interesting to me even on their
homepage. All right. Up next, firestarter. Jotaro's a comedy, the remake of firestarter, I should say.
Jotaro's a comedy, a Gmail, I'm sorry, Jotaro's a comedy at Instagram and Twitter.
Come to Joey Roses, visit our website for our hours of operation. Joey Roses NYC .com. And then also
I'm hitting the road, folks. Sorry, Austin and Houston got fucked up. It was out of my hands, but
got plenty of other dates coming up, starting in July with San Francisco and Fairfield, Connecticut.
Go to Jotaro's a info .com for all dates and tickets.
I am the Patrick Walsh on Twitter and Instagram. I got nothing to plug at this time. We love you guys.
Thank you very much. We'll see you next time and we'll see you in hell.