I'll see you at Hal today we're talking about the Howling Oh
Oh, not the full series, but the the original Joe Dante as Pat would say his name flick from 1981. And I am Joe DeRosa. And that is Patrick Walsh.
I am. Yeah, this is the flick from 1981. I'm the prick from 1981. Patty Walsh, the year I was born January 5th.
I love Joe DeRosa. I will never pronounce his name correctly. And we'll get there. But for me, I'm one of the few people, not not one of the few people, but I really only treasure a small window of Joe Dante's career, about 10 years. And I don't love the earliest stuff like some do. So I wonder, I wonder how we'll talk about the howling today. I don't know your opinion on the film, Joe.
I'll save my opinion on the film. I don't really know much of his early work outside of this. I never see piranha. I never saw piranha, which is I'm surprised to say I think I own it and I've never seen it.
Yeah, I mean, it's it's beloved. I watched it over the pandemic. I do got to give some movies a bit of a pass if I watched them over the pandemic because some movies just went in one ear and out the other during that time period.
Yeah, I'm not a big, I'm not a huge fan of piranha. I think, you know, for me, the howling is the start of where he really starts to get good, but his first masterpiece has got to be gremlins in my opinion.
But we'll get there. We'll get there. By the way, by the by. There's a great video circulating online. I don't have Twitter anymore, which as everyone told me it would has changed my life for the better immeasurably in about two weeks.
I'm going to take more to immeasurably. Yeah. But still I have a couple of accounts and their film accounts that I check once in a while. One is a Blu -ray news account and one is a buddy of mine who does great movie news and stuff.
The insider, if you're ever looking for him, Jeff Snyder, he's he's he's great. He's like gossipy without being obnoxious about it. He's got a lot of great Hollywood stuff. Anyway, the insider had posted and if you're looking for the clip, that's one place to find it.
It is Richard Donner. This is such a funny story. Richard Donner, the director of lethal weapon and lost boys and goonies and all these great movies had a very, very difficult shoot on the goonies because it was a very long shoot and it was a bunch of like hormonal adolescent boys and they drove him insane.
He liked the course, but they like really drove him nuts and he was really rattled by the end of the shoot. So he says like the day it wraps. He's like, oh man, he's so relieved and he goes to Hawaii with this wife to relax and enjoy himself.
And Steven Spielberg, two days into his Hawaiian vacation, flies out with the entire group of kids, the entire all the goonies kids.
And they all run in. So there's Richard Donner, like sitting peacefully looking out at the beach and all these kids that he just escaped from come running out and they're like, I don't know. It's like a young Josh Brolin and Sean Asin and all the kids.
Really, really just cool to see, you know, and then as the icing on the cake, outcome, all the frittellies as well and he's flown out and Ramsey and chunk and all of them, you know, sloth.
And they're all there in Hawaii with Steven Spielberg as this prank on Richard Donner. You should watch it. It's really, really cute and funny.
Okay.
Is that making sense that you were looking at me, Joe, as if I was speaking Swahili.
No, no, you were making a story.
You were making sense. I was pulling up a news story. I wanted to, I forget sometimes people aren't looking into my eyes. They're looking through me at the screen.
I would, I wanted to talk, I wanted to ask you if are you excited about the full Monte sequel series that's about to come out.
Well, I'll tell you this. I'm, I'm baffled by a show about male strippers being on Disney plus A. That makes no sense to me.
Because the full Monte strippers strippers, right? It's kind of like funny, like old men.
Yeah, of course, but the full, the full Monte is an R rated movie. Disney plus doesn't allow R rated things. So I'm just kind of baffled by it, but I haven't seen the full Monte in at least 25 years.
But when I saw it in theaters, I fucking love that movie. I really did love that movie. It's really funny and really sweet. And I'm sure it holds up. I liked it a lot.
I love Robert Carlisle, the guy from Trainspotting and this movie. And I think they brought the cast back if I'm not mistaken.
There's also here's another piece of news psycho.
Suns of anarchy stars reunite for a PETA ad campaign where they say real men don't chain dogs. If that doesn't ring as is legitimate.
Guys, for the love of God, I don't know. What does that know? Why does that bother you?
It's I'm sure these, these actors are against animal cruelty. Sure.
The fact that they're doing it as characters, they portrayed who did horrible things. Yeah, true.
Or not even as characters, but as nods to characters that were in that were like hell's angels. Yeah.
A real men don't chain up dog. I got news for you guys. PETA don't like the term real men either. It's just it's just dumb. It's just fucking dumb.
I think just do the fucking ad in that. The Suns of Anarchy. And I for some reason watched every episode of that show.
Even at the end when the episodes were clocking in at like 90 minutes and it's not good. But there's something addictive about it.
And they do seem like the type that would go out beat the shit out of a family of four, but then have a weird code about abusing dogs.
So I actually do think it is in character with the Suns of Anarchy. They had a weird moral code about them for certain things.
They like the underdogs. I've been what I've been what this won't be my new psycho because I'm not far enough into it.
But I've been watching rescue me. I never watched rescue me. That's a great show. At least at first for a couple of seasons. It's really good.
I've enjoyed it so far. But the entire for so for instance, what I'm talking about the entire second episode is called as the title is gay.
And it's about how they can't deal with like they can't deal with homosexuality. And there's a gay and openly gay firefighter who's taking credit for heroics that he didn't do.
Yeah.
And it's it's challenging because you're kind of like waiting for the moment where like one of them is going to be gay and that's going to be the big thing is like.
But they it doesn't come maybe comes later in the I don't know but.
But but you're also like no that is how these guys probably would have thought and spoke at this time period and whatever.
So yeah.
But it would be like watching the guys recapturing the rescue me rolls and being like real man doll kittens love cat.
Dennis Larry is essentially playing himself but he's never been better than on that show. He's great.
He did get kind of screwed though because he had the Alec Baldwin part in the department.
I think I mentioned that on the show before and the schedule on rescue me made him unable to do it and he was like miserable.
However, Baldwin kills that part. He's so funny in that part.
It's up there.
It's like behind right behind like Glenn Gary for me was Baldwin.
Yeah.
Guys stealing every scene he's in.
I think Larry and he wasn't his prime because he was an excellent.
He gave an excellent performance on rescuing me but he was great.
He wouldn't have had the same oomph that Baldwin had.
I don't think.
I yeah.
It's that would be good for our recasting episode because I'm like okay.
If I had to see somebody else in that role, I could see Larry but not as quite as good.
But I hear you.
He rescue me was done by Peter Tolen who was one of the writers in addition to Kenneth Lonergan on.
Analyze this.
You had Harold Rammus Kenneth Lonergan and Peter Tolen.
And Peter Tolen was a legendary sitcom writer.
He's written for so many great shows throughout the years.
Murphy Brown and all kinds of stuff came up in the sitcom world.
And then really transition beautifully to drama with rescue me.
And then in recent years came out of the closet and he's married kids the whole nine yards.
I think he's doing a show at FX now about that journey for himself.
But it's fascinating then to look back at rescue me and you'll see as you watch it, Joe, there's a lot of gay themes in rescue me.
There's a there's a whole sub plot of a guy who starts getting bro jobs where he just has a gay friend come over and blow him and leave.
I had a feeling that it was headed in that direction and they're kind of setting you up with this insane toxic masculinity that is then going to be followed with.
It's burying.
Yeah.
Well, it's interesting sexuality in places.
Right because he, you know, I don't know, I would assume I've never met the man and I would assume he wasn't open and out in these writers rooms, but he always brings gay issues to his show is really fascinating.
I think and he's a great great writer.
Good show.
It goes off like all seven and eight season shows go off the rails by the end and I've been rescue me is no exception.
But for a while, it's great.
Frazier, yes, release date announced he said the looks like October 1st. I'm very excited. He said they shot 10 episodes.
He said it's very good.
Well, of course, he's going to say that, but I hope that it is.
You know, man, Roz is back, which is really cool.
So both, both BB Newworth and how am I blanking on for the love?
Perry gilpen.
Perry gilpen are back as regulars.
There's rumors that Daphne is off so back, but we'll see, but they're abandoning mad dog.
Well, he, he goes back to Boston as the plot of the show, like which I like, which I mean we're going to get some cheers cameos.
There's no way we're not going to get some cheers.
So I think it's going to be a really fun. I don't know. I hope I, you know, these, these sequels seasons have not been good.
But I also think Frazier is the kind of show that doesn't need to change much to still be good. It's not like, oh, they couldn't do that now when you watch Frazier.
It's like, yeah, this is all pretty.
It's written well, it'll be fine.
Yeah, we'll see anyway.
Excited for that.
One of the few.
One down to that movie corner.
Sure.
I'm not against it. I'm not against it.
Because I've seen some shit.
I've seen some shit.
Oh, I got a text from her old friend Morgan Murphy, Joe.
You see her in New York, ever?
Does she live here?
I guess not.
She lives in my neighborhood.
If she does, then no question.
Quite offended.
I'll go ahead.
I got a, I'm on topic here.
I got two werewolf movies.
Yeah.
Did a rewatch of silver bullet.
And seen that since you and I were in theater together at that festival.
Well, my Ohio harvest.
And if memory serves you and I watch on a 10 p .m. show that day, we would have been 25 drinks in.
Well, we had just landed.
We didn't really.
Oh, the first was the right of the first night, the first night.
So only 15.
Yeah.
But I, yeah.
I got these three points, then.
I got the screen factory, Blu -ray.
It looks great.
It plays great.
It feels great.
I really enjoy silver bullet.
I would put silver bullet in the.
I have slowly devised a top five of werewolf movies.
Silver bullet is in that top five.
I'm going to say it is in the number.
Three slot.
Okay.
I'm going to put it in the three slot.
There's not that many, I guess.
I love the OG wolf man.
I kind of like Nicholson wolf to be honest with you.
There's way more werewolf movies than you think.
I watched a YouTube video where a guy covered every werewolf movie ever.
And it was crazy how many there are.
Anyway, for my personal top five, I'm going to put silver bullet in that third position.
I really like silver bullet.
The wolf doesn't really look that good, but you got your boy from.
I'm.
Twin peaks in there as the priest who eventually has one eyed because he gets maimed as a wolf as he turns out to be the wolf.
Who who.
The guy from Twin peaks.
No.
The guy that's no.
He's married to.
I mean, you know, two.
Yeah.
No, I know you're talking.
Paul skinny southern guy looks like he should be a country singer, but is it?
Yeah.
He plays the priest who turns out to be the wolf.
It's based on the book cycle of the werewolf by Stephen King, which I own.
It's very fun book to read.
Anyway, Corey hame.
Gary bucy at his best.
I mean, this is this is peak but this is the bucy you want.
He's he's endearing, but crazy.
People forget he was nominated for an Oscar for Buddy Holly story.
He was a great actor.
I really enjoy silver bullet.
Atmosphericly, it's very fun.
It's quintessential 80s horror.
It's a great flick.
I just wish the monster looked cooler.
The wolf just looks kind of dumb, but it's hard to make it convincing where wolf.
Much harder than a vampire.
Yeah.
You go down to your dime store.
You got a vampire by some teeth.
Yeah.
But yeah, it's overcast jewel.
If you don't want to go down to the store, you know, jewel had them fangs almost no special features.
By the way, on this screen factory, you got an interview with the guy.
I was just talking about an interview with one of the female actors that was in the thing.
And that's it.
Right.
That's that's rare for scream for much.
There might be a little vignette or something.
I'm not remembering, but you know.
But anyway, silver bullet.
I'd say it's one of the better Stephen King adaptations.
I before I get to my movie would would love to point out somebody in the comments on Patreon.
You're going to love this, Joe.
That love and death show that I talked about on the last podcast with Jesse Plemons and Elizabeth Olson.
Was based on a true crime book by none other than John Bloom.
Joe Bob Briggs.
Oh, really?
Blue my mind because we were talking about Joe Bob on the last episode too.
And I looked it up because I was like, okay, this guy's got to be mistaken.
Correct.
That's wild.
So I assume he gets a nice little chunk of change, probably more than he gets for hosting the show.
He's got to get something that they adapted his book.
You do got to wonder how a man like Joe Bob survives.
I mean, other than just paycheck to paycheck.
I mean, when he was doing the TNT horror hosting, I mean, it couldn't have...
I mean, that could go two ways.
You either go, there's no way that paid anything or you go, no, back then.
Back then.
You made 35 grand in episode doing that.
Like back then and stuff.
He would have been fine.
And look, when I saw him here at the Egyptian, he packed that place.
You know, he can pack a theater and pretty much anywhere.
I don't know.
He's probably got about as much money as John Waters as my guest.
You know, they're happy.
They're doing fine.
They don't have as much as you'd like them to have, but they're doing fine.
John Waters has way more money than you think.
Two of his hairs broke.
You're right.
Yeah.
I mean, it's wild.
That guy is that guy's...
He's a multi -millionaire without a question.
Yeah.
Okay.
I hope Joe Bob's doing better than we think.
I mean, I love the man.
I do wish they would give him better movies to talk about.
Yeah.
Is it my turn?
No.
I just...
No, I went around with it.
So I saw champions.
New to Peacock.
It was in theaters one week ago.
They're like, why are movies going away?
Anyway, I didn't go see it in the theater because I was like,
it's going to be on Peacock in a week.
It was directed by Bobby Farley.
The other Farley, Peter Farley is the one who directed Green Book.
And which one best picture.
So this is Bobby's solo directorial debut.
But it feels just like a Farley Brothers movie without the bite
and the grossed out and the big gags.
It's much more realistic.
It's much more in tone with...
Actually, it's in tone with his Peter Falk lady's wrestling movie
I watched called All the Marbles from 1979.
And it feels like...
It's nowhere near as good as bad news bears.
But it feels like that.
Kind of a shaggy story.
It's not going for huge jokes.
It's going for little character moments.
But the Farley Brothers are so good.
The reason that their movies no matter how gross and depraved they get
were successful is because they know how to get you on the side
of their hero.
Kingpin is a ludicrous movie.
But you totally care about Woody Harrelson from the jump.
And you're rooting for him from scene one.
Same with Ben Stiller.
We start with him getting dumped in high school at the prom.
And he gets his dick and balls caught.
And you know, you're immediately on the side of this guy.
That's what they do best.
And they do it here with Woody.
You love Woody from the jump.
You care about him.
It's your classic Mighty Ducks type thing where he gets a DUI.
Literally the plot of the Mighty Ducks.
He gets a DUI.
And as a sign to coach a kids in this case basketball team.
And the hook is that they have Down syndrome.
So there's a scene in court where Woody Harrelson actually uses the R word repeatedly.
And you're watching it.
And his lawyers like, oh, you can't say that.
What do you can't say that?
And I thought it was going to be along the lines of the ringer,
which was that Johnny Knoxville posing as handicap in the special Olympics.
That came out 20 years ago.
And that was much more like raunchy and tone.
I thought that's what this was going to be.
But actually it's really more about Woody learning to love these kids than learning to love him.
He has a romance with Caitlin Olson that is really sweet.
It's like it's the movies two hours.
And you don't care because Caitlin and Woody have really great chemistry together.
I wouldn't be surprised if they work together again.
They seem natural like a couple.
And the movie just works.
You know, it's not a masterpiece, but it's very entertaining.
It's like a paint by numbers.
But it's how long it's been since we've had a good paint by number sports movie.
It really works.
So check it out.
I said.
All right.
I watched the wolf of snow holler.
Yeah.
Which I would put at number four in my top five were wolf movies of all time.
I love this movie.
I thought it was excellently done.
I thought it was.
I liked it.
Really well written.
Really well directed.
Blanking on the guy's name as always Jim Cummings.
Yeah.
Wrote and directed this thing.
He writes and directs a lot of his own stuff.
He's hilarious in it.
He plays a guy like his dad played by Robert Forster is sick.
He's having marital issues or whatever.
He's having problems with his kid.
He's being overprotective about his daughter who's coming into our own as a as a budding teenager
who's exploring her sexuality.
And just the performance from him alone of freaking out in every scene.
There's a running gag where he repeatedly slaps people because he gets so bad.
It's really funny.
And to boot.
It's a great werewolf mystery and spoiler alert.
It turns out that the werewolf that you do see and is really cool looking.
Turns out to just be a psychopath putting a costume on and killing people.
But you know, it's it's for own tents and purposes a monster movie.
It's got some real drama to it.
You care about these characters.
Love seeing Ricky Lynn home in there always always like to see Ricky and stuff.
I really love the movie.
It's funny.
It's it's tense.
It's it's got depth.
And it's forsters.
I believe last film role.
It also has this really great commentary on PC culture in it.
Like it's it.
It really gets into that and weighs into that and.
Kind of examines it from all angles about, you know,
it's somebody being too sensitive.
Are they not being sensitive enough.
Does this kind of behavior need to stop is you know.
And I like when a movie does that and doesn't take a hard stance from one direction or the other on it.
It's just kind of explores what it is and the effect that it has on a workplace, particularly a sheriff's office that's exploring murders that are turning up in the town.
And the best line regarding the PC culture theme in the movie is Robert Forster.
It's in the trailer where he goes now is the time I would say we should pray but I won't because of the god damn lawyers, which is a really really funny line.
So I highly highly recommend the wolf of snow holler and the only reason it's at number four is because there are some other classics in front of it on my list.
And you could argue that it's technically not a werewolf movie since there's no real werewolf in it but but I got it at number.
Fair enough.
I saw last night my new 4k of in the heat of the night directed by Norman juicin who also did moon struck very and fiddler on the roof very diverse career all over the place.
And the heat of the night one best picture in 1967 I saw when I was a kid and I always sort of associated it with to kill a mockingbird you know like yes a little bit preachy but an amazingly well done entertainment.
But I hadn't seen it in years I watched a kill a mockingbird pretty often I actually think that's a near perfect movie.
But I hadn't seen this one really since I was like 12 13 print looks amazing.
And it's Sidney Poitier and Rod Steiger Rod Steiger won the best actor Oscar but it's Sidney Poitier movie of course.
He is a black man waiting at the train station for his train.
There is a murder in the town it's a small racist southern town in the sixties.
And they're looking around for who could have done it they see this black guy sitting alone at the train station and bring him down to the police where.
Once they kind of shake him down and you know knock him around a bit they realize he is a policeman who was in town visiting his mom.
They apologize but it's it's at a time when there was extreme hatred between whites and blacks especially in the small southern towns so.
Sidney Poitier is about to leave and his boss gets on the phone and says hey if you've got a murder you can't solve you should definitely talk to Virgil Sidney Poitier.
He's like a master at this stuff he's very very gifted in you know what you would call today forensics you know.
So even though these guys have already gotten off on the shaky racist foot they have to team up to solve this murder together.
And it's great it's one of the you know the OG kind of classic template buddy movies.
You know it leads directly to like 48 hours which is a more comedic version of this kind of story but.
It's a great movie you know like they don't really pull any punches there's there's a few very famous scenes one of the most famous lines of all time is he's like what do they call you up there and Philadelphia.
Virgil and he's like they call me Mr. Tabs and then you know that's a very famous line the sequel was called they call me Mr. Tabs I'm going to watch that tonight I've never seen it it's on the blue right gets it had two sequels.
I've never seen either one of them but they came as special features that's a good special feature when they toss you in a couple extra movies.
So I highly recommend it you know I think even though one best picture it weird you never hear it talked about for some reason outside of seeing city party I do that line sometimes and montage and stuff.
But the other big scene that you know I cheer alone in my house it's just a perfectly directed scene but they go to this old white rich guy you know real creepy guy who's in this greenhouse talking to him and at some point.
He doesn't like the way Sydney party is talking to him and slaps him across the face and then Sydney Watson in the same second.
Slaps him right back and the guys so shocked that he's like crying it's this old man like shocked and crying amazing scene.
The murder mystery is is what it is it's not that great it's all about the interplay between stiger and Sydney the great together a lot of cat.
Have you seen the movie jump no check it out it's great movie all right.
I was a kid I used to watch the series in the heat of the night which had Carol O 'Connor post.
I hated the series because it was not because it was bad.
I couldn't get past Carol O 'Connor talking in a different voice I just didn't.
And he does like that it's like a quiet like southern like you'd be like these boys.
They got it and you're like man this guy's a hell of an actor but I hate it.
Yeah yeah I agree.
All right did I talk about Lake boat last time.
No I didn't know all right well Lake boats my final entry not a werewolf movie.
A David mammoth movie written I made fun of Lake boat because it was on the movie web top whatever mammoth list.
Above many other mammoth movies I thought should have been in front of it but I was saying that without having seen it.
In all fairness now that I've watched it I would say I might have been a little off in my judgment there.
Lake boat the screenplay is written by mammoth.
Based on one of his plays I believe it's directed by Joe Montana.
Yes Joe Montana is not in it he just directed it.
It stars and this is why it's on theme Dennis Leary Robert forster.
Dennis Dennis Larry Robert forster.
Who else.
Why am I blanking on this Charles Durning.
George went.
Damn Andy Garcia.
Yes.
Who else Andy Garcia.
It's just got such a hell of a cast to it.
It's about it's about a young man played by David mammoths in real life his step brother.
And it's based on mammoths own experience with this where he takes a gig on a lake boat where you basically go on a route on a lake boat over the course of two weeks and you get paid to do odd jobs.
And it's this experience he's going to get picked up on the other side of the boat trip in Boston by his mother he's on break from college.
And it starts as just sort of an examination of what it's like for a bunch of men to work together in a sort of closed off environment, which is what a lot of the earlier in eighties mammoth stuff is you know like that's kind of a clingarry his that's kind of like what American buffalo is.
And it's very funny and very course.
The guy that plays the dad in in in Rushmore is in it.
The guy that looks exactly like William H. Macy except old.
You don't talk about plays the dad in Rushmore he's he's Jason what's his face is not Jay what's the kid who's the kid in Rushmore.
Jason Schwarzen.
Yeah he places dad.
I remember the guy that places dad in Rushmore not at all you're not talking about Brian Cox.
You don't want to see more sell the old yet yes yes and it looks exactly like William H. Macy the guy from Casabetti's movies.
Yes.
That guy has a line and you'll if you'll all look part of the expression where he's telling the younger character he's giving the younger character advice on women.
And he says the only way to a woman's country is the world.
The wild scripts.
There's a lot there's a lot of that kind of stuff in it.
They're they're continuously talking about Andy Garcia his character throughout the movie as a guy that was supposed to be on the trip with them and part of the crew.
Who didn't make the trip.
And they're all spec you know it's like this all these storied versions of why he didn't make the trip I heard he met a broad and a bar and got into a knife fight.
Another guy's like I heard he had a shoot out with the cops whenever.
And again it's just kind of exploring what it's like I think when or at least in that time period what it was like when a bunch of dudes were sort of locked away together the way they would talk.
The the coarseness of it all yeah they would drink blah blah blah all that stuff what it becomes to be about and it is actually quite endearing is these grizzled old men see their past in this young new crew member and take a great investment in what he's going to do with his life and what his future will be.
And it actually becomes quite touching and there is there are two scenes in this thing that almost brought me to tears.
There's a scene with Robert Forster where he's drunk and he's in the kids cabin and he's like let me ask you something.
Or he goes I'm going to tell you something I never told anybody before I tried to kill myself once and he tells this story and it is fucking heartbreaking.
And you see this guy drop his guard for the first time ever and it's like oh my god it's and it's it is the best acting I've ever seen Robert Forster do it's a full monologue.
It's never written by mammoth it's amazing it's amazing.
I never heard of the movie I'll look it up.
It's on to be for free.
Sorry on your Amazon prime.
The other part and this got me even worse is a turning plays the skipper of the boat and he's he's a real hard ass.
He's always yelling at everybody and everything and blah blah blah.
And he's the oldest guy on the boat and he also has a job that he is below below his rank he should be at his age past this position he has.
Yeah so that adds more weight to this scene into his character but he's always kind of barking at everybody and blah blah blah and everybody's a fucking idiot and this and that whatever.
The kid is in the kitchen he's because he is cooking duties on the boat and he's cleaning the stainless steel appliances after he made the meal for the night and Charles Durning comes in and he's kind of just talking to him and he goes you having a good time.
And the kids like yeah yeah I'm in the good time and Charles Durning goes to leave and then he turns around and he goes.
He goes you want to know a trick and the kids like yeah sure he goes you want to know how to get stains out of stainless steel and he's like yeah.
And he goes you clean it first then you wipe it down with boiling water that's get that's what gets the spots off of it permanently and the kid goes thank you and Charles Durning looks at him.
So earnestly it just goes you'll remember I told you that right and you realize like Jesus Christ this guy's like trying to impart something before he dies.
Right like this is his legacy and it is a fucking beautiful moment it's so simple.
Durning you're like though that's why Charles Durning was an actor like there it is right there he look at what he just put into that line.
It's amazing it's a really really I'm not going to say the movie's not without its flaws.
You know I think Montana is competent enough as a director he does some stuff that I'm like you know I didn't like that choice.
But overall it's an interesting watch you will laugh and it is in its classic mammoth dialogue like it's just it's you know again it's foul it's course it's direct.
Stick dialogue I recommend Lakeboat I think it's worth a watch all right all right I'll check it out if I added it to my watch list just now and my last one is called close it is.
Indie movie a 24 put it out but it's not a horror movie it's like.
French drama some subtitles.
It is two 13 year old boys who are close you know like so I guess some of it's being French but some of it's just like.
They're little and they like sleep in the same bed when they stay at each other's house and they're just very close they have a very affectionate relationship.
But as they enter their teens at school people start making fun of them people start speculating that they're gay so at first there are girls asking are you guys a couple.
And they're like no but then the boys at school start making fun of them about it and one of the two boys starts to pull away from the other so he just abandons him and their friendship.
In favor of doing more masculine things to kind of take this speculation off of him and this really deeply hurts the other boy.
Then it goes into in my opinion some kind of a bit of a hallmark or a a tiered jerkery path that I didn't care for as much in the second half it's very depressing and not nearly as interesting as what goes on in the first half.
To me that's a really interesting story about that time and a kids life where you're like hey this thing that you've been doing your whole life is now going to make people make fun of you or speculate about you etc.
They also don't tell you whether these kids are having gay feelings for each other it's kind of left open to you.
And doing any material like this with children is always a little uncomfortable but the movie doesn't feel that way at all it definitely doesn't feel exploitative or anything like that my guess is it's PG 13 but I don't know.
It was really it was something especially the first half I had never seen anything like it and I really enjoyed it the second half works it's just kind of more obvious and more.
You know sometimes it's just sort of like misery porn at a certain point and I rather they had just kept exploring the issues they were exploring personally but it's a good movie check it out I would imagine it'll be streaming shortly I rented it for like three bucks or something.
Which brings us to the howling Mr Joe danti a film that like myself is over 40 years old and Joe.
Oh yeah now I've never seen any of the sequels I am the how have you seen all what isn't the second one called like your sister's a werewolf your sister's a werewolf it was also called.
I think it was called dog bitch in oversee I'm not kidding I think that's literally what it was called overseas yeah it's but it's the sequel is based on the sequel novel like it is.
You know there was a there was a sequel novel to the original novel and the sequel is based on it in fact the howling.
For I think is reborn or whatever that one apparently follows the original novel a little more closely than the Joe Dante movie does yeah I've seen the sequel the sequels a wild ride starring Christopher Lee as like a van Helsing type werewolf hunter.
It's very sexually charged it's super 80s like it's it's it's a scene that second that second movie is a scene I wouldn't say it's good is it worth a watch that's up to you.
I'll probably watch you know I I certainly think if you if you like a bit of of the marriage you want to you'd probably have a fun time watching the sequel because it's it's pretty fucking goofy.
I tried to watch the later installments because I was like well these are tried to wear with movies even though they're direct they were directed videos.
They they from what I remember they just sucked but I'm not against revisiting them.
This this initial film is the film I mean there's a reason that it's still talked about you know yeah I like the howling a lot it was substantially rewritten by John sales.
It's one of the great all time independent filmmakers and really an under scene filmmaker criteria is put out a few of his movies but my big recommendation for him is this movie called loan star.
With which with Chris Christofferson Matthew McConaughey there's tons of great people in it but that is a perfect screenplay it's like a novel I really urge you to watch loan star.
But it's amazing he got his start in master movies before he he kind of branched off and started doing his own independence he did piranha for Dante and he did the howling as well.
So for me this movies best scene really is pre wear wolf stuff I love this opening it's like a great grind house opening where D Wallace is a news anchor who's being stalked by the serial killer and she does this police sting to capture him meet him in like a porn booth she goes in she's this very graphic video.
So the police enter kill him and the news anchor is kind of suffering from the PTSD basically horribly horribly frightening scene.
Now it is and it's shot really excitingly like I just was like wow I don't even remember this and the reason I didn't is because it has nothing to do with the movie but it's a great cold open.
There's there's a reason for that so two things about this cold open number one the cold open made me go I got to buy the 4k of this.
The DVD looks really cool because the DVD does have a VHS green equality to it so I'm going to keep the DVD but the 4k I was like these reds and these colors I mean it's just stunning.
But the interesting thing about the cold open is Joe Dante said that they were making this movie at a time when the studio said well nobody wants to see a werewolf movie everybody wants to see a slasher movie he goes so we made an opening that like a slasher movie.
The part where it's the killers I don't remember if you said this but it's he played by Robert Picardo he which is so stable.
See him in something like this because yeah aside from this and him playing the mags whatever the witch in legend Robert Picardo always plays pretty affable like kind of goofy lovable guy I think he was like a Nickelodeon sitcom too.
Yeah I was I was like the alternate universe David cross you know sure but he he when he's standing behind her and he's talking to her and that booth and she's he's playing the snuff film and then he's like and he's like turn around and his voice like goes into that weird modulated whatever like yeah it's a really creepy scene.
And it's so funny talking about a different time when when the cop just kills him and then the like police chief and everybody come down there like what the hell happened here in his partners just like I don't know ask trigger happy like you like that's a different conversation these days yeah yeah.
But the that cold open is great and it sets up that she needs to be sent away to this the carabee can't yeah the colony which when she arrives is she's greeted by a bonfire on the beach where they're cooking prime rib on open flame everybody's drinking and dancing I'm like this looks like a fucking blast yeah like oh my God they're all living in these beautiful log cabins and.
Right you know and then the madness begins the penny drops as they say yeah basically you know a werewolf breeding ground out here well you learn eventually at the end of the movie that these are where this is their society right and the doctor who sends her up there who's also there moderating the colony
you learn is also aware of and he basically has you know it's that classic storyline and this might have been the first time anybody ever did this storyline I don't know but it's the concept of we need to evolve societies evolving we can't kill and eat people anymore we have to like go to a place where we grow our own food meaning animals and eat it.
And you find out later that that the most of the wolves are not happy about that they want to be feral and wild and free as they always were particularly.
I'm John what's his name yeah my brain sucks Jesus I'm carrying John carries this doing he's he's played a real wild he tries to kill himself.
At the picnic or the beach bonfire yeah and you don't know why but he's complaining about his teeth can't go on like this I can't go on like this you realize later it's because he's a goddamn werewolf right he doesn't want to eat steak and what's the people also have Dennis Dugan in this film the director of happy Gilmore big daddy Jack and Jill grown ups etc he's in he's got a pretty substantial role in this yeah it's like third building yeah.
As D Wallace and her husband are at this camp and seeing weird things sort of unfold like hearing howls in the night and that sort of thing.
Her colleagues one of them being the guy you just mentioned and then another woman who are a couple in the movie are doing research about werewolves and slowly piecing together.
Our friend might be in the company of wolves up at this place and we need to go help her this the pinnacle of their research is the scene obviously with dick miller what a great fucking scene that was with him as the proprietor of like the occult store like it you it's it couldn't be more perfectly like you couldn't cast
a guy that's that's running in a colt store just for the money better than dick miller what he's like when they're when he's like yeah that's any he's he's breaking down the werewolves for them he's going yeah that's what they'll tell you but that ain't true about werewolves they can shape shift any times what it called shape shift they don't need to move at the lady's like is that true he's like is it true yeah I got a book that says it's true I don't give a shit
it's a really that's even really made me laugh I he's great dick miller and Robert Picard are in most Joe Dante movies they're the trash man in the burbs I play this the trash man yeah the howling really is probably most known for its transformation Rick Baker was going to do the transformation but left to go do American werewolf in London which Joe I did not hear that mentioned on your list.
Oh because I never finished my list I was waiting I was waiting to talk about the howling American werewolf in London is my number one yes the wolf man starring Lawn Cheney junior the original is my number five because it's the OG it is right where it all begins I would argue that some of the other Lawn Cheney junior wolf man movies are probably you could say are probably
constructurally better then the wolf man the original wolf man is got to give it in the top five my number two is the howling I think that this is a great wherewolf movie I think that the the fuckin transformation scene with Picardo in that when he confronts D Wallace finally that that's yeah that's like it goes on for like three minutes it's why it's awesome yeah I mean well that's that's what I was saying so.
So when he left to do American War with in London, which has probably the great transformation
scene, Rob Boateen, who is another sort of legendary special effects makeup guy stepped
up.
And it clearly he decided this was kind of his time to really shine because this really
gives it a run for its money.
The transformation work here is amazing.
They do just stay on it forever.
They're not using a bunch of camera tricks.
It looks great.
And most of the effects are practical or at least seem practical.
Like, could they even use like shadows at certain points because they didn't have the
money to do, you know, certain things like when the werewolves have sex.
Yeah.
There's like a hand drawn animation, which the last time I think that's ever occurred was
in the Batman Tim Burton Batman, there's like the hand drawn overhead shot of Batman walking.
But that adds such a cool little element.
I like that it looks like a cartoon figure like it adds like this cool stylistic element to
it.
But the transformation, the choices they made, it's not just that makeup wise, it looks awesome
and it looks scary because his eyes are this color and his fangs look like this.
The choices they make were like his skin is like becomes like tumored and is like bubbling.
Yeah.
It's so gross.
And then she throws the acid on his face to get away.
DeWalist does.
And then when her friend, the Adam Sandler director, shows up to save the day, he goes into that
same room and Picardo comes back in.
He's for some reason changed back into a person, I guess, because of the acid.
And now that that practical effect there is incredible where like his fucking skull is showing.
It looks right.
Yeah.
It's so unsettling, man.
Like, it's, it's awesome.
What an awesome, awesome, practical effects movie this is.
It's a very cool movie.
It led directly to Dante getting gremlins, which I think is even better than explorers, which
I've never seen.
Have you seen that, Joe?
Yeah.
Many times.
I watched it constantly as a kid.
I loved it.
I have no idea how I would have missed that, but and I just watched it again recently.
It's, you know, it's a kids movie.
It's, it's very endearing.
It's a very sweet kids movie.
It's interesting, too, because River Phoenix plays out of the three kids.
He plays the nerd.
Okay.
Yeah.
And that was when I first saw River Phoenix and something like little, didn't you know, he
was going to be like the heart throb and everything else he ever fucking did.
But explorers is, yeah, it's, it's, I don't know if you watched it now.
You would be like, that's a really good kids movie.
I don't know if you'd enjoy it, though, you know, I'll watch it tonight.
Um, but that run, I promise fine, but piranha, the hollering, gremlins, explorers, interspace,
the burbs, gremlins to matinee, which I love.
Small soldiers are taking a step down, loony tunes back in action, you're taking a step
down.
And any, I own the whole, but I ain't never seen the whole and bearing the X.
I don't even know what that is.
I will say this about loony tunes back in action.
Yeah.
Uh, as far as loony tunes back in action goes, you're, you got the best version of that.
You were going to get with Joe Dante.
It's not a good movie, right.
But Joe Dante is Joe Dante for a reason.
That's basically as good as you were going to get.
Um, but, but back to the, to the howling, uh, it's got a great ending on it.
And the ending is that, you know, you're, the, I didn't remember how it ended.
So what I thought was going to happen, because if you look up the movie, you'll see one of
the things you, one of the pictures they always show is D Wallace with her eyes glowing, right.
I assumed that because I couldn't remember the ending that it was like, Oh, it's going
to be that classic.
They save the day.
And then it's, this is the ending of Bore Dello of blood.
They're walking off to, to go now be in love as the two survivors and then all of a sudden
the woman turns and re -realize, Oh, God, she got bitten by a wolf and we didn't realize it.
And the end of the thriller video, yes, which is another amazing werewolf transformation,
which is also, I think the same guys, yeah, same thing, the bubbling of the skin.
Anyway, um, but that's not the ending.
The ending, you see her get bit in the climax and you're like, what the fuck?
They're just going to show that she got bit.
That's not, how are they going to have a twist now?
Right.
And they still do have a twist.
And the twist is, as a news anchor, she's going to go on the air for the first time and transform
in front of people on camera.
And then her friend is going to kill her, yes, on camera because that's what they need to do
to prove that this is real and that people need to be aware that these beasts are among us.
And they do it.
And in fact, that is how the sequel starts out.
It starts out at her funeral and her brother is there and Christopher Lee shows up.
And he's like, your sister was aware of a wolf.
That's why it's called that.
Right.
It's a pretty wild fucking ending then met with an almost sitcom button,
where it cuts to guys watching the movie, the news footage in a bar.
One guy goes, they can do anything with special effects these days.
Another guy goes, that was real.
That just happened.
She turned into a damn wolf and he killed her.
And but he's saying it without emotion.
Yeah.
And then the next guy goes, you're drunk and he goes, so doesn't mean it wasn't real.
And then you land on the end of the bar and this woman who's one of the werewolves who was a nymphomaniac.
That they just that you meet earlier in the film.
She's still alive.
You think she perished when they burned the colony down the end of the film and she's still alive.
And she goes and the guy next to her goes, all of a pepper steak.
And can I get a burger for the lady?
And you hear off camera, the bartender say, how do you want that burger cooked?
She looks into camera, breaks the fourth wall and goes bloody.
Yeah.
Sometimes old Joe doesn't get the balance just right.
Sometimes he gets it perfect as a gremlins with the comedy and the other stuff.
But yeah, that little bit of a weird ending.
But it's a tight 90 minute starts as a serial killer thing goes into a weird cult beach party thing,
goes into a werewolf adventure.
And it all works.
I really, I think it's a really good movie.
Yeah, I like the howling quite a bit.
My hog is up solidly for it.
Could there be improvements, of course, or there are things that they would probably do
a bit differently nowadays, sure, but from a structural standpoint,
from a storytelling standpoint, from an acting standpoint.
And definitely from a fixed standpoint, it bangs on all cylinders.
It's what you want.
I agree.
I do have it in 4k.
It certainly looked a lot better than the last time I watched it, which was probably VHS.
So yeah, I would recommend the upgrade on it.
Sometimes, you know, the 80s ones don't look as good.
It's best, I always say read a couple reviews before you make a dip.
But for the most part, these 4k have been knockin' me out.
I am on only Instagram at the Patrick Walsh.
The Miss Pat show is airing on BT Plus.
And I am on a strike.
I don't have much to announce.
I want to plug.
Oh, well, actually, I do.
The Taste Buds live stream got postponed.
Unfortunately, so I got COVID the day of, which was a real bummer.
But it's now happening May 31st at 9pm.
Moment .co slash Taste Buds.
To get your ticket, if you already had a ticket, it's been transferred.
And if you can't make it, you can get a refund through Moment .co.
Thanks for bearing with us on that.
And come to Joey Roses if you're here in New York City.
Joey Roses NYC .com for all information.
We're open seven days a week.
Sandwiches full bar.
You know the deal.
We will be back with some good stuff.
We love you all.
We'll see you next time.
And we'll see you in hell.