I'll see you in hell.
And when the sound of your screams becomes a thing of my dreams, you know I'll say.
You know I will.
I'll see you in hell.
Folks, it's We'll See You in Hell.
Here we go.
Another rep.
Hello, my friend, Joe.
Yeah.
I love it. Is this going to be the new on with the Joe?
No, I didn't. It didn't wind up in the last cut.
Oh, that's right, because we had to restart.
You just ruined it.
Sorry.
You should have been like, haha.
That's a great new thing you just did, Pat.
That's what I was, yeah, I thought. I was very touched.
Very flattered.
Go ahead. What's that?
No, I thought you said you were alright, Spider.
Yeah, folks, we're here. We're queer. Get used to it.
I wanted to talk right off the bat so we don't forget, because we forgot last time, a little news psycho.
Blumhouse, Joe's favorite studio.
The horror studio behind Get Out and Megan is extending its reach from the big screen to the real world.
They are launching a new exhibit at the Stanley Hotel in Estes Park, known as the inspiration for Stephen King's The Shining.
They're curating the Stanley Film Center Exhibit Space, a mini -academy museum dedicated to horror, drawing from Blumhouse's catalog of film, TV, and game offerings.
That's what bothered me a little bit.
What's that?
It's a museum just devoted to Blumhouse?
I thought this was going to be a cool horror museum, and what better place than The Shining Hotel?
Pat, what part of my ranting and raving that Jason Blum is an egomaniac has not registered yet?
The guy is out of control. He is a massive egomaniac.
Yeah.
He just is, you know?
No, that really annoyed me when I read that, because I was like, look, I might like to go up to this if they're turning The Shining Hotel into a cool new horror museum,
but I don't need to see the best artifacts from, I mean, I can't even think of one of their fucking movies right now.
Hey guys, here's the red door from the last Insidious movie.
Right.
Isn't that cool?
You're like, what?
Here's some ornaments from the fourth Black Christmas remake.
It's like, I just don't give a shit.
I've only been in the parking lot of The Shining Hotel because I was there.
I've been to Colorado twice, once with Joe early on in our friendship and podcast, and once with some friends, and we went to The Shining Hotel and it was closed.
It was a real bummer, but we saw it from the outside and it was very cool.
But yeah, it's just kind of like, who do you think you are, man?
Like, what Blumhouse artifacts do we need?
Is it the new Michael Myers mask?
Yeah.
Who cares?
Replica of drumstick used by Miles Teller.
Okay, I guess.
Yeah.
Even the good movies, I wouldn't give a shit.
It's too new.
If you showed me Get Out memorabilia, Get Out's a good movie, but if you showed me Get Out memorabilia, I'd be like, I don't care.
It just happened a couple of years ago.
That's not memorabilia to me.
Memorabilia is like, you know, hey, here are the slippers from Wizard of Oz, like shit like that.
We're like, wow, that's pretty cool.
I mean, it'll be the Get Out teacup.
Like, I think Get Out's a masterpiece.
I don't think that there's a lot of memorable props from the film.
I don't know.
It's a bummer to me.
And I love the idea.
I love the idea of a horror museum at The Shining Hotel.
It's genius.
And yet, and yet that's the problem.
Guys, these are actual discarded Activia containers that were eaten by Jamie Lee Curtis in between takes.
And then she would actually shit during the takes.
Can I tell you something from last night?
And we still haven't found the culprit.
You ever been on the subway?
I mean, look, you live in New York.
You've been on the subway when there's the piss smell.
Everyone has.
It's kind of the defining smell of the subway and of New York at times.
It's my favorite Ben Bailey joke because he goes, smells like piss.
Now, I have a theory.
I think people are pissing down there.
I don't even know who Ben Bailey is.
He's a comic.
He was the host of Cash Cab, the famous comic.
Oh, sure.
OK.
Anyway, go ahead.
I'm sorry.
No, it's just there.
There's very few times in my life where I have known.
OK, someone in this area has shat their pants because that's a whole nother thing.
Now you can.
I've definitely sat next to a unhoused person on the subway who you can tell has some shit going on or something.
But I'm at work last night on the Miss Pat show.
We did two episodes, one at two and one at six.
That used to be how Multicam worked.
You do two episodes.
We don't do that anymore.
I've never been on a show that's done that.
But last night, Raven Simone, the Cosby kid, was directing our episode.
She did a fantastic job.
She's been doing it for a long time.
But she wanted to do one at two and one at six.
So you get two shots at it.
Right.
So it's a long fucking day.
And last night I'm getting out about 11 or whatever.
And you do the whole cast bow thing where everybody comes out from the cast lowest to highest and the audience applauds.
I'm standing there with a few of the writers and we're clapping for the cast as they come out.
And I swear to God, and I've reached a point in my life where I know the difference between a shit and a fart, Joe.
The smell started pummeling my nostrils of somebody in my very near vicinity has shat their pants.
It is an unmistakable odor.
And the two writers I'm standing with, I'm like, this is so awkward because one of my coworkers has shat their pants.
It was close and it was pungent.
And I looked at both of them and they were both reacting like, oh, my God, who just shat their pants.
So me and I'm not going to say names, but me and my buddy from the show quickly walk away from the smell.
And immediately the smell was gone.
And we were like, oh, no, it's the third guy.
He shat his pants.
To confirm or deny, I go over and ask him, hey, did you find out who shat themselves?
And I don't smell it on him.
We never got an answer.
But somebody in a workplace, and when I really thought about it, sadly, tragically, it was probably somebody on the crew.
They're going to say Raven Simone.
I was like, Jesus.
No, but my guess is when it's a multi -camera show, you got guys up on seated cranes almost.
They're sitting up high like in a bulldozer.
And I think somebody was probably sitting up there shooting the show, thought he could make it.
Because I've never seen a cameraman go, hey, stop production.
I got to go to the bathroom.
I've never seen it.
Time is money.
I bet he sat up there and thought he'd be fine and shat his fucking pants.
Because it was so strong and pungent and disgusting.
It was a fresh shit.
Like we were standing there as the shit emerged from the colon.
As you do.
All right.
Well, there you go.
Not the way you want to end the work week.
I got to tell you.
Well, while we're on, ouch, while we're on personal stories, scenes from our lives, we'll call it.
Sure.
This morning, I was -
You shat your pants.
I shat my pants.
I was woken, awakened, awoken.
I'm at my house right now, the doorbell ringing repeatedly.
What time?
About 8 a .m.
Now, I actually would have been awake already, but I woke up at 4 a .m. with -
Me too.
What I can only describe as a unfounded panic.
I don't even know what it was caused by.
So somewhere around 5 a .m., I fell back asleep and I said, all right, I can sleep till like 9 and then get up.
Right.
So like quarter to 8, 8, the doorbell starts.
I'm just completely disoriented.
I'm like, what is going on?
It's the ring, knock, knock, knock, ring, knock, knock, knock.
And I mean repeatedly.
Yeah.
To the point I'm coming down the stairs.
Like, you know, man named Otto style.
Like, all right.
Probably the first person to ever reference man with Otto in that way.
You know how we all know how he did in that movie.
So I'm just like, I'm like, all right.
You know, like curmudgeon -y guy coming to the door.
Yeah.
I opened the door to what would make any grown man comfortable?
A small child.
Yeah.
I'm like, what is going on right now?
I'm immediately thrown off.
I'm like, yes, can I help you?
Did we have a date?
I said Friday, sweetie.
No, it's a kid and she's like, I don't know, 10 maybe, I would guess 10.
Okay.
She's very nervous and she's doing the thing where a kid, like a nervous kid is talking to you
and she's like squirming and like won't stop her feet from shuffling and stuff.
Yeah.
And on top of it, she's not making a ton of sense.
Not because of anything other than she's a kid and she's like clearly terrified.
Right.
I'm like, hi, can I help you?
I'm thinking she's going to be selling something for school or something.
And she's like, I miss my bus.
If I don't get to school, I'm in so much trouble.
And I was like, what are you talking about?
And she's like, I miss my bus.
If I don't get to school, my mom is going to be so mad at me.
And I was like, okay.
I assume you threw her in the car and took her to school.
Right, Joe?
Yeah.
It's a bunch of neighbors watched.
Coming to you live from jail.
And I go, hold on a second.
Hold on.
I go, hold on.
You missed your bus.
Yeah.
I go, okay.
What do you need right now?
She goes, my mom is going to be so mad that I miss my bus.
I go, okay, let's call your mom.
She goes, no, she's going to be so mad.
And I go, well, okay.
What school do you go to?
And she goes, I forget the name of it.
I go, all right, I'm going to call your school.
Okay.
I go to shut the door.
And she goes, can I come inside?
And I said, no, you cannot come inside.
Absolutely not.
Which this is the sick fucking world we live in, by the way.
Absolutely.
Yeah, who needs?
The fact that everyone's mind goes to perverts now is, look,
maybe it's obviously it's for the best, but it's also for the worst.
By the way, there's an active bus stop across the street with kids on it.
Yeah.
I mean, this is like a goddamn, you want to talk about running a gauntlet.
A kid comes to your door in need and your minds go, what do I do?
Shouldn't I do?
Whatever.
Right.
So I go, no, just wait outside.
Is it freezing?
So I shut the door.
It's like 38 fucking degrees.
Yeah, okay.
But she was dressed.
I mean, she had a coat.
It wasn't like she was out in the cold.
She was dressed for school.
So I shut the door.
I call the school a couple times.
They don't answer.
Great.
I go back outside.
I don't see her.
I'm like, now I'm like, was this a scam or something?
Like, what is going on?
It's like leave the world behind.
What's going on here?
And then she comes from the side of the house and I'm like, oh, hi.
And I go, listen, I called your school.
They're not answering.
I go, where does your mom work?
And she goes, I don't know.
And I go, I don't know the name of it.
And I go, okay, do you know the number?
And she goes, yeah.
And I go, okay, we have to call your mom.
And she goes, we can't.
She's going to be so mad.
I go, sweetie, it's okay.
She's not going to be mad.
She needs to know that you're okay.
All right.
So we have to call your mom.
And she goes, okay.
And then she goes, she doesn't really speak English though.
So I have to talk to her.
You can't call her.
And I said, okay, do you have her number so we can call her?
And she goes, I can call her from my iPad.
And I said, okay, that's fine.
Whatever you want to do.
She goes, hold on.
I'll be right back.
Let me go get it.
She goes into the house next door.
I go, hold on a second.
You live next door?
She goes, yeah.
I go, wow.
I go, and you can get into your house.
And she goes, yeah.
And she goes inside, comes back out with the iPad.
Yeah.
And calls her mom.
And I go.
That's a parent's fault.
Your parents should give you an action plan for if something goes wrong in the child's
life.
The one part I forgot was when she knocked on the door, she said, is so -and -so here?
And I said, no, she doesn't live here anymore.
It was I guess the lady that lived here before me.
And she called her mom.
And I said, okay, so you're okay, right?
And she goes, yeah.
And I said, what's your name?
And she told me.
And I said, okay, I'm Joe.
And I said, have a good day.
And she went inside her house.
And I went inside my house.
And then I saw I had a missed call from the school.
And I called the school.
And I said, look, I don't know what's going on.
I think her mom's coming to get her, she said.
But this little girl lives next door to me couldn't.
She missed her bus.
I apologize.
I'm blanking on what her name is already.
I just met her.
But anyway, that's why I was calling.
And the lady was like, you're very sweet, sir.
Thank you so much.
And I was like, yeah, no problem.
All right.
I'll talk to you later.
But I mean, what a way to wake up.
What a way to start the day.
I had yesterday a very traumatic wake up as well.
I had to be at work at eight.
And I wake up to three emails from a name I don't recognize,
Michelle something.
And I'm like, what is this?
It says urgent in all caps.
So I'm thinking it's spam.
Normally, I would just delete something like that if I don't recognize them.
But she says I'm your neighbor across the street.
So my house has been left unattended now for two months.
Rob any robbers listening to the show?
Oh, neighbor in L .A.
You mean?
Yeah.
OK.
So I had there were there were two big torrential rainstorms in L .A.
over the last year.
And in the first one, water started coming in my light socket in my bathroom,
like coming through the overhead light socket while it was on.
So the lights on and water is coming out.
I was like, if I turn this off, am I going to kill myself?
I thought it was going to be like Daniel Stern and Home Alone or something where you see my skeleton.
When I turned the light off, I called a roofer.
They come over.
They fully repair my roof.
They're like, you're good.
You had a little hole up there.
It's not a new roof situation.
You're all good.
I go, OK.
The next time there's a rain, which in L .A. is going to be three to four months,
there's water trickling in from up there.
And I call the guy.
I'm like, hey, man, you did not fix this.
It's still coming in.
That's why I hired you was to fix this.
So I can't pay you, but you need to come over and fix it.
Sure.
He was like, no problem.
I got it.
When it stopped raining, he comes by, put up the bucket, whatever.
Problem is, if I don't catch it, it splashes around and damage.
It's that bathroom upstairs, which has really, really cool wallpaper.
And the previous owner really decorated my house beautifully.
And it's it's clearly just really nice, fancy wallpaper.
And it was discolored because the water was splashing up on it.
And it kind of bothered me.
At some point, I'm going to have to redo it.
But the guy comes over.
He goes, all right, you're all good.
I saw what happened.
You know, it must have just been coming down really hard and knocked off my patch.
And now we're all good.
But right before I left, there was a light rain and I walked in to go to the bathroom
and there was a big puddle of water on the floor.
Jesus Christ.
So I'm like, fuck.
And I'm leaving the next day.
But I texted him and I'm like, hey, it didn't work, man.
And like, I don't want you to come over and keep fixing it.
If you're not going to do it, do the work.
But like, I paid you six hundred dollars.
You know, so you do have to come make it so water isn't coming through my roof.
And if I need a new roof, just tell me, like, help me out here.
He's like, yeah, I can't get over there before you leave town.
But let's set it up for when you get back.
This lady texts me or she emails me three times.
I don't have her phone number.
I barely speak to this lady.
And she goes, hey, I'm sorry to alarm you this early in the morning.
But she's like, I just went out for a run and there's the I heard the sound of like
extreme water coming out of your house.
And it was trickling out of your porch and onto the street.
And I'm like, holy shit, I look up, it's been raining in L .A.
and there's extreme rain planned for all week.
And I'm like, holy shit, my house is just flooding.
I'm imagining my furniture being destroyed, my home value being destroyed.
No one back home has a key.
I have somebody coming by to get the mail, but they don't have access to my house.
So I'm looking for plane tickets.
I'm like, I'm just going to call into work.
I got to go back home and see like how badly fucked my life is.
And thankfully, she left her number and I called her before I booked it.
And I'm like, can you just do me a solid and just like stay on the phone with me
and put my mind at ease?
And she's like, yeah, I gave her the code to my porch.
She gets onto the porch.
She's looking around.
I go, can you turn your phone around and show me what it looks like inside my house?
Looked completely perfect and normal.
I was like the verge of tears.
I thought this is the, you know, not only the most valuable thing I own, but by
about a billion percent, the most valuable thing I own is my house.
And she's looking in.
She's like, I don't see any water on the floor.
And I'm like, all right.
Well, if that bathroom is filling up with water, then it would have trickled out.
Like she would have been able to see it.
But I'm like, are there other spots?
Do you see, do you see any other leaking or water coming in?
She goes, no.
And she goes, oh, wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
She goes over and it turns out I had a busted sprinkler head.
It's like, thank Christ.
It was an outside situation.
My sprinklers are on a timer.
So it's going to happen, you know, a few more times while I'm away.
But it's just, you know, it's one of those things where you just got water spraying off
into the distance and it's no big deal.
To say, I mean, I thought it's, it's my house is so full of water.
It's seeping out into the street.
That's, I mean, that's a panic like none other.
That's ridiculous.
That's quite a relief, quite a relief, but it made me realize that I can't just leave
my house unattended anymore.
I got to have somebody go by with the key and check on it and just pay them and do
whatever I got to do.
Cause it was too, too stressful.
That sucks.
Yeah.
And how fragile, you know, life is like these people who get their basement flooded
and lose like every photograph they've ever taken and all that.
It's like, yeah, tough.
It's horrible.
I don't really keep anything of value around my movie collection, my vet, my vinyl
collection, boy guy, I didn't even think about that.
You know, like going up my, uh, my vinyl rack, just like taking it out, that would
have destroyed those.
Yeah.
It's terrible, man.
I need a new plan for the house.
I, uh, come into ATL.
Well, that roofer thing, man, almost sounds like a, almost sounds like a hustle.
Like I'm going to keep fucking shitty.
Like anytime I'm going to keep miss fixing it.
So then you can, you'll go, then when I hit you with the w it's going to cost 20
grand thing, you're like, okay, just please whatever.
Yeah, probably.
You know, like what a fucking asshole, man.
Either way, whether he's hustling you or not, what an asshole.
Yeah.
He came down.
I'm like, so how do I know you did it right on the second time he came?
And he goes, um, well here, I can show you on my phone.
I'll go up there and take a picture and then I'll show you on my phone.
I'm like, okay.
So then he shows me like a picture of the roof.
I'm like, yeah, I realize I don't even know enough about roofs to know
if he did it right.
That's the problem is my fucking dad, who was a carpenter, mind you, never
taught me how to do a single thing.
And I, you know, as soon as I'm honest with these guys that I don't
know, I'm sure they just see dollar signs in their eyes.
I don't know how to do plumbing or anything.
It's not, I don't know.
Everybody's a shit.
Everybody's shit.
They see me like the housewife who brings in the Buick and they, you
know, with a busted windshield wiper and they hit her up for $3 ,000 repairs.
I'm at the same level of knowledge.
Yeah.
I need to get some paperwork drawn up and my cousin's a lawyer and I was
talking to my cousin about it and he's like kind of advising me and stuff.
And I go, what should this cost?
He's like, yeah, these are pretty boilerplate docs.
Three grand.
Right.
About three grand.
I go, okay.
I'll let you know what he says.
I talked to the lawyer I was going to hire.
I go, you know, just basics, ins and outs.
Here's all the information.
You know, we talked about the other day.
As you said, as you said, meaning the lawyer, this is a very simple process.
How long will it take you?
What's your rate?
She's like, well, my rate's about 400 an hour, but he's like, low end.
6, 6 ,500 will go from there.
Low end.
Yeah.
And I go, yeah, I'm going to have to think about that because I'm going to
whatever.
I don't want to.
It's nothing bad.
I just don't want to give too many details here.
It's just a private matter.
But I said, I'm going to pay.
I said, the whole reason for doing this is for me not to pay money, a lot of money on
something.
And now I'm going to pay you that amount.
Yeah.
Just to, for protection or whatever.
And he goes, he goes, yeah, well, I mean, you know, what we're doing here though,
we're trying to protect you to make.
And I'm like, right.
I go, well, I just have to think about it.
And he goes, okay, you think about it.
You get back to me.
And I'm like, anytime they dismiss you like that, it's like, yep.
Oh, you're doing a fast one.
Yeah.
Okay.
You're an asshole.
Thank you.
Fuck off.
Yeah.
Okay.
You think about it.
That's like, I'm not wasting any more time because I can't take advantage of you.
And I thought I could is what that means.
So anyway, let's go to the movie corner.
I have, I have just the opposite to discuss today in the movie corner from people ripping
us off.
I want to discuss my theme for the movie corner today is, is rogues, rogues, people
waving their middle finger at the way it gets done.
I'm going to start with a document.
It's three documentaries I watched about radicals and rogues in the art industry.
And I'm going to start with radical wolf, the Tom Wolf documentary.
What a fabulous doc.
I loved every minute of this thing.
Have you ever read a Tom Wolf book?
I haven't.
And I am ordering them presently.
So what inspired you to, what inspired you to watch it?
I was on a plane.
Okay.
Yeah.
And I said, this, this looks like a good plane thing to watch.
And I thought Tom Wolf was Tobias Wolf.
And I had seen that movie.
Yeah.
Great.
I was like, I'll watch a doc about this guy.
And, and then I was watching it.
I was like, wait, Tobias Wolf was gay.
What is, wait a minute.
He's got a wife and kid.
Well, I realized it's not the same person.
I didn't know Tobias Wolf was gay.
Well, in the movie, in the movie, he kisses his best friend.
Like they, they insinuated in the movie that he's gay.
So I thought he would, you know, no recollection.
Yeah.
Anyway, maybe he wasn't, but.
I fucking love that movie.
Wait, are you thinking of basketball diaries?
No, no, no.
De Niro and, and yeah.
He kisses his friend on the lips when they're playing piano.
Oh, I do remember that.
I do remember that.
Yes.
Anyway.
That's a really underrated movie.
I used to love that fucking movie.
It's okay.
I need to watch it again.
Yeah.
I haven't seen it in years, but anyway.
So I was hooked from the, from the jump of this thing.
Here's why.
Here's why this guy now fascinates me.
I love any writer who is universally lauded.
Any person who is universally lauded in the entertainment industry.
Who does not follow the paint by numbers, political ethos or pathos,
whatever the word is of this industry.
Like I really like when that happens.
And Tom Wolf is one of these characters.
He's somebody who repeatedly they say throughout this movie.
Like I, you know, interviewing people from like the New Yorker being like,
look, I didn't always agree with this politics,
but the guy is one of the greatest writers that's ever lived.
He could take you apart at the seams with one sentence.
Yeah.
I love that his foundation was kind of built and based in the fact
that he came up from nothing as a boy from the South,
got into Yale and hated how condescending and elitist
the wealthy liberal class at Yale was to him.
And kind of that started his trajectory.
And you know, the thing he's most famous for outside of the right stuff
and Bonfire of the Vanities is, you know,
he wrote that piece called Radical Chic,
which was about Leonard Bernstein hosting the Black Panthers at his apartment.
And they're reading excerpts from this thing.
And it's so fucking funny, man, where he's just being like,
he's talking about like the cheese balls and he's like, they are divine.
The way the almond, the almond covering cuts so gently through the cheese.
I wonder if the Black Panthers prefer their cheese balls like this.
It's really, really, really funny shit.
And I was like, I gotta, I gotta read all this, man.
This guy, I find him fascinating.
And, you know, quite frankly, it just reminds me of a better time.
And, you know, I blame both sides of the political aisle for this now.
You can't go on anything anymore
without it being either you subscribing to the belief system of that thing
or being completely challenged on your belief system on that thing.
And this is, you know, you see a guy like this talking with
members of the conservative media and members of the liberal media,
and they're just having conversations.
They're just having conversations.
He's talking to Dick Cavett.
He's talking to William F. Buckley.
And I was like, that is how it's supposed to be.
It is not supposed to be that just because you do an interview on Fox News
or on CNN, just for lack of better examples,
that that interview is about your defense
or condemnation of a political belief system.
And unfortunately, that's where we're at now.
But I really enjoyed what it just it just seemed to me like a better time
where people could say, I don't agree with you on stuff,
but, man, I admire your talent.
I admire your wit and I enjoy your writing and your work
and vice versa with him as an author.
So I found it fascinating.
And I look forward to reading some of his stuff very much in the vein of
Nora Efron, which I've talked about in recent months.
She's very similar to me, but from the other side of the aisle,
she definitely does not lean conservative.
But she's very similar to me, where she's a true liberal,
where those beliefs come across in the work,
but they're not what define her.
And she's not condemning anybody that doesn't think that way.
And she's just saying, this is who I am.
And it's wonderful.
And these types of writers, these opinionated writers who are so scathingly funny,
they're just hard to come by anymore.
They're just really, really hard to come by anymore.
I think maybe I'm wrong and we're not well read enough, but.
Yeah, I'll check it out.
I've never read any of his books.
I own several of them.
I realize sometimes I am much, much less well.
I read a bunch up until I hit the workforce, basically, and then I just stopped.
Yeah.
And I would love to read more than I do.
But lately, it's got to be nonfiction, self -help, et cetera.
I rarely get into a fiction book anymore, and I'd like to change that.
But if I didn't do it over the pandemic, I'm not going to do it.
Well, I only got halfway through.
I got to finish it.
But through the Toni Morrison documentary, which is also great,
but I'm not reviewing because I haven't finished it yet.
But I just went and bought yesterday, Beloved and The Bluest Eye.
Yeah.
I'm enjoying these documentaries and learning about other artists recently.
And trying to explore their work.
I watched Self -Reliance on Hulu.
The Hulu original game is weak as fuck.
We're talking about a Hulu original this week on the show, too, with No One Will Save You.
But has there been a great Hulu original?
I don't know.
I know people really love that Palm Springs movie.
I thought it was a pretty solid flick, but they haven't had a great one.
Hellraiser, and they got a horror arm and all that.
Well, Homecoming was Hulu, wasn't it?
Amazon.
Oh, okay.
All right.
I don't mind.
Hulu shows.
I'm talking Hulu original movies for the most part.
Oh, okay.
I got you.
And this movie looks like a Fox pilot from five years ago.
It's written, starring, and directed by Jake Johnson from New Girl.
I know that show has its big fans.
I watched it for a couple of seasons and thought it was pretty solid,
but I'm not obsessive like some.
I like Jake Johnson.
I played poker with the man many, many times.
I really could not stand this movie, though.
I really could not stand it.
I think it's really badly directed.
The premise doesn't work.
The script doesn't work.
There's improv moments scattered about this very tight narrative that don't work
because the movie's not functioning as a comedy.
It's not funny at all.
I don't know.
It's trying to have everything.
It's trying to have its cake and eat it too.
It's trying to be disturbing and funny and suspenseful,
and it winds up being nothing.
When a man is offered a million dollars to play a game on a reality show,
or it's not a reality show.
That's the kind of dumber thing about it.
When a man is offered a million dollars to play a game in which hunters try to kill him,
he thinks he has found the perfect loophole.
They can only attack when he's alone.
His only problem is that none of his friends or family believe that the game is real.
He enlists a homeless guy played by Biff Wyff from the very funny
I Think You Should Leave sketch to hang out with him
because these mysterious people who are maybe going to kill him
can't attack unless he's alone.
Which guy is Biff Wyff on I Think You Should Leave?
He was the Santa Claus guy.
Oh, okay. That's what I thought.
There's a romance in there with Anna Kendrick that doesn't hit.
He has a scene with Christopher Lloyd as his father in the backseat of a car that doesn't hit.
There's a scene that opens the movie.
He's walking down the street.
That's how the movie starts.
He's walking along.
Andy Samberg pulls up in the back of a limo, rolls down the window.
And I'm like, what?
I knew Andy Samberg produced the movie.
And then I heard what should have just made me turn the movie off, honestly,
because I knew it wasn't for me.
First line of the movie is, are you Andy Samberg?
Oh, boy.
He's not playing some mysterious guy.
He's playing Andy Samberg.
And, God, it just sucks, man.
And I think Jake Japherson is a funny and smart guy.
This is just a Biff Wyff.
Sometimes your first time out of the gate, you don't got it.
But I couldn't stand it, and I wish I didn't watch it.
It put me in a terrible mood.
It looks bad.
Scenes are staged and shot badly.
Just not a good film.
And I also don't believe that guy going to his family and being like,
they're going to kill me.
I need people to stay close to me, OK?
Like, how hard is that for someone in your extended family to go,
sure, yeah, I'll hang out with you?
They don't paint him as like this repellent, awful guy.
OK, I don't even know if I believe you,
but I can hang out with you for the next 24 hours to make sure you don't get shot.
It's like it didn't do the bare minimum of just like making sure we believe any of this.
And I hated it.
So next.
Next Rogue documentary or documentary about Rogue I watched was a Quincy.
About Quincy Jones.
I guess this was on.
God, I want to say HBO Max, but I don't have HBO Max.
What the hell did I see Quincy on?
I saw it on something.
Anyway, it was awesome.
Quincy Jones, just the man, the myth, the legend, the the the the the it's wild.
The ground that this guy broke in the entertainment industry, the effect he had on it.
I mean, this is it's just nuts.
Yeah, like him talking about literally growing up so poor they used to eat rat.
It was like like my grandmother cooked whatever meat she could get and we would eat rats.
He talks about like he's like he's like one point he's on Dr.
Dre's podcast and he's showing him like scars.
Yeah.
Like you see this on my hand.
That's from when I was 11.
These kids stabbed a switch blade through my hand to a to a fence.
I'm like, Jesus Christ, man.
Like, yeah, insane, insane obstacles.
This guy overcame.
Then he gets into the music industry.
He starts composing and he's like, this is a time when like black people were not allowed to compose for cinema.
And he just breaks down every boundary and not just becomes successful, becomes a titan unmatched.
Like talks about how Frank Sinatra was like, you are the guy.
Period.
And then so not like talking about when he first started working with Sinatra in Vegas,
how they make him and Sammy Davis or him and Count Basie stay across town because it was segregated.
And then Sinatra was like, we're going to change that.
And they did.
Then like him doing all the stuff with Michael Jackson and we are the world.
And then like then he gets into the eighties and nineties and he does the back on the block album and he works with all the rappers
because he's like, this is the next thing.
And like, you know, like and just constantly, constantly, constantly doing, making strides and making amazing music
and then also pushing everything forward for the cause of black culture and fair treatment of black artists and all this stuff.
And, you know, he did the color purple for Christ sakes.
It's like it's wild, the shit that this guy has done.
And the whole movie is kind of like built around the crux of he's being asked to speak at the opening of this of this museum about black artists in America and the history of it.
And he has to curate the event.
And it's all kind of built around that.
But it's also built around the fact that he's he's old.
And then when the time of this was shot, he was approaching 80.
He has like two strokes in the movie because he's diabetic.
He has the first one pretty early on in the movie.
And Rashida Jones is, I think, kind of she's with him through the whole thing.
I think she's kind of helming the ship of the documentary.
Yeah.
And he's in the hospital recovering from like a diabetic stroke.
And you're like, what happened?
And the doctor's like, you have been drinking too much.
And he's not like a fall down drunk.
He's just like, yeah, baby, I party like I work hard.
I play hard. I'm up around the clock.
Yeah, I drink.
I've got a wonderful family.
They love me.
And there's never the part where the other shoe drops.
There's never the part where where it's like, you know, and then the bastard side of him is seen like that never happens.
You know, he they do talk about how he's married a couple of times.
They talk about how he wasn't the most faithful guy.
Right.
But, you know, I don't know.
Like, I know that's not great, but like it's like you're kind of waiting like if this other side of him is going to emerge.
And it never really does, which is a relief, because that's how these documentaries always seem to go.
Eventually, at some point, when somebody that great, you know, that's why I always say I hate watching a biopic.
Every biopic should be subtitled.
Remember when you liked this guy?
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
And both in the Tom Wolf one and in this one, like none of that ever occurs, which is is nice to see.
Is this the Quincy Dock from five years ago or is this a new thing?
Oh, I saw that.
OK, I saw that.
And the great there's a great final spoiler alert.
There's a great final line.
The last clip is he's in an interview as it's going to the credits and the reporter goes, it might even be Barbara Walters.
She goes, my God, movies, music, composer, conductor.
Charity.
Is there anything you're not good at?
And he goes, uh, marriage.
You and me both quints.
Anyway, it's a really wonderful film.
One of those ones where I immediately called my mom and said, you should really watch this.
This is really good.
There you go.
I saw so I've had people requesting this this title and I have seen it and I will talk about it.
The Curse on Showtime or Paramount Plus.
I was very excited about this.
I love everybody involved.
It is Nathan Fielder.
It is Benny Safdie, one of the Safdie brothers who did Uncut Gems and Good Time and Emma Stone.
Majority of the episodes were written and directed by either Fielder and or Safdie, sometimes together.
And Emma Stone plays the wife of Nathan Fielder.
I am not going to spoil the finale, but this is a 10 episode show that should have been six.
That's often the case these days.
It is so I'm watching this thing getting increasingly frustrated with it.
It just keeps bringing up new stories and not really going anywhere with them.
When the show ends, I would argue that none of these stories and loose ends have been tied up in any way.
So obviously that's a choice, but it's also just not good writing.
You can't keep us for nine episodes.
You can't keep introducing more and more stories and new things and new dilemmas.
And then at the end, just do something crazy and not wrap any of that up.
And that's what they did.
The ending, however, is so memorable and so crazy.
And I think that critics for once are being very responsible about it because it is so nuts.
I listen and have long been a fan of The Best Show with Tom Sharplin.
He had them on his show and he said, kind of the beautiful thing about it is that nobody in the world can guess how this show ends.
No one will be able to guess how this show ends.
They're absolutely right.
Even though I knew going in something crazy and unexpected was going to happen, it still blew my mind.
And the finale is a piece of art really unlike anything I've ever seen.
I do think, though, that the people, all my friends on Letterboxd who are giving it five out of five stars,
Christopher Nolan just called it a masterpiece of tone.
And like he's raving about it, like it's one of the great things of all time, comparing it to Twin Peaks and et cetera.
I think the proper way to talk about this is to say it's a moderately entertaining,
awkward comedy in the classic Nathan Fielder style, except it's scripted.
And it builds to a truly mind blowing and exceptional and unexpected and crazy hour of television that is well worth the time you spent to get there.
However, if they had done that and say ended half of the stories that they brought up, I would I would be a lot more enthusiastic about it.
So it's really what can you say? You know, I agree with Christopher Nolan.
There's never been anything like it.
I would also say without that ending, we're really just talking about kind of a generic, awkward comedy.
There are funny bits in the very first episode.
You see Nathan Fielder's penis, which is I pray for his sake that it's a prosthetic, but it is the smallest penis I've ever seen.
So Emma Stone is falling out of love with him.
And Safdie plays the sleazy reality show producer who decides, OK, these two are doing a fix up show like one of those house flip shows for HGTV.
He realizes they're too boring and Nathan Fielder is not funny or interesting enough or compelling enough to get the show picked up.
So he starts exploiting the problems in their marriage.
You see Nathan Fielder is already such a cuck in the show and Emma Stone is so actively trying to get out of the relationship that when we see him with a micro penis, it's kind of a hat on a hat.
It is funny.
Later on, Corbin Bernsen enters the show as Emma Stone's father.
We see that he has a tiny penis.
None of this really goes anywhere.
There's just they just keep throwing stuff at you.
And some of it works.
Some of it doesn't.
There's a lengthy subplot with the guy from Captain Phillips, the I'm the captain now guy who I never thought I would see in anything else again.
He's in there.
His daughters are the ones who put the quote curse on Nathan Fielder.
But yeah, I don't know.
It needed a little more time in the incubator for me.
However, every one of my life is obsessed with it and calling it a masterpiece.
I just think that's owed to a mind blowing ending.
If it's if it's worth it to you, if somebody told you there's a 10 hour movie and it's all worth it for the 10th hour, would you want to watch that answer that question yourself?
You know, ultimately, I'm sort of glad I watched it, but I don't think it's as great as everyone's making it out to be because they didn't do the job of a TV show.
So there you go.
You have to tell me a complete story.
You can't at the end go.
I guess we just won't do anything.
We're going to do this now.
It's not fair.
All right.
Last but not least, excuse me.
The Image Revolution, which is the documentary about Image Comics, Todd McFarland's, you know, he's the most known of the of the team at Image.
But, you know, again, talk about Rogue.
Todd McFarland in the I guess it's early 90s got fed up that the entire comic book business was just Marvel and DC and that they had a lot of rules and gave their artists basically zero royalties on the characters they created.
One of the film opens, the film opens with, you know, a little on screen factoid whatever about Jack Kirby, one of the most famous comic book artists of all time and creators saying that, you know, he created I think he created Spider -Man and the Hulk and some other people.
No, he created the Hulk and I don't know, whatever.
One is he created some iconic characters.
They say like, despite Marvel making billions of dollars.
He worked till the day he died because his royalties were so small.
Yeah.
On these characters he created and Todd McFarland basically gets fed up.
And is like, I'm going to start my own company.
And I'm not only going to start my own company, I'm going to fucking turn the industry on its ear.
And I'm going to take the best artists and creators at the two major outlets with me.
And he does it.
Put seven guys together, they leave and they go make Image Comics.
And Image Comics becomes the biggest thing in comic books and they become overnight instantly mega successes.
And then, of course, there's the down slide where there's too much money coming in, the egos get inflated.
Things fall apart, but eventually come back together again.
You know, the most famous characters that come out of Image is obviously Spawn.
But it's a great documentary and it's a great way to see a bunch of guys say fuck you to the system.
It's the thing that I keep haranguing about on this show and everywhere else in my life about you don't have to work for, let's call it the man in quotes.
Yeah.
I loved Issa Rae this week, you know, a five season smash with Insecure, a show I really liked at the beginning a lot.
It kind of lost me over time, but she was like, they just canceled a couple of her shows and she's like, I'm going independent.
She's like, these executives are so stupid.
They have and plus I know what executive covered her show and it's the same as the cool kids.
And I loved hearing all this because I knew exactly who she meant.
That's great.
But she goes, they're too old and they're just cling on to power.
It's the same shit as politicians.
They cling to their power.
They won't let it go.
They're trying to have this massive creative influence on the show, but they're not equipped to do so.
So I'm taking my shit and I'm going.
I'm going independent and well, I hope she does, but yeah, it's time.
Definitely.
It's, you know, and yeah, the thing ends with Todd McFarlane just going, don't work for Marvel or DC.
Somebody's ringing my doorbell.
I'm not going to answer it.
I'm going to let it go.
The police about that call this morning.
It's another kid.
I heard this is the house the kids go to.
I told my mom I was coming over here because you kind of let kids in.
Yeah.
So anyway, yeah, it's it's a really, really fascinating documentary.
I'm glad to hear that about Issa Rae too.
That's awesome.
You know, yeah, it's it's it's, you know, and by the way, the after image sort of has a fall from grace.
Yeah.
The comeback is Walking Dead.
Really? I did not.
They pick up Walking Dead as a comic book.
And they're like and like, you know, and that guy now, the guy that created Walking Dead is now a major part.
He's like now like a like a partner, whatever, at Image Comics.
Right.
And even that guy was is a super rogue because he like he talks about how through his childhood, like being a part of Image was like his
dream.
Mm hmm.
And he gets in and he's working there and he's like pitching them this comic.
He's like, I have this comic.
I want to do it.
And the guys at Image are like, dude, it's a zombie story.
Like, nobody cares.
Right.
Nobody. These things don't sell like nobody wants it.
They're like, there's no hook.
And he goes, oh, I forgot to tell you the hook.
And they're like, well, what's the hook?
And he goes, this is all just the foundation for an alien invasion.
The zombie virus is planted here by aliens and slowly the human race will become so weak that the aliens can take the planet over.
And they're like, wow, OK, that's a really cool hook.
And he goes, I'm going to put Easter eggs in throughout the entire series.
And eventually this bombshell will drop.
And if you go back and reread, you'll see you'll see all the Easter eggs.
I only saw the first season of the Walking Dead.
Was that even the plot of the show or they dropped that aspect?
Well, they well, this is before the show.
This is just the comic.
So then they put out the first four issues of the comic and it sells pretty well.
And they're like, this is great.
Like, it's doing pretty well.
Where are the Easter eggs?
We're not seeing them.
And they said he starts laughing in their face and he's like, there's no alien invasion.
I just told you that.
So you would make the comic.
Yeah.
I'm like, the balls on this fucking guy.
That's insane.
Right.
And four issues and it's doing well enough that he's like, fuck it.
I'm just going to tell them and laugh in their face.
And they said that it is consecutively outsold itself.
Yeah.
Like, and then it becomes the TV show and then all that stuff.
So it's just a really, really inspiring documentary.
And Todd McFarlane is really a fucking character, man.
He's real.
Everybody in this thing is such like a character.
It's very entertaining to watch.
I will check that out.
And I saw a picture called silenced.
I saw a clip of it on must have been reels, tick tock, whatever.
But it's by Hwang Dong Hyuk, who was the guy who did squid games.
And this came out in 2011.
And I like squid games.
You know, I'm not dying.
I don't even know if I'll watch a season two of it.
I think that was another thing over the pandemic where we were just so
happy to have something good that we kind of overpraised it.
But I did like squid games.
And sort of the weirdest most.
Did you watch squid games?
No, I didn't really have an interest.
I don't that sort of thing.
Squid games, hunger games, like not audition, Battle Royale, whatever.
I don't know.
I'm just not that interested in that sort of shit.
I hear you.
But this, you know, I was curious as to what the guy had done before he became
like one of the biggest creators in the world because that show was so massive.
And it's a super disturbing movie that it was just too much for me to enjoy.
It's based on actual events, which makes it so much worse.
I started to kind of read the Wikipedia about the true story.
And I was like, nope, not before bed.
But it took place at a school for the blind.
I'm sorry, the deaf.
OK, sorry.
And it's young deaf kids who were the victims of repeated sexual assaults by
faculty members over a period of five years in the early 2000s.
And, you know, it's effective in the way that squid games was squid games.
If you remember, had that really weird rig.
There's the weird, creepy, like molesting guy, the big fat guy.
And he gets his comeuppance.
And this guy has got an obsession with it.
I hope nothing happened to him when he was a kid.
But it's too there's too much dramatization of what's happening to the kids.
No, it's just like at some point you're like, I don't want to be watching this.
And it's not because I don't want people checking my history.
It's because I don't want to expose myself to this.
I was lucky enough to make it out of my childhood without something horrific like
this occurring.
And, you know, Joe, you and I were talking about Sleepers the other day and how
great Kevin Bacon was in that movie.
Really, that's an underrated movie, too.
Talk about a cast.
I mean, yeah, holy shit.
But Sleepers is a movie that is devoted to child abuse, child molestation.
But there's not long scenes where they pan away and you hear a child screaming in
pain, you know, that kind of stuff.
Ultimately, if you like this, I don't know.
I don't mean you like this sort of thing.
But, you know, it's just there's too much wallowing and misery and human pain and
suffering for me.
And the story was so unpleasant that I can't, I don't understand why people
thought, oh, obviously we need a movie about this.
Now, a documentary about this might be absolutely fascinating because how did
this go on for so long?
It's a really gross situation where the teachers are all sort of in on it and
passing them around and et cetera, et cetera.
I cannot recommend this.
The reason it's getting a bit of a resurgence is because of squid games.
You can watch this on Netflix or on Tubi if you want to.
I do not recommend the movie we are talking about on today's show.
We have probably said this title wrong more than we've said it right, but it's
called No One Will Save You.
That's right.
From the Man Who Made Spontaneous, which I have heard is great and have not seen.
Have you seen Spontaneous Joe?
Now, I looked up this guy's catalog.
He's done stuff that I've heard of, but I don't know that I've seen any of it.
Same.
But he did the babysitter on Netflix, which I hear is pretty fun.
He did Love and Monsters, which I hear is pretty fun.
Spontaneous, which I hear is pretty fun.
The Cate Blanchett one was the one that...
What's that?
I don't remember.
Couldn't tell you.
But I think it's Cate Blanchett.
Anyway, the guy does this thing.
It stars the girl from Booksmart, not Beanie, but the other girl.
It is Caitlin Deaver, who I do like, and it is essentially a one -woman show here.
And it is a dialogue -free movie.
So our previous film we discussed, Joe discussed how it ripped off the Twilight Zone episode.
And this one, I have not seen the Twilight Zone episode in question,
but it apparently rips off the 1960 Invaders episode of the Twilight Zone.
It also rips off The Monsters are on Maple Street.
It manages to rip off both episodes.
This is, as Pat said, a dialogue -free movie.
Something odd is afoot.
It is a sort of surreal reality that we're watching from the jump.
I don't really quite understand why that is, other than it's just a stylistic choice.
I don't understand why it is dialogue -free, other than that is just a stylistic choice.
It is just a stylistic choice.
For scenes with the aliens, it's effective.
The aliens don't speak. She wouldn't be talking to them.
They can't understand each other. It's really effective.
But you can't have her go into town and interact with other human beings and adults and nobody speaks.
You could have done a movie that's 75 % silent, you know,
but they're so committed to this gimmick that it winds up kind of fucking with the believability of the movie.
Yeah, they clearly, there's one line of dialogue and they clearly said,
or the writer said, we're just going to, wouldn't it be cool if the only line was at this one point in the climax and whatever.
And it's about a woman dealing with the loss of her mother and of her best friend.
You don't know why the best friend is dead.
You assume the mother's died, you know, even if it's tragic, but just by acceptable circumstances,
you immediately get the hint that the best friend is dead because of something that has to do with this girl,
because everybody in town is shunning her.
I don't, when it is revealed what happened,
I don't buy for a second that an entire town would shun a woman in her late twenties because of an accident from when she was 11.
Joe, you are a billion percent right.
Thank you.
Why? It just doesn't hold up. A childhood accident?
You know, it doesn't make any sense.
Also self -defense when you see what happened.
Yeah, it's stupid.
So there's this confusing ground that is laid immediately where, again, you're like, what year is this supposed to be?
Why is nobody talking?
It has a 50s vibe to it almost.
Why is she dancing in her house by herself? Is she crazy? Is she mute?
Like, you don't know what the fuck is happening.
She's giving adult -child vibes, then you see her drinking wine.
Yes.
Like, it's just, yeah.
And then the aliens attack.
You don't know that they're aliens at first.
You think it might just be a monster, which is fun and exciting because those sequences are very well shot.
It is creepy.
It's creepy and like a in a sort of devilish like troll is loose in the house kind of way, like Cat's Eye.
It was giving me the happening vibes.
Not the happening. Science vibes.
So it's fun and creepy.
And then you see that it is an alien.
And when you see that it's an alien, it's because it is the most generic people, for Christ's sake, enough with the fucking big -eyed, bald, no -nose aliens.
How many times are they going to make these communion aliens in a movie? Stop it.
It goes back to Close Encounters.
I mean, it goes back farther than that.
You can do anything you want.
You can come up with any creature design you want.
It's like when Predator came out, they're like, hey, let's give them something that's unlike anything we've ever seen before.
You know, the aliens and aliens are they're unlike anything we've seen before.
The second alien coming out of the mouth, you know, that stuff's awesome.
But you've got to put your spin on it.
The big -eyed alien, like from American Dad.
Yeah. Why have we decided that's what aliens look like?
Why?
Because the reason why is because in accounts from people, they're described that way.
But that's not what we're watching. We're not watching.
We're not watching Fire in the Sky.
We're not watching a movie about a guy's account about an alien abduction.
We're watching a completely fictitious movie about aliens coming in that's supposed to be fun and scary.
Make some cool fucking aliens.
Make them look a little monstrous or something.
Which even Quiet Place did, which you also mentioned that this movie rips off a little bit.
So this movie 100 percent feels like Quiet Place.
You've got somebody who's not talking for some reason and aliens invading.
This movie rips off Close Encounters because the whole point of the alien invasion is that they are going to infect the people around them.
And the people will just become drones controlled by the aliens.
And they're trying to get everybody to assimilate to that.
It rips off Monsters on Maple Street because what do the aliens do in order to make the invasion work?
They shut off anything that is powered.
Your car, your electricity, anything.
The phones, anything.
It's the invaders because it's a dialogue free alien invasion.
This thing is every it's well shot.
It's well acted.
And there are some genuinely freaky, creepy sequences.
But every single aspect of this is derivative of something else.
The way their bodies go stiff and they get lifted up into the light is fire in the sky.
The noises the aliens make when they communicate is fucking Attack of the Clones and Star Wars.
It's like every single thing down to the way the aliens look is ripped off of something else.
And no, that's true.
It's just I just don't get the.
I said to I said to Pat when I was watching this, I said it's at a point.
No, actually, I didn't say this to you.
I'm sorry. I said this to Pinkstone.
I said it's at a point.
I said I don't even think people are stealing this stuff.
I think nobody is in charge anymore that has any fucking concept of history of what's been done and what hasn't been done.
When you're in your early 20s and late teens and you first start pursuing a path in creativity,
you have all kinds of ideas that you think are the best ideas in the world.
And it takes other people around you that you tell those ideas to to help you vet them.
And they go, that's been done, dude. I know you think it's cool and original.
It's been done.
There's nobody saying it's been done anymore because nobody knows what the fuck has been done anymore.
Yeah.
And the parameters for which you can actually say to somebody or pursue the the accusation of you stole that are so fucking broad and loose and and and un executable at this point that it doesn't even matter.
So we've we've now gotten to this place where nobody knows the history.
Nobody's worried about knowing the history.
You couldn't do anything about it, even if it was stolen from you.
And my guess, my guess, Joe, is this guy does know the history.
If he's he's made eight genre pictures in a world where we have streamers where you can pull up anything in five seconds.
There's no way he hasn't seen these movies, Close Encounters and shit.
You know, I what you're saying definitely happens, of course, with first time filmmakers.
But I don't believe this guy doesn't know what he's ripping off.
I bet he used them in the pit.
It's a good point.
I just I'm at a point where, look, I've worked in in a good number of writers rooms nowhere near what Pat has worked in because I'm not a career writer.
But but I've worked in enough writers rooms to know this also, Pat.
And I'll add this.
I'm pretty well schooled in standup comedy.
And there's a reason I do it for a living.
It's it was a passion of mine from a very early age.
And I know a lot of standup comedy.
I've gotten more scowls and and annoyed reactions in writers rooms for pointing out so and so did that joke already in the special from 19 whatever.
Oh, yeah.
And I've gotten but it's got to be done sometime.
Yeah. Then I've gotten like thanks for catching that.
And I've been told by people I don't care.
We didn't steal it.
We just thought of it right now.
Right. Yeah. But but it doesn't matter.
It's it's been done.
They don't want to hear it.
So everything's been done.
Yeah.
Everything's been done.
Doesn't matter. Right.
And now like this word homage has been so bastardized.
It just means theft now.
Yeah.
It's not theft.
I remember when that fucking show came out where it was where it was.
It was I think I've probably talked about this.
It was the sixth.
It was a comedy, but it was a sixth sense.
Deadbeat or whatever.
Oh, sure. Yeah.
And I met a girl.
I knew a girl who was friends with the creator.
She's like, yeah, my friend created that show Deadbeat.
And I go, yeah, you mean the fucking thing that's just ripped off from a sixth sense?
Yeah.
And she goes, see, that's the thing, though.
See, what it was was they said, wouldn't it be funny?
And I go, it doesn't fucking matter.
Right.
They took the fucking idea.
And because they added pot or whatever the fuck they added to this, they now it's not stealing.
Yeah.
Have some fucking dignity.
How about that, everybody?
I know people who, when they pitch something, they'll look through a bunch of serious movies,
pick one, say it's Fatal Attraction, and then go, it's the comedy Fatal Attraction.
They just do that.
They just pick a movie and say, but it's a comedy.
And that's their pitch.
And those sell.
They always sell.
It's the old, it's this meets this.
That's the quickest way to a sale is this successful thing meets this successful thing.
And it sucks because it should be.
Here's an original mind -blowing idea.
But it's never that.
And I can even live with it's this versus that.
Like if somebody said, look, man, it's, you know, there's this new multicam coming out.
It's really crazy.
It's Friends, except it's during the apocalypse.
Right.
I can live with that.
Okay, I get it.
You're taking a very famous thing and meshing it with it.
Fine.
This is, to me, is not doing that.
This is just taking really great elements from better things and cobbling them together.
Yeah.
To make, in order for this guy to tell a story, which by the way, is a who gives a shit story.
How many more fucking movies do we need about aliens invading a fucking farmhouse?
Like, who fucking cares, man?
That's why he did the no talking bit.
Because everyone's like, ooh, that's a good hook.
Because without it, you are left with one of the more generic alien pictures of all time.
You're left with something that could have come out in 1950.
Just a real generic straightforward thing.
What puts it in the modern era is that it's a trauma thing.
You know, once she learns to overcome her trauma, then the aliens leave her alone.
The aliens were to believe that the aliens are coming to Earth to help one young girl overcome trauma.
They never explained that.
And it's stupid.
It's so stupid.
And then what happens is, is the aliens body snatch everybody on Earth or everybody in her town or whatever.
And then because they're now all possessed drones, they all like her in the end.
Right.
And she's dancing with all of them in a fucking, it's fucking stupid.
The ending was really stupid, really stupid.
Here's Stephen King on the movie.
No one will save you.
Brilliant, daring, involving, scary.
You have to go back over 60 years to a Twilight Zone episode called The Invaders to find anything remotely like it.
Truly unique.
He's old and he's cashing in.
I can't blame the guy.
Look, the guy has put his work in.
He produced the movie.
I mean, that must be his opinion.
He's playing nice, dude.
He's old.
He's put his work in.
He was a fuck you prick for decades.
Guillermo del Toro has also raved about this and said he feels it's a very Catholic story and a story of guilt and redemption and all this.
And then the director goes, I guess Guillermo didn't realize that I grew up in a Catholic seminary in Ireland.
I feel so seen this morning.
Whatever.
It's like the director really said that.
Yeah.
By the way, if this movie was about Guillermo, it'd be about him overcoming his guilt of stealing the shape of water from that short film.
You know, I mean, fuck off with all this, man.
When I saw those raves are really what made me excited about it because I just was kind of like this looks kind of generic, whatever.
And it is.
And, you know, when I'm comparing it to other Hulu originals, when I'm comparing it to Self -Reliance, which I talked about on the show, it's a solid, competently made movie.
It's just so down the middle that I just didn't enjoy it.
And it's gimmick is an annoying one and not a believable one, frankly.
It reads as gimmick, not as though there's a reason for it.
Quiet Place was fun because they couldn't speak.
In this movie, they can speak and they don't because it helps the tone.
Because of the power when she finally has the hallucination of her mother or whatever it is and says, I'm sorry, whatever the fuck.
I'm like, this is stupid, man.
I realize finally in this moment, I realize why I get so mad about this stuff when it comes to entertainment.
In a world where we are publicly calling out one another, every single politician, we're tweeting at presidents, scathing things.
We're dressing down every corporation on planet Earth and their policies and all this and calling bullshit on every waking fucking thing you can imagine on the Internet.
It pisses me off that there's this still this charade perpetuated by Hollywood.
I love Guillermo del Toro.
But stop fucking with me, man.
Stop. You know what I mean?
Like, stop, dude.
Address the shape of water thing.
Stop.
It just annoys the shit out of me, man.
Like, it's come on.
Be better than this.
It just bothers me.
Do better.
That applies to everybody except fucking filmmakers, apparently.
We need, honestly, we need a Cat Williams, a three -hour discussion with Cat Williams about the state of the horror film industry, really.
Who could do it?
Who could be the, like Crispin Glover.
He's the Cat Williams of genre films.
He needs to get out there and do his thing.
No, we let a lot slide under the guise of influences and homage, as you said, and tribute.
And, oh yeah, that was my little shout out to, oh, you mean when you stole the third act of that movie?
That's your homage?
You know, okay.
Anyway.
Yeah, yeah.
All right.
Well, my, again, it's like the last film.
It's not a, it's not, I'm not down over this.
It's just, it's well executed.
I just wish they would have just done better.
And it's, you know, it's, you know, mildly flaccid hog once again.
You know, well executed, well written, well acted, well directed.
Well written in the sense of just the plotting of it.
But, well, it's not that well written.
I hate the fucking ending and I hated the, it's well directed and well acted.
And it could have been a, it could have been a cool movie.
It just could.
Why aliens, too?
Make it like, even Steven Spielberg with Crystal Skull was like, I'm not doing aliens.
So they changed it to interdimensional beings.
Like, it could have just been monsters that are infecting the town and nobody, you wouldn't, it wouldn't matter.
They didn't need to come from space.
There didn't need to be an explanation.
I don't know.
Yeah.
There's just very little novel or interesting about the execution except the mute thing.
And that doesn't work as well as they think.
I liked both of the movies we discussed this week about equally.
I probably liked the first one more, but it was 50 minutes longer than No One Will Save You.
So I put them at about the same average place.
I agree.
Not sure what we'll be getting into later on in the month.
I'm not sure what big movies come out in February.
It's usually not, what's coming out soon?
Do you know?
Ghostbusters, I guess, but that's not till March.
March.
I think we'll probably do poor things.
I'm really trying to get out to see that.
It's 2 .30.
I've seen poor things.
2 .30.
Jesus Christ.
I think I already, I already talked about it on the solo.
So if we don't get there, we don't get there.
All right.
I do want to see it, but just 2 .30.
I mean, it's like, you can't just go sit in a goddamn movie theater anymore.
It's like, I got to block out a four hour fucking day now to go see a movie.
Like Christ Almighty, man.
Argyle, that movie about the fucking cat with Dua Lipa in it, that movie's 2 .30.
Oh my God.
Argyle.
I don't want to see five minutes of it.
Except the scenes with Dua Lipa.
All right, folks.
I'm on the road, Nashville, Charleston, and Charlottesville.
Then right after that, West Coast, San Diego, LA, and San Fran.
Pat, oh, you'll be in Atlanta.
Shit.
I was going to say, I won't see you.
Anyway, that's coming up.
And also too, folks, if you're going to South by Southwest, I hope that you are.
Salsa Windfall officially is playing South by Southwest, which is wild.
I can't believe it's happening.
That's going to be on the 12th, I believe, of March.
Also that day, I'll be doing the Sandwich Summit at 5 PM at the Creek and Cave and some other stuff.
So hope to see you out there.
Jodorosa .com for tickets on everything.
Come to Joey Roses, joeroses .com if you're in New York.
The Patrick Walsh on Instagram.
See you in Hellpod on Instagram.
We are, as you know, Patreon only.
Thank you all for your support and your love.
There's always great discussions going on in the comments there, and I assume still on the Facebook page, though I am not there.
We will see you next time.
We love you, and we will see you in Hell.