Welcome to will see you in hell it's the podcast that talks about movies I am
Joe DeRosa and I am Patch Walsh you had Joe there sounding like a one of those lines you call like when
you're waiting at the bank you wait for just which which which which one should I push that kind
of thing is that what you're going for now I just I'm just sort of robotics see whatever comes
out you know what I mean okay it sounded a little flippant I thought I thought it sounded a little
like like oh here we go again I guess now I have to do the podcast okay I didn't mean you're doing
like an AI type character no no no no I'm just uh I'm so sick of life just trying to find new ways
to talk anything but interesting at this point I've been doing that for years then you know you
do it in your wife's like why did you say the word like that and you want to be like because I'm
clinging on to my sanity barely and I'm just me pronouncing words differently is probably a better
look than me screaming into the abyss for eight hours a day so let's just have some more fun with language
shall we shall we and he called her tuts tuts yeah um how are how are you well I'm all right I I'm
uh clean shaven for the first time in ages which is always it's kind of weird period when you shave
where your face is is horrifying to you and your loved ones just just because it's it's like how you
ever see those videos of like a baby who sees their dad without a beard and starts sobbing yes and you
can get in your head and say like oh I have a terrible face but it's just you get used to somebody so
every time I pass a mirror now I like jump but then in two three days I'll be like oh it's coming in
a little bit a little stubble I'm kind of got like a Michael Keaton vibe going you know it did
startle me when you popped on the screen here today I was also I've just out of bed and and making
a hideous face when you logged in so yeah but I was just surprised me I shouldn't say not startles
it sounds harsh it did I mean look at me though I'm kind of sexy I don't want to I don't want to do
see when you get the gray like it's weird because the beard I like it I like like like you know I'm
just a guy full of shame I like wearing a jacket at all times I like covering my face with a beard at
all times but the truth is when I shave the beard nowadays I'm cutting off a lot of gray and I look
younger I would say yes you do look younger but at the same time it's just like a a big Irish
tasty face coming in here which is I mean the gray beard also the fact that you're not
smoking the corn cob pipe anymore I'd say shaved a few years off yeah well I like the sweet taste
of corn cob Joe and I always have as a penis ever been referred to as a corn cob I mean how
does that never have been how have I never heard one of my thousands of crass friends call a penis
a corn cob I'm sure it's happened I would I would almost guarantee it's happened for all frosty
at the only time I've ever heard corn cob pipe was in frosty the snowman that's well that was his
brand yes yes and I believe frosty would go into like the the bodega and be like let me get um
let me get a box of the corn cob pipes you know you gotta yeah you gotta order it like the way
you order the condoms like I'll take the snickers the snapple beef jerky at a box of corn cob pipe
yeah you're gonna drop them in this top hat I'm wearing by the way a box they they
disposable you gotta get those those just thinking of like when I said his brand I was picture in
another guy like reaching back for his wallet at the bet the bodega who's always like all right let me
get uh let me get uh yeah let me get uh you know like Jesus dude yeah yeah waiting in line for
it's there was a sandwich the sandwich king of a story of the best sandwich prior to Joe's I assume
I haven't had it yet but uh sandwich king is great I love sandwich king the best but uh it was known
for that just guys standing in line for like 10 minutes and they get up there and be like oh okay uh
what do you got in terms of breads it's like Jesus dude and it's not called sandwich king
the real name the deli itself has a real name but then it's also called the sandwich king
like if you googled it I don't think sandwich king sandwich king didn't you used to not come up I don't
I don't think it was under maybe I'm misremembering this I might be wrong anyway if you're ever
in a story uh go to sandwich king get yourself a sandwich the size of your like leg yeah and if he
if he still works there uh 15 years later make sure you go to the handicapped kid who would now be
a handicapped adult because he he built the best sandwiches oh okay very nice I would always be like
I'll wait for the handicapped talent dressed in a three piece suit uh yeah and yeah did you
know your usual because you could you say I always wanted to say the usual I never got to say
that anywhere I didn't do it often I used to have respect for myself I wouldn't get a 10 pound sandwich
that often but when I did it was beautiful yeah it's a it's an amazing sandwich um just piled high
we used to get those when I lived with Okerson we would get them on um because we lived in Queens we
would get them on Sunday and watch the Eagles yeah it was like one of the only things that
ever made me want to watch football like Eagles like I care just enough about my hometown to to watch
an Eagles game when I don't like football right and then um and then if you get eat if you eat giant
hoagie's the whole time it's pretty well you know you could be watching anything at that point yeah
yeah I've watched your birth I did it once uh with my buddy E and we sat on the uh the roof of my
apartment building and I had like I'm almost like I'm gonna go get some mustard or whatever and
I'm up and I'm talking to him I've gotten some beers and some mustard or something and I'm like
yeah man I don't know I feel like best best case scenario I can get like half of this thing down
and I look over it in the one minute it had taken me to go down and get some beers he had finished his
sandwich it was a much heaviery and you know yeah yeah and it was like a smoke outline of a sandwich
hovering in the air between his hands and was there a backup sandwich this these are the days
where Ian might have gotten a backup sandwich for afterwards too he didn't but we did when we used to go
to diners at three in the morning we'd eat and then he'd order like $60 worth of to go food
and just like be shoveling it in while dozing off in bed and does and then fall asleep tragic Jesus
scrape there's a scrape there's a lot of darkness out there in this world a lot of darkness
speaking to diet I have uh transitioned into a partially that's the wrong way I was gonna say
partially vegetarian diet that's not the right way to phrase it but a less meat heavy diet okay
you know almost you know very little red meat in the rotation a lot of chicken a lot of vegetarian
meats say ton and some fish and I gotta tell you the difference um yeah well no I don't do the
say time I just hope food like the butt beyond meat okay imposing burgers made tacos with beyond
ground meat the other night okay and they were delicious uh but uh I gotta tell you the differences
immediate but what's the difference like I know it cuts down like on inflammation they say
which maybe just makes you look less well let's start let's start with the bowel movements oh please
just not I was hoping you'd say that no prep there and then just you know you don't you don't feel
bloated sure I don't have that bloated feeling I don't like my stomach doesn't feel upset
okay I don't know it's just a game changer I hope I can stick with it uh I hope you can too Joe
we're we're getting to those ages where red meat is just bad for you bad for the hard red meat I
also pork I cut out you know it's just the other one yeah trying to I'm not saying I'll never
eat them but I'm just trying to stay you know not eating lunch meats anymore you've asked I hope
I've never really been that you've been that guy who gets lunch meat at the store I don't know why
but yeah meat meats and cheese are not really my thing lately that was the thing too cutting back on
cheese was huge yeah it's delicious but it's bad it's bad for you it's all cholesterol yeah you don't
have high cholesterol that surprises me I've never heard you mention uh I have elevated
elevated not high my doctor my recent blood work my doctor was like look you know you could get it
down if you can get it down another 20 points that'd be amazing it's not great now but it's not
terrible right and uh he was like if you had any other problems I might be a little more concerned
but you you got a pretty clean blood panel here so okay you know I don't know I don't understand it
I know I know people that are in far not just far better shape than me people that like work out
right and are physically or you can see visually they are in good shape yeah and they're like
prediabetic and it's weird yeah I think a lot of it's jeans yeah I think a lot of it's jeans my
my dad has always been in terrible shape my mom has always been in fantastic shape eating healthy
worked out twice a day since we were little kids and still does and my mom always had high cholesterol
my dad was always perfectly healthy crazy it's odd but I can't believe my liver numbers came back
yeah I think I think again that's genetics you know like anytime I go and like a buddy of mine who
you know Joe but I'll tell you after but he was like he goes yeah I've just been drinking my
way through the quarantine just seriously he goes into and I can consider today still the
quarantine it's like I just didn't stop and I just keep drinking and drinking and drinking and drinking
and drinking and I wake up and I drink and then he's like I went in for like a checkup and you just
don't think of it because you've never heard anything serious before but the doctor said comes in
immediately normally there's that 20 minutes of waiting on the the tissue paper table but he comes
in and he's clearly like frazzled it was like okay have you been drinking a lot he goes yeah yeah
I'm not even gonna try to lie to you I have and he's like you're you're entire insides have taken
big turns in the last year and a half and he's like okay okay but I never had that I go in even
even when I know I've had like a rough month and drank a lot I go in and they're always like looks
good I think that's the Irish and it's it's I do think it's genetics my buddy chip says to that he's
like I think it's also just lifestyle yeah your body gets used to look I grew up eating McDonald's
right you know I've probably talked about it on the show before but like staple meals in my house
three times a week where like one was pizza hut one was McDonald's one was like cheese steak knife
I my mom never told me that stuff's bad for you like we just that's just how we ate
and I didn't start drinking for most people it was a late age till I was like probably like
19 or 18 but when I did I didn't stop and I made a career of it
um and it's weird like I think I think my buddy's got a point like he's like your body is just like
yeah this is I know how to work this this is I know how to process all this this is what we do
yeah it's these kids you know especially now much more than when we were little and especially in
LA of course but you see these parents who are like you know treating their kids diet as as strictly
as they treat their own yeah like the kid at a restaurant is like getting you know they're measuring
out stuff and all this kind of stuff that kid to me is the one who's gonna grow up with like severe
ibs and can't eat anything and and yeast disorders and all kinds of stuff it's like how they say you
know the parents who who are pure out this is pre pandemic but the parents who are purelling their
kids hands every day and scrubbing their kids they don't build up natural immunities so by the time
grow up they get sick constantly I mean I used to just eat grass and roll around and you know
roll around the mud and everything else and it's just it makes you a more hail and hearty kind of
a person you can you can fight off more shit it's the first time I've ever heard anybody use the
expression hail and hearty I enjoyed it first the first time I've used it since Darryl Hammond at
saturday and alive used to go good you don't get me some soups from hail and hearty because the name
of the soup I didn't know that that had a meeting beyond the name I don't know why it came out
of my mouth no okay but hail no hail and hearty means like a strapping strong I didn't know that
I thought it thought it was just the name of the soup place and the soup restaurant
yeah there's something to that man it's there's something you know you see it sometimes with like
rock stars and stuff like you know some legendary party guy gets sober and then he dies
you know like yeah you pickled yourself I mean you know like yeah yeah it's very strange or even
just like from a talent perspective like a guy like Miles Davis is a great example like he kicks the
heroin and then you're like all right Miles and I heard all the I need to hear of this record now
you know like it's yeah there's something to it um yeah I was uh that's weird I've started writing
to two Miles Davis jazz and Miles Davis which I was a real indicator that I'm getting old but
I was just like I've never had the patience for even five seconds of jazz now I'm like
up do bar jazz you know what they say writing is like jazz well it is we're going to find the rhythm
and my writing is especially like jazz in that very few people like it and there's not a lot of money
in it these days oh because you were kidding when you texted me that you were writing to
Joe no I texted Joe yeah that I had like the giant headphones on like Sam Jackson and do the right
thing and stuff but it was true I have these old headphones specifically for making vinyl sound great
and the great thing about I listen mostly to bitches brew was my favorite Miles Davis album but the
great thing about it is every side of that record is like 40 minutes so you don't have to flip it
I hate these records where they'll have two songs on each side yeah and they're like because get it
because we we we mastered it at a thousand bpm or whatever the fuck the bullshit it's 390 gram vinyl
right and you're like well I'm not you know Philip Dolby so I can't tell I'm half deaf
fucked fine that's what the guy had the vinyl shop I went to buy a new needle the other day very
expensive and he's like well here's your two options and one was like significantly priceier than
the other and I'm like look you're a you're a vinyl shop owner like yeah look look at like a dumb guy
who's had his hearing destroyed by decades of concerts do you really think there's a difference in
this and he just shot me straight he was like there'll be no difference to you at all
you know he could have lied to me and gotten 200 extra bucks but the what's it called
I was watching it reminds me of I was watching with a friend who had never seen it
modern romance by Albert Brooks classic I am for my money it's his best film that's it's my favorite
Albert Brooks film I know a lot of people would disagree with that but I didn't just think
pieces on modern romance if it came out today it's it's an amazing movie the commentary it's so
right to write yourself that part of yeah one of the most despicable human beings I mean my friend
had never seen it I put it on yeah we both we're laughing every five seconds through like the first 45
minutes of this thing I was like yeah you I can't remember the last time I've seen a comedy this
concentrated so like well when he goes to his brother that's what I was going to bring out that's the
record needle salesman and he goes he goes I that's too much I don't need to I just need one 75
dollars is very expensive and Bob I said goes I'm sorry I misjudged you I'm not perfect
yeah yeah and then well my favorite line of that whole exchange is when he's like yeah you need
this to protect yourself or you'll know it better than me just watch it but he's like you really think
I need that you know and then that super day of goes you know there are people out there all they do
is rape no no no that's he says Albert Brooks says that to his girlfriend she's leaving for work
she's in like a low cut top and he's gonna wear that to work and then she's walking out of the
door he goes honey there's people out there all they do is rape that's ridiculous that's fantastic
it's a it's a it's such an amazing movie the greatest my in my opinion the greatest line in the movie
is is at the beginning when he's breaking up with her he goes he goes I I this is you've heard of a
no -win situation this is a no -win situation she goes with no -win situation what's that and he
goes you've never heard of a no -win situation Vietnam this yeah he's great he seemed he seemed sluggish
on curb but you know he's an old man at this point but I thought they gave him nothing to do I was
very upset aside from getting to be in scenes with our friend Laura Kite Lager the best yes the
best I mean she was very funny I was like give him something to do like yeah it's you know like I
don't know or maybe he was just maybe that he just didn't do I don't know I don't want to knock the
guy but I texted Laura I was like congratulations you were even funnier than Lucy Lou but yeah it's
Lucy Lou's plan Larry's girlfriend he doesn't look at her smile at her laugh at anything she says
and then Kite Lager says three lines in the backseat and David's like cracking up it was it's so
clear that he just like I wish I didn't have to share scenes with Lucy Lou and I can instead do it
with the comedian yeah the I would love to see I think Kite Lager would be an amazing
uh counter -part for Larry David like as a girlfriend character I was really I texted her and I'm
like how many are you in because she settled into that world so easily yeah and she's like that's
it it was just a one -off and I was like fuck because I thought she fitted it fit into the world great
but yeah she's great doing that dry flippant you know sarcastic she's just she's very good at that
yeah uh I got to tell you speaking of the world in collapse I woke up this morning I I'm trying
to not do this but I do it I wake up and immediately get on my phone immediately I'm assaulted with
the worst news of all time but this morning's was something different first thing I see was a video
of it was in it was in Florida but it's this pretty big band there's bands that do this and tour
and you and I would never know who they are see that they wind up making a lot of money on the casino
circuit and all that but it was a all brass alt and classic rock cover band like all horns
uh led by you know a sexy woman who sings so they're like holy shit look at this massive crowd
it's a big event there's kids there you know it's it's brass covers of songs so they're playing
a rage against the machine song you know one of I can't even tell them apart but this is the one where
it's like you know let's let's say it was fuck you I won't do what you tell me but it wasn't you know
but she's up there and go you know sing in the lyrics sing in the lyrics and they bring up this big
tall fat 50 -year -old dude onto the stage she lays him down in his back on the stage you see everyone
in the audience because there's a guy filming it everybody around him is like what's going on and people
look really kind of disturbed yeah she pulls her pants and underwear down so she's clearly just
been like secretly fucked up and nobody knew how fucked up she was pulls her pants and underwear down
and for almost a minute squeezes out like a hose level amount of piss she bends over and
just pisses all over this guy's face and it's not a trickle we're talking like you're seeing
it splash off his face and he's going like you know like just hitting him like a hose the crowd
you know there's a few guys of course we're like whoo most people who are not super fucked up are sitting
there like I'm here there was there was comments like hey other people in the band were like this is not
us this will never happen again we you know we we had a little too much fun last night or whatever but
one of the wildest things I've ever seen you know it'd be wild at a punk show yeah
but this kind of thing I mean there's kids there there's kids there and the comments were like
my my funniest slash saddest one was this dad who was like you know my son is a gifted drum bonus and I'm
always trying to get him to to pursue it and not not think that it's dorky so I finally told him
like look here's people playing cool music with brass instruments we go I get him there and you know
an hour and we're watching a woman pee in a man's face it's like really insane was the do you
think the guy was in on it we're just some rando oh definitely some rando definitely he was he
was wasted too but it's like I don't know if you saw the smash mouth video from a few weeks back but
he gets up there and he's doing all star blacked out drunk and then he starts doing the Hitler salute
and then he starts screaming at the audience and it's like we've got these people I think not that
these are big huge artists or something smash mouth and the all brass rock cover band but
they've been cooped up some of them are having mental issues like many of us are and now they need
money in the only way somebody like that can get money is going out on tour so they're out there
completely unwell and just having some freakouts on stage no more sadly faith no more had to cancel
their tour or postpone it because they said Mike Patton Mike Patton released a statement and he was
just like I'm not mentally prepared to do this right now like yeah I saw that I admire the hell of it
that's that's what keeps you from you know being out on the road and being in someone's face on stage
yeah it's uh woo shout outs this is a real lane switch shout out to the uh Facebook group
I went on to the chat finally yes I'm coming folks I'm coming I'm coming right now literally I can
see it um I went in met some lovely people saw some lovely people some I knew some was my first time
meeting um everybody was really sweet the movie they were discussing was session nine
no I've never seen the David the company no I'm sorry David Karusa Karusa
I'm a said Danny Bona Ducci and then I said David the company and then David Karusa
um we they they discussed I think a bit more of it before I got in there than than I heard but
I was sick and bad with a science infection and Will Potter dropped the wine and said hey man if you're
around and you want to pop in we're doing the group and I was like you know what I'm sick and bad
I just might and I did and it really lifted my spirits and had a great time I was in there for
I don't know an hour maybe 90 minutes just kind of chopping it up and I I previewed some of the stuff
I'd be discussing on today's episode uh so uh that was kind of fun too what what were these things
are they still to come or have you already discussed them one's a scary stuff okay which I just was
actually showing everybody this comic book and and they it was it was very endearing everybody was
like we just got a private scary stuff it's like I didn't think of it like that but uh but uh
but that was very nice here yeah so I got a scary stuff there's a magazine it used to be called
the creeps okay it's a comic book it's a modern comic book it's anthology horror stories exactly in
the vein of Tales in the Crypt the old Tales in the Crypt um it's a fun comic you can find it at
Barnes and Noble uh wherever um you know and there's a horror host and it named the creep or whatever
the fuck is name I don't know Mr. Creepy or something anyway um I enjoy the magazine I had always got
it mixed up with the magazine called Creepy which was running from the 60s through the 80s or 90s
which was the same thing um I thought it was the same magazine and I realized it was two
slightly different titles and then I looked it up and read that the creeps people were being sued by
Creepy okay because they were like you copied almost identically our name you used the same font
you used the same style of artwork yeah and you're using uh you've established a publishing company
that's a variation of the name of our original publishing company okay you're clearly trying to
make people think that this is you know us yeah the defense from the creeps was well we have a lot
of your original artists here and basically we're trying to do you know an homage or whatever to your
thing we're trying to relaunch basically the brand anyway they lost the fight and they had to change
the name of the magazine which I get I kind of get where both parties were coming from I get a little
more where Creepy the original thing was coming from though yeah so the creeps they change it to
Creepy and now it's all about delicious breakfast crepes you ready to hear what they changed it to
I'm ready yeah shutter oh no is this new yeah so they haven't heard of shutter I'm sure they have I
mean I have a subscription I got my second issue of I have the inaugural issue of shutter okay in my
bedroom as we speak it came out and no ties to the channel zero wow as far as I know zero you know
uh it would say on it it would say there would be AMC you know whatever there's something you know
there's none of that I got a little scary stuff uh the predator franchise which has fallen on
just as hard times as terminator and a lot of these franchises in recent years
uh it's directed by Dan Trachtenberg who I fucking really like I loved 10 clover field lane as
we discussed on this show I thought that was you know one of the best kind of modern horror things
I thought it was really fun and scary and loved John Goodman in it here's the plot outline he's
directing it it's coming to Hulu in summer 2022 it's real hard to get excited about anything
anymore isn't it yeah like a new predator movie coming to Hulu yeah a brief plot lot plot outline
reads set in the world of the Comanche Nation 300 years ago the action thriller follows Nauru the skilled
warrior who fiercely protects her tribe against a highly evolved alien predator Nauru wants to prove
her worth as a warrior and certainly gets her chance when she comes face to face with the most dangerous
under of all the otherworldly predator it was supposed to be a surprise according to the director
but Disney plus day announced it and now it's coming well it's called prey prey yes it's unclear whether
we'll get a theatrical release I would hope so but uh there we are predator look I think the premise
sounds cool I like that it's a period piece and I was like oh like Comanche Indians against a predator
and like the poster look pretty cool too it's all like smoky and foggy and everything I was like
this could be really cool also too if you get into the lore of American Indian tribes and stuff with
like their belief in gods or whatever like you know that I I was like there's a lot there's a lot
I'll do it respectfully too it's not like every 80s horror movie where it was just like or even the
pet cemetery remake where it's just like yeah it's an Indian burial ground that's that's all we know
and we won't look into their actual customs of at all right so I think there's I think there's I think
there's ripe stuff there um whether they do a good job with it or not who knows but um you know I think
uh tract and burgs at capable director yeah but I also thought um what's his face was too and it was
the worst of any predator movie ever that last one with that what's his name did for him it was tough
I do I don't think it was any worse than the alien versus predators certainly but yeah it wasn't great
I I would put it equal to the second alien versus predator but I I actually think the original alien
versus predator was far superior which is not saying much but yeah I had pitched um
in a predator prequel where it was sort of the college years you know we see him in roll and
and this is what I thought was the most interesting take on it he was Ivy League right yeah he kind
of the fall of this guy as he as he starts on top and all this promise right and by the end of his
life he's killing cabins full of uh astronauts just just starting to let the hair grow out
yeah and and by the way we will get into the cultural appropriation of the predator's hairstyle
because he was doing dreads at a time when yeah yeah did one semester abroad in Jamaica thought
yeah gave him the right briefly considered the title predator colon Jamaican me crazy and it was
going to be set totally in Jamaica and his kind of post college trip they didn't like that either
all right fair enough I mean I just saw the trailer this is a this is more I guess these are
sort of new psycho things but I just saw the warwick Davis did a video introducing the new cast of
the will of TV series that's coming out the sequel series which I'm not a huge fan of well but I'm
curious enough and I love warwick Davis but what's great about the video is he does like a comedy video
yeah like you think he's just going to be introducing the cast and he does like the whole life
is short rickie jervais thing like okay okay is he in it yeah he plays well again grandpa will okay
yeah and uh but he he goes yeah that's one of the things she this this one of the actress goes
what are they going to do to your face uh what and she goes are they going to Irish man your face
you look so old yeah and he goes and he goes uh he goes no they're not going to Irish man my face this
takes place several years after the original and one of the plot points is how good Willow looks
for his age read the new pages that's a really funny video um yeah which will totally be nothing like
the show no it was such a weird approach to the video but I I thought it was really funny I was deeply
disturbed by that I didn't watch any of it but like now we're doing these like Netflix day and
they announced it and everyone celebrates or Disney plus day and it's like
you're making people and lots of people celebrate and network you know it's like when we were kids
there wasn't like a big let's all celebrate the great programming of ABC day or maybe there wasn't
I forgot it right it's just this it's gross to me you know as as we're watching society be ripped apart
by capitalism that we have days now where millions of people gather to celebrate a network it's gross
that's all I can say yeah being a fan or being loyal to a streaming service it doesn't sit right with me
it's right up there with people applauding you know Instagram rules and and Twitter censorship and all
the stuff it's it's all the same it's just like guys these are corporate monsters like they don't
they're not on your side not at all now and it's just nuts but um yeah so I you know
just well let's move to the corner if we could because I want to yeah on theme I'd like to discuss two
things I watched quickly sure with you know as we talk about continuation and whatever and I also
wanted to bring these up as an extension of the Halloween episode yeah I'll do it quick I wanted to
put my money where my mouth is this is one of the things I told the guys the gang on the thing I was
gonna talk about I went back and rewatched Halloween six and Halloween resurrection which are the two
Halloween's that I said where equally as bad as Halloween kills and that's because that's how bad
Halloween kills was I can say without doubt they are better than Halloween Halloween kills is the
worst Halloween movie wow I mean that's that is saying a lot you know uh Halloween six it's at least
interestingly directed um and if you can get past the goofy aspect of Michael Myers is like a demon
from a cult or whatever the fuck it is which every horror franchise was doing at that time they did it
with Freddie they did it with Jason yeah if you can get and if you can get past that you'll realize two
things number one it's not a bad Halloween movie and number two that their version of it is actually
better than the Freddie or Jason versions of that goofy -ass device yeah Halloween resurrection does a
very good job at least of ending the Jamie Lee Curtis storyline and establishing a new character and a
heroine and also fulfilling the the or filling the mold of a of a 90s late 90s horror movie that's
style of I know what you did last summer kind of thing yeah I can't say any of these positives oh and in
fact by the way the Tommy Doyle thing and Halloween kills is they do it better in Halloween six
even that makes more sense you know the red one yeah okay um so that all said I can't give any of
these compliments to Halloween six there's nothing about the direction that's interesting aside from the
fact that they manage to pull off a sequence that looks sort of like it's from the original movie in
the beginning uh they do nothing original with the characters it's all been done before and and the
the it doesn't even fill the mold of modern horror so it officially in my book is the worst Halloween
movie I don't count the zombie ones by the way I mean big shoes I think I watched them all last year
if not two years ago and my immediate instinct after a first viewing of Halloween kills was that it
was the worst one of the franchise but that second viewing not that I caught a lot of great stuff I
missed or something but I was just like okay removed from expectations the kills are kind of cool
I guess but plot -wise yeah it's a god damn mess I saw one of the most anticipated movies of the year
licorice pizza directed and written by Paul Thomas Anderson the title has not grown on me
I thought that it would but I just think it's a really bad title licorice pizza was apparently a record
store a vinyl store in the valley in the 70s and that's where this movie is set 1973 in the San
Fernando Valley north of me here in LA they don't go to licorice pizza in the movie nobody says licorice
pizza so I'm even more thrown by the title to be honest but um I love the movie I Paul Thomas Anderson
I think is one of our three four five best working directors today I think he's one of the few directors
who's still churning out you know a movie where when it comes out everyone with any interest in film
discusses it has an opinion on it wants to rank it amongst his other movies and for me this ranks
near the very bottom it ranks around the inherent vice days which I did like more on a second viewing
I expect I will like licorice pizza more on a second viewing but it's it's not hitting the heights
of of Anderson and I don't think it's one that's gonna grow on me through the years and reach the
heights of a boogie nights where there will be blood or magnolia or whatever that said
this is a very charming movie very sweet it stars Paul uh Philip Seymour Hoffman's son
Cooper Hoffman who it's weird he's a great actor great shot or you know 15 year old actor whatever and
but he doesn't look a lot like him but there's just moments where he does a little something with his
face or his eyes where you see his dad and it's kind of like it it takes it sets you back a little
bit it's crazy um Alana Hyme I love the band Hyme which is three sisters she's the star
Anderson is directed some of their music videos her and her two sisters are in this
they're all great actresses either their naturals or Anderson is just a great director of actors
which obviously he is but Alana Hyme is incredible in what I think is her first movie
he got Sean Penn playing Jack Holden who was a stand -in for William Holden the alcoholic actor from
the fifties to small part Bradley Cooper has a very small part and Penn and Cooper don't come in until
like the 90 minute mark and then they're in it very briefly so I get the feeling he pitched them
hey I've got a movie starring Alana Hyme and Cooper Hoffman and they said you better put some
fucking stars in this thing right um you know Benny Softy the guy who did uncut gems and also
was in the film uh good time plays a political candidate there's a lot of like taxi driver kind
of stuff where you don't know if this guy's going to assassinate him or what's going on there
but it's clearly it's his most kind of ultimate type movie there's a bunch of stories going on
um there's a lot of sweet moments a lot of very funny moments a lot of very strange moments
um it's something you got to kind of like with all his you come out you're like I don't know if I
like that or not and that's usually the sign of an artist the man is an artist I love his work
this just for me on a first viewing it ranks near the bottom of his stuff it doesn't mean don't look
forward to it it's a very entertaining film and I saw it in 70 millimeter which is pretty cool
you know it's like it really the grain everyone talks about you wouldn't believe the grain or whatever
and I kind of yeah laugh at how stupid they sound but then you see it and it's like no that's pretty
cool it looks great you can uh you can keep going I I feel that I already did three basically between
modern romance and these two and then uh oh chase yeah we then I would have been at it a little while
I had to scary another scary stuff to plug but you you go ahead and then we'll talk about our movie
okay uh liquor speeds it comes out at Christmas so it's got you got a ways to go tell that one
it's got a screener of Spencer which as you do that as you would guess by the title is a biopic about
Princess Diana yeah what I guess they figured Diana is just too boring a title but well that guy
made Jackie too about Jackie O 'Nassus and I was one of the most boring movies I've ever seen so I'll
I will watch Spencer I like Kristen Stewart um continuing our discussion from our last recording uh you
had mentioned win a stranger calls yeah yeah I watched it I you know it passed the time it did have
kind of that TV movie feel uh kind of a nice familiar old -fashioned afternoon kind of viewing feel to it
Charles Durning in this thing if somehow I accidentally watched like six Charles Durning movies
in the last week but there is an extended chase sequence where Charles Durning who is 65 and 340 pounds
by the way he's chasing someone on foot but I believe he's about 33 in this movie he's he always
Durning and there's one of those guys it's like he looked like that from day one to the final day
he reminds me I didn't he wasn't this fat but he reminds me a great deal of my uh my grandpa my Irish
grandpa I don't know if Durning is Irish I feel like he's got some in there but um yeah I mean you watch
for five good minutes as Charles Durning chases on foot after this suspect and it to me I just thought it
was kind of hilarious it's like if this guy would go above a light jog he would escape Charles Durning
with no problem but uh the opening scene is justifiably famous it was borrowed I would say by scream they
always referenced um the opening of that movie as an inspiration for the Drew Barrymore opening of
scream Carol Kane is great I'd outside a psycho maybe and and she doesn't die so it's very different
it doesn't die in the beginning anyway but um it's very weird because Carol Kane leaves the movie
for like 45 minutes and I thought it was like her being stalked so it's a very strange structure to
the movie but I liked it enough I'm glad I watched it and that led me to the little girl who lives
down the lane which is another one that I kind of associate with when a stranger calls uh because it's
started as a TV movie and it became kind of famous and I always wondered is this some kind of fucked up
movie like it's Jodie Foster at age like 14 or something I was like what is the plot and it is it's
pretty fucked up movie she is a girl whose mom is mom is like an alcoholic abusive person you don't
see the mom her dad is also unseen but when he dies basically he's like I can't let you fall under
your evil abusive moms clutches so I'm gonna give you my house and he basically lets this girl live
alone in a house and kind of make her own rules and she's very mature Jodie Foster is excellent in the
movie as she always is but when you see her as a kid and this is why Scorsese Castor and
Alice doesn't live here and taxi driver you know he she's a talent from from day one huge talent
but you're watching it and you're like okay so I guess the theme here is that the theme seems to be
kids should be able to live by themselves and make their own decisions which is an interesting and odd
theme but then Martin Sheen starts coming over to visit and he wants to fuck Jodie Foster
very odd early role for Martin as a as a pedophile he keeps dropping by and like making passes
Jodie Foster befriends this kid in the neighborhood they start having sort of a relationship you can't
tell if it gets sexual or not but it's uncomfortable again because she's a kid there is a scene where she
takes her clothes off and I actually looked away I think that's just something to do with getting 40
getting to be 42 40 also but it's like it's weird and when you look at the Wikipedia page apparently it
was a big controversy they asked Jodie Foster to do a nude scene and at 14 she was like no so they
brought in a nude double so there's a scene where Jodie Foster is taking her clothes off and they cut
select the ass and side boob of a grown woman but it's made to seem like Jodie Foster it's very
strange and uncomfortable Jodie Foster I don't get that because they had to attack she's
driver they had to bring in her older sister to do the scenes yeah with kytel where they were like being
like sexual in any way and that was not nude that was just him like kissing her and stuff like
I don't get either and she was apparently very upset with them because I think they did it without
her knowledge and she didn't like that everyone thinks this is her nude body and she was a little girl
and there's a there's a weirdness tied to it for sure but I mean the movie the movie feels like a
pretty solid movie of the week you know it's got a TV feel for sure but there's a real
weird and kind of unsettling sinister vibe to it it's not horror definitely wouldn't say
there's some real ridiculous shit in it like that basically she keeps saying my dad's upstairs my
dad's sick and at the cop comes over and it's like why need to see him I can't keep just taking
your word for it I need to see him and this guy she's dating comes downstairs dressed in a full
mission impossible style old man mask and wearing some of her dad's clothes and like pretends and she's
like oh my god what a great idea and they hug and everything but you're like why did he have an old
man mask on him you know there's some things in it that just don't add up but it's got a nice unsettling
vibe to it I enjoyed the film I think it's on like five different streaming services right now for
some reason so it might be public domain at this point but worth a watch you know all right good enough
good enough and now we move to the the old universal horror classic the invisible man which is
currently on the criterion channel and elsewhere it's based on the hg wells short story and it
starts clawed reins Joe have you read the original story no I'm not much a reader yeah I need to read
more no I never read the original story you know I was curious to go back and read it after seeing
the movie but you know these I think like anything else literature has a certain shelf life
you know unless you're really truly you know have a laquacious as they say appetite for it you know
it's tough it's kind of tough to go back and read some of the hg wells stuff if you're a science fiction
or suspense or fantasy fan because of the language in which it's written it's it's a lot drier you
know right and it moves at a very different pace so but that's not the discredit the writing it's just
you know again it's a little tougher for somebody who's not an avid reader for me to get into but
I was excited to watch this movie it's been on my shelf for I've had this universal complete monster's
blue ray set for as long as I can remember I got a great deal on it a couple of years back on Amazon
and I finally at Halloween cracked it open do the one with with the 10 films or the one with like
50 because I actually upgraded to the the one that has like the invisible man returns the
evil man goes on a high I have I have that one it's the it's the full set same I got it like on
Amazon one day for like $45 it was a crazy deal but um so I'd seen many of the movies in this I just
hadn't seen all of them and one of the ones I'd never seen was the invisible man so I popped it in
finally and I got to say on first watch you know um sort of hiccups and hurdles of films of
that era aside yeah it's a 1933 so like it's it's even earlier than most of those classics like
Casablancaid Wizard of Oz it's about 10 years before that yeah I thought it was awesome I thought
it was an awesome movie um and it really brought up all the stuff I had said in criticism we we
had slightly different opinions of the on the remake yeah I loved it but it really brought up
well then we had very different opinions because I remember hating it but it brought up the criticisms
I had of the remake and it reinforced them which my first and strongest and foremost will always be
a universal horror movie should be fun in some way and this establishes a very fun setting immediately
it opens with a snowy road on a dark night how much did you want to drink at that bar
while it like those outside all I could think about the whole time I'm serious it's it's sense so you know
you're in it yeah you go into this weird rustic tavern in the middle of nowhere there's a man
wrapped in full bandages coming in it starts it it hooks you in man it's creepy it's weird and
thought this is crazy and then I also thought you know if me Joe and Vince were sitting at the
roost and somebody walked in covered in bandages I doubt we'd bat an eye to be honest I think we've
seen things almost that crazy in there for sure for sure but um you know just from the jump like
the the how mysterious and demanding he's being with the staff I must have a robe and I must not
disturb don't I say yeah it just kind of sets the tone and then when the in keepers will not
leave him to his privacy he finally says okay you don't want to let me have privacy then you're
going to get what you deserve and he takes the bandages off for the first time in an amazing
effect especially for that time period where they're unraveling and he's not there uh all the effects
just fantastic yeah and he's cackling laughing and it's just fun it's just like this is
and it's a similar plot a guy becomes invisible and loses his mind um you know the Elizabeth
moth one moth one I would give the criticism that Richard Mathis and gave to the remake of his
terror at 20 ,000 feet which is John lift gals starts in a manic mess as a manic mess where do you go
from there and that was my biggest issue with the Elizabeth moth one was the guy starts as a terrible
piece of shit and then it just there's nowhere to go um whereas this was like a once promising scientist
right deteriorates more and more and becomes more and more sinister throughout the movie um yeah
it's clawed reins uh from Casablanca and he gives just it we especially because you don't see him
I mean what an amazing vocal performance he's so funny uh and so conceited like when he comes in
they're like they just like want to like knock on his door basically and they're basically saying hello
and he's like you're crazy to know more about beyond you you're dying to know who I am like he's a huge
ego maniac and uh the voice he uses is so funny he's kind of over the top and you don't really see him
until the very end but to me he was he was perfectly over the top the in one of them originally
what's that the casting didn't want him the director wanted him director was like that's our guy
in the cast oh yeah he was like they're producers were like are you nuts this guy's terrible
and uh he's so good and uh his love interest is glorious Stewart who you might know as the old woman
from Titanic uh the lady who was like 90 years old and got nominated for an Oscar so
that's kind of a cool uh movie fact the lady who plays the like the lady of the house the lady who
runs that bar is one of the most over the top performances I've seen in my entire life outrageous
and hilarious right hilarious they do a few they cut to a few reaction shots of hers that like
curly from the three stages would be like hey let's tone this down like she does like a triple take
at one point but I will say and the movie's only 70 minutes yet another reason to love this thing a lot
of these universal movies are only uh an hour yeah get in make it out yeah and the story is told
you know you don't feel like you're missing anything but um that lady goes so over the top and she
screams every line that I will say by the end of the movie I I was praying that the invisible man would
just pray that it would happen soon it does like as he throws it down the stairs at one point
does something a lot of people in this killing some people I love that she's bossing the husband around
like the husband the big surly tough you know bar owner husband is like afraid of his wife
you know and she's screaming at him the whole time that's very comical for that time period
I love the fat dumb cop that they have as kind of comic relief as well you know at one point
he tells the the guys telling them what the plan is and he's sitting there like he might as well
be eating a sandwich but yeah he hears the plan that they're going to use to catch in and he's like oh
yeah that's okay like a real sort of modern comedy like he he's like not impressed by the plan
that they're going to use there's funny stuff in it uh details really great details that I'm
assuming came from the book but you know I love when Claude Reigns goes back to his um associate's home
yeah and basically takes his associate hostage and says like you're going to do my bidding
because I have I I now have unlimited power because I'm invisible I can do anything I want I can
torture you I can murder you you'll never know where I am and if you want to live you'll do my
bidding and the guy reluctantly agrees but like even in that scene when Claude Reigns is laying
out the rules for how they're going to coexist and like at one point says like you know you you can't
look at me while I eat yeah because you can see the food digesting and all that stuff I was like
that's such a cool cool detail to put in there man like that little stuff to me you know I don't know
if they got into that I never saw hollow man I didn't have any interest but I don't know if they
got into that hollow man I know they didn't get into it in the blunt house version but I haven't seen
us in the theater but in hollow man it's like the second he's invisible he's like oh sweet I can
write people now yeah yeah for some reason the plot of hollow man and it's it's not not fun to watch
really well that's in the uh that's in the comic book version of the league of extraordinary
gentlemen the invisible man they when they go to recruit him for the team they find him at a
convent uh and all the nuns are becoming pregnant they think it's a macular conception is happening
because he's fucking them while they sleep we're okay um so they don't know how they're getting pregnant
so I wonder if that is an aspect of the book um because that is something that's re occurred in some
of the invisible man mythologies yeah but um I I think you know seeing these if you don't
have if you haven't had the chance and you have the money to buy some blu -rays I would highly
recommend buying some of your favorite universal monster movies um on blu -ray uh these things look
to me this is I always felt this is what blu -ray was made for I you know there are certain new films like
if you you know a new star wars on blu -ray or 4k obviously is gonna look as yeah great as it's ever
gonna look but you know something like uh and we've talked about on the show something like um you
know demons were demons too or house or you know one of these eighties horror movies that we all know and
love blu -ray to me doesn't do it a great service because it makes something that needs to be a little
shady and dark and shadowy to crisp but you look at these old black and whites and they just shine
man they look spectacular contrasts that you get in these pictures yeah it's like you don't want
to clean up Texas chainsaw massacre but these movies were designed to look as beautiful as possible
and in black and white so like they when cleaned up especially for stuff it's a hundred years old I
mean it it does look incredible and you were supposed to hundred years old Jesus yeah I mean 33 to 21
yeah yeah wow uh this guy James whale did I mean several of them he did Frankenstein
brighter Frankenstein and then uh the old dark house which I haven't seen but but is beloved as an
early horror movie as well it's on shutter um yeah was like gay man which is which was not uh done
at that time yeah at all but um yeah he's a great visual director there's some of the the issues
that a lot of people have with with old movies which is like there's a couple scenes where they're
clearly both talking into a giant potted plant that you know must hold the hold a microphone
sure you know and those scenes are a little awkward but it's film history too so there's kind of a
a dual enjoyment they're great stories beautifully told they're funny but it's also a great way to
see how early films were made because these effects of like you know a gun floating around in the
sky or whatever it's it doesn't look all that much worse than like memoirs of an invisible man with
Chevy Chase you know like no they they did such an amazing job and they're inventing this technology
on the fly at that time most movies were people sitting at a table talking so there's a special and
they're so fun especially at Halloween time you can watch yeah and have them in 10 hours there's a
special feature on the blu -ray where they show how they do the famous scene of the unveiling
in front of the mirror yeah and it's a composite shot it's four cameras they to shoot the reflection
with the bandages the reflection without the bandages the profile of him with the bandages the behind
the thing it was like crazy it was just crazy like and and it was all being done through composite work
that was being shot in camera no you know you couldn't erase things back then you couldn't just you
know there was no computer effects right um you know so it I agree it's these these are marvelous to
watch for that reason but not that reason alone and then um these universal news they're also the perfect
like Sunday rainy afternoon movies like they're just they're great man you know it's a kind of
cloudy day and you you don't want to get out of your pajamas putting these on and
watching them in bed or or on your couch it's just they're very comforting man like it's
they're just a great experience yeah it's it's it's fun I'm so glad I had the set I've definitely
seen all of the main ones in that first set that I owned and then sold which was like Frankenstein
bride creature the black lagoon the the flagships of each franchise but I have not seen any of the follow -ups
like the the more the returns or Frankenstein goes to war or whatever it may be so I'm excited to see
him I don't I'm sure there's some that are better than others but um definitely that first run
it's it's pretty hard to beat that's why they've been trying to to do it again now for
100 years they they they had the Tom Cruise whatever that that whole side thing fell apart
I forgot that the other day that they did a whole picture of them like this is going to be the
new universal monsters and it never materialized because they weren't doing well no because Dracula
untold which I thought was kind of a cool movie uh didn't do well and establishing a new Dracula
but I thought it was still a cool movie both man didn't do well with Hopkins which I thought was
but fun I wanted it yeah I wanted it to be way more awesome than I was and then the mummy I didn't see
but it man it bombed the new one who was even in that new mummy well also Crow played Dr. Jekyll in it
yeah and um and then cruise cruise wasn't the I don't forget who played the mummy I you don't
even remember it's crazy that that movie just like came and went and nobody gave a shit cruise never
has bombs like that no no once in a blue moon but very rare yeah the worst you could say about
cruise is like was that movie he did where is the pilot smuggle in the drugs yeah yeah yeah how
much talking about the worst you could say is something like that where you're like it didn't get a
lot of attention but it was critically claimed or whatever yeah yeah so um anyway folks go check out
those blue rays two hogs or way up I believe for the invisible man yeah I mean I was telling Joe I
follow a lot of friends and other people on letterbox and it seems like everyone washed invisible man
around Halloween uh people are discovering it loving it and talking about how funny it is and
that's very cool for a movie that old uh criterion channel currently has many of the universal horror
classics but you can find them elsewhere and you can usually if you keep an eye on it get great deals
on the on the blue race set yeah and the sequel stars price so I look for yeah we should do
sometime on the show Abbott and Castello meet Frankenstein because I truly do think it is the greatest
of all hard times as I was a child but I own it I would love to all right all right folks we'll be
back next time with uh wrong turn and perhaps a little discussion about wrong turn two um Joey Rose
is gonna discuss wrong turn two for sure okay well then we'll discuss wrong turns one and two uh Joey
Rose is my sandwich shop slash bar is as you're hearing this this is the week we are opening uh the week
of the november 15th we are doing our soft opening events this week which will lead into our
grand opening either this weekend coming up or the following week but this is it keep your eye out
uh it's happening thank you all for your interest in support I'm super excited follow us at Joey
Rose's hard eight on instagram and twitter and I'll be seeing you I hope incredible I intend to make
a trip across the country to try this sandwich sooner rather than later um that's all we got folks we'll
be back next time to talk about those wrong turns thank you for joining us thank you to Emily thank
you for being patreon supporters we love you we'll see you next time and we'll see you in l