Folks, it's a very special Christmas edition of We'll See You in Hell, where you're
a new favorite podcast host, myself and my partner, Pat Walsh, bring to you discussion
about a very Christmassy movie, The Day of the Beast.
The Day of the Beast.
Joe and I were looking for a new Christmas title.
We like to do a Christmas movie each year, Christmas Horror, and yeah, this is one that
Joe Bob did.
I've heard a lot about Spanish film for a little education for our viewers.
Did it live up to the hype?
We'll find out in just a little short time.
My cat likes to wait until I start and then start tangling herself in the cords, wrapping
herself in the earphones.
She's become like, she's old too.
She's like, would be like a 90 year old woman, but she's just getting ripe.
Yeah, it's like she's gone, like she spent her like young cat years sleeping and now
that she's old, she just wants to ruin your day.
That sounds like what a 90 year old person in general would do, you know, take youth
for granted and then try to ruin everybody else's life.
Joe, did you have your parents out for Thanksgiving?
I did for the day.
OK, what did you do?
Have we not talked since Thanksgiving?
I don't think so.
Oh, that's right.
Well, no, because when we recorded the episodes for the first.
We recorded those before Thanksgiving, I think.
Yeah, yeah.
No, you're right. Here we are.
Before Christmas, my folks came up for the day.
It was just the three of us.
We they brought the entire Thanksgiving dinner.
I supplied dessert and an antipasta.
OK, for beforehand, where I went down to little Italy
and bought all sorts of meats and things.
Why do they call it as pasta?
Just because like it's Italian, but basically your food divided
into two groups in Italy or what?
I pasta and antipasta.
I mean, if you were to take it literally in English.
Terms. Yeah.
Which I'm assuming that's not what it is, but.
I think it just means it's because it's the meal is usually pasta.
This is before.
OK, the antipasta.
This is the repost repost.
I think they like to give it a devilish.
All right, sort of tone, you know, and why not creepypasta books?
Speaking of antipasta pet.
Oh, well, wait. So, yeah, so then they came up.
We we ate.
My dad and I drank some wine.
OK, we watched Christmas vacation.
Love it. Never gets old to me.
Never. My mom, surprisingly.
Throughout the entire movie with William Hickey was like,
oh, I hate him.
What? I hate the voice.
And I said in the character in the movie, she goes,
I hate this character in this movie.
I hate him in everything. Wow.
All right. I mean, I completely disagree.
I disagree, too.
But he does always play a very unlikable sort of person.
So like, maybe that's more what it is.
Did he ever do it like a twilight zone?
Was he a 40s, 50s actor?
He didn't get famous till Kritzi's honor.
I I don't think, yeah, I think he I think he broke in the 80s.
You know, as a character actor, I don't know.
I mean, I'm sure he was probably in stuff when he was younger.
But what a dream, you know, to like do whatever you're going to do for your life.
And then you become like a beloved character actor in your 80s.
What a dream. He wasn't in his 80s in your 40s.
Yeah, we've we've I think we've talked about this.
I think he was in his 60s when he died.
I think he had a you know, he had a condition or something, I think.
But he he oh, yeah.
He died at 69 in 1997.
Yeah, I thought he was 112 years old, you know, but
he what's it called?
He was in Tales from the Crypt.
OK, the one that Schwarzenegger directed about the old man
that trades his body for the audience.
Yeah. Yeah. Swat the swap.
Not a great one for the switch. Yeah.
It's a it's a it's not it's not one of my favorites, but it is a like
that is a quintessential Tales from the Crypt, like the the the twist of irony.
And yeah, every every part of it is so Tales from the Mad Scientist
and played by the guy from
well, that guy's in a bunch of tales from the crypts.
He plays the bartender in in
cutting cards. Right.
I forget the character actor's name, but so, you know, they're showing that
that beloved, I guess it's the first ever Tales from the Crypt.
At the Los Feliz three this week on the Santa one that Zemeckis did.
Yeah, it's a good one.
They're playing it before rare exports or something.
Jonah Ray now hosts some event up there.
I thought you meant Jonah Hill for a second. I got disgusted.
No, I was like, oh, Jonah Ray, OK.
Why aren't I hosting movies and events?
I think it would take socializing, getting out of the house,
getting to know some of the people that run these events.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
I guess you're right.
It looks so William Hickey looks like he was he wasn't a bunch of TV
and little bit parts.
He was in the producers.
As Bill Hickey, the drunk, by the way, we're talking about the guy
on Christmas occasion who goes, you couldn't hear a dump truck
driving through a nitroglycerin plant.
But yeah, he act he was in Mikey and Nicky, which I just watched
and I didn't recognize him.
So maybe he did have that voice thing come on later.
But definitely as Mikey, what's Mikey and Mickey?
You'd love it. It's Falk and Cassavetes as two fucked up friends.
It's a great it's on criteria and you would love that movie.
OK, is it Cassavetes directed or no?
No, weirdly, it's Elaine May, but she's trying to do it
in the style of Cassavetes for sure.
And she cast two friends to to do a lot of improv and riff off each other.
But they're great.
Did you ever watch Husbands like I told you to?
So I haven't seen it.
I got to I got to watch.
I should get this criterion channel, but then I never get it
because then I feel like I won't have an excuse to then buy the criterion
blu rays, which helps take away depression for seven and a half minutes
once a month, seven and a half minutes when you place the order.
And let's not forget the seven and a half when they show up as well.
That's it's usually reduced at that point.
Yeah, it is diminishing.
By the time you're watching the movie, I'm sad again.
There's no. Yeah.
Then you regret buying it and wasting your money.
It looks like the last film of Bill Hickey was
or the last major film was Mouse Hunt, where he portrayed
Rudolph Smuts, which is a really good name.
It's a great day.
I love the man in Forget Paris.
Yeah, I used to really like Forget Paris.
Oh, Yoda, you want it.
You got it.
That's the best bit in that movie.
And that's something all parents do is just read every store
name and street sign that you pass. Great bit in that movie.
He he was also in the.
Jerky Boys film, never saw it.
He plays Uncle Freddy of the famed Uncle Freddy Jerky Boys prank call.
Are there are they scripted prank calls in the film?
Are they include some improvs? What's the deal?
I would assume they probably rift some stuff, but no, they're not.
It's not like a Borat thing where it goes in and out of reality and scripted.
It's a scripted movie.
And the gag is, is that they have to use their prank
call character skills to get out of jams that they're in
with the mob throughout the film. Got you.
It's it's not a good movie, but there are funny scenes.
There's a funny there's a really funny scene when they prank.
Alan Arkin plays a mob boss and they and they prank call him. Yeah.
And they're doing like all the jerky boys lingo that they did on the tapes.
So like Johnny Brennan is doing the Frank Rizzo character.
And he's like, he's like, listen to me, you fucking milky liquor.
And like Alan, the gag is as Alan Arkin being like,
what the hell is a milky liquor?
Like he doesn't he doesn't understand a good thing or a bad thing.
I don't know. Yeah, that that seems very, very funny.
But well, the movie itself is what was the deal with them?
Were they they were passed around on on burnt tapes or what?
Like I know I've never heard them.
It was a huge.
Prank call underground circuit in the late 80s, early 90s.
And there were several infamous prank callers
and the jerky boys were became the most famous of them all.
But there was another guy who did what was called
what was known as the Amanda White call,
which is ranked on many prank call.
This is the greatest prank call of all time.
To this day, nobody knows his identity.
He says he calls himself Mark Knopfler when he calls people
of dire straits. Yeah. Yeah.
OK. He never references dire straits.
He just says his name is Mark Knopfler. OK.
There was Captain Janks.
There was the two bar guys that the Simpsons based the Mo prank calls on.
Always great.
Yeah, that's like a real series of prank calls
where these guys called this place called Two Bar.
OK. You can go like, you know, is there a coal cuts there?
And, you know, and they just keep calling the guys getting more and more angry.
At one point, he cuts.
That's not a good one.
No coal cuts is coal cuts there.
You know, it's like coal.
Yeah, like the dumbest.
Was it were they were they ever like clever, like a Phil Hendry,
or was it just simply like, you know, cheap gross out kind of?
My dick hurts kind of stuff.
I mean, a lot of them are very clever.
The jerky boys especially are like, yeah, they're fucking brilliant, man.
Like, all right, I'm going to check them out.
Start with the first record and just move forward.
But they're they're they're they're so fucking funny, man.
Like and some of it is just pure aggression.
But a lot of it, too, is just is really funny character stuff.
And they do a lot.
Yeah, Johnny Brennan still does it.
He put out a jerky boys record a couple of months ago,
but him and it was him and this guy, Kamal, but Kamal doesn't do it anymore.
They've had a falling out, unfortunately.
But I would start with the first record and slowly move through.
And they kind of changed the game on the third record.
They started doing a thing where they put ads out and had people calling them.
OK. And just running people in circles on the phone, like saying that, you know,
the ad would say like they had lawn equipment for sale.
Uh huh. You know, the like ridiculous shit.
It's really funny.
But I'll just look up the the Amanda White call is out is pretty outrageous.
The whole premise is a guy just calls a guy's a woman's husband.
Yeah. Starts asking if his wife is home.
And the guy's like and he just keeps asking more questions.
And he's like, all right, well, tell her Mark called him.
I'm getting pretty excited here to talk to her.
And the husband's like, why, why?
And he starts getting pissed.
And that's the that's the whole premise.
He gets the guy so fucking mad.
It's going to get the wife killed.
Yeah. And then at one point, I've never heard this in a prank call.
He flips it on the guy. OK.
So in the middle of it, the guy's just like, he's like, what do you expect me to do?
What do you expect me to do?
You expect me to just sit here and be calm while you, you know,
call by my way.
And the guy's like, what do I expect? I expect you to hang up.
It's a fucking prank, asshole.
It's not real.
And then by the end of the guy who did not trust his wife, clearly
got revealed on that call.
And by the end of the call, the prank guy is being like, all right, then I got to go.
I got to go. The guy is going on.
It's all right. I'm crazy.
It's fucking crazy.
Anyway, you used to call, do prank calls and dial
sex chat lines and stuff from we do that in neighbors' garages.
If they had a phone in the garage, we'd sneak in call.
Love it. We used to do prank calls.
I was always terrified doing them, that we were going to like go to jail.
Yeah. Or something.
I didn't understand how the law worked.
And it was scary.
I once called 9 -1 -1 from a Denny's because I got sick of waiting
for my parents to pay the check.
And they were like,
this is illegal.
And someone is coming to where you have placed the call.
Probably bullshit.
But I was terrified for weeks after that,
that like they would know where I was living or something.
Got a ticket to Barbados.
Yeah.
Till things still things cool down a little bit.
Eight years old, packing a suitcase.
Smoking a chain, smoking a cigarette.
Yeah, it's a.
It was a different time.
It took until I saw the movie Shortcuts,
where when I was probably 18 years old,
that it occurred to me that the women on those sex chat things
might not be the women they use in the advertisement.
Couldn't believe it.
Neither could I.
Yeah.
Neither could I when I first when that was first revealed to me.
I think I discovered that
when I saw CB4 and they had
Shirley Hemphill being from what's happened and being like a pit,
her number was nine seven six piss.
She was talking really sexy and porn pit.
And I was like, I bet that is what it is.
It's just like a regular lady.
Yeah. Like just saying crazy shit in a room, you know.
Yeah. Dark.
That's something I think I would have enjoyed doing in another life,
but I bet it doesn't pay great.
I bet at the time it did.
Yeah, possibly.
I know. I mean, in the in shortcuts, she's literally like
changing her baby while she does it, which I found an extra layer of disturbing.
Remember the Seinfeld where Jamie Gertz does it?
Yeah, Gertz. She was something is.
Where is she these days?
I don't know.
She could be one like your morning where you Google her
and decide that you're going to get married because she happens to be single.
Done that 18 times with the with the dark haired woman from Weird Science,
not Kelly LeBrock, the the the one that Wyatt hooks up with.
Oh, sure, sure.
She's a yoga instructor, I believe, or a Pilates instructor in L .A.
She's like fifty five.
Looks like she's your age today.
Get out here.
Said it on the radio once.
So if anybody can introduce me to this woman, I want to meet her.
Didn't happen.
Well, tell her you got a podcast that'll get her on there.
And then one thing leads to another.
I usually lead with Hoagie store.
If podcast doesn't charm her out of her negligee, Hoagie
store definitely will.
How's it going over there?
It looks like a fun time over on the the Instagram.
I mean, it's fun.
It's it's going pretty well.
All things considered.
But now this this this rain of COVID now, yeah.
So you're like, I mean, we're allowed to be open.
A lot of places are voluntarily closing.
Yeah. And you're in your own like we had a good night last night.
Girl friend of mine brought her birthday party in.
And we were pretty busy.
But, you know, you're sitting there legally operating a bar
and you're and you feel like you're doing something wrong
because COVID is happening.
And and then I, you know, then I start getting nervous.
Like my whole thing this week, I was supposed to go to a concert last night.
I bailed because I'm trying not to see czar face.
And I didn't go because I was there.
Rapper. Yeah.
OK, they're different from Scarface.
The rapper. Yes. Yes.
But I didn't go because I was I was like, I don't need to test the fates here.
Like I'm seeing my folks this week. Right.
And my folks are vax and boosted.
Everybody I know is vaxed.
And some of them are boosted.
I don't I'm not worried that I'm necessarily going to get anybody sick.
But it's like, God forbid, you test positive for COVID.
It's like you can't.
That's it. You can't go home.
You got to just sit in your house.
So now I'm scared still that I'm going to test positive. Yeah.
I mean, look, I got boosted.
Wife hasn't yet. She's in medicine.
We're traveling next week.
I think most people are traveling next week.
And apparently this is insanely contagious.
So it looks like we're just heading into the exact same scenario.
Yeah. Did last year and the year before.
And apparently the booster does nothing against the Omicron or booster.
Yeah, it's I even as I was getting it, I was like, why am I doing this?
But they said apparently that the first dose or two doses
you had are like water by now, and you need to get the boost.
But then again, why am I believing what anyone says to me at this?
It's nice of them. Can you hear that?
What I like is that, yes.
It's me pouring a glass of wine.
Well, OK, not even three hours somewhere, not even out of my bed clothes.
And I might have to work later. Yeah.
But I don't give a shit anymore.
I hear you. Who was the who was the gentleman
who orders five sandwiches at your bar that I saw on Instagram? Charles.
So that's he's dropping 50 bucks a day in there. He came.
It was wild. He came in yesterday.
He was like he ordered three sandwiches and I go.
He does them one after the other.
Not like he's not like a bar fly who's drinking all day.
He doesn't drink at all. He just gets the sandwiches and leaves. Wow.
So he ordered all three or not all three.
There's more than three, but he ordered three.
And he said, Charles, I've seen you in here before.
Thanks for coming back.
Have you utilized the two for one deal
that you return customers can get with with this card or whatever?
He said, I've done it four times.
And I was like, wow, so you really like the sandwiches.
And he's like, yeah.
So he gets the sandwiches, he leaves.
Comes back hours later, and I was like, what are you doing back here, man?
And he's like, came back for another sandwich fifth of the day.
And I was like, holy shit.
And he and he was like, it's not the first time I've done this a bunch.
He knows a picture on the wall.
So what's the deal?
You you order, you get a coupon to get two free next time.
One free. There's there's hours, certain hours in the day
where you can get two for one if you're bringing back the coupon,
if you have it on you.
But yeah, but he was the second guy
that I'd met this week that had done five in a day.
It's great. I got to get out there.
I loved Pepitone's comment.
You could admit that Charles is a paid model.
I thought that was very I didn't see that.
That's very funny, because I
I wish I saw that.
I always troll Eddie on Twitter or on Instagram and write.
It'll be like him getting a standing ovation and he'll be like, thank you.
You know, Boston, what an amazing show.
And then always right.
It's embarrassing that you would superimpose yourself
in front of a standing ovation like this, grow up.
So that's funny that he did it back to me.
Yes. Yeah. Yeah.
Anyways, I actually do for Thanksgiving.
Well, we got way off of that. I'm sorry.
Oh, please. I'm used to it in this in this friendship.
I went up to Sacramento to see my wife's family.
Old sack, old sack or new sack.
Those are the names of the two neighborhoods.
Old Sacramento is called old sack.
I think we were an old sack.
It was wrinklier than most.
It was it was completely unmemorable.
I don't I mean, we had a good time, you know,
ate the turkey, you know.
Yeah. Yeah.
I don't I find the older I get.
I like Thanksgiving meal less.
I used to order it at diners.
I'll get the Thanksgiving meal, whatever.
Nothing drier than the Thanksgiving meal at the diner.
You got to douse the cranberry sauce with gravy.
Well, I don't like it's just I don't like that.
The turkey, the mashed potatoes and the gravy are all like beige, you know,
like it's just a visually boring meal.
And then the cranberry, I think the only reason cranberry is still in the mix
is because it's the only thing with some real flavor.
Well, you got real color issues on Thanksgiving.
The green bean casserole ain't nothing to write home about visually.
The sweet potatoes look like literally look like slop. Yeah.
Any time any of the other greens you might see, you know, a broccoli and cheese.
Yes. You know, it's you know,
they're very bland colors to remind you of the hellish winter you're entering.
And then it's also like a giant like a big softball sized roll.
Like we don't need the roll.
God's sake.
Like it's just it takes up too much space.
It's another beige, not colorful, not good tasting thing.
I don't know. It's dull to me.
I've always been offended by the biscuits at a dinner, at a meal.
Yeah. I just like you.
You want me to take you want to give space for me.
And the other delectables to this role,
get the fuck out of my face. Get out of here. Shame. Shame.
But Christmas will be my first time back in Missouri in quite a while.
You're going to Philly.
Well, Jersey, my folks live in Jersey now.
Oh, sorry. Yeah, that's OK.
So I'm going down there.
And Christ, man, I'm just like.
I don't know, just fucking trying not to get, you know, I had a cold last week.
I did three rapid tests, all negative. Yeah.
So I assume it's, you know, you can hear it.
It's a it's a head cold.
It's going around. A lot of my friends have it. But.
But it's reassuring to know that they've also described
Omnicron is feeling like a cold.
Which, yeah, if that's all it is, what I don't know.
I'm not going to say wash.
What the hell are we doing?
I don't understand.
I don't know.
Wouldn't the rapid tests tell you if you had Omnicron, too?
Or, yeah, but then they say you got to get a PCR
because you can't trust the rabbit.
But then every time you get a rapid test and I ask the person,
how reliable is this?
They go rapid test is ninety eight point five PCR is ninety nine.
It's like what do we we're splitting hairs here for Christ's sake. Yeah.
You know, so now I'm like, I don't want to take another test
because I don't have like if I don't feel sick,
they say that you're not contagious.
So don't take a test if you don't feel sick.
But then I want to be safe because I'm seeing my folks.
You know, who the fuck knows what I'm lost.
I'm lost.
Would you get your folks for Christmas, Pat?
Let's talk about that.
Oh, nothing yet.
I mean, what was that five years ago?
The speaking of beige, that jacket for my dad, which he's never worn.
The all time arguably greatest moment on the show.
I haven't gotten him anything yet, and I should.
My mom does the same thing every year.
I don't want anything.
You know, there's nothing I really.
But you have to get her something.
So it's like, but I have to get you something, Mom.
So come on. My dad had a good chuckle.
He I texted him, you know, do you want anything?
What do you want for Christmas? What can I get you?
He goes, oh, no, no, no.
Just seeing you is more than enough for me.
Don't need any gifts.
And then a list of 10 things he wanted.
It's funny.
No, it wasn't intended as a joke.
Oh, but you said he had a good chuckle.
I thought you said just a chuckle at my dad kind of chuckle.
It wasn't a bit. That's a great bit.
No, he's that wouldn't have been a bit. No.
He wanted like a like New Balance gift card.
My God, like, do you just like Google dad dad gifts?
Yeah, the my friend Jim would call my friend Ritz every year on his birthday.
Yeah. And then go on and on.
I can't believe my present got lost in the mail again.
The fourth year in a row. This is ridiculous.
I thought it was a funny bit.
It is. That's a good bit.
Air sirens. There you go.
Let's this the swan song of.
Soothing sounds of New York City.
That's what I meant to say. What's the swan song again?
Is that death swan song is your last song.
Siren song is actually what you're listening to.
But a siren song is like a beautiful woman going like,
like calling you to her to kill you.
Not necessarily. It could be to blow or make love to you.
They fuck you and kill you though. Usually in Greek literature, I believe it's,
that's the thing is like they lure you in with the, with the beauty.
Yeah. I wish I had taken that message to heart, you know,
excuse me. Tied to this succubus right now.
She there? Yeah. She's walking, getting ready to leave.
Okay. Does she think jokes like that are funny?
She get a laugh out of that. Yeah. Usually a mock offended, you know,
okay. Good bit. Good bit.
I'd like to get married just for the bits, you know,
like that's because you watch a lot of sitcoms. Yeah.
The husband might tell you, Joe, it ain't all bits, baby.
Um, I've told you that Lucille ball story, right?
It takes one second. My old coworker worked, or she, uh,
was friends with a bagger at her local grocery store. It was a very old guy,
black guy, which I think is kind of important. And she goes, uh,
so what's your story? Like, what'd you do before, before this? You know,
what was your life like? And he goes, well, for many, many years,
I was the live in assistant or live in a help Butler,
whatever to Lucille ball. Oh, wow. And she goes, oh my God, that's crazy.
I love Lucille ball. She's the funniest. And he stops bagging,
looks her in the eye and goes, miss ball. Ain't so funny at home.
One of my favorites, just everything you'd ever want to know told in that one
you could see it in the interviews. Like the old interviews were there.
You could shoot. There's not a glimmer of light in those eyes, man.
She is fucking, uh,
I'm kind of excited to see this be in the Ricardo's, even though I,
I don't understand the casting at all, but you know, I'll check her out.
I'm boycotting it because I'm offended that Javier Bardem is playing a Cuban.
He went through it. He was like, he goes, look, and I'm not,
I'm not going against any of these actors,
but why didn't anybody say anything when Affleck and Damon were playing French
soldiers in the last three months ago? He's like,
so all white people can play all white people,
but I have to play like the tiniest group that never gets parts.
He's, he's absolutely right. I saw that. Uh, I gotta tell you,
I'm fine as Hollywood will hear him say that and go, you're right.
We next time we'll get two French actors. So the last dual can bomb even harder.
I have no problem with him portraying a Cuban physically is my issue.
He doesn't look at all like Ricky Ricardo or Desi Arnaz.
He looks more like Desi Arnaz than she looks like Lucille Ball.
See, I think she looks a lot like Lucille once they had her in the, in the getup.
I guess I haven't seen her cause they were kind of trying to hide her in the
trailer. It seemed like, but I'm going to watch that with my folks on Christmas.
That's a good one. Yeah. And I'm going to watch the Rocky four new edit.
Tell me how that is. If it's worth my while.
Apparently it's a completely different film,
a much more serious movie and apparently it's great.
All right. I've heard the real thing to watch is Stallone doing his commentary
on it. He talks about like all the mistakes he's made in his career.
And like, it's apparently an amazing discussion.
Six drinks in. Yeah. Well, all the mistakes he's made in his career.
I mean, that could be a 12 hour thing movie ends and he's just talking over a
black screen. Yeah. Oh, sure. They love you. Nor in part three,
ask him what they think when part five comes out.
Uh, that's a, that's a franchise with legs, man. Better, better, uh, um,
better movies across the board than the Halloween's it's,
it's a more consistent franchise than Halloween Friday the 13th. Uh,
a lot of your big ones.
I am of the belief and opinion that there are only two substandard Rocky films.
Yeah. Part two and part four,
the original part four I thought was cartoonishly, um, uh, patriotic.
And, you know,
and then all the other shit that everybody's made fun of over the years,
the robot and all that stuff. But I think one is amazing.
I think three is great. I think five is a really, really interesting story.
I think six is one of the best in the franchise. Rocky Balboa.
I was crying in the theater, but Rocky two, in my opinion,
and I, I'm do a rewatch has always been my second favorite.
It's just the original, except he wins. I mean, it is the dream.
A lot of people love to, I never really liked to,
cause it focuses too much on like too much Adrian in a coma.
It's Adrian a coma. And that's a lot of him being like, Hey Adrian,
we got money now. Let's buy a car. You know, like I just,
I just was never, it didn't have the, the weight of the, the first one.
It was more like, can this guy prove himself versus this guy, you know,
the blood, sweat and tears to prove himself to himself.
The second one's about him sort of proving himself to the press. Right.
And which is fine. But then, but in the third one,
I felt like the stakes came back because it's like Mickey dies.
He's up against the toughest opponent ever. Yeah. You know,
and even in the fourth one seeing a parent, so apparently a lot of,
here's some of the changes in the fourth one. They got rid of the,
in the new version, they got rid of the robot, which is great.
Wasn't for like 83 minutes or something that I don't know.
I thought I remembered it being short as hell.
I don't know what, how much they could cut, but yeah, they got, they got,
well they've added stuff like they've,
there's all this alternate footage in apparently apparently they completely
strengthen the relationship between Creed and Rocky.
Apparently the fight between Creed and Drago is a
lot more even. Okay.
So it makes way more sense that they don't call the fight sooner. Right.
They take the robot out and my friend was telling me too,
it sets up five way more. There's way more of a set up to five.
Like when five opens and he's shaking. Yeah. And he's like,
something's wrong like, cause he gets, he's got hit too hard. He said,
they set that up way up more. So when it goes into five, it's like, oh,
of course this is what happens now. Yeah. So, um,
he just said it's a much more serious film and it really gets way deeper into
like the relationship of Apollo and Rocky, which is awesome.
Because then it further justifies the Creed movies, which I love Creed one.
I thought Creed two stunk, but, um,
Creed two did stink, but Creed one was, uh, I mean, I was just like,
this franchise is going to go forever. They can do no wrong.
They keep reinventing themselves and it's always good.
If he said right now, yeah,
I'm going to make another Rocky where Rocky fights again.
I'd be there opening night. I mean, this, this, um, yeah, it's, it's,
it's Indiana Jones. It's Han Solo at 80. It's all those things. I'll,
I'll see it. Um, I'm there. I don't care.
Best thing they did in Creed was give him the, uh, the old lady glasses.
I just, that was such a great character touch. He's got almost like,
like what are they pink bifocals in that movie? It just, it made the character.
It's exactly what he would be wearing.
Cause he found him. Didn't,
doesn't he say he found them in the lost and found at the restaurant or
whatever? I think so. How did Adrian get into a coma in part two, by the way,
did Rocky swinging at somebody and hit her by mistake.
Is she in a coma or she just in the hospital because of pregnancy
complications from my recollection,
they shoot her in a coma from every possible angle and it takes up about a half
hour of the film and it's very boring. Yeah,
that was probably a lot of Shire's got to do Godfather too. Right. Yeah.
How do we write around it?
Well, no hours of footage or in a bed. No, it would have been after Godfather too,
which means she wouldn't get another acting role till Godfather three
or rad. I guess the BMX biking film, by the way, I haven't watched it yet,
but I heard last night that Joe Bob showed Gator bait and
that was a VHS I got as a gag gift from my friends as a birthday
present. And it was basically deliverance,
but with a hot woman who gets revenge on them and is also naked the whole time.
And I laughed at the gag gift. I never opened it. And then years later,
I sold it on Amazon for $500 VHS Gator bait.
You know, rads been re -released finally. I got it. I have it on Blu -ray.
Cause you need to see it in Blu -ray. I'm sure.
I want to actually see the film to see how bad it is.
I've never saw it as a kid and it was long out of print by the time I'd heard
the stories.
My friends and I used to watch it at least a couple of times a year and just
howl laughing. It's, it's amazing. So it's one of the best, so bad, it's good.
Better than room, I would say for sure. And that department.
All right. Yeah. So, oh, yeah, no, that's what I,
yeah, let's go. Let's go to the movie.
Okay. So yeah, I'm going to do a couple of TV shows here to kick things off.
The first, that's what I'm doing. All TV shows today.
I did my whole movie corner yesterday. So I, I still have some,
but not quite enough.
Nothing for the next step is enough. I got three shows for this episode and
that's it.
All right. So that means you'll be tapping your watch the entire time I do
mine. Yeah.
A lot of heavy exhales.
As I'm sure your most annoying friend has told you, uh,
succession is a very good show.
Everybody loves talking about succession and I've enjoyed it.
They just finished their season three by the guy who did peep show.
And I think that really, uh,
dark bleak worldview and sense of humor really shines through.
Thing is I got a little annoyed, I guess, of it being so quippy.
It's all these amazing actors led by the amazing Brian Cox.
And they're always quipping as if it's like a multicam sitcom.
And for some reason it took me out of the show. I don't,
I don't know why it was more quippy than peep show,
which was a standard half hour comedy. And I was like,
why aren't they letting any like humanity in?
Like these people never say a single kind word to one another.
And I've been watching this for like 30 hours. Then I finally clicked.
They don't think these people are deserving of humanity.
These are the people who are destroying our world financially. Right.
And the quips are a defense mechanism because they don't know how to
communicate with each other.
Kieran Culkin in particular can only communicate in these sarcastic quips,
even when he's trying to convey emotion.
So the quips and everything took on the sad tone. I don't know if it's,
everything seems very deliberate and intentional with the show.
And I think that guy is a genius. I mean, he did peep show in his twenties,
but, um, it's, it's just very,
very good. And this third season is the best season.
I think most people thought it was going too slow,
but they were trying to really dig into these characters who I think are just
fascinating. I had written them off as all being one note,
just being mean people in general. Uh,
this year I just thought they outdid themselves. And the last three, four,
in addition to being very funny, uh,
just had like big jaw on the floor twists again, amazing acting,
amazing dialogue.
And you get a real sense of who these people are at their core and their
emotions and so forth, which is what I was craving.
I highly recommend succession. Not that you need to be told again,
but it is a very good show.
Well, we've talked about it briefly, but I'll go into another HBO show.
Uh, Curve is now, I don't know, six episodes in or something.
What started as a sort of disappointing season initially,
little slow has only gotten better with each episode.
And by the last episode, which was titled, what have I done?
Because that's what Larry David says to himself after he has sex with Tracy
Ullman's character. Tracy Ullman is really good on the show.
She comes in, man, with a grand slam performance,
like playing, I feel like they're friends. And he was like, Tracy,
I need you to be the most off -putting human being that has ever lived.
Well, I mean, I bet, you know, she's probably been on their list.
She's in the HBO family and,
but I bet he was waiting until they had the perfect part for her or something
because she really does just kill it. And you see Vince Vaughn,
all the other actors just like playing themselves.
She came in with a full character. She's far from herself. It's great.
Yeah. Always complaining about gas. Like it's just, she's amazing in it.
Uh, and I, I, I, I, the show is really, really, really stepped up.
I like, I like, um,
I love where they've got Garland's character,
especially since Garland just got, he parted ways with the Goldbergs officially.
Right. I saw him seem like he was done anyway, but like, I,
did you read that interview to me? It was the best interview because he clearly
didn't care about losing that job.
So he was able to speak freely and openly and he knew Larry David would have his
back. And I like both sides of the interview. They were both like,
at least acknowledge that we live in a world with human beings,
which these stories often,
which I thought was cool. And I thought I liked that he was just like,
it just comes down to a difference of opinion.
I joke in a certain way and people weren't into it and it was,
none of it was, seemed to be sexual. It was all just like,
they thought it was like my vagina hurts stuff like that. Yeah.
And then like the one thing which has been on every set I've ever been on talk
like that, you know, but, um, he, uh,
I love that they've reduced his character now to just being,
a piece of garbage. Like he's always been, I mean, he's, he's,
he's had an affair every year, but I think this is the first time there,
he's like paying for abortions and so forth.
Yeah. And you know, the whole thing with the, with the shower gel,
where he's like, oh yeah, fucking look, one guy's Elon Gold's assistant.
And he's like, I'm going to kind of smell like this.
And my wife doesn't know like,
Yeah. And they cut to the assistant and she's like 21, you know,
yeah. Yeah. That, you know, uh,
I like the Larry David doesn't even fight him on any of it. He's just like,
Oh yeah. Okay. All right. That's pretty crazy. You know, like, uh,
you know, they, it is, it is late era Seinfeld at this point,
the characters have become sort of caricatures of themselves,
which is not necessarily a bad thing that happens at the end of Seinfeld,
which Cheryl has just become wholly unlikable. She's just awful. Yeah.
All the time.
You get the feeling that Larry's taken out some stuff on his real life,
ex wife on that one.
Susie is just fucking miserable, like constantly.
Jeff is a piece of garbage. JB smooth says,
tap that ass in every single scene he's in. That's,
it's like, that's all he talks about now. They, they,
and nobody does physical humor anymore,
but when they shot those shelves falling down that JB
smooth that I was just, I, I rewound it again and again,
like I used to rewind like a great fall that somebody would do.
I used to love falls more than people getting hit in the nuts,
but like the way they had each shelf,
like almost like a mousetrap lead into bringing down the rest of the unit,
just a beautiful thing. I didn't like the Josh Gad underwear episode.
And Larry David has done that before where he stopped going to his therapist
cause he was wearing a thong, bad underwear. It's like the exact same story.
I, I, I enjoyed Josh Gad in that episode. Okay. I thought it was funny.
I, I hear you though. He is repeating certain things.
Yeah. You know, they, what did they just repeat where I was like,
he did this already where it was, um,
he just did this. There was the thing that's pretty often the new episode.
Yeah. Where I was like, he already, he already did. Oh, no, it wasn't.
I was rewatching the Steve Coogan episode with the therapist.
Yeah. Where he's got to impress Cheryl's therapist.
So Cheryl will take them back and he stages the purse snatching. Yes. Right.
And I was like, that's what he did in season four that made him, but it was real,
but that's what makes the woman he's starring in the producers with one of sex
with him. Right. Exactly. So I was like, well, maybe he's just saying like, no,
this worked before. So I'll do it again. I don't know. But it's,
you know, even though I would put this probably near the bottom of the curb
seasons, I just feel like I'm happy to have it on the air when it's on.
I'm happy that the episodes are 45 minutes or whatever they are. It's just,
it's a joy each week.
And shout outs to, uh, we're Dinsky.
I never can say his goddamn name. Right. I'm friendly with the man.
He's a good guy, but he's very John Rudnitsky. You were knit rude Nitsky.
Yes. Yeah. Uh, I know him, John from comedy and he's a great guy.
And it was really great to see him on the show. And he was very funny.
He was very funny. I love that they just blatantly made fun of the
Asia Argento scandal of her fucking the 17 year old kid.
And right. We talk about this already. No, but yeah,
I didn't put that together with Asia Argento. Yeah.
And then the great lie, the line of the season, I would,
what would have happened to you if a beautiful woman took advantage of you when
you were in high school, they would have named the school after me. Yeah. Yeah.
A great delivery. Tom Sharpling,
who I always love listening to has been talking about,
he hates this season of curb, but he,
he was marveling at how amazing he said in the early days of curb,
Larry was a terrible actor and the stories were as good as comedy
writing gets. Right. Now he thinks the writing is terrible.
And Larry David has become the finest actor on earth. And it,
I don't know that I ever saw that much of a difference in him,
but like when he's screaming at somebody, like you do buy it. I mean,
he is good at what he does. He always has been in my opinion. Yeah.
I speaking of succession,
I link over because a succession writer EP named Georgia
Pritchett did the shrink next door.
And I just watched the last episode on Apple TV.
It's an eight episode series, apparently based on a podcast.
And I'm like, okay,
you got Paul Rudd and Will Ferrell playing like eighties, New York Jews,
and using, you know, that kind of like, you know, uh,
kind of a Woody Allen, Alan Alda voice, both of them, which is funny,
although also strange because neither of them are Jewish and it's crazy what
gets allowed and what doesn't. But I'm like, okay, we got Farrell Rudd,
show Walter directing. I've liked pretty much everything.
Show Walter's done, uh, and a succession EP at the helm.
What could go wrong? Catherine Han in a supporting role.
My old friend Lindsay craft in a supporting role. Great to see her. Um,
this thing is stacked as can be. It looks great. It's got such a pedigree.
I don't know that I've ever liked a show less.
It is one of the most unappealing,
unlikable hate hateable shows I think I've ever seen.
Paul Rudd plays an asshole, which he, to my knowledge has never done.
Not that I've seen. He's very good. Wet hot. He's a great asshole. Oh,
sure. Sure. Sure. The ultimate Paul Rudd plays this, uh,
shrink who starts treating Will Ferrell for some kind of mild depression.
And by the end of the show, you know, or the podcast, it's a real life story.
He's taken over the man's life. Him and his wife move into Will Ferrell's house.
Um, he's having big parties there all the time.
He's basically using him for his money and so on. So this happened.
Will Ferrell is so good in it that it just makes you deeply sad the entire time.
You just feel sad and terrible for him. It's like, what about Bob?
If instead of Richard Dreyfuss, you know, being a loose cannon,
he just like took it and was sad that everything, everything Bill Murray did,
like, you know, like it doesn't work.
Even though that may have been what happened and even though it may have been
an interesting podcast,
you're watching Paul Rudd very slowly and the episodes get longer as they go.
They start at 30 and they end at like 55.
He just very slowly takes over Will Ferrell's life. And Will Ferrell's like,
I wish you wouldn't do this kind of wishy washy. That's it.
That's the whole show.
And the only reason I finished it was because it was Ferrell and Rudd.
And I was like, they had to do this for some reason,
but it's just really a bad show.
All right. Didn't waste, uh, speaking of bad shows,
I watched the latest installment. Yes.
I didn't get all the way through it. I'm not going to lie to you. All right.
Of live in front of a studio audience.
Oh, I watched it too.
The latest circle jerk of Hollywood celebs getting together on television for
no apparent reason other than to show you that the show is going to be a
show that they're friends with one another. Yeah. Um,
I mean, just an infuriating display.
The first I loved how they packed in 20 guest stars into the facts of life and
then the black version, different strokes.
There was three characters in the whole thing. No special guests.
It's I mean that, that, that, okay. So first of all, these, these,
these shows, and I will speak to that.
These shows started out as being renditions of Norman Lear scripts.
That were relevant to the times and trying to show people we can laugh at our
problems, which is what his original sitcoms attempted to do. Yeah.
He, these are more scripts, but from shows that he was involved in,
but the facts of life and different strokes had known none of the weight or
water carried by the previous shows like Maude,
which I don't understand why you wouldn't do Maude right now.
Do Maude would you have played B Arthur?
What's her name? From two and a half men, the mom, Melanie Linsky. No,
no, no. The mom. Oh, Holland Taylor. Yeah. You get a holler.
Maude was like, well, you're right. I guess B Arthur was probably only 40 with that
kid. She looked 70. She had gray hair. She was Steve Martin. She had gray hair.
So she was like 20. Uh, uh, but, but look there,
get fucking Katherine Hahn would be a great Maude.
She could play attitude and all that stuff.
It's like one of the Sykes would be a great Maude.
There's a lot of great mods that out there that you could,
that you could throw into this role. And it's like, you know, um,
that's a show that, that spoke to something to go back and do this again. Now,
not good times, not all in the family, not the Jeffersons,
but facts of life and different strokes.
And then to pick two episodes of each that also say nothing facts of life.
It's like about them planning a Christmas party. Yeah.
And the different strokes is the episode where Willis moves out cause he's
tired of sharing everything with Arnold. Then he misses Arnold.
Gives a shit.
And then Kevin and Kevin Hart was playing it like it was Malcolm X.
I mean he was really good, but it's just to what end the show,
you could tell that the writing on both of these shows,
I've never really seen much of either. We're just weak. You know,
they're real generic. I don't know why they picked them.
I just saw Kevin at the comedy seller. I should have asked him.
I should have asked him about this. I didn't.
I chose instead to just insult him as I do with all comedians.
I said, I, as soon as I saw him, I said, your dramatic acting bugs me.
Which he laughed at to his credit. But, but no, he,
it's have you watched that show with him and Snipes?
That's what I was talking about. No, I heard it's pretty good.
I don't know. All right. I gotta watch it. I'm gonna watch a show.
But no, it's my point is, is like,
they're not even trying to do this convincingly at this point where it's like
they're casting Kevin Hart as a 12 year old kid.
They're casting Jennifer Aniston as, you know,
and Katherine Hahn as 16 year old girls. It's stupid.
It's stupid. There's no wink to camera with any of it. There's no like, Hey,
remember how they did this? I got to tell you, honestly,
I almost thought it was almost making fun of Gary Coleman because he had that
disorder, that growth disorder. I was like,
are they making a joke about how Gary Coleman was like 25,
but he looked like he was 11 or whatever. So like,
I thought it was just odd through and through.
I didn't see the point of any of it. I understand why Norman Lear would do it.
He's 99 years old. He's still relevant. That's an amazing accomplishment,
but more power to him. I,
I do think normally is the greatest man ever to step into the realm of
television. If you look at his, just based on his resume,
whether you like his work or not, he's, he's hit consistent grand slams.
And I just don't see why they did this.
And it was just so bad, man. It was like,
it was, well, when Arnett Bateman came in in the bad wigs and short shorts,
I was like, come on guys. And then John Stewart walks in, you know,
playing a high schooler. He looks like he's 85 years old.
I mean, John Stewart at this point looks like Jessica Tandy. It's like,
you know, it's like, he took a turn there when he retired. It just like,
he looks like the ravages of time have just taken on his face.
I saw him in the, in the, in the club the other night. I thought it was,
emo Phillips.
Yeah. Yeah. And I was like, holy shit, that's John Stewart.
Like no disrespect, but I was like, but you know, why are we shoot? But,
but here's the thing age gracefully, God bless,
but then don't shoehorn that guy. It bothers me.
There's all this pissing and moaning in Hollywood about prejudice,
about ageism, about miscasting, about whitewashing, all these things.
And then they turn around and do something like this, where they act like,
well, if we do it as a joke, then it's fine. Right? No,
it's not fine.
There was a million young actors you could have put in these roles to give them
a further boost in their careers. There was a, there was,
there was a million middle -aged act, middle -aged, you know,
I know you said John Stewart, middle -aged, I mean, but truly middle -aged,
late thirties, early forties
that you could have put into these. I guess Kevin is, you know,
Damon Wayne's is 61 years old. He's playing Willis. This is insane.
This is absolutely insane. And to me, this is,
Aniston said she'll do it. If we get Katherine Hahn to do this,
Will Arnett said he'll do it. If he, if it's him and Bateman,
Kev said it's gotta be Damon. You know what I mean?
That's, that's what it reeked up to me. Maybe I'm wrong. Fine.
Whatever people helping their friends. But this just, to me,
just felt like a big celebrity fucking circle jerk. The only,
the only true casting they did to me was they had that lady from,
I guess she was from downtown, downtown Abbey.
And Dowd is from a Handmaid's Tale or Handmaid's Tale. I mean, as, as,
as a Gar, Mrs. Garrett. Yeah, she was good. Yeah.
And then they had Lithgow as Mr. Drummond. And I was like that,
those two castings make sense. Right. And like, you know,
the average American sitcom watcher is not sitting at home going,
why isn't John Lithgow in anything anymore? You know what I mean?
That was not stunt casting. That was like, no,
John Lithgow would make a great Mr. Drummond. Yeah. So, uh,
and same with Andowd. So, um,
I just was appalled by the whole goddamn thing. Why is Jimmy Kimmel there?
I mean, no offense to Jimmy Kimmel. Why is he there?
I think he puts them together, honestly.
I think it might've been his idea and I think Will Ferrell has something to do
with it as well. But, um, yeah, they were really, really bad. And, uh,
I watched the whole thing myself. My last one is, come on, come on,
the new film from Mike Mills, who did Beginners. Uh,
I really love Beginners.
I think it is an awesome movie with Christopher Plummer and, uh,
what's the boy's name? Ewan McGregs. Really love that movie.
You know, I auditioned for that. I didn't get it.
For the Ewan McGregor role?
The Plummer role. They said I looked too old. Nobody would,
nobody would buy it. Uh, well,
no wonder you're speaking out against ageism in the industry. Uh,
he also did 20th century women, which I liked, maybe not as much as most,
but I liked it. And come on, come on is pretty good.
It's Joaquin Phoenix as a documentary filmmaker,
whose latest project involves gifted children.
And wouldn't you know he has to go take care of his
nephew who's about 10. Uh,
and the kid is an amazing act. A kid,
it was the best child performance I've seen in years. I was like,
this kid is absolutely incredible.
And then I found out that the kid is British on top of everything else.
He's doing an American accent. He's 10 years old.
Is it one of these things where Joaquin's like a grizzly?
He's not grizzly, but you know,
it's the thing where they learn a lot from each other. The, uh,
the kid's father is having a bipolar disorder and a manic episode.
So the mom goes to kind of check in on him and Joaquin Phoenix watches him.
Um, at some point he has to move the kid to New York because he's got to keep
kind of moving and the kid winds up, you know, changing his life.
So it's a very, I mean, you've seen this type of story a lot,
but it's Joaquin Phoenix who's great. This kid's great.
It's good to see Joaquin playing a normal person for the first time in a long
time. Uh, I don't think I've ever seen it. Yeah, I know.
I can't remember the last time.
It's shot in black and white for no reason at all,
but it gives it kind of that Manhattan, meaning Woody Allen's Manhattan feel.
They use kind of a similar music as well. Uh, it's entertaining.
It's definitely a good, uh, one to watch with your parents.
It's not a slam dunk or anything,
but as far as guy bonding with a kid movies go, it's definitely above average.
Okay. I'm going to save my third for the next episode. Fair enough.
Let's get to our movie of the day. Let's do it. Day of the Beast.
Uh, yeah, I mean, you talk, Joe,
I'm having some sort of weird coffee issue in my chest.
COVID it might be COVID. I think I swallowed coffee wrong.
Well, I will say this.
My day of the beast blu -ray is sitting unopened on my shelf next to the,
on the shelf I have for the several movies I haven't watched yet. Yeah.
Uh, I bought this. It's next to your, uh, Warner Herzog box that ice.
And the Bergman box that's up there.
Bergman box set is actually under the TV opened to look as if I had watched it.
So when I have a lady over, she thinks, Oh, did I leave that out? Yeah.
She goes, she goes, Oh, Igmar Bergman. Fancy.
I date a zip. Yeah. I date women from guys and dolls.
You're dating, uh, Andrew Dias Clay's, uh, girlfriend from his act.
Yeah.
Anyway, so, um, it's anyway,
so I have a shelf of stuff mostly hard that I haven't seen yet that I bought
because I wanted to see it, uh, or bought because I was told it was a must -own
or whatever. So, um, day of the beast is up there. I bought it on blind faith.
I got it from the archive in, uh, in Connecticut,
the store I've talked about that the vinegar syndrome runs. Great store.
Yeah.
Was happy to give them my money for a movie that I'd never seen that I'd heard
great things about.
The reason it is sitting on open and on watch still is because it's one of the
ones I put aside based on the two sentence premise
I had heard of it and the cover art alone.
I was like, this is going to be gnarly.
I got to be in the mood for this. So I put it aside. Haven't watched it yet.
Then we said we were going to do it for this. And I said, you know what?
I could open it,
but I could also just watch it on Joe Bob and still have my copy on open.
Uh, I watched it on Joe Bob and the first thing I texted to you, Pat,
was I thought this was going to be like a blood bath, you know,
grisly, just disturbing picture. And it's like a fucking, it's not,
it's like a fucking, uh, Roberto Benini movie. It's like a, it's like a,
it's almost lighthearted. It's very odd.
Yeah. It's like Roberto Benini should have starred in the movie,
you know, like, and, and, uh,
Joe Bob keeps talking about Buster Keaton and all this. Um,
it's also violent and R rated.
And yet it's got this like child's comedy feel to it,
like a, like the sense of humor is along the same lines as like a home alone or
something. It's very, it is very odd.
Um, yeah. And it's really well made. I mean, the scenes where they're like,
you know, there are,
there are action set pieces are oftentimes very well put together,
very well choreographed,
but the movie is neither scary or funny and it's a horror comedy.
So the whole time I was just kind of like, what am I watching?
I kept thinking, you know,
that maybe it is ripe for a remake because the story should be so much more
compelling than it is.
That's all I thought about the whole time I watched it was I would love to
remake this with like Will Ferrell and have it be
lighthearted and whatever.
And then it just evolves and just gets darker and darker by the end you're
disturbed by it. But you know, the premise of the movie is,
you've got a priest who's also a theology professor who has
decoded the book of revelations and found out that the book of revelations
actually pinpoints the exact time and date of the birth of the
Antichrist, which is going to be midnight, Christmas morning,
1995 or whatever year this movie came out.
He also figures out that the location of the birth will be in Madrid, Spain.
It's a Spanish speaking film,
which also might be why some of the humor was lost on us.
It's hard to read subtitles and laugh, you know, right. But, um,
so anyway, the, the loose premise here is he's going to,
he's a man that has never sinned. He lives a pious life.
He is going to start sinning incessantly to get into the devil's good graces.
Yes. So he can summon the devil,
find the location of the birth of the Antichrist and kill the baby.
Wild premise, great premise, very funny premise.
He teams up with this obese death metal fan,
Jack Black and my remake. Yes.
And then a host of a occult TV show as well.
It's it's the kind of thing we're just armed with that paragraph.
You could probably go in and set up that pitch. It sounds like a great movie.
I don't know why this wasn't.
And it's like the biggest hit ever in Spain and won all these awards.
So it could just be, we're missing something.
Joe Bob kept talking about the political undertones. I didn't catch that. You know,
well, it won five of their Oscars, whatever their Oscars are called. And,
and, um, Goya's Goya's and the political undertones were the fact that,
um, anything that mocked the church in any way, shape or form was,
was highly, uh, I guess illegals the right way.
I don't know if illegals were, but it was not, it was not allowed in Spain.
So he said the fact that this movie had come this far and, and,
and made the statements and jokes that it did about the church and religion.
That was a huge step. Uh,
what's interesting is Joe Bob only gave it three stars. I mean, yeah.
And he's introducing the film. So you're kind of like, all right,
maybe you don't want to get as much as you're letting on here.
Right. Not a great sign,
but then also the political undertones of he was basically saying that Madrid at
that time was in the state of affairs,
that America is sort of in now where everything was very divided.
There was a lot of, um,
there were a lot of a vandal,
a vandalism events happening and people were really in dire straits.
And, and one of the things Mark Knopfler,
yes, one of the things he said was that they were lighting homeless people on
fire in the movie. And that actually happened in New York a couple of times,
right? When,
when all the turmoil and stuff was happening two summers ago or last summer,
well, to what end, why were they doing that? Not that,
not that there'd be a good reason, but yeah,
some men just want to see the well burn. I don't know what I guess, you know,
but, um, but anyway, um,
there was a lot of shit going on. So, um, I got that part of it.
It didn't, it just didn't, it didn't launch.
It starts so good.
It starts with this cold open where the priest is telling another priest that
what's happening. And, and the other priest says, we need to be careful.
He's a formidable adversary, Satan,
and he might even be listening to us now and he'll,
he'll be ahead of us at every step. And the other priest says,
we're going to succeed. We can do this. And as soon as they stand up across,
falls a giant cross falls and smashes one of the priests, I was like,
that's really funny. This is going to be funny.
And then they just didn't steer hard enough into this
guy becoming a center.
He did like mischievous little funny sort of things.
Like he pushes a mime off a stoop and steals some change from a homeless
guy or whatever. They were, they were mischievous,
but he never really toes the line.
And like there's nothing sexual, you know, like that's where I would go.
That's what I thought too.
I thought there was going to be some kind of like,
he's got to go have an orgy. And,
and then I thought also it was going to turn into like this man is being like,
sort of now he's being turned, right?
Intempted by these, these desires that he's awakened or whatever.
There was, there wasn't really a lot of that.
He did go to extreme lengths to accomplish his mission,
but I guess there were moments where you kind of thought like maybe he had,
he had kind of turned for the worst, but it wasn't very robust. But,
but there was also the,
the thing in the beginning where he was like saying like the whole established,
the plot being established was like,
it had to be that he had to convince Satan that he was
sinning because he wanted to be with Satan. Right.
And that God forbid Satan heard them plotting this, it wouldn't work.
And then in most of the times when he's like going to do something terrible
or he has to, you know, achieve some goal to get to this summoning,
you know, achieve some tasks to get to this goal of summoning the devil.
He's like telling the, like when he needs the blood of the Virgin,
he's telling her, yeah, like this is what I'm doing.
Please don't think I'm crazy. And you're like, right. That's ruining it.
Like you should just be doing these things. Yeah.
And it would be insane and damned who you
end or whatever, but like, that's it. So that bothered me.
What also bothered me was when they finally do, as you can imagine,
summon the devil, because you don't have a movie if they don't,
but they eventually do summon the devil. They run.
I, for the life of me, couldn't wrap my head around it. Yeah.
They go through all this trouble to summon the devil and then the devil shows
up and they run, they flee. I, and I was like, what did,
what are they running for? I don't understand.
Yeah. I lost the thread and had to go off Wikipedia near the end.
I was like, I'm not following this. I don't,
I don't understand what's motivating them to do anything that they're doing.
And that obviously took a lot of attention and fun out of the end of the
What did you find out anything?
No, I just sort of read,
read exactly what was happening while watching it because I thought I must be
missing something just same as you. I'm like, why aren't they,
where is the big showdown? All right, you son of a bitch, let's do this.
You know, like it just didn't happen. Yeah. It was that it was,
the premise definitely suggests a much cooler movie than what you're given.
It was also the whole thing of like, where he kept saying, like I've, I've,
I've sacrificed eternal salvation to save the world. Yeah. It's like,
but you haven't for two reasons.
If God knows that you're doing what you're doing, correct.
You're not fooling God. God is omnipotent and omniscient.
He would know that you were doing what you're doing for a reason. Yeah.
That would reward you if nothing else. And then number two,
you're not sacrificing it. If every time you do a terrible thing,
you're basically almost apologizing. Right.
So I just didn't quite get it. Um,
I thought that the friendship between the priest and the,
and the fat sweaty metalhead was endearing. Um,
I was bummed to see that. I think he dies at the end, right?
He does. Yeah. He's a big actor in Spain.
He did these movies called torrent a that actually have two different friends
that wrote for the American remake of torrent a,
which was supposed to star Sasha Baron Cohen and will never be made now,
but it's like the most hit basically it's about a racist cop and it's a broad
comedy. So it's like a racist, sexist, misogynistic cop. All right. Uh,
it'll never get made, but.
Yeah. So I, I, uh, I liked the character quite a bit.
I thought the relationship was endearing. Um, I would have, you know,
when he does,
when the priest does do something that causes a potential future dilemma for
him, for instance, he accidentally murders the,
you know,
the madam of the bed and breakfast he's staying in or the hostel he's staying
in. Yeah.
None of it ever really seems to come back and bite him in the ass.
When he's fleeing the scene of the murder,
the cops are pulling up as he's walking out of the door and they don't,
the cops don't go, Hey, you. Yeah. Yeah. There's just,
there's so many little moments that just don't add up and it leaves you not
giving a shit about anything.
It shows you how important it is in a movie to make sure everything checks out
and makes sense.
So I guess from a life is beautiful type standpoint
and also in a country where apparently, you know,
making anything light about the church was, was, you know,
really, which is not allowed.
I guess that it's sort of, is it, is it an innovative film and interesting,
uh, and, and, and tonally interesting, uh, and I guess challenging in its own way,
but, but to, I don't know,
I feel like to see this now with all the hoopla around it. And I was like,
and I really thought this was going to be,
I thought this was going to be like a Cronenberg esque, like, or, or like early,
early del Toro, you know, like I just, I just,
I'm really was very, very disappointed. That said,
I thought the bones of the movie itself were good and it deserves a better
treatment. The director went on to do many,
many things that are very interesting. And apparently he has a script.
He's circulating, as Joe Bob said, that is so not PC.
Nobody will make it. And Joe Bob would even say what the premise was,
which is nuts. We all, of course want to know what the premise is, Joe Bob,
and you can say it, you're on a shutter, but, uh, no, I felt the same. It was,
it just left me cold. Um,
but maybe it means a lot to the Spanish people in which case great.
It's certainly a, like, like I'm saying, the action, the stunts,
the choreography and stuff that was all good. The story itself,
I think needs to be remade or at least something in the same world,
because it just, the whole time you're waiting for it to kick off.
And it never really does. In my opinion, it's on shutter.
Give it a watch if you want, but I think it's safe to say two hogs down here.
Yeah. I'll give it a hog.
Down, not straight forward, sort of tilted.
Like you just peed. Yeah. Like I'm, like, I,
like I'm pushing P out in cause I'm outside and I want to get it done fast.
Okay. Fair enough. Uh, speaking of Cronenbergian,
there's nothing more Cronenbergian than the film we'll be doing next.
Videodrome directed by David Cronenberg. Uh,
we will see you next time and we will see you.
In hell.