Welcome to Will See You In Hell, the podcast you turn to when you want to hear discussions
about your favorite John reflects. I'm Joe DeRosa and I'm Patrick Walsh. Hello, everybody. We are
what are we one day away from Halloween on our end. It's Friday, Friday before Halloween.
Oh, I thought you meant it was the day before the election, folks. It's a kind of scary.
No, the election is in whatever three days, four days, it's a heavy weekend this year.
Yeah, everyone I know is just on on complete edge. I got a text from a buddy of mine last night.
I was asleep at 3 .30 in the morning and he's like, I know this is crazy, but can you talk
this morning? I was like, Hey, buddy, sorry. He's like, just disregard. Forget I sent that.
But I'm like, that's where everybody's at. Is that a sending 3 .30 AM text kind of vibe going on in
the world right now? Yeah, I was saying to you before I got on. I went out with some friends last night.
For a buddy's birthday and just got drunk beyond. I can't even. Yeah, I mean, I'm talking like John
Wayne drunk, like those stories you hear about them going around Hollywood into like chasins and
just shit faced. Yeah, yeah. I was not drinking or doing weed throughout October and then my wife
left on a trip and I just started drinking. So yeah, I'm going to start drinking today during this.
I was power eating ring baloney as we were booting up the zoom here. So I could get something
into my stomach just so I could have some drinks. It's bad. We're in a good way.
I mean, yeah, it's past the point of funny, you know, and I think I think our meters in terms of
like what is acceptable are just going to be so off going forward. There's no even base decency
anymore. And I don't know where we go from here to see Trump Jr. grinding his jaw like a full
on meth addict. Like, have you seen this clip of him? He's waiting to be interviewed and he's just like
sparks coming off of his teeth. He's so coked up on air talking shit about Hunter Biden. No one cares
about. And he's like, well, look what people don't understand about Hunter. And it's like that's not
having the bombshell impact you thought it was going to have because nobody in the world gives a
shit or knows who Hunter Biden is. We know who you are because you're on Fox News every night grinding
your fucking teeth. Um, this is how far battle is sons, you know, like it's pathetic. This is how far
all of it's fallen or how contradictory it's all got like, you know, I texted you the other day.
And I said, can I have one moment of consistency please with the headline attached of
Putin. Putin criticizes Trump's criticism of Biden's businesses in Russia. I was like, what the
fuck is happening right now? And then I saw, I was on YouTube and I stumbled onto an Alex Jones
video, which those are always a lot of fun. Sure. And he said that he had he had he had die hard proof
that Hunter Biden was having sex with children in China or somewhere. Uh -huh. And he said he had
and I was like, well, Jesus Christ, let me see this. What is, what is this? Right. Let me see the,
see what Joe, you might want to clarify. Let me see what this proof is that he says he has like,
what is, what, what the hell does he have here? Like, what could he possibly have? Right. Also too,
that he could show on YouTube. Yeah. The video getting pulled out. So I'm watching the,
Alex Jones video. And, you know, you get like halfway through it and you're like, he doesn't have
any proof. Yeah. So if so I start scrolling down to the comments, this is the point I'm getting
out. I scroll down to the comments to see like, you know, is there a comment saying like, oh,
jump to this point and he'll show you the, you know, dossier or whatever. And as I'm scrolling down,
Alex Jones fans are going, you know, Alex either show the pictures or shut up. If you don't have
any proof of this, I can count Alex Jones's people are turning on it. There is, we are zigzagging
all over the place. No, it's, it's real bad. It's real bad. The, um, my favorite this week was when,
uh, after this Hunter Biden stuff, nothing came of it. And they had a, I don't know if you saw
the source that Tucker Carlson was saying he had, but I got to bring his name up. I think this
is the guy Alex Jones was talking about with this magical, what is it called the magical laptop
for the laptop of death? It's got some crazy name that they've given it. The laptop, but the,
the guy's name, hang on. I will find it as God is my witness. What was it? Andy? God damn it.
I wrote it down. Andy Richter. Yes, it was Andy Richter. He's branching out these days. It's
new territory. All right. I'm going to search Tucker. You know, Andy Richter was in, uh,
scary movie too, which I watched this week. This is dropping an end bomb.
Really? Love anybody ever. I'm going to take him down. Just, just look it up in a hip -hoppy way.
Uh, in a hip -hoppy way. Yes. Okay. Well, I mean, the movie was made by black people. So I guess
it's fine. Well, it's, it's similar to when, uh, Will Ferrer was playing Robert Goulet and hit the
hard R on us, which is on his best of, it's a hilarious sketch. I can't deny it. Okay. So here it is.
There would needs more horse. The glue one. The, um, and this is one of the funniest
sentences in modern politics. It says, um, for so first off, the Hunter Biden dossier that went viral
on right -wing internet sites and was later disseminated by Trump's close associates appears to be
from a fake intelligence firm. And here's the sentence that I loved and laughed so hard at. The author
of the report, Martin Aspin does not exist. And Martin Aspin is like one step above, like looking
around the room and going like, um, my name is Hunter dossier. It's up there with Ron Mexico,
which was, things don't was telling me was the alias that, uh, Michael, uh, Vic used when he went
to get a herpes test. Oh, for Christ. He called himself Ron Mexico. That's pretty good. It's hilarious.
I don't know that he did it to be funny. Uh, or I don't know. Yeah. But it's actually calling more
attention to yourself than if you just said, I'm Michael. Yeah. That's a hairy crumb level. Like,
you know, he's gonna pinch it. Yeah. For sure. I'm doing a hairy crumb because I,
uh, whenever I hit certain pockets, you might know it as, uh, extreme depression, but I hit pockets where
I like can't laugh. Yeah. Uh, that are just like these dark bits I get into. And I've been in one.
It might be time for Harry Crumb to shake it up a little bit. I, you know what? That sounds great.
I think what I might do after we're done today is put Harry Crumb on and get shit faced. Yeah,
that sounds pretty good. You know, yeah. It's the best. Like says, hell yeah, Harry Crumb. Finally,
somebody else shares the love. Man, God, people get mad at us for liking that movie. No, I have,
I have many friends that have always loved it. Uh, now, Joe, you just sort of put your hair under the,
the rain of the, uh, the headphones. But I wanted to tell you when you first came on,
your perfect costume is a racer head. Oh, yeah. Your hair is sticking straight up. Like,
oh, I could be a racer head. I just got to put a suit on. Yeah. That's what I'm going to do.
All right. There you go. Yeah. I'll, I'll dress in a suit, uh, to get completely wasted tomorrow.
That'll be how I change it up. Also, I feel like dressing like a racer head. You're going to get like
weird golf girls who are like, he knows who a racer head is. I better make out with him.
Yeah. Yeah. And I'll say, I'll, yeah, I never mind. I was going to make a dirty joke for you to say,
do you have COVID? Because I guess you have to worry about that and STD's now.
Uh, I go by the doctor saying your, uh, Bobby, Mexico, you know, yeah, Bobby,
Mexico. Look, I'm strictly on the, she looks clean, uh, testing at this point. I don't, yeah, I'm so
desperate for human contact. I can't, I'm just, I can't anymore. Um, I was going to say, uh,
wait, what were we just talking about? We were talking about a racer head for Halloween.
I feel like I need a little more for a racer head costume than just the, I don't feel like
that's going to be obvious. I feel like they, they're going to be like, is that, who would you?
Kramer? Are you, uh, when you, when your face appeared on the zoom, you looked exactly like the
criterion blue rate cover for a racer? You don't need to do that much, but so carry that around
with me, just in case anybody's confused or, you know, be black and white. Yeah. Yeah. We're just
yell racial slurs and goes, no, I'm Kramer. Sure. Sure. And that's the joke. Uh, anyway,
I got a news psycho forest pet. Sure. Why, why wait? Why wait? Let's jump into a news psycho. I hear you.
Uh, what the hell is it? Uh, Netflix. I've heard of it. The balls on these fucks increasing.
I saw the monthly from 14 to 18. I thought that I was, I've been paying $9 .99 this whole time.
So I was, it was a double wake up call that how much I'm paying. And just as it won't do anything,
it won't harm them in any way. But I'm going to take a few months off just to say fuck you.
There's stock went up 5%. Yeah. Uh, with this jump, uh, now we did a story on without a country regarding
Netflix and cuties. Right. Uh, which I did see and I did like, uh, I thought it was actually a very
well done movie. And I didn't even want that on my Netflix history quite frankly. I could just see
myself in a, in a back room at the, at the precinct. Yeah. Showing my viewing history.
My, and I thought would be more like, uh, DeRosa's name popped up on this list twice now.
Yeah. Uh, but, but, uh, no, but, uh, it's actually a very good movie. It's quite challenging in
its own way. But I thought it was very good. Harrington thought it was terrible and that it basically
was pornography, starring children. Okay. I didn't agree with that take. Yeah. Um, but anyway,
that we covered a thing, uh, about them this week on the, on my other show because, um, they're
apparently, their stock is down like, I think it was 800 % or something like that. Right.
Because of people jumping ship because of cuties. Okay. And what I said was, I don't agree with
their reason for jumping ship. I think this, uh, movie has been completely misinterpreted and not
given the chance it deserves. And that what it is trying to fight is, is the very thing that these
people who are banning it or trying, or boycotting it, they're trying to fight. It's trying to fight
the sexualization of children. That's the point. But that said, I do like the end result. I like that
somebody's given the giant a nice fucking smack in the face. Uh, you know, Netflix, it's, it's way too
big for their breaches at this point. Uh, I mean, they are doubling. And in some cases,
tripling what your other subscription services are charging. So for, at a time for them to go up that
much, when Apple and granted Apple TV has a limited selection, but if they're, they're five bucks,
people are going to go, oh, shit, I'll just do one of these that are cheaper. Well, you're going to
lose their hold. They're, they're, that's too much. What, here's what they're hoping for. I promise you
this. Yeah. The, the strategy here is we will, uh, we will, we have become such a necessity to people
that they will now drop the other services in favor of us because they want to cut costs so they can
keep ours or people are lazy. They're never even going to realize that the price went up and, and
they'll just never cancel it. In both cases, fuck you. It's a real shitty thing to do. It's the same
maneuver or same strategy Apple takes with, you know, all their fucking, uh, you know, you know,
sort of, uh, what's the, like, they're, they're, they're tethering bullshit where every app you get
and every, and every program that you use and every website and whatever you go to, it's like,
connect your phone to this. That's, that's, that's that. And then the sky and the cloud and everything.
And then you're sitting there going, I can't stop buying Apple products because I'm just so dug in
at this point. It's going to be too much of a hit on my life. And then you go, okay, I, I guess I'll
just have to spend $2 ,000 for a new laptop instead of a reasonable 750, you know, right? What they are
doing now also is removing, uh, basically everything. So you have to buy everything piecemeal. So now we
don't have the charging port. Now we don't have the headphones. Right. Now, you know, so, uh,
dropping the computer cost with that not at all. It's like when I bought my, uh, laptop here,
I was like, okay, um, I'll, I'll be able to watch DVDs now when I go to stay at a hotel or
something. Nope. That, that drives gone. You have to buy an additional drive, put out by Apple
to watch DVDs. But instead the price keeps going up as they add all this shit. So my phone's been
completely busted this entire pandemic. And I just let it sit in the drawer. If I have to make a call,
I get it out. But I'm like, I'll wait as long as I fucking need to. I'm not make, you know,
rollin' calls all day during this fucking pandemic. Right. Right. No, I hear you. I, uh, I got the,
I just got the iPhone SE, which is basically like the smaller version of the 11.
That was an iPhone designed by SE Hinton, the author of the outsiders, correct? Yeah. Yeah.
They let it by. Yeah. Yeah. It's got pony boys face on it instead of the Apple. Uh -huh. But they,
added the button back. Uh -huh. The phone button or the home button is back on this model. Okay.
It's like a smaller iPhone. The only reason I got it was because I dropped my iPhone 8 so many times.
I mean, it was, I was getting like glass in my fingers at this point. Yeah. And they're like, well,
do I spend $300 and have the glass fixed? Or do I spend $400 and get a new phone? And you're like,
I'll get the new phone. That's the biggest way they get you. Well, do I really want to look through
this? I'll just spend another $500. It's, it's all a scam. Horrible scam. Yeah. Everything sucks.
Everything's terrible. Uh, God knows what's going to be blood in the streets in about three days. Uh,
I would venture to guess. Look, you know, I hope you guys are just sitting and listening and having
a nice time. But I think way more important than staying inside for the pandemic, which I still feel
is of some importance, at least wear a mask. The, um, I think the big issue this coming week is going
to be the impending civil war. And it, you know, it's like, you can't really say it without smiling
because it seems so far fetched. But there, there's two options. There is Trump one in which case,
I think everybody's asshole seals up and we're all like, what the fuck does this mean for us? Are
Trump loses and incites his base to take to the streets, which he will do, but he doesn't have to
do it. It'll happen. So I think, you know, like Walmart stopped selling guns because of Walmart
knowing their base and knowing how bad it's going to get. I granted all these people are armed to
the teeth already. Right. It's like, if Walmart is, is shutting down their guns at a time when
they could be doing a lot of gun sales, shits, shits going to go down, shits bad, you know,
in my opinion, and I think most people's opinion, there's a, there's a, let's take back the streets
mentality. Like they've given this kid written house hundreds of thousands of dollars
to kick out a written house who shot the gun, the unarmed man on the street. Yeah. Um, you know,
it's bad. I think they also know that if Trump is still in charge, they'll all be pardoned,
which is why you see cops now yanking people out of their cars and beating the shit out of them.
Should be fun. All right. Stay inside this week. This week's not going to be good for anybody.
Stay and kids stay in school too. Stay in your, oh, man, I, I almost started crying
yesterday. I went out for a brief walk. That wasn't why I was crying, but I have fallen
out of shape. The garage door across the street from mine opens up. And I see there are three
little girls sitting at a big table, each with a little computer in front of them, each like in
school in their garage. And I was just like, woo, like it, it's so, all we have is like our memories
of being a kid and a teenager. That's like when life is good. These kids aren't going to have that.
All right. Let's, let's change the subject. Oh my god. Yeah. So, all right. Yeah. Here's
a funny right wing thing. I don't, I think you'll think this is funny. I mean, look, I know it's
in this day and age, it's not an appropriate joke, but it's really funny. I took a walk down James
Woods's Twitter feed. He'd reach for sure. Because I just was like, what happened to this man? I was
watching Carson reruns. Also in scary movie too with Andy Richter, James Woods. He's like so
funny on cars. He's so charming. I'm like, what happened? Yeah. But he brought up the Jennifer
Lawrence story that, you know, she can, she just told the press that she confronted Anderson Cooper
because Anderson Cooper claimed that she faked her fall at the Oscars. Uh -huh. So Jennifer Lawrence
approached him at a party a few years ago and was like, you know, like I didn't fake that.
That was humiliating. And I'm like, kind of pissed that you said that I faked it. Right. And she goes
and her quote to him was, have you ever tried walking up the stairs wearing a ball gown?
So James Woods tweets, Jennifer Lawrence confronts Anderson Cooper about Oscar fall, asking him, have you
ever walked up the stairs wearing a ball gown? And then he just wrote, um, okay. Okay. Okay.
Like he still got it. He still got it. He just used it in the wrong places. He's used it in the
wrong way. He doesn't got it. I mean, that's like the joke your uncle would make it. Thanks. I know.
I know. It's, but I'm, you know, I'm just saying the man still knows how to craft a joke.
If only he would use his powers for good in some way. Sure. No, it's something I think it's with him
and with Voight and with a few of these others. I think what it boils down to is Hollywood doesn't want
them anymore. Um, they need some excuse, any excuse to why that is. And it's just like, oh, it's
because I'm a right winger or whatever. Or they go into that because there are other celebrities who
have Scott Bayo, et cetera, who, uh, who are like come join us over here. It just seems kind of now
the, the resting place for careers is like the right wing, really, which is odd to me.
Well, I mean, excuse me, how, um, Voight works a decent amount still. How? I mean, I know he's
Republican and he supports Trump, but like how hard, like woods is, woods is like dropped from his
agency nuts? Like he's like, he's like, it's like, I think a lot of it could be defined as hate
speech. You know what I mean? Like, like, yeah, he's not crazy like that, right? I think Voight's
just a little more like, it's more like, why are you a Republican? Well, except he's slapped Frank
Waley. I don't know if we were talking about that on the show or or not. He's slapped Frank Waley.
Were we talking about that on the show? No, Frank, let me rephrase my question. Not why are you a
Republican? Why do you like Trump? Right. Yeah. I mean, I always thought Voight is the same way as
being at least a, a compassionate human being. Um, Frank Waley the other day tweeted this thing
from the set of Ray Downivan, where somebody got a picture of John Voight slapping Frank Waley as
hard as he could across the face. Um, which Frank Waley claimed was because Voight couldn't keep up,
acting wise and knowing his lines. So apparently he's not a great guy. It's also like
these little pockets of bad behavior getting out are great to me, but I always just think,
yeah, I've seen worse, you know, in my short time in the business, I've seen worse.
They're just, they're, they're horrible people. And I think, yeah, not all celebrities, of course.
But you see it now with these, yeah, with these videos coming out. Um, but first it was the
hallelujah video or whatever it was. The one where they all sang. But these celebrities are so
starved for attention that I don't know if you saw this Kim Kardashian's father video, but that
to me is, I don't think that imagine. That is, imagine, thank you Mike, imagine there's no having one
a song written by a multi millionaire. But um, the video is Kim Kardashian posts. And every time
you think I'm not going to talk about these people, they, they force you to Kim Kardashian posted,
Kanye got me the sweetest 40th birthday gift. I can't believe this. I'm blown away, blah, blah.
What Kanye did was create at, at the cost of probably a half million dollars or more.
A hologram of Robert Kardashian, Kim's deceased father.
It's a two minute video that you absolutely need to watch. It's not, uh, it's not an optional thing.
But it's, it's Robert Kardashian. He comes out and there, there it is. There's the picture. They,
guess, I guess they got somebody to do the voice. He comes out and he goes, uh, I've been watching over
you, Kim, you and all your sisters and he goes, I even know it when you have one of your pee fees.
What's that mean? Looked it up. Urban dictionary. A pee fee is a pussy fart.
Oh boy. The dad makes several jokes about how he's a ghost now. And he always, he knows when Kim is
having her pussy farts. Which, so Kanye shows this to Kim and her family. So anyway, he goes on and on.
And then he says, I want to tell you how proud I am of you. I want to tell you that I know you've
married the most, most, most, most, most genius man in the world. Oh boy. This, I was thinking, now,
my, my beautiful wife's mother died when she was very young. I never met her mother, the same as
her mother who was riffing about pussy farts and talking about what a genius I am that Heather would
immediately divorce me. We have no problems right now. We are, we are, we are at a really great spot in
our marriage. Everything is going beautifully. She would divorce me immediately. And anyone I told
that story to would go, yeah, she's right to. Right. Right. Uh, I mean, look, it's a different family.
You know, it's a very different family. Yeah. I mean, I don't know. I don't know. Maybe, maybe that was,
maybe like, that was a call. I mean, look, I'm, how can you justify it? I'm just trying to find
some explanation. Maybe that was a callback. So like, when she was little, she would say, like,
I had a p -feet daddy or something like that. Like, maybe, but I mean, it is weird.
The, the other part that's going to make your, you cringe is like, we, he goes, we, remember,
we always used to drive to the grocery store and listen to this. And they play 20 seconds of, uh,
let's go to the hop. Let's go to one of the holograms, snaps and dances. I mean, it's, it's,
you have to watch it. That's all I'll say. That's scary stuff. Believe me.
Joe, let's go over to the movie corner, shall we? Yeah. Well, yeah, actually, let me kick us off.
Okay. Right. Because it relates right to what we're talking about. Uh,
Tray Parker, Matt Stone have a new, I don't know if it's a one time thing they did or if they're
going to do a bunch of episodes, but they have a new, uh, show one episode is out online.
It's called sassy news. I saw it's a deep fake thing. It's a deep fake show. Yeah. It was supposed
to be a movie, but yeah, it's made, it's made, it's made using deep fakes. And the plot of it is,
it's that it's an investigative news show where they debunk deep faking. Okay. Uh, so it's,
it's a little layered, but it is fucking hilarious. Uh,
Tray Parker plays the lead guy who's a news anchor named Will sassy, I believe. Okay. Uh, and he's
a, uh, some Will sassy or racer. I would say it's, well, it's Trump's face almost like a
rip Taylor body. Okay. And he's sassy. That's his whole thing. He's like, no, this is the sassy news.
Like he talks like Paul Lind. Okay. Gotcha. And, uh,
and it's just him trying to debunk deep fakes. And you know, so then every time he's like,
I sat down with, with Jared Kushner to discuss this. It's clearly not real. But it's presented to you
as if it's actually Jared Kushner. Right. Jared Kushner was Jared Kushner's face on a boy's body. Uh,
the boy's voice who kept calling, uh, Trump daddy and law Trump. Uh, and then they do,
then when they watch deep fakes in the show, they're so crazy and fake. Like it'll be like a puppet of
Tom Cruise yelling vagina poop. I think that's the phrase. They say, like, you know, it's a deep
fake because they make them say things like vagina poop. Uh -huh. So they'll be like, here's a deep
fake of Tom Cruise. And they show up a puppet that's like a sock puppet. Go vagina poop. And then it
comes back to Will sassy. And he's like, now that was Tom Cruise. Correct. Guys, like, no, that's
what I'm trying to say. These are deep things. It's really, really fucking funny. And it sounds
like how long are these episodes? It seems like something that would be good for five minutes.
I was just going to say it's, you think it's something, like, as I explained it, I know it sounds
like something that you would go, this, this can't last. Yeah. I don't know. The one I watched,
I think it was like 20 minutes. I laughed the entire time. They do other stuff too, but the overarching,
like, if it was, it could work certainly as a 90 minute film. Yeah. I think I was what I was
supposed to be. So I don't know how many episodes there's going to be. I saw the one I loved it.
It was really, really, really funny. And it was also one of those ideas that was so
under everybody's nose. Yeah. It's just like, oh, of course. It's on your feet for right now. You
link to it through like a movie site. But look it up. All right. We are doing this week,
the Mortuary Academy, which is new to Shutter, and is a anthology horror, three store,
actually, it's four stories if you want to count the wraparound. But so for my three movie corner
picks this week, I'll be doing three different anthology horror films. I've been watching a bunch of
I know you're a fan of those, Joseph. We'll start with the original tales from the crypt,
which I had never seen. I am slowly working my way through the television show. I'm on season four.
But yeah, tales from the crypt, you know, these things all are almost identical. You know,
the anthology horror, aside from your real shining examples, your creep shows, whatever,
you're usually talking about two that the second the movie's over, you can't really remember
anything about. You're talking about two that are really good, fun, scary, whatever with a great twist.
And what it really boils down to is these things are about as good as their wraparound because
that's how you remember them. I had to get all their Wikipedia pages out to even distinguish between
them. They're all amicus productions, which is sort of a, what do you know about amicus, Joe? British,
obviously. Yeah, amicus is a British film production company. They're sort of, they're often confused,
their movies are often confused with hammer. Yeah, a lot of crossover cast stylistically,
very similar. But I don't think amicus specialized in horror to the extent that hammer did. I think
they just, they did a few things. I watched some amicus films myself last week. I have one of the
box sets. But I like their work quite a bit. I like a lot of what they've done. I like what they do
too. I feel like they don't, at least from what I've seen, and I have watched it a lot this week,
but they've just kind of never really exploded off the screen, but they definitely keep your interest
till the end. They're all short. They're all fun. The, the real appeals of this format is that
you're the story, even if you don't like it at last 15 minutes. Yeah. Yeah. I like that first
tales from the crypt. I also like, have you seen Vault of Horror yet? Not yet. No. But, you know,
Tales from the Crypt, it's got Joan Collins with the Santa Claus one. You know, I feel like they did
that one better as the premiere of the Tales from the Crypt show. It's a slightly different story,
but the mechus one is a better version. Yeah. Second one here is basically down to one good
scare at the end, but it's a wife cheating type story. You know, he, yeah. I don't know, I don't
want to spoil the one twist, but there's one. Peter Cushing is in almost all these. Peter Cushing
to me is, while he's a good actor, it does not bring the same appeal of a Vincent price, but he's
kind of their Vincent price. And then the fourth one here is, you know, the classic Chinese figurine
and the couple's collection, which grants three wishes to the owner. I mean, these all kind of go
back to the same stuff, but the Cryptkeeper here is very dull, especially compared to what came later.
It's just an old British guy who lives in a crypt. Well, he, but he does resemble the comic book
version of the Cryptkeeper. The HBO version is very, that was its own thing. That's not what he's
like in the comics. Right. But without that Cryptkeeper. What's that without that Cryptkeeper? You know,
I don't think Tales from the Crypt goes as long as it does. I think that was a big part of the reason
of its success. It definitely wouldn't have kept going if Ralph Richardson was the Cryptkeeper throughout
the series. It's certainly, it's certainly, yeah, it was a pipe, it was a pop culture phenomenon
at the time, and it's, it certainly helped. Yeah. Really, Tales from the Crypt, I thought was fun,
but not my favorite of these for sure. Joe. I watched a picture called Ghost Story
with Fred Astaire. Yes, the Fred Astaire one. Actually, I bought it. I got it when
a screen factory was doing a big sale a few months ago. I grabbed it then on Blu -ray. I'd seen it
once before and moderately enjoyed it, but remembered wanting to see it again, and I think I got it
for six bucks or something like that. It's, it is in its own way an anthology film.
Not structured like traditional anthologies, but you know, it's about a group of men called the
something club. I forget they're the, they're the, oh, god damn it. What does, what it, it doesn't
matter. There, it's a group of men who get to old men that get together until Ghost Stories to one
another, which as I was watching the film, I was like, oh, that'd be fun to do. Why don't I
find a group of guys that we can get together with and tell Ghost, and then that's as far into
the thought I got before I was like, you would look like a fucking lunatic if you did this. This is
insane. But anyway, it makes sense in the movie. So, so you get to see one or two stories that,
you know, they sort of show you or transpire as they're telling them to one another.
But really, what the bulk of that movie is about is it's a mysterious woman is appearing
to certain people and murdering them and, you know, one dominoe leads to the next. And as they fall,
you, you know, the mystery unravels of who this ghost is, who the spirit is, or whatever.
I described this movie as a perfect, perfect Sunday afternoon. It's raining outside horror movie.
If you're expecting anything more than that, I don't think you'll get much out of it. But great
performance by John Hausman. Everybody's good at it. And a dick shot at it too, by the way, 1983.
Full dick. Who's dick, Fred Astaire? Yeah. And then he then he goes, it's not my dick, it's my
prostate. No, it's the guy that plays the counselor in Nightmare on Home Street 3. Okay.
You see his dick in it. All right. What is the context? I thought Ghost Story was like PG.
Uh, I won't ruin it. Okay. We're weirdly, I'd be ruining a twist if I told you how he sees dick.
Is it like the end of sleep away camp where you think it's a woman the whole time?
It turns out, yeah, no, yeah, they walk in on him and I got nothing. Yeah, yeah. No, just
but it's worthwhile. Again, perfect Sunday afternoon rainy, which I also think the the
Amicus pictures are those kinds of films. I think for sure. You know, that kind of thing.
I saw from beyond the grave, which is another anthology from Amicus.
I own it. See it several times. Yeah, it's fun. I mean, so it's an antique shop owned by Peter
Cushing again. I mean, him and Price would do, I think for these a year. I mean, they had six
Vincent Price nights on TMC this week and he had eight movies a night, you know.
Yeah, I mean, you throw Christopher Lee into the mix. I mean, nobody could get, I mean, they must have
just been hated amongst the other actors like, you know, of course. I mean, but to me, that's the
dream. I was watching a madhouse or no, I was watching a manhouse, but I was watching not the
cursed alley John Lericette version, the Vincent Price version. But I was watching raw meat on the
criterion channel, which is a 70s British movie. And Christopher Lee has one scene where he comes in
and shakes down Donald Pleasants and basically it's like, there's the fourth horseman. Yeah,
he's like, you know, you're out of your element, bitch is like, Christopher Lee comes in and tells him
and the scene is so fun and funny and crazy and over the top. And I was like, man, if I was 65, 70
and for the last 15, 20 years of my life, I would just do four movies a year where my only direction was
go as big and over the top as you want. Yeah, what a dream. You know, and I mean, you want to talk
about, by the way, a guy that had the greatest last act of all time. Here's a guy that in the final
decade of his life starred duly in the Lord of the Rings trilogy and the Star Wars prequel trilogy,
right? That is insane. Yeah, you're I mean, yeah, you're talking Chris Lee. Yeah, you know, because they
they all kind of wound up after slumming it, let's say, even though a lot of these movies are great
for two decades and then went out on top. Like Vincent Price got one of his best roles as Edward
Scissorhand's father, you know, like he's so good in that movie. Yeah. And then Vincent Timberton
did that stop motion tribute to Vincent Price, which is great too. But anyway, this is Peter Cushing
in a shop basically anyone who tries to cajole the proprietor or negotiate the price down anyway or
really do just very reasonable things. But then they're punished through the course of some sort of
story. Like one of the guys is punished because the guys like Peter Cushing's like, it'll be five
dollars. And he's like, what'd you take full night? And he's like, sure, he's immediately like horribly
punished for it. Is that is that I never made that connection? I could have just said, no, I'm
standing firm. Five. I never made that connection. I always thought that he was willing to give them
a better price because it was like, it is your fate to own this thing. That is going to like
destroy you. Is it a vengeance thing? I didn't, I never even realized that. Yeah. I mean, this is a
nasty fate awaits those who cheat the shop's proprietor. So like, I mean, they really leave it open
to what counts as cheating. But when I also realized is I'm such a movie buff, it usually I recognize
what's being spoofed. But sometimes when you're a kid, you see the spoof before the movie, you know?
So the Simpsons was huge for that. Like, when I was 10, 12, you'd see a spoof of something,
and I'd be like, Dad, what is this? And he's like, Oh, it's the great escape or whatever.
But there is a scene during, I mean, all the Simpsons tree house of horrors are just amazing. And they
work as anthology horror in their own right. But one of my all -time favorites is they go to this
this thing that must have been based on Peter Cushing, but he's running a frogurt shop. And
I don't even remember the specifics, but he goes, everything he asks about, there's a curse on it.
And he's like, well, I guess I'll just get a sample of the froyo when he goes, the frogurt is also
cursed. You know, and it's like each thing has a curse. It's very, very funny. But I remember the line,
the frogurt is also cursed. This one was really fun. I liked it probably more than
else from the crypt. I won't go through each one because I don't think the stories are incredibly
strong. I also don't think that the, you know, the Peter Cushing thing is incredibly strong,
although I did like at the end when he looks at the camera and is like, come by again sometime. I've
noticed the cape that the actor gets that like turns him into a real vampire or is it a different one?
No. It's like a couple of these have been set in, yeah. No, it's, he's got an out, there's an
elemental on his shoulder, you know, like what you never see. So it's just kind of like this really
cheap thing of people saying like, there's something on your shoulder, but there isn't and
I feel like it's fun. The premise was a guy gets an antique from a place. Yeah, you know,
something. There's always one of those. It's got Donald Pleasants and his daughter Angela Pleasants
are in a story where they're trying to marry her off and that one's pretty fun. But yeah, it's
again, I would call it maybe a B, you know, because there's also so from B, there's firmly beyond
the great and then there's a, they mix up immediately when you want to circus one, there's a circus
one with Burgess Meredith. I'm not there yet. God, Mike, can you look that up? I'm blanking. These
fucking things, man, I mean, you're right. They start to really bleed together after a while. Like,
it's all the same actors. They all follow rough with the same structure. Yeah. All right, I watched
my last one. Let's see, what do I only do for the last one here? Oh, yeah, this is good for the
season. I can't recommend this film highly enough. I rewatched because I own it and I loved it as
a kid. Something wicked this way comes. The Ray Bradbury story that was turned into a film for Disney
on a battery to either rent or watch. Yeah, it's torture garden. Thank you, Mike.
No, you can't rent it or download it. You have to buy the DVD, which is only eight bucks right now
on Amazon Prime. I highly, highly recommend grabbing a copy of it. Bradbury wrote the screenplay,
stars Jason Robards. You know, who's the other guy? The guy that plays Royal Evans or Royal,
no, Royal Dano, the old cowboy actor. And then last but certainly not least, Jonathan Price playing
the villain. Yeah. And easily, I would say top 10 movie villains all time. I mean, he's
fucking incredible. It's a great Halloween fall type horror movie. It's
dastardly and sinister and way beyond anything I've ever seen Disney do. Yeah, this came out around
the time of the black hole, a little apparently extensive reshoots to make it more family friendly.
So you can imagine what it was originally. It's really dark. My favorite scene in the movie is
Jonathan Price. His name is his character's name is Mr. Dark. And he, you know, he's, he's
a mythical, you know, supernatural being whatever. But the whole there's this real heavy
movie theme to the movie about loss and aging. And Robards plays a very old dad to a young boy.
Like he's like a guy in his 60s, but his kids like nine, you know. And he is just wrought with like
regret and like, I'm too old. I'm not young anymore. I can't like play with my son and stuff like
that. It's very sad. And there's an amazing scene with Jonathan Price where Robards plays a
library. And Jonathan Price goes into his library and he's taunting him to sell out his own son.
So Jonathan Price can like kidnap the kid and do awful shit to him or whatever. And the way
he taunts him is he has a book. And he's like, he's saying, I can make you young again.
The way he taunts Robards. And he's like, he's like, and he goes, 30? 30? I can make you 30. And he's
when he's soliloquies about the year and how great that year is for a man in his life, whatever.
And then he goes going, going, going, and then he rips the page out and he goes 31. And he goes
and that's a little bit gone. And he just keeps doing it. It's it's fucking amazing. It's such an
awesome sinister scene in a movie. And it's so sad because you know, it's destroying this man.
And you know, and it's Jason Robards. So the guy, the guy can act, you know, why doesn't he
want to do it? Because it's it's an exchange for him to set to turn his son over. Oh,
to turn. I don't understand. So he's 30. But then he can't play with his son anyway, right?
No, no. What do you mean? If they take the sun, he's not going to be able to play with his dance.
I know. But it's just it's just playing on a man who desperately wants to be young again.
Yeah. And this guy waving in his face like I could I could do it. I could tempt you with this.
All you have to do is tell me where your son is hiding. Yeah. And it's just it's just it's it's
that's what I'm saying. That's why I point out like Robards like the the emotion coming out of his
face. Yeah. Without he has no lines in the scene. And it's him and everything on his face is like
I want this so badly right now. But I can't turn my son over to you. But should I get it? It's
just all there on his face like it's brilliant. It's a brilliant scene. I'm going to I'm going to buy it.
I love Robards. All of his 70s shit amazing. I mean Magnolia. He's fucking amazing. Yeah.
All right. My last one was my favorite of these. And it's another amicus. Another anthology. Another
asylum. It's called a a amicus anthology asylum. This one is part of I talked about it on the
solo movie corner this month. Edgar Wright has my thousand favorite movies on movie M U B I. It's
very easy to find the list came out two or three years ago. And it's just full of great genre pictures
that he loves. And some of them are completely unheard of. I haven't watched one yet that I fell
was a waste of time. You know there's some I wouldn't I don't love as much as him but he really loved
asylum. And I'm with him on that one for sure. This one was written by Robert Block who wrote Psycho.
So pretty good pedigree there. He wrote the novel Psycho and also the movie the adaptation. So
this one is the framing story as they arrive at an asylum and he's being interviewed for a job
there to work at the asylum. And then he basically they say I'll let you work at the asylum
if you figure which of which of our inmates here used to be a doctor. No, which is just an insane
he needs to speak to the better business bureau frankly because that that does not seem like
an appropriate stipulation for getting a job. But I thought all of these were really fun. The stories
were great. There were there was a little more kind of sick funniness to these that I really liked.
My favorite is the one that I think most people are going to love which is called mannequins of horror.
And that is where a guy sort of wheels his little robot demon version of himself to life. And it's this
little thing kind of crawling around. And what these things should realize is that the best one of
these is always about a killer doll. Always. Trilogy of terror, which I also watched with Karen Black,
you know, the first two stories are average at best. And then the third one with a little
goblin or whatever is fucking awesome. This is the same way. There's just something about a killer doll
that, you know, child's play wisely decided to catch eyes. Another one that does that. Yeah,
it's not my favorite of the three stories, but it ends with the little troll story, which is, you know,
very certain what you're talking about. Right. So yeah, this is Herbert Lomb who you'll recognize
if you're a pink pant fan. And I just thought this one was a blast. It was 88 minutes. You know,
again, I'm always big on that. What I'm realizing is horror by and large is a 90 minute genre.
I've watched so many horror movies in the last couple of weeks and they're all right around 90. And I'm
always very, very appreciative of that. But anyway, I think if you're going to watch one of these,
my pick would be asylum. Tails from the crib, probably the most famous. But they're all roughly
the same. I mean, if you watch them all back to back, just watching a bunch of twilight zones,
they're all fun. They're all quick little stories. They always have a little moral. But I dig them.
And have you done your third jump? Yeah. All right. Then let's bring it to sort of the latest
example of the anthology horror. And part of what I enjoyed about it was that it has some fun
with the sort of horror or overused aspects of anthology horror. It is called the mortuary collection.
It is done by a gentleman named Ryan Spindell, who I was curious if he's the brother of Tyler Spindell,
who I met with who directed the wrong missy. But anyway, mortuary is four stories by decade,
which I didn't even really notice, but once in the 50s, once in the 60s, etc. And it stars Clancy Brown
in the crypt keeper role in the guy who runs the asylum role. But Clancy Brown is a great actor.
It's great to see him get this kind of big juicy part. And I loved Brown. I thought he had a great job.
Yeah. I don't think we've seen the last of Brown's character or the mortuary collection in general.
I think that there'll be a mortuary collection too. And I'll happily watch it. Yeah.
I think so too. And I agree. I liked, so right off the bat with this thing,
I was roped in immediately aesthetically by it, just the opening credits, the music, the way it was shot,
the set design, the intro to Brown's character when he leans down to that kid that rings the doorbell
and the mortuary and how it helped you. I was like very old Disney haunted house record.
Right. Kind of stuff. So I was hooked in from the jump immediately.
And the story unfolds when a girl comes to the establishment to inquire about a job that's
apparently available there. And she says, you know, tell me some stories about the dead bodies in
here. And you know, because he says, everybody's got a story. Every death has a story, not just how,
but why. And so he tells her these stories. And one of the things I really like that they did was they
picked four stories that hit what I think are sort of the cliche notes of an anthology collection of
stories. They're like, there's like the monster one. There's the one that deals with sex. There's the
one that deals with murder and so on and so forth. And after each one of these stories, there would be,
not after all of them, but after some of them, there would be a back and forth between this girl and
Clancy Brown's character about sort of analyzing the story, sometimes criticizing it, whatever. And
I thought all of that framework did a really nice job to explain to the viewer, this is why an
anthology is usually set up like this. This is the reason that you have this story. And this is
the reason you have that story. And you know, that's sort of thing. So I really like that
self -effacing sort of commentary that was injected into the into the picture into the narrative.
And you know, I did it in a good way, you know, sometimes that kind of stuff is like essentially
just looking into the camera and jacking yourself off. But it was fun here. I mean,
and it shouldn't have worked. I mean, this girl being jaded about anthology horror,
the 12 year old girl is kind of ridiculous. But it was funny and it worked in the context of it.
And maybe just because I watched so many this week, but it worked for me.
Yeah, I thought it was, I thought it was truly a love letter to fans of this genre. When I started
the film, I had been talking to Pinkstone about it for a while because we're both huge anthology
fans. So we always kind of try to keep tabs on if we find a new one or if there's something coming
out or whatever. And we had been talking about this one because I said, it looks like the real deal.
And I texted him within the first 10 minutes and I was like, look, man, it's, you know, it's just
getting rolling. But so far, it's a home run. Like they're hitting all, they're hitting all the right
notes here. And I felt that they did throughout the film. And my takeaway at the very end of it was
for any part that wasn't, you know, the most interesting storyline in the world or maybe a character
that I wasn't that into, it was completely made up for with mood and the aesthetics of the film
and just just the nuts and bolts of this thing were so strong that I felt like it was one worth
owning, which that's also saying a lot for me these days. I mean, I own a considerable amount of
horror movies at this point. And I've got plenty on my shelf that I could do without keeping.
I just don't get rid of them. You have a horror movie podcast, you probably should just keep
your horror movies. But this was one that I would add to the collection. And I'm very picky about
that anymore. So I like, I really liked it. And I do hope there's a sequel. And I felt like a kind of
nailed what they were trying to do with Creep Show and manage sometimes to do with it. I felt like
this was what Creep Show should have been. But again, I don't or not again, but I don't know if it's
a shutter production or if they just licensed the film, you know, yeah, I don't know. I mean,
I completely agree that it is a better version of Creep Show. And Creep Show had the name attachment.
It had the hype machine attached to it. It had me way more excited. But ultimately, I feel like this
probably was done outside of shutter because shutter just seems to only put forth the barest
minimum of money. And that's their business model right now. And they're pretty new. And I get it
and fine. But yeah, this was so much better than Creep Show that what they should do in my opinion.
And no last night, they premiered some animated new Creep Show special that I'll check out.
I watched half of it. No good. I haven't finished it and I haven't really formed an opinion yet.
I'm not a create. We should we should do an episode. One of our next episodes should be reviewing
that. I think, I mean, it's a Creep Show special. It's like, you know, but anyway, so I want to talk
about it. If I'm running shutter, I would go, hey, sorry to the guys running Creep Show,
we're bringing this guy over from mortuary collection. I mean, he's got a better grasp on anthology
or in my opinion. But yeah, it worked for me in a big way. It all the effects look good, realistic.
The so the first one is just kind of like a help wanted where this girl goes to meet Clancy Brown,
which is fun. Then there's a bathroom one where an octopus comes out of a mirror kind of. And
this movie's going to suck. And then the girl immediately goes, that story kind of sucked. I
mean, it was yeah, and I was like, Oh, okay. Then I was concerned it was going to be two tongue and
cheek. And they didn't go that route either. They were, they handled the tone very well throughout.
The second one was my favorite, which was the sex based one where the guy, the guy plays a great
asshole whoever the kid was, but he was awesome. Yeah. And I mean, for something to be that outrageous
and that silly, but they pulled it off. I think that's an almost impossible feat. And it was
particularly nuts because I was under the impression after the first couple segments that this was
like a goose bumps, you know, like a fun for the whole family thing. And then you see this guy's
dick and et cetera. But that one I thought was really, really well done. And that was the turning point
for you was that was what you saw the dick. That's when you weren't absolutely got it. And it's,
you know, it's it did a great job on praying on people's fears. I mean, it follows was a great example
of the STD horror, but I always felt there was much more to be done in that genre. And that's kind of
what this was. And yet again, and another example of a filmmaker going, no, it's not about STDs,
it's like, it's that classic, yeah, you know, George Romero being like, we didn't intend for the
main guy to be black. He just was like, you're destroying everything that makes this movie brilliant
right now. And why not just say that you wanted everyone, everyone is praising you for. You know,
I'm not adding you that the guy's black. The third segment involved a guy I used to see all the time
because he was really good friends with a girl I was dating. And now I just talk to him over Twitter
once in a while, but his name is Barrick Hardley. And he is a great actor who I have seen in all kinds
commercials and stuff. But this was kind of the biggest juicy as role I've seen him have. And he did
a great job. I loved him to the point that he was my favorite person in the whole movie. I looked him
up. Yeah, it was such a fan of his performance. That was a weighty performance he had to give there.
I mean, that was a very emotionally charged story. And I thought he was fantastic. And I was watching
it. And I was kind of like, oh, he's almost like he's got an Eric Warheim quality. He's got to
map McCarthy quality too. He reminded me of Matt McCarthy a little bit. But I thought he was great,
man. And I immediately was looking to see what other things he's been in. And he's done some horror.
But now that you've seen him, you'll notice him in like every fifth commercial. He's just got one
of those faces. But very nice man. And I thought he was great in this too. I thought the story was
just very sad, you know, and kind of off the fun track that the rest of the movie was on. But
other than that, it was it was sad and it was very, that was the one that story that was like,
this is a little too straightforward. You know, and it's it's it's a classic premise, you know,
it's it's the telltale hard. It's the person murders and then the guilt is making them
experience. Yeah, it appears to be a supernatural happening. But but that last story I loved,
I thought the twist of the last one really got me the babysitter story.
Yeah, yeah, I thought, yeah, I thought that was a really fun story. And that was another place where
they were sort of winking the camera a little bit like by showing the babysitter watching a Halloween
style movie on TV called the babysitter murders. And then like them showing you the movie inside the
movie and right it was pretty cool. It was it was it was pretty cool. I this guy clearly is a big
horror fan and as a great love for the genre and clearly a great love for a particular time of the
genre, which excites me because we've seen there's been a ton of throwbacks to one specific area of
horror lately. And that has been, you know, the stranger things. You know, sort of sure visually
poltergeist meets sound the soundtrack of John Carpenter. You know what I mean? Like that's
what all those movies are sort of a lot of these movies are tackling now with the throwbacks.
I'm very happy to be seeing now a movie that throws back to a different side of the 80s horror die
which I think is great. And it's also something that what's his name? The House of the Devil
did. Oh yeah, T .I. West. Yeah, yeah. Yeah, I was. Yeah. So I'm glad to just see another guy out there
kind of taking on a different part from that time period or a different a different approach to sort
of throwing back to a certain part of that time. But in fact, I think the movie takes place.
I mean, it's clearly the first story you're in like the 60s or 50s because of the way she's
dressed. And the second story is kind of like the 60s. And then the third fourth stories are like the
70s. Even though it wasn't clear to me. It wasn't clear to me, but apparently it goes 50s, 60s, 70s, 80s
up the way. Okay. Yeah. So I really. Yeah, I thought it was great.
That's it. Yeah. I mean, I think a lot of times the reason. What? No, I just said that's it.
I was starting to talk and you said that's it. I was like, all right, Joe, Jesus Christ.
No, I think the it is one of the better examples I've seen of anthology horror. And you know,
I've yet to see that a plus version. And I'd love to. I don't even consider Creepshow and a plus
version. But it's I hope more people want to do these things. You know, there was one on shutter
recently that Joe Bob hosted. I won't say the name of it because I don't remember it. And I don't
want to shit on it. But it was really rough to watch. And it's hard to do. Well, this one does it
very, very well. I think sometimes the reason an older movie gets classic status is because it's
been around for 50 years. But this is just as good as any of those Amicus ones I mentioned.
And considering their considered class to the genre, that's high praise. So, um, yeah,
recommended the mortuary collection. It's on shutter. We will be back next week or, you know,
we released these two at a time. So our next episode will be Borat 2 or Borat subsequent movie film.
Uh, and then the evil dead evil dead to evil dead remake episode that we've been hinting at will
come later. We just wanted to hit Borat and hit mortuary collection while they were new and fresh
in people's minds. Yeah. Yeah. Wait. Yeah. You got to hit these things while they're fresh. I say
that also at the end of my date. I just would like I'd like to hit it while it's fresh. Uh,
did that go over pretty well? Great. Surprisingly. Yeah. You wouldn't think it would at the beginning of
the date before we go out. I'd like to just hit it while it's fresh. Well, this is why it's better
to work with a partner writing partner. Uh, so yeah. So evil dead stuff is coming up, uh, uh, uh,
creep show special coming up and then whatever the hell else. Uh, but before we go, I want to point
out something, um, that story that you love in a silent mannequins of death or horror. There's a
particularly good version of that story. It was made for the monster's TV show, um, which monsters
was the follow -up to tales from the dark side. Um, I don't know why they ended tales from the dark side.
They did and then they started monsters and it was basically the same show except every episode
had to have a monster in it. Anyway, um, great version of that story done for that show. That show's
kind of hard to come by these days. Uh, I bought it on DVD, the entire series for I think $17
dollars, uh, about 10 years ago and, uh, now it sells for 200 on Amazon Prime. Um, so it's way
out of print. Um, but I think you can stream it or at least pay to watch it on Amazon Prime. Uh,
sorry, on the Amazon website it goes for 200. If you want to stream it or watch it on Amazon Prime,
I do think it's available. And anyway, just to know for you fans out there, if you want to check it out,
thanks for listening people. And Patty usually says it, but I'll say it today. We'll see you next time and
we'll see you in hell.