I'll see you in hell.
Welcome to Will see you in hell.
It's the Godzilla versus Kong edition.
Big blockbuster flick.
Try to bring us all back to normal.
Out of this pandemic rut, we've all been in, revitalized the film,
and movie going industry as they put it.
Yeah, it did really well.
It marks my second movie back in theaters.
I again went at like the most off -brand time and sat in a secluded corner.
It's fine.
You know, it doesn't feel like going to the movies used to feel.
It feels sort of scary and weird and whatever.
But yeah, I wanted to see this on the big screen.
Get out of the house a little bit.
I was surprised, as I'm sure you were too, Joe,
but I will Smith recording one of his wraps for the film,
where he sort of walks you through the plot of Godzilla versus Kong.
I miss that, by the way, wraps about the movie.
Not at all.
I'm a huge wrap fan.
In fact, I'm looking at last night,
so I have these floating shelves on my wall, okay?
Like Harry Potter floating or...
Yeah, magical.
They're charged.
Enchanted.
It'd be which, I think, is the turn.
But I had all my video games on them,
because my video game consoles are on shelves next to them.
And then last night, I realized that I had half my video games
in this closet over here that you can't see,
because I had too many.
And I was like, wait a minute.
Why don't I put all my video games in that closet
and just make it the video game closet?
No, okay.
And then in...
I can use the ladies.
I can use these shelves now for all my wrap CDs
that I have in a bar, in boxes,
because I had nowhere to put them.
So I got all my wrap CDs back on the wall,
all organized.
I got my wrap cassettes on the other wall.
I got my wrap records in the other room.
Very, very proud of this collection.
I really love looking at it.
It makes me feel good.
So no, I don't miss Will Smith wrapping the plot of something.
Yeah, have you been diagnosed with OCD at any point?
No, but I have been diagnosed with DSLs.
That you do have.
And CBH's child bear and hips.
Yeah, look, I...
What the hell was I just talking about?
You were about to make fun of me because I said I like looking at my organized collection.
Yeah, no, OCD.
I mean, that kind of opened up some doors for me.
It was when my therapist was like, you realize you have pretty severe OCD.
Lends itself more to what they call rumination,
which is where I can't stop obsessing over the worst incidents of my life and past.
But it also goes for stuff like organizing.
Like, my happiest time is organizing my collections of vinyl or blu -rays or whatever,
finding a new way to stack them so I can display them better.
It sounds like you have at least touch as well.
Yeah, I...
You move your collections around all the time.
I'm big on my collections and I've been over the last few years.
I've been big on...
grooming my collections.
And by that, I mean...
You plan on having sex with it?
Yeah, yeah.
In about a year.
No, I've been grooming my collections.
Like, you know, like, I've been tapering them down in ways.
I've been cutting the fat.
I've been focusing them.
So my music collection now is, you know, I...
Look, I've got a lot of...
Not a lot, but I've got a good amount of vinyl of stuff I really like.
But like, my vinyl, my music collection is very, very...
hip -hop focused and very hip -hop focused from specific decades of hip -hop.
So my movie collection, I have other genres,
but my movie collection is really focused on sci -fi horror and fantasy.
You know, like, that's the bulk of it.
So I like that because it just...
I don't know.
To me, when you're collecting,
it just focuses the beam a little bit more to me.
And it stops me from buying every last stupid thing
that I ever think I might want.
Which is what I did for many years.
And, you know, that's how you get to the point where you go,
do I need the opposite of sex on DVD?
Or, you know what I mean?
You're like, why do I have this stuff?
Like, you know, because you just buy...
I own precious at one point.
Yeah.
You got a name.
Did I give it to you?
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Not to name drop, but Amy Schumer had a joke about it.
She's like, you're going precious.
She owns the movie precious.
And she...
Yeah, she couldn't get over it.
She was like, why do you own this?
And yeah, I don't know.
I was like, I don't know.
I never saw it.
So I just bought it and I liked it.
But I don't think I'm ever going to watch it again.
No, it's not one you leave it.
Yeah.
I'm big on like, I'll see...
You know, like an artist I've always heard people like,
but I've never heard.
And I'll find him in a dollar bin.
So like, boss scags.
I was like, people love boss scags.
I don't think I've ever heard a song of his.
And then one day there was six of his albums for one dollar each.
And I'm like, well, shit, I'll listen.
I've never listened to...
Still to this day, I've never heard boss scags.
And I have these shitty looking albums
messing up my collection.
So I like the in and out of it.
I like a year later being like, boy, I must have been stoned
at Amoeba that day.
Let me get rid of this thing.
I bought for 20 bucks.
Then you get on Amazon.
It's going for 175.
That's the thrill.
That's the hunt.
That's the dude.
Yeah, you sound like Tom Sizemore and Heat.
I'm a lot like Tom Sizemore.
Yeah, yeah.
See, baby, to me, the action is the juice.
That's my favorite line in the movie.
Yes.
I saw a great tweet today that said,
Heat, the beauty of Michael Man's movies,
it said is that it's telling you how much you can get done
when you only get horny twice a year.
Like, that's his ethos is like,
you can get so much done if you only get horny twice a year.
And he's like, something we all could aspire to, really.
And I'm like, that's a really great point.
I mean, De Niro seems like a man who's never heard of sex
when Amy Brennan comes on to him.
And then he's like, yeah, while I'm here, I'll do it.
But yeah, I've also got to get back
to running through a parking lot with a machine gun.
Yeah.
Yeah, that scene at the coffee shop is insane.
When like she tries to flirt with him and he's just like,
why are you so interested in what I do, lady?
Like, you're like, buddy, take it easy, man.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, and then he lives in that apartment
that has no furniture.
And then Val Kilmer, I remember when he gets thrown out
his wife through Ashley Judd,
throws him out of his, he's just sleeping on that tile floor
with no blanket or anything.
Yeah.
And then De Niro goes, you want some breakfast?
And I'm like, and walks towards the kitchen
as if he has supplies to make breakfast in a house
that doesn't even have a bed in it.
The next scene they cut to him, he's in an apron.
Says every day I'm brustling on it.
He's cooking up an amazing frittata.
I just want to watch heat again.
By the way, they did a new blu -ray of heat
that I heard was like worth it for the image upgrade,
the image in the sound.
And it goes for five bucks this thing.
And if it looks as good as it looks,
it's enough to make me want to jump to 4K
and see if I feel like I'm involved in these shootouts.
Because one of the best looking and sounding blu -rays
is that new heat one that goes for five bucks.
It's one to pick up.
Just make sure you get the latest version.
I think I might have that one.
I had it on DVD and then I upgraded to a blu -ray.
Yeah.
So I feel like maybe that's the one I got.
I hope I got it like two years ago, though.
Then you probably got the right one.
There was an old early edition of heat.
I think was maybe even a flip disk.
That's how long ago it came out.
That's what I had.
I had the flip disk DVD.
Parable.
Yeah. Parable stuff.
Yeah.
I told you, I had to upgrade the thing,
which I finally got the collectors one I wanted.
The Carpenter version.
Yeah.
Because my original DVD was so old
that it was in like four three
and it had a full black box all the way around it.
Okay.
And it was just sat in the center.
It was terrible, dude.
It was like the TV was like,
what is this?
What am I doing with this?
You remember the first blu -ray you bought?
Yeah.
I do.
The first blu -ray ever bought was I bought two.
Because there was a store
called, I can't remember the name of it,
but it was in Hell's Kitchen when I lived over there.
And they sold DVDs,
used cell phones and used video games.
And I had built up
hundreds of dollars in credits from trade -ins there.
And then they closed
and never gave me the money back
or anything, which was nice.
But I got my first two blu -rays ever there.
I got Inception and the 18.
And I, the movie of the 18.
I watched the 18 immediately,
enjoyed it, then got rid of it,
because I know I would never watch it again.
And Inception set in the slip cover
for five years on my shelf.
And then finally, I just gave it away.
And I, to this day, I've never.
That was my boss's gigs.
Never saw Inception.
Every time I would look at it, I would just be like,
I don't have the fucking time for this right now, man.
Jesus Christ.
It's a pretty neat movie,
but that's one you'd want it to be a flipper
where you could stop in the middle for a little bit.
My first DVD purchase,
I went to, let's see if this is just a midwestern thing.
Have you ever heard of Suncoast Motion Picture Company?
It was in every mall.
Yeah, the most overpriced ways to buy your movies
and VHS tapes, but I went all the time.
And I loved it.
In, yeah, I loved it too.
They had, they had this big sale.
It was one of those sales before I learned
that you can just say sale
and actually not be a good deal at all.
But I was like, ooh, a sale on Blu -rays
and I just got a new Blu -ray player.
So I go in and I think the special
was $4 for $100 or something.
And I got, the green mile, I know, was one of them.
And he, but they were all that like, really shitty fl -
all that to open it.
Just not fun, not good looking Blu -rays.
The first Blu -ray I rented, I remember, was drowning Mona.
The Danny DeVito movie?
That middler, yeah.
I was, I, just the worst way to show off the system.
I just was like, it came out and I was like,
I need to rent a Blu -ray.
I think I still worked at Blockbuster.
But that was, that's not really your showcase disc
that you put on to kind of spotlight.
The many things of Blu -ray can do.
I remember, I might have told the star of the show before,
but I remember Jay Okerson saying to me,
you got to come over and check out my new HD.
It was when HDTVs came out.
It goes, I got a huge HDTV.
It's like 75 inches.
You got to come over and check it out, dude.
And he goes, and dude, I got Ford Fairlane on my DVR.
And I go, yeah, no, I love Ford Fairlane.
I mean, I already own it on DVD, though.
And he goes, yeah, but you don't have it in HD, man.
I have an, it's like, who cares?
Yeah, it's not going to look much different, I don't think.
That movie was never breathtaking.
No, no, no.
But, well, now, do you remember, I'm sure you do,
but there was a competitor for Blu -ray much in the same way
that Betamax fell by the wayside with VHS.
Was it HD DVD?
Was HD DVD?
And I had a friend named Dave, who owned hundreds of movies
in that format because he was always a fiscally smart guy.
And he did this thing where he was,
as soon as I knew it was on its way out,
I bought an entire movie catalog
because I was able to get him for 50 cents a piece.
And he was like, who cares?
I have the player, and I can watch them.
And I have HD movies.
He better buy a backup player, though,
before they stop making them.
They don't make them anymore.
Yeah, so I mean, I was like, all right.
I'm going to buy a backup Blu -ray.
I bought a cheap Sony for $90 or something,
just because it's a good little player for cheap.
But also, when this, I would say we're five years away
from them not making Blu -ray players.
They don't make new VCRs, do they?
No, I own two VCRs for that reason.
My friend told me that a friend of his just paid $600 for a VCR
for Christ's thing because they're just, you know,
they're out of print.
And then also, if you need an elderly couple,
and I left a six -hour porn tape in it,
a six -hour MMF porn tape.
Are DVD players already out of print?
I bet a DVD player could get a garage sale
or something for $5, but Blu -ray players
are still very much being made.
DVD players, I think you'd have to buy a Blu -ray player
that would play DVDs and most do.
You know what I'm going to look for when we hang up today?
I'm going to go on that old Amazon,
that old Evil Amazon, and I'm going to look up
a Blu -ray DVD VHS combo.
Because that does exist.
That is a thing that exists.
Really?
Yeah.
Yeah, there's a brief crossover period for all that stuff.
Wow, okay.
So, I think so.
I mean, there's definitely a DVD VHS combo.
Maybe I'll just get one of those.
I just got an email that I have 200 best buy points
that are expiring, and that's the kind of thing
where you could show up and you've got a 24 cent credit
or maybe I've got 20 bucks, I don't know.
200 best buy points, I feel like it doesn't.
If they're expiring and they're worthless,
it's probably two bucks, yeah, at most.
It probably means like you could trade the 200 points
towards a coupon for that, you know what I mean?
It's like one of those.
When it's real money and credit,
like it doesn't expire, you know?
Yeah.
You think that as buy would have fallen by the wayside
but you still walk in there even during the pandemic
and it's pretty, you know, it's not crowded
but there's a solid amount of people.
I guess because they keep it alive
with washing machines and stuff but each time I go
there's one less shelf of movies, you know,
like they keep minimizing it to almost nothing
but the discount ones.
The movie sections are terrible now at Best Buy.
Unfortunately, it bums me out
because it used to be a fun place to buy DVDs and stuff.
That was my go -to.
Their video game section is still going strong.
Their TV section is still amazing.
Okay.
Great soundbar department, great computer department.
It's a great place to go for like cellphones
and computers and stuff.
And I will say the people there seem to give a shit
enough to like, you know,
briefly talk to you and recommend products and stuff
which is rare these days.
Yeah, I agree.
I agree.
Then with Home Depot, you know,
if you grab somebody odds are you're going to walk away
with the correct answer which is not something
that you can count on much.
Home Depot is, it's incredible.
Yeah.
I don't know what they do at that training course
but I mean, I've never seen so many aisles
with so many products in each aisle.
And you ask anybody like,
I've gone up to somebody and been like,
I need this screw and they're like,
aisle seven on the left.
You got to look at the bottom though
because you're like,
Jesus, man, it's insane.
I don't know how they do it.
Yeah, it's, I always have to go maybe every three months
or something and when I'm in there,
it makes me wish that I was,
I was like every, every guy's dad I knew when I was a kid.
The guy just always out building to get away from the wife
and making a shit or something in the backyard.
I wish I cared or liked that stuff.
I'm usually just going in there to, you know,
pick up a point set at Christmas time or something
but the sawdust smell and everything.
I'm like, I wish this did something for me
and I was like building a project.
Maybe I should give it a try
but I feel like I would suck at it.
I enjoy a handy work.
I enjoy it.
In fact, I might do some tonight.
I got a little, I got some spackling to do
on some coals in the wall,
some cracks left from mishung things
and then I've got some touch up paint
to cover up the damage.
Anyway, so I'm going to do, yeah,
I like doing that kind of stuff.
I'm going to do a bit of that.
You know, today I put a, put a, put a, put an old spring
steam record on it.
I'll tell you what I put on the tight jeans as well.
The tight jeans, I'll tell you what D
manly is the entire thing when I work around the house
is that I'm usually doing it as I drink red wine.
And saying red, red wine.
That's right.
Right. I crank you be 40.
Yeah.
And that cheap trick cover of don't be cruel.
And then I dance around their finest hour.
I've listened to a lot of cheap trick lately.
That ain't their finest hour.
Yeah, I know.
Well, you think that ain't their finest hour.
Did you hear the new record that came out this week?
I didn't even know they had one.
Is it bad?
Oh no, it's awesome, dude.
Yeah, you love the ACDC record.
The new one, I don't know, but it's ACDC.
I still haven't heard it.
There's, you know, you know, you're going to get a little
at the very least a little like, you know,
so what if you burn in?
Do it again.
You know, like, there's still going to be gross in their own way.
Like cheap trick isn't like, they're not that kind of band.
They're not, you know, they're not like a motorhead kind of band
where they're going to not keep the freak flag going.
But then, I mean, look, they made some awesome albums too.
Don't knock cheap trick.
I'm not.
I just, I was never into them, but,
but, you know, I do agree that, you know,
dream police and all that stuff is obviously not the cheap
trick of today.
I mean, they're, they're like fucking.
Look, even dream police was not really the cheap trick.
That was a little past their prime.
Their biggest hit is from, is from lap of luxury.
It's from the dopey crow record.
Is the flame their biggest flame?
Yeah, I don't even consider that cheap trick, really.
Oh, it's hard.
I got that vinyl for Christmas one year.
I think I've told you.
Because I like the dopey work that Jesus, I hope you like crap.
What is that from?
Happy birthday.
I'm not going to take credit for it.
Maybe it was on an old Conan O 'Brien bit or something.
I have a soul Christmas record with a song on it called Happy Birthday Jesus.
That's pretty awesome.
Who sings it?
I forget.
There are, there are sort of more obscure songs,
but they're all Chris.
They're all soul Christmas songs.
It's, it's a fucking amazing record.
And it's, it's rare.
It's way out of print now.
But there's three, there were three volumes of it.
And the volume three has that sort.
I think it was a spade Hollywood minute now that I think about it.
He was like, you know, let's just say City Slickers 2.
He's like, oh, City Slickers 2 is coming out on Christmas day.
Hey, Happy Birthday, Jesus.
I hope you like crap.
I think that must have been mad.
Very funny, very funny.
I got a quick scary stuff before we go to movie town.
But I, you know, I play the old video games.
I've been, I've been adoring this to the tail end of the pandemic.
I started buying up horror movie themed Atari 2600 games.
And there are way more than you think there was an alien game
for the Atari 2600.
It's basically a Pac -Man clone.
But it's really fun.
And I got that.
And that's cool.
There's a Gremlins game that's really awesome.
Where you run back and forth.
Catching, what are you catching?
I forget.
You got to catch stuff.
It's kind of like that kaboom game.
And then the pods hatch and it turns into like space invaders.
Is the Gremlins like to send down.
That's really cool.
And then I bought, and it was the most money I ever spent on a game.
I don't want to say what I spent.
But the original version of this game is so rare
that an actual copy of it, the cheapest one I could find was $700.
And I was like, Lord, I'm not doing that.
So I bought a repro.
And the repro was expensive because even the repros are like,
Hey, dude, you're not finding this anywhere.
But I got the Texas chainsaw massacre.
This was an officially licensed Atari 2600 game.
Where you play leather face.
And you go back and forth with your chainsaw and you kill kids.
That's the game.
That's not children.
I mean, no like teenagers it's supposed to be, you know.
And when the women scream because the sound chip is so bad in the Atari,
it's just a beep.
So you're going back and forth and it'll go like this ear piercing beat.
Yeah.
And it's supposed to be the lady screaming she's scared.
It's not an amazing game, but it's certainly interesting.
And I'm glad I own it because is it rare because it was shut down for its violence
or something or just it's just rare because it's true.
It's not a great game.
I don't think it sold very well.
And I think it was just it probably just didn't get a lot of play.
You know, the same company made a Halloween game too,
which people actually say the Halloween game is actually pretty good.
But that's also equally as hard to come by.
There's an episode 13th game also, right?
Friday the 13th was Nintendo.
I have a ROM of that.
I don't have an actual copy.
But those games are I don't think or too rare.
The um, that game sucks.
I hate that fucking game.
But the nightmare known street game for NES is pretty fun actually.
Way better than you think it would be.
But the uh, the what's it called?
What the hell is it just going to say?
God damn it.
Oh, I remember an episode of the Angry Video Game Nerd
where he reviews the Texas Chainsaw Massacre game
and he buys it at the beginning of the episode for $150.
Okay.
And now that same cartridge is worth,
you know, it's worth,
some people have sold it for $1 ,000.
I mean, it's, it's worth a lot of money.
All right, all right.
Anyway, that's it.
Scary stuff.
Can you hear those people outside?
Do I need to shut this door?
I mean, it's not super annoying or anything.
I bet I can hear it.
Let me shut the door.
Hold on.
All right.
Well, let me take this over to the movie corner while Joe does that.
Folks, I continuing on the documentary theme
from our last episode watched another documentary
new to Hulu called Collective.
And Collective is nominated for Best Documentary Film
at this year's Academy Awards.
Absolutely deservedly so.
It is the best documentary I've seen
in quite some time.
And it makes you realize how cheapened
the word documentary has become.
I mean, like I talked about on the last episode,
Kid 90 is home, home videos of Salay Moon Fry.
Counts as a documentary now.
This is a really beautifully put together
expose.
It's kind of like a real life spotlight
or all the president's men kind of thing
where there's just this outrage journalist
in Romania.
He's a sports journalist, no less.
Who there's a big rock show, much like the one we had here
with great white.
What is the big, great white hit, Joe?
Once bit and twice shab, baby.
But very tragically, they were performing a show
at a small club and it caught fire and people died.
This was a very similar incident in a Romanian club.
It's a death metal band playing.
And look, you need to be aware right up front
because I felt so bad for Heather.
She's watching a few minutes of this documentary
before she goes to bed.
Like the second scene of the movie
is live footage of this place
being burned to the ground and people burning
and it was really tough to watch.
And it also, Joe, the place looks exactly
like the Fonda.
So you know how there's that upstairs
wait, not the Fonda.
What's the place at, it's not the Roxy either.
The place on the play, no, but way further down
where we saw Fumenshu with the balcony.
Oh, um,
the troubadour, troubadour, yeah, troubadour, sorry.
But it looks exactly like the troubadour
and they see a little bit of flame in the balcony.
And the singers like, oops,
well, that wasn't intentional.
That's not part of the show.
Can we get that put out please?
And then one second later, like that movie back draft,
you see this like the balcony go up completely in flames.
Everybody beneath it start running out.
It's really traumatic and it made me think
like if I'm going to go to the troubadour again,
I'm going to need to check where
their fucking fire exits are.
But this sports guy's like reporting on this story
and comes to find out that a lot of the people
who escape this tragedy with severe burns
later died, like a really
shocking amount of them died.
And they come to find out that they were using
disinfectant on these people
that was diluted 10 times
to the point where it's like water essentially.
So you see things in this,
like there are people completely covered in burns
beyond anything I'd seen outside of like,
you know, uh, return of the living dead type stuff.
And there's maggots crawling in the burns.
And so nurses at this hospital were filming it
and bring it to this guy who's reporting on it
and we're like, look, this is a guy with literally his,
his face is an open wound
and there's maggots crawling on it
and he's under our care in the hospital.
So this sports reporter uncovers this gigantic
story wherein
they're just lying to the American people
in such a shameless way that like so many people
were killed that didn't need to be by this.
They exposed the chemical factory that was diluting them.
They exposed the Romanian health care system
where doctors are literally
bribing nurses and bribing patients.
Patients are bribing doctors to get better care.
Look, as disastrous as this year has been for us
as a country, it makes you sort of grateful
that we have a better system in place than they do there.
But it's just a great straightforward look
at like how a news story comes together
and this guy is awesome.
There's people in the streets in Romania
chanting this sports reporter's name.
Great story.
They do it without any schmaltz or cheese.
It's just like really good reporting.
Definitely worth checking out if you'd like to watch the Oscars
and see the nominated movies
because this is a really deserving movie collective.
It's a foreign doc
and it's not a light watch, of course, but I recommend it.
All right, doors shut.
Do I, was it noisy when I got up to go?
No, it was fun.
All right, good.
All right, I'm all right folks, what do we got here?
I'm trying to decide which one of these I want to go with.
I'll keep it light today.
I watched the Mad About You reboot.
Start to finish.
Turned it on as a joke, as a goof.
I was like, there's no way this is going to be good.
I just want to see what it's like.
By the beginning of episode two, I was madly in love.
I was mad about the show.
Yeah, frankly.
With these characters, I loved everybody
and I wanted to keep watch and see where it went.
It was very sad when I got through all the episodes.
It was more sad to see it was just the limited series
and they weren't going to do another one.
So, Dick Kahn, come back.
Oh, yeah.
He's got the funniest line in episode one.
The last, the newest season is about their daughter going to college
and emptiness syndrome and all that stuff.
And Dick Kahn's intro is the doorbell rings.
They open the door and he's standing there and he goes,
when a child leaves the nest, it's like a death.
I brought you bagels.
He's very funny in it.
They ramp him up in that last season of it to like where he's like,
you know, if you, so anyway, I went back and watch,
I'm now watching the series from the beginning
because it's all on Amazon Prime.
I never really watched it.
Very enjoyable show.
It's kind of like if Annie Hall was a TV show,
or when Harry Met Sally was a TV show, it was a better description.
I've seen a bunch of cold opens of it.
So, it must have come on after Frazier or Seinfeld.
It was on.
I never stuck with it.
It wasn't for me.
It was on with Seinfeld on Thursdays for a while.
And there's, in fact, the,
Kramer was in the episode I just watched.
As Kramer?
Yeah.
Paul Reiser's old apartment is Kramer's
apartment.
Okay.
I bet Larry David hated the Kramer, didn't that?
Probably.
Yeah.
So, apparently Seinfeld shows up at one point too.
But like the gag with Seinfeld is like, I don't know who you are.
Like, and he's kind of saying like, he's kind of making fun of the crossover idea.
Like, this is stupid.
Right.
Apparently, but they do a lot of nods to other TV show.
There's a lot of crossover episodes.
Jerry Lewis was on one.
I just saw Carol Burnett plays Helen Hunt's mom.
Carol O 'Connor plays her dad.
Like, it's, you know, it's a very, very charming, very sweet,
surprisingly edgy show.
And it's, it's very well done.
It's the kind of sitcom where I'm like, man,
if you got to be in a sitcom like this,
this would be really cool.
They're doing like a little play every week.
This is really cool.
So, um, I like it.
I like the show.
And, oh, and then the last thing I was going to say was is Richard Kind.
You know, in the, in the normal series, he's like,
you know, he's like a nebushy guy and whatever.
But like, in that new season, they, they kicked him up into like,
curb your enthusiasm zone.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, that's what you want.
Yeah, of course.
But he's in a Carol Burnett comes back for one episode in the, in the last season.
Yeah, everybody comes back.
Everybody comes back.
And it's, uh, it's an enjoyable, uh, it's an enjoyable time.
I remember one cold open of it where they were brushing their teeth together
and she accidentally spat on the back of his head
while he was spitting.
And I remember thinking that was funny when I was 12 or whatever.
Yeah, it's cute.
It's charming.
It's a charming sweet show.
I met with Paul Reiser.
I was meeting to write on.
He did the Paul Reiser show for NBC.
Uh, maybe 2008, I want to say, and it was going to be his curb,
but, um, it did not work at all.
Andy Daley was on and who's very funny and it had a good cast, but it just didn't work.
But, um, went in and met with him.
He could not have been more of what you wanted.
Like, it was like, can I get you guys a soda?
You know, it was like going over to your friend's house and you're,
if you love your friend's dad, he comes down to the basement or something.
He riffs so hard, like you couldn't get a word in.
Just joke, joke, joke, joke, joke, joke, and then making fun of you,
you know, in the Rickles kind of way.
And, um, they eventually decided they were just going to write all the episodes themselves.
It was him and a writing partner.
So unfortunate, because I think I might have gotten the job,
but he was, he was the best.
I really liked him.
He wrote a lot of mad about you.
He was, he co -created the show, which I never know.
He was an EP on it.
Um, it's not, it's, it's an interesting show because you believe that they're in love.
That's the entire show.
The entire show is contingent on,
is the chemistry between these two actors good enough.
And it is.
They pull it off.
You believe they're a real couple,
which is a very hard thing to do.
If you took that element,
if it was, if it was two ticks to the left off,
it wouldn't fucking work.
There would be so much of the laughter is based in just their interaction
and not on punchlines or whatever.
So it's a very well done show.
But I mean, Jesus Christ, you want to talk about
you think back to sitcoms then.
And you know, you must see TV and NBC Thursday nights.
I mean, did you're talking like,
they were coming out of Cosby.
They were coming out of the Cosby show.
And being like, now we got,
you know, cheers is coming to an end.
You know what I mean?
It's like, we got your Frazier.
We got your Seinfeld.
We got your friends.
We got your mad about you.
Fuck you.
Like, it was just like,
they always had you covered with like the best of the best shows.
And then just one year, you were like,
wait a minute, something slipping here in a big way.
And then you just kept going.
I watched the last week was very puff piece type documentaries.
This piece or this week is a
docs that kind of strive to change the world,
including the 350 minute,
although you can just watch it in six parts.
Queue into the storm,
which was on HBO.
And now I assume HBO Max.
It was an absolutely riveting watch.
Joe, I think you would love it.
I don't know why this isn't being reported on,
but they find out who queue is in the documentary.
Like, that's pretty good for a documentary.
So, you know, I thought this was like one of these things we'll never know.
And at the end of it, it would be one of those,
you know, so many documentaries end now with,
I guess we'll never know who killed them.
And you're like, well, why did I watch this for 10 fucking hours?
This thing gets you an answer.
It tells you who queue is.
You meet with some of the most fascinating scum of the Earth -type characters.
All these like internet developers living off the grid in the Philippines and Thailand
and ties to child pornography and ties to all kinds of unsavory stuff.
There's a dad and his son who they focus on for most of the movie
that are just, I mean, they got to make this thing into a scripted feature.
They just will.
They're amazing characters.
And the guy kind of pulling all the strings who started the 4chan site that became 8chan
is also an unbelievable character.
I won't spoil it for you.
But to me, when it first starts and you're watching clips from the insurrection,
I was like, I don't need to be fucking watching a documentary about the insurrection two months after
it happened.
Right.
But then it just gets deeper and deeper and deeper.
I really love that it sounds like what you were describing with the Malcolm X documentary last time,
where you just sort of, I wish I had waited until all the parts were available.
Now they are because I was hooked.
I would have stayed up and watched the whole thing the first night.
Recommended.
It's a good way to kill some time while you're trapped in your home.
And it's a great way to learn about QAnon.
I knew nothing.
I think that's the best way to live your life is not knowing about QAnon.
But obviously, they're becoming a bigger and bigger force and they were certainly involved
in it. And this documentary makes it clear that they were very involved in the last four
years of life here with Trump and so on.
I urge you to check it out.
All right.
I'm going to do a rewatch.
It's in a real Keaton kick this week and I rewatched the dream team.
I rewatched the founder.
What a masterful film.
It's just a great movie.
He's fucking awesome in it.
Everybody's awesome in it.
It even makes, I love what's his name in it too.
And I usually don't like him.
The real -life Ron Burgundy guy that's married to Melissa, whatever her name is.
What?
The guy that impersonates Ron Burgundy, but in real life with the mustache.
Nick Offerman.
Nick Off.
Oh, I never thought of him at Ron Burgundy, but yes, that makes sense.
Yeah, he's always kind of, I swear, I was always like, all right, you're just doing like,
you're like, you're acting like Will Farrell in real life, you know what I mean?
Anyway, yeah, I like the founder.
I think he's great in that movie.
I think everybody's great in the movie.
I love the movie.
And Keaton even gets, God, man, the guy's so funny.
He's there like some genuine laughs in the movie.
When that scene where he finds out that one of his franchises is putting lettuce on the burgers,
and he walks out to them on the golf course, and he goes, he goes,
what is this?
What is this?
Lettuce?
He's doing that classic like Keaton Venom.
I just, he's just, it's just a great movie.
It's heartbreaking at times.
I don't know how much of it, I know that the deal that they strike that seems terribly unfair to
the McDonald Brothers is real, and that is what happened.
But I've also read interviews with them where they said they were very happy with their deal.
And so I don't know how much of it was truly like
this guy took it out from under them and pushed them out,
and how much of it was just, we signed a short -sighted deal.
What are you going to do?
You know what I mean?
So, but I am happy to report that McDonald's has started recognizing them on like the founders day
or whatever when they do that.
McDonald's has also started recognizing me when I walk in and place my order for a
400 -piece chicken McNuck.
Right, right.
They call you, and they call you Big Mac.
They go, yeah, yeah, yeah, I got you.
You know, Joe, we've, we've joked about this movie for years now on the show, but the Greg
Keneer windshield wiper inventor movie, Flash of Genius.
Your love of the founder confirms it for me.
You would love Flash of Genius.
There's, I, I don't understand how it could be interesting.
It is, and it's a good movie, and Keneer's great at it.
Sorry.
I believe you.
I, you know, I watched, look, I'll do my third down too.
I watched Mystery Man, because you said it, you said Keneer.
I love Mystery Man.
Love, I haven't seen it in many years.
I couldn't do it.
I just, I wouldn't do it.
No, I tried.
I was like, I should love this movie.
It's been still or Garofalo's in there.
Keneer, I didn't even know Keneer was in it.
Hank is area, William H. Macy has the shovel.
It just wasn't resonating.
The jokes weren't hitting.
William H. Macy being like, I shovel great.
And his wife being like, baby, you shovel better than anybody.
It's like, I get why that's supposed to be funny,
but I just don't think it's funny.
And I don't know.
I just, it just, I don't know.
I wasn't feeling it.
It was sort of the first of the big mainstream superhero spoofs.
You know, that John was done to death now.
But it was pretty fresh at the time.
I remember laughing a lot, although it feels like a movie
that was very much of its time and might not hold up.
That was, it was an Arty Lang.
It was at the Jerry Stiller roast,
because Janine was there sitting next to Ben Stiller.
Yeah, I don't remember if it was Arty Lang or not.
But the joke, somebody mentioned him,
him Mr. Human and they go, hey, Janine,
you know, you're allowed to say no, right?
It was Jeff Ross Arty Lang.
It might have been Jeff Ross.
I don't think it was Arty Lang.
Yeah, I think it was maybe Jeff Ross.
Anyway, that's also what's coming from Jeff Ross box.
Folks, I saw, while we were on, while we were on Keaton,
I got, I might as well talk about the Dream Team.
Now the Dream Team is a movie that I remember just loving
when I was a kid.
Just loving it and wasn't streaming anywhere.
So I ordered a DVD of it.
Maybe the day after I ordered the DVD,
the Blu -ray was released of the Dream Team.
I was like, I didn't even know they're still releasing Blu -rays.
And they just came out with a Dream Team Blu -ray.
The Dream Team Blu -ray just, who was asking for that?
So folks, here's where things get real dicey.
I bought the Blu -ray.
And now I have two copies of the Dream Team listed
for purchase up on Amazon because I don't want either of them in my home.
You were so excited.
You texted me at the launch of this thing.
You hit play.
You were like, I'm watching the Dream Team.
You were so excited.
I didn't have the heart to say, Pat,
I have never enjoyed that movie.
Because you know, you don't want to piss on a guy's parade.
So I was like, maybe I'm wrong.
And then an hour later, I get this message from you,
where you're like, this fucking thing got there.
Nine times out of 10, when I revisit something,
I loved as a kid.
My taste was pretty good as a kid.
If I watched something that I thought sucked when I was a kid,
it usually still sucks.
Something that I thought was good, usually still good.
Something Dream Team must have hit me at a spot
where I just had no fucking taste.
I know early on in my movie going,
when I would just see any movie about adults,
or maybe that was one of the first PG -13s I could see,
then I'd have an extra layer of excitement
that the movie did not warrant.
Keaton is doing this around the same time as Batman.
In my mind, he's visibly coked out in some scenes.
He's got that exhausted coke look.
In real life, you don't think he's doing like a character thing.
No, no, no, I mean, he was always on coke back then.
But he looks exhausted and kind of blown out in this movie.
He's got a terrible mullet.
He looks like a horse.
His love interest is Lorraine Bronco
from the Super -Rino's and Goodfellas.
I love Lorraine Bronco,
but she is the kind of actress that has to play
a certain kind of role.
It's just like, you know it when you see it,
and it's not Michael Keaton's love interest in the Dream Team.
I guess it's a year ahead of Goodfellas,
maybe, was when she did this.
She's so wrong for the part.
When the Dream Team started,
if can I jump in?
My favorite Lorraine Bronco miscasting
was medicine man with Sean Connery,
where she's supposed to be some kind of jungle scientist
or something.
It's ridiculous.
She's awful in that movie.
Yes, that's true.
And there's no chemistry between the two of them.
They like had her walking through the jungle holding
like a bagel in that movie.
It was like, what are you guys doing?
Yeah, medicine man is a terrible film
that from my memory anyway.
But Dream Team, the premise is basically,
it's Kuku's Nest with Keaton and the Nicholson role.
And the whole movie is the day out.
So in Kuku's Nest, they all go out on the boat
and have a big adventure.
This is that movie stretched to feature length.
It's a great idea for a film.
They'll probably remake it soon.
Because, and look, this is a remake job I would take
because the elements are there for it to be great.
And you just watch the movie slip away
minute after minute.
What is good about it is Keaton is funny.
Christopher Lloyd is amazing in it.
I was texting Joe about my love for Chris Lloyd.
Judge Doom, Doc Brown.
He's awesome in nobody, the new Odin Kirk picture.
He's been great for years.
Reverend Jim, of course, on Taxi.
Joe sent me something Tony Danza said was that,
Christopher Lloyd was so good.
Go ahead.
Well, I'll say it.
Yeah, I said it.
Tony Danza, yeah, Tony Danza said he was so good in,
he was so good as Reverend Jim in Taxi had heard his career.
Yeah, he said it very lovingly.
He was like Christopher Lloyd is one of the best guys I've ever known.
He's so talented.
He's so, this is what I love that why I switched gears.
So I turned really turned on a dime on Tony Danza.
I was kind of thought he was a jackass and you really like him that much.
And then I saw him in Don John.
I was like, he's a really good actor, man.
And then I saw this interview with him.
And I was like, wow, man, like he really is like a good heart.
Like you, because he's the way he said it.
He's like, he deserve more, man.
Like, you know, like he was just like this fucking guy.
So it's not fair the way it works.
Like he's, he's too unsung, you know, not that he had a bad run.
Jesus Christ.
I mean, you know, his Doc Brown, all that shit.
Yeah, he was in some huge hits.
But yeah, you know, he, like,
I don't know that anyone outside.
You have to go to dramatic actors, you know,
De Niro, whatever.
But I don't know that anyone has committed more to characters ever.
You never catch him out of a character.
Or, you know, like I was particularly watching him in this movie
because it's so boring and stupid that I would just turn my eye to him.
There's all these shots of the five guy, the four guys in a van driving.
Right.
And you watch Peter Boyle, you know, he's looking out the window.
You watch Michael Keaton, he's, he's checking his watch.
And every scene, even when the camera is not on him,
Chris Lloyd is completely this character.
And that was the one positive takeaway from the movie.
It's just like what, what a, I don't know.
I've been seeing a lot of him lately and I think he is unsung.
But the dream team is him.
Peter Boyle, who you meet completely naked,
you really see his ass and almost his dick.
Uh, Peter Boyle's one note throughout the entire movie is that he's,
uh, he thinks he's God, basically.
But it just depends on the joke.
In some scenes, he's very religious.
In some scenes, he thinks he thinks he's God.
But all he does is speak in these really shitty one liners.
He has a terrible scene where he goes to a black church and does a big dance
in front of everybody.
Yeah, I remember that scene.
Oh, miserable.
I mean, forget the, the, uh, any race, racial implications.
It's just terribly unfunny.
And then you've got,
who's the other guy, Steven first, sorry, from Animal House.
Who is fine?
I mean, he's, I always liked him.
Okay, he's playing basically the fat guy,
who's the most mentally disturbed guy.
But, yeah, doesn't he like, he's like a Gora Fobick or something here?
Gora Fobick.
It's very funny to look at like 1989.
You got four mental patients teaming up in a movie,
and all of them are white dudes in their mid 40s.
It's just like that diversity was like,
we'll make one of them fat is what it used to be.
Yeah, yeah.
So he's bald, that one's bald.
Right, exactly.
The movie, if you track it as Christopher Lloyd's movie,
I mean, he has a scene where he goes back to the wife he left
because you can see that
he became so kind of OCD and so kind of in his own head
that he abandoned his wife and child.
So there's this quick scene out of nowhere
where he goes and checks in with them.
And they're like, we'll always have your place,
your place ready for you whenever you're ready to come back.
And he leaves.
And it's an oddly emotional affecting scene,
only because of him.
You got some some run -of -the -mill actress
doing the scene with him, whatever.
But Lloyd plays the hurt and like you feel the whole marriage
between them and his eyes and he does his best.
But the movie is like sub -perfect strangers by the end of it.
Yeah, it's kind of fun and interesting
when they're still at the mental hospital
and when they go out in the city,
they witness a mob hit.
Yeah, that's what happens in another you,
the prior wilder movie.
It's got my favorite Gene Wilder scene of all time.
The premise is great of priors of con man,
Gene Wilder's a pathological liar.
Like as soon as prior starts conning somebody,
Wilder goes off through, that's all you need.
Yeah, then they tied into like,
there's a guy who's a businessman
and he's trying to get this illegal oil thing done.
And it's just like,
oh, for Christ's sake.
It was every movie in the fucking 80s.
Like, you know, there's always a jewel high stores,
you know, three minute a baby,
I think has a fucking jewel heist in it.
Yeah, so you can just have a movie
with people hanging out sometimes.
Be, uh, do yourself a favor, folks.
If you haven't seen this,
go back to two episodes of Taxi to watch.
Watch the episode.
I can't remember the name of it,
but it's a two -parter that's one of the finales.
It might be the finale of the second and the last season.
But they do, uh,
they do like flashbacks of when they were,
who they were before they worked at the cap stand.
And the Christopher Lloyd one is amazing
because it's before he's attending Harvard.
And he's like,
this brilliant guy.
And Tom Hanks plays his roommate.
And they're all in pot brownies.
And Tom Hanks is like, you know,
one of his lines is Tom Hanks goes,
like, you want a brownie?
They're good.
And then Christopher Lloyd goes,
congratulations.
You almost completed a sentence.
You know, he's like one of those guys like this, not.
And then they're pushing him to eat one of the brownies.
And he's like,
marijuana is a gateway drug for certain people.
I could be one of those people.
See, this is what it's doing that he eats one.
And you realize that's what got him to.
That's like what starts the chain of Domino.
So that one's great.
But the best one ever is,
I think it's called Laka the Playboy.
And it's about Andy Kaufman.
His character Laka is tired of striking out with women.
And being such a chump.
And he locks himself for two weeks in his apartment.
And only listens to radio DJs and reads playboy.
So he can figure out how to pick up women and be American.
And when he emerges,
he's a completely different human being.
And he's such a fucking asshole.
And it's one of the greatest performances you've ever seen.
Like, because he comes out and he's like,
Hey, baby, how are you doing?
Walk with me, talk with me.
Real cheesy.
Yeah, but it works.
It works.
I've only seen the first season of taxi.
I own them.
I've only seen the first season.
I got to get back into it.
I think it gets better after the first season.
The first season is a little heavy.
It is, yeah.
And it really leans.
You can tell they didn't realize what they had
was an ensemble show on their hands.
It leans way heavy on Judhurst in that first season.
And I like Judhurst, but you're like,
guys, like, well, they also do a lot of proof people.
Yeah, they'll do a whole episode about one of them.
That's so, yeah, they do it all the time.
And you're like, boy, I kind of want to see these 10 hilarious people
interact with each other once in a while.
Instead of going out on dates with people will never see again.
Watch them.
Do yourself a favor tonight.
Watch that lot of the Playboy episode.
It delivers.
Oh boy, does it deliver, man?
I will watch.
And before we get off Danza,
he came to Conan when I was there.
And I would walk them out to their point where they would stand
before the band would fire up and they'd walk out on stage.
And I'd have to talk to them for a couple of minutes.
So Danza, he's tap dancing the whole time to get his energy up.
And he's an amazing tap dancer.
And he's talking to me while he's tap dancing.
Where are you from, kid?
And he goes, hey, yeah, can I ask you a question?
And I said, yeah, he goes, you like to puck?
I go, yeah, of course, I like to puck.
He goes, it's the craziest thing.
I, I became his pen pal when he was in prison.
I wrote him every day like, hey, I'm thinking of you.
You know, somebody out here on the outsides pulling for you,
you know, we became really good pen pals when he was in prison.
Terrible thing that happened to him.
And then out goes Tony Danza.
I never found out why.
I never found out any more details than that.
That is wild.
Do you know this?
He went and taught five years ago at a high school for a year
and wrote a book about it like not theater.
Not theater science.
That's awesome.
He went and taught.
They did a reality show about it too.
But he and it was for real.
It wasn't like a funny like, no, but it wasn't like.
I thought it was like, oh, this is cute.
And it's like, he wrote a true memoir about it
about how hard it was to teach and how much he respects his teachers.
And like, but he went and fucking did it.
I was like, what the fuck, man?
Like, it literally teach like in the inner city or something.
Yeah, like some high school and like on Staten Island or something.
Did they call it Danza wrist mines?
No, you're good though.
You are good.
I think it was called like, hey, teacher something like that.
But like, it was like, he, uh, he, I just was like,
man, I really respect this guy.
Like, he's like a guy.
Fieri.
I forget who has the joke about Guy Fieri about why is everybody always
shitting on this guy?
He's amazing.
Like look at all this wonderful stuff he's done for human being.
Guy Fieri, by the way, uh, uh, was was was was he, uh, what was he doing?
He was he was he had a TV show and development with the first it was going to be the first
ever trans celebrity chef.
Yeah.
I don't know if it happened or not.
But it was like, or if it came out, I don't think it did.
But, uh, this is the level of humanitarian of this guy going out like,
well, whatever he did during this pandemic, when that started coming out,
then people started to change their minds about him.
There's 150 ,000, he ordered 150 million dollars for restaurants across America.
Yeah.
It's more than anything the government did at all.
And also he wasn't the one telling you about it.
You found out about it after the fact.
Yeah.
I don't know.
Anyway, Dan's a, Dan's a Fieri.
Let's get these two together and something.
Sure.
I love it.
All right.
And I want you all to join John.
Good movie.
Just interesting movie.
Not a pick me up.
No, no.
You really think it's going to be like this guy going around bang and hot,
asked through the whole thing.
And then it's just like, no, no, no.
It's about how fucked up this guy is and he germs off too much.
Right.
That scene though with Joe Hanson in the hallway where she's rubbing her butt on his dick is like
yeah.
Yeah.
Hachi.
And now just married to Colin Joest.
I should say that to Colin next time I see him.
Hey, man, that's seen in that movie where your wife rubs her ass on his dick.
I'm sure it's heard worse.
Hachi.
Yeah.
Just stare at dead the eye.
Then, you know, maybe a minute later hit him with the mochi.
Like make him wait for the mochi.
You think you're not going to do it.
But then you hit as he's leaving.
Yeah, hours later, he's walking out.
Wait, Colin, I wasn't done.
He looks over.
Mochi.
Yeah.
Good.
Oh boy.
All right.
Godzilla Kong.
Let's get down to this fucking piece of shit.
Now, Joe, you're going to have to do the synopsis because I'm honestly not sure I know
what happens in the first hour of this film.
Pat, or I know is this.
Yes.
You got yourself a Godzilla.
You got yourself a King Kong.
Yeah.
King Kong is living in some sort of facility that they've built over Skull Island at this point.
Which I don't understand how that works.
Anyway, for some reason, think the way to deal with this Godzilla issue is to get another monster
out here to fight him because Godzilla appears to have attacked something.
She's attacked a bay.
He's, she, I don't know if Godzilla's a male female female.
But anyway, Godzilla's attacked a base in Hong Kong that Friday night lights works at Kyle
Chandler.
By the way, phoning it into the extent that I don't know that he's aware he's in the film.
And maybe they just suit like bofinger style superimposed him in from something else.
I think it's a case of, oh, I got one scene, but a fucking blow me.
All right.
They give him nothing to do in the movie.
He's, his daughter is played by Millie Bobby Brown, who, folks, I'm not trying to pick on a kid here.
She's officially annoying.
Okay.
She's officially an annoying, she's going through this thing like she's supposed to be like this
badass rebellious character.
Okay.
That's fine.
She is doing every cliche gesture and thing I've ever seen a cliche badass to.
There's a part where she takes the keys and flick the car keys and does that thing.
You know what I mean?
I mean, lift the, for the listeners, yeah, the jingle.
Her friend is like, you can't drive the car.
It's not yours.
It's mine.
My brother, this is my brother's van that I stole to help you.
And she goes, my mission, my wheel.
Then almost pulls away with the fat kid who brought her the van, hanging halfway out of the van.
It's like, you're not really a badass.
You're just kind of an asshole.
You know what I mean?
Like, yeah.
Anyway, um,
Fomka, whatever the fucking name is.
Or, no, I'm sorry, Vera Farmega shows up for about six hot minutes in this thing.
Almost forgot she was in it.
To set up
that we need to go into hollow earth, which is
the skull island in the middle of the earth that nobody knew existed, where there's gravity.
And, and then also no gravity and sunlight and clouds and an atmosphere.
And like 70s pop hits because I guess somebody saw Guardians of the Galaxy.
Yeah.
And the plot, so to what I reckon is, the plot of this thing is if we can get Kong to help us,
get Godzilla to stand down, will treat Kong to what he always has wanted, which is taking him to
middle hollow earth, which is a place where monsters come from that will be his home.
Except that's what fucking skull island is.
So just make all the monsters come from skull island
and take the battle to fucking skull island.
And then for whatever reason, it moves across the ocean.
Yeah, to Hong Kong or whatever.
The reason Godzilla is attacking Hong Kong, by the way, or the facility in Hong Kong,
is because he knows they're building mecha Godzilla there, which is a pretty cool little plot point.
I thought that was kind of neat.
But like everything with these movies, they blew the load on the wrong movie.
They already made Godzilla king of the monsters.
That had four monsters in it.
This is down to two, and a big robot.
So, not a monster can talk, you know, which uh,
oh yeah, that's yeah, Kong knows sign language somehow because this little girl taught it to him or
something.
It's just, I mean, to me, it's like, hey, I hate superhero movies, but at least they can
communicate with each other.
I mean, we're literally watching two computer -generated animals fight.
And the fights are cool.
The fights are something to be seen, you know.
The fights are cool.
I made me wish I had seen it in 3D.
I like that they made a visual, it's Adam Wingard who did the guest and a lot of,
you know, good indie stuff.
Did he do a lot of good indie stuff?
I thought it was the guest than this.
He did the guest.
And then he did Kong skull island.
Wasn't that his number two?
No, Wingard had a couple movies.
Grace Guy, I met him once on Douglas movies.
Let me look.
But yeah, you know, he made a real visual choice to make it kind of, you know, neon.
I know it's inspired by, uh, what is it, Joe?
The
Manja?
Magna, mag, mag, manga.
Manga, I think it is.
Yeah, I never remember how to say it.
Um, but look, those did have a visual style of them.
The fights were cool.
I saw, you know, so many people on Twitter like, hey, it gave me
Godzilla fight and Kong.
That's all I needed to see, whatever.
And it's like, but shouldn't we be asking a little more now?
This movie is one of the most expensive movies ever produced.
It has to be you're a fucking idiot.
If you think that the two fight scenes between them carries this thing,
which by the way was what everybody bitched about with Batman versus Superman,
they only fight.
It's like, guys, they only fight in this for like a total of 12 minutes.
They make you wait forever for it.
I mean, you haven't even mentioned 10 characters in this fucking thing.
Yeah, it's like Alexander, scars guard is in there.
If for what is what is his, I don't know.
And then they got this Ricardo Montabon ripoff guy.
It's laughable.
Like the main villain.
I'm like, this is like peeled out of the naked gun.
Like, this is a they don't bring back anyone you liked.
Like, I was like, oh, is John Goodman in it?
No.
Well, that's Riley in it.
No, that's because those took place in the 60s though.
That one took place in the 60s.
Oh, that's right.
Yeah, I forget that too.
They bring back a lot of people.
They also add in some new people,
but really nobody leaves an impact of any kind.
It just kind of they're all not good characters.
There's nothing going on with them.
It's another fucking stranger things rip off too,
which is strange because Millie Bobby B is in this.
And like, the two kids that know the podcast of the guy
who does all the conspiracy stuff, they find him.
It's just like what in Stranger Things,
when the kids go find the Brett Gelman character.
It's the same thing in this.
And then they go on the kid mission where they get trapped in the facility.
And I mean, my God, guys,
suspension of disbelief is not strong enough a term
for what you need to get through this fucking thing.
I mean, they're in spaceships at one point.
They've got weapons that it's so fucking crazy and so ungrounded.
And it was just too much for me.
I was like, okay, so I'm supposed to believe
that this place exists in the middle of the earth
that has an atmosphere and sunlight
that monsters came from.
And apparently that's where Godzilla is from.
But it was never discovered until two years ago.
Okay, then I'm supposed to also accept that this uncharted
Skull Island place.
Again, nobody knew where it was until the 60s or whatever.
But it's where the mom.
Okay, fine.
Okay, so that's two things now.
Okay, then I'm also supposed to believe
that humans have the ability to create something so cybernetically advanced
that they could create mecha Godzilla.
Okay, fine.
Now I'm supposed to believe that a guy, this is all in the movie,
that a human being plugs into it.
Yeah.
And through, I think it's through technology,
they based on camera or whatever that whatever the three headed monster is.
I can't remember that this guy plugs into this thing
and goes into a brain trance with his brain.
And that's how he controls mecha Godzilla.
Okay, anything else?
Yes, also we have spaceships that are able,
also, and human beings are able to travel to the center of the earth.
Guys, we can't go like,
I think the greatest depth in the ocean we've ever been to is like 20 miles or something like that.
It's like, because you'll be immediately be crushed by the pressure of the water.
Like there's shit on the bottom of the ocean that we haven't discovered
because we have no way of getting to it.
This is way, way, way too much shit, guys.
All you had to do was cons out of the water.
He's attacking this facility because they got some fucking robot thing that he knows is in there
and they want to fight him or Godzilla's out of the water.
I mean, they get conned to come over from Skull Island to fight it.
And at the end, they bring con back to Skull Island and maybe Godzilla goes back there too
because that's originally where he can't, it is so insane and convoluted and nonsensical
and it's just a bad, it's just a bad fuck.
Oh, and then on top of it too, the monkey knows sign language.
It's crazy, man.
It's crazy.
It's so needlessly complicated that I couldn't follow it.
And I was also just like, but why should I be having a hard time following it?
It's not like when I go to see Avengers 4 and I don't remember the other 50 movies in the franchise.
That's on me, my brain doesn't absorb it.
But I remember Kong Skull Island, I remember the gist, I remember the Godzilla's, they sucked,
but I watched them both and I'm watching this and I'm just like,
give me one thing to care about, one person to latch onto, it's actually a good double feature with
Train to Besan, which is the other one that we did because in a similar way, they both have a big
bench of characters and a big bench of like subplots that they're following.
And in one case, it's done beautifully where you know the bare minimum, but you know enough
to care about everybody and their whole journey throughout the entire movie.
That's Train to Besan.
This one, you know nothing about anyone, you don't care about anybody and at some point,
especially in the first hour, which is brutal, you don't care what's happening, you don't
understand what's happening and it starts to seem like they're juggling balls to keep you
from thinking about the fact that you don't know what's going on.
Right.
It almost seems like it's a slide of hand trying to distract you because I just couldn't
put it together, I didn't even know what was going on and then at the end then they beat each other
up and you're like, okay, that's fun.
I get that.
But what was that hour?
And looking on the Wikipedia, the movie has an A from CinemaScore.
Almost no movies get an A plus.
Give me a break.
Everybody fucking loved it.
It's like, but what did you do for that hour?
You liked all that?
I don't know.
A terrible movie.
It's a terrible movie with some of the best action I've seen in a while,
but 12 minutes of amazing action does not make for a good film.
I'm sorry, it's just not enough.
If it was, you know, if we were talking about something like,
for instance, VFW, where so much of the movie is based in the chaos and the fighting with the,
you know, the guys in the place fighting the crazy, drugged out people and the murders and the killing.
Yeah, you'd be something a little bit different, you know?
If you're talking about the expendables where so much of it is the jeeps riding
and the thing exploded and they shot that guy and then they killed all these people in the boat.
But it's not that kind of movie.
It's a movie that really, as you said, makes you wait for the action.
And while you're waiting, it's terrible.
Yeah.
So, okay, you want it to be terrible in the downtime.
You better fucking clip the ends of that downtime then, man.
Like, keep this fucking thing moving.
So, or if you're going to build up to, you know, 10, 15 minutes of action,
well, you don't have to convoluted to that extent because at the end, none of it matters.
You don't, nobody remembers anything that happens in the first hour of this movie.
I guarantee it.
You don't care.
But it's like, nobody knows.
And make it fun.
Make it more like Kong Skoliel,
and which was not a classic, either.
But at least they knew to like hang out with some great character actors and have some fun
and keep it light.
That's all you need.
I mean, we don't, yeah.
But try and have convoluted stuff because they think it's,
that's what people like about the Marvel movies is that they're convoluted.
That's not what people like about them.
Nobody knows what's going on.
You know, and again, yet another suspension of disbelief,
like you're supposed to just accept that these two things,
these two monsters are fighting in the middle of one of the world's most notable cities.
And there's no, and only an elite team of military know what was going on.
And nobody's attacking.
You know, there's no chop.
You know, it pisses me off, too, that all the posters in the billboard said,
one will fall.
And it's like, well, spoiler alert, no, because they both live at the end.
Because the selfish, greedy, suit,
fox can't, God forbid, they don't ring out every fucking dime from a franchise.
They can't even give this fucking thing proper closure
and let one of these animals or both of them go down and die.
You're going to reboot it in two years anyway, guys.
Just kill them off.
Who gives a shit?
Kill them both off.
And then one year from now, call it God's Eleverses Kong Resurrection.
They've been doing it for decades.
I mean, Jesus Christ, man.
So it's just, Wingard has talented.
He did your next, which I liked and you didn't.
He did, I know you did.
I liked it.
And he did the gas, which is awesome.
He did Blair Witch, which we did on the show and did not like.
I liked Blair Witch.
Death Note, which I never saw.
Death Note was terrible.
And now he's been set to direct and co -write a sequel to Face Off
and an adaptation of Thundercats.
Yes, which he said will be based or inspired by God's Eleverses Kong.
I think is what he said, something.
I don't remember who fucking knows.
Anyway, hogs are down, hogs are down.
hogs are down folks.
Thanks for listening.
Thanks for the support.
Thanks for, we really do mean that we can't say it enough.
If you got some time and you want some more of me on a podcast,
listen to Taste Buds on the No Presh Network channel on YouTube.
New episodes every Monday at 11 a .m.
Sal Volcano and I argue food.
And you can also find Chris DeStefano and his podcast
and Sal's podcast there called Hey, Bay.
Do you shout out this show on your show?
Yeah, I do.
I plug it sometimes.
Not every episode, but I also don't plug,
I don't plug Taste Buds in every episode of this.
But yeah, I do.
I plug.
I think that's why honestly our patreon went up a little bit
because I think it's a new outlet of audit of people
that are not hearing that hadn't heard of this show.
Right.
All right, let's do it.
Relax.
Good job.
I'm the Patrick Walls Twitter and Instagram.
I might, I don't know how long the cat's been meowing.
Is that been audible?
Well, we both got some annoying things in the background.
Yeah, next, next month not undecided yet what we'll be doing.
But my Mike Nichol's career retrospective which will also
double as a very brief Mel Brooks retrospective
because if I had to suffer through the movies
I might as well give it to you.
But that will be dropping I would say next week
the solo movie corner.
We will see you next time and we will see you in hell.