Welcome to a very special edition of We'll see you in hell and by special
I mean, I'm still here, Pat still here and isn't that special enough that we're
alive to see another day. I mean, you're you're calling out the bare minimum of
life here, Joe, but yes, it is. It is nice. I was just telling Joe it's raining. I
was out. Usually if I'm gonna do something like get groceries, I go at like 11 .50 p .m.
Right before they're about to close and there's no one there and there's no line. I love
a late night grocery shop. Today, I did a Costco and it's raining. It hasn't rained here
in a long time. This Costco is always like as you enter the store, it's like you're an hour
and 15 minutes into 28 days later every time you go in there. You hit that atwater village
one. Yeah, I guess dawn of the dead might be more appropriate because it's a giant warehouse
shopping center. But like there was every picnic so there's a there's 50 picnic tables
out front where you can eat either the $9 .99 pizza or the $1 hotdog, which the CEO of Costco
said he'd rather die than raise the price of a hotdog, which I thought was awesome. I have
never had any food from Costco, but every single spot at the picnic table, I don't mean
all the picnic tables were taken. I mean, there was five people on either bench of each picnic
table. These people just devouring plates of hotdogs and pizzas. Mm -hmm. Look great. You know,
if that's a cheap option and that's how you feed your family, muzzle. I love that Costco
provides that service. But some madhouse before you even enter the store, I'm in a line of
cards, all the carts at Costco are twice the size of a regular cart. So every time you
turn a corner, you're bashing into some old lady. It's rough. It's real rough. They need
to check your receipts on the way out. Yeah, it's a lot. It's a lot. Then as I'm walking out,
I go or I have, look, I'm going to just be honest with you. I decided to stock the house. I've
been living the life of a divorced bachelor man here for a while. And I was like, I'm just going
to stock the house with everything I need every, you know, salt pepper, like down to that stuff.
Like I got to restock everything. So I spent about 400 bucks, you know, not jump change. And
she starts ringing me up and she goes, can I see your Costco card, please? And I realized that the
Costco card is under my ex -wife's name. 400 dollars worth of groceries. This cart just keeps
piling and piling. And I'm looking through my wallet. And then I said, I'm just going to have to
give you my number. Now she's got everything wrong up. I go, I'll just, I'll just give you my cell
number. No, sir, I need the card. Why are you different than every other store in the world?
Like, can I just give you your number to bring it up? She's like, absolutely not, sir. We don't allow.
At the cost of what people in the line cost to this Costco need to see this damn card. What
what what other underworld cult have you joined at Costco that they need to see this membership?
What's going to leak out? I mean, it costs what $60 a year or something. So like, you can't trust me.
She goes, can you go over and get a day pass? Like I'm at the fucking gym. I said, man,
immediately I've been waiting 30 seconds. The line starts turning against me like lighting torches.
And this guy leans over and he goes, Hey, buddy, can you step aside? Can you step aside?
I just took a breath. I didn't even look at him or acknowledge him. I'm doing better due to my
breathing and my therapy. Just sat there, chilled. Finally, this manager comes over. She goes, what's the
problem? And I said, I have $400 something dollars worth of groceries. They won't accept my wife's card.
She goes, there's your name on her account. I said, yes, I have my own card. I do not have it with me.
She goes, well, why can look that up? If I look at the cashier, like, oh, really? That'd be nice. Thanks.
She takes my driver's license and walks. Joe, I'm not kidding. When I say 500 yards away from me,
she just keeps walking and walking and walking. And I watch her disappear into some back room.
And then the line starts really getting heated. And then the cashier to her credit goes,
guys, there's 50 other lanes. Can you just go to a different lane?
The guy goes, yeah, well, then I'm going to have to restart the waiting again.
She's like, yeah, you'd have to restart the waiting again. It's like Jesus Christ. It was a nightmare.
I got out of it. She goes, yeah, he's under his wife's card. I'm like, thank you. They let me free.
But it's like, you can't help a man out. I'm going to spend $400 in your shop.
And you're going to turn me away from doing that. Are you an idiot?
They don't need your money.
They turn shroder away. They don't care about you. Costco. Yeah, that was one of the famous
mask videos that leaked was him yelling at the Costco lady. Or they might have been BJs. I don't know.
It's like Ricky, go to another big budget store of Christ.
I think it was Costco. There wasn't a single mask in that store. You feel like you can just sort of
see COVID dripping off of each thing that you touch in there. But I'm fine with it.
Yeah, it's I'm not breathing. And I'm not going to therapy. And I'm not doing better.
Well, these two might go hand in hand. I got to tell you, I've been dry as a sober as a judge
with the exception of one day. I drank on Halloween. That was the only day.
Nothing. No drinking a pumpkin spice, Jamison.
Yeah, they had a giant tub of pumpkin spice hummus at Costco. Take that on your fucking taste.
But yeah, I got sick looking at it. On Halloween, I only drank cocktails that had the the fog rolling
out of them like like Al Vyre drink. Sure. Oh, yeah. There's somewhere a wolf house as it gets set
under table. I know that joke in young Frank, it's not wear wolf. Yeah. It's wet. And he goes,
well, there, there, where will yeah, I was just thinking the other day. I was thinking about how I love
my mother. If I may, you know, we're a woman that put up with however many years of my god damn
father, she's just been a treat from the jump, not without her flaws, but a lovely woman.
I was thinking about her. I was getting emotional thinking about my mom. And I was remembering young
Frankenstein. My mom's alive, by the way, I could call her. I didn't call her. I just, she had called
me and left a message and I just thought about how much I liked her and then didn't call her back.
But yeah, when I watch young Frankenstein as a kid, I used to like be so tickled by the things that
would make my mom laugh, because she was normally just reading a book while we were watching any movie
or any show she would just read a book. But then sometimes she would pay attention to the movie for a second.
That werewolf bit had tears streaming down her face. She was like gasping for air. Very funny joke.
Yeah. I mean, it's funny that what sells it is, it's the genius of Gene Hackman or Wilder. You got
Hackman in there too, though. Yes. But the way Wilder does the, I don't, I don't want to talk that
way. Like, it's like the, it's a guy that just understands like what funny is. There's no
anymore paper. Although you never really saw film and be funny and much else. He was amazing in
young Frankenstein. That era would argue with you that the he was, I mean, I get you. I got you,
but he doesn't make me laugh like a like a, you know, but anyway, I was going to say about how sad I
was. You told the story in the middle of it, but yeah, I was going to go on with. I wasn't done with
the one day. No, it's just funny. No, I, I, so, so I haven't, I haven't cleaned the system. I've
been on a diet. I've stuck to it. Yes. I feel horrible. I feel terrible. I mean, I feel healthier.
Like, you know, I sleep better and I, I guess I, you know, I don't, my body feels better, but
I feel terrible. You can't, you, there's nothing to numb me from this world. It's horrible. And
then it's just terrible. It's a terrible, terrible thing. I mean, the, the ideal for a human being
is that you don't need to numb every day life, but I don't see that ever being my day to day. I
don't understand. I don't understand. If one more person posts a selfie that they voted,
you basic, I say, Bish to, to, to, to G Den gender it even more. It's, it's like walking around
on Ash Wednesday with the ash on your, stop it. Yeah. Can the bar get any lower for what people want
accolades for at this point? My God almighty. I stand against Kanye. Oh, do you? You stand against
a lunatic? Yeah. Really? I had crazy anymore. I mean, you can, you can vote. I didn't,
haven't, I might run up there today and do it, but I, I generally do it at home and it takes one
minute. And these people like with these smug looks on their face about how they vote good for you,
because no matter what we do, three people are going to say, no, they're all, they're all ready to say
no election counts anymore. And it's been proven. So I don't know. I'm never going to go
full Joe and say don't vote or face George Carlin, if you will. But I say, I don't see the point.
I don't even say that anymore. I say vote if you want to. Then shut the fuck up. For sure.
Please. Like my God. It's also base anymore. I can't stand it. My God, you can't look at the God
damn inner. I mean, how do you live? I'm forced to be on the internet. I'm forced. And by the way,
by the way, for everybody that's going to say in reaction to what I'm about to say, because I'm
about to say because of my line of work, I'm forced to be on the internet. And so for everybody about
to say, and it's only probably a few of you, well, then you shouldn't have gone to that line of work.
It wasn't part of it when I started, when I started as a comedian, there was no such thing as
social media. You didn't have to do any of this. And then when social media became a thing,
you still didn't have to do it. It was only in recent years that they were like, if you have any
sort of business, you have to be on social media period to promote it. And you're like, okay,
I guess you just have to do it. And then social media turned on us and said, well, there's an
algorithm. And if you don't play with the algorithm, I've been suspended twice now in the last
two months from TikTok, twice. What are you posting on TikTok? Jokes, like old jokes, new jokes, old jokes.
Yeah, with the words on the screen kind of vibe. Yeah. Okay. It's twice I've been suspended.
I don't want to be on the goddamn platform to begin with because the jokes are risky or what?
The nurse thing? No, the nurse one didn't get barred. I got barred for one of them.
One of them thinking you can't criticize a nurse or you'll be shut down. Like fuck off.
The latest joke that got no, my comic book joke. You saw that in my hour when I said, when I go,
do we need diversity here at Marvel? Should I stay late and create some new characters?
Yeah. And the boss goes, no, I draw a pussy on Thor. We're good. Let's get out of it.
It's a fucking joke about like the laziness of just making new things like for people.
She hulk. Well, she hulks old school. That's, you know, but by the way, the bit didn't get pulled
down from Instagram. And I've actually had people, I blocked a guy the other day because he just was like,
calm down. There are plenty of new original. I was like, I can't even with this shit.
Yeah, you can't really engage. You can't really engage the Kanye shit. Well, Twitter,
everyone's everyone's like, I can't believe I'm running away now because Elon Musk bought it.
Now, I'm never going to tweet again. A, you're lying because you tweet 14 times a day, which means
you're on Twitter 15 hours a day. And B, who do you think's running it now? Mother Teresa?
What are you a fucking idiot? Let me give you a compliment.
I don't want to running any of these sites. It is worth it. You still use Instagram, don't you? That's
your fucking Zuckerberg. Okay. You like him? Yeah, it's crazy that people are now going, I'm worried
about the spread of misinformation on Twitter. Now you're worried. Now you're worried. Every day,
they post like, hey, this video that you've all been mocking for 24 hours, it was doctored and fake.
They do it every day and people still get worked up. I'm pretty much off Twitter. I briefly thought I
was going to get addicted to TikTok because I started watching some reels and I lost five hours one
night. But those get that gets boring very quickly too. I'm kind of starting to move away from it
in a positive way. Your life immediately gets better when you're not looking at it.
I started paying a guy to do all this for me. So I wouldn't have to deal with it. But then you
still do because now I have to deal with him calling me and saying because he has to send me a
report every week to show the stats. So I know that my money's being spent properly and he's great at
what he does. He's awesome. But now I have to deal with when he calls me and he goes, TikTok is
it's stalled because we got booted again and we have to wait two weeks where we're allowed to boast.
Fucking Alex Winter posts on Twitter. Yeah, suddenly he's one of our greatest political minds.
He goes like so many others just here to announce that I'll be over on this platform now that I'm
leaving this one. So Alex Winter now has decided Elon Musk was the last straw for him on Twitter
before that. It was just a grand old positive non toxic environment. And we were all wondering,
hey, I need my daily dose of wisdom from Bill or Ted. I need to know what either Bill or Ted says
about politics. Give me a break and say what you really mean, Alex. I'm going back to the box
they've kept me in until they do Bill and Ted for her. Yeah, exactly. That's very mean. I'm just
kidding. I should have stayed in the box for three. Should have let that one incubate a little bit more.
It's Kanye shit. I so near the but I just want to say I'm just it was a mean joke about Alex. I'm
kidding. I don't know. He doesn't listen. But I mean, my point is like I'm pointing out the statement
not the person. That's all I was going to try. Anyway, good. I went this Kanye stuff has been a real
thrill for me. I went my ex used to give me a lot of shit about not hanging out with her friends enough.
I went near the end of our time together. I went and hung out with her friends one night.
We're there like five hours playing drinking. That was a good time talking laugh and having fun.
A bunch of her friends. Then somebody mentions Kanye and how much she loves Kanye and supports him.
And I go, well, have you been paying attention like this week to what Kanye has been up to? I was
but this this guy is a maniac. And at the time, Kanye's manager or something had like shook down
a voting booth for a Trump supporter and got arrested. And I was like, he's very interest. He's like
in politics. Like he's in Trump's camp and wearing the mug. And she goes, no, he's not. No, he's not.
I go, he's talking about I go, I'll bring up a picture. She goes, he's not. He's doing it as an act.
He's he's one of the only people he's playing 3D chess. She's saying, he's trying to get everybody on
on the Republican side to open their minds and open their hearts. And that's what Kim's doing too
because she tried to get one guy out of jail, even though she has 800 bajillion dollars. She did
one good thing. So this girl's lecturing me, lecturing on how great Kanye is. And also,
I don't really believe we should completely cancel somebody just because they do one thing or
say one thing wrong. I say, well, now I agree with you, but we're talking about a decade of insane
behavior. And he's off his meds and something is wrong whenever. Then the guys, because this is an
attractive young girl, the guys there. Hey, come on, man. I think she's got it. I mean,
I like my voice wasn't even raised. I like Kanye goes over to the girl. Hey, I love Kanye too.
You know, sometimes it's hard to say it out loud, but you're not wrong. You're not wrong. Come on,
man. Like pulling me away from her. Annie Hall style subtitles should have came up on the screen
as he was talking that said, yeah, I'm basically maneuvering to get you to blow me later at my house
tonight. That's what those subtitles should have said. What a fucking little fucking worm.
That's modern day chivalry for you. Oh, let me step in for the little lady and talk for
yeah, fuck off, dude. The entire room's like, yeah, you know, I still like Kanye too. And I just
completely stopped talking and waited until finally, I was allowed to go home, which was often what
happens when you go hang out with your wife's friends. That by the way, oh, good, sorry. I like these,
they don't listen either, but I like these people just fine. But it was this bad evening. And then when
this Kanye stuff started, this, the, I hate Jews thing, the I'm going death gone three on the Jews,
I so desperately wanted to text each one of these people. And I didn't do it. It's like,
you're, you're a mister. Everyone deserves a second shot about the people you love. You don't hold
that same compassion for anyone else in the world. No, fuck off. Well, I'll take you back one
further with Kanye. Yeah, I've, I've always had an issue with him. I've always found him arrogant. I
performed it. When the college dropout album came out, I was performing at a college that day. And I,
this was when Kanye was first getting into the mainstream. Yes. But he had been around the hip -hop
scene for, you know, if you listened to rap at that time, you knew who he was. But he, that album
came out the same day. The 50 cents album came out. And the kids were asking while I was on stage,
like Kanye or 50. And I was, I remember saying that I was opening for Bill Burr. And I said 50 cent
fuck Kanye West. He's an asshole. I don't like him. And I got booed for saying that. And Burr
went on after me and was like, are you and that's he's a fucking great derailleur. He doesn't like
anything about, you know, and Burr to this day will call me and be like, I don't know how you called
it. You called it, you know, like, but which is very funny. You know how you called it because you can
tell with people. Yeah, because people who have this like bullshit filter, like the two of us,
can tell when you got a fucking poser loser chunk of crap. You can tell and half the people
are pretending they like him, half genuinely love him, whatever. But you sit there and the whole time,
you're like, no, this is a bad guy. And everyone is against you for, it's been 15, 20 years now.
And by the way, he's brilliant. Don't don't get us wrong. He's brilliant. His music can be
a complete fucking idiot and a monster. But this is where, this is where I fully checked out in
this moment. Yes. And I keep saying this to people. You didn't realize he was crazy when he
went on morning radio and scream that he was Shakespeare. Yes. This wasn't a tip off for anybody.
No, because this stupid self celebratory self serving materialistic. I hate capitalism,
but I want to fucking wear diamonds and all that bullshit hypocritical fucking culture we live in.
No, because everybody when he was saying that was going, you go, dude, you go, get it, get it.
Let the haters. Hey, let the shut the fuck up. We have lost the concept of humility.
Everybody thinks that they need to be stroking themselves or stroked at all fucking times.
And these are the kind of monsters we fucking created now. And it's Trump. It's Kanye.
It's fucking Kim Kardashian. It's, it's, and it goes on and on. But anyway,
it does. The man is unhinged. When was the last time you threw on kids love ghosts?
It was the last time you threw on the the sixth song album he did with Kid Cutty. The last album
people loved was Life of Pablo, which had four good songs on it out of 16. You're hanging on to
somebody who's who's done. And the people who say that we won't let our black stars get too big.
Give me a break. It has nothing to do with race, especially when the man starts calling for
death, gone three on the Jews. This is just a bad human being. So rotten apple. He made three,
he made four, three excellent albums and a couple are really good ones. I'll give him that.
This is great. The man's always come up with the corneous fucking rhymes. I mean, embarrassing rhymes.
Go back and listen to some of that. This is where I would, uh, the one thing I would disagree
on. I think the reason that people say it becomes racial is because so many more white lunatics get
away with it than lunatics of other races. You know what I mean? Why lunatic is operating at Kanye's
level other than Trump. Trump's the perfect man. Well, I mean, I guess it is true that we came
president and we did kind of cancel Kanye. That's kind of a good point. That's what we could argue.
We could argue Tom Cruise in his own way. We could. We could see Cruise keeps to himself.
That's the one time Cruise poked his head out of his little hutch was to call Matt Lauer glib.
And that's when like the AI wires started showing in the back of his neck. And then the miscavages
ganked his chain back and put him back in the hutch. Alex Alex Jones would still be functioning if he
didn't go puff his chest out and do all that dumb shit with the public shooting stuff. If he didn't do
that, he'd still be sitting there in his like Fox News studio that he built at his house.
Yeah. Screaming as a millionaire. And it's like, dude, you put, I think that is the, you make
an interesting point. That is the crime of it. You put, you puff your chest out too much. That's
what it is. Cruise keeps his head down. You know, Christ on even army hammer and guys like that,
where you hear these crazy things like the guy just was like, I'm going to move away for a
little while. So I can deal with my issues. I'm going to eat a couple of friends and come,
I don't know why we're making him Lord Michaels, but yeah, speaking of army hammer, I was talking to
a friend about this the other night. I don't think you and I have discussed this yet on the show.
Isn't it odd that the tell me, call me by your name director is now his new movie is a cannibal
movie. Joe, I talked about this the other night, buddy of mine, I went to a movie and I saw
the poster and I was like, how is no one talking about this? These two made calling by your name
with army hammer in like a very close three way relationship with like a working relationship.
Then the next thing they do is a cannibal movie while he's under apparently legal investigation
for eating people. It is so crazy. And then when I saw one interviewer ask him, like, do you find
that? And he's like, honestly, I won't even entertain the questions ridiculous. It's like, no,
it's a pretty good question. And I feel like I feel like under a different set of circumstances,
army hammer would have been in this movie. Oh, for sure. And we never seen a lot of that.
No, I'm saying, I'm saying if it wasn't, let's say army hammer never had any controversy.
Yes, I feel like this movie might have been, you know, they're, you know, like when Meg Ryan and
Tom Hanks said, you've got mail and it wasn't sequenced Seattle, but it was a re - you know, convening
of the two. Yeah, you know, this is a weird love story or an off beat love story. Well, no,
this is weird. It's cannibal. There's no lifestyle just. That's not off beat. That's like when I
let's date a tight person. But I guess, I guess it's the one connective thread it would have to
call me by your name is it's a love story that that is coming with your name was, was was a
unique love story because of the time period it took place and all that stuff, right? I think
yeah, it was a period. Yeah, it was just a coming of age gay story at a time where gay people want to
work out. So this is this is a modern day story, but yeah, it's cannibals, which I don't think
will ever be if they my who knows of this fucking culture, maybe you just never know. Anyway,
I want to show you want protection for for what they believe they will get it in a world they unionize
in a world where everybody goes on Twitter and complains about capitalism. Yeah. And the problems
in this country, I just want to show we've talked it's streamer season again folks. It's when
they start sending you the movies to watch. Yeah. And if you're in the unions in the entertainment
industry, you get screeners. I don't want to brag, but I've received not one, but two copies
of 13 miners or whatever the fuck this thing is called. I didn't even know it existed. Ron Howard's
new cave movie. Yeah, anything that goes to Amazon Prime does not count as a movie release. It's
like no one talks about it. No one watches it. I didn't know. It's Vigo Mortensen and Colin
Farrell, Ron Howard directed had no idea it existed either just showed up at my door. And these are
the only two I've received and the the testimonial on the box, which I took a picture of and said to Pat,
this is how low we've sucked people. This is how low the bar is. It was
devastatingly realistic cave sets. That was the devastating. Imagine the guy watching it being
devastated when he first sees the cave. Realistic cave. He's like default and platoon.
These caves throws his hands up. Have you ever in your life seen a critic
accolade on a trail or anything that mentioned the sets? No. The movie let alone cave sets.
It's also like, do you know that they weren't in a cave? I mean, how are you calling it?
I mean, I know. Get it if you're talking about like, you know, the age of innocence or something
and you go, my god, the sets they built in this thing. It's brilliant, you know? Yeah. You're doing a
movie in a cave. You're probably going to have a lot of brown walls and rocks. But this is the
most I said capitalism for reason, Amazon prime nobody nobody is more grotesque with their spending
than Amazon prime with their productions and the Lord of the Rings thing being the worst offender.
But we've talked in the past about the waste, the money they waste on sending you things in the
mail that nobody wants or needs. I got one. This takes the cake. I've never gotten something this
fucking useless during streaming season. Yes. That could have cost more money. Did you get this thing?
Did you get the passport? I did get the passport. Yeah. And by the way, that's after five straight
years of being criticized for sending out like music boxes that contained the screener. Like hand -carved
wouldn't be jeweled music boxes. This thing, this is this is how desperate they are.
Or I don't that's what's not the right word. I don't even understand. It's a fake passport
that inside of it has a QR code. I guess you can get like a free month pass on Amazon Prime.
If as if you didn't know how to get on to Amazon Prime to watch things or whatever. And then inside
of it are get ready for this. Streaming instructions. And then screen mirroring instructions.
This is how fucking gluttonous and ghost these fucking people are. That they have to be a part of the
conversation. That they will send you a they will spend millions of dollars on making fake passports
to send you screening instructions in the mail for the biggest streaming service outside
of Netflix. It's so insane. They have everyone's email address. And I know this because they email you
10 times a day. They could very easily say, Hey, here's a list of what we have screening on Amazon
and here's how you access it in an email and not not have done this. But nobody cares. It's just a
wasteful roast culture. Nothing will ever make them not crave the awards. Clearly not a global pandemic.
Even in the midst of it, it was like, now we're still going to still going to put on the big pop and
circumstance. And these celebrities are probably like we're returning back to normal life again.
You know, that's how they see the award shows for them. Fuck off.
Joe, we better get to the movie corner. Let's do it. I actually
my my movies are so contradictory. Oh, by the way, we're reviewing resurrection today.
Yes, resurrection, critically claimed. Probably more of a thriller than horror. It premiered on
shutter a couple of weeks back after a brief theatrical and critically acclaimed release.
We'll get to it shortly. I movie corner, I am watching
because of I really put a lot of thought into my movie watching this holiday season
in the real with the realization that if you if you really carve out the right movies to watch during
each holiday month, the spirit of the month is more alive. It makes the holiday feel longer and
more fulfilling and all that stuff. So in October, obviously, it was a lot of horror movies for
Halloween. And there are some Hollywood horror movies in November now, but in November, I tried to
really watch. I'm trying to watch movies that are atominal, romantic comedies that take place in
New York, preferably in the fall. Clearly, you did the movie that combines them both,
autumn and New York, starring Richard Geer and Winona Ryder. I did not. Not yet at least. I've
never seen it. I heard it. I hear it's terrible, but it is crazily bad. Yeah. All right. Well,
maybe I'll watch it. Maybe we should should we review that for thank. Oh no, these are the
thanksgiving episode. No, these are there. Is it worth doing autumn in New York as an episode or
is it or no? No. And I remember nothing about it. I don't need to see that again. It's not like
funny bad. Well, I started with, well, I've got two. So the first six here,
you know what? I'll do the Woody Allen's first. I did three Woody Allen's that I think really
encapsulate the three of the best romantic comedies and his three of my, arguably my three of his
movies that are my favorites that I also never noticed function. You know what? No, I'll do those
in the next episode. You know what? I'm just going to do them now. Sorry. I have it a tough time.
Oh, brief, brief meltdown there. You know what? No, I didn't want to go on this order. I'll do the
Woody Allen's in the next episode. I want to, I want to stick with the order that I was in going
in here. So I started with the all -time classic, the all -time great one, Harry Met Sally. That is
as autumn, as New York, as whatever, as it gets. I've seen the movie there. Dare say you compare
it to like the 30s romantic, the movies that started the genre. I think you're still talking about
one of the top two romantic comedies of all time. It's just, I love it so much. I will cry every time
at the end, because that's how I roll. It's kind of wild. Like the shit Billy Crystal is saying it's
the top of the movie. You're like, Jesus Christ. Like only works because it's crystal, you know?
It's like you just know him at least at that time. You knew him as like a good quality funny charming
dude. So you let it slide. But he's also saying how man think? My favorite joke in the movie is when
and it's a little bit of like the Mr. Settler and I think when he when they're on the initial road
trip in the beginning to New York, when he hits on her, she's appalled because he's dating her friend,
she go and they're walking the car and she goes, just let it lie. Let's forget you set it and let
it lie. And they get into the car and he goes, so you want to get a hotel room and he goes, you see
what I did there? I didn't let it lie. Yeah. Classic Billy Crystal Classic New York Joe,
like New York style, cat skillsy, whatever joke. It's just a beautiful movie. Bruno Kirby is fantastic.
Carrie Fisher is fantastic. You believe they're like a little bonus. You always forget they're
even in it. And they're like this great side bonus. The wagon wheel coffee table argument is so great.
Um, you know, the, the chemistry between Crystal and Meg Ryan, like just the whole, it's just a
beautiful, beautiful movie. It is, you know, they asked, I think Albert Brooks was offered at first.
He said, no, it's too much like a Woody Allen movie, which it is very Woody Allen,
initially, the interviews with the couples and all that stuff. But I think it still stands on
its own and Rob Reiner. And Rob Reiner was unstoppable for a minute. He had a string of movies that
was like this. A few good men. Missed 10 were a streak almost on parallel in a variety of genres,
no less. Yeah, the guy just knew how to tell a story. Let me just, let me just shout it out.
You see kicked things off with this is spinal tap, like the definitive mockumentary. The sure thing
is a great romantic comedy, a minor movie for Sherb with QSAC, but it's entertaining. Then you got
stand by me. One of the best king adaptations, one of the best coming of age movies. Then you got
the princess bride, the best and funniest fairy tale movie ever made without, without question. Wow.
And when Harry met Sally, followed Harry met Sally with misery in a completely different genre.
Then he makes one of the all time great courtroom dramas, few good men. Then if you'll remember after
that run, he made North and everyone shat on him for the rest of his life. That's how sick this
business is. He didn't do a single good movie after that. You know what? I kind of like the story
of us with Willis and Fifre. That's a divorced movie. Kind of the marriage story of its day.
And I like American president. So he he rained it back in. American president. That's with
Klein, right? Yeah. That's not a bad movie. And he did your precious LBJ that I remember you
reviewing on here. I liked LBJ. You know, not bad, but but you know, it's not the old stuff
right by any stretch. But anyway, when Harry met Sally, I mean, if you haven't seen it, it's an easy
one to write off. It's like I met somebody recently that never saw a Christmas story. And I was like,
what are you talking about? And she was like, it's fucking on 24 hours a day. It annoys me. I don't
give a shit. And I'm like, I get it. If you weren't alive and seeing that movie before they started
doing that, I would write it off too. It becomes like Shawshank redemption or one of those movies where
you're like, Oh, Christ, it's on every goddamn day on, you know. So do yourself a favor. Don't
this grow ahead and see an anchor man because she was like, I just don't want to see some
frat dude movie or whatever. And I'm like, that's, that's not how it started even. It became that same
with Lebowski. Yeah. But it's like, no, these are really weird, bizarre comedies. They're not like
frat movies. Not that there's not good frat movies, folks. I, did I talk on this show, Joe, about
Triangle of Sadness? I didn't. No, you texted me. That was it. Okay. Triangle of Sadness.
Is my favorite movie of the year, my second favorite of the year, maybe after after sun,
which I'd also like to talk about. But what a, what a great movie. Triangle of Sadness is a much
longer movie than I was anticipating. It's almost three hours. It is the new movie from Ruben Osland
who did force measure, which is one of my favorite movies of recent years. And he did the square,
which I liked quite a bit too. This is almost as good as force measure. It's not quite as perfect as
that movie. But it's three parts. The first part is a young influencer couple. Somehow he found
people that look as incredibly perfect physically as an Instagram influencer. But they're also great
actors. I don't know how he did it. I'm sure that required a lot of searching. But it's this couple.
The female has way more followers than the male. And the big kind of center chunk of this first
act of the movie is them having this discussion about why he has to pay for everything.
Because he's the guy. She makes more money than him. She's trying to talk with him about it but can't
help kind of cutting at him. And he can't help but take certain things personally. Even though she
might not even be intending that. So it felt like this amazing almost like a half -hour real -time
discussion felt so real to me just a couple discussing money. Little by little you start to realize
the whole movie is about money, about capitalism, about the way the world is today. Because act two,
the young influencer couple gets to go on a cruise for free. This giant luxury cruise of like the
richest people in the world. This of course proving the point that the rich get richer. If you are an
incredibly successful Instagram influencer, they give you more and more and more shit. Joe and I
make a nice living in the entertainment industry. So they send us 100 free movies at the end of the
year. It's like they want to reward the people who already have stuff. So you get on this cruise.
Woody Harrelson is the very drunk captain. But he is also like very politically minded and he's
disgusted by everyone on this ship. And his job is to do the captain's dinner where he goes out and
meets all these rich people on the boat. But he gets completely fucked up and can't mask his
disgust for all of them. Then we hit the part you might have seen a little hints of in the trailer
where everyone on this ship pukes and shits and diaries and etc. This goes on for a very long time.
They it's it's not like a something about Mary where you see come for a second and you're shocked and
you move on. It's like it's it's beyond a Monty Python meaning of life. It's beyond bridesmaids.
They do cut they cut away enough so that it's not just awful because I imagine people in the audience
probably gag watching this. So it's a big year for throwing up in the movies between this and
terrifying too. But it's a big long disgusting set piece. Maybe if I watch it again I'd be
surprised that they didn't show that much because maybe it just feels like they did but it's really
gross and it's hard to come back from. But the movie at this point already had me so much and then
the third act I can't even really tell you what goes on in the third act except to say when the
second act ends you're done. You've watched an amazing movie. So when the third act starts you're
kind of like I don't want this. I got another 45 minutes now. I'm telling you to just ride ride it.
Maybe watch it in two parts if you need to. I think the movie is very very very good. Brilliant.
Kubrickian I would say and the best satire of capitalism I've seen in a very long time.
Very movie. Perfect for this moment in time. Loved it.
Second movie on my autumn list. You've got mail. Wonderful little diddy also starring Meg Ryan.
No I think you talked about you got mail in the movie corner this year. I did? No. Have you watched it
twice recently? I mean I love the film. No criticism. I've only seen it twice. So I might have
done it. Well yeah maybe this was a rewatch. Well I'll keep it quick. No no no. Please I love
that movie. It's a wonderful movie. Once again it's another one of these movies you might write it off
because you go oh gosh it's one of these paint by number you know milk toast romantic comedies.
It's a great movie. It's great. You got Dabney Coleman and one of his later roles where he still
looks like Dabney Coleman which is fun. It smells like Dabney Coleman. It's the last time we got
Hanks as just Hanks like he's Tom Hanks. He does like funny Tom Hanks shit in this. He doesn't have an
accent. He's charming Tom Hanks. He's got like Tom Hanks freak out moments. The moment we're
because they're corresponding through through the email and he doesn't know what she looks like
and then he sends Dave Chappelle who's also very funny in this. He sends Dave Chappelle into spy to see
what she looks like. Right. And then Dave Chappelle is like she she looks good. You know she's very
pretty. Hanks does that thing where he jumps up and he grabs the fence and he's shaking it and he's
like I know it. I know it. Yeah. Yeah. It's just like a shade of him you haven't you don't see
anymore because he's always immersed in some goddamn fucking vocal exercise or something you know
anyway um and you know Meg Ryan is delightful. Greg Keneer is great in it. Here's the thing you know
it is my biggest takeaway of the movie and this made me sad. Keneer plays a sort of bleeding heart
upper west side liberal writer. By the way who's very against computers he's very against email and
he's like that these things will be the death of us and you're supposed to find that funny and then
and now you're like oh my god he was he was right. He was a prophet. Greg Keneer and you've got male was
a prophet. Um I'm yelling that on a street corner later to the taste by several policemen
shitting my pants. But uh this is the thing he he he's dating Meg Ryan and halfway
for whatever it is through the movie they realize they're not in love with each other anymore and
it's a very amicable breakup and it's very sweet when they break up actually but he
falls in love with the woman I forget her name but she she played Niles's fiance on Frazier
um before he gets dates that Daphne and she's like a sort of almost like a William F Buckley type
TV whatever like Republican whatever and he falls they fall in love with each other
and yeah and they're so opposite and he's like I know isn't it weird that I would like somebody like
and you're like you're like yeah remember that used to happen
yeah people that were from different walks of life with with like one another
yeah it made me really sad I know well it's it's Hank and and Hank's dating Parker Poezie at first
on that movie yeah and that's the other thing she's yeah they're they're yeah he's I love she's awesome
in it I love Parker Poezie but they it's it's it's a different way of doing comedy the Adam Sandler
comedy is the villain a hundred percent of the time is a piece of shit like Shooter McGavin let's say
yeah yeah the villain from the moment he's on screen till the second he leaves is doing the worst thing
possible saying the worst thing possible the much more realistic and sometimes interesting villain in a
movie like this are are how Nora Efron does it there's a reason she I mean people consider
romantic comedies a trifle like horror they're not serious so they don't take them seriously but Nora
Efron is is clearly the master of the genre I think when Harry Matt Sally beats Woody Allen at his own
game really but you've got male you've got male for starters but you've also got Parker Poezie and Greg
as the quote villains that's also the bill Pullman part in sleepless in Seattle right but they're nice
good quality people well Poezie's not Poezie's really quite shitty and that's not a joke maybe I was
just so attracted to right in mind but she's she's a little he narcissistic right she's narcissistic and
she's she all she cares about is getting ahead there's a great line in the movie where Tom Hanks
Chapelle asks Tom Hanks how she's doing and he goes you know you know her she could make coffee nervous
like she's so just like yeah can he was much more like more like a wet blanket but a good guy you know
what I mean right and I would argue you can see you can imagine Parker Poezie and the great
Kineer character which you're saying you see it in the movie itself having a healthy happy life
with somebody else this just isn't quite right and that's normally what a breakup is right most
of these romantic comedies start with the girl coming home and the guy's fucking her best friend or
whatever Nora Efron just told like the truth of like what actual human relationships are and sometimes
they just don't work out and sometimes this guy's perfect on paper but he boars me and I want this
other guy who's wrong from it whatever but she just really has a way of painting people with a complete
talent I would say and she goes she goes a step further at the end
you know this actually bothered me the first time I watched it watched it and then didn't bother me
the second time I watched it at the end Tom Hanks the store does close like the big conglomerate
bookstore that Tom Hanks and Daveney Coleman open does put Meg Ryan's store out of business yeah
and there is no and they still fall in love and that's it and it's left open ended we'll
where what happens next we don't know in most movies it would have been he buys the shop for her
and they operate together and it's it's everything's perfect and and Nora Efron's like no that's not
what happens like she closes but they're in love and they they'll figure it out or whatever
so it's it's it's a really lovely little movie and also too it's it's what I was saying to
sell the other day I was thinking about moving from the lower east side to a different part of Manhattan
and he was like why do you want to move and I said I'm tired of living in this movie I've been living
in this movie long enough yeah I've been living in the Scorsese movie since I've been in New York I
think I want to live now in like the Albert Brookesy movie like right or like a you've got now where
it's like oh it's a tree on my street and you know yeah so this is one of those movies that makes you
want to experience that type of New York like it's very quaint and yeah it's I mean this happens a lot
when I watch older movies lately but it also just reminds you of how infrequently we are seeing
movies that are shot where they're supposed to be set anymore oh yeah it's almost never
like oh yeah I'll go to my next one are you friends with Joe Koi I'm yeah I know Joe we don't
talk on the phone or anything I'm gonna I'm gonna review Easter Sunday on my my other little no you
can you can review I don't care I'm I will take know it doesn't look like a good movie I don't give
a shit okay I'll go into it I mean I watched it the other night it's the worst movie I've seen
in a very long time it was I looked it up and it looked like it cost 17 million dollars I would have
guessed 500k and what we're talking about if things not looking like they are shot on location
I'm watching it with a buddy of mine over here and we both jumped up from the couch I'm not
kidding I'm not exaggerating as if watching a horror movie we both jumped up from the couch like
pointing at the screen they were doing a shot of Joe Koi his son played by Brandon Wardell which makes
what no sense his son his son all right played by Brandon Wardell who I know and we'll reserve
Brandon Wardell at school high school now Brandon Wardell is 30 and he's got a receding
hairline like a lot of 30 year olds no criticism but they've combed his hair over like he's playing
a teenager in high school with a comb over and racially he does not look like he is Joe Koi's son why
is he playing this role Joe yeah Brandon just because you're small doesn't mean you look young like
Brandon doesn't have the Michael J Fox thing where it was like he was 30 in family time whatever
you know he's like he doesn't have that thing I find Brandon super funny online and when I met him
once he was super nice I'm not criticizing him at all he was offered a role for paying money and he
took it I'm saying why was he offered it I mean the producers are who's the casting director sure but
they're talking outside of Brandon's high school or whatever and it's green screened
like they're it's supposed to be you know just like a suburban high school and they cut to to Joe
Koi or whatever and it's like a completely different backdrop like they're doing really cheap
green screens to simulate streets to simulate you know outside of school to see these are not
expensive locations so then I'm like we're like this is what look at these editing choices and you're
seeing like the wrong side you know how like the first thing you learn is that you shoot over the
right shoulder and over the left shoulder and you know what I mean what do you call that in film
school okay OTS and over the shoulder right and over the shoulder so any scene of two people
having a conversation at a diner Pacino and De Niro and he you got to get that coverage and he's
missing it like we're getting angles of people where half their face is not on screen and my buddy finally
halfway through left and he was like this is not a professional movie this should not have been
released I don't can't believe this I watched till the bitter end there's a long scene where they all do
uh tonight's gonna be a good night the black eyed peas the whole family does it as karaoke and the
camera shoots to the TV with the words on it for like 15 second chunks like for the audience to
sing along oh oh you know it's just filming the TV which has the lyrics on it and not this family
this big family celebrating and enjoying themselves they're staying on the words who directed it
Jay and forgive me I've never heard his name settle out check your hand reservoir that can't be
right but it's a it's a valiant guess and I mean the guy from the guy from broken lizard oh yeah who is
directed so much television arrested development episodes like he's directed feature films he directed
super troopers and all those movies I don't know if they had a week between Joe Koi's tour dates
and I don't know what happened here but this is a god damn disaster I will see that there were
professionals behind the camera but my mind is blown honestly I will say this and we're still seeing
it and we're gonna continue to see it for a while but there we we are witnessing such a bad quality
output right now and it's all it's got to be pandemic related it's just got to be the way things
got hit I'm listening last night I liked the last spoon record more than you did but but I but it
but it didn't blow me the only week spoon record it didn't blow me it did I liked it it didn't blow me
away but it I liked it but I'm listening to hot thoughts last night which is the one before this
and I'm like I remember when hot thoughts came out and I was like yeah it's cool I listen to last
night I'm like this album is an epic feet compared to the new one and I'm like this is the
difference because they were able to work on a god damn record and think straight like yeah that's
true it's it's it's the budget hits from the pandemic it's the logistical stuff it's the mental
fucking collective breakdown everybody's having you're just seeing it now in the output of everything
and you know why why are the Ghostbusters shot on green screen at the end of Ghostbusters
who the fuck knows I can't make better tales on any of this shit yeah yeah no you're absolutely right
there is so and we I mentioned Bill and Ted three earlier it's a great example just things are
looking like dog shit and what's scary is that according to my even my friends on letterbox and
stuff it's like people are greedily lapping up the dog shit but the standards can't keep falling
the way they're falling I mean this was not a professional film Easter Sunday um don't don't
don't watch it the hell day is it oh two Monday okay I'm just gonna clean this is what I mean I don't
even know what day it is anymore all right my last one is um this is a little more of a cheat than
the other two but it is a movie that always does remind me of the fall and uh and it does take
place in New York and it's one of my favorite New York movies heaven help us these are all I've never
seen it where where's where she's streaming I'll watch it tonight I don't know if it's I think you
can watch it on cinamax but not HBO max which is annoying sounds like it'll be on to be um I don't
know I have a DVD of it for a while you couldn't see it anywhere um anyway it's a great movie it stars
Andrew McCarthy uh it stars Kevin Dylan it stars James Hurd it stars Donald Sutherland and it stars
uh Mary Stewart Masterson I always got it mixed up with the chocolate war which I have seen are they
similar boys school Catholic school Catholic yeah and you know and I think three p .m. high
always kind of got yes I like shoved in there um this movie is a great great movie uh I love it
uh it's it's a Catholic school in the 60s it's relatable to me yeah I went to Catholic school in the 80s
but there's there's some carryover uh from what these kids experienced in school to what I experienced
in school um it's you know the basic plot is Andrew McCarthy is the new kid at school and it's his
experience in going through the school coming of age uh corporal punishment is still a thing at their
school uh and they get into all that Kevin Dylan plays the sort of bully sort of bad kid but they're
all kind of friends Kevin Dylan says the I hate saying the f word but the f word uh
every single time he's on screen at least twice uh I'm not saying so that makes it
slur you mean not the f slur yeah I'm not saying so that makes it great I'm just saying like
it's it's a movie about that time uh and the way those kids acted and and what kids in a
boy school acted like um again not that different from when I went to high school uh I didn't go to
boy school but uh it's it's a very touching film um and even with the Kevin Dylan character if you
don't you get glimpses into his home life and you start to understand why he is the way he is
so again as we spoke about earlier uh it's a movie about characters that are flawed uh that
that have different aspects to them most of them are likable um people um some of them not
but even the ones that aren't are they they're layered and they have they have uh they have
uh interesting aspects to them that make them well -rounded characters um in my opinion the movie was
poorly reviewed when it came out ebert gave it a really bad review which surprises me I find the
movie delightful and and very very funny uh it's worth the love the f slur the slur I like all the slurs
but uh uh uh I'm kidding everybody please um Wallace Sean is in it and has a very funny cameo where he
speaks to the kids they have a mixer where the girl school comes to the boy school for a dance
and Wallace Sean gives a speech about lust to the kids before the dance starts
and it's very very funny where he's like you know you know telling them that if they lust for
each other you'll end up in the pit where serpents will devour you for eternity it's it's a very very
funny movie um I put it in my watch list right here on letterbox that that means I will watch it take
give it a watch give it a watch uh folks I'll do a brief one here I rewatched one of my very favorite
Halloween bought terminal films myself and that is sleepy hollow oh yeah that's on my list
loved the Disney uh ikabod crane story was a big fan um I remember when this came out I was a
senior in high school and Burton had just you know delivered grand slam after grand slam up to this point
uh and I was very excited but I thought Johnny Depp again because it's kind of that scorsese
um the caprio thing where you just want him to work with other people so ikabod crane I always thought of
as such a kind of goofy character that so many other people could have been better except I was blown
away when I saw it then and despite the man's personal troubles I was blown away by his performance now
Johnny Depp is so funny in this he's great but he doesn't let his little quirks and eccentricities
derail the whole movie he just is a coward he's a scaredy cat but he's not like leaping up into
a woman's arms you know and shrieking or something like he would do in a later Tim Burton movie
he's a real person he's just not cut out for this kind of work and I think he's so funny in this
movie I love the script it is Andrew Kevin Walker who did seven and this and not a whole lot
else really which is weird but um the cast of this thing you got Jeffrey Jones noted pedophile Jeffrey
Jones in a sexy no less you get to see his upper back which is somehow the worst thing you'd ever
want to see if it comes um Ian McDermott the Emma Palpatine in a rare non -star wars appearance
the great Richard Griffiths from naked gun two and a half and with male and I Michael Goe who are
gouged whoever you pronounce it who is from Batman of course Alfred Chris Walken killing it as the
headless horseman just chewing up the sanery Richie Richie Miranda Richardson Michael Gambin who I
always love and then here's this is when Hollywood you should just be a great factory Casper Van Deen stars
in Starship Troopers he does the tone of the movie perfectly but everyone kind of agrees this guy
is not a great actor so they and he was Tarzan as well they tried to redo Tarzan with him they realize
the public doesn't want this guy so they lock him into the handsome drip who's competing for Richie
with Johnny Depp and he's perfect in it that's what that's what Hollywood used to do now you don't work
as a lead now you'll be this guy and then you're great now we have Sam Worthington who for some reason
has had a fucking 25 year career he's still around like a Joe where's gonna be the star of the five
biggest movies of the next five years well that's but that's yeah they let him do 10 -20 movies though
they let it go yeah I don't count that as the same though that's that's like no no offense to Mark
Hamill and the big fan but that's like if they made more Star Wars you have to have Mark you know what I
mean like he's the Worthington is the guy in Avatar so that's it right it's not quite the same as no you're
right you're right but I'm looking at this now I realize even in the extended cast and I'm scrolling
down like a hundred and fifty names everyone is white but you know it was a different time the very
white movie well and a when a white period of time I assume in Sleepy Hollow but really
steal in the show for me and kind of making me realize as an adult what this movie really is
because I hadn't seen a lot of Hammer Horror I hadn't seen any when I saw this in high school
Christopher Lee who was amazing in this movie oh yeah I forgot and that's really the nod I think
to this being a modern day Hammer Horror movie which must have just been Tim Burton's intent I'm sure
if I watched a little documentary or listened to his commentary he'd mention it I read this huge
interview book with Tim Burton when I was in high school and he talks about Hammer Horror a lot
so this to me is his opportunity to make one and I would say it is the best Hammer Horror movie
it's not an official one but when you got all these guys having fun in the cast these old snooty British
actors everybody's kind of in on the joke but Burton used to be a master of tone he rode the tone perfectly
so you still bought it as a horror movie and as a thriller and as a mystery you disagreed with me
greatly when I said this but I will say it again and it's a bad movie dark shadows is a bad movie
there but for the first 35 minutes it rides the same tone as a sleepy hollow and then becomes a
stupid slapstick come and that's what ruins it if they stayed with the tone through the beginning where
it's like it's it's not funny at all it's like this vampire and I'm like this is fucking cool all right
and then yeah and then it just turns into the stupidest fucking movie ever and that he lost his
I don't know what happened maybe I want to try that again I would want to sit Wednesday
yeah and I and there's a few of his I never saw a dumbbell and stuff and I've kind of given up
but there's a few I want to see his willy walk again just because I hate it so much time will be kind
I don't know I revisited I didn't enjoy dumbbell was to me unwatchable yeah um yeah
yeah you know anyway walk us through the plot of this week's film and between this and another movie
that hopefully we'll at least mention on the show at some point uh speak no evil I realized that
movies in the horror and thriller genre have run out of titles what speak no evil and
resurrection and so I mean there have been dozens of movies with these titles and you can't
solve them apart and they all kind of sound alike and it's becoming kind of a bummer and they all
star Rebecca Hall oddly enough she's in all of these movies Rebecca Hall is stars in resurrection a movie
that as far as I can tell was assembled from deleted scenes from the other six movies she just did
that were like this yeah the lighthouse or whatever that the nighthouse yeah Rebecca Hall once again
playing a single woman slash mother uh uh she's got a daughter in this she's strangely
at the beginning a bit more protective of her daughter than she needs to be you're not sure why
uh but she's a woman very much in control of her life they illustrate that with this sexual affair
she's having with a married man and no part of that affair is like when are you gonna leave her or
anything like that she's literally like yeah I call this guy and I fuck him and it's great and then
who gives a shit I'm free so she's very very very in control of her life in every aspect and she's
got a great relationship with her daughter and then she sees Tim Curry at a um lecture or something she's
attending for her job and she has a panic attack and you don't know why wait you said Tim Curry it's
Tim Roth or Tim Roth excuse me and then she uh you see Tim Roth later she approaches him she says
stay out of my life uh you know what are you doing here and you and then you learn eventually
what's going on is is she and Tim Curry had an affair when she was about 18 and he was in his
Roth sorry and he was in his 20s and she was like 18 he's sort of like this like um I'm forgetting
the names of the cults but you know he's one of these culty leader kind of guys like uh that would
make her yeah one of those one of ours about yeah um and he would make her do these things called
forgivenesses where she would have to like walk barefoot everywhere for a month or you know these
things that induced physical pain but were meant to strengthen her as a person and strengthen their
relationship um it all sounds very sick and manipulative and twisted uh and it's capped off with
you learning that they had a baby together and Tim Roth she came home one day and the baby's
fingers were on the countertop and Tim Roth was claiming that he had eaten the baby and the baby was
now living inside of him she left him at this point in her life she was traumatized. What was on that
yeah that's really weird like this movie is going about its business like a standard stranger from my past
comes back to haunt me kind of thing and Tim Roth gives this real creepy smile in his first scene
that's like it reminds you a that he's good because Tim Roth hasn't tried in a while it feels like
but he's I thought Tim Roth was really good in this movie he's he's both very good in it and he
plays Rebecca Hall's a great actress we give her shit because she's done the same part a lot but she's
great she he plays it very like he plays this he plays it like a very friendly not creepy
friendly either he just plays it like a he plays it like matter of fact like well obviously your
sons inside of me and you know yeah so then you know because this is on shutter that's the point I
started thinking is there a baby inside of him you know like is this supernatural what's going on yeah
and that's I that's where I would pause this if you plan on watching it on shutter and then we'll
discuss the end of the movie from here because it does take quite a turn carry on just
so that's but that's basically it is he's now in her life and he says basically like I you
you learn that her daughter she doesn't know who the father is because she drank a lot and fucked a lot
and whatever and she's that's her choice by the way yeah she's unbothered by that she doesn't care
that's what I mean like she's very in control of her life yeah when the movie stars she's got this
dude that just like comes over foxer and leaves yeah yeah the yeah have it yeah the marry guys so
so anyway the um she Tim Roth is now posing a threat to her daughter and that is what makes her
crumble that's the Achilles heel he's gonna hurt her daughter there's this is a major plot point
that I really had a problem with she goes to the police to get help they're like man we realize
you're scared he hasn't done anything we can't do anything right however
after that he does do things he admits to her that he attacked her daughter and he admit
what she ends up in the hospital for he openly threatens her and then she doesn't go back to the police
that's the part where I started to be like come on man with it like you you can you can go to the police
at that point and open a file you absolutely can open a case file at that point so it bothered me a
little bit that it was so flimsily explained away that like see the cops won't believe her and it's like
I guess but she goes to the cops at the wrong time she has nothing to go to them with and also
why the fuck is she telling the cops this story about her past relationship with this guy
that she tells to the intern at her work which is how we learn of it yeah very valid I mean
I often kind of get swept up in a movie and don't ask these questions but you're always very
funny about pointing them out I agree that doesn't make any sense it didn't ruin it I just was like
you could get an assist here lady you know like you know yeah no it's it's definitely just
screenwriting like withholding information from us and that that while it can work it's never
quite as effective as when all the pieces make sense and lock into place and etc etc so basically you're
barreling towards a climax of she's going to have to meet Tim Roth at some point you're going to find
out is this baby actually inside of him or not which as Pat pointed out because it's on shutter
because of the way Tim Roth plays it and how she plays it and lastly because of the type of movie
Rebecca Hall does a lot you're pretty sure he's got a god damn baby you know like you're like
I think that thing might be in there so and I just thought they didn't have the special effects to show
us like the hand pushing out of the belly button or anything so we were just waiting till the end so
that's kind of like what you're building towards um you know the ending does come it's it's left
ambiguous to a point but it is quite graphic you can interpret it however you want I think it's pretty
clear in the very end that even though she ends up murdering Tim Roth and cutting the baby out of him
the baby cries it's alive she saved it it shows her at the very end with the baby and her daughter
and Rebecca Hall stares into the camera and you realize this is probably a fantasy sequence
um I didn't quite like that scene because I felt like well it's it's insanely gory like a movie that
has been a very controlled thriller with no violence suddenly she's pulling out big chunks of
intestines and stuff right so that's crazy that's although you know the other one speak no evil didn't
have any supernatural elements either shutter I think it's just a home now for extreme movies as well
as straight horror but that's the only moment that could be considered horrific I think it was a
psychological thriller really and that this guy fucked with her and drove her drove her nuts
through gaslighting her about the baby I didn't really see it as open to interpretation but maybe
I'm wrong I don't know well that fantasy sequence at the end obviously is seems like fake right to me
yes but yeah so I thought well you just answered my question I was kind of like well but wait why would
she be inventing this they haven't hinted that she but it's like you just said it's that it's that
the man tortures a woman until she snaps mentally and when she's living in this crazed delirious
whatever right so that makes sense but I mean look overall it's it's a good enough movie it's
not bad I liked it more than like the nighthouse but I still didn't love it I had to watch it in
pieces because I was kind of like yeah all right here's another you know because I put this neck
a neck with with night nighthouse I think I you know it almost felt like one continuous movie to
me but nighthouse had a couple of really good scares and you know this had probably better acting you
know I they both had pros and cons but they really do feel like they're the same movie in a lot of
ways even though the plots are different just like that very gray it's like remember dark water with
Jennifer Connolly like and even the rain like that was the vibe for a long time like dark dreary
you know a sad woman ghostly looking woman walking through the rain and stuff and that vibe is
coming back in a big way I don't know why but that was like early 2000s horror always looked like
that to me yeah this yeah I don't know I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't have too much more to
say about this it's well acted for sure well shot for sure but it just doesn't have
any real bite to it there's sort of I mean you know even like what you just said with the gaslight
and concept they don't even really like steer into that like it's it's like kind of the I guess
that's maybe what bothered me about like the the the bad execution of how she's handling this with
the authorities it's like a person she's proven that she's a very strong willed woman she's been
through Helen back yeah and she put her life back together in the best way possible and it's not
enough to me that just a shitty guy comes back and fucks with her and and it all unravels like I feel
like like and and then you look at the Halloween trilogy the new ones and it's the exact opposite
of that it's like this woman went through a traumatic thing and now I'm supposed to believe she's like
a militia expert and I don't buy that either but I think somewhere this this doesn't go far enough
in that direction like you know this I feel like this person would be more prepared for the resurfacing
of this individual and if they did resurface she would take greater action like she would be like
I'm taking my daughter and I'm going away somewhere yeah the only thing I would buy is if she's
still if he's still had some sort of weird psychosexual hold over her then I'd buy her sticking around
but it does feel like that kind of thriller or horror movie where information is being kept from you
just to keep it a vague mysterious movie and sometimes the characters wind up acting in stupid ways
like Joe is very well pointing out like she's like they're not they're not they're not acting the
way a real person would they're acting in a way that the writer needs them to act for you to interpret
the story a certain way really yeah because you never see you never see any weakness with her with him
yeah there's never that moment where you're like oh my god he's got this hold on her she's very much
like get the fuck away from me I'll kill you right through the whole thing and then the only reason she
doesn't is because he's going to like hurt her daughter or he you know she tries to shoot him at one
point he he like wrestles the gun out of her hand um and then I guess because in the end you realize
she does believe the babies and well no she doesn't when she shows up at the hotel she doesn't believe it
and then she apparently feels it like kicking his belly right and then that chain I guess that
changes her my I don't know I don't know it's okay it's an okay movie it's a it's a sideways hog for me
it's not bad it's not great you're not going to be mad that you watched it you're just going to kind of
be like okay yeah I'm uh exactly where I was with the lake house I'm a little elevated above the
equator but pretty much just sticking straight out uh I am on Twitter and Instagram at the
Patrick Walsh I did my friend Rob Sheridan's really funny video podcast up all night with Bob which
is available on YouTube uh he had me on for the Halloween episode so you know of course shout it out
and talked about a lot of scary movies and stuff and bizarrely Joe is what I've been meaning to tell
you he goes I want us to read this script at the beginning uh just don't don't don't let don't look at
the words until we start and I'm like okay so we start and then I quickly realized that we were doing
the opening of the Paul Lind Halloween special which I have never seen but he was like do you want to
be Paul Lind or Margaret Hamilton and I was like I don't know I've never seen this but that's
the bit we did so that's very funny it was a terribly written comedy piece I must say yeah it's not
it's not good uh I uh Joe De Rosa comedy Instagram Twitter and I think that's what it is on TikTok too
if you can find me on there uh I'll be uh do live shows coming up folks listen Texas if you're around
Houston Texas I'll be at the come and take it festival the weekend before Thanksgiving I'm doing my
one -man show I never promised you a Rose Garden uh on the Saturday and Sunday of that weekend you can
go to joderosainfo .com for tickets um I know there's Helian's down there so please come out for that uh
and then in December pat and I will be in uh St. Petersburg coastal creative for a live show there's tickets
available please get them again through joderosainfo .com uh the two nights following the live pod I'll be doing
the show my the solo show get tickets for that if you can let's make a weekend out of it um I also
have dates coming up in January in uh Austin Texas at the Vulcan and then later in January I'll be
out there Joey Roses by the way is now open seven days a week we open 11 30 a .m. every day come
join us we get new sandwiches we get all kinds of fun stuff going on if you're in New York big
celebration that Joey Roses on black Friday for our one year anniversary come through uh Joey
Roses NYC dot com and we'll be back next time with smile smile we will see you next time and we will
see you in hell