I'll see you in hell Welcome to We'll see you in hell.
You know the podcast.
You know the movies.
So you come to the podcast to hear the show about the movies.
My name is Joe DeRosa and I'm Patrick Walsh.
It's almost become a running bit how bad your intros could get.
Like I'd love to see them typed out and just see how almost none of them
even make sense as senses.
I don't know what to say anymore.
Maybe I'll take over and you know at least care.
No I care.
Don't make it sound like I don't care.
I just feel like people don't want to hear.
It's weird.
Maybe I'm wrong.
I feel like people don't want to hear the same fucking thing every time.
So then I try to get loose with it.
I try to get a little juice on the loose.
And it doesn't always work.
You know, but I would say it doesn't ever work.
I forgot we last episode we did Huey, Halloween.
I can't believe I forgot to tell this story.
Okay.
But what if we were talking about the com the cameos in it.
Yeah.
And one of my favorite cameos in it was Colin Quinn.
I always like seeing Colin Quinn pop up and stuff.
And I find him very funny and he's a friend.
So I was talking to him on a zoom a birthday zoom
with a bunch of other comedians.
And I made the mistake that you can't make with comedians
which is to compliment another comedian in front of everybody.
So I go, Colin, I just saw you in Huey, Halloween.
You were really funny in it.
And he goes shut up, Joe.
My god shut shut up.
Right.
Completely bats it down.
And I'm like, I'm big serious.
I'm not making fun of you.
And he's like, and he's like blows it up.
And then an hour later he calls me.
And he's like, I appreciate the compliment.
You need to understand why I thought you might have been setting me up.
You get a smashing.
And I was like, no, I wasn't.
That was really cool.
But he's like, yeah.
Thank you. That's very nice.
And nice of him to call.
Yeah.
I get those kind of calls, Pat.
You know, sometimes the phone rings, it's Colin Quinn.
I don't.
You know, I know.
I see two of it that you don't.
I tell these people, don't call him.
He's just son of a bitch, I say.
Yeah.
I talked to John Galecki the other night.
He's a name.
He's a name in Hollywood.
I'm going to review one of his films today.
Really?
Well, I can't even imagine what that would be.
In the movie corner.
It's not the cleanse.
It is.
Oh, haven't you ever talked about the cleansing?
No, we've talked about it privately.
I've never talked about it on the show.
Okay, great.
All right.
I like Galecki.
He's a good man.
He, for his level of money and fame, is about as good a man as can be in this, in this God
for second business.
So yeah, I'm doing sober October and it's just so stupid.
Why would you do that?
I got to tell you, I feel good, but always when I do this, I'm like, if I just felt 10 % better.
Yeah, it'd be worth it.
Yeah.
But, you know, I feel a little better.
I definitely am less depressed, which is good.
I think because I don't have the alcohol and weed impacting my anti -depressant.
But yeah, I just, you always want it to be so much better than it actually is, you know.
Right.
You feel a little bit better, but then you're like, man, wouldn't I feel 1000 times better if
I could light up or whatever, you know.
Well, they say the sober folk say that it takes about six months for that to kick in.
Who the hell has got six months?
I mean, I don't have that kind of time to wait around to see if I enjoy that.
Life's too short for that.
Yeah.
So I actually was thinking about taking a little break just to lose some weight.
I was at a show last night at the stress factory in New Jersey, New Brunswick.
I actually performed last night for the first time in six months.
Now, Joe, you told me you quit stand -up comedy.
Is that not true?
I did not do stand -up.
My friend, Jay Okerson, has a show called What's Your Fucking Deal?
It's all crowd work.
Okay.
And a lot of the time when he does it, I do the crowd mic for him.
So I'm there to riff with him and riff with the comedians that come on stage and riff with audience members
and just kind of help keep things moving.
Are you masked or just roaming freely through a crowd and holding microphones to people?
We had to have, we had to have, no, I had to stay six feet away from people.
Okay.
And they had to have a masked person bring the mic to the people to talk and then between any part,
but after every person spoke into it, the mic had to be sanitized and switched.
And it was a big fucking, it was an ordeal.
I mean, honestly, a lot went into this production last night and everybody did a really nice job.
But everybody was so funny.
And it was really, really a blast.
It was very uplifting.
It was very, very fun.
A lot of laughs.
And it was fun to perform again, but not in a stand -up way.
But anyway, the point I'm getting at is we had several drinks after words.
And a friend of mine took a picture of me where she caught me from the side when I wasn't paying attention.
Then she showed me the picture.
And I looked as if I had disengaged my jaw and was swallowing some kind of animal hole.
I was disgusted with myself.
I almost spit on her phone like on the picture.
It disgusted me so much.
Yeah.
So I've got, I mean, you're looking at me right now.
I don't look ridiculous, but I mean some from certain angles got almighty.
Something is wrong.
Yeah.
So I got to lose some weight.
Well, just as I was saying, I wish I felt better because then I would just never drink again.
I always lose like a pound when I don't drink for a month.
And it's like it's just you wish you'd lose 10.
Well, do you eat right?
Well, you're not drinking?
Yeah, I eat much better when I'm not drinking.
I mean, I'm doing fine.
I work out more when I don't drink.
I get the appeal, but it's just, it's never enough to make it to make the switch final.
You can't, I mean, here's the thing, man, and this is the problem with it.
When we stop drinking, we treat ourselves, you know, all the little ice cream, all the little...
You can't.
Yeah.
It's the sugar period has to go.
You can't, you just can't have it.
You got to drink diet.
So when you want to soda, you got to drink crystal light when you want to lemonade.
And you got to not eat fucking bread all the time.
It's fucking sucks, man.
Yeah.
You know, like, but I mean, it doesn't suck.
There's wasted.
It's easier now than ever before, but.
Yeah.
No, I...
The quarantine has been good for me in that regard.
I...
If you don't bring stuff into the house, you don't eat it.
I had a brief postmates period then.
That's where you get into trouble.
And I was telling Joe the other day, they were selling cereal for $1 .50 a box at the grocery store.
I used to be a big cereal head.
I hadn't eaten it in ages.
But man, I got some lucky charm, some cinnamon toast crunch.
Amazing.
Yeah.
It's great.
I went through a big cereal phase.
Yeah.
At the beginning of this thing.
And I wasn't joking when I told you I had like a six box rotation going on.
I mean, I was just...
But I'll tell you, dude, it's killing me right now.
I saw a commercial this morning for frosts and flakes with marshmallows.
And it is...
Yeah.
It's a real struggle to not run to the store right now and get that.
No, I said when I brought him in, this is a one time deal and I'll hold to that.
But what sucks is we get in these pockets and generally Joe and I are like, you know, I'm not fucking in me, bud.
You know, like we got good stories.
But now it's just like, I don't do anything.
I did...
I did my yearly...
I usually do it over Christmas break.
But now I'm like, this is a whole year has been Christmas break.
I redid my Blu -ray movie DVD collection.
And I was so proud of it.
I posted my first photo to Instagram in ages.
But that...
I did my record collection.
I'm selling a lot on Amazon.
And that's kind of keep me going, you know.
It's just sort of like that's my life now.
But I always...
I really like reorganizing my stuff.
It's one of the benefits of having a collection.
You know, you're like, oh, I have this.
Oh, you know.
The reason I was 15 minutes late today, Pat.
Yeah.
For us to start was I was in my bedroom in my new apartment.
My new lavish apartment.
It looks nice from what I could refer to it.
It's very nice.
I like it.
But I was in my bedroom and I had this epiphany.
I'd set it up and what I thought was the best way possible when I moved in.
And then I was laying on my bed today just kind of taken a little breath.
And I was looking at the room and I was like, wait a minute.
That should be over there.
And that should be there.
And I got up and I was moving massive shelves by myself.
It was a lot of heavy lifting.
And I was drenched.
But I just reorganized the entire room.
And then all of a sudden a space opened up for me to have a TV.
And what you know what I mean?
Like it just made so much more sense.
God, it felt so good, dude.
Yeah.
You know, I have a touch of OCD.
And I've always been somebody who likes, you know, I did, first I did my movies.
Then I did my albums.
Then I did my books.
But just, you know, getting everything in its proper place or putting everything in it.
You know, it makes me feel better.
And I'm just doing it for myself.
No one's even in my home.
Yeah, you got to, you got to organize your stuff because that was one of the good things about moving into this new apartment.
I finally had room for everything.
So I was able to get my video games up on a shelf.
Yeah.
And out of like storage bins.
And I was able to get a bigger shelf for my DVDs and blue rays and rearrange them.
I don't have anywhere near as big a collection as you do.
But I have a pretty good collection here.
But organizing them is so key.
Because I had, I would have three month stretches where I wouldn't even know what I had on the shelf.
Right.
I told you like I, or I might have said it up to story all right.
I don't want to repeat myself.
But I've been in the shortest way I can say it is I've bought things that I already owned.
Because I forgot I own them because I couldn't access them.
I couldn't see where they were.
Right.
So you forgot.
I was bought today.
I almost bought the conjuring too on blue ray.
And I looked over at my shelf and immediately saw it.
And I was like, see, that's why it's organized.
Yeah.
There you go.
Amazon is doing right now.
This promotion that they never advertise.
And I know you're not supposed to support Amazon.
But they do bring stuff to your house and not many places do.
I'm all day long on Amazon.
Yeah.
Sorry.
I just am.
I wish I wasn't.
But they do this by two get one thing a couple times a year.
And they, I always just see it by accident.
I'll be looking at something and it'll say by two get one.
And then you click on it.
And then you have access to all the blue rays and vinyl and everything that they are selling under it.
But for some reason, they don't want to tell you about it.
You have to stumble upon it.
How do you find them?
I'll help you out.
I'll basically the only way to find it is to go click on something that click on an item that has it.
So let's say it's sex pistols out on vinyl.
Then you'll notice below and it'll say by two get one.
Then you click on it.
And then it'll open up the world.
And then on the left side, you can click on it.
I want to see all the blue rays.
I want to see all the.
You want to get in these amazing deals.
You know, the last time I did it, I would, I got a couple criterion box sets.
And it was like, you know, you can save $100.
If you're buying $300 box sets, you get one for free.
That's a huge savings.
Anyway, it's a good.
I'm going to need you to send me that tonight.
I'll do it right after we're done.
Yeah.
But, you know, it's easy to get carried away and just start, you know, click, click, click, click.
And then you get shit coming to the house.
But I have really been selling a ton.
And that's been making it fun for me because I'm like, I'll use the money I made selling stuff.
And I've mentioned this on here before, but I know a lot of people are hurting for money right now.
If you are a collector, like myself, like Joe, so much is going out of print.
That I have been making so much fucking money.
This one year, I was like, maybe I'll try the deft tones, you know.
People like them.
And pop market is this great vinyl vinyl website that now has nothing but shit.
But for a while, they had amazing deals.
And they had every deft tones album for like 10 bucks.
And I bought like eight of them and never opened them.
As soon as they got here, I was like, why did I do this?
But they were $10 albums.
They're sure enough.
They've been sitting on my shelf.
I looked them up.
All these deft tones albums went out of print.
I sold each one for about 100 bucks a piece.
Easy, it's Christ.
You know, like, and that's what's been going on.
I mean, I look through.
Not granted.
If it's something I love.
So like, I know you don't like the Beatles.
You don't have to, you don't have to tell me.
But I've got this Beatles mono box set with all their albums.
And their recreations of the originals.
And when I bought it, it was like $250 bucks.
But you know, it's 14 albums.
I listened to it all the time.
I looked it up today.
It's going for $1 ,500 you.
That's right.
So now I'm like, well shit.
I mean, you know, you have to kind of weigh how much do I want this in my life.
Something like that.
I'm like, when I have kids, they're going to want to listen to these Beatles albums.
So maybe I won't get rid of it.
But it's like, man, I've been doing some deals and Blu -rays are the same.
Vinyl vinyl is definitely you get more money for them.
But there are Blu -rays that go out of print.
And you can get $100.
Those shout factories, scream factories.
What I've started doing is buying them even if I don't like the movie and not opening it.
You know, because they're going out of print faster than Criterion.
Well, I'm sure the people that actually want the movie really appreciate you doing that.
Look, we're in a world where the fucking president is paying $750 in taxes.
I will take every opportunity to butt -fuck this system.
You know, like God.
That I don't disagree with.
But you don't want to butt -fuck the fans.
It's my point.
Like I feel like I'm butt -fucking Amazon.
Oh, you know, you're right.
You're the person who has to spend $100 to get something.
Yeah, because there's a kid out there that's like, I really wanted that thing.
And now I can't get it because some guy bought it.
Like it's driving me nuts right now with fucking, you know, the next gen consoles are coming out for video games.
The PS5s and the Xbox ones are the Xbox Series X.
And you can't get the fucking things because some asshole goes on and buys like five of them.
Yeah.
And now they turn around another selling those on eBay for $1 ,000.
And you're like, you fucking scumbags, man.
Oh, God, it makes me mad.
I waited forever to get an Oculus Quest on your recommendation.
Then I get it and it's like Oculus Quest 2 coming out.
You know, that's always the issue with this electronics.
There's something new coming down the pipe.
It's all good.
You're not, you didn't, what's it called?
You didn't miss out on, it's not different enough that it's, you know what I mean?
Yeah, you got screwed.
I'm waiting for the Oculus Quest 3 before I upgrade.
And also to the original one that you bought is more comfortable of a headset.
It's got better lenses in it, but it's a more comfortable headset.
Speaking of which, that's a scary stuff I've been meaning to do for a while is the Oculus Quest.
If you don't have one of these things or you've never used them, I mean, it's a VR headset.
It's called the Quest because it does not need to hook up to anything.
I mean, I think it's fairly well known by now, but you don't have to hook it up to anything.
Everything is contained within the headset itself.
The controllers are battery operated.
You plug it into the wall to charge it when it's charged.
You unplug it, you're free to roam.
It's incredible.
It's an incredible, incredible device.
And for the money you pay, I think the, you know, the number ones are going now for like two or three hundred bucks.
And I think the two's are going for that too.
It's just such an amazing experience.
And it's real.
This is virtual reality, like it's finally happened and we were able to do it the right way now.
And it's fucking awesome.
And for horror and sci -fi fans, it gets no better.
I mean, it's every single game on this thing is some kind of fantasy horror or sci -fi, something or other.
They've got games where you're like basically in Lord of the Rings style shit fighting ogres with swords.
The Vader immortal series is incredible.
Like if you ever wanted to play and feel like you were in the world of Star Wars, you know, using the force and picking things up off the ground and throwing them with your hand.
And it's so fucking cool.
And then there's crazy horror shit that looks so intense.
I won't even do it.
There's an exorcist game.
I'm like, fuck that.
It's too scary.
I'm not doing it.
Joe talked me into getting one.
I think the original intent was so we could do commentaries together.
And if we can, I don't know how to do it, but I guess we could still try that.
But now that we've got this great this setup, we could do commentaries right on our computer screens.
It is really awesome.
I'm a big fan.
And the boxing games are a, they're super realistic, but great workouts.
The problem is you start sweating and you got this five pound thing on your head.
It's a bit, bit uncomfortable.
Yeah.
Well, also to your wildly swinging at air, so I threw my shoulder around doing the boxing things.
But they're awesome, man.
They're a lot of fun.
What's been good for me is I've been lifting weights, but you wind up working the same muscles.
And whenever I do the boxing, it works all different muscles and is a really good workout.
But I have the Vader things.
I have a couple really fun games that what I really like is like the National Geographic type stuff,
where you're climbing a mountain.
And the first time I did it, when you turn around and see that also behind you is off the edge of a cliff.
That's the coolest part of it to me is that it is fully immersive and surrounding.
People rave about the porn experience and it is pretty sweet.
I've never done the porn yet.
It's pretty good.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's good.
No, they're awesome.
I'm really glad I got it.
I got it right at the beginning of quarantine.
I drove to Best Buy and they dropped it in my trunk like some sort of drug deal and it's been great.
But the charge on it is also really good.
You can use it for like an hour and a half or something.
I'm a big fan.
I need to find out what other games I should get into.
Excess one actually sounds fun to me, but you can, especially if you're a weed smoker,
you can just sort of feel like you're a part of the world.
First time I did it, my wife just looked at me with just complete shame and disgust, but I put it on.
And the very first thing I did was it was like I was trying to dodge something.
It was a sample of this game, one of the most popular games where you're almost like robot men
and you're dodging things.
I don't know the name of it, but it's really cool.
Super hot.
Yeah, that's what it is, I think.
Yeah.
But the very first thing I did, I put it on my head.
I'm like, well, this is really neat.
I kicked my leg up to kick something and shattered my shin.
And against our glass coffee table and fell to the ground and pain wearing this helmet.
And of course, having started there to witness this was pretty humiliating.
But it feels very real.
I mean, you feel like you're in it and in danger and it's very cool.
What games do you have again?
Not many, but I even like going online and just doing the immersive nature stuff or mountain climbing and stuff.
I have the boxing.
I have the fun when I do with my little cousins, which is the Beat Saber.
I like Beat Sabers a lot of fun.
But the issue is, I just got this very strongly worded email saying like,
you need to be on Facebook.
You can't keep doing this without Facebook.
We'll limit your options if you don't sign up to Facebook and I'm like, fuck you.
You know, they are already.
I was like, I don't want to do this.
So I've clicked no on it 50 times and now it's like, now we're making you do it.
Are you're going to lose features?
And I'm like, then I guess I lose features.
I'm not doing it.
I feel like that's, yeah, I feel like there's a way around that.
I feel like that's not as, yeah, it's worded.
I think it's, it's a little misleading the way it's worded.
Okay.
All right.
I think it was sent me a free $10 credit.
I like that.
I got Vader part two.
See, I tried to do the first Vader.
The issue is, you know, some of these games, you need a lot more room than the average person
has.
You know, so I, you know, if I really want to do the Vader ride, I think I have to sort
of move stuff around in my house.
You do.
I have to, I finally have like a proper six by six, six foot by six foot area that I can
do it in.
Yeah.
But you do usually do.
You got to slide back, you know, fucking, you know, you got to slide back a coffee table
or something like that.
Right.
You know, it's, it's worth it, man.
It's, it's, it's really, really fun, man.
So I highly recommend that and scary stuff this week that you get yourself an Oculus Quest.
If you can afford one, I know a few hundred bucks these days is pricey.
So I'm not insinuating that that's somehow money to throw away easily, but I will say you
will get your money's worth and then some.
So that's the best plug I could give for it for product.
If you're taking it seriously and trapped inside your house, I mean, it's a, it's a
good time killer for sure.
Yeah.
Exactly.
So anyway, why don't we go to the movie corner, Pat?
Absolutely.
And I think what I will do going off my aversion to Facebook is I watched the documentary on
Netflix that everybody's talking about, the social dilemma.
You got to watch that.
I just, I'm afraid I'm going to get too depressed.
It is unbelievably depressing.
You talk to some big former executives of these places, you know, Facebook, Pinterest,
Instagram, whatever.
And they talk about, you know, very openly and honestly, what, what they do, how they
control you.
And, you know, some stuff I knew, some stuff I didn't, but like, they know how, what pictures
you look at, how long you look at them.
They know what to show you.
They said the reason and, and of course, a lot of people are aware of this, but the extent
of it is pretty sickening.
The big part of the reason this country is getting more and more and more and more divided
is that, you know, how you'll think, how can these idiots think that?
How can they believe that that's true?
But because they know so well what you believe and what you click on and what you like,
you're only seeing your stuff.
So they were like, you have to start following people that have very different ideologies, ideologies
to you or you're just going to get fucked.
You're only seeing your news and they're only seeing their news.
So what they believe to be 100 % true is 100 % different than what you believe to be 100 % true.
And you're both wrong.
And, you know, your, your, your other podcast is about this, but I mean, people cannot
connect and meet in the middle because they're not being given any other option.
They're just being, it's like, well, no, I see this all day.
And Facebook is the absolute worst for it.
I've been off Facebook for a while as is Joe, but you should really take your account down.
Yeah, I'm, I literally am on there to, as I've said, I'm on there, I'm not even on there.
These, my accounts are active.
I have Emily doing my accounts for me now.
I didn't mean you.
I mean, yeah, no, no, no, no, I know.
I'm saying that's, but to me, that's the way you do it.
Like if you need to have these things, these social media outlets functioning, which I do
because I need to keep people in the know, and I'm not saying that I won't ever send a
tweet out or something, but I am not looking at these things on a day -to -day basis.
And I think that if you are going to have these things open, you need to find a means to which
you are able to limit yourself.
I'm fortunate enough to have a friend and Emily through this show that, that she's helping me out,
you know, but like it's terrible.
It's fucking terrible.
They do this graph of suicide rates amongst like young girl, the suicide rates of young girls
like age 10 to 12 used to be, it wasn't a blip like it didn't show up on a graph.
And the year that Facebook comes out, you watch the graph just start slowly skyrocketing higher and higher.
And people don't want to go on date, like there are girls who are 18 who have never been in a date
because they think they're ugly.
There are people who want massive surgeries at age 15 to look more like their Snapchat filter makes them look.
It's insane.
It's fascinating.
It's the rare documentary I wish was longer.
It's a tight 90 and for some reason, this has gotten a lot of criticism and deservedly so.
For some reason, it's about half weird reenactments.
So there's a family that they have sort of act out this stuff.
And it's really unnecessary.
You wish they had more interviews with people.
Then they also have Vincent Carthiser, the guy from Mad Men playing three different people who are like in the internet
deciding what you see and what you don't see.
And I guess it sort of helps illustrate the problem, but your average intelligent person does not need it.
So half the documentary you wish that they would have done differently.
But the information is very important.
And all these people by the end are just like if they think we're too far gone.
You know, that's what's sort of pressing about it is they're like we are absolutely fucked.
You know, we until somebody says we value people's lives more than money.
And you just know that's not going to happen.
They talk about our Saturday morning cartoons.
You used to have very strict government regulated guidelines of what what kids could be shown.
What advertisements could be targeted to kids, et cetera.
And that's all gone, you know, like every single one of these people they talk to who had worked
in these industries does not allow their child to be on social media at all.
And I think that says a lot.
People think they are ready to, you know, get the they live glasses.
You know, everybody thinks they're so ready.
Rip the curtain off.
I'm ready. I want to know everything.
I want to know everything.
And it's like you're not ready.
Nobody's fucking ready.
Right.
It's it's a sense of spoiled entitlement that is leading to the social destruction.
I mean, that's what it is.
This this internet social media is a is a plague that will not kill us outwardly.
But very much very much like COVID -19 will slowly kill us.
You know what I mean?
Like you know, so I mean, I know the body account for COVID is pretty is is high.
For a year or whatever it's been.
But but my point is is COVID is not a plague that will, you know, it's not the the stand.
You know what I mean?
It's not going to rush through and wipe out humanity.
But it'll slowly leave its mark in the in the big picture sense.
And I think that that's what social media is.
And I think that it's very interesting.
And and oddly chillingly coincidental that both of these things are happening right now.
That social media is coming to a head as as a actual literal plague is is making its way around.
That this virtual one is also finally really hitting its peak.
Yeah.
What it has done in such a short amount of time is incredible.
Like I know what it's done to me.
A rather I would say intelligent 40 year old man.
So when I think about a nine year old girl, you know, starting on this path,
it is very very dark to me.
I will not have my kids using social media until their at least their brain is formed.
Because what it does is it forms their brain.
But I got to tell you what it's one of the reasons I don't want to have kids.
Yeah.
Not because social media exists because I don't want to deal with being the parent that is the only
parent saying no, right?
I don't want to deal with that.
I don't want to deal with I don't want to invite that level of scrutiny into my life from other people
where I have to then be the weird family on the block that doesn't have the TV set,
you know, which is equivalent to this was in the 80s or whatever.
You know, it's like you can't be there was a time where you could be a strict parent
and your kids might hate you for it and other people might judge you for it.
But it ended there.
Your strict parent.
That's it.
Yeah.
I don't want my kids play video games, whatever it was.
Now being a strict parent, you literally run a risk of having your livelihood destroyed
because the people around you don't agree with it and think that somehow you're being abusive
emotionally to a child.
Not to mention that a child now has the power to take you to task or worse.
Yeah.
Over your treatment of them because they and we're giving levity to this.
We're giving children, you know, once you have parents, you know, taking what their five
year olds are saying as law and as something that could be applicable to the rest of their lives
and not saying, well, sweetie, you're a child.
So let's talk about it and I want to be open about it and I love you and let's whatever.
But we can't, this is a process and it's not a race.
It's a marathon one once that went away.
It's like, what are we doing here?
This is crazy.
We have handed the reins over to children completely.
We have grown adults doing Snapchat, like, you know,
you get nurses in hospital wings during a fucking pandemic doing Snapchat dances.
It's like, these are the people that are, these are the adults taking care of us and they're
trying to be accepted by 12 year olds right now. What the fuck is going on?
Right. You know, there, there's a man in this.
He is, I hate to say, the strangest looking person I've ever seen in my life.
You will know him when you see him, but I thought it was another one of these reenactments.
I thought it was the predator or some sort of like, I did not believe that he was a real person.
You'll know him when you see him. He's the guy with red locks.
But he's got some very interesting things to say.
And he's basically just like one person out of 10 ,000 saying like, I'm not going to do this
is what's going to keep society going.
I hope so.
There he is.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
But yeah, he's like, this startled me.
I'm sorry, I don't mean to be mean, but we jumped when we watched it.
And to see him talk is even stranger.
You know, he's just like anyone who shuts this down is all that's going to keep society intact
because you know, we need some people to not do this or we're all going to just end.
And you know, to hear the experts who have made a lot of money off this,
talk about how it's the end of civilization.
You know it, but the documentary does a really good job of laying it out plainly.
And I recommend it to everybody.
I wish it was a little better, but the information is very important.
All right.
Well, quick news psycho.
And this is actually a positive.
We're doing the movie corner right now.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
I got confused for a second.
Sorry.
Well, let me inject it.
It's just a plug.
Not for me, but in search of darkness part two is coming out.
The trailer has been released.
Oh, looks great coming out.
I don't know.
But this year though.
Yeah, I think so.
And a little at least four hours again or I think so.
You can go to it.
Give me a second.
I think it's called 80s movie.
Doc, is that the website?
80s movie doc .com.
80s hard doc.
That's what it is.
Go to 80s hard doc 80s hard doc .com.
And you'll get the info on in search of darkness says it's coming out in November 2020.
Physical ships December 2020.
Very cool.
But the reason I bring it up now is again, I get nothing out of plugging this.
I just love the documentary and I want them excited for the next one.
The reason I bring it up now is because they're also launching a social
online community where you can watch horror together
and discuss horror and all this stuff.
And something that will be monitored and look, I'm all for free speech.
I'm all for you should be allowed to express yourself obviously.
But sadly, we're at a point where I feel relieved
when you see that something that says we're going to be an online horror community
says we're going to monitor it and make sure that's what it sticks to.
It's sad that it's come to that.
But anyway, it looks like a really cool thing they're launching.
So go to that website to check it out.
Okay, I'm going to review, as I said, Johnny Glecky's the cleanse.
I really like this film.
It's a movie about a master cleanse where you go away to a retreat
and you drink these shakes and you I think vomit up a monster or worm or something.
And then you have to sort of then nurture that thing and take care of it.
And then things start to go a little haywire and things start to get a little more sinister
at this camp where they're all doing this master cleanse and it sort of becomes a love story
between Johnny and this other woman.
But it's a fun movie.
It's super, super indie.
It's very well done.
It shows what people can do on a on a short budget and still make it very quality
and show that you don't have to skimp on quality just because it's not a big budget studio release.
Johnny's great in it.
Everybody's great in it.
It's a fun watch.
It certainly would fall into the category of quirky horror, maybe even horror comedy.
Not terribly scary.
Just a very sort of a strange film.
But excessively strange.
Not, you know, David Lynch Strange.
So check it out.
That's it.
All right.
I have been enjoying Criterion Channel's 70s horror
package that I mentioned last time and summer better than others, of course.
But I watched a movie I've always heard about.
Let's scare Jessica to death.
And it's from 1971.
I have heard it called David Lynchian.
I have heard it.
You know, a lot of people have said like this would be released today as an A24 movie
and you wouldn't have to change a thing.
And most notably Stephen King has called it one of the scariest movies ever made.
So as I said on Letterbox, I assume Stephen King watched this movie while insanely high on cocaine.
I would say it is one of, I would say Hocus Pocus is scarier than let's scare Jessica to death.
But yeah, it's not a good movie.
What it does have going for it is a very strong performance from Jessica herself.
The plot is very cool.
I think A24 could remake this movie and it would be very interesting.
But to me, it just didn't work.
It was dull and not scary.
Basically, it is a woman who is released from a mental institution.
And then she starts seeing horrifying visions of people dying and ghosts and etc.
And naturally nobody believes her because she just came out of a mental institution.
It's a great setup.
And something of a horror classic.
I know that Arrow released a version of it.
But yeah, it didn't work for me at all.
Your take away may vary from mine.
I know a lot of people love it, but I was pretty bored by it.
All right, I want to scare me.
Well, actually, should we just cover this one on a different episode?
I'm happy to watch it.
All right, we'll do that on a different episode.
I watched Frankenstein Unbound.
Okay.
It's a Roger...
Okay, so I watched this because it's based on a story by...
I think the guy's name is Brian Fallis or Brian Salis or something like that.
He wrote, means like a dick.
So it's his name is probably not Fallis.
Not Fallis, like F -A -L -I, not Fallis or pH.
However, fuck, it was spelled different.
I can't remember his last name.
He's an author, though.
Science fiction author.
He just died a few years ago.
But he wrote a short story called Super Toys Last all summer long.
And that's the story that Kubrick optioned and A -I was based on.
Okay.
So I was kind of watching a little bit of A -I either,
and I didn't see it in a while.
And I forgot how well done that movie is.
And I started kind of going down a little bit of a rabbit hole
with the author of that short story.
And saw that he wrote a book called Frankenstein Unbound.
And I said, I remember that.
I was just like, maybe when I was a kid.
So I rewatched it because I remembered as a kid not liking it.
But now I felt that I could approach it differently.
And sure enough, I did enjoy it.
It's a science fiction take on the Frankenstein story.
It starts in the future, the near future.
And it centers around John Hurt who plays a scientist,
who because of a weapon he creates for national defense,
these things called time slip start happening.
And he gets sucked back into sort of Victorian times.
And sure enough meets Dr. Frankenstein.
And realizes, oh my God, this person was real.
And Raul Julia plays Frankenstein.
And they're both great.
Him and Hurt are both great.
Frankenstein's monster, I don't know the actor that plays him,
but he's, it's scary, he looks like a monster.
I like when they make Frankenstein's monster look like a monster.
And not just like some fucking dead guy would stitch it in his head.
And then Mary Shelley's in it.
One of my favorite Seinfeld bits is about Frankenstein.
He missed the sport coat.
I like a Frankenstein in a sport coat.
Yeah, that's very funny.
Bridget fond of plays Mary Shelley.
Which is, it's just kind of a cool way, it's a cool story where it's like you realize Mary Shelley
and Lord Byron actually live near this actual Dr. Frankenstein.
And that's where she gets the inspiration from the story.
For the story, it's also directed by Roger Corman.
It was the first film he directed and I think 20 years.
And it might be the last film he directed.
And it's pretty good.
I liked it.
It does not leak of the sort of Grindhouse B movie cinema that Roger Corman is known for.
I'm not knocking it.
I'm just saying it doesn't feel like that at all.
It feels like a studio, a major studio film.
And he does a good job with that kind of money behind him.
I liked it.
I think for the performances alone, it's worth watching.
It's an interesting plot. It's an interesting story.
And it's got enough twists and turns on there to keep you guessing.
It's certainly not perfect by any stretch, but it's a fun watch.
It's a very fun watch and it's a fun.
I think anytime they can do a new or different take on the Frankenstein story,
yeah, I'm always there for that.
Because I think I find that story a bit more interesting than the Dracula story.
And I would say out of all horror stories,
these are the two that kind of get revisited the most.
Sure. So worth watching.
Well, it's quite a coincidence, Joe,
because I watched a Frankenstein movie that I had never seen called
Mary Shelley's Frankenstein came out in the mid 90s.
And it's one of the few Robert De Niro movies I hadn't seen.
Have you seen Mary Shelley's Frankenstein?
I've seen it and the casting of De Niro
as the monster couldn't be worse to me.
I mean, it's just, it takes, he does a good job.
It just pull, you can't knock, you can't get around it.
It's, it can't be Robert De Niro. It's distracting.
Yeah, I mean, so Kenneth Brenna, I really like him as a director.
He's his style of directing and I'm not talking about four or whatever the fuck he did.
You know, he's, he does things in this very like gothic style.
He likes a big swooping camera, you know, like crazy camera angles
and like somebody screaming and then the camera shooting up 100 feet into the air and stuff.
You know, I like that. A lot of people find that too flashy
and it takes them out of the movie, but I tend to like it.
Brenna plays, Dr. Frankenstein, Robert De Niro plays, Frankenstein's monster.
You got Helen Abautum Carter, Kenneth Brenna,
cheated on his wife Emma Thompson with Helen Abautum Carter on this movie.
And she swooped in, she was, she swooped in with Burton.
She did. I think she must kind of like that.
There are women who like being the other woman, you know, but I really had a good time with it.
It's not great. I mean, it's kind of ludicrous, but when it opens, you know, like it opens
in an almost Burton -esque kind of artificial Arctic world. And that's how the book opens.
That's how the novel opens, yeah. I liked that it stayed true to the book.
I thought that the style it was done in was very similar to Coppola's Bram Stoker's Dracula,
obviously. And Coppola was going to direct it, handed the reins off to Brenna.
Apparently they had major disagreements and arguments in the editing room about it,
but it's a nice companion piece to Bram Stoker. I watched Bram Stoker's Dracula last year or
a couple years ago, and fucking loved it. I think that is sort of the best example of like
modernizing it and making it kind of fun. I really think it's one of Coppola's best movies.
I love Bram Stoker's Dracula. I love it. And Merry Christmas, Stan, is similar,
but not as good and not as fun. And Deniro is good at it. It is, you're absolutely right. It's
just like you can't help but see Robert Deniro, you know. The acting is kind of a little tongue
and cheek every time two people kiss the camera swirls around them like 500 times. But there's some,
there's, there's a sort of campy font about it that I really liked. I had a good time with it.
All right. Was that your number? That was your third, right? It was. But I also, I watched a
Roger Korman, Mask of the Red Death, which is on Shutter now and being discussed a lot.
Was it worth watching? I've never seen it. It's great. I mean, I always thought of Korman as being
like, he'd shoot movies for 20 bucks. I think that's more than movies he produced. But the use of color
in the movie is fucking amazing. I mean, it's a, it's a post story. Vincent Price is awesome in it.
And it's in the news a lot lately because it is about a man who basically invites people into his
home to keep them safe from the plague and then they wind up getting the plague. But
the movie is beautiful to look at. I would, I would recommend it. It's a lot. Check it out.
Final film for me. I watched, oh, and Mike said first movie from Korman in 10, it was in 10 years
and it was his final film directed. Thank you, Mike. I watched a film called The Shed, The Shed,
which was a shutter original, I guess. It was on shutter, right? Not much to say here. Very cool premise.
It was about kids that the high school kid who was bullied, who finds that there's a vampire living
in his shed on his farm and realizes he can use it for sinister purposes. I was very intrigued by
that idea. Sounded spooky, sounded fun, sounded auto me, started to flick up, opened, cold open,
as Frank Whaley being hunted by a vampire in the woods. I'm like, I love Frank Whaley. Whaley gets
bitten, title comes up and you realize Whaley is going to be the vampire in the shed, which sucks
because he has not one line in the entire film and you see him for, you know, the four whole minutes,
yeah, total. It's a, it's an okay film. It's, it has its moments, the actors in it are really great
you know, Timothy Bottoms unfortunately is the only one that I didn't like and he plays the kids
like asshole grandfather, never liked Timothy Bottoms. I like Timothy Bottoms but he just,
he just comes off as hokey to me in this, it's two, it's just over the top, I don't buy it.
But the kids in it are all great. Whaley does a good job as the monster for as little as you see him.
And it kind of goes from being this sort of interesting predicament that these kids are put in
with what do they do with this vampire and is it moral or immoral of them to sort of feed these
bullies to it that have made their lives living hell, living hells, excuse me, since since they can
remember. And then it kind of turns into more of a survival vampire thing, sort of lost boys
ask where they're stuck in a house at the end and it's all kind of going down inside the house.
It did a good job at tricking me at times. There were moments where you're like, what are they doing?
This is ridiculous. And then they would kind of spin you the other way and you go, oh you got me,
god damn it, you tricked me. But for some reason the movie just never fully comes together. But
definitely an e for effort. I would watch the directors work again. I would watch the writers work
again. I just don't know I watch this movie again. All right. Did you see Whaley go after John Void a
couple weeks ago on Twitter? No. You know Void has become one of the him and James Woods are about
two of the only vocal Trump supporters in the entertainment industry. But is Void obnoxious about
it? Or is he just a, you know, Woods is like. Woods is like starting way more obnoxious about it
for sure. But Whaley tells a story about, I guess it was Raid Donovan. And he's basically like
your piece of shit. I hate you John Void whatever. He went after him pretty hard, but he showed up photo
of it as proof. But he goes, you couldn't keep up with me, which I took to mean couldn't remember
your lines or couldn't hang whatever. And smacked him across the face. Void hits Frank Whaley. They
have, they somebody caught a photo of it. And Whaley was just like, he was so sick of the Trump
shit. He was just like, I'm going to take this public. It was kind of interesting. But
Wow. Whaley. Well, he goes in on people. I like him man. I've always loved Whaley. Career
opportunities, baby. Yeah. He's said on the on the doors, DVDs, bonus features. Everybody's
praising Val Kilmer. Who was great in the movie? Yeah. For only wanting to be called Jim.
You know, they said two weeks into rehearsals. He a formal a memo went out to everybody.
Wow. You're only allowed to refer to Val as Jim from now on. And Frank and everybody's praising it
like, oh, he was so immersed. He was drowning in this role. It was wonderful. And then it gets to
Whaley and he goes, yeah, I remember that. That was the point where I decided I would only call him
asshole. That's funny. Apparently, Wesley Snipes did the same and Blade Trinity had everyone
call him Blade. Right. Are you kidding? You're kidding, right? No. No, no, no. Oh, if you've never read
it, look up Patton Oswald's big interview about Blade 3. I mean, he's got some amazing stories.
Just a huge weed cloud coming out of Snipes trailer every day. Yeah.
But yeah, he made everybody call him Blade and was apparently a huge asshole as well. But Snipes
appears to have gotten a shit together. I loved him so much in that Dolomite movie. He was so funny.
He was great. All right. Let's get to our movie on hand. Yes. Before we forget, so we'll do
it in Hubey, but we're going to be doing Evil Dead 1, 2, and the remake on next month's episode,
for sure. That'll be one of the episodes. An army of dark two. We'll throw it in soon.
We've done our, we did an episode on army. All right. Never mind. And that's all I know we've
been doing this a long time is that I was like, didn't we do that? Look it up and we had, I can't
remember anymore. Yeah, I have to go back and look. Yeah, but so November 1st episodes,
you know, we thought Evil Dead 1 and 2 would be fun classics to review, but also to in the spirit
of the season, you know, the day after Halloween and all that. So yeah. Anyway, Varadica, Dan Ziggs.
Well, tell us what it's about, John. I got to, it's going to look weird for a minute.
I got to plug in my computer, but just told tight walk us through the alleged plot of Varadica.
So, Varadica is an anthology horror film written, directed, and co -deepied by Danzig,
Glenn Danzig, infamous singer of the misfits, and of course, the band Danzig.
It is based on a comic book series apparently that he does.
I think the comic book series is a different name, though. I don't think the comic book series
is called Varadica. It's called something, might just be called Varadica. Well, I'm going to look
this up as I'm explaining this because I want to not fuck it up. Okay, based on the line of comic books
published by Dan Ziggs company, Varadica. So he's got a company called Varadica and they publish
comic books. Okay, so that's what the movie was based on. It's three stories with a wrap around.
The first story is called the albino spider of Dejet. The second story is called Change of Face.
Third story is called Drukia Contessa of Blood. As I said, Danzig wrote, directed. I believe
also produced, no, it didn't produce, but did co was a coast and a photographer on this.
What is there to say other than I am not sure Glenn Danzig has ever seen a movie in his life?
This thing, this was arguably, I'm not exaggerating. This was arguably the worst movie I've ever seen
in my life. I think it was the worst movie I've ever seen for sure. It was so
bad that it made me not like Danzig anymore. I'm like angry at Danzig now. I'm annoyed. I'm annoyed
the audacity of this man, the fucking balls on this guy to put this movie out. Well, our buddy Vince
Avril went and saw the misfits I wish I had when they played here in LA last year and he said that
from the stage, Danzig was like, why is it only the rich can beat and kill their wives and girlfriends?
So clearly there's some issues with Danzig. I don't know much about the man outside of loving
the misfits and loving the song Mother, but this movie is inept in way. It's inept in similar ways
to the room and I've heard this described as the horror version of the room, but the room is
fun to watch. This is one of the most boring movies. Maybe with an audience, people had a good time,
but the reason I don't think it's going to catch on as one of these plan 9 or the room type things
is because it is excruciating to watch. It is so boring, but what it shares with those movies is a
complete lack of knowledge of storytelling, how to shoot a movie, what movies are. It is embarrassing.
And apparently, the guy in the room now kind of says, oh yeah, I knew that was funny here,
whatever. Danzig at screenings was like, I don't know why people were laughing. He thought this was
a good movie. Well, and it pisses me off too, man, because like here's the thing. I understand why
Shutter picked this up. I understand. Look, I left to watch it as soon as I saw it was on there
because I had heard so much terrible shit about it. But what does bother me is like, Danzig is
getting to do the rounds in the horror community. And he's getting to talk about that. Like, Shutter's,
I forget the name of the show, but Shutter's got that interview show where they talk to horror creators.
And you know, I wish I could remember the name of it. Mike, if you could look that up, I'd appreciate it.
Do you mean the Eli Roth one? Not the Eli Roth one. No, there's one. It's a kid. It's a young kid.
And each episode will be focused on one creator. You know what I mean? Okay.
And you know, he has real people on there that do real work. And like, I get it. Danzig is an icon.
And you're going to have Danzig come on and talk about his movie. But it's like, it's not even like
if he would have gone on there to talk about it before it was released, I would have understood.
He's on there talking about it after it's released, which means they've seen this movie, which bothers me
because it's like, it's not the core mic. I for it's called like,
fuck, that's going to drive me crazy. Anyway, it bothers me because as a horror fan, as a film fan,
you know, if I watch this, I wouldn't want to have Danzig on my show to talk to about this.
I'd be like, you don't know what the fuck you're talking. I'm not going to sit there and have a serious
conversation with you about films. I don't care what you like or what you're a fan of or what you've
seen. You don't know what the fuck you're doing. You don't know how to do this. It's bad.
So anyway, it just bothers me. Like I remember when when Rob Zombie did house house of a thousand
corpses. I was in the movies with Pinkstone and the trailer came on. And it was like, it was literally
like Stephen King, Toby Hooper, Clive Barker, Wes Craven, and now Rob Zombie. And I remember
Pinkstone turned to me and going, who the fuck does he think he is? Yeah. Like you don't get to just
be part of that. And we've seen your movies now. You're not. Yeah. You're not. So it makes a lot
more sense than it does Danzig after seeing this. At least he has some, I mean, Rob Zombie like them
or not knows how to make a movie. Yeah. No, I agree. Rob Zombie has has some redeeming qualities.
And I've never seen Devils rejects, but people say it's great. And that's the good one. That's
the good one. But yeah, there is some sense of there's something there. But yeah, this thing is,
like you said, it is painfully fucking boring. The stories make no sense. He's clearly trying to go
through for some sort of like Argento fever dream kind of bullshit thing that he doesn't know how
to do. I mean, for him as a cinematographer on this film, to look at these shots and think that
this looks good in any way or captures any sort of mood or spirit or anything. Every part of this
is terrible. Well, it's it's soft core porn. Except that it's not sexy in any way. Like it's
everyone in it. Everyone in it is porny looks like you know, they're porn stars. Yeah, some of
them are actually which is fine. I'm not knocking the porn stars, but right. And they're all naked
throughout. There are there are in the middle story, I would say 20 minutes of just watching women
like do full song strip teases. And the movie is boring even with that going on. Everyone is naked
throughout. The last story everyone's naked for the entire running time. And it's the most boring of the
three. It's appalling. The first story and it was actually the only like jolt the movie had. It
doesn't even really attempt to be scary for most of the time, but there's this couple making out.
And the guy wants her to take her shirt off and she won't do it. And then finally she does. And she
has eyeballs for nipples. And you know, it's sort of an arresting image. I haven't seen it. I was like
okay, but they do nothing with it. And the ending of that story is that the cops find her body. Sorry
last line is she's got eyes for nipples. And then it ends. Right. This is after they're stating
how the movie how the thing started. They're just saying it. And this is after an 18 -minute stretch of
the eyes for nipples having nothing to do with anything. No. And that a spider comes out of her at night
and goes around raping and murdering women. Right. And they go it makes no it makes no
fucking sense at all. The makeup job on the on the spider is terrible. The eyes on the tits.
It literally looks like if you took like doll eyes and just glued them to your nipples like it looks
absurd. The only bright spot in this movie is Xbox. The wrestler shows up at one point. I'm a fan
who is he just plays like a balance is something very small. I don't remember. But not everybody in
the movie is a porn star. But it's a lot it's if there's a handful of porn stars in this. There's
there's less people in whatever. Danzig and the only reason I bring that up is to say that Danzig
clearly has a certain taste for for that type of performance. And this thing is riddled with pointless
fucking nudity pointless sex like it's it's it's just stupid. It just doesn't make any fucking sense.
The second I was laughing with Pinkstone because I go the second story he's so he's so desperately
trying to be an artist with this thing. And the second story is about a stripper who has a burned
face. So she takes women's faces and wears them on stage. And I go and it's and it's called change
of face. And I was like even Danzig in his desperation to be Argento can't not do the
crypt keeper plan words thing like he can't resist. Well the lady who is essentially the crypt keeper
who's another burlesque type woman nothing she says makes any sense. She's she's a lady who
introduces each story and there's kind of a pond here and there but they don't work. And
God it just made my head hurt. I mean you you can't finish it in one sitting. I defy you
unless you do it in three. I did do it in three sittings. And by the way she calls the audience
throughout the entire film my darklings. Darklings. Fucking asshole. It's fine a line is like stay dark.
Yes, stay dark. Just the most generic shit. And what's strange to me is like clearly you wanted to
make a porno, Danzig. They'd let you go make a porno. Why are you doing this? And like for this
like the last one is kind of the lady from Bathory of the story about the lady who bathes in blood.
They did this. They kind of paid similar homage in hostile to the lady who you know wants to
bathe nude and blood or whatever. But God that story fucking sucked. It's like a period piece.
As Joe pointed out, you know, he has so little budget that you see sets wobble. I mean I saw sets
wobble when people bump into them. And he's trying to do a period piece with no money.
The as as as Salvo Kano says the stones. The stones on this guy. I mean balls to try to pull off a
period. It literally looks like when you go into Halloween adventure. And they have like here's
our medieval costumes and they have that piece of vinyl that's supposed to look like a castle wall.
Right. Like that's what it looks like. It looks fuck and you want to talk about a story that goes
nowhere. That that third story, it's literally just that lady killing women bathing in their blood.
And then it just ends. It's five of those. Yeah. And then it just ends. There's no point to any of it.
As for the misfits, as for Danzig. So I love the misfits music. And I really only know mother.
And it's honestly it's one of my favorite songs. I love Danzig and the singer.
I'm curious to hear his new album of Elvis covers, you know. I like his voice. I heard one of them.
It's not bad. But I'm telling you it's Danzig one and two. And then it's a you're going on. It's a
hard fall off the fucking cliff. I believe that. I believe he has a song in this movie at some point. But
you're watching it that when the first story started, I know nothing about Danzig the man. So I
thought when the first one starts and everybody's talking in these horrible, horrible French accents
and the story made no sense, I thought to myself, oh, I guess Danzig is a Tommy Wiseau type character
from France or from some strange part of the world. And he doesn't understand and is trying to do
a movie in English, but but there's no connection. I look him up. He's from New Jersey.
I mean, to set the whole thing in France, it makes no sense. Like it feels like a movie that was
written and directed by somebody not from here. And when I say not from here, I don't even mean
just like a foreigner. I mean somebody from space. And it's like somebody who had never watched movies,
who doesn't know how just the basics of filmmaking or storytelling or anything works. It's terrible.
But it's not fun too. So like sometimes these, you know, like plan nine is fun because it was made
by a guy who passionately loved movies couldn't do it well. The room is, is funny because like, okay,
this guy completely is insane, but Danzig doesn't seem insane. And knowing he's from New Jersey blew
my mind because I'm like, this is just a normal guy who chose to tell these stories. That's what,
that's what pissed me off about it. And that's what I said, I hurt my opinion of Danzig because
this is not Edward being an eccentric and an an an an an optimist to a fault
right to get the job done. This is not Tommy Wiseau somehow having a budget to create something
that he has no business creating. Yeah. And having no idea what he's doing. This is a guy that really
thinks I deserve to do this. I should be doing this. I have something to contribute
and is proud of this. Yeah. He's proud of this. I don't, I don't understand. And then when I watched him
in the interview on that show that I can't remember the name of, like he's a film buff. He's citing all
kinds of fucking deep cuts and it's like, you know what good looks like. Yeah. How can you not
understand that this is shit? Like, I just don't get it, man. It's, it's, I think we both are in
agreement that if it's not the worst move we've ever seen, then it's only because we can't remember
another one. But, you know, like, it's, like, you know, how like a late night showtime or a late
night cinematics, you know, will be this soft core porn and the story doesn't make any sense and
doing it whatever. Like, you wouldn't consider that the worst move you've ever seen because
it's objective is for you to jack off. It's objective is the same objective as pornography.
What makes this worse than even soft core made for TV porn is that it does think it's something
and it just makes it look even stupider. I, I so much more admire a late night showtime movie
made for you to jack off before you go to bed. Then I admire this. You know, it was just a piece of
shit. A piece of shit. Yeah. Absolutely. Absolute piece of shit. Hot two hogs way down on this one.
Fuck this movie. Fuck it. Yeah. An absolute embarrassment. And I, I guess what I expected is because I
had friends, including Vince and everybody who were excited to go because it's like, can you believe
Danzig made this movie? And they're saying it's the worst movie ever. And that, that fun
experience that you're expecting to have you won't have. So don't do it. Don't get your friends
together and have a bunch of drinks and go, oh, we're going to have a blast watching this piece of
shit because you won't. Well, you'll be talking to each other about other stuff 20 minutes in. Yeah.
And, but here's one of the reasons that you won't have a fun experience is because it's not fun
to watch a goddamn like right off the bat, there's a guy being like super aggressive and
appropriately with a with a prostitute. Right. You know, you're like, this is a guy paying for sex
and you're like, and you, but you don't even know that. So when he starts getting, not that it's okay
to get aggressive because he paid for it. But my point is is like, you just think it's like a people
on a date. Yeah. And then he starts getting like real like aggressive and like, that's disturbing
because it for obvious fucking reasons. And then like, like I said, the lady cries out a spider
and then the spider goes around raping and you're like, I don't want to watch this. This is, yeah,
fucking depressing and depraved and boring and stupid. And it thinks it's making some kind of point
and it's not. And then you get into the second story and it's 20 minute stretches of like you said,
like girl stripping and you're like, you know, go make a fucking porn like you said. And then the third
one is just a lady that murders women and bays in their blood. And you're like, where is the,
what is the point of any of this? Yeah. So it does one dialogue exchange in particular in that second
story. The cop, the actor plays the cop fucking sucks too. But it's terrible. And it's supposed to be,
you could tell it's supposed to be funny a little bit. And it's like not. And it's just, he goes into
the stripper backstage. So you can see more naked women. And he goes back there and he's like,
hey, you guys got to tell me, you know, what where is the woman? Whatever. And they're like, what are
you going to do? Shoot us? Well, no, I'm not going to shoot you. But I will want, like the, there
are joke attempts that, to me, it reeks of a guy who didn't know the language. That's why I'm blown away
by it. All right, folks, F minus, you know, F minus. Yeah, I can't give it a low enough score.
This is like one of those, you want to, you want to even be able to crank off to it?
I tried, folks. This is, this is one of those, this is like one of those Amazon reviews where they go,
I wish I could give it no stars. It won't let me. Yeah, this is one of those. Well, I did on
letterbox. I had to give it a half star. And I hated myself for doing it because they won't let you
do zero. Yeah, I can't believe it's got even a 28 % on Rotten Tomatoes. A few reviewers were like,
this is going to be a lot of fun to watch and just have that. And when I'm like, no, it sucks, every
part of this sucks. Anyway, folks, yeah, but it just like they say, you know, especially people who
are like, you can't do a bad review. They're like, nobody sets out to make a bad movie. This really
feels like they set out to do it, you know, like it feels lazy on top of everything else. I hate it.
I hate it. I hate it. I hate it. I hate it. I hate it. Happy Halloween from all of us here at
we'll see you at L. We'll be back. I think that evil dead one, two and remake is going to be a really
fun app. And I know Emily told you we were going to do different ones. I'm sorry about that, but we
forgot it was Halloween because, you know, what's happening in the world. But the Patrick Walsh Twitter
Instagram and letterboxed Joseph. Jotaro's a comedy on Instagram and Twitter. Jotaro's a
comedian on Facebook. Check out without a country on the gas digital network. As you know,
promo code WAC gets yourself two week trial and then a salvo cano and I will have our podcasts
coming out soon. I'll keep you posted on that. And I think I'm going to do an audio book of my
horror fiction that I've written over the years. I've been really toying with the idea. And I would
love to hear from the Helians if you guys would be interested in that and hearing that. So let me
know and that's it. See you next time. I'd be interested. See you next time. And we'll see you in hell.