I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, and when the sound of your screams becomes
a thing of my dreams, you know I'll say, I'll see you in hell, you know I will, I'll see
you in hell, you know I will.
Folks, welcome to We'll See You In Hell, the month of December, here we go.
It's Christmas time, it's Christmas time, and we're gonna start this Christmas month
off the way anybody starts their Christmas off, by reviewing Strange Darling.
Strange Darling, this is for that guy, maybe it's two guys, I hope it's more than two,
but I think it's only one, who has requested that we review Strange Darling daily, seemingly
daily for months and months since the film's release, maybe even prior to the film's release.
When are you guys gonna do Strange Darling?
Um, now, we're gonna do it now, alright buddy, Jesus Christ.
Merry fucking Christmas, there's your fucking...
What are you gonna do Strange Darling, it's always like, you know, he's always just like
in the crowd, both hands up to his lips, yelling it at me every, I'm like, alright, I mean
It hasn't even hit streaming yet, you're being irrational with how many times you're asking
for this, but we watched it, we watched your precious movie about a woman who lies, your
favorite topic, whoever you are, you love when women lie, don't you?
Well, let's not, this is one where I would also say yet again, I've been saying this
more and more recently, if you haven't seen it and you want to see it, do not listen to
this because the spoilers will...
Spoil.
Yeah, but it's beyond, it's not, they're not your average spoilers, they will ruin the
movie for you, so...
Yeah, I mean, it's success status out here.
Yes.
Joe, I'm bringing this for the first time, I think ever, on this podcast, I gotta have
you check out this fucking fog, I guess you don't know what it looks like every day here,
but you can't see a goddamn thing, that's usually a street, houses, trees, nothing
is visible.
No, that's wild looking, that looks like Predator.
I've never seen anything like it.
Just when you thought...
And I've been rooming with Anthony Hopkins, he's going through a break up and he's staying
here and I opened the back door this morning and he was like, you've gotta close that door,
there's a wolf out there, watch for the stars.
What movie is that?
I don't know, Wolfman?
Oh, oh, I thought you were doing...
I'm just talking it like, you know, it just seems like that kind of fog where like some
old British guy is going to be like, the windows, close the chimneys and the flumes.
I thought you were just doing the edge, that that was a bear.
I love the edge too.
There's a goddamn bear out there.
There's a bear.
I'm gonna kill the fucking bear.
This bear is pushing me to the edge.
Turns and winks to the camera.
Time is a brutal bitch, isn't it?
You know, like Alec Baldwin was like the Gosling in the edge.
I just, I watched only Scorsese's chapter of New York stories last night with Nolte
and Rosanna Arquette.
It's a very good story, a little short story that Scorsese did and Buscemi plays a performance
artist in it and he's referred to by Nick Nolte as, no, I see why you like him, you
pretty boy like that.
Pretty boy.
Time really, really changes the way people are perceived.
I mean, they're talking about Buscemi like he's the hottest thing since sliced bread.
Listen, I've been a fan of Buscemi since Tales from the Dark Side, the movie, which is one
of his earlier roles.
He's never been a pretty boy.
That's ridiculous.
Maybe that's just wishful thinking from Scorsese because it makes him even prettier, I don't
know.
Well, just when you thought, I'm going to go back to your fog, it couldn't be more depressing
that the sun goes down at 4 or 15 p .m.
Yeah.
They're going to hit you with an all -day heavy fog.
Here in PA, it's just been overcast every day.
Like it hits like 3 p .m. and I'm like, I guess I should turn my Christmas tree lights on.
It's dark.
Yeah.
And I'm like, what time?
It's 3 p .m.?
Last night, I went into my bedroom for a minute and I laid down on the bed.
I was looking at my phone and then I was like, Jesus Christ, I got to get up and cook dinner,
man, or else I'm going to be, by the time I eat, it's going to be 10 p .m.
I look at the clock, it was 6 10.
I was like, I can't keep track of anything.
I don't know what's going on.
No, I've been firing up a movie at like 5 o 'clock p .m., asleep by 6, in bed at like 8 15, awake,
crazily awake at 3 a .m., falling back asleep around a 6 to 8.
It's a hellish existence.
Hellish.
Yeah.
Other than that, I'm doing really well, though.
Well, was it like this, I guess, when we were younger?
No, it really wasn't.
It didn't fuck up my sleeping like this.
I would have one day where I would go, oh, I get an extra hour.
And then one day where I go, ah, shit, I lose an hour.
Beyond that, it never affected me.
And now it's like, Christ, if I don't see some fucking sunlight today,
I'm going to just have to buy that gun I've been eyeing, you know?
Well, lucky for me, my doctor said this to me the other day.
She goes, you know, it's important that you get sun.
And I go, yeah, no, no, it's nice to walk around outside when it's 31 degrees.
Yeah.
At 10 o 'clock in the morning.
I'm like, what do you want me to do here?
I can't.
What am I supposed to do?
Sit down in a lawn chair?
It's 30 degrees outside.
This is crazy.
You need to get the piece of aluminum foil and a paper plate that you can put under your chin.
It's Michael Imperiali style.
I was going to say, I think one of the things that's amplifying the seasonal depression for
everybody is, you know, there used to be a sort of common experience at this time of year, meaning,
you know, one aspect was they'd show the frosty thing at this time on this day.
And everybody said, oh, frosty is on.
We got to watch it.
And then streaming happens and that sort of thing goes away.
You know what I mean?
And then you go, well, you still have the holiday on the days that you have it.
And then COVID happens and then that goes away.
And then, you know, you're doing Christmas in March because everybody was sick or whatever.
And then you say, well, at least the season is whatever.
And then the economy crashes or spike, whatever the hell is happening.
And whatever it is, they just keep moving the start of it up.
It's like September 28th, they're playing Christmas carols now.
There's no sort of, and then the last, of course, the straw that broke the camel's
is the fact that now anything you celebrate that has anything to do with anything,
whether it's church related or holiday related or state related or whatever,
there are dozens of people that will call you an idiot or a Nazi or a child molester.
So you really can't enjoy anything as a community anymore, which really makes this
seasonal depression apparent.
Yeah, I mean, there was always this feeling of if we're fucked, we're fucked together.
You know, it's one of the best things about America.
And now it's, oh, you're fucked.
Sorry, I'm trying to help you.
That one half is saying to the other half.
And everyone hates everyone and no one agrees on anything, including movies.
Movies are political.
Actors are political.
If an actor says, hey, vote Kamala, then every time they have any movie come out
or anything posted or anything happens for the next year, every comment is,
well, I'm not going to see your movie.
You voted for that idiot, Kamala.
It's a real drag.
Also, you're speaking about the economy.
I go up, you know, meet a friend for breakfast or something.
The other day I'm like, I'm done.
Breakfast burrito at my low.
You know, Fred 62, which is like a slightly elevated diner.
Breakfast burrito was twenty four ninety nine.
Can I tell you?
Can I tell you, Pat?
I know you hate that place.
I fucking hate Fred 62.
Well, you didn't even more now.
I said to the waiter, I go, wait a minute.
I go, I don't complain about shit.
Did you just say is this twenty five dollars?
He goes, bro, I wouldn't eat here.
It's and and classic like classic.
I don't want to say classic L .A. thing.
Classic Hollywood thing, meaning people in the entertainment industry
who happen to live in Los Angeles.
But classic Hollywood thing.
Somebody would say, you know, because everybody cool and heavy quotes
lived on that side of town, us included.
And because that seemed like the hip place to live.
And and then you'd say, let's meet up for a brunch or whatever.
And they'd say, Fred 62, everybody wanted to go to fucking Fred 62.
And every time I'd go, you know, House of Pies is right across the street.
And that's like an awesome diner.
That's like normal.
And they'd scoff.
Yeah, you can't get your diet shit at Fred.
Yeah, I think I think we'd do better.
But and then, of course, you'd seen these same fucking imbeciles
at House of Pies at 2am stuffing their fat drunk faces.
You know, at 2am, it was fine, you know.
But God forbid you go in at 1230 and get a whoo.
And then Joe would put his head right down next to the table,
like right next to that napkin dispenser.
And he'd be like, yeah, feast piggy feast, you fucking swine.
And I'd be like, Joe, Joe, Joe, it's just breakfast, buddy.
It's just just just breakfast.
Joe's like pulling his shirt off and stuff.
It was crazy.
Yeah, nobody's there, Joe.
Who are you saying that to?
Seeing my reflection in the napkin.
Do I look like this?
Yeah, yeah.
It's like the cover of what is that movie?
It looks like the cover of.
Oh, God, what is that first Clive Barker movie?
Where the guy.
Oh, God, I'll look at that.
Nightbreed, Lord of Illusions, Hellraiser.
That's all I know.
No, no, it's the first movie.
He didn't direct it.
He just wrote it.
But it's, hold on, I'll find it in a second here.
But the cover is exactly, it's, I'm going to send you the image.
It's a guy shirtless in a diner.
It's just, it's exactly what you think.
My face would look like screaming into a napkin dispenser.
Underworld.
There it is.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, I remember Underworld.
I don't think I've ever seen this, but.
I haven't seen it.
Oh, God, and of course, you Google Underworld and it's.
Brings up.
It brings up old what's -her -name.
Beckinsale.
She's lost her mind, right?
Has she?
By the way, when I say, when I casually comment that someone's lost their mind,
please note it is with no judgment.
And if anything, recognition, they say game recognize game.
I recognize when somebody's lost their fucking mind.
What, what did she do?
She's just, you can Google.
I mean, it's, um, she'll do like Instagram videos and stuff.
She's, she's down to like 80 pounds.
That's not good.
You know, she was, she's still beautiful, but she was about as attractive a human being
as, as there's ever been.
And she got into the Ozempic or something and, and she's got the crazy eyes.
And it's just what happens when you're an A -ish lister who slides to not being relevant anymore.
It's sad.
And if you haven't done the mental work and accepted that that will happen to you,
you will lose your mind a little bit as she is.
Uh, looking at, uh, looking at, uh, chat.
Okay.
I sent you the.
Oh, for the underworld picture.
Yeah, that's exactly what.
Wait, this says transmutations.
It's called, they retitled it transmutate.
I don't fucking know.
It's one of these things where it's called, it was called underworld and they retitled it
probably when the other underworld came out.
I don't know.
Anyway, there you go.
Yeah, it does.
Um, um, speaking of people losing their mind and we might review this on the show,
we won't get into the movie itself at the moment, but just a new psycho.
And everybody's talking about it.
We've got to touch on it.
These goddamn wicked interviews.
Oh, are the craziest things I've ever seen in my life.
Joe texts me the other day at like 11 AM.
I'm seated for wicked.
My, my, my heart sank.
I thought I was going to get to avoid wicked every year.
I pick a big movie where I'm like, you're pardoned.
You don't have to watch this horse shit, Pat.
You can avoid it.
Now I think we got to do it for the show.
I mean, I agreed.
I'll go see it, but you're right.
These interviews, I don't know anything about Cynthia Arrivo outside of these interviews.
So naturally I think she's a absolute lunatic and Ariana Grande is so unbelievably beautiful
that I was just kind of swayed.
I don't know if she's always been this nuts, but yeah, these interviews are giving, uh,
scary.
They're both insane.
Ariana Grande to me reads like everybody's favorite niece in the family.
Like, like the little girl that the entire family has to revolve around.
And everybody, it's Christmas.
Let's all give Ariana her presents now.
Let's all watch Ariana.
And everybody's got to fucking worship it, you know.
And, and the fact that she's like four, two, um, you know, she still has that vibe of like
a kid.
So like, which is why Pat's attracted to her.
I wanna stop it.
Uh, the, uh, but so, so she's -
If anything, I'm attracted to her because her boyfriend is so repulsive that I feel
like I stand a chance.
Who's her boyfriend?
The Howdy Doody looking motherfucker.
He's in, he's in the movie.
He's got like orange hair.
He looks like a little boy.
Oh, the guy that, okay.
Anyway, he's dated like, they're like big Sean and these rappers and, uh, Pete Davidson.
And now suddenly we're, we're with this guy, Bob's big boy.
I mean, I love Pete, but let's not talk like he's some fucking runway model.
I'm just saying, you know, the ladies seem to like what he's slowly bringing to the table.
He also dated Beckinsale.
Yes, he did.
Maybe he drives them nuts.
They can't get enough.
Well, anyway, she just gives me the vibes of.
You know, everybody's got to give us homework.
Yeah.
Kid in the family.
It's just, she's annoying and crazy.
Then what's the, what's the witch's name?
Cynthia Areva.
Who I was a fan of because I knew her from, um, uh, the outsider.
Oh yeah.
That's where I've seen her.
Yes.
I liked that show.
She was great in that.
I must've seen her in one or two other things, but I was always been a fan of hers.
She's in these interviews dressed crazier than the people in Oz dress in the movie.
I'm like, guys, get over yourselves enough.
I get it.
You only live once.
Celebrate.
Celebrate yourself.
Have style.
Take chances.
But for Christ sakes, every fingernail is a different pattern and every finger has a
ring on it.
And she's wearing a dress that has like shoulder spikes that go up past her head.
It's like, guys, you look like lunatics.
You look like you just jumped out of like Mad Max or something.
And you're then, you know, doing this thing where it's like,
you're then sitting, you can't look that imposing
and intimidating and then sit down and cry about the lyrics to Defying Gravity.
You're not seeing these lyrics for the first time either.
You've been performing this for two years.
The interviewer is like, did you know, that's the craziest one I saw.
She was like, did you know that many queer listeners are holding space
for Defying Gravity as a very meaningful, this term holding space.
I still don't know what it means.
It's been explained to me many times.
And it's just like, I'm thinking about it, but it seems like weirdly non -committal.
But so basically it's like, did you know that a lot of gay people
are finding great meaning in this song?
And they're both like, this is the first I've ever heard of that.
Oh my God, you've just touched me so intimately.
Oh my God, is that true?
It's like, what are you doing?
Are you on something?
What are these reactions?
Yeah, well, I want to see, I want to see all those,
you're not going to like what I'm about to say.
I would see all those Largo comics take a shot at this fucking thing,
like they do with Rogan and anything on the macho meathead side of the track.
I want to see them take this apart.
But they do, not everybody, but there's a couple who are equal opportunities.
I could point you.
By the way, I wasn't calling Joe a meathead.
I was making fun of how they talk.
But anyway, yeah, it's just, this is crazy.
Okay, I'll take your word for it.
This is just crazy.
I just, yeah, it's, and God, the disrespect.
The disrespect to Harvey Milk and all the other people
that have changed the tide of society for gay rights,
the sacrifices they made for these two to sit there and say,
the lyrics to a wicked song are changing things.
My God, my God.
It's like going up to Harriet Tubman and going, you know,
the lyrics from Wicked, Ms. Tubman, are really making a difference.
Oh, are they?
I asked a male friend of mine to just sort of explain Wicked to me because I'm like,
they've been advertising this show since I moved to New York 20 years ago.
It was on Broadway with Chenoweth.
Now we got a movie.
When I was in St. Louis, they'd advertise the touring company.
And every time, whenever they do an ad for this,
it ends with one of the witches go, I haven't seen it.
One of the witches goes, it's cutting out.
No, no, you're, yeah.
And I asked my friend, I'm like, that is not, it's not a hard note to hit.
I just hit it.
I didn't hit it expertly, but I hit it.
Um, it's not impressive.
It doesn't sound good.
It's not really melodic.
It's not catchy.
What is it?
And he very solemnly told me like, Pat, that's one of the most impressive
and like mind blowing notes hit in Broadway history.
Oh, shut the who's your idiot friend?
He's like, Chris, he's like when Chenoweth first did it, like it just like blew minds
and he's like, you know, it's just like that really a production is,
is judged on how well the actress hits that note.
I'm like, well, it ain't working on me.
I don't get it.
Well, here's, here's, here's the, here's the last thing I'll say about these
interviews.
Yeah.
Ariana, Cynthia.
Cynthia Arrivo, Joe.
Cynthia, I'm bad with names.
I'm sorry.
You have to remember black woman's names just as you would remember a white woman.
It's, it's what she is Ariana White.
I thought she was.
I guess she's Latina.
Yeah.
Latin X.
But anyway, Ariana, Cynthia.
She's Latina is what she is.
Folks, Grande.
More like the, more like Shorto.
I don't know a lot of Spanish, but.
Uh, all I'll say is this.
You're promoting a fucking Wizard of Oz movie.
Stop behaving in the interviews like you're asking them to show you on the doll
where the guy touched you, right?
Just stop.
Yeah.
In these interviews, like it's okay.
You can cry.
Is this an intervention?
We're holding space for you while you cry about the people who are holding space for your songs,
which you didn't write.
But for some reason are getting highly emotional about.
All right.
Speaking of interviews.
Oh, really quick.
I'm sorry.
Did I cut you off?
Go ahead.
I'm sorry.
Oh, you're fine.
Go ahead.
You did, but it's fine.
I'm sorry.
Well, just, uh, interesting.
Um, Rebecca, this is a news cycle, Rebecca Hall.
Yeah.
Recently kind of walked back her comments about Woody Allen, but this was very interesting.
Um, she was one of the main people that denounced, uh, working with him and expressed her regret.
Profoundly sorry.
She said, I made a mistake.
I wouldn't or decision that I wouldn't make the same one today.
Um, but in a recent interview, it was revisited and she said, I don't think it's the responsibility
of his actors to speak on that situation.
And she kind of just said, look, you know, I'm paraphrasing here, but I don't think it's
our, you know, we, it's not our job to be judge and jury about that situation.
And, um, you know, I said what I said at the time, but I don't mean here.
Here's the actual, why am I trying to parasite?
Every interview that followed revolved around Allen and Weinstein.
And I was in a tangle.
Like in this moment, it's the most important thing to believe the women.
Yes, of course, there's going to be complications and nuances in these stories,
but we're redressing a balance here.
So I felt like I wanted to do something definitive.
That's when she made the statement trying to articulate her discomfort, but remain balanced.
Uh, quote, but it just became another person denounces Woody Allen and regrets working
with him, which is not what I actually said.
I don't regret working with him.
He gave me a great job opportunity and he was kind to me.
I have no idea beyond that.
I don't talk to him anymore, but I don't think that we should be the ones
who are doing the judge and jury on this.
Uh, I don't think that makes me apathetic or not engaged.
I just think it's my job.
I just think that's interesting that we're finally getting to a place again
where people can say, look, I don't want to comment on that, man, you know, and,
I'm going to reserve, I'm going to be supportive.
I'm going to, uh, believe in justice and integrity and all that stuff.
But, but at the same time, I'm allowed to, to hold my tongue on this
and work with a person in the chance that I may or may not
know everything about their situation.
I mean, that's, that's a massive swing, uh,
I mean, that's a much more nuanced statement than I even saw advertised.
Most of the click bait articles were like Rebecca hall says she loved
working with noted pedophile Woody Allen.
Yeah.
They're like, oh, okay, cool.
But, um, you do, unfortunately folks have to read the article nowadays.
And I always ask myself lately, which helps me regulate my internet usage much better.
Pat, you're about to click on this to find out like,
you know, why Kelsey Grammer has been blacklisted from dinner, you know,
and as I'm about to click on it, I go, do you actually care?
And the answer 99 .9 % of the time is no.
Right.
But, um, if you do click and read these headlines are rarely actually telling you what happened.
I've been trying to figure out for weeks, like I'm some sort of homicide detective,
what the hell happened to Jay Leno?
I don't know what's going on with Jay.
Jay gets interviewed by local news.
He said he was staying at a Hampton Inn and strike one.
Jay Leno has a billion dollars from the tonight show that he doesn't touch
because he uses his standup money where he also makes tons and tons of money.
Why are you staying at a Hampton Inn?
My, I, I guess his Joe doesn't, you don't stay at
Hampton Inn.
No, but my, my guess is he's staying at a Hampton Inn because he was, he was doing a club.
He was like on the road or something.
Yeah.
My guess is he always stayed at that hotel and he's like, no, when I, that's like my tradition.
When I come here, I stay there.
I'm keeping it real.
I'm, I'm being a comic.
That's my guess of why he would do that.
He claims that he left the hotel, walked down a large hill to get to a restaurant.
Yes.
Fell.
His face is badly bruised as though he's been beaten.
It does not look like a spill down a hill to me at all.
And then he's wearing an eye patch and he's, his wife has dementia, which is incredibly sad.
And in the comments, people are like, no way, man.
He owes fucking somebody money.
He's distracting himself with sports betting because his wife is, is slipping mentally
and he owes somebody.
And it's like, Jay Leno doesn't owe somebody the kind of money where he gets thrown down
a hill by a couple of goons.
What's going on?
Is he slipping?
No, I think, I think he, no, I think, I think it's all, all your answers are right there.
He doesn't spend a lot of money, hence the billion in the bank.
He's on the road because he doesn't spend a lot of money.
He stays in the Hampton Inn, whatever, because he's a simple guy.
You know, that's like, I don't need a big fancy hotel.
I like this place, whatever.
Stays there.
Just like in the old days, I'm going to walk down the hill and get food.
That's what I used to do.
That's what a comic does.
Falls.
Just like comics do.
I fell down a hill.
And then still shows up and does the show as you do when you're on the road and something
shitty happens.
You're like, I still have to go do that show or I'm not going to get paid.
I think that's all it is.
That's my personal thing.
But I don't know.
You know, is he a sports better?
Is that where that came from?
Don't know.
The other ones were like, he was definitely fucking some guy's wife who kicked open the
door of the hotel room and beat the shit out of him.
It's like, you know, there's a million things that could have happened.
And it could have just been, he fell down a hill.
I don't know.
I mean, it is.
I will say this.
The odd part to me is not the circumstances of the accident described.
It's the timing.
Yeah.
He's now been in.
This is his third physical thing in a year.
Yeah.
The first was his face burn thing.
The second was he got in that car accident or something.
And the third is this.
And I'm like, what is going on with this guy?
Did he make some pact with the devil or something?
Something's amiss.
Anyway, you know, the nation is hurting when our celebrities are losing credibility.
You know, celebrities.
Let's get to that movie con.
I'd like to kick things off with music box,
Yacht Rock, a documentary with doc and all caps.
D O C K.
So music box is sort of the new VH one, you know, it's this offshoot that Bill Simmons has
on HBO Max where he produces like four, five, six music documentaries,
kind of niche music documentaries every year.
I have seen most of them.
I've seen all the ones I care about.
The one about Woodstock 99 was fascinating.
Um, there's been great ones.
There's been really fun ones and interesting ones.
Studio 54 and this and that.
Yacht Rock is a genre I'm not a super enthusiast of.
I do think that there are about 10 perfect Yacht Rock songs.
Yeah.
You know, usually with Michael McDonald somewhere in the credits.
So I ride like the wind, I ride like the wind.
A lot of great ones.
A lot of ones I forgot.
We got Christopher Cross, you know, Toto, McDonald, of course.
And they talk to all your big Yacht Rock people.
They talk about what is and what is not Yacht Rock or Hall and Oates.
Not really because they have more of a white rhythm and blues or a white soul vibe to them.
But even just that, uh, classifying a genre of music.
I found this really, really interesting.
And in addition to that, you got a bunch of like really catchy snippets of songs.
I found myself on Spotify going, maybe I do like some of this music.
Well, I spent last night listening to George Benson while I was writing.
It's really entertaining.
Some good tunes, some funny tales.
Since this is Yacht Rock, you're not getting a lot of the, uh, you know, coked out, um,
you know, we picked up a bunch of sex workers in a van and we drove across the border.
Not so much.
This is Christopher Cross we're talking about.
So it's not a lot of like crazy road stories.
It's just sort of a fun look at a genre that I didn't know that a great deal about.
And it's really entertaining and I recommend it.
You ever hear the Donald Fagan thing?
Where the, he's on the phone and the interviewer goes.
That was for this documentary.
Oh, and he goes, go fuck yourself and hangs up on him.
Yeah, they put that's at the very end of the documentary, uh,
because he hates the term Yacht Rock, which I get.
I mean, the balls on a guy from Steely Dan being like, how dare you insinuate my music is soft.
But I do like that he did that.
Yacht Rock to me is yet another one of these things that was entirely ironic.
Yeah.
And, and there are some great songs, but I, you know, I saw a Yacht Rock cover band the
other night called Boathouse Row and, uh, and they were great.
It was a lot of fun, but like that to me is what Yacht Rock is.
It's like, give me two hours of the greatest hits and we're done here.
Like, so to me that, that far more to me is, I haven't seen the documentary, but that far
more to me is not, I'm not saying it's an unskilled genre, sub genre of music, but
a genre to be celebrated is like punk rock.
Yeah.
Wow. There's like so much here.
Hip hop. Wow. There's so much here.
Yacht Rock. There's not so much here.
There's a lot of shit you never want to listen to.
And then there's some really nice cream that's floated up.
But now like every ironic thing from 20 years ago, we're now taking it very artistically
seriously. I don't, I don't know if that says anything about us, but that's what it is.
I do want to see this. I saw the trailer.
I'm just happy they finally got Questlove to chime in.
Yeah. The Keegan -Michael Key of the music doc world.
The Bobby Cannavale. It used to be
Vernon Reed of In Living Color was the go -to on VH1 or Henry Rollins. You could be doing
a documentary about Hanson and Rollins. Yeah, Rollins, Ricky Rachman.
Oh yeah. Yeah.
But it's like, and then Matt, who's the full? Pinfield.
Pinfield. He was always in there.
I still remember coming home that first day and tearing open the cellophane on my first
Queen record. It's like, all right, Matt. All right, bud.
But you're like, guys, get out, Quest, get out of the house, man. How much music?
He listened. Questlove only watched,
he only watches music and then an exactly equal amount of time he spends talking about music
and documentaries. And these are the only two things that he does.
Wild. Yeah.
Anyway, I've heard that he's actually
wild drumming for Jimmy Fallon. He'll often be doing a talk,
shooting a talking head for a documentary off to the side.
Yeah, it's, it's up to you, Joe. You're up next.
Oh, I forgot we were doing the movie corner. I got so wrapped up in Yacht Rock.
I'll keep it light. I watched, well, I watched a documentary. I watched the
Wolf Man's Got Nards, which is about the history of the Monster Squad.
The Monster Squad, you know, who doesn't love the Monster Squad?
Written by and directed by the great Fred Decker, co -written by Shane Black.
You know, it's an interesting enough documentary.
They, they get interviews in with, you know, most of the original cast.
You're missing interviews with a couple key people you really want to hear from.
There's no Tom Noonan, which is a real bummer.
Sadly, the actor that plays, I forget his, his character's name.
Hor, oh yeah, Horace. My name is Horace.
Sadly, the actor played Horace died in the 90s of like, and it was like terrible. You're like,
you can tell he's not alive by the way they're sort of talking about him.
Yeah.
To begin with, and you're like, what happened here, man? Is this going to be one of these,
like he got like into heroin or something? And it's not, it's literally, he like got sick and
went in the hospital and they gave him the wrong medicine and his body had this reaction to it and
he died. Like it's, it's very sad. Not that the heroin thing wouldn't be sad, but you know what
I mean. Anyway, it's a nice documentary. There aren't any terribly crazy stories
from the set of Monster Squad, but I will say this and I know I'm always focusing on what I
like more than what I do, but what I don't like is, and it's nice to see this movie has
touched people's lives. There's some beautiful things. There's an incredibly beautiful interview
with a guy who talks about how when he was 12 years old, he got diagnosed with HIV,
I guess from a blood transfusion, and he got kicked out of his school because it was like at
time when like it was like AIDS, phobia, mania, whatever you want to call it. And he talks about
watching the Monster Squad at that age while that was happening and he's like crying and being like,
it was like one of the only things I could escape into at the worst time of my life. It's very
beautiful. That story is awesome. There's a couple stories like that in there that are really
beautiful. But when you start to get into college film professors being like, now when I show the
film to my class, I'm like, guys, nobody should be showing the Monster Squad in a film class,
like in a film theory class. Come on, guys. Come on, stop. They asked Fred Decker at one point,
they go, they say it's a cult classic. Would you agree that it's a cult film? And he goes,
I don't know what that means. I don't know what a cult film is. So I can't answer. It's like, Fred?
Fred? Yeah, you do. Yes, you do. Yeah, you do, buddy. Somebody else goes, I don't call it a
cult film. I call it a classic film. Well, great. You could call it a fucking, you know, you could
call it Esther's fucking Follies. It doesn't matter what the fuck you call it. It's what the fuck it
is, you know? Yeah, yeah. I call it a foreign language international drama. Okay, great. It's
not. It's a fucking cult film about Dracula. Like, so they put a little too fine a point on it
at times, but it's an enjoyable enough documentary. And it is touching to see how much the cast still
cares. And they all go to all the Q &As and the screenings and whatever, because it is the
definitive movie of, it ate shit at the box office, and then had a new life on home video
and on cable, which was interesting. I've only seen the film one time. I own the 4K.
I intend to give it another try. And I think I only saw it with you. I think we did a commentary
on it. I don't remember. It's a good movie. I don't own it. I should probably buy it, but.
Uh, I watched For My Consideration, 2024 Academy Awards, A Real Pain, written and directed by Jesse
Eisenberg and starring Jesse Eisenberg, as well as Kieran Culkin. First things first, Eisenberg and
Kieran Culkin are obviously a great match to play what I thought were brothers, but they're actually
mismatched cousins. Their vibe is a little too similar. You know, they definitely do great work
to make Kieran Culkin the more outrageous, outspoken, live life to the fullest type guy,
and make Eisenberg the same character that Eisenberg has been playing for literally 20 years now,
anxious neurotic Jew. Eisenberg is not drastically different than the old Woody Allen template,
except he's not as funny. But I love Eisenberg. I do. I always like him and find him interesting
and compelling. And I think it's interesting that he has been a star for as long as he has,
while nobody seems to like love him. You know, there's no like huge, there's no women who are
like, oh my God, he's so hot. There's no men who are like, you know what actor I really love
is fucking Jesse Eisenberg, but he hangs in there. And I like him. Whatever he brings, it's different
and I generally enjoy it. This movie is a Fox Searchlight movie. I thought Fox Searchlight had
gone under. They're making the exact same types of movies they've been making now since I was in high
school. Low budget, low stakes, two or three characters, a small story, usually an A to B
journey and a little indie drama. These movies used to rule Hollywood. They would always be up
for Oscars. They would release 30 of them a year, you know, a trans mother and her long lost son,
you know, go from California to Texas to do X, you know, there's been a million of them.
This ultimately does not have enough interesting, I didn't think to make it special. I think the
reason it's being so highly praised is because movies are so bad that a slightly above average
thing looks amazing nowadays. I've been running into that issue myself on this show. I'm like,
don't want to hate everything, but I'm not going to start saying things are great that aren't.
And I think that's kind of what's happening with A Real Pain. It's a very slight, at times amusing
story of two mismatched cousins traveling, an odd couple, even a planes trains type story, but it goes
nowhere for me. You know, Culkin is formerly suicidal. He's clearly struggling with
and it's a movie that reminded me a great deal of like Sideways and the comparison does not help it
because Sideways was deeper than this, sadder than this, better performed than this,
way funnier than this. So you're left with a movie that kind of feels like a rough draft of something
that would become a great film like Sideways. This needed another pass, another draft and I'm
out. It's really average to me. It's just kind of two cousins bickering, but it's not a bad movie.
It's entertaining and it's 90 minutes. I understand I do this on the show quite a bit. It sounds like
I hate something, but then I say it's pretty good. I'm just saying it bothers me when something this
slight is like praise to the level of this movie has been, but it's an entertaining, small, small
movie. Joe? Also Jennifer Grey, by the way, from Ferris Bueller and Dirty Dancing. Great to see her
again as kind of a lady on the trip with them. Sorry. I only have one more. I rewatched on
Thanksgiving night and this is sort of along the lines of The Monster Squad. It's about a kid
facing off with monsters. Invaders from Mars, the original. Man,
man do I, I really like this movie a lot. I've seen it a handful of times. I own a DVD of it.
The DVD I own is kind of fun to watch because it has all the pops and scratches in it still. It's
just a bad transfer of the film, but that actually adds. I forgot how much I enjoyed seeing stuff like
that in an old film after watching all these 4Ks and Blu -ray upgrades and everything.
It's great. It's pretty simple. Martians land. A kid knows they've landed. They're taking over
people in the town like body snatcher style and he's got to lead the charge to stop them.
It's a very easy point A to point B story. It's a lot of fun. It's got some really fun
old school 1950s special effects and there's some truly creepy moments, especially for a movie that
old. It's great. I'm going to buy, this is one of the few movies where I'm going to buy a 4K
or a Blu -ray or whatever, a remastered version of it and also keep the DVD to have both
experiences. I also am going to buy the remake that Tobey Hooper did, which I haven't seen since
I was a kid, but I really, really want to see that again now. Anyway, Invaders from Mars,
I strongly recommend it. It's a hell of a fun old throwback drive -in popcorn kind of watch.
I didn't know that one was a remake. They used to, for some reason, show Tobey Hooper's Invaders
from Mars every Saturday on my local channel 11, so I've seen it a million times, but not the OG.
I will close with another for my consideration title, Thelma starring the great June Squibb,
who both Joseph and I had the brief but wonderful pleasure of working with on
Living Biblically. She had a very small part in the cold open and she was awesome. I loved her.
Thelma is about a 93 -year -old woman played by Squibb. She gets duped by a phone scammer
pretending to be her grandson. This is a very common scheme. Grandma, it's Patrick. I need help.
I need you to wire me $10 ,000 or whatever, and the family starts kind of looking at her like,
she's slipping, she fell for this, we should put her in a home kind of vibe.
To prove that she does not need that sort of treatment, she sets out on her little scooter
and with the help of Dick Roundtree, better known as Shaft, Richard Roundtree,
the two senior citizens go on a cross -country trip to get back the money that was stolen from her
from another legend, Malcolm McDowell. The movie is really sweet and cute and fun and funny.
I liked it very much. Again, you're talking about a movie that would never come anywhere near Oscar
consideration even 10 years ago, but lately with so much less movies getting made, so much lower
quality movies getting made, a lot of slider fare gets pushed to the forefront,
but Thelma's really fun. It's on Hulu. Like the Eisenberg movie, it's a tight 90,
which hopefully that's starting to return to filmmaking,
and I dug it. You got Parker Posey and Clark Gregg who are always fun as Thelma's kids
who are looking out for her. The relationship between Thelma and the grandson feels very real,
very sweet, and there's some good laughs in it. I liked Thelma. I urge you to check it out
when it drops, which is now. It should be if it's not already streaming.
Well, it is. It's on Hulu and it's on Amazon Prime to rent for pretty cheap.
I wrote a treatment for a movie a few years ago that's very similar in plot to this,
so it bummed me out to hear about this movie, but mine wasn't a comedy. Mine was very much
not a comedy, but I don't know. Was it like Liam Neeson? No, I don't want to say anymore,
but it's similar enough that I was bummed out when I heard this. I'm like,
I'm going to have to fucking change everything now. Anyway, or maybe I don't have to. You don't
have to anymore. I think you just make a movie and go, no, that's my long legs has proven. You
can just remake a fucking movie somebody else made already and just call it something else.
Alright, Strange Darling is our movie for today's episode. You know, a cast of what I thought were
unknowns, and then I went on and looked at their Instagrams and everybody has 500 ,000 followers.
Yeah, well, Kyle Gellner we talked about on the Smile 2 episode. He was in Smile 1 and 2. He's
in a lot of kind of like horror movies. I guess he's sort of an indie heartthrob or something,
but yeah. I didn't know the other people either, except Ed Begley Jr., another heartthrob who I've
worked with. Ed Begley, Barbara Hershey. I guess it's not really unknown. Our star is the immaculate
Willa Fitzgerald. She is really, really tremendous. And then there's a couple other supporting
characters. Giovanni Ribisi is the cinematographer of this movie, and I got to give my hats off to
Giovanni. Very, very well shot film. Very well shot. Yeah, it's got a different vibe to the way
it looks and feels. Joe and I both discussed being very annoyed by the opening title card,
which says a giant letter shot in 35 millimeter. And it's like, yeah, so are a lot of movies, dude.
So are a great deal of movies. But that's typical actor shit, you know. He's good at it. My assumption
is he stopped getting acting work, pivoted to cinematography, and he'll probably do very well.
He's got a good eye for it. I thought, yeah, I had to get past that. And I also had to get past,
again, if you haven't seen it and you want to see it, do not listen to this.
I also had to kind of get past the opening scroll narration that Jason Patrick does.
Oh, I didn't know that. I didn't know that either until I looked up the movie. But
it was just very, it was Texas Chainsaw Massacre. It's like, guys, this is the opening of Texas.
You don't have to do a scroll. I mean, you could, but it's clearly a nod. But for such an original
and creative movie, the nod was so blatant that I was like, is this where we're going with this?
Is this going to be another like in a violent nature where I'm like, you're just doing a version
of what, and it wasn't. It kind of felt like Fargo too, that like treating a fake incident
as like a true story thing, which I guess Fargo kind of took from Texas Chainsaw Massacre.
Well, no, because Fargo just says, based on true story, and they leave it at that.
They don't have more in there at the beginning of Fargo?
I don't think so. But Texas Chainsaw Massacre starts with a scroll like this.
And it's like, yeah, in 1979, the most heinous crimes. It's the same exact thing.
But anyway, that's fine. The movie in and of itself as a whole, very Tarantino -y.
There's a lot of Tarantino in this with the way the chapters work. And not even just the
fact that they chapter the movie, but the way the chapter graphics rewind and like, you know,
all those little things. It's like six chapters, but you start with three, then you go to one,
then you go to five. But it's a simple plot. There's a serial killer on the loose.
This movie is going to document the final killings and the killing spree.
And it opens with a guy, this Kyle character, chasing a woman with a shotgun.
I figured out instantly, yeah, she's going to be the killer and he's not. And they're doing a nice
setup here to make me think he's going to be the killer. Now, I second guessed that a few times,
but I did end up being right. And I did think that that was a nice twist. And I usually
suck at guessing twists, but for some reason, I guess this one. I do too. I mean, there's about
25 big twists in this thing. And when that kind of happens, you start to feel a little jerked around
you start to feel like you can't really trust whatever you're looking at, but that can be fun
too. And I think this movie is pretty fun. The reason I didn't think they were going that route
is because of what it says about that character. And because people today can only see a movie as
if a female character acts poorly, then the person who made the film must hate women,
all women. And what does this say about women and et cetera. And I just thought they wouldn't have
the balls to go there because the ultimate or the initial twist is that this woman likes rough sex.
She gets men to engage in rough sex with her and then flips the switch on them and kills them.
And she also says, you know, you have to make this super convincing to where like I'm scared
for my life and I don't know what's real and what's not. And are you really trying to hurt me or is
it sex and blah, blah, blah. So that setup is a very dicey one for a movie made in 2024. And to
the movie's credit, it definitely goes there and stays there. You know, it's a movie about
women lying about sexual assault, which is always going to be tricky to say the least. And I think
it pulls it off pretty well. Yeah, it is interesting. They do that thing with the two cops
toward the end where she's chained to the freezer. Yeah. And they come in and the cop
that's been chasing her is dead. And, you know, the female cop is like our first order of business
is to help this woman who was wounded get the care she needs. And the other cop is like, she
could have done this and we don't know and we have to follow. So they're arguing over protocol.
And the woman plays the gender card immediately. The female cop plays the gender card almost
immediately and says, just because I have a vagina doesn't mean you don't have to listen to
me or something. And the male cop is like, it's got nothing to do with that. I'm telling you,
she could have done this. Like, we have to be careful. I was actually surprised they ran with
that. And then - Me too. And I can't imagine that when police show up on a scene like that,
that they would ever suspect the woman of any wrongdoing. Well, I don't know.
I have no idea. But the fact that they actually did that and I was like, they're not going to
reveal to these cops that she's just going to get away now and that's going to be the end of it. And
it's like, no, they're going to reveal that she is the killer, that the female cop was wrong,
that the male cop was right. However, we're going to turn that on its ear because she's
going to let the female cop go and she's going to kill the male cop. And I bet you if you re -watched
this, she says at one point when she's explaining why she murders people, she says sometimes she
sees devils. She doesn't see people. I bet you if you re -watch this, well, I shouldn't say that
because she kills, I don't know. I just have a feeling like there's some small details where
it's like, oh, this guy does something that is a little off and that's why she kills him.
Because every time she kills somebody she doesn't want to kill, she apologizes and says,
I didn't want to do that, but I had to. And then she will let other people go.
So I'm like, I wonder if there's some sort of pattern in there that you don't catch the first
why she kills, who she kills, but maybe I'm overthinking it. But anyway,
everything you said, yes, it's an interesting take on this sort of thing because they don't make any
apologies about making the female character just a heinous fucking human being. That's it. She's
down to her, with the rough sex thing where the cop is being like, and when they're in the hotel,
he's like, I don't feel comfortable with this. And the way she keeps pulling him back into the
abuse fantasy and everything. It's dark and there's never, that's why it kind of annoyed me
when the two cops show up at the end, that the redheaded cop even says the thing about,
just because I have a vagina. They were doing such a good job of not letting you just internally
question these things about gender or whatever as you watched it. And that was a moment where I was
like, that must be in there for a reason because it's so heavy handed. And there's no other heavy
handed moment like that. That was the one moment where I was like, that was very heavy handed and
kind of clumsy. And maybe that was the point was like, look, this person puts too much focus on
gender and now, you know, the fucking serial killer got loose because of it, you know?
Yeah. Yeah. That was the most surprising aspect to me is that, you know, like I have a friend who's
got a brilliant idea for a thriller with a trans killer, you know, and you know, Silence of the
Lambs, you could argue is that too. There's a whole documentary made about, you know, how trans
people going back to psycho and beyond are villains and how that's dangerous or whatever.
And this person can't get the movie made because it's like, you can't have a trans killer. And it's
like, don't we want to make movies about the entire trans experience, good and bad? And it's like,
yeah, but nobody's going to let you make a movie with a trans killer. You could do a whole show
about whether or not that's. I think real quick, I think the answer to that is, is that the problem
becomes, no, no, no, you can do that. The problem is that it's too repeatedly portrayed that way.
You know what I mean? Yeah. Yeah. But I'll say this too, and I'm going to talk about psycho on
the next episode. I just rewatch psycho or all of them. Yeah. And I'll do them in the movie corner.
It's not a movie. He's not a fucking trans killer. He's a guy that dresses up as his mother
because he's got a dual personality. Those are two different things. It really annoys me that they
put on a dress. That's he's a trans killer. They're saying bad things about trans. No,
they're not. He doesn't like to dress up as a woman. He doesn't think of himself as a woman.
He is sick and thinks his mother is still alive and is living it out by dressing up as her.
Those are two very different fucking things. Totally. I think, you know, the reason that that
and others are, are, are, are discussed is because it's kind of the only way
an entire generation saw trans people was either it was comedically Mrs. Doubtfire
or it was they're a vicious murderer, I guess, you know? So in this, you know, even the idea
of having a woman lie about this, who is kind of, you know, she's an antihero, but sort of
the hero of the thing, you know, in a weird way. It is crazy. It's what gives the movie its edge.
It's what gives the movie its pulse. In addition to, to, you know, I don't know, would we have
noticed the cinematography if it wasn't Giovanni Ribisi? Would we have noticed it if it wasn't
this film was shot in 35 millimeter? Maybe it's really good. But that, and I think the subject
matter and its willingness to go and dig into the discomfort of the story is what makes this movie
really work. And I think it is fun that the six act structure and the way it kind of plays with
time may not be totally fresh and novel, but it's certainly a lot more entertaining than a
presentation of these events would have been. And I look forward to seeing what this guy does next
because I like the movie a lot. I agree. I look forward to seeing what Emma, the lead, stars in
again after this. She was, or Willa, excuse me. I had never heard of her, but she's,
she's fucking tremendous, man. Holy shit. She is great. She's great folks. Well,
step up to the plate. We'll be back folks next episode with Christmas,
the new Christmas classic Nutcrackers. I'll see you this weekend in Somerville, Massachusetts.
If you haven't gotten your tickets yet, please get your tickets now at Joe DeRosa comedy.
No, I'm sorry, just joderosa .com. Big Christmas holiday show this coming Saturday, December 7th,
Somerville, Massachusetts at the Crystal Ballroom Me, Salsa Windfall, and many surprises.
Trust me on that. I will see you there. Folks, we are on See You in Hell Pod on Instagram.
I'm at the Patrick Walsh. We will be back with a review of Nutcrackers and maybe more Christmas
horror as the month trails on. We'll see you next time and we'll see you in hell.