Folks, it's we'll see you in hell back for the month of September with some big old
movies to talk about.
My name is Joe DeRosa.
And my name is Patrick Walsh.
We are reviewing Barbie, which is one half of the big Barbenheimer double
feature that brought America back to the cinema again.
Thank God I saw Barbie.
I was baffled by it.
I've been speaking negatively about it to all those who will
listen, and then yesterday I saw it again because everybody loves it.
So I saw it again.
Did it change my mind?
I will let you know when we get there, Joe, what's new with you?
I've had, well, I will say this.
I've had anxiety about this movie because before I saw it, I did that
pretty scathing take on it.
And then like two days after that posted that episode posted, everything hit the
internet where people were like, if you're a man that thinks this, you're an
idiot sex, and I was like, Oh Jesus, that's not what I said.
See the, the idea that if you like or dislike a movie, it means you are
something is so fucked up and wrong.
That is not what art is about the idea that if you enjoyed green book, you're
racist, the idea that if you did not enjoy Barbie, you're a misogynist.
These are crazy viewpoints, in my opinion, crazy, unhinged.
Yeah.
This, this, this really gets a bread East and Ellis going the off.
I'm sure it does.
He, he goes off about this on his podcast, man.
He gets real hot.
Yeah.
Oh, I didn't like it.
So I'm a racist.
I guess I can't not appreciate poor editing anymore.
He, he really gets wound up about it.
I agree.
I agree with him.
That's how I feel.
Um, anyway, what's new with me, Pat?
I'm in the final stages of the house, home, home purchase.
Uh,
yeah, it grows up and you grows up.
Yeah.
Um, that's been fun.
If, uh, if you ever wanted to wake up at 4 AM, 6 30 AM, and then just that
your regular wake up time, whenever that may be with searing stomach pains that
you've made the worst mistake of your life, I warned you, Joe, I warned you.
I was like, it's worth it, but you were going to have a lot of stress and anxiety.
Yeah.
Uh, and then you'll have moments with your real estate agent where they say
things like you're like asking questions.
Cause you don't know what's going on.
Cause you've never done it.
When I, when I started 10 years ago to buy my house, I did not
know what the word escrow meant.
I had no clue.
Yeah.
I didn't know what that meant.
Turns out it means it's an account in between the parties
where they hold your money.
I didn't know the fuck that bet.
Yeah.
It's a, it's really just adding a step where your money is an extreme
jeopardy to the process and it's the most money you've ever spent on anything.
Um, it's like, thanks guys.
And by the way, to add to it, we were in contract at a different
house and it fell apart.
So my deposit money was sitting in an escrow account on a different house.
And I was waiting to get that back as I was going forward with a new house.
So I had money all over the place.
I was, and people let me just quell any.
I do not have money to throw around like that.
This was a huge decision for me.
Uh, it was not an easy thing.
So I, um, I was, uh, it was just wild.
And then you couple that with the three other career pursuits I've chosen
that have zero stability in any of them.
And, you know, you're just a mess.
I was having some, I was, I'm trying to do a little bit of a booze dry out
cause I was having some drunks like where you'd have, you'd get in there.
And I find myself in the middle of like fifth avenue coming out of a bar on the
phone with a friend of mine going like, Oh, I guess I'm the fucking stooge.
I guess nobody needs to call me back.
I'm only the one making a life fucking decision here.
I was like, Oh boy, this is, this is, yeah.
Yeah.
Like New York family tourists, like watching you shuffle down the
sidewalk, yelling at yourself.
I, uh, I, uh, wake up call.
They got the, I love New York shirts on taking photos of you.
They just let them walk the streets there.
I had a moment I was walking.
This was not directly related, but clearly my reaction was a result.
And of the fact that I hate lifestyle cyclists, but I was walking through a
bike path where they're supposed to yield to pedestrians cause it's a foot.
There's a pedestrian thoroughfare and the guy didn't stop, almost hit me.
And then went fucking asshole to me.
And I go, you're supposed to yield to the pedestrians.
You fucking cocksucker.
And then I turned and there was a two dad family with their two young
children, quietly shaking their heads at me in judgment.
And I was just like, yeah, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I just realized now it might've been because of the implication
of the word cocksucker, which I did not mean as a judgment of lifestyle.
I was just yelling it.
Joe, I don't think there's any might about it.
That's a, that was not the word to choose in that scenario.
I didn't know.
I know.
I said the, I say we've discussed it.
It's one, it's one word.
I won't let go because it does apply to both male and female.
So I do think it's fair.
And I'll admit this readily.
I would, uh, trans women, women, Bailey J dear friend of mine.
I would suck her dick.
So I think I'm, I think I'm allowed to use the word.
We'll see.
Maybe I get canceled after this episode.
Maybe this is the end.
Uh, I have completely stopped talking.
So everyone please, please notice that I am not speaking.
Um, the, uh, what was I going to say?
Um, Oh, this will, this would get you dude.
Wow.
My real estate agent at one point, again, cause you're asking all these
questions because you don't know the terminology, you don't know what the
words mean and I'm asking, I'm going, so, so I, so the mortgage, I'm going
through the steps of the mortgage rep said this and so she, she determined
that if we did the deal this way, it would be the best for me.
Now what I'm thinking is that is better because it takes more money out of the
loan, but then I do have to put a little more down, which I think in the, in my
real estate agent goes, I'm just, I'm, let me cut you off.
I'm just trying to get to the bottom of this question.
What are you asking me?
And, and you want to get in your car and drive to their home.
Yeah.
It makes you so mad.
You know, but they're doing it every day for 15 years.
I, I told this woman early on, I was like, I called you up.
We've never met and I'm going to now hand you this giant commission.
All I ask is that you talk to me as if I have a severe brain
disorder throughout this process.
Right.
Like do not, don't condescend.
You know, don't be like, you don't know what this is.
I don't know what anything is.
Right.
Just hold my hand, dumb it down.
Don't laugh when I asked stupid naive questions.
And she was great about it, but I, you know, I had to say that a few times, like
you can't talk like you talk to your other realtor friends about buying a house.
I last week, I, you know, I would have never dreamed of buying a house.
So I need some help.
Yeah.
They, they do like to give you that sort of Glenn Gary, Glenn Ross.
No, this is how we all talk at the bar after the big sale, dude.
And you're like, come on, man.
Yeah.
But anyway, Pat, I'm not going to go ahead.
Good.
I was just going to say, at least you don't have a, a stalker slash murderer
living behind you as I did when I moved into this house.
No, not, not living behind my house, but, uh, perhaps in other areas of
life, uh, a wild year, but a wild year.
Yeah.
A little stalker.
I can't get into it.
Uh, I'm afraid to get into it.
Well, please call me after the show.
I'd love to hear about it.
Sure.
I, um, I have been dealing with an Amazon dispute that I finally snapped off the
other day and now I have had stress the past few days that I'm going to lose my
Amazon account because of how I responded, but let me just read this to you.
I, so I had bought an on arrow when one of their big 50 % off sales, uh, legend,
the Tom Cruise Ridley Scott movie, great flick, Tim Curry.
And I bought this limited edition has like four cuts of the movie.
It's like how Ridley Scott did with his Blade Runner where he's like,
you don't like this one.
How about this one?
It's 40 minutes longer and it's got two unicorns instead of one.
By the way, just to add, just to add insult injury, cause I don't even
know where this is going.
It's no, it's not going anywhere.
Good.
I have that same version.
Uh, I got it on the regular Blu ray.
It was $11, but because arrow put their insignia on it, it was probably $57.
That's right.
I love arrow, but I mean, sometimes you're like, come on guys.
Geez.
Yeah.
No, I had bought it in a half off sale and then decided that I don't
need legend in my life basically.
And it was new and had gone out of print this particular edition.
So it was going for like 60 bucks.
And I go, ah, that's good enough.
I'll double my money.
I sell it.
The big thing now on Amazon is people with blatant scam attempts.
Hey, sorry.
I just got the package and it's completely destroyed.
I need a full refund.
You're like, oh, okay.
Well, let me just run that by Amazon customer service.
And then you never hear from them again.
Like these people are just lying and they want them as soon as you
call them out, they drop usually.
This guy goes, hello, this item was sent new and sealed in a padded
envelope that I packaged myself, by the way.
Hello.
The item came badly damaged the packaging outside as well as the
contents inside, I am a collector and expected very good condition.
Huh?
Then why did you order a new item?
New is better than very good.
Um, this is not in very good condition.
I do not see how I can resell this in the future.
If I decide to therefore I would like a large discount on this item, please.
Because for the price that I paid, I shouldn't get a damaged product.
I wrote back, you were sent a brand new factory sealed item, which I carefully
packaged in a padded envelope.
What sort of damage did it have?
He sends back four identical photos of the upper left corner of the Blu -ray
sealed and in mint condition.
There is, there is nothing at all.
It's just a perfectly sealed Blu -ray box.
And he sends me four of the same photos.
Then he goes, so like, you know, here it is.
Basically I go, now, wait a minute.
You said that the inside of the package was damaged, but you
haven't opened the package.
That felt really good because I knew I had them there.
Yeah.
He says, sorry, that other message was supposed to be for eBay.
Okay.
I bought a used copy of legend from them, from the eBay people, but I was
going to keep this one completely sealed.
So it's the outside box that is damaged and the seal is broken.
Definitely not able to resell it as new.
Oh shit.
This was not cheap.
I wanted it to look perfect.
Not torn on all sides.
I said, you sent me the same picture four times of the same
corner and there is no tear.
If you have other photos that prove the damage, please send them.
He does not.
He says also, right.
Because by the way, by the way, he's not going to tear it because he's
not going to tear his own product because he's scaring you.
Yeah.
So he, he's stuck down now.
He's really stuck.
Yeah.
Yes.
He says as a response to me saying, let me see the other corners.
He goes, also, maybe try packaging it in a box with bubble wrap.
Maybe that would have been better and less likely to get damaged and torn
corners and ripped seal.
You think we've already discussed that it was sent to him in
a fucking padded envelope.
I write back.
I don't understand your messages at all.
It's not clearly written.
I will say this feels very suspicious to me.
Even in the photo you sent, there is clearly nothing wrong with the product.
Of course you can resell it as new.
It is new.
It's completely sealed and nobody would complain about whatever you're
supposed to be showing me with these photos.
If anything, these photos proves that it was sent to you
in sealed and mint condition.
Now here's where I'm nicer than I need to be.
If you want a full refund, ship it back to me.
If you want to keep it, enjoy.
Didn't have to do that.
He escalates it to Amazon.
He complains to Amazon.
So now they're involved.
So of course with Amazon customer service, they don't actually do anything for you.
They don't help, but they got involved.
They sent this to me.
Then I sent back to him.
Let me find my.
Yeah.
Okay.
You are the customer in question.
I explained the whole situation exactly what happened.
I won't read it that all to you again, but I was like, if the customer will
accept a $5 undeserved and unwarranted partial refund to stop harassing me and
leave me the fuck alone, I'll send him $5 right now.
Otherwise the options are send it back for a full refund or keep it.
That was a week ago, have not heard anything back.
And I think the guy is probably just like, Oh, I guess I just got to keep the
exact item I bought that was sent to me and the exact condition it was promised
after taking a week of my life up dealing with this shit.
Yeah, that sucks.
That sucks.
I hate it.
They treat you because you sell shit on Amazon that you're supposed to be like
best buy and dealing with these people.
And I'm like, no, if you're going to talk to me like that enough, I don't
know why you put yourself through it, but I also don't know why, if you're
going to put yourself through it, why are you doing it on Amazon?
You'd be much better off, you know, there's there because, because anybody
buying from Amazon is going to think that they do deserve that full corporate
protection, whereas, you know, if you do it as an individual seller on eBay, I
think there's a little more breathing room there for, you know, I'm buying
from a human being on eBay.
That's my issue.
Nobody really, I buy shit all the time on eBay.
In fact, I buy it on eBay instead of Amazon because Amazon, like the out of
print stuff on Amazon is always way overpriced.
So I go to eBay.
Yeah.
eBay, but I mean, eBay, you're good.
Well, I think it's like your average person Googles, I want to buy Tron
or get on Amazon and types in Tron.
If they don't have it, they buy a used version of it.
So I'm making 10 sales a week.
And whenever I try to sell anything on eBay, it goes the whole time.
And then doesn't sell.
Okay.
All right.
Also, they charge fees for listing.
Amazon only takes fees if they sell, they take a big fucking fee, but
it just sounds like such a goddamn headache.
This, this one was losing.
I was losing my mind for sure.
Yeah.
Every morning I would wake up to like new emails.
He's also one of these guys where, you know, he's like wasted.
Every email came in at like 4 0 9 AM.
It's like, I'm not dealing with you anymore.
But you have to, if you don't respond to somebody's message within 24 hours, you
get like two of those and your account is done at Amazon.
You have to respond.
Sure.
Anyway.
Now, what name would you have called this man?
I know the name I would have called him, but
his name was Nicky.
I'm going to call him Pricky.
All right.
Fair enough.
Uh, the, uh, I, uh, I thought I had
something else to tell you.
I, it's, well, no, I did.
I remember what it was now.
It's gets, uh, I'm not embarrassed to say it's good to see you.
We didn't record really in August.
We, we kind of batch recorded all at once, which we never do.
And, uh, this month we're back to more of our regular thing.
And, um, I just haven't seen you.
We've texted here or there out of each other's lives for about a month.
Yes.
And it felt a little odd to me.
If I'm being just right to me.
Felt just, just, I knew you were going to do that.
I knew you'd do that.
You don't know how to say, I love you.
I get it.
Joe, the other day you said you want to record and I said, just then, yeah,
I'm actually looking forward to it.
It's been a while.
I said, I said it then myself.
I, you said that I didn't say that.
Oh, I didn't say maybe I did.
I said, I said, I said I'm okay.
I thought I might've been in a drunken stoop or somewhere, you know,
Googling what the word escrow means.
I, uh, Joe, at one point, and I know he didn't want me to share this with
everybody, but he texted me, what is a house?
And I knew that he was a little out of his league with this purchase, but.
Now you just walk up to a door and ask to buy it, right?
Is it like a trick or treat scenario?
These are all for sale.
That's great.
Um, yeah.
Anyway, I, uh, I, when I saw Barbie, I saw for the first time the full
trailer for Wonka and my God, I mean, I was actually, so I liked the
Paddington pictures.
I think the people who are obsessed with Paddington are sad and pathetic
and probably closet furries.
But I think he was a good director.
He's kind of like the poor man's Wes Anderson and he'd be great
for the world of Willy Wonka.
Saw this trailer.
It didn't seem to have any of that visual flair.
Um, it seems to be a two person cast.
One Keegan, Michael Key, maybe playing a variety of roles.
I couldn't tell he's in a fat suit at one point.
I haven't seen the full, I assume I haven't seen the trailer.
My assumption of that is he's in a fat blueberry.
Yeah.
He's like testing the candies or whatever.
Um, but Keegan is heavily featured in the trailer.
And then the only other actor that seems to have a part is Wonka
himself, Tim Chalamet, who was playing one of the great eccentric characters
in the history of both literature and film.
And he is playing it how he has played every other role.
Just like a teenage dork who everybody thinks is hot for some reason.
He's doing nothing with the character.
No spin on it.
He's just Tim Chalamet as Bill Wonka, the guy growing up.
It's like a prequel, but we haven't seen Timmy play anything
but a pouting brooding team.
Like that's all he's played in every fucking movie seems to be doing here.
No, no one wants that from Willy Wonka.
So maybe he ain't so good.
I don't know.
You know, he's, I mean, he's clearly a very, very limited actor, but like,
you know, you don't go from Gene Wilder to Tim Chalamet in any way, in any
capacity, you can't make that transition.
It doesn't make any sense.
You know, I know like a feral or somebody is too old for it.
But that's the more of the world you should be looking at.
What about a Sam Rockwell or something, an eccentric, a weirdo.
I love Rockwell.
That'd be, that's not, I don't agree with that casting, but I, I look,
Depp was great casting.
I just don't like what Burton let him do with it.
Yeah.
He played like Michael Jackson.
I actually forgot that existed until you said that just now.
Depp could have been great cast.
By the way, classic, classic, classic, classic Hollywood.
I love watching this machine just keep a rolling, doing the same, committing
the same offenses over it, like they just won't let go of their precious
sacred fucking whiteness, uh, as they, as they stand out there and scream
diversity and doing the right thing and blah, blah, fucking blah.
I love that they want, they needed to do Oompa Loompas.
So they took old Hugh Grant and shrunk them on down, uh, and, and deprived
and deprived actual little people of the parts because they said, well, if we do
that, then we have to worry about treating them properly.
Wouldn't it be easier just to get a regular size man and shrink him down?
And then we can do whatever the fuck we want.
Trust me, that is the motivation.
That is a hundred percent the motivation.
Yeah.
Well, see the other one was deep Roy and the other Willy Wonka and he
played all the Oompa Loompas, but he was a little person and that movie came out.
20 years ago.
It's very odd.
Uh, and also the Oompa Loompas in general are controversial because in
the book they're essentially slaves.
They're, they're black pygmies who are bought from Africa, you know, like it's
the role doll has a lot of things lately that are controversial.
I actually saw Wes Anderson speak with passion for the first time ever, because
they were asking him if he approves of people making edits to his books and he
was very adamant about him being against that.
Um, but yeah, Dowell was a controversial figure, you know, but it's like in
trying to do these Oompa Loompa things, right?
There's always a weirdness about it.
And Hugh Grant, as, as he, all of them, or is he the main Oompa Loompa or what?
I'm sure he's all of them.
They're clearly trying to draw a visual connection to the wilder one.
Cause Hugh Grant is done up exactly like the Oompa Loompas in that movie.
Exactly.
They're going to do the classic thing they do where they're going to go, now
we're going to make a prequel to this thing that was made in the seventies and
is cherished and beloved, uh, and we're going to do a prequel that is so big and
so insane and so vast that when you watch it as a prequel, it's not going to
make any fucking sense in relation to the original.
Yeah.
It's just another thing that doesn't need to be done.
It's another example of how Hollywood won't put their money where their mouth
is, they'll sit there and say, we should be ashamed of, of certain things and
that road doll included in his books.
But instead of taking an actual stance, which I wouldn't agree with of, of not
work utilizing the guy's work, people are complicated.
People make mistakes.
People have problematic viewpoints.
We all do.
Uh, but instead of just taking an actual stance, which would be not utilizing the,
the, the work instead, no, we want our cake and eat it too.
So we'll try to get people to edit the books so we can keep pumping out these
fucking garbage movies.
Right.
That's the only reason they're editing those fucking books is so they can,
because the studios have a stranglehold and everything, and they want to
make these movies, I promise you it's directly connected and it's, it's just
gross by the way, yeah, keep editing books because God forbid any of you
teach your kids anything fucking absentee parents, what a bunch of wastes
everybody is God almighty.
Whew.
You said to me once, and I know you didn't mean all, all the elements of it.
Yeah.
But I got overall what you meant.
You, you texted me once.
You said, just had one of those very troubling viewings of taxi driver where
you sit there going exactly.
I'd be like, yes, yes, Travis.
That's where I'm at.
Where is this big rain?
Where is it?
Come on.
I like, I wanted to get biblical, like send this flood.
Christ man.
Yeah.
Everybody is such a fucking half ass waste.
So exhausted with it.
Yeah.
I find myself parked across from pimps down at skim row all the time, watching
them their day to day operations.
Um, anyway, why don't you take us to that movie corner?
Let's perk things up.
Oh wait, I got a scary stuff.
Sure.
Sorry.
Uh, I got a nice scary stuff here.
Uh, I bought, uh, swamp thing, uh, and return of something.
Never seen either.
I I'm a big fan of both.
I actually do.
I, this is sacrilege.
West Craven did swamp thing.
I kind of like return of swamp thing better.
It's it's self -effacing.
It's tongue in cheek.
It has a lot of fun with it.
Not to the extent that like gremlins too does with gremlins, but it's, it's a fun
sequel and it's still Dick Durak, a swamp thing.
Um, uh, what's his name?
Uh, oh gosh, Luis Jordan as a arcane, uh, Adrian Barbeau does not come back in the
sequel, but Heather Locklear plays the female lead in the sequel, uh, Abby arcane.
Uh, anyway, uh, I got the four Ks.
These were put out.
I bought these in Austin.
Uh, shout outs to Waterloo records.
Uh, these were put out by a company.
Well, Christ, not even the same company.
The first one I got is by MVD rewind.
Okay.
Uh, I don't know who the, who that is, but they did a really nice job with it.
Transfer looks really nice.
And this, this version finally has the unrated international cut, uh, which
is also restored to four K.
Uh, a lot of, a lot of tit in that uncut version, a lot of tit, including full
boob shots of Adrian Barbeau, uh, which was wild cause I'd never seen the uncut.
So I was watching it and all of a sudden all these boobs are flying around.
I was like, what the fuck?
I thought this movie was PG.
And I was like, oh, I guess this is the uncut and it's weird.
Barbeau was married to Carpenter.
You know that John Carpenter.
Yeah.
Well, she says in the special feature, she's like, I didn't really know Wes very
well, uh, I hated horror movies.
I'm not, I'm still not a fan.
She goes, not cause I don't respect them.
I, they scare me.
She said, but when I got the offer for this, my husband at the time, John
Carpenter was like, you have to work with Wes Craven.
Um, it's weird though, cause the uncut version, aside from the boobs, there's
nothing really are rated about it.
Like I think their boobs.
No, the, that's the first version.
Barbeau.
Okay.
Um, the, but it's weird.
Cause it's like Craven, you just put a lot of boobs in it.
Why?
And I feel like the studio was like, what are you the eighties, baby?
Yeah.
But there's like, there's no, nobody curses.
Nobody says fuck.
There's no gratuitous violence.
I feel like the studio was like, why'd you put all these tits in this?
Just cut that out.
It's a PG movie for God's sake.
They don't need, it doesn't make sense.
Were the comic books heavy with nudity?
No, no, it was very odd choice.
Uh, anyway, and then return to swamp thing was put up by light year.
Again, a company I'm unfamiliar with, but did a really nice job.
This was directed by Jim Wiernowski, who is a B movie director who directed
movies such as the witches of breast wick.
Uh, the Blair boobs project, like shit like that, like, you know, but.
He'll be hearing from a lawyer.
I did a student film in college with a group called the Nair bitch project.
Okay.
How'd that go?
It was awful.
Yeah.
I imagine that it was when I realized I don't want to do group projects.
Cause I kept saying like, this sucks guys.
No, well, that's not really great input.
So it was near bitch, meaning like Nair, like the hair removal.
Right.
It said, no, I get it.
Yeah, I got the, I got it.
You didn't have to explain.
Uh, I liked the second one too.
Cause it not only has arcane, but as Abby arcane.
And then it also, I'm a fan of the comics.
It also has the unmen, which are like the mutated monsters that arcane makes.
Uh, anyway, both are the first one is a pretty somber flick, but
it's very good, I think.
Uh, and the second one is, is a lot of fun.
Uh, they're both great watches in my opinion.
I'm happy to own these four K's check them out.
I also bought the complete DC series of Swamp Thing.
I'm trying to find the TV series that star Dick Duroc from the nineties.
If anybody out there has it or knows where to get it, I'm having a hard
time finding it complete anywhere.
Um, and, uh, and I'm about to buy the box set of all the Alan Moore comics again.
I had them and I sold them.
I don't know why I did that, but I'm on a real Swamp Thing kick.
Um, I'm unfamiliar.
I'm going to check them out.
I, Joe will probably do talk to me.
Don't you think?
Yeah.
If I ever see it, I saw it last night.
All right.
I'll hold off.
Uh, yeah, I would say hold off.
Okay.
Let me kick off that movie corner.
I think you'll like talk to me.
With, um, foreign away, not that there's any competition, the funniest movie of
the year, um, which is kind of, we're in September here.
I mean, it's kind of saying something.
Um, but it is called bottoms.
It is directed by Emma Silligman who did Shiva baby, which is another excellent,
excellent low budget indie comedy that I loved a great kind of anxiety comedy
starring Rachel Sinatra.
Oh, Rachel Senate.
I'm not sure I've heard both.
Um, used to follow me on Twitter.
I'm a big fan.
I find her to be extremely funny.
Um, I like her dark, weird sense of humor.
I like her vibe.
I don't, um, know too much about her beyond that.
IO at a Barry from the bear plays her best friend.
And basically they are two teenage lesbians in high school who want to lose
their virginities to cheerleaders, kind of your classic American pie type plot.
In order to get there, they form a fight club, a female fight club, kind of training
women for self -defense.
Um, but in a very unexpected tone to this movie, there is like, it's actually sort
of in a, in a same way as theater camp, which came out a month ago, which I also
loved, it seems really inspired by wet out American summer, um, because it works
as both what it is and also as a complete satire of those things.
It also seems weirdly inspired by not another teen movie, which is an extremely
funny parody that not enough people have seen.
It's a really great spoof movie that came out in the late nineties, but, um,
bottoms is dirty.
It's very, very violent, which I don't think anybody in the theater was expecting.
And it's got an insane surreal tone to it.
Like there are jokes that are, that are out of the naked gun next to like really
savage, smart, satirical jokes about sexual assault and what women have to go
through and et cetera, et cetera.
Um, I totally loved it.
I thought it was a much more successful feminist statement than the movie we're
discussing this week on the show, um, because it remembered to be entertaining
and really, really funny and all kinds of other stuff, in addition to the
message that it's trying to get across.
I love bottoms thought it was great.
And I think now with Shiva baby, it was sort of like the clerks into mall rats,
the very similar vibe as the baby, but blown up and made sort of a big broad
comedy.
Uh, I love these two.
I'm very excited to see what they do next.
Big fan.
Great.
Uh, let's see here.
I'm stuck on which I want to pursue for my movie corner this week, but I think
I'm going to do, I got to talk about this.
I watched, I re all right.
I watched, uh, a movie called and so it goes.
Rob Reiner directed Diane Keaton stars, uh, completely unfamiliar with this
movie.
Michael Douglas is the male lead in this.
I only watched it because I had rewatched something's got to give.
Yeah.
So I'll, I'll circle back to, and so it goes after you do your next one, but I'll
do something's got to give now something's got to give.
I got a lot to say about it.
So it goes, something's got to give though.
Just a delightful rewatch.
Yeah.
I love the movie.
Uh, I've been a real Nora Efron kick lately.
I thought she was behind something's got to give.
I was wrong.
It's Nancy Myers, but that's what made me, that's what led me to rewatching it is
I can't stop reading and listening to Nora Efron at the moment.
I'm obsessed with Nora Efron and I'm very sad that she's dead because she is
somebody that I desperately want to meet and talk to.
Um, but she's wonderful.
I was trying to find other stuff of hers.
I hadn't seen in a while or seen at all.
And for some reason, something's got to give came up incorrectly.
And I was like, Oh, I haven't seen that.
I love that movie.
Rewatched it.
Loved it every bit as much, regardless of her not being involved.
Nancy Myers is wonderful too.
Um, uh, it's just a great romantic comedy.
Um, it's, you know, it's a little through the lens of, of yesteryear.
It's a very male gaze, uh, romantic comedy, but it's delightful.
It's Keaton at her best.
What do you mean?
Like a lot of shots of like Diane Keaton in a bikini or what are you talking about?
I don't know the last time you saw it, but it's very much like, like you're
supposed to like, you know, she's got her massive reservations about Jack
Nicholson and with good reason because he's this playboy that fucks young
women all the time and like, it's a lot of him being like, just relax, honey.
I'm not asking you to get married.
You know what I mean?
Like it's a lot of like head padding from the male character.
Now granted in the end, he goes on this journey to find out if he's a decent
man and he finds out all these women from his past hate his guts, but even
in that, when he ends up seemingly alone at the end, before you know that they're
going to end up together and he's crying, you are supposed to feel sorry for it.
So it's very much from the male perspective.
Listen, I love the movie.
I'm not knocking it.
It's Keaton.
It's my favorite kind of Keaton when she's endearing and sweet and flighty.
And she's very, very funny in it.
The sequence when he, she sees him out with the other woman and she's
heartbroken and she's crying constantly.
And it's just the montage of her crying.
And one of the shots is her waking up first thing in the morning.
And she immediately starts crying.
Like that sequence is so funny.
Um, and he's awesome in it.
It's great Nicholson.
It's like that great classic, like charming, you know, it's one of those
Nicholson movies where you're like, I wish Jack Nicholson was like my uncle,
you know, like he's like the cool uncle that you want, um, Keanu Reeves, lovely.
Francis McDormand, very funny in it.
Um, there's a really funny scene where Francis McDormand,
McDormand takes Jack Nicholson to task.
She's like a, she's a professor of feminist studies.
When she tells Jack Nicholson that he's like, ah, and she takes him to task at
dinner and goes way too hard and then it cuts to Diane Keaton being like, are
you insane, what is wrong with you?
So it does, it does very, in a very funny way, take a very balanced, uh, uh,
to an extent, a balanced approach to the sexes and all that stuff.
Uh, and it's just a funny movie, you know, it's, it's a great movie
to watch with your folks.
Yes, Diane Keaton, full frontal nudity in it.
She looks great.
Uh, I wasn't mad at that.
Um, it's a wonderful little flick.
If you haven't seen it, it's definitely one that, you know, a lot of people
glaze over, especially since Nancy Myers, I believe followed it with it's
complicated, which is not a great movie.
I really like it's complicated.
I liked it when I first saw it.
And then I watched you and Martin.
Yeah.
I, I liked it when I saw the theater and then I saw Eugene Merman make fun of it
so bad on stage that it ruined it.
And I was like, I guess I don't like that movie anymore.
Maybe I got to go back to that one for me.
It was just, just watching those three go out.
It was fun.
So anyway, something's got to give, which will bring me to.
And so it goes, but go ahead.
All right.
I saw a strays, um, strays sucked.
It is, see, again, we talk all this time about where, what happened to comedy,
what happened to the R rated comedy, but sometimes what, what comes out is not
what you're looking for, unfortunately.
Uh, this was directed by Josh Greenbaum who did the very funny Barb and star go
to Vista Del Mar, which I remember as being like that, that almost feels like
the height of the pandemic when that movie came out, um, strays is nowhere
near that good, that creative, that funny, it is just simply dogs voiced by
actors, uh, Will Ferrell, Jamie Foxx, Randall Park, Isla Fisher, and they
travel across the country at the opening scenes are Will Forte is the owner
of the Will Ferrell dog.
Will Ferrell playing the straight man in the movie, very weird choice.
Um, but Forte plays an alcoholic, abusive owner who's always yelling
like, fuck you dog.
And, you know, being really abusive.
Is he funny?
He's playing it pretty broad.
I didn't laugh.
No, he's, he's almost too mean to be funny because he's being
mean to a cute little dog.
Um, so the dog escapes.
Then when he reunites with these other dogs, they're like, no, your owner's
an asshole, your owner's not a good person.
And that he finally explained to him that you were being abused as a dog,
even though all dogs love their owners.
And when he realizes that he's been abused, then the entire movie's plot is
that they're going to go find Will Forte and bite his dick off.
That is the entire premise of the film.
Okay.
Um, that scene actually, where they go and bite his dick off is the
funniest scene in the movie.
So it does build to something kind of funny.
However, the rest of it.
Look, you know, I love a dick joke, a ball joke, a cum joke, whatever.
There are thousands of them.
It's like, they say it's the kind of comedy where they say dick four
times in like a discussion.
And you're like, guys, say cock, sprinkle something else.
Like we're tired of this.
Like they weren't getting laughs because there's no power to shock when it's
just a dog saying dick a thousand times.
Um, it's a lot of humping reveals.
Wait, where's Trixie?
Oh, they look over Trixie's being humped by, you know, a bigger dog.
It's just every obvious thing.
Do the dogs stumble upon a mushroom patch?
You better believe it.
You know, it's so it's just following all the beats of like the, you know,
the Rogan type movies, but with dogs.
And I don't think that was necessarily a terrible idea.
I just don't think it's, it's funny enough or smart enough or
clever enough, unfortunately.
Will Ferrell, uh, you know, I was always a big fan and I still respect the man
greatly for all he's done, but my God, it's like, he, he is, I'm sorry.
He's like comedy fucking kryptonite anymore, man.
Like, I don't understand.
He's not capable of being funny anymore.
Like he's not funny in Barbie and they, and they give them funny and Barbie,
they give them nothing funny to do.
The one part in Barbie where he makes me laugh is when he goes, yes, what are
your dreams, my child or whatever.
He does that thing.
He says that line at the end.
That's very much like a Ron Burgundy kind of line.
And I'm like, that's literally the only Will Ferrell laugh.
And it's like, because you have him playing a dick who's not funny, but then
he's also on top of it, just not funny.
Like, I don't know what's going on, man.
Like it's weird.
But anyway, I thought, well, is he just getting older or something?
But like his personality getting older should just make him
funnier and funnier really.
Well, my guess is he's lost his confidence, you know, like he was
the biggest comedy star and what you're saying about him is what
everybody's saying about him.
What happened to him?
Why isn't he funny?
Why does he make such bad movies?
And there's only so many poorly received moves you can do before you just stop
believing in your bag of tricks.
I'll inject a quick one then before.
And so it goes, I rewatch semi -pro semi -pro when it came out in comparison
to what else the other things Will Ferrell was doing at the time was
considered it was a flop.
It didn't, wasn't well received critically.
I remember seeing it in theater and being like, yeah, there's a
couple of funny parts, but whatever.
I rewatched this thing the other night.
I was laughing from start to finish.
I'm like, this thing is a, is an 11 on a one to scale 10 compared to any modern
comedy, especially the ones that Will Ferrell's doing.
And I was like, yeah, this is like why this guy was funny.
Right.
Like, and, and the setups in it are funny.
Like, like the, the, well, you know why?
Because it's from that period where irony was still a thing.
That that's it.
Like, you know, we'll, we'll our nets in it playing a complete dick.
You know, there's that great scene where they're all talking about how
they fucked Andy Daly's wife.
Uh -huh.
You know, I don't remember the movie, but yeah, they're all playing poker and
making jokes that they fucked Andy Daly's wife and they're all laughing really hard.
And then I think Andy Daly, it's like Andy Daly, Tim Meadows.
We learned that it's a bunch of guys.
Uh, uh, Andy Richter's in it and, uh, Andy Daly goes, you know, we're saying
things that are funny because they're not true.
It's meanwhile, you know, it's absolutely true.
They've all got this life.
Yeah.
Woody Harrelson's in it.
Woody Harrelson's awesome in it.
Uh, Laura, uh, uh, Tierney, uh, or Mara Tierney, excuse me.
It's a great cast and everybody hits a home run.
Rob Quarterly's in it.
that I was talking with friends about this the other night.
There was not a comedy made for about a seven year period that did not have
Rob Quarterly as a funny, douchey friend.
Yeah.
It was in everything.
I just rewatched the heartbreak kid with Ben Stiller, the remake.
And he's in it for no reason.
Like he doesn't even need a friend in the movie.
He's, he's like barely in it, but it's like they, they, whenever they're
like the hero needs a friend, they go with Cordray and I do not know why.
He's not like a electric performer or something.
The, uh, yeah, there's a great scene in, uh, my favorite scene in semi -pro
is he, uh, Matt Walsh plays a priest who coaches all the games.
Yeah.
And he calls a foul on Will Ferrell and Will Ferrell goes, suck my cock.
I'll kill your family.
And, uh, Matt Walsh blows the whistle and he goes, you're out of here, Jackie.
And, and Will Ferrell immediately goes, what, what did I say?
What did I say?
I didn't do anything.
And Matt Walsh keeps yelling, you said S my C Jackie, you said S my C.
It's just really fucked the funny man.
Yeah.
Uh, God damn it.
We used to get comedies like this and you knew that these guys were idiots
and assholes and that was the joke.
That was the joke.
Anyway, go ahead.
Uh, um, I saw a very interesting movie that I have long wanted to see and
heard about, but did not ever watch called the tribe and the tribe is
streaming on a variety of services.
You can find it pretty easily.
It was a very controversial movie.
It came out in 2014.
It's directed by one of your favorite directors, Joe Mira Slav, Slavush Pitsky.
You always sort of, you know, recommended his stuff to me.
Mira Slav, Slavush Pitsky.
Um, I don't think Joe's listening to me.
I am the tribe.
Well, you didn't listen to my swamp, my swamp thing.
You, you, you were, you were, I said the sentence, I said,
Adrienne Barbeau, frontal nudity.
And then you, I go, so there's a lot of nudity.
You go Locklear, no, no, no, no.
That was a follow -up question.
I'm thrilled that there's Barbeau nudity, but now I would like to know.
Does Locklear get any, you don't get any Locklear.
I'm sorry.
I was, I was like, sounds like a slang term for ass.
Let's go get some Locklear tonight.
Boys.
I'm, I'm listening to you.
The tribe is a pretty nuts movie.
It is Russian.
It is set at a boarding school for the deaf and dumb.
And there is no, so everyone, every character is signing and
there are no subtitles.
So for this 130 minute movie, you're just watching people sign and having to
guess at what they're saying and you're not reading lips.
It's just simply, you don't know what's happening.
Um, that is annoying.
Okay.
It is bothersome.
However, at a certain point you're like, Oh, this is what it feels like to be
deaf.
That's the kind of interesting hook of the movie.
Then the movie starts going in real weird places, sort of a Lord of the
flies type vibe where these deaf and dumb kids are revealed to have like
a sick cult at the school and the new deaf kid who you go in to the movie
with his first day at school gets swept up in this group.
And this group is like violent.
They sell drugs.
They force other girls into prostitution.
So it's really depraved and disturbing.
There are scenes of assault.
Um, so trigger warnings for that.
There is unbelievably graphic sex between these deaf kids who do not
necessarily look of age.
So I get why the movie was controversial.
Um, it's certainly disturbing, but sort of the beauty of it is you're in this
like really intense thriller and you, you know, what's an ideal thriller, one
where you don't really know what's happening.
You're, you're, you're left in the dark a little bit.
So the fact that you don't even know what people are saying, it really does
add kind of a cool, exciting layer of suspense and what the fuck is going on.
And blah, blah, blah, not a perfect movie by any means.
Um, you're going to be left with a lot of questions like, well, why are all
of these deaf and dumb kids so evil?
And you don't really get an answer, but I think it's kind of that Lord of the
flies answer of, you know, people are very impressionable when they're young.
And if somebody's like, Hey, this is what we do here.
We prostitute and do drugs and beat the shit out of people.
Um, you might to fit in, go ahead and do that.
So it's a very dark movie, but pretty cool.
If that sounds like an experience you would enjoy having check it out.
All right, finally.
And so it goes, this is what I was going to say about it.
And so it goes, now I watched this because something he's got to
give delighted me so much.
I said, I need more Keaton.
This happened to me last time.
I watched a goddamn dying Keaton movie.
I watched family stone was so delighted.
Had to then watch the big wedding.
Disasterous.
I watched Keaton, Keaton's she's not Bruce Willis, but she's making two or
three movies a year that nobody really knows about buddy.
I think she's surpassed anybody in this department.
Yeah.
What I'm getting to this thing is a, is a, is supposedly a romantic comedy
with her and Michael Douglas.
The thing is it also Rob Reiner in his own movie, uh, in a, in a, I guess,
comedic role supposed to be funny.
There's a scene, one of Rob Reiner's big jokes in the movie is he's sort of a
doofus and he walks to pick Diane Keaton up for a date and there's a slip and
slide and the button of the scene is literally Rob Reiner walking onto the
slip and slide and him going, whoa, and falling down and that's, I mean, this
is the level of humor in this fucking thing.
These types of gags are butted up against the storyline of Diane Keaton
being a struggling singer.
There's something she's never done in eight other fucking movies.
Uh, and Michael Keaton being an old curmudgeon who is the landlord and
next door neighbor to her in this apartment building she lives in seems
like the scene is set for a fairly innocent romp.
Yeah.
However, the primary storyline of this movie, all of this is secondary to the
primary storyline, which is Michael Keaton's drug addict son has to go to
jail and Michael Keaton, who is a widow or widower has to take care of his
granddaughter that he's estranged from, uh, while he tries to sell the mansion
estate he and his wife lived in for $8 .5 million, no part of this movie is
relatable in any way, shape or form, minus a guy taking custody of his
deadbeat son's kid.
Yeah.
It's way too dark.
It's way too zany.
And then the parts in between where you're just supposed to be sort of
delighted, I mean, there's a scene in this thing where, you know, it'll be
like a, uh, it's supposed to be like a funny romantic encounter with Keaton
and Douglas and then, and then the next scene is like him taking his granddaughter
to meet her mom and the mom is a junkie with scabs on her arms and she's falling
over cause she's high.
I mean, this fucking thing is such a goddamn mess and here's what I'm getting
at. It's a terrible, terrible, terrible movie.
Here's what I'm getting written by.
I'm looking it up cause I was not familiar with it written by Mark
Andrus, the Academy Award nominated screenwriter of as good as it gets.
This, it tries to do what as good as it gets does.
And it fails completely.
Now this maybe was a better movie before editing.
I don't know.
Maybe this isn't what they shot.
But it will lead me to the major point I have here.
Has there ever been a greater fall off from Hollywood royalty in quality than
what Diane Keaton and Rob Reiner are doing?
I mean, Jesus Christ, man, Rob Reiner is responsible for four, maybe five of some
of the all time top 100 in the last 40 years movies that have come out in
mainstream in the mainstream sense.
This fucking guy, I looked it up on IMDb, dude, he hasn't had a commercial or
financial hit in like eight movies.
Yeah.
They just keep letting him do shit.
I don't understand why.
And then the same thing with Keaton.
It's like, what the fuck is going on?
He did a movie about having a drug addicted son, like a little drama.
And I remember thinking like, oh wow, he's like at an indie level of movies,
but he must have a, I think he has a son with drug problems is why
that kept seeping into his movies.
And maybe that's what made him not be as great anymore.
I don't know.
Because he, if you look at the first half of his career, you read that
list of movies and then you just start going down from there.
It's, it's tough.
It's a huge drop off.
I'm just perplexed by the whole thing.
I'm just, I don't understand how he keeps to get what fucking Coppola
Coppola, the Godfather, Apocalypse Now, the outsiders, they gave that guy
like two moderate bombs and they were like, get the fuck out of here.
Like Rob Reiner, I think it's his politics.
I think it's because he's such like a mouthpiece for like the liberal
causes of Hollywood that he's like grand, like that's it.
He's in, he's grandfathered and he's protected.
He's allowed to just keep fucking up or people keep giving him money.
Because he gets behind these causes.
I don't understand how else it can be possible.
And he had a really tremendous amount of success.
I mean, even Coppola's big hits were always like Apocalypse Now nearly
bankrupted and destroyed a studio.
So like he just lost control of his budgets.
But the thing is everyone's like, Oh, it's a, we're going to, this
megapolis is going to be a return to form for Coppola.
Truth is his indie movies for the last 15, 20 years have been nearly
unwatchable.
They're not good.
No, they're not.
Spike Lee posted that he saw footage from it and he said it was unbelievable.
Yeah.
But who knows?
So, but, um, I'm excited to see it.
Of course.
I will not watch.
And so it goes.
Thank you, Joe.
Do not, uh, but let us, let us get to the movie at hand, the biggest
movie of the year, the highest grossing movie in the history of
Warner Brothers pictures, Warner Brothers, one of the oldest and biggest
studios, Barbie is their biggest film.
And that's what we're talking about today.
It was written by the great indie filmmaker, Noah Baumbach and his, uh,
partner in life and in writing lately, uh, Greta Gerwig Greta Gerwig directs.
And basically what this is, is a Roger Rabbit type movie where we have two
worlds, Barbie world and the real world.
The connection between the two is not made super clear, but you know, we sort
of get that that's a fantasy world and the, the people in the real world play
with Barbies and therefore it's, it's confusing.
I saw it a second time and I was confused.
And they make a couple of jokes again, that Will Ferrell scene.
They're like, is it like a magical world?
Or is, and then they're like, yeah.
You know, so they, they do that kind of thing where they acknowledge
that maybe it's not super clear.
But, um, didn't have to be unclear.
Didn't have to be unclear.
Could have been written.
Why don't you clear it up?
Take could have been, you know, you're getting to my first big gripe with the movie.
It's it's make the real world real and they don't, they make the real world as
absurd and fantastic as the Barbie world.
So now you're going, what the fuck is going on here?
I don't understand.
All this had to be was there's a Barbie world.
And when they go into the real world, it's kind of a extraordinary occurrence.
Like the Barbie, who knew folks, Barbie has the same plot as masters of the
universe starring Dolph Lundgren.
It starts in Atternia.
They go to the real world for the bulk of the movie, and then they go back
to Atternia for the big finale.
That's masters of the universe.
That's what happens in Barbie, except in masters of the universe, a terrible film.
They had the logic to go, well, it's not going to make any fucking sense when
He -Man goes to the real world.
So the people have to be surprised.
And in this, they go, another Barbie has escaped.
And you're like, wait, what?
Yeah.
What?
Oh my God, that could be catastrophic.
No, it's, it's clearly not catastrophic.
It doesn't, nothing happens because of it.
Yeah.
It's like the crocodile Dundee thing.
You know, they, they first get to the real world and they're dressed like Barbie.
So you got Gosling and Barbie dressed in like eighties biker gear.
The thing is all these people at the beach, they got teenage boys pointing at
Margot Robbie wearing a skin tight leotard and being like, look at this idiot.
Yeah.
You know, it's just right there.
It's like, guys, that is not how a teenage boy would react to the most
beautiful woman on earth wearing next to nothing skating by them, you know?
Um, there's nobody's that, that to me was the, the issue, the plot of the
movie is really hard to summarize.
When I went to Palm Springs with all my friends and their kids and their wives
and husbands, me and a few of the, the little boys went to Ninja Turtles.
And cause I had already seen Barbie and everybody else went to see Barbie.
It was, it was fun.
It was cool.
I liked it, but when they, it was more of an art piece.
Really?
It's like, it was about the, the drawing almost like, like a spider verse.
It was a very interesting style of animation and I liked it.
Old school hip hop soundtrack.
It was, it was fun.
Um, but I asked, you know, like you're sitting at a big table with all these
kids and it's a kick for me to be around kids.
I don't have my own and I never around them.
So I'm asking all these kids what they thought of Barbie.
No one, no one was even really able to answer what they thought of it.
And one of the Ninja Turtles kids was like, what's it even about?
One of the moms was starting to explain it and couldn't just like
give up.
It's like, it's not a clear movie.
Um, so it's very hard to be like, here's the plot of it.
What it is though, is almost a textbook on feminism for young girls.
And maybe I guess other people that don't know about feminism, but at some
point this movie becomes strictly a metaphor for a lot of things because
they also try to go into codependency.
They're like, Ken, you have to be your own man.
You can't just be, um, a guy who's, who's only a man when he's around
a woman and stuff like that.
So what people's complaining about it being too woke really.
That's not my complaint.
My complaint is that the movie is about wokeness in a way.
At the expense of story, character, everything else, it's like, it's all
message and not enough story, not enough juice, you know, uh, that was
what bothered me about it is that there's a million ideas, the production
design on the thing looks incredible.
It's a Barbie dream house brought to life.
I mean, that, that was really impressive at the end of it.
I don't know what to say about it.
It just kind of tried to do too much and didn't do it all well enough.
I think, uh, production design was fantastic.
The performances were fantastic.
Kate McKinnon, hilarious.
Ryan Gosling, hilarious.
Um, the jokes and the commentary through those jokes on gender and
society and sexism and that sort of thing were very funny.
My issues with the movie were two things.
Structurally, it was a fucking disaster.
I couldn't make sense of what was going on and I'm sorry.
It just takes me out of it.
It's why I go so hard on so many of the horror movies we review.
And I've said it before and I'll say it again.
There are, there have to be rules in your fantastic universe.
And if you don't establish them and follow them, it becomes a
bloated convoluted mess.
And that's what happened in this.
And I thought I'm getting really irritated at people saying it's not,
it's got nothing to do with woke.
There is no mess at bullshit.
The fucking message is as heavy handed as anything can be.
Okay.
Which is fine.
Oh yeah.
But if you're going to make, if you're going to design a message and explore
that message, at least make the message accurate to the world we live in.
I thought it really undercut itself.
I thought it did a great job of poking my reactionary self.
You know, I was watching it going, Oh, so the cans, cause they're men, they're
just objects and this and that.
Well, that's as fucked up as if a man did that to a woman.
They did a great job of leading me down the road to think that's where
they were going with it.
And then the Barbies learning, no, that's not the way either.
We were wrong to do it.
I was like, wow, they got me my hats off to them.
That's great.
But then they fucking undercut it with lines like, you know, maybe one day
when they're I'm paraphrasing, but maybe one day when, when the Supreme
Court in the real world has women, the, the Barbie one can have men.
It's like, guys, the Supreme Court is 45 % female.
You know, Bill Maher talked about, uh, the, the Mattel corporation.
He goes, the problem is the Mattel corporation, there are several women
that sit on that board of directors.
Like that was the only part I didn't like where it, but at the same time, I
okay, they're going to do the thing where, look, a friend of mine said, I
can't get too mad at an overcorrection after all the stuff I've seen that's
catered just to man in my life.
And I said, okay, that's a very, very fair point.
Yeah, that's a very fair point.
What bothers me though is when the overcorrection comes from a place as if
other corrections or overcorrections aren't already being made.
Now I get it.
Barbie can't exist in the light of everything else being made.
Movies take time.
Things take time.
They go through development.
There's a lot of cooks in that kitchen, blah, blah, blah.
But to me, this really took a stance and is being celebrated in certain
ways from a perspective as if we didn't just see a He -Man overhaul where
He -Man dies and, and, uh, uh, Teala, whoever becomes the main character and
focus of it, like that stuff is happening too, that these corrections and these
course corrections and overcorrections are happening all over the place.
So I think it undercuts the point and the message when you don't accurately
address things, uh, you know, I don't know, maybe I'm, maybe I'm putting
too fine a point on it, but that was my
issue with that.
There is that, uh, this Simu Liu or whatever it was like, well, maybe we
can get a guy on the Supreme court and, uh, Issa Rae is like, Oh no, no,
we're not going to be doing that.
Like, okay.
They do sometimes go for that kind of cheap little joke.
Um, how I felt, especially the first time watching it was bothered.
I hate being the enemy.
You know, the, the difference between how women were portrayed in movies is
that women weren't the enemy, you know, like I, they didn't make a lot of movies
where it was like, women are awful.
You know what I mean?
And this one really felt the first time I watched it, like the point of
the movie was men are awful.
Um, the second time I was able to get on its wavelength more, get what it's
doing more, be less defensive.
Um, and I did get much more out of it.
I do think it's a goddamn mess though.
I think if it had come out five years ago, its content in terms of its
feminism would have been super groundbreaking.
If they had made a Barbie movie when we were in high school, that movie would
have been Cameron Diaz in a skin tight bikini, you know, like fucking everybody.
So we've made a lot of progress and that's great, but it felt, uh, especially
like when America, Ferrarra has given this big, a woman has to be this.
Hey, that speech was done better and gone girl.
Um, the standing ovation it got the first time I saw it indicates to me
that, that, that speech really struck a chord with women and, and great.
But the movie itself, uh, is a mess.
It has an, it's narrated by Helen Mirren, but then there's
also a Rhea Perlman character.
Rhea Perlman is playing the head of, of Mattel, but she's also dead.
She's a ghost.
And, um, that man, like you gotta cut some of this out.
My, here's, here's what it is.
When I see these big movies there, I'm like, God, you're throwing in everything
but the kitchen sink and you're not doing anything right.
Like this is terrible.
Or you have no new ideas.
You're not even trying.
What I want to give Barbie a great deal of credit for is that
it is trying a lot of shit.
Greta Gerwig is clearly a very intelligent woman.
I love the movies of Noah Baumbach.
I loved Lady Bird and some of the stuff Greta Gerwig has done, Francis Ha.
But this is just simply a case of too much coming at me at once
and too much of it not working.
The stuff that works, works great.
The real Perlman as a ghost head of Mattel, that stuff doesn't work at
all.
I think I also didn't like Barbie.
The last line of the movie is Barbie, uh, going to the gynecologist.
Well, and I found that odd as well.
Well, that, I didn't think that was odd.
I think it's poor writing.
I think her, I think the notion of her becoming real and going to the
gynecologist is very interesting and unique.
And I think it's something that a lot of girls can relate to and women can
relate to.
I say girls, because I feel like there are girls coming of age as they see
this movie and going, Oh my God, I just had to do that for the first time.
That's probably a really special moment for a young woman or even older
woman to see on the screen.
I appreciate that.
There's, there's a, there's an emotion to that, that I really do appreciate
and think is wonderful.
Again, it's under, it's undercut with bad writing because when you make it so
the real world isn't that much less insane than the Barbie world, her
becoming a real person doesn't mean anything.
It doesn't mean anything.
You it's not Pinocchio.
Like there has to be a fucking sacrifice.
She has to be real.
What does that mean?
Well, it means she's just going to live over there and she can go back to the
Barbie world whenever she feels like it.
But also now the Barbie world is becoming like the real, it doesn't, I'm
just like, set up some goddamn rules, show me a journey of the character,
make it fun and funny.
They did that.
They did most of that.
Yeah.
Like when she, early on, when she's on the bench with the old woman and she's
like, you're beautiful and I love that your skin is old or whatever.
Um, there, there's a, there's a cleaner path through this material that would
have made this an absolutely brilliant movie on all, on all fronts.
Well, what it is, I think is about a half brilliant movie and a half mess.
Well, which is still better than most.
You know, I, I walked away the second time with a lot more respect for it.
And I got to admit what you're talking about them kind of pulling a
fast one on you and stuff.
I had that feeling a few times.
You know, I was like, boy, why really let this movie bother
me the first time I saw it.
And, um, and that made me kind of question myself a little bit too.
You know, it's, it is a super strong kind of in -your -face feminist movie.
I think it's a wonderful sort of first movie for little girls to see.
Absolutely.
I would be thrilled for my, my, you know, daughter to get that message
as opposed to whatever 1999s version of the Barbie movie would have been.
I agree with that.
I just think we had tightened it up a bit.
I thought it was a, I thought overall when I left, I was like, yeah, it was,
it was good.
It was fun.
I thought it undercut itself in areas, but I thought it was fun.
Uh, that's basically my takeaway.
Um, I think that Noah Baumbach and, uh, Greta Gerwig are both intelligent.
I'm not just going to single out Greta like Pat did, cause that's sexist.
Uh, the, I love Noah Baumbach.
No, I'm, uh, but I think that they're both very intelligent filmmakers
and both very intelligent writers.
And I say that as somebody who's not a big fan of, of all their work, I like
some of what they do, other stuff I don't care for.
Um, but that's what, that was the one hardship, heartache, uh, aspect I had
with this movie was that it is smart.
It's coming from smart people.
Some of the writing should have been smarter as I was in a writing, in a movie
that is smart enough as I'm sitting there.
And Margot Robbie is crying about how she's going to just have to be ordinary
and not beautiful and perfect.
And I'm going, Jesus Christ, guys, it's fucking Margot Robbie.
And then Helen Mirren in the voiceover goes, we realize this point being made
by Margot Robbie is not the best way to make it, but you get what we're trying to
say.
I was like, in a movie that is smart enough to do that, to recognize that
and call it out and be brilliant enough to do that, that movie is also smart
enough to write the line instead of Helen Mirren going, perhaps one day when
the real world, da, da, da, da, she, she, the line could have been, we realize
there are women on the Supreme court, but men will have to work their way up the
ladder in this world, just as women had to and still need to in the real.
It's such a slight change that to me completely reframes the point, the angle
and doesn't leave certain people in the audience going, wait, what?
And that's, that's my only criticism of the film, aside from the convolutedness
of the rules of it all is don't think just because you're making a message with
whatever your movie is that, Oh, deal with it.
It's just a message.
That's Michael Moore bullshit.
That's why nobody fucking takes Michael Moore seriously anymore.
Cause too many fucking times he came out and went, Oh, big deal.
Those facts were fudged.
Who cares?
Yeah.
You know, it's not, it's, it's come on.
Like let's, let's, let's rise to the occasion and be consistent and, and take
responsibility for the things that we're saying.
I get it.
It's been in balance for a long time.
I'm not saying it hasn't, but let's move forward.
It's also must just be so impossible to do a movie like this, where you're
tackling like big important issues that are in the zeitgeist when all sides
are going to be offended.
That's it.
That's why it's so crazy that this movie made so much money is because it is
really political and it's odd.
I'm sure people kind of got tricked by that probably why people are upset
about it's quote wokeness, but yeah, you know, I think, I think we're pretty
clear here, we it's got great things about it and it's got frustrating things
about it, but it's certainly a much more interesting take on Barbie than I
was expecting for sure.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
This, you know, funny enough, this movie is, is the modern version of Howard
Stern, half the people are watching it.
Uh, well, excuse me.
There is a portion of people that are watching it strictly for the gender
charge of it all that they want to relate to.
There are people that are watching it just because they think it's the greatest,
funniest thing that's ever existed.
And then there are people that hate it with all their might that are still
watching it for that reason.
So, uh, it's an interesting thing.
I agree with you.
The feet of it in and of itself is pretty spectacular.
I thought that myself, I also was excited for women seeing this movie
and knowing in the way, and look, I did not like the Ghostbusters reboot.
However, I was truly excited for women that they got something like that
because they don't get it very often.
Uh, or at least at that time it's happening more now.
Um, so I, I, I left Barbie with, with an excitement for, uh, the, the
audience it was really directed at.
And, uh, despite my gripes thought it was a solid movie and, and, and
had some really, really big laughs in it.
So I would say my hog is up for Barbie, uh, for the most part.
Uh, and my hog is going to be just pretty much straight forward.
Uh, but I enjoyed aspects of it for sure.
We will be back with a review of the new killer gnome home.
And I can call it a gnome invasion movie, uh, on shutter called Unwelcome.
Uh, plug wise, Joe and I have a show coming up, a live show in New York,
which is opening for a Joe's band salsa windfall.
If you have not checked out salsa windfall, uh, I absolutely love the album.
It's on Spotify.
I thought it was catchy as hell.
More books than a fish fish store.
Right.
Thank you.
I'm very flattered and touched that you enjoy the album.
You have great taste in music aside from your take on the new Queens
of the stone age album, and, uh, I appreciate that.
Tell us, tell us what the dates are on that event.
That's October 28th.
That's a big event.
It is called Festifol, uh, salsa windfall.
My band headlining at our first live show in 25 years.
Very excited about that.
Uh, also performing as Pat said, we'll see you in hell live.
Uh, we'll be doing a thing, our thing there.
We've got esoteric and seven L from czar face coming down to do a set.
That's going to be awesome.
Uh, we got the stumble bombs who are a lot of fun kicking things off.
And we've also got an 80s dance party happening after all the festivities.
All of it is happening at Arlene's grocery.
Uh, you can get tickets on my website, joderosa .com.
And then of course, we're going to have a big after party at my bar, Joey
roses, after all is said and done at Arlene's New York city, hell of a
Halloween weekend, uh, we're going to have a lot of fun, please come out for that.
Uh, I'm also on tour like crazy and I hope to see you.
I got dates, dates, dates.
Where are my dates?
Hold on a second.
Uh, Avenal, New Jersey on September 16th, Toronto, uh, Ontario, September 21st
to the 23rd, um, Philadelphia PA on November 11th, Pittsburgh PA, November
17th, Buffalo, New York, November 18th, Denver, Colorado, November 30th, Phoenix,
Arizona, December 1st, Salt Lake city, December 3rd, all of these shows I will
be doing my new hour, I never promised you a Rose garden, all of these venues
are very cool, independent, uh, awesome places.
I hope to see you tickets and show information available on my website,
joderosa .com and, uh, we'll see you next time and we'll see you in hell.