One more tie welcome
We'll see you in the podcast where we talk about movies and it's Christmas time
Hello everybody. How are you? I'm Joe to Rosa and I'm Patrick Walsh. It's great to see you
What's happening Joe since the last time we chatted? Well, we both pied backstay was I lying?
I was in there a long time all number one all number one. Yeah, there might be something wrong
I
Just had a lot of water. I got a lot of bathrooms back there. You know what it was
I just remembered that last night I drank so many things of water because I had the airplane
Year closing which I always get
And here I am with it still really 24 hours later
It never goes away from it and I'm flying on to New York
So I'll just for the next until next year. I will have like a clogged ear and you sitting on this side of me
Is no good eat a much like George Bailey, and it's a wonderful life
Excuse me the shopkeeper and it's a wonderful life who was deaf in one ear. No, no George Bailey is
Supposing it's lapsing on the other bad here. Yes. Sorry. Yes. Yes. Yeah, George Bailey because he saves his brother
Just won't get to it. Yeah, we'll get but
We are going you are coming to New York. I'm going back to New York because I live there
Yeah, you're coming up and we're gonna go see David Cromhol's our friend in
Leopold style, I think it's called it's called Leopold stat and he said that it is a long, extremely
serious and sad play about Judaism
And that's what Joe and I are doing baby
We're taking up New York. We have a 3 p .m. matinee on Sunday
To see that
We're gonna the Luppets aren't the only ones that can take Manhattan. Yeah
I have a face in the Muppets and us. Yes
I have a feeling we'll be drinking after that thing. Oh sure. Yeah sure
I'm excited. I'm seeing that I have two friends in Broadway plays, you know, it's pretty exciting
It also makes you feel like a loser else
Well, my friend and and boss on the miss patch show Jordan Cooper
Has written and is starring in a one -man show where he plays a drag queen
on Broadway and I'm excited to see it because he that's not his vibe at all at work
So I've never seen this side of him, but he's now is this the one man Christmas Carol that I'm hearing about?
No, he said I asked him what it's about and he goes it's a play about a government campaign
To give every black person in America a ticket back to Africa
So this is gonna be a wild weekend for me
A wild these shows I'm seeing like the both of them when they told me what the shows were about I was like okay
Thought it was gonna be like a musical or something, but all right
I would have liked it if it was a drag Christmas Carol called it's a Christmas Carol honey
I think well now it's Hany or Henty I believe what you want
It was Hany and now it's Henty I thought you were gonna say a Christmas Carol and like his name was Carl
But this Christmas he's becoming Carol
Yeah see this is it writes itself. Yeah
Well, I'll tell him when I see him hey
You're 27 and you have a one -man show on Broadway, but my buddy has some notes
Now he's in his late 40s not mid mid take it easy. I'm kidding. I'm kidding take it easy
But no, I'm excited to see it. It's a
And it is a comedy too, so I'm sure it's like a set. Yeah, it sounds very spherical. That sounds good
I think it's not a comedy from from what he said, but it's like when I was reading reviews of his show
It which one? Cremalt? Well, yeah, the Cremalt show he every review is like
important
This was really important. This was really an intense day of the theater. It's gonna be rough
I think but it'll be great. And then I just I
My buddy show I
I asked Horton is not a word I want you don't want to say
I was kidding. Yeah, but I asked I asked Miss Pat
What Jordan's show was like and she said to me she goes I love the show
But immediately she launched into a story about how some her words bitch
Behind her would not stop eating chips
She
She goes I got up and I said look bitch. I paid $200 for this ticket
You put the fucking chips in your purse and I was like I mean she went on and on and on and on and on and then at the end of it
I was like but I asked how the show was
It's very fun. It's a very a comedian thing to do you just get lost on a long rant. Yeah, yeah
She was so mad about this lady and I was like when did you see it last time? Tell me about it
I just did 22 minutes on clerks three. That's what I'm saying. Yeah, I know. That's what I'm saying
Yeah
Anyway, today we're gonna on Broadway
Yeah, that's like an old that's like a battle joke
Jehira I'm on Broadway
Right at the corner of 60 second yeah
Anyway off off off off Broadway. Yes
I were today. We're doing national ampune's Christmas vacation
And it's a wonderful life. We're doing extended reviews of both
Uh in order to get the Christmas quota in here
We were oh my god. We for oh no, we're also doing
We that that mean okay. Yeah, we still have sorry
I got confused for seconds. I was like that's all the episodes for this month. It's not also this month. We are doing
Silent night deadly night three and four and five and well we've done five. We'll talk about it a little bit
But make no mistake five will be discussed because I rewatched five will creep in
But that'll be its own episode too
What are the same franchise that yeah, I know let's don't don't spoil it
I'm not gonna spoil it, but that shit. Yeah, that shit yet
clerks three makes it look like you know, Amestad or something
You gotta let this go
And your love of Amestad is
Questionable as well right now the tattoo was a bit much
The Alestad tattoo. Yeah, and the guy tried to talk me out of the tramp stamp
But I said hey if you're gonna do it, let's do it. You are the only guy. I know with a jimon hansu tramp stand
Anyone had the new seven up with a twist of jimon
Jesus
You still act what was the one where he oh, it was quiet place two where they were like wait a minute
We don't have any black people in here. So they had jimon hansu academy award nominated actor
Enter and then immediately died. Yeah, immediately
Did the literal Eddie Murphy joke of like Star Trek the black guys first like the joke from 1983. Yeah, like they did it like in the time
It took for you to go. Oh wait, that's the guy from Amestad and in America like an arrow goes
Into his chest like okay
Are you excited for these quiet place spin -offs now that are coming? No
No, I'm not I don't remember anything about the second one
I thought the first one was awesome when I was high and then less awesome on a sober viewing
I'd look there's no better director in Hollywood than the office's John Krasinski don't get me wrong
Up there with Elizabeth Banks
Ah, we gotta get there cocaine bear cocaine bear looks pretty cool actually honestly that's gonna put banks on the map
Yeah, I I'm rooting for banks on that one. I'm ready for cocaine bear. It's the new snacks on a plane
I bet it'll be better than snacks on a plane. It looks looks cool. It looks fun
And I like that it's it looks like it's gonna balance
Horror or suspense whatever you want to call it with co -comedy. Oh, okay
Don't get me wrong. They ain't no way. I'm not seeing that all fucking tutored up
Let's hope this fentanyl thing dies out in time. Yeah
Can't trust it. Can't do cocaine anymore. Can't trust it. I have a cocaine bear as big gay guy that sells me pure cocaine
So that works out
There's no way that's not gonna be a porno. Oh for sure. There's no way that won't be uh, yeah, put it right on his snout
Um
I as he claws your trunk listen
folks
What is in our uh
Our movie corner with Joe and I were just noticing that they are doing a sequel to
A classic comedy election very excited about that came out in one of the great years for film 1999 the year
I graduated from high school
Don't know why I decided to share that with you, but um
It uh election. I love Reese Weatherspoon is amazing in it. Broderick's amazing in it. It's an Alexander Payne's a classic
It's the pain debut from that mistaken no pain debut was citizen Ruth with lord
Election was big. I remember it was an MTV films release and they had done like Joe's apartment the movie about the singing cockroaches
Now I was like oh, this will be good
And then I was like wow, this is very good. How did they make this amazing? We rented it
We I remember I was I think it was a freshman or I was a sophomore in college when it came out and we had an apartment
And we rented it because it was like the best thing available to rent and we were like same thing
We're kind of rolling our eyes like this is gonna suck
And because back then that's what you did you still rented a movie even if you thought it was gonna suck
I guess there was no that was like you didn't have many options
Anyway, so we put it on and I remember
I remember renting de Snyder's strange land
I have heard good the lead singer of twisted sister made a horror movie
And I rented it because there was nothing else to rent
But I remember about 20 minutes into election us being like holy shit
This is awesome. It's great movie like like and I remember the line like the first line that we were enjoying it
But the first line that got us was it her pussy gets so wet
That no that yeah, that's the moment when you go holy shit. This movie is gonna be awesome
Every watch selection like three months ago and when that creepy other teacher says her pussy gets so wet
I was like whoa it's still shocking. It's very shocking. There's one other thing about Tracy Fleck. You should know her pussy gets so wet
I also forgot that other teacher fucks her too. It's like really fucking dark movie. That's an amazing edit
But the the the the the
Remember the laugh getting me was Chris Klein when he goes
We say about dating that girl at school and he goes and after and after and after we had studied we go to her place for a fuck and a hot tub
And I really suck my penis, which I'm told is a good sign
Was his other one. Yeah, I was just like oh, and then when he breaks his legs skiing and he's going why me god
We're like this is really fucking funny
Matthew broader getting stung in the eye by the bee
It's just so good um him
Hovering over the bathtub washclothing down as genitals before he returns home to his wife
The oh that's a dark movie anyway to finish my sentence from seven minutes ago. They're making election
Two well, it's called Tracy Fleck can't win
It's based on a book that is that was released this year that was written by the same author
Tom parada
Yeah, and when I when I saw the headline I was like oh Christ and this is gonna and then I started reading
I was like wait, it's same author. He's producing. Oh, Alexander Payne's directing. Oh, he's writing again with the same guy
Oh Reese is coming. I'm excited about it. I'm excited too. It's going to pair my own plus. So I won't see it, but it looks sounds cool
Yeah, what's what's I got to tell you something
We're gonna we're gonna get paramount plus what am I gonna mortgage my home now to watch TV
By the way, I get fucking peacock because I for whatever sick reason
I've seen every episode of SNL since I was a little kid and I still watch it even though I've not smiled in 20 years watching it
But I go I guess I got to get peacock it used to be on Hulu. I got peacock too. My doctor says it'll go away in a few days
Anyway, folks
That's the one where it's multicolored right
but
peacock which I got SNL for it doesn't get SNL till noon Sunday
The peacock and then you watch it with commercials
I have
The worst streaming service of them all this will be unless they want to buy a project for me unless yeah
Yeah, this will be a little more inside, but you know, I'm a video game collector
I bought the new it I was one of the six people that bought the new Atari console the Atari VCS
The overpriced new Atari console Atari just released a new 50th anniversary collection
Which is available on every console except Atari's own console
And I emailed them yeah, and I'm sure you did
As one of these how well can you read this email to us?
It wasn't that bad exclamation points
This is what I said wasn't it to whom it made concern?
Yes, so was was the subject
So I'm sorry. Oh, I'll read you
This is gonna be rough. It's not that bad
All right ready. Yeah
Thank you for current take your time by the way. Well, hold on a second
It's I'm looking it up. Give me a second. You put me on the spot
Thank you doing great, sir
Oh my god if I had known I would never give me a second
Exactly, oh, I got a vamp over here. Oh vamp
Vamp blonde baby
Little horror comedy for you
I don't understand when I
Me what do you mean?
Here to that to vamp I'll read you a text from my friend Ian
How long before you and Joe are wobbly etching a thrice divorced septogenarian
Wait what it's a I'm vamping that's a text I just got I think people think of Tampa is like a godless place
It's godless. Is it godless?
How is it godless?
I mean, it seems I don't like god myself. He's cursed me many times over but
Scientology's big
Miami
Bienvenito amy amy from what I hear it's a party in the city where the heat is on
I
My amy's supposed to be what giant butts and fun, right?
Okay, I know cocaine and butts is what I know about my amy scar face
Yes, that's right
What's that? Have you found it? You know Google? No, I can't find it. It's not I'm searching it
It's not coming up for some reason then it's time to give up
It's time to give up and rejoin the body. Anyway, I wrote I wrote to them. I said look
As one of the people that supported this concept
console
I find it a little confusing
That your new release which I would like to own is only available on the consoles competing with the console
I bought that put out the collection itself
Shling he's typing on a typewriter
Yeah, and they wrote back and they said like that Kermit meme worries. Why am I obsessed with the muppets today? I don't know
They wrote back and they said we thank you for reaching out. Yes, we understand your frustration
How many times did you receive an email that said we understand your frustration?
We're delayed with the release of the Atari 50th anniversary collection for our own console
Please be patient. It will be coming soon. Which means it's never coming. No
So I asked for it for Christmas for my Nintendo Switch from my mom. Okay. I'll be getting that
Yeah, the godfather 4k collection good and the two books about canon films
I was as I was putting my 4k's into my collection of blu -rays swapping out. That's your this is your nickname for your balls
What your 4k's my 4k's you said I was putting my 4k's into my collection
Okay, yes, meaning your harem. I I call my balls 4k's because people love to look at them for sure
And yeah, love to look at them and yes
And the clarity on these balls right
I did trim up today because I'm traveling and you never know
You know
No, there's so few people here. I'm my proof
Speaking of my balls
I got to share this with you because I'm not I have just wait a second
You're putting your 4k's into what happened. Yeah, I was putting my I was replacing my blu -rays with 4k's selling stuff on Amazon
But this it was like a 12 -hour day of me listening to music and like rearranging my collection
Which to me is a very meditative meditative. Yeah, I agree. I like doing that
And I enjoy it, but at a certain point every time I'm doing it
I turn a corner where I feel
deeply ashamed and sick and by myself and my collection because you have so much
Because I'm collecting it because of my age and I'm still like pruning a collection of things. It's just
Sad. I did a secret. You're sad too. Yeah. No, I did a
I did a polyanna the other day on Bobby Kelly's podcast and I brought
What's that where you braid your hair into?
I don't know. I don't know what a polyanna is
It's like polyamory except with. Oh, okay. No. What is poly? A lot of people are poly on taking it
It's like you can have sex with multiple people
Like you're in an open relationship. You're in an open relationship. And then what is sapio -sexual? You're attracted to intelligence?
You're attracted to intelligence
Meaning even if the person's disgusting, but they're smart like you'd fuck all lines time
All right, the audacity of people
Well, I know. I know what see I have my own thing. I'm attracted to people that can speak
Oh good for you and then category all your fucking own pansexual. You're attracted to everyone
bisexual. You're attracted to just men and women
But pan adds in trans
And non -binary. Okay. All right. Just curious
non -binary
Don't don't do it. Whatever you don't do. I'm saying that doesn't
Up that would fall under bisexual, wouldn't it?
By if you if you if I was attracted to to people that present as men
Yeah, and you said to me well, I'm a woman even though I have a beard because that's how I identify
That what part of me would be like no, I'm not attracted to you anymore
I'd be like no, I'm still I'm physically still attracted to you
You present in a way that of something I'm attracted to than I think you're pansexual
It's just
sexual
It's just what you my friend said to me. What's the what's the term for where she goes?
She goes I have a I'm I forget the term she goes, but I'm the thing where
If I'm not attracted you at all physically
I can become attracted to you as I get to know you and when I and I go yeah
I have had that since birth. It's called I'll fuck anything
It's not special stop putting a title on everything because you like to fuck
That's all I'm saying yeah
Thank you
Um, I was gonna be in trouble. No, you're fine. You are fine
There were some moments there where I was concerned, but you pulled it off
Uh, I was dating this girl off tender. I've just put a pen in it in dating
If you like it then you better put a pen on it
Because of this but this girl I have been dating for a bit and she told me her last two
Her last boyfriend was pansexual or no poly sorry
Her last boyfriend was poly and she was like, but I wasn't so he like
Would go out and hook up with people, but I didn't and didn't feel comfortable with it
And then I just hated it and it gave me bad self esteem and I was like yeah, it sounds horrible
So we were talking about that and then she asked me a couple questions about my divorce
We and we we had been out like four or five times, but she hadn't asked about it
So she asked me and it was a pretty personal question
Now I was answering it
Generally people say don't talk about your exes on a date, but since she asked
And she goes oh
The second I finished saying one little personal piece of information. She goes I'm so glad you were so open about your divorce
Because now I can tell you something
Now I was like what's that?
She goes
Well, um, I am actually married myself
And I said well, I'm not you're not you're not meeting me there. I just told you I was divorced
She's like no, I'm I'm still married. She goes but that last relationship with the guy who was Polly was after
Polly that's what it is yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, I've only said it nine times
I don't just started paying attention. I don't listen
I'm here for the check shows over there going Kevin Smith clerks three
So she goes I'm actually married and I said what what do you mean? She goes well
Even my last year and a half relationship with the guy who was Polly I was married
She goes so it's not a big deal. I don't worry somebody's gonna like come after you and I'm like okay
She goes what happened was
About 10 years ago. I met this guy. We got married. He went to prison
I'm sorry. I jumped it
He went to prison and and his lawyer
Said to him you have a much better chance of getting paroled if you are a married man
So she married him
Not for like like it's like a green card type situation she married him in the hopes to do without a prison
But he never did so after five years of this she goes hey
Sorry, I can't just be cell about the rest of my life. I gotta go date people
So she I go was he okay with you dating this Polly guy for a year and a half she goes no
I'm like well, then he's probably not cool with me
Why did he go to prison like that? She goes don't worry. He's in prison. Yeah exactly
Yeah, I go. Why did he go to prison? She goes well. I can't tell you everything
What the I'm a government informant right? Yeah, you asked me a single question about my divorce
So you can tell me that you are married to a man in prison after we have been intimate dozens of times
That's outrageous outrageous and I'm like so I can't in that instant go well
I'm dumping you, but I had to kind of be like hand. Yeah, I guess you yes you absolutely
I was just kind of like you can say get the fuck out of here you sociopath
Before you get us both killed. I guess you're right
I didn't like and I was talking to my you know who I was talking to Tim Hedrick
That's who I was talking to my buddy who looks at this guy and Tim goes
Pat pat pat pat
That guy is going to put a hit out on you
He's like if you never watch Oz do you ever watch any of these shows they can feel like it
Then you better put a hit on it. It's like they can kill people on the outside. Yeah
So I you know I'm out of that one now too
But dating hasn't been going great is my
Moral there
It's not fun out there by the way. I'm also pansexual. I'm into lost boys listen
I
I'm pansexual as well. I'm turned on by Creighton barrel
Do they sell pots and pans of Creighton bear?
Uh, I should have gone with Williams Sonoma
All right, yeah, I got a new boyfriend. That's my safe. That's my safe word William Sonoma
That's my safe word when I you go do bondage. Yeah, yeah William Sonoma. Yes
All right, let's let's review or discuss rather our first of our Christmas films
Sure national ampounds
Christmas vacation
Yeah
Chevy Chase's if I'm not mistaken last
like quality film
I think it was Christmas vacation and then nothing but trouble which is
Sort of the I like top -to -up time machine which he appeared in yeah, but that's not a Chevy Chase movie. No
You know, but I think it was it was it was Christmas vacay and then
Uh, nothing but trouble and then after nothing but trouble
I think it was memoirs and an invisible man and then it was John Carpenter's memoirs. I know wild, right?
No, he cops and robbers. Yeah, it's like it's just no day
Yeah, just never it never swung back
Yeah, man of the house with JTT
There was a lot of shit in there
Vegas vacay of course, which you like hey
It's okay. I think it's in a
I think it is like like a barely a click above
National ampune's Christmas vacation to Eddie's island adventure. Yeah, it is better than that
It is better than that, but I think like it's like barely fucking better than that like it's I remember laughing out loud when they
Had war in the casino and the guy just goes you lose and takes his money and now they have war in Vegas
Every Vegas casino, but um
Christmas vacation I
Was
Nine or ten. I remember seeing the preview and I was all excited. Yes, they had the cat blowing up under the tree
Which they would never put on television now
That thing had nine lives. It just using them all yeah, then
But I've seen this movie at least once a year for my entire life since it hit video
I mean it's it's it's become this Christmas story
Those are the two new and elf is the new one as well or just they're always on I don't give a rat's ass about elf
I really like all the can hold a candle to these other ones. I've tried many times with elf. I just don't it's not bad
I just don't care. I'm just saying whatever and a wasted Bob new heart, you know, you've got Bob new heart as an elf
Why is he not stammering all over the fucking movie? I tell you you want a funny Bob new heart in a movie in and out
Yes, the principal trying to say gay trying to say the word gay. Yeah in place. Yeah, and plays a bass. You're a
Yeah
Anyway, but I just rewatched Christmas fake. Hey, I don't know if I I've always loved the movie
I don't know if I just wasn't really in the mood. It didn't
Oh, didn't quite hit me the way it used to hit me. Well, we really should have talked before. I wouldn't have come
um
No, I wasn't man at it. I just it just wasn't hit me in the way. I you know, we talked about
Recently in the movie corner. We talked about European vacation
And the one thing I pointed out about you're in the European vacation that I really do enjoy and I stand by this and it did affect this viewing
I don't like the version of the kids in Christmas vacation. I think it's a waste. I think they're too young
Way too young we get into like such a cool
area particularly with Rusty
um in the first two where he's a kid kind of coming of age
There's the beer gag in the first one the second one. He's all horned up. You just all he's just chasing skirts the whole movie
In the first two movies Audrey is coming into her own she smokes pot in in the first one with with Eddie's daughter in the second one
She's obsessed with Williams vodka her boyfriend
This one. It's just they make Julia Julia Lewis's Audrey just the bratty bitchy whiny kid and then
Galeki as Russ is just the adoring son
They're just pointless. They just don't serve any purpose to the entire plot. They don't give Galeki anything
But Julia Lewis is the most accurate portrayal of like a teenage girl
I think and her rolling her eyes at him and all that I think she does add a lot of comedy to the movie
I agree I agree that she's a very accurate portrayal, but she doesn't have anything
There's no like let's because they've added 18 characters
Well, yeah, yes, so so that's that's my first strike against the movie
I could give two shits about the neighbors played by Julia Louise
Dreyfus and the other guy's guest brother of Christopher guest
It is pretty funny. I like all of it and I don't like this negativity and I won't let it stand. I don't dislike it. I just
Um or wrong anyway, it just let's but let's talk about the movie
You know, I mean it's it's for certainly the first to get sort of zany
There's not much of a plot to it. No, it is a it's a collection of sort of vignettes and sketches, but the fact that it has like
Every single scene in it everyone relates to it hits all the things that you know Christmas movies did before
It's like when a stand -up gets up and talks about like let's say Joe where to get up and talk about airlines
You'd be like oh christ, but if you found some great new way in and hit everything no other comic ad yes
That's what I feel like Christmas vacation is it has all these traditions
But it pokes fun of them in a way that hadn't really been done before it is a little slapsticky a little broad now
Even when I was a kid when Chevy chase steps on the board and it hits him in the face
Then he turns around and steps on the other board and it hits him in the face
I was like all right, but then when he steps on the board a third time. I was like now wait a minute
That's too much and sometimes the movie is guilty of that
Giving you one too many hits and the nuts. It's in the balls the the the timpani noise
Did you bring a saw
It was a little bit up down the tree a little bit of that and then the tree is dug up by the roots as if there was any way
They could have done this with their hands. It's fine
Sometimes John Hughes is a gag guy who doesn't think through whether a thing could actually happen
When they pull the tree out by the roots is insane. I'll give you the thing what the lights is great
By the way Joe, those are great socks. I wasn't aware though that somebody dropped a house on your sister
And I'm sorry to hear that
There is
I was self conscious about putting these socks on tonight. I think with good reason
Huh
Those are nice pants. I didn't know they came in a cut of yick
A cut of yick
Let's think of Billy Crystal. Oh, okay. Yeah nice pants. I didn't know they made those in atrocious
It's like a win -hary met salad you anyway. No, it isn't
It's like an air bud golden receiver joke when air in the salad great jokes. It's like a 700 Sundays joke
Give me an exact anyway
Look the plot as it was of all these movies is Chevy chase wants to make the best blank ever. It's okay, so so I'll say that so
First of all, I need to just say because I've been dying to say to somebody my favorite line in any vacation movie ever
and
Certainly the Chevy chase has probably ever said outside of in three amigos when he goes do you serve anything do you have anything besides Mexican food
When he yeah in Mexico, which isn't credible that it also do you know what nada means? Is it a light chicken gravy?
I like when the kid goes can I have your watch when you are dead. I always felt that was funny as well
But can I go oh? Oh, I was sorry. Yeah, but my favorite line in any vacation movie is in the first one
Which is when they first established that he goes too far and when he has the meltdown in the car. Yeah
He goes holy shit
I must be out of my fucking mind. I want a pilgrimage to see a fucking moose
Yes, that's that's the line that makes me laugh the hardest out of any Christmas vacation movie and I like
They don't really call back to that ever until this one
And I like in the like the fact that with very like probably within the first 20 minutes
When he's in bed with Beverly, D 'Angelo
She immediately establishes like you go too far
They set it up beautifully. It's a beautiful setup. You know what you do
They all watching the movie know what you do. It's a really really good setup and and then from there on out
It's sort of just a stage for all of that to to transpire
Correct. Yeah, but that's enough for me especially as for the third in a franchise
By the way, has there ever been a franchise that was something
Something like national ampune like they never did mad magazines something. It's really weird
No national ampune was was the like it wasn't at that point not even a magazine you could buy it only place arrogant enough to do that
Yeah, really weird. Yeah, yeah MTV didn't go MTV's election
Yeah, you know, but I actually
What's that the best which is the best well the first one is the best
VK vacation animal. I go one in three animal house sucks. I go one in three
One in three and I don't think animal house sucks. I'd put it out. I think in three
But wait, what else is there besides animal house in the three vacation? There's dorm days with Paris Hilton
And while there was one well
animal so the rise of Tosh
National ampune
National match animal house is very funny. I don't like I think animal house stinks
It's like porquies with a fat guy, but way way way better than pork
I don't think I don't think John Belushi is funny. I just don't
Sir would you I didn't realize you were now a host of the podcast
Uh, I know
No, it's okay. Don't worry about it. No, I think national ampune's vacation is his hands down the best national ampune's well
Well caddy shack is an un it doesn't unofficial. It's an unofficial
There was also class reunion, but it's not an official and American pie isn't American pie sort of no, okay
But they were right about van wilder. I believe I guess now they can't get them made they used they did a bunch of
Directed DVDs ship for all they became they got sold and then they became like frat guy frat house comedy
Yes, but anyway, which is how they started with animal house everybody's like oh, well, it's not animal house
It's a fucking frat comedy guys like anyway
Okay, Christmas vacation look let's not forget
Now they might have been the first to do it
So maybe that's where the precedent gets that but this is sort of a thing that happens with comedy franchises
Let's make the third one a Christmas one
They did it with Harold and Kumar, right? It's it's kind of a thing that you that might be it, but yeah, that's it
But it's a good point
And people consider yeah, Guardians of the right was that a movie was a Christmas special
But won't but won't Guardians of the galaxy three be called Guardians of the Galaxy three
Yes, not for right no three. Yes the defense restaurant
But I will say that
You know link with Harold and Kumar that's considered to be the second best of that trilogy and it's not great
But compared to two it's really fucking good
I wonder if some of our nostalgia for Christmas vacation is that is that
Compared to two
It's it's it's a return to form it feels a little more like the first movie
It's a it's a bit more innocent the second one turned into a bit of a tit rom
Sure, but you know, and I'm not knocking it. I'm picking 13 tit rom which is rare and also too
It it mirrors the first one in the sense that it also
Doesn't have much of a plot as you said. It's sort of a string of
Incidents yeah that relate to yeah, so
But let's talk about the funny the funny in this movie
Well, John to me the whole movie is funny. It's John Hughes
So every line of dialogue is pretty funny every situation is pretty funny
As I get older like the sledding hijinks are less amusing to me
You know a little bit of it's kind of broad wacky kid stuff
But I think that's why it lasts is that kids love it adults love it. Yeah, it's really love Christmas vacation
My dad really loves Christmas vacation because they put all that work into the Christmas lights and everything and no one ever gives a shit
That's that stuff was great the sledding thing even as a kid. I didn't give a shit little lights are not twinkling Clark. Yeah, I know
Thanks for knowing
The the four parents are excellent. Oh, yeah, yeah, the four parents are excellent
And it's so weird that when Beverly D 'Angelo's parents come in
You just with Clark's parents. You're like of course
His parents are the most like Norman Rockwell, and it's like that's why he's like that when her parents come in you're like
Yes
There are the ultimate wasps right like they're the ultimate just like callous wasps. It's drunk the whole time
It just makes sense. It makes so much sense that they like Eddie. Yes, but don't like Clark and that doesn't make any real sense
But it does you know what I mean? Yeah, but but but which brings me to I love to when when
At the end when Clark's dad is he's like you cocked it up
You know you went dots you got to calm down when he then they had that little discussion in the back room
Then he's like how did you make this look so easy all those years every Christmas was perfect
He's like I had a lot of help from Jack Daniels. Yeah, that it's not a big laugh for anything
But I'm always like like John Hughes gives you those moments so that you see the history between
Father and son all the relic all the relations makes sense
Even cousin Eddie shows up. He's coming in from a different movie sort of
But he's hilarious has Randy quayed was that his end of the row?
I guess he still did buy by law. No, he quayed was in a bunch of shit after that. He really loses shit
What what happened? It's it's it's not so like two it's later than you think it's like 2006 or something
I definitely watched a video of him having sex with his wife in a cave
That they put online he he anyone else see this thing or was it just me?
She had a mask on yes exactly
Yeah, it was raw. I'm bummed. I miss Randy quayed. I miss Randy quayed he comes in in this thing and you're like
He's amazing. He's he's he's
I would go as far as to say as we've said about Bill marine kingpin
Randy quayed gives an Oscar worthy performance in this movie completely agree
Hit that scene that entire sequence yeah when they're drinking the egg nog out of the moose heads
And with the fucking when he's talking about when mill that keeps falling apart when he's talking about how his daughters the
The weight guesser at the carnival. Yeah, yeah, barking for the yak woman
You see these big horns coming out of her head sweet as pie hell of a cook. Yeah
And then he does the little spinning thing that we have when I was a kid he spends it and they all fall. Yeah, yeah that thing
Which and then and then Joe what was the last comment a new comedy you watch maybe an HBO max original
Right how does it stack up to Christmas vacation that you that you spent the beginning of this shitting on but not listen
I'm not shitting on pair to Christmas story Christmas
All right, you still think it sucks. No. I don't think it sucks. All right. I'm just saying
It part of this is me in my problems on the inside emotionally. I know and where I'm at in life, but
It's but the the that scene with the
What do you call it the windmill? I don't know whatever the fuck that thing is
That sets up the greatest callback in the entire movie when he's having the meltdown
And he goes over and he's pouring
Full
The eggdog like it's whiskey. Yeah going
We're gonna have the half -half happiest Christmas since Bing Crosby dance with Danny fucking gay and when Santa squeezes
His fat white ass down the chimney tomorrow. He's gonna find the happiest bunch of asshole
This side of the loony bin. I didn't watch it this year
That's from memory. He said to a tripod and
That was back when I wasn't calling you tripod in the back
I'm sure you're well hung but I was talking to the tripod to the right
When you got that was back when if you got a you when you got a random fucking a PG movie it was like crazy
And they're always John Hughes. Yeah, he always got a fucking somehow that was nuts
What else with this movie? This course at the end of the road for Hughes because then the next year was home alone
And then from then on he was
Oh, he was early sue he I don't mean he didn't have any more success
I mean he only made movies about kid drill bit Taylor
Well, yeah, he got ghost riding credit on that. I tried to watch that the other night sucks terrible sucks
But he just kept getting younger and younger he was like they loved home alone. I'll make babies day out about a baby doing it
And then it you know, I'm surprised I'm bet he saw look who's talking and was like fuck they did sperm that can talk fuck
By the way, RIP cursed the alley. Yeah
That made me real sad. Yeah, is this is trump country down here, right?
Like 100 % I don't care. I really don't but like 90 %
Okay, I don't want to get beat up in the park. I don't want to get beat up ever
Um
What's his face Bill Hickey of course. Oh the great William Hickey. You couldn't hear a dump truck driving through a nitroglycerin plan. Yeah
I also love William Hickey's performance and it's a wonderful life
He's not in there. He's not but he's very old
He's tremendous in it. Yes the
Arguably the funniest well the funniest
By the way, did you know that William Hickey's wife is played by Mae Kestell the voice of Betty Boop. Yes
I didn't know that
Next time you watch it you hear it in her voice. She sounds like Betty Boop. Yeah
You can you can read that and other stuff in Pat's new book facts that won't get you laid
We'll see the night is young
And I shaved my balls chapter one the supporting cast of Christmas vacation
By the way, it's just bullet points that stuff doesn't even even when I'm on a date with someone who has no interest in movies
Those facts come out and if you think that was a lukewarm reception
Where do you talk into one person who doesn't care about movies that you're telling that the grand the great aunt in Christmas vacation was the original voice of Betty Boop
Um
Next to the egg -nog scene the funniest scene in the movie is the dinner scene. Oh, sure because that's one of
Well, shit. I don't know him talking to Mary
In the department store is pretty great very funny, but very erotic. Yeah, and they have her swimming in their pool
Yeah, crazy every one of these movies. He wants to tag some fucking
Well, this one's this one he's fantasizing about a lady in his pool
Invocation he's chasing a woman with his family in the car and then when they get to a hotel
He swims nude with her with his kids upstairs. It's a really crazy development in vacation
Um, but what's the theme of that movie how you feel trapped how the married man with kids feels trapped
It's a very dark theme, but it's right. It's right. It's right
The uh
What
It is it is wild because you think it's just no you do you think it's just about people going across to see a moose
Yeah, it's not to battle out more than that
Oh, yeah, for sure that the line that sums up all vacation is when the guy that owns the amusement park where he goes
He goes to smell from the back seat was unbearable
Like it's too meant to be like why have I done this? Yeah, yeah, my plight. It's my cross to bear is the father. Yeah
It's it's it's dark. Yeah anyway Clark Rizwald was my dad right down to the way two short shorts
Except he was always in the explosive rant mode. Yeah, so like you never really got the other side, but yeah
Um, the scene in christmas vacation at the dinner scene
I love that scene for two reasons and it's why the reason again also why I think the ignore scene is the funniest scene
Well, I think this is the second funny scene is it lets
Chevy chase and randy quay shine
It's randy quay loving the
Jell -O mold with the cat food in it and like just like letting that character explode and be disgusting in the way is and then Chevy chase eating
The turkey that's too dry the jell -O mold
Just a bit chewing like
Yeah, yeah, like they're doing the old like somebody's flossing at the table
Yeah, when he puts the jell -O in his mouth and he realizes there's cat food
And he and he start doing like the chewing with his front teeth. Yeah, that's like curly. Yeah, it's just it's just
That's an amazing scene. That's an amazing scene
It goes a little off the rails at the end of the movie when they kidnap
Bill Murray's brother
Love it because he doesn't get his Christmas bonus. Yeah
You're Christmas Merry Christmas. Happy Hanukkah. Kiss my ass. Kiss his ass. Kiss your ass. Yeah. Yeah
I love that. Happy Hanukkah's the last
No, I love everything about that movie except the
Animated opening but I like that song by darling. I hate that they don't play the theme song
I hate that they don't play the holiday road. Yeah. Do they play it in European? Yes. Oh, okay. Yeah
In fact, I think European also opens with it like yeah, they didn't want to pay Lindsey Buckingham
And all the dogs that barked on and they all get their cut
I feel like they just thought it didn't fit. I mean how it's it's not a road movie. It's that's true
You know, but um, but it was a holiday move
It was so we would have accepted and it is um
I'm trying to think what else in a Christmas vacation is that I want to touch on if if anything
I think we kind of hit all look
I my hog is is is still up for Christmas vacation
It's not down. It's just it didn't hit me quite this year top the tree like a shining star
But you didn't watch it this year
But I will and I'd like to hear what you think I didn't want to give in the mental state you've been in
Upon a rewind still able to laugh. I don't know
Well, it's still a good Christmas movie. It is, but you know, I I feel like if I rewashed even the original Christmas story
I would I would find it a little more thin than I used to find these movies. Jesus Christ rich little Christmas Carol
Doesn't hit me like like us not liking anything does it doesn't mean we also have to go back and stop liking things that we already like
Here's then what's what's the end of this road
Well, we're gonna be like a man out tonight in a parking lot with a revolver
You're gonna be as grumpy as as Tom Hanks and a man called Otto
Oh, god, Jesus Christ. Tommy Hanks. He's uh, I I wish we knew why he was making the choices
He's making let's get to our next movie which actually has a lot of layover like you you know John
He was was a huge fan of Frank capper and it's wonderful life
They watch it's a wonderful life in Christmas vacation as they do in every Christmas movie because it's a wonderful life for a long time
Nobody owned the copyright much like night of the living dead
So that's why you see it in gremlins and all kinds of movies because they can use it for free another fun fact that won't give me lead
but
This movie also Christmas vacation they do the nulpost thing
Yes, the nulpost because in in it's one of a life that thing keeps wobbling and it and finally he has the breakdown
But then Chevy chase saws it off. There's a lot of tie -ins between the movies
But it's a one of a life
You know on letter box, which I do
You put out you pick your top four movies
Everybody has that on their letter box page. It's one of a life is in my top four
That's how much I love the movie. I think it's it's a masterful film. It's perfect
I'm not gonna talk too much about the four keb, but Jesus Christ it looked incredible
I thought it was made yesterday. I watched in four came myself. Yeah, it was it was pretty stunning
Uh, to me as I was talking about with Joe
James Stewart and it's wonderful life one of the great performances of all time with Jack lemon and Glen Gary
Yeah, Nicholson and about Schmidt. Uh, have you all seen it's a wonderful?
It's a wonderful movie
They should have called it
It's great, and it's like
The the reason it is great is the darkness of it like Jimmy Stewart in the movie is
contemplating suicide for the bulk of the film
Well, at least the last half of the film what's so interesting about it is
It's also about a guy who hates his life and kind of hates his wife and family that they there there is some some there's a resentment
Yes, there's a certainly there's certainly a resentment so as soon as the movie starts
They have the the star that the thing with the stars talking to one another where it's supposed to be the angels up in heaven talking
And this man down on earth needs help. He's depressed. He's going to kill himself. He's going to rob himself of God's greatest gift which is life
We need you to go down there and help him. You're his garden angel. So right off the bat. You know something's
A foot obviously and then the movie starts
In you're watching scene after scene of this
Kid with this wonderful life
That's the title
uh
Growing up getting older and doing all these great things and then it starts to slowly take a turn and what's so interesting about this movie and I never
Sort of at a time stamp until this last time I watched it
Everybody knows that it's about a guy that wants to kill himself and then the angel shows him what life would be like if he never existed and that's what makes him want to live
They don't get to that
This is a two hour and ten minute movie. They don't get to that until literally the last 30 minutes
Yeah, it is it's also a two ten movie that
I was shocked when they're they're bringing in the money at the end of this thing because it feels so fast
And it's black and white and it was made like a hundred years ago. Yeah, they do my lightning quick over a 90 minute build up
Yeah of getting to know this guy
Getting to know what his life is getting to know what his dreams are
Why it does matter that those dreams are dashed why it does matter that he never gets out of this town
Why
His feats as a wonderful person are important to the story why his relationship to his family is important to the story
They build and build and build which is so interesting because
If you watch the
documentary
Full -tilt boogie which is the documentary that Tarantino made about from Dustel Dawn worth Robert
Not expected to mention full -tilt boogie right now, but but go on well
It's it's it's a really great documentary to watch if you're interested in in construction of film because Tarantino talks in that about
The way to make a good horror movie is you have to make people care about your characters
And that's why Dustel Dawn works because you spend an hour with these characters even though they're
Awful you spend an hour with them and and then the vampires come out
And ultimately like the way you want to watch this movie is not knowing the vampires are coming
To just have that surprise happen
Ultimately the way you'd want to watch it's a wonderful life is not ever knowing that this weird thing in the third act
Is going to happen where the angel prevents him or shows him
Life without him because up until that point
It's just a drama about this guy's life where you're sitting there going
You should be grateful you idiot. Yeah, but I also understand why you're not
Yeah
Well, I mean he's got like the simplest way to put it is he's got the grass is always greener thing
But anytime he gets an opportunity to
Go to leave his town to make something of himself to be more than what he thinks he deserves
He something happens that keeps him stuck in town. Yeah, which is everybody's story
Like I always think I knew that if I didn't move out of Missouri the second I graduated college and I moved
September 1st when I graduated college to New York
Because I knew that I would just get comfortable and stuck there for the rest of my life
It would have been very very easy
And if I smoked weed at that time, I would still be a Missouri much like Kevin Smith
But I didn't smoke or drink and I it was just very easy for me to be like I have to get out of here and I did but
You have very limited time to make that choice. I also don't think everybody's miserable who stays in their hometown
I don't you know, but this is just a guy who
starts to resent his his gifts. He's got these beautiful kids beautiful wife
And he's always just like what could have been might have been worse than what he's got
But he doesn't and that's everybody's life. So everybody watching it
It just feels like you and when he goes home and he's yelling at his kids
They wouldn't let on a if if if now it would be John Cena playing George Bailey
But they wouldn't let him go home and yell at his kids like stop playing that
Quit playing that song, you know, they would never let somebody yell at their kids like that because it makes him so unlike
He's unhinged for like 45 minutes of this movie. He's he's unhinged. He's getting barfights. He's screaming at his kids
Yeah, that's what makes it work. That's what the darkness makes the end hit
The catalyst for the ending without sobbing. I was I was bawling watching the ending like I always do the catalyst for the
for his
breakdown is
his uncle
Not even his uncle's a bit of a fuck up and his he and his uncle have taken over the the dead father's
Company and his uncle misplaced his $8 ,000 through no real fault of his own. He just leaves it on the
bank counter and
Some fault but then but the villain discovers it mr. Potter
Great villain mr. Punter. Yeah, the villain discovers it
And doesn't tell the
They rely on his when he goes George. I'm an old man and most people don't like me
One of his first lines in the movie so
But that's the thing because now it's like
This is the this is the straw that breaks the camel's back. George Bailey is now facing potential jail time
Money is lost that they owe
It's gonna look like they were fast and loose with investors money and other people's money and bubble
But like a Bernie made off thing. Yeah
Made off with his money. Yeah, there you go
And whenever do that at the time or yeah, yes, yeah many a lot
uh
But that's what sends him over the top and then he goes home. He's taken out of the kids
He's taken out of the wife. He's and
What's really interesting about this is
There were a lot of movies that during this time period that came out that would have handled that situation
quite differently
He would have been
More abusive where if you watched it now you would go. Oh my god. That's
Oh, that's a lot
He hit the wife, you know, whatever
They don't do any of that. Yeah, it's a guy that's like justifiably angry
Taking out too much frustration on his kids and his wife
But like in the way that a guy having an awful day might
And you go intense and they very wisely keep cutting to Donna Reed who's looking at him as if to say like you're not normally like this
Right, that's what keeps it kind of safe. It's like this is abnormal
It's also a movie by the way that
What year did this come out 1942 42 yeah at the end of the movie when the whole town is coming together
Did you did you feel it was an accurate portrayal of life in 1942? I wasn't born yet. I don't know
It's about to honestly answer that god damn it. It's it's a very it's a very
very interesting movie and it's very ahead of its time in the way
That it deals with
It the fact that it deals with race without dealing with race is what makes it so interesting the fact that it deals with gender and
Male and female roles in society without dealing with them is very interesting the fact that
They've got a character. There's that blonde that's just aching for it through the entire movie
She's trying to there's the plan that really wants to fuck Jimmy Stewart
Which is always a weird vibe when somebody wants to fuck Jimmy Stewart and he's like, oh, I don't know
I'm not sure he turns into John Mulaney. Yeah
But there when we see her in the town square and she's she's like oh and she will go over to talk to Jimmy Stewart
She's being almost talked to like pushed up against a wall by two men one of whom is about 55 years old
She's like 20 well
Jimmy Stewart in the first scene by the way is like how old are you Mary?
And she goes 18 is that a problem and he goes wrong not at all she goes whoa no she goes
I'm sorry is that too old too old. Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, and you're and it's not you're not supposed to be like
You're supposed to be like oh yeah, that's probably too old for some guys. Yeah, yeah, um, but
No, it's good for us, but it's so interesting the way that the way she the way she's portrayed in that situation is portrayed that
They they do there's a heavy insinuation that
She might be not that she should be it and they don't shame her for the sexuality in any way nobody goes
Oh old Mary is
Yeah, nobody does anything like that. She's just who she is and there's an insinuation that
She might be doing it for the wrong reasons we're not sure
And then when she goes to him says I'm moving to New York and whatever and you just go oh okay cool
And then when he's not alive and the angel shows him if you hadn't been born and you see her
now as the dancer in the sort of salacious
go -go club whatever you call
And even then in that moment it's not that it's like it's like see what sex
Leads to it's not like that. It's just
She's kind of in a bad situation with these roughnecks that run the club or whatever she never found love. She just this is kind of yeah
I love that's my favorite sequence in the whole movie when he's running down the main street of pottersville
Which is what it's called because if he wasn't born this guy potter takes it over and calls it pottersville
And he's running down the main street and main street in small town USA
Murray Christmas movie house
Well book no no not that part now when he's when he's when he's not alive
And he's running down the street and you're you're seeing that it's become New York City
It's become Times Square and it's everything
He always wanted to find and pursue somewhere else
And now he's running down his own street and he's and he was realizing again
This amazing commentary on capitalism and over development and selling off the real estate
Without calling it out without saying what it is yeah
Just running down and seeing a bar every three feet and him realizing like oh my god this place has been destroyed
It's fucking riveting man. It's so fed of its time. It's crazy. Yeah, mr. Potter is your stand -in for
Bezos or Elon mother or whoever else is doing all this shit now mr. Potters hilarious
There was an SNL sketch but could I love because musk was your favorite SNL host
This year right boy. He was funny wasn't he?
We knew he was a great guy but the comedy
The there's an SNL sketch where Dana Carvey is playing Jimmy Stewart who does a great impression and they all
Drag mr. Potter out of the wheelchair and beat him to death is anyone ever seen that sketch?
Really funny sketch that I don't remember what else goes on in it, but that was really
It was the alternate ending
Because you hate him so much you you want to see him get some sort of come up and so they all beat the shit out of him
But the movie is amazing
Jimmy Stewart
This you know he's got his speeches in the movie, but he's just on fire throughout
I guess he was 30 or something in this I don't know
But he's incredible. He's always been a great actor, but he's never had a better part
No, this movie is is the movie where you realize why he was an American icon why he was a cinematic icon the Hacks of his day
No question. Yeah, and and you get to see a guy where you're like, oh my god
It's it's funny. I said John Nolini earlier, but it is it's very John Nolini
He's he's this sort of all -American sort of boy next door guy, but there's this darkness
That's just swirling around and and he doesn't play into it
He just kind of lets it exist there if carry grand really like I'm sure the people who would have been his his
Equals at the time carry grand what I love carry grand he would have sucked in the part Gregory Peck has never
Never been able to act in my opinion Gary Cooper's not a great actor
That he's the he's the guy without him. I don't think the movie is is the classic. It is
I love everything about it. Oh, let's not forget down to read my god down to read is right in it
She's she's it makes me very emotional and at the end you know what I actually thought this time at it shows how old and depressed
I'm getting is that it was the first time like every time I've seen it. I've been like
That angel's right
You know no man. It's a failure who has friends. That's so sweet whatever. I like I cried at that part of course
Yeah, this time I watched it and I was like what if you were watching this movie and you didn't have any friends
I bet it would make you kill yourself. I
That's honestly what I thought I
I will say I might not have been in the best mine statement. All I was watching is I would like to do a remake where the guy realizes
Yeah, it is better if I'm not born. Yeah
This seems awesome. There are people who the world would be better if they weren't born
And I talked about it and nauseam on the podcast, but we're talking about the movie. I got to mention it again. It's it's why
It is
In my opinion the most brilliant Christmas episode of a sitcom ever
The fact that marry with children would like the first and only people to go
What if everything is better because he's not bored?
Good idea. It's so funny. Yeah, and then the fact that they were like oh, and we call it
It's a wonderful life. It almost sounds like it's a wonderful like yeah
God you you've talked about this when you're like driving to the writers room and you're like oh, I got an idea
Yeah, it's very it's whoever thought of that was driving it like holy shit. Yeah, I got a winner on my hands here. Yeah
Anyway, it's a wonderful life on 4k
For I believe 799 on Amazon. Yeah, you can buy the I bought it for I think 799 well worth it
Looks incredible. It's just the best. I it is one of my all -time favorite movies. It's classic
It'll make you feel better make you feel better about your shitty life
Uh, or we're not better and just maybe you jump off a bridge. Yeah, exactly
What's that?
It'll make you feel yes, and that's rare on this day and age
Who has uh who bought
Who bought meat and greet tickets
Oh, good
Two people listen guys. I'm just gonna open it up to the floor
Say uh
You can all meet and greet after this if you like
I don't think anybody will be a fit. I'm sorry if you
How much extra did it cost?
I
Will
And I think I speak for Joe here. We'll fuck the meeting great people
I'll fuck everybody in this room. Yes for at least two seconds each
And I will finish in each of those two seconds
Everybody gets an orgasm tonight
Thank you
Oh, when you say finish you mean that they'll finish too
Yeah, I can bring you to orgasm you're like that that uh, I just really watched the last wall
It's a muddy waters that that song that's also in good fellows where he goes uh, he's bragging about himself
And he's like I can make love to you woman in five minutes time
I was like what that's not really a good breath, but I think after all this time
I realize that he means I'll may I'll get you there and fuck yeah
All right, yeah, all right
Where did we why are we talking about this? I don't know you brought it up
I just the wine is hitting me. Yeah quite a bit. I think this has been great. We've given people
To under the radar movies to check out
Christmas occasion. It's a wonderful life. Check them out. We can't and let this just be known that if there's gonna be a live show
We'll probably get sort of drunk throughout it
I feel great
Yeah, uh, I'm realizing now that I I don't know if you saw this blue in my beer that has slightly changed the color
But I did blue chew an edible into my beer. Not a blue chew. Oh
So it's
So you'll just be high and limp. Well now it's disintegrated. So we'll see we'll see you're an edible too
I've had three glasses of wine, but it's hit me like a freight train right
I went to beer because I took a week off drinking and I knew if I had wine
I'd be out here slamming chairs on the floor like you did
Well, that was Kevin Smith's fault. Yeah
Folks, thanks for coming out
Very Christmas happy christmas happy quanza. Thank you all for coming. See you next time. See you next time and see you now