And when the sound of your screams becomes a thing of my dreams, you know I'll stay, stay, stay, stay, stay, stay, stay, stay, stay, stay, stay, stay, stay, stay, stay, stay.
Hey!
Hello!
How are ya?
You know what you're not doing is your whole like, hello all you fucking dicks who do the bang a bang a boo.
I'll do it. Ready?
Hey! It's your favorite podcast talking about horror movies, sci -fi movies, fantasy flicks and action movies.
We'll see you in hell you motherfuckers!
I forgot that I did that so you just said it.
Yes. I peed pre -show in the woman's bathroom.
The second the stream started hitting the toilet I was like, this is sort of a political statement.
Yeah. Now did you do a tuck? Did you do a sitting tuck?
Or a stand? Did you piss all over the seat like the man you are?
I guarantee you will notice no difference from before I went into that bathroom and when I came out.
That's my guarantee to you, the ladies of the North Bar.
I also am glad I went in because I saw a sign that made me laugh out loud whilst peeing.
And it said, so you know how there's not your father's root beer in that line of liquor, alcohol?
There's one in there that says, not your father's mountain ale.
You know how your dad loves drinking that shitty old fashioned mountain ale.
But this is 2019, bitches!
I feel like the person that would drink a mountain ale would be a dad.
Who are the cool kids that think they're cool?
Like, we're drinking fucking mountain ale.
What kids are skateboarding with a mountain ale?
My father's a recovering alcoholic. I don't know what he drinks now.
Does he not drink anymore?
That's correct.
I think he would benefit greatly from drinking. I'd loosen him up a little bit.
I'm glad you brought it up. I've been meaning to talk to you for a while about your drinking.
As I said in the last one, I called him earlier and said happy Father's Day to him and it's not Father's Day.
And he asked me what I'm doing tonight and I started to say a podcast and then I thought, fuck, he's retired.
He'll find and listen to the podcast where I have been trashing him for five, six years.
So I said I'm doing stand -up, which kind of I'm doing.
And then I said I met some friends, which is true, but I mean it's always a real slippery slope
because he'd hear that and then never speak to me again? Wait a minute.
I'll think about it. I'll think about it.
Yeah, I don't trash family members on this show.
Only Hollywood elite that could put money in my pocket.
I want to talk, if I could, before we get too deep into anything.
I've been receiving a series of strange messages from my landlord.
Now I'm afraid that she's going to listen to this and hear it.
But my landlord recently taped a Scientology magazine to my door.
He lives in the neighborhood of the Scientology Center, like real close.
Yeah, I work there at the deli.
He wipes the spittle from Tom Cruise's beard when he gets too excited.
What'll it be today, fellas? A Tom Cruise in a set?
That's like the sandwiches are on me.
You boys want a Travolta today? That's your regular.
That's the New York deli at the Scientology Center.
That was a moment where I was like, fuck, how much did Joe drink before shows?
He's not making sense. But now I get the bit.
Let me guess, Mr. Will's a Forest Whitaker.
Is Whitaker a Scientologist?
He was in Battlefield Earth, but he wasn't a Scientologist.
He's a Scientologist, yes.
And they couldn't fix that eye.
Maybe there's something you don't know about that eye.
Maybe that eye is looking at some shit that you just don't see yet, dude.
I saw Forest Whitaker once in my neighborhood, like this area with his bars and restaurants.
And he's standing on the side of the road with a much younger woman.
I don't know if they were dating or an assistant or what.
But she's standing in a parking spot for him as he circles the neighborhood.
And then he gets there and he rolls down the window and he's like, I don't want to park there.
And she's like, but I've been waiting. And then he drove off.
I'm not saying he's an asshole. I don't know anything about him.
But it seemed like a real rough encounter and I don't know what was happening.
You know how I'll often save a parking space if I'm alone?
Even if I'm with somebody, I'll do this. I'll get out and I'll take a big shit right in the space.
And then nobody parks there.
I would hope not.
I thought that was going to do better.
You're Scientologist. I interrupted.
Anyway, she taped a Scientology magazine to my door one day.
And there was an invite to go see a woman perform Pamela something or other.
I didn't know who she was.
And so there was a note.
The magazine was rolled up and then taped to the magazine was a note inviting me, in handwriting from my landlord,
inviting me to go see this Pamela person perform at the Celebrity Center.
That's what they call it, to not freak anybody out.
Quick pause. In Los Angeles, there is a celebrity -only church for the Scientologists.
Which, by the way, includes, tragically, Beck, folks.
Yeah.
We all love Beck.
Any Scientologists here tonight?
It's okay. Juliette Lewis.
Been to my home. Scientologist.
Who also, and I said in the last show, I spoke of Elizabeth Moss.
She looks like she smells.
We've been doing a lot of bashing of people with troubling eyes tonight.
Juliette Lewis also looks like she stinks.
She doesn't. She doesn't.
I'll be the judge of that.
When I go to this Celebrity Center performance.
Anyway, there was a note that said that I should go.
She was inviting me to join her and some friends to go see this Pamela person perform.
And in the note she wrote, this is a good show to see because it's something that will teach you how to rise above the vultures.
The vultures out there.
That's her opening line.
Who are looking to feed off of your life force.
Ever hear of the soft cell?
Jesus Christ.
I mean, she's right.
So I was like, well, that's weird.
And I just threw it in my closet with the note.
And I was like, maybe one day this will be material.
But I'm not going to go to the thing.
So then I get a follow -up email from my landlord.
And it says the subject of the email is choice of words.
So she drunk?
Put a Scientology pamphlet on your door?
No, that's what I thought.
I thought she was going to be like, hey, sorry if I came on too strong with the vulture talk.
You know, there's some decent vultures out there.
I don't know.
Something like that.
My father's a vulture.
My father's half vulture.
I love vultures.
Big vulture fan.
Yeah.
So the subject of the email was choice of words.
And it just said this.
It said, in the note I wrote you, I should have put in vampires instead of vultures.
Vultures go after the kill, but vampires do the killing.
This is illegal.
That's illegal.
Big space.
By the way, Pamela is a singer.
Is she trying to set you up?
I don't know.
So I write back, hey, how about you fix the washing machine?
Yeah.
Hey, lady, how many Scientologists does it take to get hot water in this joint?
Anyway, so I write back, thanks.
I'm unavailable that night.
Yeah.
Hope you enjoy it.
I'm just trying to be nice.
You're definitely getting future dates because you left it open.
She'll ask you again.
So believe it or not, this is not the weirdest of the two messages I've received in the last month.
Here's the second one.
Got this today.
Wrote it immediately.
Was like, I got to talk about that on the pod.
Subject, ring binders.
Ring binders.
Three ring binders.
Yeah, like three ring binders.
There's no subtext.
It's not a metaphor for anything.
Three ring binders.
Ready?
Hey, Joe.
I have an excessive amount of three ring binders.
Most are one -inch diameter rings and one very large diameter blue binder.
I'm giving them away except for a couple of small ones.
You're welcome to take a binder or two or three.
I'll also ask the others in the building if they would like to have some.
I immediately write back.
Thanks.
I'm not going to say her name.
I'll take three of the binders.
Yeah, I said thanks.
I actually have a few too many myself.
But I'll let you know if I'm ever in need of any.
I'm expecting that to be the end of the exchange.
I get another response.
Ready?
This sounds threatening.
What no one takes, I am taking to goodwill.
She's literally given the it's now or never on the three ring binders deal.
And imagine the joy in the homeless people's eyes when they get that sweet, sweet three ring binders.
Use three ring binder to keep their papers and files in order.
That's the end of it.
I don't know what to yeah, it's odd.
It's an odd and it's only four units.
So in the building, the whole building is only four units.
I feel that as if I've moved into some sort of Rosemary's baby situation where there's some kind of cult going on that I don't know about.
Yeah, it's a little odd.
It's a little odd.
When I moved in, there was a pamphlet for Scientology, but there was also a Christian pamphlet and a Christmas card.
So I thought she was kind of just being like, hey, whatever fucking weirdo you are, welcome.
I mean, you live in like the epicenter of Scientology.
Yeah, I'm right in the middle of it, man.
And, you know, it's you know, it's it's it's yeah, it's right.
But you never see any of them.
I've never seen one of the celebrities ever.
Celebrity Scientologists.
I mean, they're in the nicer part of town.
Are there any we don't know about the Robices?
Absolutely.
Jason Lee.
Yes, that's correct.
You know how Jason Lee left his first wife?
This is true.
She got a letter from him that's from the church that said, like, you're a pollute, whatever the fucking term is.
Yeah, polluter.
Suppressive person.
She got a letter that said you're a suppressive person.
And then she goes, and then I never heard from him again.
That was how that was it.
That was that's how he broke up with her.
Look, if I went out of my marriage, that's the route I'm taking.
That sounds very clean to me.
I like where that's going.
And the Kirstie Alley.
And Kirstie Alley went after went after Remini.
Like, you better shut your fucking mouth.
Because Remini is out there being like, they're all evil people.
Yeah, that's my Remini impression.
I know some people who did a show with Remini.
I think she might be an evil person herself.
But these actors are sick.
These actors are sick.
They're sick.
All of them.
Well, I did.
I said her name.
How much more of a reveal can I do?
I can give you her home address if you want.
But I don't know what it is.
Folks, so I guess we should get on with the show.
And again, I've chosen another Chicago artist tonight.
And get on at the same time.
With the Joe Child.
Things are going to get easier.
Joe Child, things will get brighter.
Someday, yeah.
You won't be working in a bowling alley.
That's all I got.
Very nice.
And a request.
Back to that same old place.
Sweet home.
Chicago Joe.
I think you said Sweet Jome.
Which would have worked better.
But it's too late now.
Who sang...
I would say the best Chicago movie.
My favorite Chicago movies are Ferris Bueller and the Blues Brothers.
Meaning they're awesome but also use the city in an incredible way.
You see the entire city.
Would you say that the city is a character in those films?
I would.
Who sang Ooh Child?
You know, I played the role of New York City in the HBO show Girls.
I thought I did a good job.
Yeah.
Never mind.
I feel like I know where that was going.
I was going to make...
I did portray Ben Frywater in Showtime's Roadies.
That's correct.
Thanks.
By the way, you know how every commercial is 30 seconds?
We were watching the Tonys.
The Showtime commercials are five seconds.
It's like they're buying things.
Wait, what do you give me for 40 grand?
Doesn't Showtime have any money at this point?
I mean the commercial for that new Kevin Bacon show,
and it was like Kevin Bacon, you see the corner of his face,
and then it's like City by the Sea.
I don't even know what it's about.
I think they just reused shots from Footloose.
And they were like, he's in it, but it's called City by the Sea.
You know Kevin Bacon.
He can't look more like a pedophile at this point.
Bacon is really...
It's just...
That face is not looking friendly.
He has portrayed a pedophile.
He's played too many Creeps at this point,
and I can't get away from it.
Well, he played pedophiles in The Woodsman and Sleepers,
which is a very underrated movie.
Yeah.
A blowjob.
He says it with a Philly accent.
He plays a guy from Philly.
What do you guys want?
A blowjob.
A hoagie and a blowjob.
You just want to get some blowjobs from these kids?
We call them Sleepers, dude.
We had for a while stopped bringing Molestation into every other podcast,
but now it's back with a vengeance.
Folks, I just got back from Ireland and Scotland,
and then we popped over to Chernobyl
to sort of see this.
Has anybody seen Chernobyl?
Jesus Christ.
Why does everything we watch have to make us even more depressed?
I've seen three of the five.
It is a masterful show.
It is incredible.
The guy, Jerome, what's the guy's name?
Jared Harris.
Jerry Lewis.
Everybody in it's incredible.
But in the next on,
so I would just watch the third one,
and they were like, next on Chernobyl,
and included in the next on package was a man going,
there's going to be a nationwide elimination of all animals.
This includes those that are domesticated.
We will have to kill all pets so that the disease does not spread.
I'm like, that's your comeback next week?
I've got to watch a bunch of dogs get murdered?
Well, it didn't happen, though, did it?
Chernobyl's a government conspiracy.
Oh, boy.
Joe's like these Scientologists, huh?
Now, let me talk to you about how Chernobyl was a conspiracy.
I'm kidding. I'm joking.
It's a great show, but my God, I don't even want to finish it.
But anyway, we go to Ireland, we go to Scotland.
Beautiful, but, and we're all drinking here tonight,
I hope you are, unless you're sober, and God bless.
But I was blown away,
because you think of Ireland as the most alcoholic place in the land.
Everyone who comes from Ireland is an alcoholic, essentially.
I hate to paint with that broad a brush,
but I can bring it over to a family reunion if you'd like.
They, you couldn't get a pore in Ireland that went above the ice cubes.
I mean, they measured out, like, as if they were in a lab,
and if it was one drop too many, it would blow up.
You would get, like, three drops of something.
And I kind of laughed the first time, and then I started getting doubles,
but the doubles, A, you're still paying 20 bucks,
but they were nowhere near an actual human drink.
And that was everywhere in Ireland.
Then the beers, the most alcoholic beer they offer is a Guinness,
which is like a 4 .2 or something.
So you couldn't get drunk there, hardly.
My wife couldn't get drunk. We were trying actively to get drunk.
And I just didn't get it.
So I asked this guy in Scotland once we got there,
what's the deal with this? What is the issue?
I always thought these were huge drinking countries,
because Scotland was the same way.
He goes, we're a little different than you, mate.
We like to drink all day, so we make it last.
And I was like, no, when I go out with Joe,
we have 40 full drinks, and we're there all day.
So you don't win this.
He was trying to be like, no, you wee pussy, you don't understand.
And I was like, no, you're just wrong. I couldn't believe it.
It might be a sign when Ireland and Scotland are insinuating
that our lifestyle is too sad.
It might be. It's time to reevaluate.
This guy who did our bus tour of Ireland,
I drove around on our honeymoon in Greece.
I drove on these winding fucking roads in a smart car,
and the slightest wind would nearly bring you to your death.
So I go, I just want to get on a tour bus.
And we went up and saw all this beautiful shit in Scotland.
But our driver was this big dude, red beard,
younger than me, probably, Scottish guy.
And he's driving, and it's getting really weird,
where cars are pulling out way ahead of us,
but we're nearly hitting them.
There's like 15 people on the bus, and then people start going,
could somebody please talk to him?
Somebody needs to step up and say something, right?
And we all banded together,
much like in Clint Eastwood's 5 '10 to Paris.
And I was like, hey, buddy, what's the deal, man?
We're all just getting kind of worried.
Like, aren't we like 20 minutes away from the destination?
There was still light out,
because we'd get to these places at like four,
and it'd be the end of the day.
And you're supposed to be on the tour till like eight.
We had had three days in a row where, like, we just ended early.
And you, of course, pay for the tour.
So he goes, ah, yeah, mate, I'm sorry.
I got to get to the pub.
And I kind of chuckled, like, oh, okay.
And he goes, no, I'm serious. I got to get to the pub.
And I was like, oh, okay.
We park the bus when we get to the place,
and he all but ran into the bar.
And we're all just there at 4 p .m.
with like six hours of daylight left.
It gets dark there at midnight.
And we're just, all the people on the tour are like,
where do we go? Where are we staying?
So Heather and I, you know, bring our stuff to it.
We find out where we're going. We go to our place.
And then we have dinner. We have drinks.
And on the way home, we hear music coming out of a bar.
So we go in, and he's there like can't stand up,
like falling over.
And then he's picking us up the next morning at 6 .30.
So like especially the last night we went out till 2,
he's there again, like can't stand up.
And we're like, but you're driving us.
Pat, I feel as if I'm on this tour at the point of this tour.
Look, I would like you to speed it up
so I could get to the pub at this point.
I was blown away. I was blown away.
And I hate to base a whole trip review on the alcohol,
but like that's what I'm doing.
I couldn't believe it.
My darkest point on this trip was
I forgot my swim trunks, ladies.
And they had this beautiful pool at the hotel.
So I had bought as a joke when I went to Vegas once,
I thought these shorts were hilarious.
They were blue with white stars on them.
And they're like polo shorts, and they were five bucks.
And they're very comfortable, and I wear them.
So I'm wearing them the next day.
I wore them to swim because I had brought them.
So they're super wet, and I couldn't put them in my suitcase.
So I wore them to take the train to the airport.
And we're walking, and we missed our train.
And I'm running through the town square,
and Heather points out to me that I am wearing a red shirt
and blue and white starred shorts
running through the town square of Ireland to catch it.
Like, wait, wait for the train.
I must look like the shittiest American of all time.
But we had a nice time.
All in all, though, I can't say I strongly recommend either place.
I had drinks thrown at me in Scotland on stage.
That was the only time that's ever happened to me.
I pissed off a woman in the audience so bad
that she threw a full fucking drink.
What did you say to her?
Oh, I'll tell you.
I used to have a joke in my act then
where I'd go, where I'd go...
I said, I go, you know,
I was in a parking lot the other day,
and this lady wouldn't move her car.
She was parked illegally, and she was blocking all the lanes.
I honked at her, and I go, hey, lady, move your car.
And she got out of her car and went like this to me,
like gave me the, you know,
the like, what are you going to do about it thing?
And I go, if we were truly equal as genders,
then why can't I fist fight that woman right now?
She's calling me out.
And then a lady in the audience got really mad at me
and was booing me, like saying that I was sexist and all that stuff.
So then I said, well, I'm not going to leave the stage now.
And then I just stood up there for as long as I could.
I actually won the audience back,
but this lady still didn't like me.
So I closed with a joke where I said, listen,
you know, I made a joke about fighting women.
That's not funny, obviously.
You know, like I feel for...
I have a heart. I feel for gender issues.
And like I've dated abused women.
It's not, you know, it's no joke.
I don't know if any of you have ever dated an abused woman,
but, you know, it's tough when you first start...
when you first start dating them, you're like,
I just want to teach you how to be loved again,
and I want to teach you what's right,
and I just want to get you as far away from that monster as possible.
And then like two months in, you're like,
I see where that guy was coming from.
Full drink.
Loved.
Hit me right in the chest.
I'm an asshole.
I'm one of those, if you say don't joke,
I get real, you know.
Yeah.
I don't like, I don't know.
Anyway.
Folks...
Give me a minute on that.
I'm already feeling that other one.
Is anybody here that wasn't at the last show?
Oh, well, hello.
Welcome.
That's it, just you?
We like to make people feel welcome
by having the entire room stare at them.
No, there's a few other people, right,
that weren't at the last one?
Okay.
Welcome.
You could have answered before.
Folks, have you seen the trailer for the new Shaft?
Yes.
How do you make a sequel to a remake,
and they're all called Shaft?
You have to differentiate.
It's also called Shaft.
It's not called Son of Shaft or anything else.
It was supposed to be called Son of Shaft.
It was supposed to be called Son of Shaft,
and I don't know why they changed the name
because it literally is, in every possible sense,
Son of Shaft.
Richard Rowntree's in it, Sam Jackson is in it as his son,
and then the new kid is the new Shaft
who plays Sam Jackson's son.
Son of Shaft is such a great name for a movie.
I agree.
That also fits right in the vein of all those types of flicks
from the 70s.
Like, why would you not call it that?
No clue.
It's so...
Wait, wasn't there already a Shaft 20 years ago?
Yeah.
Well, how are we going to erase any confusion about that?
We're going to call it the same thing, Shaft.
I do like the new slogan,
more Shaft than you can handle.
That's a good slogan.
I will give them that.
These slogans are becoming too much.
That's what I'm going to talk about.
This is an ad campaign by the makers of Shaft,
and they have these Shaft Says memes,
and I urge you to look them up.
I'm going to read you a few favorites.
The only old -fashioned I'm serving
is a good old -fashioned ass -whoopin'.
I like that one.
And then a picture of Sam Jackson.
How the fuck do you milk an almond?
I'm not drinking that shit.
I like that one, too.
Did you write these?
No, but I mean, I thought...
It's also like The Ranch,
that show with Ashton Kutcher and Sam Elliott
and the date rapist.
Convicted. It's why the show was canceled.
He's also a Scientologist.
That's true.
Bringing it home.
But Sam Elliott, the very first...
I watched one episode of The Ranch
which was the pilot, and the very first joke
of the very first episode is Sam Elliott opens the refrigerator,
takes out a thing of almond milk,
and he goes, Almond milk?
What the fuck is almond milk?
How do you get milk out of a nut?
The audience laughs like,
Shaft's ripping off The Ranch!
By the way, prime opportunity
for a jerk -off joke right there.
How do you get milk out of a nut?
Then the wife comes in,
You got milk out of yours twice!
We sent them through college, remember?
Something like that.
The only IPA
I like is
I'ma put yo ass through a windshield.
And the IP
and the A are highlighted.
That's ludicrous.
Please read the avocado toast one.
I'll avocado toast
your punk ass.
I mean, these are
humiliating.
This one I do like,
What time is it? Time for you to shut your mouth.
I'll use that one.
I mean, these are humiliating to me.
But I'm gonna see Shaft.
We saw Samuel L. Jackson.
He was on 60 Minutes.
We spent the bar we were watching 60 Minutes
in the Tonys, like a married 90 -year -old
couple over there.
And Samuel L. Jackson looks the same as he did
in 1992. But I thought,
when was the last time he made a good movie
not affiliated to Tarantino? What was it?
And I'm not including the Avengers.
Yell it out. Does anyone know?
I like Black Snake Mo.
What was that one?
Basic.
What?
I've seen Basic. I don't remember Basic.
It's like Enemy at the Gates.
Gandolfini's best work.
Basic, and then there was
what's that one?
I said
no Tarantino affiliation.
I like the Kingsmen.
I like both Kingsmen. With Taran Egerton.
By the way, were we listening to
Taran Egerton play Rocket Man earlier?
I believe so.
I thought this was a karaoke place.
When it was playing.
But Taran Egerton, they make this whole deal
out of how he's really singing
all the songs.
Has anyone ever heard that he's a good singer?
Did we ask him?
Did we rehearse?
I'm going to see the film. Has anybody seen the film?
Any good? I want to see it.
I like Boheme raps.
I'm not going to see it.
I can't take another one of these.
It's going to change your life.
Is it a musical where they're actually doing musical numbers
in addition to the...
Alright, I'm into it.
I can't anymore with this shit.
You're not going to believe how
he wrote Crocodile Rock.
Who fucking cares, man?
He's like this tortured genius and he's like
I hate that song.
Crocodile Rock is the low point
of the Elton John.
I'm picturing him on an airstrip.
His friend Benny is like
you've got to write some new songs.
Get off my back, Benny!
The jet flies over.
Wait a second.
I don't know.
Some stupid shit like that.
Let's do the Milord shot to kick this off properly.
Here's to you, Chicago!
I really don't want to do this.
Neither do I.
God damn!
Boy, it really rolls over you.
It does.
Man, it's got a fucking end on that thing.
That's disgusting.
Honestly, shame on you. Whose idea was that?
Mine. Shame on you.
It's a good idea. Shame on the laugh
for getting out of it.
What's up, Joe?
Oh shit, yeah.
Thank you.
So I'm staying at this hotel.
Okay.
I'm staying at this hotel, baby.
And there is a Nordstrom
attached to it.
And I
buy clothes like once a year,
begrudgingly.
I needed new clothes. I had to have new clothes.
And the shoes that I wore all throughout my long vacation
were destroyed and I was trying to walk around the city with them.
So I go over to Nordstrom.
I walk in.
And A,
why are all men's shirts,
if you get a large men's shirt,
they range from
child small
to like sailboat sail.
On the same rack, they'll be the same size.
You'll put on the shirt and button it
and then it comes to below your kneecaps.
And then the other one, you're worried that
a love handle is going to burst out the side.
But they're the same size.
I don't know what to do. And it's humiliating. I don't like it.
But I'm already out of my comfort zone.
I go in.
And this woman comes over.
I've been there all of five seconds.
Just going to help you find anything.
I'm like, okay. But I said,
no, I'm just looking. Thank you. Great.
She walks away.
I go. I'm walking around.
And the first time my fingers touch a pair of jeans,
she pops up
and is like,
To be fair, they were the salesman's jeans.
Folks!
She goes,
You want me to get a fitting room started for you, sir?
Same woman.
And I was like, no, I'm just looking. Thank you.
I let this go on
two additional times for a total of four.
Where any time I pick something up,
she's there, and it's crowded.
They must assign a salesperson to each person in this place.
So she's like, can I help you, sir?
Can I get anything set up? And finally I said,
Hey, I'm really not trying to be rude,
but I just kind of need to go at my own pace.
I don't know what I'm looking for, but I'll definitely come find you
when I'm ready, whatever.
And she goes, Oh, no, that's okay.
Oh, no, that's okay.
And with a lot of attitude.
And she seemed furious with me.
So I was like,
all right, weird, whatever.
But I start putting together a few things,
maybe the jeans and shoes you're seeing tonight, folks.
Thank you.
Also a few saucy numbers for after the show.
Yes. A little lingerie.
Yeah.
But this other very nice lady comes up,
and she's like, Hey,
can I get you a fitting room started?
And I said, Yeah, sure, that'd be great.
She goes, You can keep looking, or whatever.
I can just put stuff in there, and you can go back there.
I'm like, Oh, thank you very much.
I go back, and as I enter the fitting room area,
coming out of the fitting room is the woman who gave me the attitude earlier.
And she goes,
Oh.
I see.
And I said, What?
And she goes,
This is an employee of the
supposed to be customer service.
She goes, I see.
When the pretty girl asks you,
and I said,
I'm sorry?
And she goes, No, no, no. I think you heard me.
And walks away.
What?
It was one of the most
insane things. A, do you get a commission at these places?
You get a commission just for
like opening a door? I don't know.
Do you or not?
So what did she care?
Did you say anything?
I was so weirded out. And then, of course,
the woman who's now letting me into the dressing room,
of course, it had this weird sexual energy.
Because she just called it out.
I was like, I'm sorry about that. And she's like, Why are you sorry?
I said, I don't know.
I never know why I'm sorry.
I've apologized to two mannequins since I've been in the store.
By the way,
are mannequins getting hotter, or am I getting horrier?
Oh, come on.
I mean, the body's on these things.
When she said that,
you should have gone,
perhaps you need to work on your appearance a bit.
Honestly, both women were very pretty.
Clearly this lady
had some sort of issue, but
I was trying to put on
this pair of jeans and was trembling.
I was so traumatized by the experience.
And then still, to prove a lesson,
I bought a lot of clothes there
to really stick it to the man.
You've got your own style of protest.
They always follow up
when they do a documentary about revolutionaries,
they'll do the Abbie Hoffman chunk.
Then they'll do the Pat Walsh segment.
Pat had a different approach.
He'd spend a lot of money at Nordstrom's.
That's a crazy fucking thing to say.
But she's working out her own shit.
I'll tell you another thing.
The bikes in this city.
What's the place?
Who are you, Lewis Black tonight?
Is it Navy Pier?
Jesus Christ!
And another thing, folks!
Yesterday I walked around this entire beautiful city.
I walked around for hours.
I did 30 ,000 steps on my pedometer thing.
And I'm having this great,
beautiful day, I'm listening to music,
I'm walking around.
And the bikes on this trail.
There is a bike lane and a people lane.
And the bikes are,
every single one that drove by,
they would almost knock into you.
A couple guys did knock into me.
And every single biker that drove past
would turn over their shoulder and be like,
like this look of disgust.
Why are you riding bikes?
I'm going to double down on something here.
You get better exercise jogging, running, walking, anything.
A bike you're sitting.
I was threatened fairly at length by cyclists.
I was threatened by several cyclists
for saying on a different podcast
that I had done
that when I open the door
and you almost crash into it,
that's your fault, not mine.
Because you need to pay attention to where you're fucking going.
I can't see behind me
as you approach my car.
And I was
threatened by several cyclists
who apparently produced movies
or something and said they'd see to it
that I never worked in this town.
They produced movies about biking.
And I said, jokes on you.
I don't work to begin with, fucko.
I hate cyclists.
It was enough to ruin my day.
I went home.
I had been out for eight hours
and after dealing with these bikers, I walked back to the hotel.
I hate cyclists.
I hate these scooter fucks.
Get into the fucking street where you belong.
I haven't seen a scooter here, though.
No, but they're abound
in many cities at this point.
Get into the fucking street where you belong.
You ride on the sidewalk.
You act like it's somebody else's fucking problem.
Get into the...
Ride your little fucking two -wheeled pussy scooter
in the fucking street.
If you can't hang with the big fucking cars
in the street, tough shit.
Okay?
It fucking makes me sick.
It makes me sick.
And they're the only vehicles
that get their own lanes outside of cars,
which I guess that's all the vehicles.
But, you know, listen, that's not the point.
There's a bike lane.
There's a fucking bike lane.
Like, get into the bike lane and ride in the bike lane.
When every cyclist in LA
just rides on the sidewalk now,
when did that become
like just okay?
Half of them are fucking deranged.
So that's the problem.
It's like, you know, it's like
a guy rides by you, and you're like,
you should ride on the sidewalk, and then you look at him
and his eyes are fucking spinning like Bugs Bunny
and you're like, yeah, ride on the sidewalk.
Have, you know, whatever. Do your thing.
And a guy wrapped me in a bike the other day
with a pair of brand new sneakers.
He goes, do you want to buy these?
I go, no.
Because the first thing I'm looking for in a vendor
is walls.
I like to walk into a structure
before I buy things.
You don't want a single option
for the shoes. You like to have a choice.
What are the odds?
This guy's riding on a bike
with one pair of shoes, trying to sell them.
What are the odds he finds somebody
willing to buy shoes from a guy
on a bike
randomly in the street, because nobody's planning
to do that. He finds the guy that was just walking
around going, fuck it, let me live a little today
and buy sneakers from a bike guy.
Who actually fits the one
pair of shoes. You're talking one in
two million at this point.
And the scooters
say on them, they say
don't ride these on the sidewalk.
It says that on
the scooter.
Well, welcome to Trump's
America, everybody.
That's a
good saver when
the bit's bombing.
I get an email the other day, it's from
Barnes and Noble, where I am
a member.
Thank you.
It says, the subject of it is
you haven't been opening our emails.
What is
going on, folks?
I bought my dad four bottles
of nice red wine
for Father's Day.
That's his favorite song.
He prefers the UB40
version.
I saw
Neil Diamond at the Hollywood Bowl
and he opted to do the rap
part.
He performed the cover of his own
great song, but he's
like 70 up there, like
red wine, you make me feel so fine.
It was rough.
So I get my dad,
here's the thing, my dad
lives in Jersey, so I had to
figure out a way to, you know, it's tough
when you mail alcohol to somebody,
because there's all these state rules
and you can't mail it from here to there.
So I find,
I'm trying to find a good wine vendor
that I can not only get the wine I'm looking for
to send him, but that will also deliver to Jersey.
I find this
website, I wish I could remember the name
of the fucking thing, because it made me so mad
and I'll never go to them again.
It was like the best place to buy wine,
Naked Wines, that's what it was, it was Naked Wines.
Your only wine vendor.
They're really bragging that they got
this shit together, right? I go on the website,
it goes, couple of
questions.
When you buy a bottle of wine,
how much of that alcohol percentage
are you actually paying for?
And I'm like, I don't fucking
know. It's a multiple choice.
30%, wrong.
20, at best.
Next question.
A $30
bottle of wine is better than a $15
bottle of wine. True or false?
I'm like, false?
Wrong!
Third question,
fourth question. These fuckers have the
audacity, it goes, okay, we're
almost done.
And I yelled by myself,
I go, fuck you!
At the TV, and got
it from Walmart or something.
This is why Walmart
exists. This is why Target and Walmart
exist, because these fucking little niche
stores make it so goddamn
annoying, sometimes you just
need socks, people.
Sometimes you just
need tube socks that
weren't stitched from
hemp in a forest somewhere.
I don't need the fucking
story of the goddamn
just give me the fucking socks,
ladies!
I'm what you call an attitude comic.
I come up with a lot of
you know.
Folks, we're doing on the show tonight
Henry portrait of a serial killer.
We're going to
do our best to make that funny.
We forgot to mention that up front.
What a fun one that was.
We should probably go to the movie corner, no?
Let me take you down,
because I'm going to,
that's movie corner.
I watched
Always Be My
Maybe.
Now I enjoyed it, folks.
It is the,
Randall Park and Ali Wong.
Michelle Bouteau is in it.
Two very likable people.
The movie was entertaining.
And my friend Ali.
Can we calm
down, though? I don't know if you people are on
Twitter.
Okay, it's Citizen Kane.
Always Be My
Maybe.
And then this Keanu Reeves
thing, okay?
So he plays, she's like, my
boyfriend's coming. They build it up for like five minutes.
Her boyfriend's coming. And then he comes in, and it's
Keanu Reeves in slow motion with that song playing.
It's like, sail!
You know that song?
Sail!
Blame it on my AT &T!
Or whatever.
So,
What song is that?
I don't know.
It's like,
it's like Imagine Dragons or something like that.
Blame it on my HIV!
It's, you know, it's a bad
song.
You know, I hear that band, I imagine
dragons blowing fire on
those fucks.
That was the Malort talking.
Which I believe is the name of one of the
dragons. Malort.
But anyway,
they're like, I didn't know Keanu Reeves was in the movie,
and of course he comes out, and you're like,
you know, here's me on my couch when I saw him.
You know, like,
a slight whatever. And he comes
out, and he's fine in it.
He's funny and charming, whatever.
If you go to Twitter tonight
and look up Keanu Reeves, always behind Maybe,
there are people pushing him for an Academy
Award.
There are people shitting their jeans
over this. Like, oh my god,
the funniest thing I've ever seen.
Because all comedy is now is celebrities
when you don't expect them.
Or people singing. That's all it is.
I was like, who cares?
I mean, just have him play the
role. But he was playing himself.
Why is that so funny to people?
I just don't get it.
It's not. People don't understand what funny is.
They think excited
is funny.
It's just like people think jump scares is scary.
It's not. Jump scare, you're startled.
I get startled when I leave a pressed shirt
hanging on my closet door,
and I forget that it's there.
And I turn around,
and I'm like, ah, fuck! Fuck!
I thought a very crisp man
was in my bedroom for a second there.
It's like, people don't know
what funny is anymore.
I mean, look, I thought
it was a very charming movie,
but I don't know. It's like
if you want to enjoy anything anymore,
you have to sort of not
read the online thing about it.
Because I wound up getting mad about a movie I liked.
I was like, just shut up!
Calm down! It's why whenever Joe doesn't see
something for like a year, I'm like, well, you're going to hate it now
because everybody loved it and you're a contrarian.
I'm not a
contrarian.
Folks!
He didn't even realize what he did.
I'm not a contrarian.
It would have been a brilliant
joke if you knew you were doing it.
If I could do stuff like that on purpose.
Did people like Always Be My Maybe generally?
Or did you not see it?
It was cute.
You know, we don't get romcoms anymore. I'm getting actually
a complete flat line.
So maybe nobody's seen it.
But I thought it was cute.
Okay. It's alright.
Yeah, it's good for mothers.
It's good for mothers.
As...
I got to watch it.
I got to watch it to support Michelle.
Yeah, as promised,
not that anybody's excited, but
as I said in the last show, I'm going to do all Twilight Zones
on this one.
I want to start with...
I will be sitting here looking uncomfortable.
I want to start with an episode,
it was episode five, titled
The Wonderkind.
I don't know if you guys saw this,
but it's about
a petulant child
who gets elected president.
Get it!
Do you get it?
Jesus fucking
Christ.
This thing goes so
outside the realm of possibility.
Rod Serling would have been watching
this like, what the fuck are you
guys doing right now?
Do they talk about why America suddenly allows
a child to be president? Or is it just...
They just...
First of all, Black Mirror did it better,
which I can't remember the name of the episode,
but the episode where the cartoon mascot
gets elected Prime Minister of
England. Oh, I hated that one, but yes.
Well, listen, they did it
better than this. Isn't that also the plot of Blank Check?
Starring Brian Bonsall of
Family Ties?
This episode, this is in
swing vote territory
of unbelievable. By the way, the guy
who wrote the book,
anyone, if you're like an aspiring writer, they tell you to
get this book called
Save the Cat. It's about screenwriting.
And the guy who wrote The
Bible on how to write a perfect
script has one produced screenplay and it's
Blank Check.
Do with that what you will.
So this episode
stars...
John Cho? Is that the guy from Harold and
Kumar? Yes.
And look, again, all the performances
are fine in this thing. The direction is fine.
It's just...
America is so
disenchanted that they elect a 12 -year -old
president. This is fucking...
I mean, come on.
So right off the bat, you're like... You have to be 40
to be president. Well,
they never quite get
into any of that.
It's just like America loves
this guy, this kid.
And they elect him president.
Now, here's the thing. If
you're willing to go on this journey
and you go, okay, we're going to just kind of
put out any question about how
this could happen or
whatever, it's the Twilight Zone, blah, blah, blah, blah,
blah, fine.
That's not enough. That's never
enough because in every one of these episodes, they always
have to go a step too far and I don't understand.
So it's not enough that John
Cho plays a sort of political
strategist who wants to sell
his soul because he just wants
the victory, which we've seen a
gazillion, fucking zillion, million
times from Tales from the Hood 1
to Tales from the Hood 2 to Tales, whatever.
Folks, movies ranging
from Tales from the Hood 1
to Tales from the Hood 2
have told this story before.
Great point, Jim.
It's a lot of tales.
At the end of this episode,
so that's not enough, just like
see what you did, a child
is president, this is horrible.
That's not enough. The last
scene has to be John Cho on an operating
table in dire need
of a life -saving operation
and a child steps
over him with a scalpel
because the boy president
made it legal for boy
children to be doctors.
You're so
outside, you're like, what the
fuck is going on right now?
Why would that be an important
issue for boy president?
Why would he care? It's not.
It's not.
There are some people that go, this is a brilliant episode.
Does he have a secretary
of Hot Fudge Sundays?
No, there's
a whole thing with, kids get to
eat candy for lunch every day.
Then John Cho will go,
Mr. President, you shouldn't be allowed to do that.
He'll be like, I'm president, I can
do whatever I want.
Literally, they're doing everything except
superimposing Trump's face on the child.
Guys, I get the metaphor,
but it's lazy. It's not
entertaining. It's just not good.
It's also real smart to bash Trump on CBS.
This won't be the network of Trump.
You know how progressive CBS is, right?
With all those real progressive shows
they do, all that cutting edge stuff
as they fucking shadow
or as they hid Les Moonves
in the fucking shadows for ten years.
Did I ever tell you about the time I met Les Moonves?
I didn't.
I had to wait in line
behind. I go, Jeremy Piven's
talking to him. And they go, just
wait. It's important that you meet him.
And I waited for a half hour as
two sexual predators
talked shop.
There's a chance
Piven is innocent.
There's a chance. There's no chance
Moonves is innocent. None.
No, obviously none.
I just wanted to say that.
Alright, fine.
Well, Piven apparently passed three lie detectors
at this point or something.
I don't know why I said correct.
I've never even heard that.
I'm just happy Jeremy is able
to go into any comedy club in the country
and do stand up right now.
Because that's kind of what we've all been waiting for.
If you walked in now, we would be asked to leave the stage pretty quickly.
He sells out places.
What is going on in this world?
Piven and Stormy Daniels doing stand up.
I mean, it's just
How many people after the show
you think go up to Piven and go, let's hug it out,
bitch.
A thousand percent
of everybody in the room.
But he's not there because he gets into his car with the doors that open
like this.
That he's valet.
Nobody respects my job.
Anybody is like, I could
do it. Stormy Daniels.
I could do it.
Why Stormy?
She's not on the wall here.
She's not coming here.
Nobody's on the wall here.
There is, right up front.
Oh.
Jesus.
I mean,
I thought all of pornography
was genuine orgasms.
This has really opened my eyes.
Anyway, sorry, go ahead.
I'll do a couple more.
You go first.
Folks, I watched
Booksmart.
I really enjoyed it.
But again, what's going on?
I mean,
the praise for this thing.
It's cute. It's funny. I liked it.
I had a good time with it. I liked the music.
I liked the way it was shot. I had a good time with it.
Could we calm down a little bit?
How was
Jonah Hill's sister
the biggest star in America?
Like, I just don't understand.
How was Jonah Hill a star in America?
I thought the two girls
were charming. I really did.
I don't know the other girl's name, but she was great.
Karen Beaver?
Okay.
Karen Beaver was in the porn, though, that we were discussing earlier.
But I don't have much
to say about it. I mean, it's entertaining, and I get why
people like it. They're both movies that are, like, kind of
cute. But I find
the praise for things to be getting
scary, in a way, to be honest.
And I
talked to everybody, and they're like, yeah, I liked it.
But the discussion around these movies is like,
we've reinvented film.
I just don't get how, look,
this is what I don't get.
Well, you love Olivia Wilde as a director.
I do. She's my favorite director.
She did do a good job. And I like Olivia Wilde.
She did a good job. What's that?
Oh, I know. I was kidding.
Go ahead.
Did you hate Booksmart?
Hold on.
What's that?
A lot of T's there.
Yes. Yes.
Okay.
Are you an aspiring filmmaker?
Well, why are you
annoyed?
No, but, I mean, look,
I hear you.
Olivia Wilde has had to put up with
nothing.
Olivia Wilde has never had a single issue in her life.
We don't know that.
I thought she did a surprisingly good job.
I know.
She did a good job.
Okay.
Well, you need to understand, Miss,
you're not
as, Miss, as a non -white.
You need
to understand something.
These privileged white men,
these privileged
white men
need to step aside
so these privileged
white women can have a shot at things.
Black, Latino, Asian,
you're just going to have to fucking
wait.
No, I'm kidding.
I'm not really kidding, but you know what I mean.
No, but here's
what bothers me about it.
We used to live in a creative culture where,
like, for instance, Terminator is a good one.
And, ooh, we're going to be talking about Terminator in a little bit.
Terminator is a good example.
When James Cameron came out with the first Terminator movie,
Harlan Ellison sued him because it was
too similar to a Harlan Ellison short
story, Dealing with the Glass Hand,
that was also turned into the most popular episode of
The Outer Limits, the original Outer Limits.
Harlan Ellison's name
is now accredited in every
Terminator movie as being one of the creators
of the characters or whatever.
I just don't understand how we've gotten to a place
creatively, and this is not a gender
issue or anything,
where the advertisements
at this point can say, this
is the female superbad
I always wanted to see, and
it's literally the same
exact movie, and nobody
goes, well, you just took
the movie. Like, it's the same
well, like, I don't understand why that's
just okay now. But you haven't seen the movie.
You told me, though, it was... It's not
identical, and she
is... It's a plot where
two nerds, one
skinny, one fat, both want to go to
a party and have to figure out
how to get to the party. I mean, that's superbad.
That's superbad. In the movie,
in the original, it was fat Jonah Hill
and skinny, weird, Michael
Sarah.
Well, one of these girls is a lesbian.
Did you know that?
What a twist.
That's not a plot point!
There's also a
bizarre five -minute scene where the
girls are Barbie dolls, where they
hallucinate that they're Barbie dolls. That scene
didn't really connect with the audience I saw it with.
you know, I didn't... I did not have the issues
that you had. I thought it was...
it was cute. But I get what you're saying.
I mean, Olivia Wilde
should, you know, maybe she put in the time.
Maybe she did a short film that was amazing we don't know
about. I don't know. But
she showed some talent.
I mean, I gotta say, she directed
it well.
Alright. Yeah.
I'm gonna...
And she was, you know, she was born with
you know, a lot of things against
her. She's got that ugly mug.
Yeah.
You know.
What? I know Olivia Wilde, but
what has she ever been in?
House?
Was she in every season of House?
Doctor House MD?
I never saw it. And she was in the OC, that's right.
Yeah, she was good in that.
I mean, maybe I'm a fan.
What the hell is drinking, buddy? I don't know drinking, buddy.
Okay.
We got this lady in the back all wound up.
All wound up about
female directors.
Taking a strange turn.
We gotta find something she likes quick.
I would actually like to talk about the episode of
The Twilight Zone that I really liked.
There's an episode with Chris O'Dowd
called The Blue Scorpion.
And I thought that Chris O'Dowd was
tremendous in it. The plot is
I'd like to quickly add that Chris O'Dowd
follows me on Twitter.
Oh, I doubt it.
Folks?
The Blue Scorpion is an episode about where Chris
O'Dowd finds his hippie father having shot
himself,
parent suicide in his home.
And it doesn't make any sense because he's like,
my father is super hippie and super
anti -gun. I don't understand.
And then he finds a gun, the gun that his
father supposedly used, and it's got a blue
scorpion on the handle. And he looks up
the gun to sell it because he wants to get rid of it.
And a gun
dealer tells him that this gun is worth
like $100 ,000.
And there's a legend that surrounds it.
That this gun, called The Blue Scorpion,
finds you.
And it kind of unfolds from there.
Well, it does unfold from there. That's how plots work.
But it does unfold from there.
And I thought that this was actually
a very, very cool
episode because it was one
of the only ones that I saw, and I saw
most of them. I think I missed two or three.
It was one of the only episodes
I saw where they really
got the spirit of what
The Twilight Zone was.
It was like when there was a point to be
made, they made the point
and they made it very sort of
elegantly and not
beating you over the head with a stick.
But they didn't feel that
every single episode had to have
a point. They didn't start with
message first. And I
thought that this was one of the only episodes
in this season where they didn't put message
first and then beat
you in the face with a 2x4 with that
message. And then
also layer the message with all this weird shit
that didn't need to be in there that made it convoluted.
So I really like the episode.
I would suggest watching it.
Are you going to do the Rogan one?
The Joe Rogan episode
of The Twilight Zone?
Seth Rogan.
That's the other one that I watched.
I'm going to talk about that last.
I'm not going to comment, but
Is anyone watching the new Twilight Zone?
Good. Don't give your money to
me.
Has anyone watched Homecoming?
With Julia Roberts?
Has anyone watched
Home Alone 2?
Lost in New York.
Directed by
Olivia Wilde.
The Sticky Bandits.
I saw all of Homecoming
on a plane. I had
watched the pilot on three different occasions
and was so bored that I went cross -eyed.
But I was on a plane
and I was like, all right, I got a five -hour
flight. I'm going to watch this five -hour
show in its entirety. And if you
get past those early kind of boring
ones, it's a really cool show.
I loved it. I thought it was awesome.
You forget the star power of Julia Roberts.
I mean, A, I guess she's
been doing things, but I feel like I haven't seen her in a movie in a long time.
And she is so
good. She's great.
I like her in a drama.
The kid in it was great. I wish I knew his name
and I don't. I've never seen him before,
but he was great. He's awesome.
Canna Valley is always delivers as
the resident Italian guy with a temper.
Yeah.
I kept waiting,
I will say, for it to go nuts
because it built up so much tension
that I really wanted it to go nuts.
And it doesn't. Maybe they're planning a season two.
I don't know. It's a show based on a podcast,
which I hate that it even works.
But it also makes me wonder if maybe
we make this into an Amazon
prime drama starring Sandy Bullock
as me and
Tiffany Haddish as you.
But I
absolutely enjoyed
the hell out of it. A lot of twists and turns.
And the coolest thing about it was I recognized
a piece of music in
like the third episode or something. I was like, what is this?
And I looked it up. All of the score
to that show are scores
from movies. From 70s
thrillers, science fiction,
etc. Which I thought was really cool.
Put somebody out of work. But what are you going to do?
I mean, we got these self -checkout things at the
grocery store. Nobody's going to have a job in five years.
And that's Trump's America.
It hits, it creates
the tone so perfectly.
They have all these sort of Hitchcockian
music beds. I bought
the Andromeda Strain
vinyl because
I heard a piece of music.
That's something you're going to listen to a lot.
Every morning.
And every time I'm about to have
sex, I put on the Andromeda
Strain movie,
I mute it, and then I put the soundtrack
on to go along.
But no,
I bought that soundtrack because a piece of music
in one of the final episodes
of Homecoming,
I was like, that's
amazing. And it took me forever
to figure out what it was
because it's not a soundtrack to Homecoming. You have to figure
out what the song is. Somebody from the AV
Club did the music from every
episode, which was great.
Sam Esmail, who did
Mr. Robot,
R2 -D Douche.
Have you seen
this Trump?
Talk about Mr.
Robot, babe.
The first season of Mr. Robot, I thought
was awesome, but also
that guy's a good writer, but he's a really incredible
director. The second season of Mr.
Robot was a crime, frankly.
It was embarrassing. I dropped out, but I
think the first three got better.
But Sam Esmail,
when he does a movie, is going to be a big deal.
He's an incredible director. He does a great job
of ratcheting up tension with visuals.
All right.
Very good show.
The podcast is actually great, too.
The podcast stars
Kathleen Keener.
Or is it Katherine Keener? I always fuck it up.
She's wonderful in it.
Strangely, David
Schwimmer
plays the Canna Valley role, and
David Schwimmer is
awesome in the podcast.
Schwimmer and App Pupil is awesome.
If you want to support another pedophile, go see that.
Brian Singer, not Schwimmer.
Schwimmer plays
a prick in that podcast.
I'm like, man, it's fucking Schwimmer.
Friends, he's always
banging his head on stuff and falling down
the steps.
I don't know about that.
No, it's true.
I always hated Ross when I was a kid.
I watch it now, and he makes me laugh.
He's great.
Chandler is mugging the shit out.
Chandler, I used to love. They used to call me Chandler in high school.
But every line is like,
could I
be?
And you're like, hey, you're supposed to be playing a real human being.
He does this.
Did you
think about it?
Yeah.
The joke that put me off of Friends
Forever, where I was like, I'll never watch this fucking show
ever again, was
Phoebe's complaining that somebody
keeps stealing her food at work from the fridge.
And she goes, and Chandler goes,
what did you do, Phoebes? And she goes,
I put a note in there and said, keep your grubby mitts off
my food. And then Chandler goes,
and exactly when
did the rest of the cast of Annie
join up with you?
And I was like, I'm fucking done.
That is the most forced fucking joke
I have ever heard.
And it bombed here, too.
All right.
Jesus Christ. Podcast
audiences are tough. I'm used
to stand up where they're like, keep the laughter
rolling. Podcast
people are like, we'll just stare in support
sometimes.
Fuck, guys.
On the plus side, Joe, you
did spit a lot while doing it.
And I
was chewing the scenery a bit with
my Chandler.
Last but not least,
I will talk about the finale
of The Twilight Zone, which was called Blurry
Man.
I saw it.
Look, you guys
should watch it, so I'll just tell you what happened.
It opens on
Seth Rogen. He plays a writer. He's
trying to break his script.
He can't
write the scene properly. He's beating himself
up. He's calling himself a hack. And then
suddenly he has the idea, I'll start
my script with the nuclear explosion
because he's writing about a nuclear fallout thing.
He writes it. He's excited.
His girlfriend comes home.
He's like, honey, we need to celebrate. Why
so glum? He opens the curtains
and then exactly what he wrote is happening
outside. Pretty cool fucking opening
to a show. Again, very Twilight
Zone -y. And then Peel
comes in, does the monologue,
and then Peel in the middle
of the monologue breaks character and goes,
I think we can beat this.
This monologue isn't good. And then camera
pulls out and
it's them shooting the episode
of The Twilight Zone. So I'm like,
this is cool. Like I'm
with this, cool. So then he talks
to the writer of the episode, says we need
a better monologue written. She
goes off to write the new monologue
and then she starts experiencing all
this weird shit where a blurry
man is following, meaning
because he's blurry.
Well, it's not like
Candy Man. There wasn't one Milky Way
in that fucking picture.
And it's kind of cool. It's like
a person writing an episode of The Twilight
Zone is in her own episode of The Twilight
Zone and she says
before it all starts to go crazy,
you know, this is The Twilight Zone.
It needs to be about something. It can't just
be scary. And Peel's
kind of like, yeah, whatever.
And I like that they're sort of
self -effacing about it and they're kind of saying
this is what people expect and we don't always
have to do that and whatever. So I felt like
in this final episode, and
again, the odowed one was the second to last
episode, I felt like they finally kind of got
to me the groove
of what this was supposed to be about.
Long story short,
you eventually find
out this blurry man that is following
her. He reveals himself.
And this is where it gets
questionable.
It's Rod Serling.
And he's dead.
In real life.
So they had
to make like a graphic
that looked like if you
cut a Rod Serling
face off the back of a cereal
box and pasted it to your
face and then went like, I'm
Rod Serling.
It did look great.
CBS doesn't have that Scorsese
de -aging
money or whatever the fuck you need
to do that.
And then Rod Serling takes the writer off
into the Twilight Zone.
And then the end of the episode
is a soliloquy, as always
at the end of every Twilight Zone, but the end of this one
is a soliloquy from
a Serling sound
alike. It's a very nice
gesture to the fans.
It's very sweet.
It's a nice wink to the camera.
I liked it.
I also understand
why you did not like it.
Hey, I wasn't going to say anything.
No, I mean
basically you're asked
the appeal of the Twilight Zone is you're doing these
dilemmas that every man has to deal with, every woman has to
deal with. The dilemma in this one is
a writer who can't
come up with a good episode of the Twilight Zone
because they're living in the shadow of Rod Serling.
Who is that for?
It's for the writing staff of the Twilight Zone.
I had no interest in it at all.
Rogan was good in it.
The girl was good in it.
Everybody was good in it.
It was a little odd, but I liked it.
One cool thing that they did in it is
they say at one point they're going back
she's telling the staff
I keep seeing this blurry man.
So the editors go back
through the episodes of the whole
season in the episode and they go look there he is
in that episode and there he is in that episode.
And apparently if you go back he actually is
in all the episodes.
It's a pretty cool little
wink to camera thing, but that's just not enough
unfortunately
to carry.
And also imagine if you're like a 13 year old
who's like cool I love Get Out and I'm going to
check out Jordan Peele's new thing, but you don't know anything
about Rod Serling. And that's the
reveal of this hour long thing.
Is this like old square dude
coming out of a blur?
It didn't do anything.
Alright, fair enough. Like I said
it was a nice love letter to fans. I enjoyed it
but I also get why people wouldn't like it.
I have another
scary stuff giveaway for
this show. Hopefully people are
as excited as they were last show.
That quote again?
I'll take it.
I mean talk about some ingrateful
people. I'm giving away free shit here.
No, I'm kidding guys.
I also want to plug something
and we're not paid to do this, but if you're
ever in Lansing, Michigan
and you're a video game collector, go to a store
called Swap Meat.
It is the best video game store
I have ever been in. Ever.
Ever. If I lived in Chicago
I literally would drive three hours
to go to it. That's no bullshit.
So check it out if you are there.
But that's not where I bought this game.
I bought this at GameStop.
Well all the shit I bought at Swap Meat I kept
because it was too cool.
But anyway,
look, old school gamers,
Mega Man
legacy collection,
Mega Man 1 through 6
all on one disc
for your Xbox One. Who's got an Xbox
One? Stand up.
I mean, we got
I see two. Okay. Three.
We got three, right? Nobody else?
Okay, we need to ask
a trivia question. Whoever
gets the question right gets the Xbox
One.
You got one?
Because I thought
Oh, I got one.
What is the
I think this is good.
We've talked about this
film a lot on the podcast.
Jeepers Creepers.
What does the creeps
License plate say?
This guy got it.
Beating you.
There you go.
Mega Man 1 through 6.
What did I think that it said?
Beating goo.
Beating goo. All right.
I was fucking beating goo.
I didn't remember that,
but thank you.
New Psycho?
Yeah, I mean, I guess we got to talk about
Did anyone see the new Sonic the Hedgehog
design?
It is so much worse than the other one.
Look, please look it up when you get out of here.
Like, holy shit. But yeah, they're just gonna keep
doing it. It's like, so everyone is like,
Oh, my God, this one is worse. Are we gonna
triple down on it? Are we just gonna
let everyone in America decide what
we watch as entertainment now?
What is this, The Twilight
Zone?
I'm praying that this is the case. I'm praying
that the guy that was like, sorry, what were you
designing? I'm praying that behind closed doors, he was like,
Yeah, you want it redesigned? You fucks.
I'll fucking redesign it.
Sorry, guys. It sucks, right?
You motherfuckers.
And then made it worse on purpose.
I love Spite, is what I'm getting at.
Oh, it's terrible. I mean, the hair on it
made me sick.
By the way, I've never played Sonic.
I don't care. I just love watching this
unfold.
They probably put a hundred million dollars
into this shit, and it's gonna come out and make
nothing. I love it. It's a great business.
Before we
move on to our film for the evening,
what did you think of that Terminator Dark Fate trailer?
Heavy on the Hamilton.
Heavy on the Hamilton. I was happy to see her.
I was happy to see Hamilton.
Schwarzenegger is apparently
playing a man that lives in a cabin.
I'm like, is he just gonna
be the guy they modeled the Terminator
after? Like, I don't give a shit about that.
Is that what it's gonna be?
It looks, it looked
cheap to me, if I'm being honest.
It looked like a direct -to -video
kind of thing. But also, too,
John Connor is, like, apparently
in a cameo in this thing.
Furlong? No, not Furlong.
Jesus Christ.
Come on, baby. Come on, baby.
Easy money. Have you seen Furlong?
If they couldn't get Furlong, they would have cast
Rosie O'Donnell. You wouldn't be able to tell the difference at this point.
They look
the same! They look the same!
No, it's not Furlong. It's fucking,
it's somebody new that's gonna just play the
character, but he's barely in it.
And this whole thing of just, like,
because I was
you. And it's like, how many
fucking times are you guys
gonna do this? How many times
are you gonna bring a new savior
into the mix? And, you know,
it was like, Cameron's coming back
and for once, I was like, you know
what? I've been too hard on James
Cameron. I gotta give this
certainly true. I gotta give this guy
a pass. He's coming back to do
the new Terminator. I'm excited.
I wanna see what he does. And I saw
this trailer and I was like, I was
right. He fucking sucks.
James Cameron
stinks.
I think he just did, like, the story for it, but
yes. I don't care what he did.
He fucking stinks. It looks fucking
ridiculous. And how many fucking
car chases are you gonna have
where the fucking Terminator goes out
into the trunk of the fucking
the hood of the car he's driving and
jump off onto the other? How many fucking times
are they gonna do that? Yeah. Oh my god.
But have you ever seen a car chase where
a big truck in slow motion fell
over?
Cause that
took me by surprise. Should we
open these gifts? No, no.
No, I don't wanna do that. I wanna know what it
is. We should get to our movie. We're at an hour
and twenty minutes right now. Oh, Jesus Christ.
Yeah, let's get to our movie. Alright. Well,
we'll open it, but let's talk about
everybody's favorite rom -com. Henry
Portugal's serial killer.
We'll do this at the end.
We'll do it at the end.
I don't like opening the
gift. Thank you for bringing the gifts. You never have to
do that. No. And apparently most of you
felt that way cause only one person brought a gift.
But never, don't bring it here.
You being here is the gift. And I don't like
opening it on stage cause I feel like it's like my fucking
baby shower or something.
Oh, Junior's gonna
like this. I don't like
doing that shit. It's like, it's weird.
Anyway,
folks, could I have a shot of tequila
silver, please?
Cause I gotta pee
real bad and why not dump more booze
on top of it?
Henry, portrait of a serial
killer. Did you know this?
One of the fine
hellions in attendance told me this outside.
Directed by the same guy
that directed wild things.
I did know that.
John McNaughton, who was on
Joe Bob's show the other night
and was a great interview. Thank you.
I guess I'll get it for you, Joe.
That was a shot of Joe, not you, honestly.
Do something. Yes. Thank you.
No, John McNaughton, who
did wild things and like, you know,
he's a good director and was
a great interview if you have Shudder.
But the movie, man,
I wish I hadn't watched it, you know?
And apparently Henry's home, this will
make you feel comfortable, is like two blocks
from here.
Well, it was
apparently it was based on a guy
and it was true, but
the guy claimed he had killed like 200 people
and that wound up being like massively
exaggerated. But it was based in
fact. But to me,
I mean,
have everyone seen it? Everyone
watched it? It was on Shudder.
Real quick, sorry.
If you haven't seen it, the movie
it's what you think it is.
It's
literally like when you watch Peter Pan.
You're like, oh, it's Peter Pan.
It's about a guy named Henry who's a
serial killer. That's basically
the ins and outs of the entire film.
And he gets his buddy to get in on it
with him named Otis. And
you know, we'll get into the deeper details later,
but that's the basics of it.
Yeah, I mean, it's a very almost documentary
like portrait of a man
killing people through the streets of Chicago.
Michael
Rooker is very good in it. The guy
who plays Otis is
he's great in it to the extent that
I hope that he is dead.
And not out
terrorizing the streets.
The Otis guy
makes Henry look like somebody you'd like to go get a
beer with.
Well, that's the thing. So yeah, the movie
centers around Henry, who's
already a sadistic serial killer.
And then his buddy and roommate, Otis,
gets in on it. And then they make Otis
you know, clearly
it's like an executive network
executive note, like, well, how are we going to make him like Henry?
And he's like, oh, we're going to put this other
guy in that's way worse.
And then you kind of think Henry looks
OK. Yeah, it's like Henry's kind of goading him into it.
But then at a certain point, he starts to like it way
too much. Yeah, it's one of those
it's that, you know, typical story.
I thought I had seen it when I was a kid and I
realized I had this book
The Entertainment Weekly, 100 Best Movies
in Every Genre. And I was trying to see
everything in it. And Henry
was very high in the thriller list.
And I thought I had finished it. But I remember
I remember the part I got out
because I wanted to get out
in this viewing of the movie. But when
it gets to that, you know
What's the part? They make you watch the
home video of the
killing a family, killing and sexually
assaulting a family. That's hard. And I
was a kid and I, you know, I
basically had to go up to my tree house and
pray or whatever I was doing at the time.
I was a very cool kid. But
I despised
it and then it got worse when I finished it.
It actually gets worse from there.
That home invasion scene
is so fucking disturbing.
It makes that goddamn
Clockwork Orange
home invasion look like a fucking
Willy Wonka sequence or something.
You're just like, Jesus Christ
Almighty. And then Joe Bob,
when he's interviewing McNaughton, they kind of had a good
chuckle about the woman being
deeply traumatized
by performing in the scene. And their
too was kind of like, yeah, you read the script, you know,
but like it, I assume
it felt sort of like actually
having that happen to you. It is so
realistic that it's like,
I mean, I hope they choreographed it to the point where everyone
was comfortable, but clearly they didn't
if this woman had a nervous breakdown after.
It's like how they say, you know, child actors.
They're like, oh, you know, he's fine. We talked about it.
It's like, how do you know?
Things they have kid actors do in these things is
insane. But anyway, go on.
Well, yeah, he snaps
the 15 year old kid's neck.
It's a rough scene.
By the way, it's not like you're treading lightly
before you get to this part.
A lot of bloody
fucking heads and
bleeding breasts. It's
fucking disturbing, man.
There's a scene where they kill
this big fat guy
who sells him a TV illegally,
like a stolen TV. They kill him with
a pen. I don't even know what the fuck they're
stabbing him with. A soldering
iron. And then he busts
a TV on the. This is actually, it gets
kind of crazy. You're like, what is this?
Nightmare on Elm Street 6. Yeah, I mean, he
smashes a TV on the guy's head and then Henry
goes, turn the TV on.
And they do. And the guy's like
I mean, that
stuff couldn't have disturbed me any less.
I didn't care. That's why I found
the turn to realism in the
last act particularly
rough because I was like, this isn't so
bad. And then things get real. One of the most
upsetting moments in the movie is
so Henry
lives with Otis and Otis's sister
comes to stay because her marriage
has fallen apart and her brother Otis is like
I told you that guy was a bum
and blah blah blah blah blah.
Otis very clearly has an
interest in his sister's thing.
Here's the thing. Otis tells
his sister eventually Henry was in jail
because he killed his mother.
And he can't remember how he did it.
Not a great sign.
It's that classic Joker from
Dark Knight thing where every time he tells
the story it's different.
So you're like, did he make it up?
Did he not? Is he not remembering?
But she asks him
how did you kill your mother and he tells her two
versions of the story and they contradict obviously.
And then she goes on to tell a story about
how she was
molested by her father
and this is supposed to be a bonding
moment between the two characters.
Which I get it. Like pain.
You bond through pain. But still it's not
exactly fucking people
sharing their dreams at the Carnegie
Deli in New York or something like that.
So it's an upsetting scene.
And then the next scene after
that after Otis and his sister
have been just like brother and sister
he asks her to get him a beer
and then she brings him the beer and then
he pulls her in to make out with her.
And yeah.
I didn't write it miss.
He pulls her in to make out with her.
He did punch it up. He did add some jokes
later to the script.
He pulls her in to make out with her and then
Henry once again, how do you make Henry
sort of redeemable? Henry goes, Otis
no.
She's your sister.
So Henry's got boundaries people.
That's what I'm getting at.
And then eventually he gets Otis to kill with
him and then it just
here's the thing.
It is a beautifully shot film.
It is a brilliantly written film.
It is a magnificently
acted film. I don't know
that I can recommend it
as a good movie to people.
It's very upsetting
and it gets into that
area where you're like
on the first show tonight when you were talking about those
pedophile documentaries.
You get to that point where you're like
do we need to see this right now?
We know this stuff exists.
We know it's terrible. It's all I can do not to wake up
screaming without watching all this stuff.
It's a rough fucking flick
man. It's a rough flick and I watched
it as I said in the last show
before I had to go on
stage in a bowling alley
that looked like every
single interior location of
Henry Portrait of a Serial Killer.
So I'm not only becoming disgusted.
I'm becoming afraid that a man
is going to come in and smash a TV over my
head while I'm on stage.
I mean it's an upsetting flick man.
I mean the live
scene after the
scene they film of this family killing
they're watching it later and like
turned on by it it seems.
And in the end then Otis does
assault his sister and Henry
our hero comes in to
rescue her
and winds up cutting off Otis's
head and then it's like
the end. No that's not
the end. That's not even close
to the end. Maybe it was the end
for me. The sister then says
the sister then says to Henry I love you
because she doesn't know he's a serial killer this whole
time. She doesn't know and she goes
I love you let's let's run away together
and Henry says in the middle of the movie
we got the trick to serial killing
is you got to keep moving. You can't
stop. You can never do it the same way twice.
You got to keep moving. That's true though.
So then they...
I've always
that's always been my philosophy for dancing.
So anyway
so they go to a motel and then
the next morning he leaves the motel
alone
and then you see him in the next scene pull
over and he takes a suitcase out of the trunk
and you realize that's the only
person that's ever loved him in
a fucking that he cut it.
It's rough stuff people.
It's not a walk in the park this
flick. It's not a lot of fun.
This could never
when this movie came out
it was one of the first movies ever
to be rated NC 17.
There was a lot of hoopla around it.
They said what can we do to get it to an R and they
said nothing.
It is too disturbing.
If you gave us a blank piece of film
we'd reconsider it but
we can't make this anything but NC 17.
The biggest champion I think who got
most people to see it was Chicago's own
one of my all time heroes
Roger Ebert who gave it four stars and everything.
What was Ebert's review though?
Because I'm torn with something like this
is this just appraised
or is this actually
saying something? I don't think it's
saying anything. I don't know.
I of course celebrate it's right
to exist
at a time where I always feel like
shit. It made me feel like triple shit.
I didn't want to see it. I wished I hadn't
seen it. I'm sorry if that was too real for you folks.
But I really
aggressively didn't like it and I
wish that I could scrub it from my brain.
Eternal Sunshine style.
But now
Henry II.
Did anybody see that? That I haven't
seen. I think that's a much more. It's like American
Psycho 2 where it's like so far
off the grid like it doesn't even count.
But I'm not going to be watching.
Is there a Henry II? Yeah there is.
Wait what? There is a Henry II.
I thought you were going to make like a joke like it was about
Caddyshack 2 or something like that.
No. Yeah. Henry II the new
batch. You know.
Henry II lost in New York.
I hate to. I didn't see. Henry II
Electric Boogaloo. The oldest one.
I'd hate to take. I'd hate
to talk anymore about this film
and destroy the electric
energy in this room right now.
It's a Chicago movie. I'm sorry people.
I told you we should have done
Child's Play.
We did discuss Child's Play.
But we'll do that when they bring the new one out in like
two weeks. You want to talk about a good poster
campaign. These posters where
Shucky is killing the Toy Story dolls
are so awesome. That's great.
Like it's such in the spirit of those movies. It's so
perfect. But I will
and this is this is sort of another
scary stuff thing but it's worth checking out.
Mike Patton fans. Anybody
in here? Great.
Mike Patton of Faith No More fame
and Mr. Bungle fame. He's got a band
Phantomus right?
Phantomus has
whether you're a Mike Patton fan or not. Phantomus
has an amazing record called The Directors
Cut. And it's
12 covers of
dark film
themes in
the style of that band. They really do
like their own take on it. And it's
got The Godfather. It's got Rosemary's
Baby. It's got
Spider Baby. It's really a cool record.
But they do do
an awesome cover of the Henry Portrait
of a Serial Killer.
And he adds the lyric to the
melody of it's
either you or them because that's the big line
of the movie. Henry goes it's either you or them.
So then they do the theme and it goes
it's either you or
them.
And it's pretty fucking awesome.
If he did it
that indicates to me that he really
loves Henry Portrait of a Serial Killer.
And to me that would strike you off
of my friend list.
I want to
know so bad what Ebert said
that's so interesting to me.
Ebert usually
you know we talked about it when we did the Silent Night
Deadly Night review. Ebert was like
this disgusting
piece of shit should be banned.
He was so offended that Santa Claus
was killing people. I'm just
shocked that he loved this movie.
I think it was that nobody is mistaking
that movie for a kids movie and
putting Santa in the kid. I
got it even though I don't agree with it. Kids
believe in Santa and you want that to go on as long
as it can I hope.
This movie is the word serial
in the title. Maybe kids thought it was a
serial movie. That's true.
Anyway it's
look it's
note for note it's a good movie.
Content wise that's a whole
different situation. This is like
listening to a G .G. Allen record folks.
Do it at your
own risk. I don't know how you're
going to feel afterwards.
But that's Henry Portrait of a Serial
Killer. Thank you.
Thank you everybody.
Thank you so much
for being here tonight. Thank you especially to those
who came from out of town which always
blows us away. We really appreciate it.
Guys we can't express enough
how much we appreciate the support. Are you all
able to hang out and drink with us for a little while?
Let's do it.
Please hang out.
Please talk. Let's interact.
Let's have fun. Let's party. Let us please show
you how much we appreciate you guys.
Thank you for being here. And hang on.
Oh.
You're really great at momentum aren't you?
Nerds ropes.
It feels very heavy for a bag
that seems to contain candy. Who is
this from?
Thank you sir. Good lord.
Oh okay I know what this is
because you reached out to me.
The greatest candy of all time
has made a comeback.
Giant Chewy Nerds.
Yeah it's good.
You reached out to me
and I was like
I was like oh awesome you know
I can't wait and then as I
logged off I was like
this motherfucker is lying to me.
I started like drooling when I thought about them.
And I'm off candy. I don't even do candy
but I'm going to tear the shit out of this.
Liz also gave us a big bag of candy
which we should have talked about on Candyman. Sorry Liz
we didn't know. Tasted Cakes?
Oh that's Philly.
Joseph?
Excellent.
I don't want to hold it right now.
Thank you very much.
We'll keep it in the bag. We appreciate it.
Is that everything?
I hopefully will not get so drunk
that I'm in bed and I'm like wait a minute
I've got that 8 pound bag
of candy and tasty cakes.
Have you ever
had a butterscotch crimpet?
Yes. You have? I have.
I was going to say first.
Thank you very much.
Thank you to all of you. We will see you next time
and we will see you in hell.
you