jota rosa here solo flying solo
For this patreon post dedicated to you the dear fans
My dear buddy patty walsh partner in crime was uh, or has been putting up some solo pats movie corners
And I thought why not?
I do the same
Because I will not be outdone
Life is a competition if not a war
And you play to the death
I challenge thee walsh
I'm kidding, of course
I love what pat's doing with the solo movie stuff and I wanted to do something similar
as a additional thank you to the fans who have been standing by and supporting us so
So amazingly uh here at the patreon only version of this show
Usually in the future i'll probably do
Yeah, you know like joe's scary stuff solo posts. Um, and i've got some stuff
In the tank that i'm sort of reviewing and
looking at and
You know games i'm playing movies i'm watching dvd sets. I'm procuring books
i'm reading that sort of stuff that i'd like to talk about but
For this inaugural post for january, uh, I wanted to do, uh more along the lines of a news psycho
Or a rant if you will, I mean maybe rants can just become
Something that fall under the umbrella of joe's scary stuff, uh, for those of you listening to this
You're familiar with the show. Obviously, you know that uh
I piss and moan there's no way to dress it up. I could say, you know, oh I you know, I like to
I don't even know what a positive way of saying it is. I couldn't even think of a positive version
or phrasing, uh, you know a descriptor of
I read piss and moan that's just all there is to it
Um, so two things, uh again that fall sort of under the blanket of the new psycho
Uh that i'm going to talk about today
Uh, you know not too long not too short just enough just enough i'm sitting here in my new
Apartment in new york city not new apartment. It's new to me. I'm newly living in it the building
I think has been here for a thousand years
Uh, but i'm enjoying it out here. There's a tremendous amount of street noise
I don't think the microphone is picking any of it up
but um
Apparently every day on my street. There's a festival of some sort
I uh
You know inside my apartment just you know, just hearing what is seeping through the window
noise wise
I would think it was the mummers parade in philadelphia
Happening on new year's day and then I look out my window and there appears to be no one
Uh, so I it's a strange phenomenon that that occurs here in new york. It's just a noisy city not complaining
uh
It I actually kind of enjoy it as some background, uh
Some back like a background backing sound bed to to my life now, uh, I like it
I like the energy, but hopefully it's not seeping into this recording
Uh, that's the one time when it's not ideal. Um, but anyway
Here in new york smoking a ciggy
Sitting at my desk
Got a coke zero next to me. That's i'm living la but i'm in new york. This is an la thing
The the coke zero and the ciggy
pre
What time is it? Well, I guess for most people it's
Pre dinner at this point. It's pre lunch for me barely post breakfast
Um, anyway
Here's the first thing I want to talk about
As a man
who travels
This great country of ours doing stand -up. I spent a lot of time on airplanes
My airline of choice is delta
Uh, I find that delta seems to operate with regularity
Uh, they don't have the cancellation and delay issues that uh, for example an american airlines has had at least with my
experiences with them
um
And they treat their customers pretty well. They're pretty fair. I've been a sky miles member for a long time
Uh, they've hooked me up with
little favors and things that they didn't really have to necessarily
uh, but they've just always seemed to
Care or be grateful that you know that a returning customer returns
So i'm not knocking delta as an airline
Um, however
Uh
Okay. Well look before I get into the negative before I get into the however, I will also say in addition
To my enjoying their uh treatment of me as a customer
Delta has a great entertainment thing going on, you know
Most flights have the little monitors and you get a slew if not a gaggle
Of free pictures and tv shows you can watch
It's pretty incredible man, you know stuff that's barely out of theaters some of it's still in theaters
an array of classics, uh
Just it's just a ton of stuff to pick from it's really really great
however
They've done something recently, I don't know why i'm not quite sure why I can speculate
Uh, but they've clearly
Uh adopted a new code or standards code
With these films because everything they are showing now on the airplane
Um, and I say everything because it's been the last four or five movies i've watched
This has been the case
They're editing these things
not
To fit the screen size and not for length. They're editing these things for content. They're bleeping and redubbing
Foul language
um
Uh, yeah, no, they do they bleep. I was gonna say maybe they don't bleep they bleep they bleep
Delta bleeps
And
Okay, so here's what's crazy. Okay. So anyway
I watched deadpool 2
And it was heavily
Edited like and when I say heavily edited, I don't mean down to
You know a light 7 30 p .m
You know soft r hard pg -13 i'm talking
You could play this thing at nine o 'clock in the morning
In a rectory and you know and and have no worries that anybody's going to get offended here. These things are sterilized
To the point of it not being enjoyable with certain movie. You can't watch a clean deadpool 2
They tried to release that clean edit in theaters nobody liked it everybody thought it sucked
The whole point of deadpool is the foul language and the quips and the quips often are dirty or sex related
That's what makes deadpool deadpool. That's why people like that character in those movies
When you cut all that out
It's like why even showing deadpool, man
Just don't show deadpool
But that was an extreme example I was like, okay, you know, I guess maybe
Yeah, this this they're not doing this to every movie. I don't know
Maybe I don't know. I don't get it
But this is the one that put me over the edge grumpy old men
I was flying home for christmas
I was actually flying from la to new york to move to new york right at christmas time
I planned things very well very smart
I'm flying back
It's like december
13th or something
Getting right into the spirit of the holidays. I'm on a plane. It's a five -hour flight
It's a late night flight. I can't sleep. I think you know what i'm gonna do
I'm watching grumpy old men
Fantastic holiday movie starts at thanksgiving ends at christmas
This is perfect
This is the perfect movie to watch in between thanksgiving and christmas
It covers all your bases
I put this thing on
It's edited
It's grumpy old men at its starting point at its bluest is a movie you can watch with your nana
At its bluest
And this thing was edited now. Here's the thing with the editing
I
could get it like I get it if you were doing it for like nudity and violence because I
Remember flying on planes before any of these films were edited
And you know sometimes you'd be sitting next to you know an older person or a kid or something
And then like some graphic like tit scene comes on and you're like, oh boy
You know and you're like trying to cover the screen with your hand. It's it's awkward
You know the same goes for extreme, you know gore or something like that some guys getting his head blown off or something and you know
you're sitting next to a
You know a seven -year -old who's weeping
I know a lot of seven -year -olds don't fly solo on planes, but just go with the scenario for a minute here
The uh, you get what i'm saying. I get how I get how that could be offensive or weird
Uh, you know and you know the airline saying, you know, we need to be concerned about all of our customers
We don't want somebody looking over
who you know
Maybe he's flying home from being in a war or something and then you know, you're you're sitting there watching
And you know it sets the poor guy off or something. You know, you don't want that. That's no good for anybody
So I get it if it was for nudity and I totally would get it. I really would man. I get it
You know, we're not in an art gallery people aren't walking into an airplane saying i'm you know here exhibit to me
Uh, and I know what i'm in for people are on an airplane for one reason mainly is it's to travel, you know
So going on to an airplane for the content of a film
Is is like going onto an airplane for the for the quality of the food or something
I get why that
Would make sense
I don't it makes no sense with the language thing
You I you have to wear head you have to wear headphones
So unless they think
Some expert lip reading nun is sitting next to me who the fuck is going to get offended at this shit only I can hear it
And then also they still show the warning grumpy old men still had a warning at the beginning of the film again
Unedited I don't think this movie needs a warning, but they they put the warning up still. What are you warning me of?
Here's a thing that once had some words that you might have found offensive that only you can hear
And you agreed to watch it still be warned
What it doesn't make any sense and
I'd even understand the warning if this was maybe shaved down to again a hard pg 13
Even a hard pg if there is such a thing this has been edited down to a light g
They bleeped the word farted
They bleeped it remember earlier when I go, I don't know if they bleep and then I go
They bleep it's because I have my notes here and I scan down and I made a note that they bleeped the word farted
They bleeped the word
Farted this is how clean they're making
Everything can't that's like they wouldn't even do that on nickelodeon for christ's sakes
Here's another one that killed me. There's another one that killed me schmuck
Which is a word used throughout the film by walter matthal and it's
One of the best things in the whole movie is getting to hear walter matthal say schmuck
It's one of the funniest elements of the entire movie and it's a it's a runner
Throughout the movie for a reason because it's hilarious and it works every time
They bleeped schmuck get this
Replaced it with yuts
People i'm not up on my uh
Jewish american
Mild insult words
But as far as I know
schmuck is no
more offensive than yuts
Putz I would get
Because putz I know that means dick sometimes
Schmuck and yet what I don't know. I is am I wrong?
Look if you know, maybe you know, maybe you I come from an italian family
Schmuck wasn't big with italian families
You know, we're more of an asshole type
You know, that's that's kind of our thing
but if you out there from
A traditional jewish american family or non -traditional jewish american family or you know a family in other words
I'm getting at they use the word schmuck a lot and the and the word yuts a lot
Let me know if one is worse than the other because i'm ripping my hair out over this. I don't understand
I just I can't even wrap my head around it. Uh, this thing was so
Sterilized
It took all the fun out of watching it. That being said I still wept uncontrollably
Without care throughout the entire movie movie kills me
Movie kills me. Uh, it's just you know matthal going into the hospital at the end
While lemon's laying in the bed and he realizes they've wasted so many years
They don't even say you just see on his face. They've wasted so many years fighting
And then finally he's come to his senses and he realizes the guy might die and he didn't have a chance to say sorry
Again, none of this is said all in the eyes, baby. Yak with the eyes
But matthal standing there and the nurse goes friend or uh family
And he just stared he stares at her. He doesn't know what to say. He's beside himself
And then she goes friend or family, sir, and he goes friend
With the lump in his throat. Oh my god, man
That fucking levels me
Weeping on the plane uncontrollably
One o 'clock in the morning on a red -eye flight
alone
You know, it's just uh, it probably wasn't the greatest look for me, but hey, I got through it I got through it now
Let's get into an actual news story
Uh for the news psycho
This is again i'm kind of cheating here
This is a this is the news story and this comes from movieweb .com uncharted movie narrows in on venom director
reuben fleischer
Uh, if you don't know what the uncharted movie is uncharted is a video game series for sony
It's exclusively a sony video game series
The games are amazing amazing i've reviewed some of them on the show, uh, you play as the protagonist nathan drake
The games basically are like the company was like well we can't I think they're naughty made by a company called naughty dog
Uh the company clearly was like we want to make an indiana jones movie
Uh our video game of those movies, but we're not allowed to because we don't have the licensing
So, uh, let's do this other guy instead and we'll call it uncharted
Uh, it's indiana jones
You know, it's a it takes place in present day, but it's it's basically indiana jones and i'm not complaining about that
They even have a few references
uh
That I think are direct references indiana jones
They don't come right out with it, but they they feel like little winks to camera to me
I feel like they're kind of like guys. We know we're kind of doing indiana jones here nathan drake is a treasure hunter
um
It's a lot of
run -ins with pirates
uh, you know and uh
Uh, you know other rival treasure hunters and vigilante groups and militias and things like that as you
Trudge through jungles and these these uncharted territories looking for treasure and all of the treasure is related in some
Sort of you know loose way to actual history. It's very very very indiana jones nathan drake is very quippy
and uh
You know, he's a handsome guy and women love him and he's got you know
He's the best trait of indiana jones that they have poured it over is he's not flawless. He fucks up
And he gets knocked on his ass a lot and that's one of the things that
As much as I love han solo that to me is what always differed indiana jones from han solo like
Han solo might get into a sticky situation, but he talks his way out of it
You've seen indiana jones literally getting knocked on his ass like like every time he gets into the fistfight with the big guy
In the movie that happens in each episode of indiana jones
He he is clearly outmatched
He's getting the shit knocked out of him and by some stroke of luck he gets out of it in crystal skull the ants eat the
guy
Uh in the raiders the propeller hits the guy
uh in temple of doom the guy gets his
Uh scarf thing or whatever. It's called caught into the rock crushing machine and he gets pulled in
You know, that's what's cool about indiana jones you you see him be
Incredibly outmatched and get it knocked around and it's it's fun to see and nathan drake is one of those heroes as well. So
They're making an uncharted movie, which i'm sure they're hoping to turn into 17 movies
Uh, it's been having problems. It's in development. I don't know if it's development hell at this point
But it's been in development for a while. It's not really getting off the ground. They keep losing directors
Now they're trying to get the director of venom because why not
Bring in a director
Of a mediocre action movie that was poorly reviewed
to take over, uh at the helm of uh, what they hope to be a major franchise anyway, nothing against reuben fleischer, but
I just don't get how that works, but that's how it works. I guess
uh anyway
Uh my problem isn't with reuben fleischer or this movie franchise potential movie franchise losing a director
This is my problem with this franchise
Originally it was supposed to be
Uh, oh no, i'm sorry not originally. Well, who was it originally? I don't remember. Uh, oh, yeah
Okay. So originally it was supposed to be mark walberg as nathan drake
age -wise
Makes perfect sense
Walberg is kind of right in that, you know pushing 50
But still in great shape weathered guy. He's seen a thing or two knows a thing or two about a thing or two
Um, you know not my favorite actor on planet earth
But usually can deliver a nice punch and a kick and a jump from an explosion pretty well
Uh mark walberg made sense to me. I don't think he had this the suave that the character called for
Uh, you know a chris pratt has much more of the swagger needed for something like this. However
For all intents and purposes mark walberg fit the bill
They have since removed mark walberg from being the main character or he stepped out or I don't know what it is now. It is tom
holland
Tom holland
As you're weathered
I've been around the world
treasure hunting
Swashbuckling
Veteran it's
How would you feel if tom holland showed up to rescue you
Because that's the kind of guy this is supposed to be this is supposed to be a guy that rescues
You know you're tied to the post in the tent
You know like marion and raiders. This is the guy that shows up. I'm gonna get you out of here
How would you feel if tom holland?
Who looks all of
He's got the ralph machio thing going on the kid. I think is 38 years old. He looks like he's 14
If tom holland showed up to rescue you if tom holland showed up to rescue me
I'll tell you what I would do as soon as he untied me. I would overpower him and then trade him
To my captors for my own escape because I know I could overpower him. That's what I would do
What is this obsession? I mean we're swinging back in this direction again in hollywood
It's well, I'm not back again. I mean, I guess we're just still in it
But I mean, I don't know if you kids remember the 90s, but uh the 80s and the 90s
80s
It was the exact opposite of this they would cast people who were like 48 years old as high school students
Watch 90210
Some of them look of age and then you had that andrea lady in there even back then people were laughing about it
They were like this lady's like
She's like 27
And she's supposed to be playing like a 17 year old. It's absurd
It's absurd even if you go back and watch your favorite 80s movies like like if you rewatch weird science
Bill paxton in that movie, you know, he plays chet's older brother. He's not supposed to be that much older
You could if you watch that movie and they said that chet was chet's or yeah
No chet chet's the older brother. Sorry chet is why it's older brother
If you watch that movie again, and they said that chet was why it's dad. You'd believe it
You know bill paxton supposed to be like 21 in that movie he looks like he looks like a
36 -year -old man with a mortgage
It's fucking crazy
They were casting down. They were aging down so much people bitch about the irishman. Oh the cgi the it's ridiculous
It's ridiculous. Yeah, is it ridiculous?
Go back and watch the karate kid
Where they had to go into a fucking welders union and pick out six guys to fill the rolls of the cobra kai
It's absurd. They look younger now in the goddamn sequel than they did back then
Anyway
They've gone the opposite in hollywood. The pendulum has swung completely in the other direction and now it's let's cast children
as as
Weathered heroes and saviors. This is fucking ridiculous, man. Nathan drake should be robert downey jr
He's not a boy. He's iron man. He's the guy that's been through it all. This is the guy leading your expedition
This is not the guy joining it
So, I don't know if they're gonna do some goddamn prequel thing or some let's start it out when he's only 19
So we can see him coming of age that way we can get 10 extra movies out of this
Which is probably what they're fucking doing and nobody wants to see that because that's that's what's cool about uncharted
You know what everybody loved indiana jones, you know what nobody gave a shit about the young indiana jones chronicles
Did you care about the time indiana jones outsmarted al capone by playing a trumpet?
Does did anybody give a shit about that?
Nobody cared not for one fucking second about the young indiana jones chronicles. Nobody gave a shit
So if they're going that route with it, fuck it. I don't want to see it
And if they're going the other route with it, fuck it. I don't want to see it
I don't want to see it
hollywood
stop
What is this phobia you have?
Of anybody over 25 years old anymore
And I know i've named examples of people who are older than that in this in this little spiel i'm on here
Uh who are working and doing very well in hollywood, but
When it comes these are people that are long established when it comes to new shit when it comes to
Let's get something new off the ground here everybody i'm trying to get this thing made now
Now and I can't talk too specifically about it
But you know
Let's just say there are characters that are men of a certain age in this movie
and
you know
One of the people I met with was like well, why do they have to be this old?
It's like and every reason for why they have to be that old is in the script
It's in the script if you read it. It's like they can't be any younger. It wouldn't make sense
And yet people still ask that question. Well from a casting standpoint, what is it guys?
The entire country isn't 19
Okay
There are plenty of people
In their 30s in their 40s in their god forbid
50s and 60s and
Can you imagine 70s and 80s in this country?
For christ's sakes you live to be 106 now
You're just going to throw those people out the window
Those are ticket buyers you fucking morons start catering to them a little bit
I'm, not saying nathan drake in the uncharted movie
You know should have to stop every 10 minutes to take a pill and changes depends or something but jesus christ guys
Anyway, it's stupid hollywood is stupid as usual everything is stupid
But I enjoyed this and I hope you did too. I hope you didn't think it was stupid
Just the first of things to come next time I promised but I don't promise what do I promise?
I can't even make myself a promise. I'm gonna make one to you people
uh, but
It'll probably be more of a review of something. We'll see
But I hope you like this guys and thank you again for your support
I appreciate it pat and I appreciate it emily pat and I appreciate it. We all appreciate it
You guys are all the best. Take care