I'll see you in hell.
Hey, when the sound of your screams
beg I'm laughing on my dreams
and I'll say, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
I saw the new one, oh, he's like I saw a cut of it where like you could still see the wires on people like when they were you know the effects weren't done and everything and I'm like alright here we go I go yeah I read a few pages of the script and it was Liam Neeson and a Girl Scout outfit and I just was like I'm not up for this right now he goes pap this is the funniest movie I've seen in 10 years wow really and no matter how many times I tried to poke at it
he because he's like I want to stress to you it's so stupid it's very very very aggressively stupid okay the acting is horrible he's like Pamela Anderson is horrible I know we're all pretending she's a good actress now because she's not wearing makeup but she's always been a terrible actress I didn't see the last stripper or whatever that movie was called but maybe that'll change my mind he's like Liam Neeson is terrible and and
a third of his lines he lets the Irish accent slip in oh yeah um he's like there's a lot of puns in it you know just like shit puns but he's like this thing just started happening in the theater where everyone by the end of it was just completely on its wavelength and hyperventilating laughing and look I don't know I'm quite well enough to know if I buy this
I know he wasn't joking or lying about it but he was trying I go is it R rated I was just curious you know because it always kind of push the envelope is this some kind of bust it's very impressive yes
but he was like there's a scene that would probably make it R but it might be cut or scaled back but and he starts to try to tell me about it and he couldn't stop laughing to get it out I've never even heard this man laugh wow he's just like there's so much great shit in it he's like and it's it's the kind of thing like
you know Conan used to do sketches where like you know you'd see a dog's paw come into frame with a gun and shoot him or something yeah yeah he's like it's like that like it's that cheap and and and and you just you're not expecting it it's super super funny and I was like you sold me I can't wait he said Paul Walter
Howzer steals it it's hilarious okay there's no real plot to speak of but I mean they really were smart hiring the lonely island dude
the guy who did pop star and all that pop stars the closest we've come to the naked gun or you know maybe walk hard but yeah I'm pop now and I can't believe I'm saying it but I'm really pumped I'm like I'm excited to see it if yeah
on the on the lesser end of that scale just morbid curiosity you know the greater end of it that it will hopefully be funny so I'm definitely going to see it I feel like it's one of those things you can't see it alone
you got to see it in a group you know and enjoy it that way but I just saw an interview with um so is it wait there's wait no no wait the Zucker brothers so it was oh yeah they're real
pissed about it the one is Jerry Zucker the one that's yeah Jerry Zucker right he's the one that's still not or David's Jerry's dad Jerry
directed ghost and David Zucker still alive and clanky he was on he was he was surprisingly he's not into the movie right clearly he did an interview on the on David's
sorry I'm sorry Jerry Zucker is not dead I apologize for saying that I just saw I saw these three men give a talk before a screening of airplane fairly recently they're not dead I'm sorry I said that's okay but he was on that guy David
Rubin the the political pundit his podcast and um or his YouTube show whatever and they talk they were they I just watched the clip of them talking about this and he's like you know I I'm not saying it I don't
want to see it and for good reason he was like I was in talks to do the fourth movie which this is yeah and I had an idea yeah and uh he goes and the script is really funny that we have
for it he goes and I he goes by the way I didn't want to do the third one even yeah they won't they really pressured us to do the third one he goes so the idea of doing a fourth one was not
intriguing to me but people seem to want it and I guess the working title was naked gun for OJ did it which is very funny but um he said he was like look man I didn't
want to do just the same thing again of the cop in LA right the same movie he was like mine was about Frank
Drebrenson but it was about how his son didn't live up to his father's you know status yeah and he was like a
lowly security guard and kind of a fuck up and he said but then he gets roped into this whole international
espionage thing and he goes and then it became it was a spoof of mission impossible and all that's right that's what I
read yeah and he was like and I was very different and he goes and everybody loved the script we were everybody's
excited and he goes you know he says been more or less words like basically because I'm old I he goes I never
got a call nothing and all of a sudden I just get wind that uh that the family guy guy that Seth
McFarland is doing it and he's like they never even called the studio how typical is that the studio
didn't even call me to tell me so you're not part of the thing that you created anymore I told me
that story last week about my buddy Josh who who wrote the hot tub time machine movies yeah wrote
them both and was not can I call to be like hey I'm up for a job on the show what show I don't believe
the way this business works yeah so he uh Zucker said he retitled his script and he's still
gonna try to get it made as the other movie oh that'd be cool and um yeah and he just was you
know of course because it was David Rubin show there was there was a there was a bit of a slant of
like do you think your politics sure kind of got you ostracized or whatever yeah I would say of course
it did and my my wonder with a guy who's in his 70s is that you know outside of Mel Brooks and
even him I even him I don't think he's like he yes he's writing the new space balls movie but I
have a feeling the other writers are probably doing more of the comedic heavy lifting uh somebody
at that age is probably not going to be writing fresh relevant comedy especially the kind that
parody needs then again it might have been great I don't know maybe nobody even read it I just
sometimes these old cranks are like my script was great and you're like I'd like to read that
script before we be agree with you the only reason I had a tendency to believe him was he wasn't saying
it like that he was just like yeah what are you gonna do like this it sucks but I don't know I had a
good script that and you know but we're not he was basically like I'm not gonna sit here and
wallow in it and feel sorry for myself this is how this business works and onto the next thing I
guess it was very I don't actually kind of peace with it I'd kind of like to read McFarlane's
version I mean I don't love Ted if I thought I haven't seen the show but I the movies I thought
had their moments and the and family guy obviously has funny moments and stuff but like he's kind
of perfect for it it's that is the style of the naked gun I mean I'm sure he would do a good job
with it but he is that once upon a time in the west but it was naked gun style this is McFarlane though
where he just didn't this is he directed it I thought no it's it's the guy who did pop star like I was saying
wait it's one of the the the new naked gun is written by two guys who wrote the chip and
Dale's movie and who wrote for like how I met your mother I know one of them and the movie was
directed by while this thing's coming right out we got posters and everything uh dormit I'm
sorry it keep a shaffer I mix him up with dormit to come but he's one of the lonely island guys
okay McFarlane produced it oh okay all right the mix so he is involved I think I think what they
were saying was McFarlane was now in control of the project I got you but you got I'll tell you
who I'm excited that's in it is cc h pounder and I'm gonna assume oh yeah she's she's uh livia
probably the the chief right yeah yeah yeah she was played by Nancy Martian livia from surprise
now is do you think Pam I mean Pam Anderson is second billing do you think she's the love
interest she must be guaranteed yeah I mean everybody I think it's probably just gonna equal what
they were in the original we got Paul Walter house or in the George Kennedy role and so on
but it was written by those two guys Anna Kiva Schaffer who you know who worked on all that hot rod
and pop star and all that maybe it'll be good I'm excited no the um
let me see here Jerry Jerry Zucker you want to talk about a weird career I was just looking at his
Wikipedia page so here's the career he directs with his you know his brother and his his other friend
their aborames airplane top secret ruthless people hilarious underrated movie with the video and
bat meddler naked gun ghost while a serious drama that was nominated for best picture and several
Academy Awards then oh no he didn't direct naked gun or two and a half so he must have been trying
to do a dramatic career he did first night with Sean Connery remember that movie yeah and Richard
gear that was that was that was six years after ghost and then rat race which was a funny movie the
complete opposite of ghost and first night it's an insane career like the broadest of comedy and then
like very somber serious romantic dramas interesting and his brother David who was was the one on the
show yeah he wrote let's see well this guy writer Kentucky fried movie writer director airplane
writer director top secret director ruthless people writer director naked gun writer director naked
gun two writer naked gun three then he produced a walk in the clouds high school high not very good
dude ready for this writer director producer basket ball yeah great move it's right it is yeah uh and
kind of crazy that those guys I mean I I assume they did some sort of rewriting on it but that was
really weird at the time those two guys starring in that movie I remember I mean they were stars I
guess but like and I guess now we can point to Seth McFarlane he that there is there is more of that
going on but you rarely see a voice person become a star anyway it's a weird business
full of weird shit speaking of weird business yeah I've got a top of the show new psycho here for us
please well actually it's not a new psycho it's just a I started making notes in my I've a you
know note at a note in my iPhone for the pod where I put all my movie corners and all that stuff and
I put a thing in here now that's a top of show it's it's usually something I think is worth bringing
up right at the beginning um sometimes it's a new psycho but this is not this has to do with our
friends over at shout slash scream factory I texted you and our dear friend Matt McCarthy about
this the other day yes uh scream factory and shout factory as we've mentioned on the show they have a
sale every other week so it's usually not big news when they're doing a sale but uh it's like
countdown to Easter sale yeah literally that's been one of them when they did the far sale I told a
story on here I believe about how one of the things I ordered was the original Halloween in 4k I
received a copy it was unwrapped and the jewel case or whatever it's called the plastic on that the
permanent plastic was damaged I wrote to them and said look guys I paid full price for this you sent
me a what seems to be a used copy of this thing right they said it's not used we we guarantee the
condition of it and uh you know but you're welcome to mail it back to us at your own expense basically
if you want to do I don't even know if they offered an exchange I don't remember but it put a bad
taste in my mouth still sure I thought adds a freak accident some intern responded to that email
I you know I can't judge the company on that it's not a big deal the disc works whatever
so anyway they announced last week they're doing a half off UHD 4k sale and I'm like well that
is an interesting sale half off the 4k is pretty good stuff I go in I find 4 or 5 for like 1899
what was in my cart uh Gretel and Hansel Aussie Perkins early work which I liked I think we did it
on the show yeah yeah we did um clue in 4k um which I don't I only own the DVD and I was like well
that's a great upgrade I'll do that same I think I might do that myself um there were three others
and I'm blanking at the moment but they were they were nice little finds and I was oh oh streets of
fire was one roller ball the James Conn futuristic roller derby movie sure I've seen it and the remake
couple just cool things that I was like you know like I've never seen roller ball or streets of
fire but I was like these are probably amazing looking in 4k these are moody 80s whatever films
um and I was excited and I was at checkout and I was like look at that man 100 bucks
five blue uh that five 4k that's a good deal yeah and I noticed that after taxes and stuff I was
just a little over what it should have been and I didn't understand why and then I looked at my
cart and there was an extra charge for three dollars and 50 cents and I said what is that
and it said it was the easy returns and protection package and it said you know do you choose not
to do this and I said yeah I choose not to do it I don't even understand what that is and when
you clicked on it it explained what it was they didn't explain beforehand they you had to
unclick it to get the information sure and it said so basically they're charging you three
and you and you you have to you have to decide to say don't charge me three yeah exactly and when
you decide 350 and when you decide to not take the charge it then tells you without this package
you are liable for return shipping package loss or damage so basically what it means is
is if you don't pay the extra three dollars and 50 cents shout factory is not responsible if your
package is lost if your product is damaged and if something's wrong and you need to make a return
within the return window now you're you're buying insurance on a $20 item yeah so 350 is not
obviously a gonna make or break anybody's life but that's bullshit that's bullshit they're
they're telling you that you have to pay now for them to do what they're supposed to do
as a company to protect you to to a limited extent as a customer and I'm paying for customer
service and that's gonna start just the fact that you're noticing that that's gotta be happening
everywhere well and by the way the fact that it gets added automatically yeah crazy and then you
have to go what is this and then you have to back by the way if you're in checkout you can't take
it off of your cart so you have to go back to the page where you didn't notice it before you click
check out just to your cart page and unclick it and then when you unclick it that's when you find out
what it's so shitty and slippery and gross and again three dollars and 50 cents is not a lot of money
but that's a terrible terrible policy and I just I didn't buy any of them I was like forget it
you're not getting my business I don't give a shit about how good this deal is I'm not playing
ball with this and now I don't have those four k's I will live without the four k's but
I'd rather pay full price at waterloo records or the archive or or a store or whatever or by the
way I'd rather give Amazon my money than do that with you guys I'm not I'm sorry that's ridiculous to
me criteria and still the best customer service in the business but yeah these I mean these
boutique labels if you're gonna stay afloat this is not the way to do it hey well I got news for
you shouting of boutique label the shout is a as as big as criterion is they've been around forever
yeah sure a major player at this point I mean they're you're not you're not vinegar syndrome or
something you know I mean like right so I'm supposed to be impossible their online system if you
have an issue with them vinegar syndrome a lot I've heard a lot of grumbling about them
you know I've met some of the people that work there because the archive is their store
and the people at the store are usually pretty helpful and nice but I you know I don't know
how what that means in terms of dealing with them online I've I've been ordered a ton of stuff
from them online they usually I like vinegar syndrome they get a little too uh niche for me it gets
a little too like yeah yeah yeah like they're I consider myself somebody who's at least heard of
95% of film and they always stump me I'm like what is this yeah it's always like the windmill killer
or something from 1974 with Charles Bronson or what I never know what's going on over there anyway
anyway let's get to that corner why not I'm excited that old corner I got a DeVito for you
right out of the gate because you said right he start start me up rewatch rewatch throw mama from the
train yeah what a wonderful movie I mean just what a wonderful movie that barely makes sense
but I didn't notice that until a recent viewing but you're correct there are holes in it but yeah it
feel it feels like it's an hour long and I wish we had three more movies with Billy Crystal and
DeVito together I was watching so Jamie my lady friend she um she had never seen when Harry
Met Sally so I said you got to see it it's it's the arguably the greatest rom com ever made like
you know this is the one you hear you've heard quotes from it your whole life and probably just
didn't even realize it show her when Harry Met Sally she loved it and she's laughing at Billy Crystal
and I'm like and we had watched you got mail so she liked to make Ryan a lot and you know so it
was fun to watch it with her and I was like hey after this we're gonna watch throw mama from the
train because if you think Billy Crystal's funny in this he's off the charts in that movie it's
it's great and then you got DeVito and it's just an awesome movie and Ramsey for Christ said yeah
nominated for an Academy Award for throw mama from the train wild deserved yeah deserved I agree
I mean imagine I you got to imagine I think they must have gone to like big older stars of the day
but like man she was perfect does it does it post stroke yeah is inhabited in certain ways by the
stroke in the movie she's got some mobility issues her speech is a little slurred and it
weirdly helps it now I was gonna say it's this it's this it's like this weird massive addition to
the character like yeah and it makes her being so mean so much better yeah somebody could be this
mean through through their troubles um anyway oh and um we we loved it we we loved watching it but
but but but halfway through the movie she goes I don't understand why wouldn't Billy Crystal just
go to the cops and just turned into DeVito and then I go valid I go they're really hanging a lot on
you just accepting that Billy Crystal is convinced they'll think he did it because of his motive
alibi theory yeah you let a lot of stuff go back then but uh but if you haven't seen the movie it's
it's it's it's brilliant it's it's it's um a remake of Hitchcock's uh strangers on the train
and instead of them just remaking it they create a new setting with new characters and in this
movie the two main characters meet because Billy Crystal is a writing professor and Danny
DeVito is a student taking his class Danny DeVito is not a good writer but very much wants to be in
his very dedicated Billy Crystal is a great writer but is not writing because of his artistry and
using the excuse of my wife stole my ex wife stole my book so therefore I cannot write so they're
completely juxtaposed characters uh Danny DeVito at one point goes to Billy Crystal for advice
on how to write a better murder mystery they start talking about how you need to you need to
eliminate a motive and establish an alibi for your characters Danny DeVito then starts talking
about how he hates his mother and wishes she was dead Billy Crystal is like I hate my ex wife I
wish he was dead but there you go Owen neither of us could kill them why we'd get caught why
because we have a motive right and he says go see a Hitchcock movie if you want to learn more about
this DeVito happens to go see strangers from a train on a train you see the scene where the two
guys meet on the train and they go and the guy goes we swap murders Chris Cross each one does the
other ones murder they're not connected Chris Cross so it's great that they remake strangers on a
train but they actually use the movie they're remaking as a plot device to put the plot of the
remake into action and Danny DeVito thinks Billy Crystal is sending me a message that I'm
supposed to go kill his wife and he's going to kill my mother and of course that's not what Billy
Crystal wants and the hilarity unfolds before that but very much so after that but it's an awesome
that that scene in in the car when Billy Crystal is driving and the radio the news thing comes on
the radio and it's like Margaret Donner author of the book hot fire or he goes Margaret Donner
fame writer was was presumed dead and Billy Crystal is going oh Margaret poor Margaret oh my god poor
Margaret and then the guy goes to the news guy goes she was author of the book bestselling book
Hot Fire which is the book she stole from him and he just goes slut that slut
it's it's an amazing yeah uh flip flop comedic flip flop it's a very very funny movie uh I
strongly recommend it it is I recall a lot of the funniest stuff being the examples of bad writing
from his class that was some of my favorite stuff yeah yeah yeah 100 girls I'd like to pork
yeah and like isn't like or just him trying to write I mean there there was a kind of a big
thing in the 80s funny farm and there's lots of movies where a frustrated middle-aged man goes
somewhere to write um and then at some point somebody realized that nobody wants to watch somebody
write it's the most boring thing in the world yeah but as a writer I always love it when you see it um
I haven't seen much I'm gonna be really trying to rack my brain to think of what I watch but I do
want to take this time to discuss this John Mulaney show which I'm not I'm not bold enough to say
that it's grown on me but I have definitely seen every episode of it it's better now than it was
when it came on a year ago or whatever but I'm still just baffled by it everyone on the couch is
usually somebody I enjoy and find funny the musical performances are always people I find cool
he had Kim deal on for Christ's sake so love deal uh he also had Randy Newman on which cancels out
Kim deal uh and then these bits you know like they're there's I don't know who they're for the studio
audience isn't laughing and at first I was like these are like Mulaney's too funny to know this isn't
funny but well I love John yeah and I would think that but also his sitcom had the same problem and
nobody knew if he was a real fucking with the audience who not everybody was like is this is he
making a joke on that show on that show he was a billion percent not making a joke and he is admitted
to that he was trying to do a straightforward sitcom which is very difficult to do but he didn't do
a good job um the this show you know I don't know if it's striving for early Conan the weirdness
of early Conan or what but like he acknowledges before and after that the bits don't work
which like Carson did to some degree and Letterman did to some degree but they were funnier about
it Mulaney seen it's this weird thing where he's like looking you in the eye confidently and being
like boy that didn't work did it and then here's a bit that nobody's going to enjoy and then
I'm like what am I watching then like last night they had um Jean Dumb it was uh Paul
Appell who's very funny from SNL writer but she comes out nobody knows who Paul Appell is you
know that's watching the show you gotta be kind of a comedy nerd so you just think it's a sketch
but she comes out this lady dressed as Jean smart on hacks see can I say something I hate
impressions like this this is like when everyone on SNL when they would do Christopher they would
do celebrity jeopardy then they'd be like Christopher Waltz and it's like no you're not doing Christopher
Waltz you're doing his character from englory as bastards yeah so Jean smart is known in television
and to some people but most people just know her as the lady from hacks yeah so set it up as
so and so from hacks they don't even mention hacks it's a lady so it's a lady Paul Appell who I
admire and I admire Jean smart as well absolutely a lot of people don't know who as you exactly
what you're saying they don't they definitely don't know Paul Appell and a lot of people don't know
who Jean smart is if they know where they know hacks or they know her as a character acts far
go whatever designing women but the entire bit was a woman who slightly looked like Jean smart
but she was saying dumb things ladies and gentlemen Jean dumb so then you're like okay you can do
one of those and it's like boy that was that was kind of a stinker right whatever but then get to
the good bit but we just keep stacking bad bits now in recent weeks the press for the show has been
sucking him off John Mulaney really can do no wrong for critics even when he definitely does
they are starting to talk about the show as being brilliant the most innovative thing on television
and you start seeing these raves about it and it's like just because it's different does not
mean it's great but I will say it's got a certain fascination that's growing each week it's
it's a baffling show I'm gonna keep watching it the music is always great and then I'll have the
occasional comedic beat where you just fucking love it he can be really funny where what he does
wrong too is he brings out normal people with the celebs which in theory is a good idea but
it's just it winds up being people who aren't funny and have no ability to speak publicly
sitting next to trained comedians which is just awkward and it seems like he wants the show to
feel as uncomfortable and unnatural as possible and maybe that's the goal but it really feels like
he's just a guy who's not comfortable in his own skin which I'm sure is a side effect of being
sober after decades of drug use but I don't know it's worth looking at because every week I'm just
like what are you you know like last night twist of the wrapper was doing ventriloquism for John
Mulaney but there it wasn't a joke it was like a segment like a piece where you know we see what
twist is up to he's he's drawing and Mulaney's like oh that's really good he's telling him how great
the drawing is but they're just two men having a serious conversation there's no comedic element to
it I can't figure the show out to me it's not it to me it feels like a kitchen sink
uh television show that is a byproduct of the online age we're living in it's it's a show that
feels like you're scrolling through Instagram yeah and you'll see a quasi famous older celebrity
next to a quite famous contemporary celebrity next to a 50 year old southern woman stand-up
comedian next to a wrapper that's got a cult following but not isn't known in the mainstream
and it's just throwing all of it against the it's just the kitchen sink it's like just make this
gumbo that basically feels like you're scrolling through Instagram there's no way the same audience
that is that has an interest in seeing uh Nikki Glazer yeah and Hannibal Burris and David
Letter maybe David Lennorin but there's no way the people who have an interest in seeing
Nikki Glazer and Hannibal Burris on the couch together have the same interest in seeing Randy
Newman then come out and do music sure it's just not the same audience in any way shape or
form and I get that that's kind of what talk shows would do yeah feels a bit like Merv Griffin
it almost feels like he's because they shoot it like that they shoot it very 70s and I'm like
yeah maybe he's doing the Merv Griffin show where it felt like this weird loose swingers party or something
well it's aiming I think for that vibe of like here's a bunch of
people from all walks of life sitting on a couch and we're all having a blast and I love that vibe
you know Carson got there sometimes we have burritos and dom deliwis and some blonde and everybody's
laughing having fun but it just never reaches fun you know like last night it's like okay Patina's
Walt who I love Sarah Silverman very funny um Richard Kind is always involved in the bits which
sometimes works sometimes don't Steve Gutenberg is out on the couch for 20 minutes in a bathrobe
but he's just doing a straight interview where they don't talk about his films at all because the
it's always got a topic last night's was about sleep so they talked to Steve Gutenberg for 20
minutes about his sleep and like I get that you're trying to do something different and I'd much
rather hear him talk about sleep than hear him talk about some new project he's pitching but I
just wish there was a little more that feels very Merv Griffin you know the bit the bit on the bit on
STV when Moranis would do Merv Griffin would always you know he did the thing where he
he he we keep talking about his suit yeah and he'd be like look at that line he's that beautiful
and then the guests are coming on he's like what is that's a beautiful suit yet and it was never
about anything it was just like small talk um well there you go so I guess I guess that's what and
look maybe it'll become great I mean you watch those early Conan's they're unwatchable I remember when
Conan first came on you we were like what is the hell is this yeah and then all of a sudden it made
sense I was obsessed with it and um may I think definitely it's that I'm older and and my there's
more things closed off in my mind that I just kind of look at it for more of a frustrated stand
and point but I do definitely think you're right it hasn't been renewed yet but if it finds its
footing I think it could start to be really delightful because I never don't enjoy watching it
but like last night's the gimmick was he wore a blindfold for the entire hour while he's
interviewing guests while he's walking around the stage while he's doing the bits and you're like
this is adding absolutely nothing comedically to the show a man wearing a blindfold is not
visually interesting and it's not funny and him him you know he's not running a marathon he's not
juggling he's walking in you know in a ten step radius so like there's like there's danger to
the blindfold it's just a man wearing something weird and it they don't discuss it in the interviews
so you're like all right but it doesn't also feel weird for weird sake it just sort of feels like
what's going on here you know and it almost needs a straight man like when Jerry Seinfeld came out
and was like what the hell is this it needs like that Jason Bateman on the couch to be like what are
you doing because that always gets the biggest laugh the audience is always like what's happening
but I'll say this if you need to see a really funny bit from the show the one where he interviews
an adult bubbles the chimp uh that Michael Jackson raised that is a genius interview it's like a
60 minutes hard hitting interview between Mulaney and a grown up bubbles the chimp and man it made me laugh
well is the chip is it just a chimp or is it a guy in a suit guy in a chimp suit yeah okay I think
it's Langston Kerman who writes for the show the funny comment oh I love Langston yeah um we wrote
together on Moshe Cashers show problematic um uh well this one is this one is off topic uh
I hate when I don't have a topic I was gonna try to stick to relationships friendships um yeah
but uh you got to think about boats regular ships uh no nothing about ships did you watch master
and commander maybe yeah I watched the carabee I finally got the movie thinner on blue ray
I love this movie it's not a good movie Tom Holland uh does uh directed this thing
and he did a nice job directing it and the script was written by the guy that wrote Beatles juice
um and it's not a bad script um Michael McDowell and uh and it stars uh old what's his name oh god
they're gonna make me Robert John Burke and Joe Montana are the stars um thinner was uh the one
of the Bachman books by Stephen King uh when he was writing under that pseudonym we did it on the show
I think we did a commentary on it on thinner pretty sure oh sure fans will know we did we at
least discussed it we at least did an episode on oh god all right well okay well you can
look let's hear that I just feel bad now it's it well it's it's about a a a large man who well
no this is about relationships it's about a large man who is involved in a hit and run with the
daughter of a gypsy uh and she is killed and he gets all it's not a hit and run he kills her with
his car and then they it does go to trial but because he's a somewhat powerful lawyer in this town
and well connected his friend the policeman who investigated the crime uh lies on his behalf and the
judge who hates the gypsies uh declares uh the main character uh in his Billy Hallick uh innocent
and because of this her father the gypsy father uh curses him he's a very large man as I said and he's
strokes his cheek and says thinner and that's the curse he starts getting thinner and thinner no
matter how much he eats and he's going to waste away into nothing uh he also curses is the gypsy
also curses his two friends he curses uh one of them uh lizard the judge and the judge starts
literally turning into like a lizard his skin starts to scale and harden and stuff and then he
uh also curses the police chief played by Daniel Von Bargain who was one of the Seinfeld bosses
he's the last boss on Seinfeld that George has uh on a boss he's got a defeat
what's the what's that company called?
do you
i feel like you'd remember if you i used to watch three episodes a night and i could have answered any
question but it's been a while where George worked was
Krueger Mr. Krueger Krueger yeah yeah yeah yeah um
he they don't they don't tell you the word that he says to to to Krueger when he touches his cheek
but it makes him he goes Krueger
well funny enough he gives him a skin disease where his his his his face gets
overrun with these gigantic cysts and pimples and stuff and Joe Montana plays a mob boss that uh
that the main character was able to get off on a uh attempted murder trial and the got in the
mob boss is like i'm forever in your debt so it comes down to the mob boss helping this guy
track down the gypsies and threaten and frighten them to a point that they finally agree to remove
the curse um and there's a lot of other stuff he thinks his wife is cheating on him and
and but he loves his daughter very much there's there's some other again it's not i wouldn't say it's
a it's a movie i love i've loved it for years pinkstone and i quote it all the time i don't think
it's a good movie i don't think it's a bad movie it's just it's a two two the average viewer it's
just a fine movie it's fine it's you'll probably be a little bored um and you might even find it
a bit forgettable but the makeup effect of him losing weight is tremendous they do it impeccably
it's very well acted it's well directed by Tom Holland and the script is strong enough i get the feeling
the original script is probably a bit stronger than what you end up seeing on the final screen but
i was just happy to finally get this thing on blue ray because and by the way the blue ray is
still like 35 bucks it's uh it's just way out blue rays now i won't do it a new blue ray i won't
do it because they very often have the 4k getting in the wings it's happened to me so many times
and i'm like i'm just not doing to do this anymore i'm i'm only buying 4k going forward
well this is one that's been out of circulation for so long i was like we're not we're probably not
getting a 4k so i'm gonna buy the i'm gonna buy the blue ray in fact i was talking about this and
we can talk to him about when we talked about tomorrow but with uh Joe Ramone who will be a guest on
one of the next episodes um i was complaining to him about ten men you know i was like it's only
out on DVD and the DVD is like 40 bucks or something yeah and he was saying uh it was because you
Disney has all these titles that they've just basically turned their back on and they're not
gonna do anything with it that's what i was saying it's all those adult Disney movies from the late 80s
all those touch-done movies i don't think are ever gonna be released so i was like all right well
then that's a good enough reason to bite the bullet eventually and just buy the DVD i guess
yeah um because that means the 4k is not coming so um anyway i really enjoyed thinner uh i
enjoyed the work of tom Holland um and uh and i really like Burke as an actor quite a bit uh
he he also played the police chief in um black clansman uh he played robo cop and robo cop three
he's a good actor i like this guy i'd like to see him i mean he's in tons of stuff but i need to
watch more of what he's been i forgot this when i watched this ages ago we're
briefly discussing doing it on the show but Joe never watched it um it's called red rooms
and it's on shutter or it was this has been a while so it might have fallen off by now but
not a classic but if you have shutter it's definitely one of the better movies on shutter it's not
a shutter original it looks great it costs some money um so it's about a high profile serial killer case
and we've got a woman kind of modeled on people like our good friends caron cagarafe and
george hard star she's obsessed with serial killers and she gets too obsessed and starts to get
kind of involved she's like at the trial like really wanting to be a part of the action and you
start to realize she's almost like a serial killer or a murder groupie um to say much more would be
to spoil it and also i saw it so i don't quite recall the the explicit details of it beyond that
but it was very well done very suspenseful um and it's a slow burn so be ready for that
but once it starts burning i mean there's stuff in this that is deeply deeply disturbing you
hear a child killed in a trial is you you just hear it but it's awful that's that's something
from this movie that really really stayed with me and i think shutter has a weird warning about it
because it is pretty unsettling but uh you know serial killer movies used to be a genre used to be
just there'd be one a month and you could you could set your clock to it those are rare too now
thrillers are gone uh red rooms is a very low budget foreign uh i'm still giving you a lot of words
that you're probably not excited about slow burn foreign um not a reading yeah um but it's i got to
tell you once it starts hitting it's suspenseful as hell and it's really disturbing so i recommend red
rooms it's good and the lead girl Juliette getty p is really really good um i only had two for today
two as well well and then let's get to the picture at hand friendship starring tim Robinson and Paul
Rudd this was a movie that was announced i guess initially about a year and change ago uh it was an
a it is an a 24 i was very curious when i heard that tim Robinson was going to be in a movie i was
very curious when i heard it was going to be a dark comedy about friendship and then it was called
friendship and i was very curious because it was a 24 uh my assumption was that this film would be
um you know a dramedy something that was a bit funny yeah but more sad and disturbing with the man
that has trouble making friends totally the same i was expecting an exploration of male loneliness
is what i was expecting with some laughs i uh was lucky enough to get to attend one of the premier
screenings at south by south west um due to uh uh uh actually because of steve burn who is friends
with olexis garcia who's one of the producers of the film i met olexis at steve show he invited me
i got to go with my buddy adamigit uh and Shane my buddy shane gillis and my buddy james my can
and we sat down and this thing started and dear god we were howling laughing from minute one
until the last second of the of the film i kept waiting for it to take that turn in the middle
where it was going to be like this isn't funny anymore now it's serious yep and it never happens
uh it is essentially you it's like following a character from a tim robinson sketch
yeah into into what his actual life is like for two you know over the course of two hours
not not in real time i just mean like for two hours you watch what this guy's life is like
yeah um basic plot is is he's a very square guy he's a very uh sort of subdued guy very
into marvel he's married with like a 16 year old son 14 15 um not an unhappy marriage but definitely not
an electric one uh quick pause i would consider that a deeply unhappy and almost disturbing marriage
with uh kate mara especially in that opening scene that opening scene was one of my hardest laughs
she's talking about how she just beat cancer and it's played pretty straight you know it's kind
of sad and she's talking about how she beat cancer whatever and she's like you know um she's
talking a lot about her male friend throughout the movie that she hangs out with a lot i took that
to mean she's definitely cheating on some robots who by the way when you finally see the middle
friend you realize he is clearly the father of her child oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah 100% so i
don't really see it as a happy marriage but my my maybe my hardest laugh is she was talking about
how they're in a a share group for survivors of cancer and she's like you know i i wasn't even able
to orgasm so i had no interest in sex and i just i lost my appetite and my hair was falling out
and then uh they cut over to timber Robinson and he goes i've been orgasm and just fine
and that that really got me it made me laugh so hard in the theater it's a lot of jokes like that
and yeah and they and not at the expense of a story there there's there's a lot of random
jokes that don't really have any connection to the plot they're just there because they're funny
yeah there's the there's the part which how refreshing is that yeah when the yeah when the
when the son and the mom kiss on the lips and timber Robinson's like you guys kiss on the lips
and they just never address it ever again the scene with him filling the coffee cup at work
to the brim walking through the hallway full cup full cup coming through when he sits down and
is trying to bring that cup to his lips i laugh so hard because i do that every morning
and every morning there are three brown drops on my clean tile and i go god damn it
why do you fill it to the brim every fucking morning and i saw that i just lost my shit i was like
yeah you just want more coffee he does Robinson does some almost chevy chase level physical shit in
this where you're like he's taking a nothing bit and making it so funny um he's so fun when
Paul Rudd lifts him up when they're in that underground tunnel and Paul Rudd like lifts him up and he
like you know he lightly gets jostled and screams as though somebody like you know shot him in the
heart there's so many moments like that he's just he is so funny like i don't make a sound
when i laugh anymore i'm usually like you know some of that's depression some of that's been working
in comedy too long you just start to go oh that's funny yeah so god did it feel good to just be like
embarrassingly laughing at something throughout he um what's it called uh the uh oh sorry so you
see throughout the movie that it kind of takes place in anywhere USA the town is a fake you
there are several times where you see like a mailing label and it's the name of a fake town and
a fake state yeah and it just says USA instead of a zip code or whatever when he's pat mentioned
Tim Robinson's characters is really into marvel but they never get specific about it he just
keeps saying there's a new marvel out we gotta go see the new marvel um so it really is is and
then screaming at anyone who might spoil something from him yeah they say the title and he yells at
them because it's spoiler so they set the stage nicely to be like look this is this is just suburban
life unhappy marriage yeah guy that is not good at fitting in because he's kind of gotten swallowed
into this system that everybody gets shuffled into he didn't take to it and then all of a sudden
he gets forced into becoming friends with Paul Rudd who is kind of adventurous kind of fun kind of
wild with a few secrets of his own I won't spoil and very cool he's a he's a weatherman he's handsome
you know he's he's hip he's everything our our boy Tim is not exactly and there is a mishap
that leads to Paul Rudd saying we can't be friends anymore and now the Tim Robinson has seen
gay paris he cannot go back to the farm and he cannot accept that this uh that this friendship is over
and and then things intensify quite a bit from there it's funny when I met the producer Alexis
I I said dude the trailer's great I can't wait to see the movie and I said it looks like a darker cable
guy that's what I thought it was gonna be yeah and he goes that's kind of what I think he said along
something along the lines of that's what we wanted people to think and then I saw the movie
and I was like it's a funnier cable guy it's like it even in more insane cable like I didn't
in a million years think the a24 Tim Robinson movie that was sort of about stalking was going to be
a zania version of a cable guy story I thought it was gonna be really dark like like when they
talk about what the cable guy was supposed to be I thought it was gonna be that and no it's non-stop
laughs I think there's one part again I don't want to spoil that is very serious for about 10 seconds
right and then it gets right back to it well well people need to realize a24 is they're they're
not creating stuff they're buying movies they're a distribution house right so like granted they
have their taste their style there's definitely a lot of people operating in that a24 style currently
but like they're just putting shit out so this is their first comedy to work at all I mean
god knows death of a unicorn did not work and that dicks the musical was even worse
but this is just super funny and I hope we get a lot more trusting funny people with five million
dollars or you know probably much to my surprise this is probably like a 30 million dollar movie
these days but just trusting funny people to make something funny like that's what used to happen
that used to be a entire genre so it was a thrill and it's kind of like what I described in this
magical naked gun screening that I wish I had gone to there was laughter but there was also you
could tell this feeling in the audience of I'm so happy to be genuinely laughing at a movie
I'm gonna I'm gonna spoil two things so if you don't want to hear this I don't consider this a
a spoiler movie at all I do because because when you see a comedy that's this funny you want to see
that you want to see it you want to experience it you don't want somebody to go and then this part
is funny you know what I mean so yeah yeah so these are two everybody says it's got the funny
as drug trip and movie history and that's not a spoiler but it's real funny so that's one of the
things I'm about to spoil yeah um that part where he does the toad thing and Jesus Christ man
that when when his trip as he goes to subway and it's supposed to be this mind bending life altering
thing that the laugh that got when he woke up and he's like I want to get to the right I just ordered
a sandwich that's it was so crazy because again that was a part that's well under the movie I was
like this is where the movie is going to go like sideways and get nuts and it's like no it's just
going to stay funny and it just did yeah well that entire subway scene I was unaware that that was
the trip I was just like what am I looking at here and then when you get to that reveal got it kill
me and then the uh what's it called um the other this this to me is also a spoiler the scene where his
wife is rediscovered and they have the party for her I'm in the pack theater he's in the garage
because you can't fit in at his wife's party he's making it all about himself you see that Tim
Robinson's character is kind of an asshole and all this that the other he's in the garage playing
the drums by himself Conor O'Malley walks in that fucking theater erupted because everybody was like
this is going to be amazing still yeah I got chills just now that scene between the two of them
I was crying laughing at that yeah I fuck you man who the fuck are you who the fuck are you it was so
crazy yeah it was it was amazing man that movie I really really think friendship I will say it I
think it is a masterpiece of modern comedy I think it is the best constructed and well-made comedy I
have seen in years and it's for me I've got to see it a few more times but for me I'm like this
could be another like kingpin or something for me this could be a really like an all-timer for
me man I really liked it my guess is a South by screening packed with comics is going to give you a
little bit of a setback when you see it like at home you're oh this isn't quite what what it was
there which is why these reviews from Con where everybody applauds for 12 minutes or so fucking stupid
like you think of course people liked it you think maybe they were influenced but
no I mean I saw a noon show on a Friday with my buddy Alex and I mean it what was kind of
throughout fun for us is like we were the only ones laughing at first and I was like well I
definitely see like if my mom went to see this you would not find Tim Robinson even remotely funny
but little by little it's just like by the end it seemed like we were in a packed sold-out house
and there was only about a quarter of the audience there like there was so much hard laugh going on
I am dying to see it again it's at the vista I might go up after we talk about it I mean
that right after this conversation just because it's got me wanting to see it again but I haven't
wanted to see a movie a second time in five years yeah I haven't wanted to see a movie the first time
in five years it's like usually I'm halfway through like you know pausing it to see how far I'm
into it like god damn and I did not want friendship to end when you think about it after I'm not
spoiling anything but a fourth of the movie is underground like Paul Rudd takes him to this
underground world like sewer system that decision alone is so insane why why would why would
sewer set pieces ever factor into this story what I love and they do it again mild spoiler but they
do a very good job of when no this is a spoiler when his wife gets lost down there they do a really
good thing you were trying not to spoil they did well it's right so it's well but they did a really
good job of when that all happens you're like was she in his head like they do a good job of me
you think it's just gonna get like supernatural like what's going on this is weird man and then no
it comes right back down to earth it's all actually happening it's all her he grounded and then
it's super funny I almost wondered if on a second viewing I'm gonna I'm gonna notice something that
makes me realize the wife wasn't lost she was fucking her axe or something like that you know like
sure because it is that kind of movie you feel like there's there's Easter eggs waiting for you
a little bit and it was what you just said about you haven't seen a movie forever that you want to
see again I haven't seen a movie for I was sad after I saw it that I had to wait two months for
you to see it because I wanted to talk about it so badly and I was just like I can't I don't
want to tell many of the jokes I don't want to ruin anything I just wanted to see it like so
that level of excitement is you know that's pretty pretty sweet there's also all these you know
Eric Rayhill is a guy we used to follow each other on Twitter and he had very few followers and he
was basically doing what I used to do on Vine 10 years ago just like kind of what what everybody does
I'm fine you know just kind of put it on and talk and he's himself but he's this very kind of
specific weird version of himself and I didn't know that he had become big enough that he's an
extra in this movie or like Whitmer Thomas who's a great comic is one of the the crew in this like
men's circle but everybody in it is pretty funny the scene where the the the black guy in the group
starts singing that song when they're in the the prayer circle or whatever had me dying as well
when he's like singing to Paul Rudd you remember that yeah yeah it was great I mean there's just
it's there's so much in it where you're like what like a 24 a lot of it is weirdness for weirdness
sake and and it works so much better in a comedy you know like when you're watching just some random
shit happen in a horror movie you can quickly lose interest but this all was building to laughs like
everything weird that happened maybe you didn't have a purpose except to make you laugh which used to
be the goal of comedies and at some point got completely lost so it was a thrill for me it really
was I loved it I kind of knew I would I was very surprised to see Tim Robinson did not have a hand
in writing it although I'm sure he maybe gave feedback or something but it's this guy Andrew D. Young
who was there when I saw it and talked about yeah he wrote it during COVID he said
for Tim I assume or no I don't think for Tim he wrote it and then he said and then he was like
he sent it to Tim and he was like we what do you think of this would you want to do this and he
said Tim Robinson was like yeah let's he said he he emailed it to him in like an hour later he called
him back and he's like let's do it he said that Tim came in and he was like you know he liked the
script he changed some stuff that he thought worked better you know in his way of it yeah you know
because his stamp is clearly on it I was shocked that Tim Robinson didn't write it that's that's
that's how I started this portion of the conversation that's what I said well that's it's you know
if you're that easy to tune out maybe that's a you problem the uh yeah no it's so but but but but
but he said but I would when he said the thing about like Tim changed some some of the lines so I was
like okay that makes sense you know yeah well I had heard our red actually in an interview they said
that Tim Robinson on day one was like let's cut all the jokes out of the script
which is I know everybody's scared of jokes these days but there are plenty of jokes in the script
written jokes hard jokes not esoteric stuff there's jokes galore so clearly they didn't stick to that
but um this guy's actually got a big TV directing career I I have met him he dated uh
kaperlant okay so he uh he you know he's did uh pen 15 which is a show I love miracle workers shrill
Dave uh he's directed all kinds of stuff high fidelity which we loved so he's a big TV director
I wasn't aware of that but he's gonna have a big film career I hope we get so many more comedies like
this um the one thing I will say as criticism and and there's always criticism even in a perfect movie
Paul Rudd you'll notice we have barely mentioned in this entire discussion and I think there's a
reason for that which is he's totally the straight man in this uh I don't know if that's by design
you know I I guess I'm sure Paul Rudd is a big fan of Tim Robinson maybe that's why he did it but
you know Paul Rudd can make 30 million dollars a movie if he wants to so he saw something here he
liked and wanted it you know wanted to get in the salarious movie but I gotta tell you
he's not given anything funny to do none of the laughs are supplied by Paul Rudd that doesn't mean
he's got a couple that's a problem per se every movie has a straight man but
plans trains the straight man is Steve Martin and he's generating an easy 50% of the laughs
so I don't know why that decision was made to not have Paul Rudd be funny he's got the
Fontana mustache from anchor man and playing like a straighter version of Brian Fantana he is
occasionally he he's a little big with it he's doing like hey buddy and give him a wink and how
you do and tagger and all that because he's a cool dude but they never push it really to a
comedic level so you know maybe because Tim Robinson's so extreme you wanted him to be straighter but
in that case and look it's stupid to criticize a movie that just flat out works and that we've
been read I don't think I think it's great that that Paul Rudd knows like hey man I'm the backseat
in this one all good for sure first it shows a lot of restraint and and he's he's good at it you
know and you get why somebody would idolize somebody as cool as Paul Rudd so that works for me though
I just wish a little bit that maybe it had been more of a what about Bob Richard Dreyfus type role
not that explosive but just more of a more of a guy who's like what the fuck is wrong with you know
like that that was my one thing the friction between the two men wasn't quite there for me because
Paul Rudd was a bit of a cartoon character like Tim Robinson and therefore the friction wasn't
quite hitting for me that is my only issue with the movie my only thing I could say that I didn't
care for yeah I disagree I thought Paul Rudd played it I thought Paul Rudd well wait you just said
he's too straight not funny but then you said he's a cartoon character I don't understand
well he doesn't have comedy but he's playing it in that kind of like he I mean he's I don't
mean cartoon character I mean he's caricature I don't know what I would say he's uh he's not like
a normal guy he's not like if you or me were in that situation with Tim Robinson to be like dude
get the fuck out of my house right and I think there might be a more comedy more tension more friction
in that kind of movie but then maybe again that movie leans more into the cable guy type thing we
were expecting Matthew Browder is a total cuck in the cable guy and maybe the decision was made to
just take it in a more interesting direction um that's all I'm saying is like every conversation I've
had about this movie nobody ever says how about that moment with Paul Rudd and maybe making him equally
funny would have completely thrown this movie off its axis so what's here works beautifully I just
had to say that one kind of thing I was like Rudd's not I couldn't get a I couldn't get a beat on
Paul Rudd in this movie I guess but I love it it's uh with ease the funniest movie in ages I mean
the the year of course but you could go further I I can't think of the last movie this funny I saw
I did see a review of overcompensating the new amazon show today that called it uh the finest
campus comedy of the year all right well it's May uh guys man there are no campus comedies that so stop
but this is it's not hyperbole to say this is easily one of the funniest movies of the last 10
years it's my hog my hog is as high as it's ever been for a movie on this show I'm actually able to
suck my own dick it's so hard we'll be back folks with Joe Ramone uh and also uh
now I can't remember the name of it John Peterson Henry Johnson that's right all right you know
what's crazy is that for years I worked with a Henry Johnson and I still can't remember the name
of this fucking movie uh folks that's it we will see you next time and we'll see you in hell