High enough, no ice that!
Bad guy.
How do you like those apples I'm done. Oh, that's it. I was just that you're gonna jump
in. I was just reading these comments and realizing that several people thought that I was asking for
strictly questions about Ready Player One. I will say you guys are terrible. Some of you at
reading pretty simple instructions. Well, we'll answer the questions. Helians, we're about to
record Ready Player One. It will take an hour. When that is done, I will check the comments in this post.
Every single question that asked in that hour will be answered in this month's Patreon. Questions can be
about anything. So everybody wrote Ready Player One questions. The first two. Well, answer them. A
deal is a deal. They could be about anything, including Ready Player One. Luckily, most people did not.
Okay, so we're good. Anyway, yeah, I thought, you know, Joe and I were gonna do an old classic
today's stir of echoes. Or I think it's classic. I don't know what Joe thinks of it. And, you know, I
didn't think just doing a normal thing is good enough for these bonus ones. You guys are paying. We
want to try to give you a little flair, a little special adish. My pants are off for this recording.
Right. And really, Ernest Scared Stupid was a perfect candidate for it, but we just toss it out for
free. And it was nice to hear how many of you loved that episode. It was very fun one to do.
It was fun. And we stuck to the movie more than I believe we usually do in a commentary episode.
Yes, although someone did point out that it was like the 18 -minute mark where I'm like, we should
talk about Ernest. I think, you know, some of them we have gone longer than that, probably. Now, do
any of the other Ernest films tread into fantasy territory? Like Ernest saves Christmas. I feel like
we could do it Christmas time. I feel like it's you could call it a fantasy film, right? I'd
love to. Well, and as you know, and Ernest goes to jail, he controls the power of electricity.
And that's the one I would like to see again. Because I remember that one being genuinely funny.
Wow, that's got a snort out of me. Just because I don't know if there are a thousand of these
or what we're going to get going. Yeah, let's go. D .D. Lashley asks, what or who was your favorite
cameo? And since I believe I believe she's referring to ready player one. So I'm going to take
that to mean, who was your favorite cameo in movie history where you're watching it and you're like,
oh, that's awesome. This guy's in or this girl's in it. And because I have mine right off hand,
right off hand, where did that voice come from? I don't know. I'm going to answer. For me,
and I saw it very, very early because we were doing a project with one of the producers at the time
that fell apart. Zombieland, that amazing, Bill Murray extended cameo. That's also mine. Was
just really? Yeah. Yeah. I really want to see Zombieland again. So let's do that soon on the show.
Because what a thrill that was Bill Murray being in it. And it was one of those rare celebrity,
Bill Murray did a celebrity cameo and get smart. And he was like in a tree. He was like a man
dressed as a tree. It was terrible. Like a lot of times these cameos, you're excited that
somebody's in it and they don't, they don't get them anything funny to do. Zombieland gave him like
extended funny shit to do. It was an awesome cameo. It really was somehow made it to home video
viewing without having that cameo ruin for me. Oh, I just, I thought just because I saw it early,
I got it protected. Well, Pinkstone was very adamantly like, do not let anybody ruin the
cameo. Yeah. You know, so I was very careful about it. Just such, just such a treat.
Crazy that we both have that loved it. Were you thinking that before I said it? Yeah. In movie
history, that's mine. And I'll add on in TV history, because I think I've mentioned it before,
Bert Reynolds on the Golden Girls, him showing up at the end of the episode where the premise is
basically that Sophia is clearly lying about partying all night with Bert Reynolds. And that's the joke.
And then he actually walks into the fucking house at the end. It's pretty nuts.
Can you imagine the overage pussy thrown at Bert Reynolds on the set of Golden Girls?
His line is, they're the easy to roommates you told me about. And Sophia says, yeah,
he goes, which one's the slut? That's his, I watch that with you. I remember that. Yeah, it's a great
reference and asks, long time listener, first time caller. Did either of you read the book?
There's only two ready player ones. All right. Good. If so, please talk about how dumb it is.
If not, just hypothesize how dumb it is. I'll take my answer off the air. I have not read the book.
I have not read the book either. But I will say this, we're not for two of my dear friends
swearing to me that it's brilliant. I was watching that movie going, how could this book be good?
Yeah. I mean, like if I had seen it without reading the book, I would have been like, yeah,
it was a pretty scary movie. I mean, it's all right. I imagine the book probably goes deeper.
Not with this. I was like, I don't want to read this book ever.
I could not have less of a desire to read the book. None.
Ready? No, I'm not player one. Yeah. No, I was, yeah. That's the stupidest thing I've ever said in this podcast.
I was trying to say something. I lost track of it. I also maybe I'm slowly having some sort of stroke.
When I started talking in that weird accent for a minute, it alarmed me. I'm sober as a judge.
I am too. My friend believes he might have had a mini stroke.
Really? Yeah, he said he was watching TV. Nobody in comedy. Just a regular friend.
He said he was watching TV and he had like he got all like weird and he was like when he was watching
the news, he was like, they've been talking about this for a while. Wait, what's going on?
And he like, didn't have his equilibrium and like interesting. Yeah, he was like, he said he thinks he might
had a mini stroke. He's got to see all these doctors now. Matt Moy, the gentleman who played the
Asian short diner owner on two broke girls, yeah, had a stroke at age 30 while he was on the show.
Yes. And it can happen. Just yet another thing to worry about. Is he okay? Did he bounce back?
It's totally okay. He said one day he could not tie his shoes. He didn't know what was happening and
he's totally fine. He wanted to do an interview with a magazine about like how this can happen
and what to watch out for and so forth and our boss goes. What do you want to be known as stroke boy?
You're on a hit show. That's nice. And that, my friends, is the television business.
You're supposed to talk about living biblically on this because you said on the other thing you would.
I will if we have time. All right. Aaron Griffith asks, was wondering if Joe got any deeper
into trailer park boys? I have. How many hours of it are there? It's 10 seasons, right?
It's an ungodly amount of content. It's like getting into, you know, it's like saying, you know,
I think I'm going to get into Sinatra when they're walking into the section at Amiba and just being
like Jesus Christ. It's a lot. But yeah, I did and I've enjoyed everything. I circle back to it
every few months and watch a few. And then I put it down again and then I circle back and watch a few.
But people are telling me that I'm, I mean, nobody said you're wrong for this but the things I've
enjoyed most and it's probably because it's where I started were the abroad stuff where they went to
America and when they went to Europe. And I like the actual show a lot too. But those were my
favorite things. I also really like the live specials quite a bit. But I love the show. I love
the troop. I'm glad they're doing it again because apparently they stopped for a while. They wanted
to do something else and then they went back to it. If I'm going in, I should just start with season one.
I wouldn't man because I, when I started watching the show, I went back and tried to start with season
one. And it's a very different dynamic. Okay. The poster boy bubbles. They got with the glasses.
He's not a main character yet. Right. I think like, I would start with the travel things.
If I were you start with the one where the, I think the first one is the one where they go to Europe.
And there's, are there no continuity or running jokes or anything to care about?
It's just literally they go to Europe and they're all excited because they're supposed to be going
on this trip and then they get there and they find out it's like a road rules kind of thing where
they have to do tasks to get money. Okay. And they're furious and and they then they suck at all the
tasks and it's sort of a little, it's a little jackassie in the sense like some of it seems real. Okay.
Whatever. It's very pretty for the new Johnny Knoxville. I'm very excited. I am too. Just a comedy with
those stunts peppered in. I'm very excited. I'm glad that he's normal Knoxville agent this one. Yeah.
I'm excited. The Pontius is in it. I got thrilled. I mean, it's a funny trailer. Yeah.
And it made you realize how few laughs are in trailers these days. Traylor's funny. And like in
the same way, I lit up when I saw Han Solo and the Force Awakened trailer. I lit up the same way
when I saw Pontius with like a squirrel biting his dick. Yeah. Which was always this thing on jackass.
And it just made me laugh so hard. Yeah. I mean, there's nothing there in terms of pure theater
laughs. Those three jackasses cannot be beat. I agree. Well, we and what it's a shame because we need
one now more than ever. And hopefully this will be it. Who knows? Yeah. This one's from me.
Kristen Lawford asks, how and why did you start with Vine Pat? As with everything else with these
apps, I mocked it and thought it was stupid until one day I was like, well, all right. Twitter,
I remember thinking, why would I give away my jokes for free? I wish I had listened to that and not
started. Right. Sure. The time I've wasted on Twitter. Jesus Christ. But Vine always seemed very
stupid. And I thought most of the content on it was at best on funny, at worst, horrifically racist.
And then one day I was like, you know, I miss acting. Take six seconds out of my day. I don't think I
ever made a Vine when I wasn't high because that was when I would get the confidence to do one. And
weirdly, I'm probably more proud of those that little collection of videos than a lot of stuff I've
done. I thought they were weird and funny and I enjoyed doing them. And the fact that I connected and
hit with people, gravy, spawned our friendship. That's true. That's why I'm buying it. Is that
guys funny? That's true. And man, I used to get a lot of six sexual DMs from people. The problem
with Vine is that I was starting it at the top of the age spectrum for Vine. And I never know if
the DMs coming to me were from 14 year old girls or people of age. It's a little nerve wrecking.
I never partook. But I loved doing it. Thank you for asking.
Heighten Davidson asks, how do you guys keep your heads with all the ups and downs of your careers?
I mean, the short answer is we don't. Right. Honestly, a big help. A big help is Mr. Joderosa.
We vent at each other. We text each other all day. Look at this fucking son of a bitch.
Look at what this asshole posted. Yeah, I sent Pat a post today from somebody and I just wrote
Jesus fuck. Yeah. All show business is is ups and downs. It's best to remember that. It's best to
remember that most things don't work. Most things don't connect. Nobody sets out to make something
that doesn't connect. But the reason you get your heart broken is because you forget that. And you
think this is going to be the thing. This is going to be huge. This is going to be, you know,
you can't think that way. You got to assume everything is going to suck. Everything is going to be
a miserable experience. And then you can make some money at it. I agree. Walsh is a pillar for me.
You know, you're good friends, which you will have few of in this business. You will keep you sane.
And, you know, doing the podcast sort of, you know, us having a standing date every, we know that we
don't hang out outside of it, but, you know, the standing date to hang out every week at least once and do
this is very helpful. It gives us a chance to bitch. It gives us a chance to just talk about stuff for
fun and not as an opportunity. But it is tough, man. It's tough. It's a lot of ups and downs.
And I got to tell you, it's easy to forget this, but most people have only downs.
And I don't mean the syndrome. I'm talking about folks, folks, you know, like some people only have
ups. That's right. Who don't generally those people who don't deserve them. Yep. But I would say,
you know, it was only 10 years ago where I was like, well, it didn't take me long either.
I was like, I'm never going to make it. Never going to connect. Nothing's ever going to hit. Never
going to get a job. And that is so much the norm out here that it's easy to forget when you have a
setback that numerous people are 50 out here. And they're like, you know, maybe tomorrow's the day. I
am. It's people like that, yeah, yeah. It's and, by the way, you could, right? You know, you never
know when fate will deal your hand, but, boy, it is not a, as David Krummel said, this shit ain't a
meritocracy. And he was absolutely right. No, it sucks. Sarah Catherine, she of two first names
ask us, would you ever consider doing a video recording of the podcast?
Absolutely. In fact, Pat and I have talked about, you know, possibly trying to turn this
into some sort of video component, you know, like a TV formatted kind of thing. I don't
know if we will, but we certainly have discussed it. And we're certainly discussing now more than
never with Ken Hamley and Emily Florence doing live shows and stuff. So the ball is finally rolling
in that direction. So I think all of that will lend itself to it. But, you know, I was thinking
the other day, we could do a video thing for the Patreon and add another tier and say, well,
if you pay this, you get a video of us doing something. But, you know, then you're getting
into editing and shooting. Yeah. I mean, we could do maybe a bonus one week. I mean, it's
amusing to me, looking at me and Joe right now to assume that anybody would want a visual
component. We're both lying down essentially in exactly the same position. You'd get to
meet Ken, Joe's dog who's looking itself. Yeah. It's not that visually exciting. And I never
understood anybody would watch a video podcast unless you got little sketches like the Norma
Donald want or something. But we would absolutely do it and we will do it, I would say. Thank
you for asking. Tucker Rouch asks, which critically acclaimed film do each of you hate the most?
Good question. Well, I mean, look, I'm going to double down on what I always say that God
damn Terminator movies aren't any good. Oh, for God's sake. And I fought with since I've fought
with Pat on the podcast about this, we recently fought in a bar about it. And my pink stone
was with us. He was jumping in on me. Everybody was pilot on me. Nobody wonder. I don't think
that they're good movies. I keep going back every time they release one. I think the first
two are absolutely fantastic. I think the first one's better than the second one. You've
heard my spiel. I don't need to do it again. But yeah, but Cameron, I think almost everything
Cameron has made. I'd say could almost do a first place tie for me as acclaimed that I think
is not good, which he he can't stop opening his fucking yeah, these days, man. Yeah. Well,
him saying he's getting superhero fatigue. I agree with you James, but then of course I saw
80 people tweet. You're the guy making five avatars, right? Yeah, yeah, yeah. So that's my answer.
Yeah, I mean, of all his movies, I would say the least successful from a storytelling standpoint
is avatar and to think that we want five is just and it's such a risk. Like on two, I have
a feeling the box office is going to dip quite a bit from one. And then by the time you get
to five, what's what's going to happen? I couldn't give a rat fucking ass. I don't think I'd
even see it. It would have to be under two hours if I'm going to see another avatar.
It won't be. I mean, it was the 3D was novel. I know that, of course, that's not the first
use of 3D, but that if I'm not mistaken, wasn't that the first like it's back in theaters.
And this is always my argument about James Cameron with almost everyone of his movies. And
it was what I said about avatar. I go, okay, it was the first like real D movie. Take that
element out of it. It's not a good fucking movie. You know, Titanic. It's like, it's not
bad, but it's like everybody's like, and the boat looks like it's actually sick. And I'm
like, yeah, okay. But at the end of the day, do you give a fuck about any of the people in
this thing? I absolutely did. And I really love Titanic. And watching it recently on 3D, maybe
love it even more. It was a bit of a mess. I'm a little out of bounds on Titanic. I'll admit
that. No, I, that's when I get people's hate. It's a little schmaltzied, but I mean, it's a
romance. And not only that, but a historical romance, which are notoriously schmaltzied
time. And you got to Caprio running around in the galley. Right. Being a fun kid. Which is
Titanic is great. Is your answer avatar? No, not at all. Oh, okay. My, I mean shit. It's
always, you know, the four year consideration movies for the Oscars that everybody starts
talking about and gets me all wound up every year. There's like 10 to think about what
is the ultimate one? It's, it's hard to say. Like what? You know, I'd have to look at like
the, the, the most critically acclaimed film list or something. I'll, I'll play it safe
here and go with like a shape of water as a recent example. All right. I mean, just there's
always several movies a year where I'm like, what are you thinking? What are you talking
about with like a hundred percent? It happens all the time. And how the fuck did that story
just go away? Shape of water? Did you watch the short film that he was accused of copying?
I didn't. Was it close? It was ridiculous. It was, you were like, there's no way this
wasn't copied. Really? Yeah. And it just went away. Funny how these Hollywood things just
go away. Okay. I'm fucking believable, man. I did not know that. I mean, especially
because that was kind of him collaborating for the first time. Down to the way it looked.
Yeah. Like the, like the art design of it. All right. I mean, look, I, another one that pops
to mind is English patient. Never saw it. Maybe that would, would be better now that I'm an adult,
but I remember really loving when Seinfeld went after the English patient because that was a time
where you never went after those big Oscar pictures where Elaine is screaming just die at the screen.
But they really were, they did some ballsy movie jobs. Absolutely. They did the JFK thing.
Right. Right. They did the shinlers list make out. Right. Those were pretty edgy for sitcoms back then.
Yeah. I mean, for me, it's always going to be one of those big sprawling epics that just bore
the shit out of me out of Africa and all those kind of movies. I hate all those kinds of flicks.
Yeah. Yeah. Oh, Christ. Yeah. Wait. Ah, that Australia movie. No, it was Australia. It's called Australia.
Sorry. I thought you meant Oz, the great and powerful, which was absolutely terrible as well.
All right. Next Q, the flip side from Mike Hasler, St. Louis's own, an old, an old commenter on my
blog that I had 15 years ago. How are you, Mike? Which notoriously disliked film will each of you
defend to the death? Joe is yours, Norbert? It's you, you people know my answer. Batman versus Superman
till the day I die. I'm going down with the ship on that one. Wow. You'll all realize one day. And by
the way, I'd like to pat myself on the back as a prequel defender and someone who saw the Star Wars
prequel several times in the theaters and argued at length for years at parties and in bars about how
they weren't bad movies. I'd like to pat myself on the back that people now are so mad at Ryan Johnson's
the last Jedi that they are now saying, including Simon Pegg, who was a prequel hater now saying,
you know, maybe the prequels weren't so bad. Maybe we had it a little better than we thought we were
apparently not happy with the last. She was apparently part of the fringe of people that we're not happy
with last Jedi. I wasn't thrilled with last Jedi, but I kind of go back and forth. I mean, I certainly
liked it. Um, yeah, for me, I mean, I have, I have tons. I mean, uh, I guess it's gotten a little
respect over time, but a review that I can almost cite verbatim was the F given to Kingpin by
Lisa Schwartzbaum and entertainment weekly in 1996. Uh, the un F idiotic. And I was pacing
stripped of her job. I agree. I tweeted at her once and she came back real hard. I was like,
oh, I was just kidding. You can not like the movie. That's fine. But, um, I mean, yeah,
Kingpin is not a, Kingpin is a pan film, for sure, but notoriously disliked that I enjoyed. Um,
I wish I was the kind of guy that could think of these immediately. Um,
and that's the look at like a list of hated movies, but I feel like there's always a couple of
years where I'm like, that was, that was pretty good. What are you talking about? Well, I remember you were
the one that told me vacation was funny. It had like a 23 % or something reboot. Sure. You know,
you said, yeah, generally it's comedy. You certainly can't trust rotten tomatoes on comedies. That's
it's just, you know, because most critics are older. I guess now in the internet age, that's not
the case, but comedy is a young man's game. Uh, okay. Yeah, I wish, I wish I had a better example.
I'll say, I'll say Kingpin, but you know, that there's a bunch. Um, and a lot of the fairly brothers
output, I thought whole, here we go. I'll go further with you because Kingpin has a lot of respect.
I thought whole pass was a funny move. I like tall pass. I didn't, I didn't hate it.
And there was a great joke and a cock joke in it. Oh, yeah, yeah, we're, oh, and Wilson had that
the giant dick next to his face. Yeah, I like tall, but today kiss was really funny in it. Simon
merchant was very funny in it. Steven merchant. Sorry. It was really funny in it. Um, and I like,
you know, I like, well, I guess I will, I will say all the fairly brothers. Yeah, that's where I was
going to go with this. All that fairly brothers output that is just shat upon three studios has
funny parts in it. Um, shallow howl has funny shit in it. Stuck on you is a pretty good Hollywood
satire. It's got some funny. I believe stuck in you was their last decent film. Okay, fair enough.
Uh, now you're also going to say the heart. Fairly enough. I can't go that far. But there are lots of
those kind of like comedies that you'll find for a dollar at the grocery store that I thought
were better than most because I'm happy to just see people trying to make me laugh. All right,
and I have low standards for comedies because they're so rarely good. Okay, um,
couple, you know, a few laughs. I'm on, I'm on board. Emily, okay, Emily is reminding me I can turn
comments off. Thank you, Emily. Josh Brown, what, what are your favorite horror comedies?
I think we've probably discussed that on the show before. Uh, mine is unquestionably dremers.
Okay. But if we're going, if we're a true horror slash comedy, I think that's got to be it.
Uh, I just thought it was really a perfect blend of action, horror, comedy, and
scintillating banter between bacon and mord. Yeah, you once called it, uh,
off the off the charts, I believe the charts. Uh, um, my intent's down the burbs,
110 % has been forever. Yeah, we'll always be, uh, yeah, burbs is fantastic.
I can't say enough good stuff about the, but I actually think the burbs is one of Tom Hanks's
best films, but it's, but it get, it just got kind of shuffled away in like 80s movie.
Right. In the 80s movie garbage, uh, toss out or whatever. It's, it's so much better than it gets
credit for. The humor is so dry. Uh, it's very smart. It actually does have creepy parts in it.
Like it's, it's really good. All right. Yeah, I mean, as far as critically pan stuff go, I mean,
Turner and Hooch money pit. Turner Hooch was, uh, no, Turner Hooch was a huge hit.
Huge hit. Yeah, I can still be a critically pan move. Critics pan, Turner and Hooch,
they as far as I can recall, uh, who's Harry Crumb? I probably has a 9 % hilarious movie.
The lot of Karen Kilgarif, once again was honestly legitimately mad at us that was we told
it a lot of 80s comedies are like that where they were just completely lambasted. I was listening,
uh, I'm listening to an audio book about the making of Caddy Shack. And they talked about how
everyone went to this press conference the day after it opened with like coke eyes hung over.
It was at Dangerfield's comedy club. The only person who dressed up was Ted Knight.
And he shows up in a blazer with his hair slick like, oh, I thought we were doing a press conference.
Why do you guys all look like shit? Bill Murray comes in and Jim Schwartz with a pizza and he's like,
sorry, I'm real hungry with giant glasses on because everyone had heard how shitty Caddy Shack was.
It was shadowed by the press and they were like, let's go in there and do this fucking shit now.
They all went out and got tanked tonight before. Uh, and now it's a legendary picture. Uh, by the way,
speaking of Turner and Hooch, yeah. Remember how you were looking at my HBO history on Hulu?
And you said, why did you watch Richie Rich? Yeah. And I said, I didn't. It just put it on there
for some reason. That was the truth. It keeps adding shit. It's got the sequel to Canine on
there now. Canine 11. Yeah. Yeah. I didn't fucking watch that. It's in my fucking recently watch.
Does somebody with terrible taste have your password? Uh, yes. Really? Yes, they do.
Well, I need do I know this person? Because this is really bad taste. Canine 11.
Richie Rich. You don't know this person. Jesus. I realized on my HBO, I had all sorts of weird shit
and I realized Pete's been using it for years. Pete, who's going into season three of an HBO show
will not spring for HBO. He uses my password. This is a man that once said to me, I've bought the movie
on iTunes because I was too lazy to get up and get the DVD out of the other room. Right. Won't spring
for the HBO girl. Well, he called, he texted me and was like, can I use your password? You want to
watch the Spielberg documentary? And I was like, Pete, you can have it, but shouldn't, well,
I don't understand. Like, not forget the money, but you work for HBO. Like what are you talking about?
And he admitted that he'd been using it for years. He had borrowed it once before. And that explains
all this weird shit. You know, I'm glad it wasn't like some soft -core erotic or something popping up.
He'll lean. He'll lean. Yeah. He left a Christmas gift here for his brother. Yeah. He dropped it and
said, I'll be back. I'll be back to get it tomorrow. I said, no problem. It was here for three months.
To the point where I texted him, hey, Pete, I have an idea for a fun hang. It's called, get this
fucking shit out of my apartment. So, you know, the HBO thing makes sense. All right. Fair enough.
All right. Amanda El Zamora asks, what has been your worst celebrity interaction?
Oh, all right. I got one. Okay. You can go first if you want.
Oh, boy. Well, I mean, unquestionably Max Weinberg drummer for Conan, the Max Weinberg 7,
biggest asshole I've ever seen. And I think I talked about him on the show, but he used to, he
about gave me an ulcer because it was kind of my first, I loved an idolized Conan so much.
I was a 22 -year -old kid working on my favorite show and everybody couldn't have been nicer,
including Conan. Conan's got a bit of a dick vibe, but you know, he says it with love.
Weinberg, man, he had to have a bucket of ice to ice down his knuckles after doing literally
the easiest drumming. And if you forgot that bucket of ice in his dressing room, he would come out
shirtless and just scream in your face. He made these interns cry, like, you know, 18 -year -old girl
sobbing every day. He brought interns out to his house to do yard work one weekend for the entire weekend,
didn't pay them. And so this is, this guy's been drumming for Bruce Springsteen for 40 years. The man
has a billion dollars. Ridiculous. Just a complete asshole. And the other would be when
Aristotle came to SNL, you know, just a nightmare, trashed, or dressing room, dog shit everywhere.
But that wasn't necessarily a mean to me. Generally celebrities are nice and they have publicists
who are mean on their behalf. Mine will always be, it's not Dave Chappelle.
I was on, I'm saying that because I was on tour with Dave Chappelle in the story. I don't want you to
think I'm going to say he was mean to me. He, Dave, was Chris Isaac? Yes. I think we may have told
both of our stories. All right. Well, the Chris Isaac story. I'm on tour with Dave. Dave's treating me
like a god damn prince amongst thieves, making me feel like I'm really part of this business. Just being
the best dude, introduced me, introduces me to Chris Isaac because he knows that I love the album Forever
Blue so much. Yeah. Chris Isaac says he turns to me. I tell him how much it meant to me to find my life.
And he said, yeah, thanks. And just turned and kept talking to Dave. Didn't just couldn't have given
rest of a shit. So anyway, I hate to hear it. I just watched Chris Isaac perform two hearts on MTV
Unplugged. That was the YouTube poll I was on the other night. Matt voice sounded as good as it did
on record. I just kind of wanted to know like does does he effortlessly hit those notes that I
hit in my car? No problem. But sure enough, he did. He sounded great. And for a guy to write those
songs and sing that well and be that handsome, I feel like Chris Isaac should have been an even bigger
star. Well, I'm going to say this. A lot of his albums suck. That's true. You get that forever
Blue record and you're like, and that's the big one. And you go, Oh, my God, I got to get more.
Can you start getting branching out? You're like, what is this? Well, they're inconsistent.
The singles are usually good. And yeah, I'll go get you. All right. Fair enough.
Misty Zavar asks, if you were on a deserted island with only a screen, electricity, a blue ray
player and your three all time favorite movies, what would those movies be? Well, just for an occasion
like this, I keep my favorite films written down in my phone, my top 10. I actually want to see
my top three in my top 10. I'd have to switch this. But hand in her sisters is my number one.
Glangarry Glen Ross is my number two. Good Fells is my number three. If I was put in on an island,
though, I'd have to move that around. Exorcist would get moved up into the top three because I'd
want a little hard now and again. And that third, I don't even think I think Kingpin would have to
go in there because I'd want a comedy. And then I got to be honest guys, I think empire strikes back
would get put in there were raiders because I need, you know, you need to escape a little once in a
while. So my top three would be different if I run an island. Yeah, I mean, island does kind of
switch it up. If you would ask me my, because you're also asking my three all -time favorite movies.
Island might switch it. I guess it shouldn't. My number one's going to be Goodfellas,
my number two's probably going to be playing strands of automobiles.
Number three, maybe sling blade.
And then my other favorites are it's a wonderful life. Do the right thing.
Jackie Brown, you know, raising Arizona. I'd want raising Arizona there. I think that's an
endlessly rewatchable picture. There you go. There's a bunch.
Just saw this on Instagram. Fantastic onion headline. I'm glad you're on Instagram.
Well, I just, I was looking to see if there was, you know, stuff to, no, I wasn't. I just,
while you were talking, I looked at it. I'm sorry. It was weak of me. That doesn't make it better.
I apologize. You give your answer and then hop on Instagram for mine. I just got, I just, I'm sorry.
I'm apologizing, but this is. People are paying for this. This is very funny. Go on, onion headline. New
California law invalidates thousands of marriages between ship captains and the sea.
Is that a brandy reference or just, you know, it's like our captains are always like,
I'm married to the sea. Right. Well, you know, the song Brandy. No, the sailor said, Brandy.
I think you meant that you're a fine girl. What a good wife you would be. But my life, my
lover, my lady is the sea. I think that comes from this, from the ship captain saying it. Yeah,
I don't think the song is from the point of view of the other ship captain. Yeah, I don't think
the guy that wrote Brandy came up with that. All right. Fair enough. Chris Marsh asks, either of you
have a good loss of virginity story. Oh, yeah. All right. I was in a bar. I didn't lose my
virginity at all. It's 21 years old. I was very old and I was in a bar and I've always had a
bit of a flair for an older woman. You know, I always find that very sexy 70, 75. Oh, that's
a spring chicken in my book. And I was 21. I was sitting next to a very attractive woman who was like
in her mid or late 30s. So at the time, that was quite an older woman to me. Yeah. And I started
talking to her. We started hitting it off. And she was a professor at a college that I had attended
and transferred out of. Okay. And I started dating her. And she told me, look, we were
fooling around one night. And she said, I want to stop this before it goes too far. She goes, I didn't
tell you this, but I'm moving away at the end of the month to Atlanta, Georgia. Okay. And I said,
okay. And she goes, so I can't sleep with you because it's just not going to mean anything. And
I don't want to do that. And I said, look, I got news for you. I'm a virgin. And man,
did she love the idea of being number one? Okay. On her last night in town, she, I would gifted my
virginity to her, made love to an older woman who showed me the ropes. How old was she? She was 37,
36 somewhere in there. You know, well, went great. Okay. Went great. Wrap it up. Yes, I wrapped it up.
Okay. Yeah. Could you wrap this up? And I also, I remember not understanding how condoms
worked at the time. I still don't thank God. I don't have to use them. And I remember asking my
friend Dan, like, you know, I used a condom. But, but my penis still felt wet when I took the condom
off. Does that mean her vaginal juices got inside the condom? And he goes, no, you fucking idiot.
That's just what your dick is like from the lubricant on the condom. Right. And he did a, he,
he mimed for me what a, what a germ would have to do to get inside the condom. Sure. And he,
and I remember the whole time that he was finger, using his fingers to show the germ walking up the
condom to the rim. He was going, did, did, did, did, did, did, did, did, did, did, uh, uh,
well, that's not entirely true though. I mean, if you're in balls deep, uh, you're getting juices
around the rim on your balls. If you didn't pull the condom all the way to the balls,
you're not getting full coverage. Juice isn't getting in the rim though. Juice isn't getting in the tip.
Juice isn't going from the rim up to the goal. That was more for the funny visual of a bug
rolling to the circus music. I don't think, uh, they like the term juice either, but, um, sorry,
I'm sorry. Her squirt, I meant to say, I lost my virginity a year later than you, Joe, uh,
which was already shockingly late, 21. I was 22. Uh, I never understood how anyone had sex.
I have been notoriously bad at like talking to girls. And then I had my first drink. And I was like,
got it. Now I understand how people have sex. It was just that easy, you know, because like,
the thing keeping me from going like, Hey, what about the two of us have sex was alcohol.
And by the way, that that's always been my line. Hey, and I put my hand on the wall behind them,
right, kind of lean at you. You'll only do this to women that work for you.
Well, I like it when they work directly beneath me, folks. And above me, uh, no, I,
yeah, I guess it's a decent story. I have my first drink. I was like, okay, I understand.
Um, because I had had a long time girlfriend as well, who basically would have been fine with
other means of sexuality, but not in the front. Um, and I did not want to lose my virginity in that
manner. Um, we went, uh, when I went to New York, basically, I had been in New York a week.
I lived with this kind of nutty woman who would drink a bottle of red wine every night,
uh, and get kind of weird and flirty, but I was not interested at all. Right. And, uh, finally,
she said, Hey, I'm going to be interviewing some new roommates for this other room.
I had this couple that lived there who I'm still friendly with that I love. She was like, they're
leaving. You want to help me meet some people. I met these applicants and there was one really,
really attractive young lady. I was like, I'd go with that one. I did. She didn't know anyone in the
city. I didn't know anyone in the city. My friends came to visit. We all got really drunk. We got back
to the apartment. I started to walk down the hall to my room. She grabbed my hand, walked me down the
hall to her room. We did it. Part of it was the drunkenness part of it was that I had been masturbating for
years and years three, four times a day. Right. Uh, but it took me, I have the exact opposite
of everyone else's virginity story. It took me forever forever to come. Right. Where I sort of
apologize. I was like, I don't know what's have. I'm sorry. It usually doesn't take this long.
Right. And then I had to say to her, which I never would say now afterwards. I was like, sorry,
you know, that was my first time. I don't know why that took so long. And she was like,
sad up and bad. It was like your first time. I mean, I was a man. It was a grown man. Right.
And I wished I had not said it. But it certainly wasn't magical. But it led to many superior times
after that. Did you have sex with her ever again? I'm saying. I just said, oh, I thought you meant
superior with other people. No, well, of course that. But we had tons of sex. And then I didn't
realize I didn't want to be living with somebody I was having sex with. I tried to break it off and
thought we could just go on being a room. We moved out and got a place together. And those
wheels were in motion once we fucked. So after we fucked, I set up at bed. It was kind of like,
now I'm having sex with somebody I'm going to be living one on one with. Yeah, that didn't feel
good. And believe it or not, that stuff went south a real fancy. Yeah. All right.
Joshua Taj Bozeman asks, how on earth does a grown adult make the sort of romantic friendships
like the one you and Joe seem to have? Not seem to. Not to mention the seemingly endless number of
friends you guys mentioned from time to time. It's not endless, believe me. Especially an adult who
dislikes bars and insanely crowded places. Are you guys just very lucky? Or am I missing the special
sauce? It's a touching question. It's a great question. It is much easier to make friends when you're
say in high school or college because you're surrounded by a lot of people with the same age,
same general interests. But I would say it was quite a fluke. I met Joe through Pete. We went to
dinner together. When I saw Joe, I was like, fuck, I hate when people bring guests. It makes me
uncomfortable. I just wanted to see my friend. Pete's big on that. We're just shitting all over Pete
this week. You don't need to add him and tell him this, folks. It's all lighthearted. But Pete's
always like, hey, here's this guy. And I was like, oh, and the Joe and I connection was immediate
and very rare. I'm not normally that person at all. In fact, I normally hate most people I meet.
So I think it's rare and you just got to, you can't put yourself in a position where you're never
going to meet me one. It's the same as dating. You have to meet someone. You don't have to go to
an insanely crowded place or a bar. But it's hard. It is hard. We are insanely lucky to answer your question.
I continually, I'm not saying as close as I got with Pat here, but I continually seemingly making
friends and adulthood, but because I am quite open to it. I also don't like people, but that makes me
open to it because when I connect with somebody uniquely, I want to be their friend. So I've connected
with Pat that night uniquely to get another Pete dig in because we all watched Ace of Ensure
when Nature calls and Pete mocked it as being a bad movie. And Pat and I were like, what the
fuck are you talking about? Idiot. So when something like that happens with me, where I really bond with
somebody, I'm like, I think any friends with this guy, right? I didn't realize that that was the
first that we hung out. Was that Ace Venture tonight? That same night about that. That was that
Pete went to Mass Hall or a little dumb. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I remember a little dumb. It's not the
rest. So that's, I think if you're open to it and you recognize a specific unique connection you have
with somebody, it's anything's possible. Yes. Find out if one of these hellions lives in your hometown.
Or so I always see these hellions talking. I'm like, I hope at least two hellions of fucked. I'll
say that. And I hope at least 50 hellions have become friends. I see you guys all interacting. You
must be friends. That's nice. It is nice. But online, you know, especially in dating, I missed
that whole world. I mean, get online if that's your thing. But you do have to leave the house to make
friends. Generally, I try activities. I wish you luck. Yeah. You know, you know, I hate to say it,
but join a team or a league or something. And that'll be a night of awkwardness. But usually you'll find
somebody you vibe with. Paul Merchie asks, asks, what's the movie you love the most that most
people hate? Man, we've answered that. Greg says, well, for Joe, it's obviously Batman versus Superman.
See? They know me. I hope they find about how shitty that movie is. We've done it. We've,
go back through the archives. Daniel Duer asks, Pat, how did you and Heather meet? And for Joe,
how did you and Con meet? Erica Branding says my friend Katie helped joke at his dog who is a rescue.
Is that your story? Oh, yeah. That is that. Well, that is well, Katie. Yeah. Katie told me.
All right. So Katie had gotten a dog. And I said, well, it's a great dog and everything. And where'd
you get him or her? I think it's her. And she said, there's this place called no KLA and KLA.
It's a no killed shelter. And you know, the good thing about them is you can you can kind of look
up the dogs on their website and stuff. Right. So I went home that night. I looked up the website.
I looked at dog profiles. They had like just like on a dating site. They had like parameters you
could put in. So I was like, okay, I don't want a dog that weighs more than this. And you know,
should be this a around this age or whatever put all that shit in. And they had a profile for old
con here at the time. His name was Chance, which I changed, obviously, but they had a video of
him. And I was like, that is literally the exact dog I want. That's a perfect dog. And I went down
to get him. And when I met him, he was kind of a douche like he didn't really talk to me. Not talk,
you know what I mean? He didn't he seemed to he seemed to give a shit. Like take it or leave it,
but I'll stay in this fucking pound. I don't care. Right. Uh, and then I met a chihuahua who was
very friendly and lovable. And I almost took the chihuahua. And I was like, I got a dice roll on
that that terrier, man, something about him. I, I just like it. Yeah. So I brought him home and the
rest is history. And then I found out actually him not being all over me was a, was a good thing.
Because it showed that he's a trained dog that isn't going to jump all over you. Uh, he was
respecting boundaries and stuff, which I didn't know that at the time. I just thought that what he
meant he wasn't friendly. Did he have the bark? That bark came later. He only barks when when we
come in the door, I guess. Unless he does it at home throughout the day. No, he barks. When somebody
comes to the door, he barks at people. But I think he just is saying hello. His tail is always wagging.
Okay. And he's never mean about it. He's never growling. It feels angry and hostile to me because
the bark is horrible. Yeah. It's a harsh, horrible bark. It's a harsh bark. And my cat has developed a
harsh meow as well. And it's getting annoying. What's a harsh meow?
That's so weird. My cat noise caused Tom to make the first move. And I've seen he jolted up
like in a horror movie. He didn't care for that. Um, but we are so adorable. And it's just a funny cat.
Like we laugh all the time at this cat. But this meowing is not helping its cuteness at all.
Listen to this bark.
Don't force him to bark. I just want to get emotional here. That was the good bark. There's a bad one,
too. Anyway, Heather and I met basically through a friend whose girlfriend was best friends with
Heather. It's kind of the standard way. Um, but we met at a music festival for the first time
going as a group. And it was one of these EDM type deals. And I was not kind of not into it.
But I really wanted to see James Murphy of LCD sound system who was DJing. So I was like, I'm going
to go watch James Murphy. And everybody else wanted to go see something else. And I was like, that's
fun. I'll go by myself. I know that I'm the other one who wants to see this. And she was like,
I'll go with you. I want to go with you. And I was like, no, because I knew she wanted to see
what everybody else was seeing. I was like, don't worry about it. This is how I didn't get laid for
so long. I was talking myself out of it. And so finally, I probably heard her fucking feelings.
I thought I was sparing her feelings and being like, you don't have to come with me. She was trying
to hang out with me. So she thought I wasn't interested. She came to a taping of a show I was writing
for. I met her briefly. And then she came to a party, which I found out later,
looking to get with the wall. She had been into me from afar. And there was a time when that
kind of had to be how you approached me because I was bad at the approach. Right. She was dressed
very provocatively. She walked past me and slapped me on the ass. And I was talking to our dear friend
comedian, Laura Kightlinger. She goes, why the fuck are you talking to me and not that dish over
there? And I was like, you're right. Struck up a conversation. Here we are five years later.
Wow. I remember being very angry because I did not want to be in a relationship. And I talked
her for like an hour and I was like, fuck. I like it. I like this story. It's a cute little story.
You might hear it at the wedding. Who knows? Oh, I plan on telling it at the wedding.
This is beach. I got a speech. I love the idea that Joe will be having his first drink in two
months at my wedding. I might not though. I might just not drink. All right. Well, then don't do the
addibles. I don't need, I don't need you weird at the way. I'm not going to get weird, relax. But I
might not drink, but I feel like you'd be so disappointed if I didn't drink it. You're
wedding. I would a little bit. But I don't care. But I don't, I just might not drink. But yeah,
that would be fun to get real shit faced. Yeah. And get up. She comes the way. She comes to the
bar to get with Pat. She's got, she's showing it off. There's a smoking patio also at my wedding.
By the way, for reefer, for whatever you want. Well, I'll be smoking a few stooages as I like to
call the shigs. We're gonna have cigars as well. Joseph Ray Goza asks, Pat, do you think you will
ever run out of ideas for on with the Joe's? I already have. Frankly, I turned to the Facebook page
because I mean, the real issue is if I thought of one on the way over here, I'd be good to go. But
the fact every week, Joe, I'm like, Oh, shit, I need to think of one now while I'm on the air.
It's too much pressure. It's like trying to piss while somebody's staring at your dick. And
look, we've all been there. And I am staring at his dick while he is doing that part. Right. So
Taylor Parrot asks, and then I assume I'll ask again, because his last name is Parrot. Well, you
ever do a live show. Big question. Maybe have us, Helians in a theater play an awesome horror movie.
You two have mics. Do commentary throughout the show. The wheels are very much in motion.
We already talked about it. We did. We look so we're gonna do one in October, hopefully.
I think we're gonna do smaller dates prior, hopefully. We'll let you know. You'll be the first to
know. Rich McBeath, hopefully a real name. For Joe, top five rap producers. Five. Sorry, it's
not a big question. Just curious. No, that's a great question. DJ premier is my number one.
Dr. Dre is my number two. The bomb squad who don't really do much together anymore. I don't think
my number three, my number four is Sir Jinx, who produced a lot of the earlier ice cube stuff.
And my five is DJ Mugs from Cypress Hill. I like the producers who yell their name at the
beginning of a track. Well, that's DJ Khaled. That's the DJs that do that. They make like mixed
tapes. And then because they're just playing you other people's songs, they have to yell their
own name over the entire night. Mike Will made it. And I guess that's in their contract. You
want to have a hit? You got to let me put this on the DJ mustard. I mean, there's some great DJs
out there. Funkmaster Flex is great. Sure. But like, you know, but some of those mixed tapes,
I've never heard of DJ Khaled one. Some of them, I'm literally like the Wendy Williams would put
them out. And it's like, this is literally just a compilation of other people's songs and you just
put your name on it. Yeah. Odd. Yeah. All right. I think that these DJs we're talking about now are
producers. They have the beats and they just go by DJ, but I don't think they're like DJ DJ.
Who? DJ Khaled, you know, he's a, I think he actually makes me. Yeah, he does. He does.
As does, you know, Mike Will, etc. He's a producer. Pat, whatever happened Emily Griffith asks,
Pat, whatever happened to your neighborhood stalker, that hey, boss story of yours still gives me
the creeps told this on the, you made it weird with Pete Holmes podcast as I believe I did the
virginity story. Sorry, but he still lives in the neighborhood. I haven't seen him in months.
I think they, I know they don't give lobotomies, but it seems like they gave him a lobotomy. He looks
comatose when I see him. He's never outside anymore. And he was a real problem for the first year.
I live there. Now have you said to him, hey, buddy, you don't lobotomy. I don't lobotomy you.
Have you said that to him yet? I will the next time I see. He won't get it because it's a lobotomy, but
yeah, I mean, he's still around until he goes off his meds again and kills us both as we sleep. And
hopefully that doesn't happen. All right. Tess Annette asks, what is both your next big project coming up?
TV gigs, writing. All right, Tess. I have a project. I have a pilot that will hopefully be
happening soon. I've postponed a lot of other stuff because it was supposed to have happened
a couple of times already, but we're having a little, a little red tape issue. So hopefully that'll
be out soon. And I'm trying to sell a book and a film. So we'll see. Yes. And I will, my show hasn't
been canceled, but it has. It also basically has. It's like a 99 .9%. And they do this because they're
miserable fox who I mean specifically CBS. Here it is. And they will try to keep you from taking
other work. And they do this to actors and they do this to writers as well. But they won't officially
cancel it. They'll leave you hanging on. Now is staffing season. The time when I should be going on
meetings to find out what my next project is. And I am doing that, folks, but I'm doing it like
illegally because I'm under contract. They'll let me know the show is canceled after that period
has ended so that I can't take work. These people are soulless and awful. They do it to the actors.
The entire cast currently can't go do other projects because they're hanging on for the show that
they just pulled off the fucking air. So I I'll wind up somewhere. I have a lot of things in the hopper.
I've got shows. I've got movie things. I've got things happening. I don't have anything to announce
just yet. But, you know, I need to have this stuff officially done before I can move on and make
announcements. We have about time for one more. We're at about 59 minutes here. I promise these people,
I was reading them till I said stop. So we got more to go. We got more to go. How many more?
And we don't always have to be an hour. We can go over on these. Well, how many more? Just so
I have an idea. The end's inside. But, you know, here we go. We'll pick it up a little bit.
And maybe there'll be some doubles. I'm enjoying myself. I'm not having a bad time. I just,
you know, got a dog and everything. Describe your dream woman. Ask some and a leapson.
And I can tell from her question. She's hoping you describe her. I'm going to go with the old
Kastanza. Marisa Tome, probably. Oh, okay. It has always been the, well, she's saying describe,
not just like pick a celebrity that you want to say. And just what Marisa Tome looks like. And then
I don't have to go through all the damn. I'm not getting into like, there's no personality.
Why that stuff? No, no, everything about everything about Marisa Tome hits what I would love
in a lady. Okay. Like the figure, the face, the spunk, the attitude, the talent, the sense of
humor, everything about her is spot on. Do you think that holding this ideal of one of the most
perfect women in the world might have kept you single low these past 40 years? No, I've never held
her as my ideal. In real life, I'll go out with anybody. But yeah, no, I'm kidding. No, I've never
held anybody the ideal. I'm just saying, you're talking like dream woman. And I did, if I had to make
a woman like weird science, I'd make Marisa Tome. I really can't disagree with that. I mean, she's
more attractive and appealing 30 years later than she was like in my cousin Benny. It's incredible.
Question for both, what is your most prized possession? I think we, am I sitting next to yours,
Joe? Yes, mine is my 1983 Mint Condition Star Wars arcade cabinet that is also rigged to play
the Empire Strikes Back game as well. And Con. And I gotta say, I feel like if Marisa Tome was in
this apartment, that would seal the deal for her, the Star Wars machine. I think she would think it
was cool. I think she might. She'd say, yeah, let's play this fucking thing. Why else do you have it?
She might. My most prized possession, I will say, is my, and I own the entire Criterion collection.
You've, you've gotten there. You finally own on Blu -ray. I own the entire Criterion. That's great.
Every Criterion Blu -ray I own, DVD, no, but Blu -ray I do. And really, all that is is when I was a kid,
I would be like, wow, what if one day I could do that? It's actually not hard to do. They come out
with three a month, it's 60 bucks. No, it is not 60 bucks. Those fucking things start at like 30,
40 bucks, man. I only buy them at the Barnes and Noble 50 % off sale, or through the Criterion website,
which is, they're always 20 bucks. You can get them for 20 on the website? When they have a sale.
When they have a sale. And when you spend a certain amount, they give you a nice $50 gift card and
ain't that much that you gotta spend. They're a great company. All right. That's probably mine.
You know, I'm a simple man. I don't, I don't have a lot of possessions. Okay.
Or my record collection, which brings us to my next question. Kevin Marcinick, what are some
records both of you have been into lately? Doesn't have to be from this year.
Uh, lately. Well, I've been listening to, oh, God. I've been listening to this Elvis comp
that I've been enjoying. Pressley or Castella? Pressley on vinyl. I've been listening to Sinatra,
the reprise years, which is a nice vinyl set. So when he said doesn't have to be from this year,
he did mean does have to be from the century. Oh boy. Oh, bad religion. The gray race just came
out on vinyl colored vinyl remastered. I just picked that up. I'm enjoying that revisiting that record.
And man, I'm blanking. I know I have something else that I've been kind of spinning a lot, but I can't
remember, but that's enough. It's a great answer. Uh, I finally, I, because I get obsessed with
shit and listen to them exclusively for long periods of time. Just now, after like a year plus, I have
broken my Tusk Fleetwood Mac addiction. I was always listening to Tusk by Fleetwood Mac,
particularly the Lindsey Buckingham songs, which they now have thrown him out of the band again.
He's out of the band again? They, what do you do? Just like the last time they had to replace him with
two people. Why is he thrown out? I'm sure he was being a dick. He's a notorious prickly kind
of perfectionist type guy. They threw him out there, placed him with the guy from the heartbreakers,
Mike Campbell, and also with Neil Finn from Crowded House. Is the, is the witch lady still in there?
What's your face? Stephen X. Yeah. Oh, yeah, I mean, without those two, there wouldn't be a band.
She's on there because she was gone for a long time, right? They've always had one of the other, but I
think next, yeah, next was out. They've had the, the keyboardist Christine McVee was out for a while.
You know, it's a, it's a band where they've all fucked. They all like cheated on their spouses with
each other. There's a lot of bad blood and probably things that didn't get resolved. They need to do
that Metallica therapy shit. They probably won't do it. I listened, lately, I listened to a lot of
rocksy music, which is a band from 70s. I love them. The song both ends burning. I listen to
every day to get ready. I listen to, well, I don't know, I tend to be a song guy. I make big playlists,
listen to a bunch of songs. I like the new LCD sound system. I don't know what to tell you.
Again, these are hard to think of on the spot. All right. The new Queen's is pretty good,
but not great. The new Queen's is done. I came and went with that one. I loved it, and then I
didn't have to stick around. But their cover of Good By Yellowberg Road is phenomenal. They did
it live when I saw them. It was great. Yeah, I think that's probably enough. I could go on and on,
but you know, whatever. Next cue. If you could switch two movie characters, what switch would
lead to the most inappropriate movies asks Brooke Adams? I don't understand that question.
If you could switch to movie care, like put somebody in another movie, let's say.
Okay. The nutty professor, the Jerry Lewis nutty professor in Schindler's list, I guess.
The best thing. That's the day of the clown crime, I believe.
Well, yeah, it's what maybe think of it, but that might get released this year, by the way,
on DVD. We might finally see that movie. Oh, really? That's a notorious Jerry Lewis bomb that
got immediately like put into a vault because they were so embarrassed by it, but it sounded like life
is beautiful. It's a guy trying to make comedy in the Holocaust. You people have seen it. Harry Sheerer
is one of them. Yeah. All right. I'll say that is a hard question. I'll say Mary Poppins in the
wrestler with Mickey Rourke. And then so he becomes Mary Poppins and she becomes the wrestler.
I think that's a good answer. Okay. Holy shit. The next question is who's your favorite wrestler?
That's weird. Synchronicity. The police. Andrew Rich asks who's your favorite wrestler?
The rock hands down of all time. I love the rock. And I've just never been into wrestling.
My favorite, I know the ultimate warrior used to scare me a lot as a kid, but you know,
I'd go with somebody big that everyone likes, you know, like either Hulk Hogan or I don't know
I mean the rock just a few people have had that kind of charisma. Yeah. I have his DVDs
in with my comedy DVDs because I literally just watched them and laugh hysterically.
It's just an amazing fucking character. I love it. All right.
I like that new breeders album quite a bit. I saw them the other night. Front row.
Absolutely killer. If they come to your city, go see them. Are both deals in the band right now?
Both deals. The Kelly deal looks like Michael Jackson. These are two of the least glamorous rock stars
of all time. I mean, she looks like Michael Jack. Her face is entirely new and it looks a little
unsettling. Really? You hate to talk about it, but it was jarring to me. Then I looked them up and
they're like 57 the breeders. Yeah. And Kim comes out. You know, I hadn't even brushed her hair. You
and especially because their twins like to see them look that different is a little weird, but
Kim deals voice is still just absolutely incredible and their new album is pretty good.
I like I liked half of it. I thought it was I had too many slow numbers on it, but I'll go back.
They tend to go more that way and they sound a better live the new songs. Sometimes that's the case.
Favorite ballad asks Patrick Baxter. So favorite
Patrick Baxter asks, what is your favorite ballad? I guess they mean what, you know, favorite slow
song or favorite sad song? My favorite ballad and it's a contender for my favorite song of all time
is it was a very good year by Frank Sinatra. I love the song used to genius effect on the sopranos
show you refused to watch. It was a season premiere. They used the song to update you on everybody in
the show. It was incredible. It's a brilliant song. It's beautifully written. It's beautifully
orchestrated. His version of it is, you know, the one for me. Oh boy. Haunting, I'd use the word
haunting. My favorite ballad. I mean, that's impossible. There's too many to choose, but a few that
spring to mind are Elliott Smith, ballad of big nothing. I find that a beautiful and insanely
depressing song. I would say I love stolen car by Bruce Springsteen. Very sad song.
And I, you know, there's too many to choose. I need time to think. I would say there's a bunch.
That's all I can say. Wicked game by Chris Isaac is a great one. Go, yeah.
Yeah. I'll get back to you. I'll get back to you. All right.
Boom, boom, boom, boom. Which VHS cover art scared you the most or left a long lasting impression
from the days of browsing the rental store before you were old enough to rent scary movies
as Derek Clark? I had, I would say all of them because all horror boxes scared the shit out of
it. It's my favorite horror movie. The exorcist cover to this day gives me the creeps,
which is funny because the cover is of the priest. He's the good guy in the movie. Right.
But it's just real fucking creepy. So that's always been the one that resonated most with me. Okay.
And yeah, I really couldn't even even name just one. But I mean,
uh, that, you know, we talked about, uh, doctor giggles, you know, for some reason.
And then you flip it to the back and there'd be a thousand things back there that would scare me.
They, they all scared. And then you see them when you're an adult and you're like, I was scared of
this. Like what, what the fuck? All right. There are a lot of these. I can't deny it. We're getting
close. Alison Lee asks, what was your favorite childhood novel? And please read Harris and me,
if you haven't, it's hilarious. Is that the Harris Whittles book? I don't know. All right.
Favorite child novel. I would think so. But, uh, my favorite childhood novel without question was
Maniac McGee. Uh, I absolutely loved it. It's, it's for, you know, a 12, 13 year old kid probably.
I recommended it to a woman I worked with and, uh, she read it to her son and it like traumatized him.
She was like, how depressed for you as a kid that you liked that book? I was like very depressed.
Uh, and, and earlier than that, I loved a book called Rent a Third Grader.
But Maniac McGee, I, I imagine would still hold up. It was great. And I loved all those Beverly
Cleary books, Ralph House, Mouse, Ramona, Ramona, the past, all that. I loved, uh, I loved the
something queer series, like something queer at the library, something queer at the museum.
There's a title you couldn't have anymore. It, it, it meant it in its traditional sense, like, uh,
you know, it was these kid detectives, something strange as a foot here. Uh, but I also really loved,
and these aren't novels, but they were books I adored as a kid, scary stories to tell in the dark,
which a lot of modern horror fans loved as kids. They're making them into film apparently,
but I mean, just talk about horrifically graphic, uh, etchings to go with these stories, uh,
and they were great stories. I, I still will listen to the audiobooks.
Uh, they're just a lot of fun. Did you do goose bumps? I was too late. I was too old for goose bumps.
And did you do the Christopher Pike, you familiar with him? No.
He had a book called Monster that had like a one paragraph hot tub jack -off sex scene that I
jacked off to 80 million times for kids. That was when you're heading into the teen years.
Christopher Pike was sort of the older goose bumps by like three, four years.
I didn't know, Christopher, when goose bumps popped, I was already like doing, uh,
tales from the crypt and rewatching tales from the dark side. That sort of thing. Okay. Fair enough.
Uh, if you could replace the lead and act and lead and act, oh, and, uh, if you personally could
replace the lead and act in any movie, which would it be? Ask Elizabeth Myers. Uh, Indiana Jones.
Andy. That'd be a very different picture. Well, I'm saying it's a fantasy, right? I mean,
right. But I don't think I could do it. I'm just saying if I could be able to wish granted,
Orhan Solo, one of those two. Right. I would say, I wish we could have prepared answers.
I, if I could have placed lead in any movie, maybe somewhere I could be like a rock star.
No, you know what, I'd want to be Rick Rannis' part in a little shop of horrors. I can sing those songs.
Well, uh, really? Yeah. That'd be fun. He's a weasel of a fucking that movie.
He's a nerd. Hills people. He's feeding him to the plant. I mean, I don't know.
Maybe I'm just none of its his fault. Uh, maybe what are, I don't know. I think, I think that'd be a
good one. That's the one that popped into my head. All right. I'm sticking with it. That's fine.
Well, we have 48 more questions to get to. So no, we're getting close. Chris Goodnight asked what was
the first game Joe remembers beating? Oh, video game. Um, Christ, it's got to be super Mario
brothers. That's got to be because that was one of the first, if I can, if I remember correct,
well, in my home, that was one of the first beatable games. You know, uh, games up until that point,
for the most part, not everything, but you know, there were, there were exceptions like adventure
or venture and stuff like that. But, you know, for the most part, games were ports of arcade games,
and they were just play for points. And eventually, maybe you can hit a kill screen if you're a
fucking psycho, but Mario brothers was the first game where it was like, I remember there being a
goal of saving the princess and being obsessed enough with the game to do it. So, uh, that is my
answer. Yeah, I think the first and only game I ever beat was Wii Mario, which me and my old roommate,
Jared had just the best time playing. And when we beat it about a week in of basically playing 24
hours a day, we stood up, hugged each other, walked down the hall and each went to our separate beds
to sleep. It was a magical moment. Beautiful. That wasn't that long ago. I'd probably 10 years here.
No, well, my story's from last week. Oh, uh, Luke Physioc asks, what is the most awkward exchange
both of you have had with a celebrity in the business? Pat, you can't pick Acroid after Conan or
Juliet Lewis at your housewarming party. Well, Juliet Lewis is the best possible one. I'm sorry.
And mine's still Chris Isaac. Yeah, I mean, this is similar to an earlier question. Um,
well, or, uh, Christopher Walken talking to us for an hour about how drummers get all the girls,
which I've also told him this by the way. Here it's the drummer gets the girls. Erica Branding asked,
what was your favorite stuffed animal growing up that you were inseparable from?
Mine was my elf whose mouth I fucked and eventually caught fire on my heated reading lamp.
That doesn't get less disturbing that story. Mine was my Chewbacca, which my mom still has an
a box in the attic ever home. And by the way, I didn't fuck my Chewbacca. I respected him.
But it's respected out. You can respect someone and fuck them. That's your problem.
Now, now fucking the doll and then letting it burn to death is, you know, never came and
else mouth. Uh, but the, uh, what's it called? Yeah, my Chewbacca, which my mom still has a box
in her attic and in my parents' house. And I go, you got to throw this thing away. Even as a
collector of shit like this, like Star Wars shit and toy throw, this thing is disgusting. It
you could give it to your son one day. I'm like, what child would want to touch this thing?
It looks disgusting. Yeah. But as a kid, I loved it.
Moms cannot give shit away. Yeah, can't give shit away. I don't think there's anything for my
childhood that still exists, but maybe that's fine. I don't need it. What are you going to do with it?
You know, I'm not a, whatever you call it, not a sentimental man. I want everything thrown away
to Anthony Manito asks, for a man without shoulders, how does Joe sound like he's constantly shrugging.
Ah, the old shoulders bit. This is back from the ONA days. It seems mean to me.
It's like, like, it was, it was a, it was a trademark on my ONA days. Uh, he's just,
that's just, he's just being funny. All right. I mean, it's just tough to, to, to get it.
Not, I'm not laughing at the joke because I'm like, because I don't like it. I'm just,
it's tough to get a good no shoulders crack in these days. I've kind of heard them all.
But fair enough. Yeah. Shane Nazarian asks, I know you guys are into Fuman, too, very much so.
Are you into any other stoner rock bands or sludge slash doom bands?
Absolutely. I mean, I, I've been waiting till this weekend because I plan to get baked and listen to
the new sleep album. I cannot wait to hear the new sleep album. I love sleep. Both the thing
and the band. Man, I'd, I'd like to check that out. I don't know. They had a new album out. Yeah.
Foo is, Foo is, is slowly becoming my favorite band of all, excuse me of all time. But uh,
I like the shrine quite a bit. Um, they're good. They're really good. Um, Sabbath, of course.
There's some choice deep purple records mainly machine head and in rock from the 70s that are
really fantastic stoner rock records. You heard a trouble. Trouble. Trouble is a great band. I
happen to hear it amoeba the other day and shazam them. They sounded like exactly like Sabbath and
they were terrific. Oh uncle acid. I like quite a bit. It's very stoner rocky. Um, smile who
became a pop band, but their first record, McKee, uh, is a super great stoner rock album. If you
find a copy of it, I suggest listening to it. It's very good. How's the pop stuff? Great.
I've never heard of them. Um, and my, you know, mine of course is those first, uh, Queens of Stone
Edge albums. Oh yeah, those two. Uh, yeah, I like, I like a great deal of stoner rock, especially when
I am stoned in terms of doom band. I never liked the cookie monster voice and that kind of shit.
Now, and you know, yeah, I agree. Uh, Ken Hanley. Love you Ken, asks,
fuck Mary Kill, Frazier, Balkey, Ernest. Uh, I'm Mary and Frage all day long baby.
I mean, they'll keep the conversation flowing. Uh, you fuck Balkey. It's an exotic night. Yeah,
you kill Ernest. I mean, the other guy's going to drive you up a fucking wall after two hours.
Weirdly, I think that Frazier would be the man to fuck and Mary. I mean, uh, Frazier's going
to be the best lay and the best conversationalist to keep it going. But if I have to choose, you do
it. You do need to kill Ernest. I mean, Ernest is many things, a sexual being is not one of them.
Balkey, yeah, you're absolutely right. Balkey, fucking Frazier, Mary. Uh,
uh, Tim, oh my god, Tim, this last name, Kalf Fleisch. Sorry, I'm sorry, Tim, but that's a crazy
last name. Where is the best place you have traveled? Uh, I've only been to London, Paris and Amsterdam.
If you're talking outside of the country and it was a dream trip, and I think Amsterdam was my
favorite part of it. It was just fantastic. Yeah, I'd probably agree. I've been, I've been to
a number of places at this point. Um, all of them were great, you know, but, uh, I think Amsterdam is
still probably my fave, which, you know, who knows, if I went back now and I wasn't like boozing it
up and everything, I don't know maybe, but I just had a partying hell of a time in Amsterdam. I really
certainly hope that that is my new answer when I am done. Uh, Matt little asks, if you've seen,
I'm dying up here on Showtime, what are your thoughts, opinions about it? I only saw the pilot,
which I guess is, is the answer to your question. And of course, it's unfair to judge a show on
its pilot, but I didn't feel like it was for me. Um, we, we've hit a, we've hit a capacity on shows
about standup comedy. Uh, I agree. I have a lot of friends on the show, so I hope it continues to
do well for them. And I hope that, uh, you know, I hope that they're enjoying the experience. Uh, but,
but I would agree. It's not really for me. I think it, it gives, it gives a little too much service
to the comedy store. I like the comedy store. I do shows there that is not a shot at the comedy store,
but I agree with Pat in the sense that we've, we've hit capacity and I'm kind of, whether it's a documentary
or a TV show or movie at this point, I'm kind of tired of this premise of the, the struggle of the
comedian and, and how we just marched to the beat of a different drummer and all this. I mean,
Jesus Christ, man, there are people starving to death around the world every day. We're sitting here
praising somebody's, uh, bravery to, to go on stage and talk about their mother. I completely agree.
Say, come on. And at the end of that pile, when it was like, you've got to talk about yourself. Don't
talk about, you know, and then get up there and then she's like, I'll do some personal material and
it connects with the audience. That's, I've seen that 50 times now in a variety of these shows. So, uh,
the line of the, I mean, the line in the first episode of the kid dies and they go, we need to get it.
We, we should book a church and then the lady goes, where in a church? Oh, yeah. I mean, it's like,
come on, man, this is like, for me, it was anybody in any walk of life taking themselves that seriously,
you make, that's what comedians are supposed to make fun of. Yeah. So anyway, for me, it was having
that, that, uh, the only black kid in the show, uh, jerk off for a priest for money. I was like,
this doesn't seem to fit into the show. That actually happens in the bottom. I make
it. I thought that was a bit much. Yeah. I thought it was a little too much. Ben Lee asks, Pat,
you have talked about enjoying a visual experience for its own sake and can let the story fall away if
the visuals are interesting enough. Examples, neon, demon, jeepers, creepers, doc strange, three movies
Joe despise. So then what explains your distaste for Blade Runner and the sequel, which when you admit
that it's visually interesting, um, I don't know what to tell you. I do think Blade Runner is
visually fantastic. Um, but for me, it is so boring that I'm not able to find any interest in it. Whereas
neon, demon, jeepers, creepers, doc strange, all three of them, uh, at least what was happening in
them kept me interested enough, not to say I didn't have story problems, but, um, you know, neon, demon,
whatever is a, is a experience as opposed to a movie. And Blade Runner was trying to be a film
noir like a plot heavy kind of thing and the plot didn't work for me. I don't know what to tell you.
I think our most controversial opinion by far is Blade Runner. People don't understand.
I don't understand. If you, if you wrote it down on paper, these are the ingredients for the movie.
I'd say this is a delicious recipe. I can't stand the fucking movie. Yeah.
Uh, Joe, any thoughts on Jeff and some aliens being yanked after an initial renewal? Your written
episode was easily the best of the bunch. Thank you for that compliment. Uh, no, no opinions. I
don't even know what got yanked to be honest. So, uh, you know, you're part of so many, uh, things in
your career that some of them are, are, are, are, are gonna be constants and others are, are jobs that
you have that, you know, you have them and then it's over. And that was sort of one of those jobs
for me. So I don't really have any thoughts. I wish those guys well though. And I hope they, uh,
land on their feet. Yes. Dan Clark asks, what should my wife and I name are upcoming child?
Con. I agree. Con. Joe, you shouldn't be asking us, Dan. You need to talk to your wife.
Uh, and congratulations and good luck. I hope it's a little hellian. Joe Price asks, ready player one,
best movie of the year or best movie ever. I haven't seen it yet, but I want to know how loud I'll
squeal when I do. Well, Joe, just listen to Monday's episode because, uh, we did not love it.
Whoo. You are going to be disappointed, my friend. And that is when I cut them off, but since there are
only a couple more that went past the thing, let's just do them and be done with it. What is a couple more?
Literally two. Oh, okay. Uh, a few. Longest episode ever with 90 minutes. That's fun. No, no,
I'm saying I'm patting us on the back. We're at 90 minutes. No commentary. That's right.
By the way, I don't feel the tired that I felt during the commentary. It's something about
I want to talk to you a lot coming at us. Yeah. Anyway, we're getting, you know, specific questions
as opposed to just talk for 90 minutes. Uh, why did Joe tell Kanye to do what he did?
Tangus is an ass. If you be a fly on the wall, if you could be a fly on the wall on any movie set,
what movie would it be? Mine would be the Twilight Zone 80s movie. Oh, you're going to see some
sites there. I would be curious on how they could let a death lead actor happen. How could be so
careless? Well, I ask you to read that Twilight Zone book that I read, which was fantastic.
That tells you exactly how it happened. But Joe, what would it be? I would be a fly on the wall
of the fly and I'd give extensive notes on the inaccuracies of how they were portraying a fly's
style. Okay. You like the fly though, right? I love it. Uh, and for me, I mean, what could be
cooler? Well, I almost, of course, I'm going to pick my two favorites. I mean, good fellows to see
that movie come together. Can you even imagine how amazing that would be? Yeah, that'd be pretty
incredible. And then my other, I got to say, plans trains. I mean, Steve Martin and John Candy hanging
out. I would honestly say in all seriousness, I would probably pick the dark crystal that is such
a marvel film like the spectacle goes beyond anything. I can even comprehend how they did all that
with puppets is I don't even understand. Yeah. And I would, that's, and the fact that they built
those sets too, like, I mean, I feel like if you were on that set, you'd literally be stepping into
that world that'd be pretty fucking cool, right? Uh, yeah. I'd also say blues brothers because
so many drugs and also you get to see James Brown, Ruth Franklin, Ray Charles.
You still get to meet John Candy. I mean, it's a dream. Yeah, it's a good one. And then
well, last question, we already answered. Caitlin McGinley asked, how did you enjoy meat?
We were set up by Pete, basically, sort of a double date situation. Situations.
Guys, this was very fun. Thank you for these excellent questions. I think it is likely we will do
this again down the line. It was a success. We don't do plugs or anything on these. So we will just
say thank you very much for being loyal Patreon supporters. We can't tell you enough. I'm
much appreciated. And we are in the work stage of putting together a live show. So we will see you next
time, folks. We love you. And we will see you in hell.