I'll see you in hell.
Welcome to We'll see you in hell.
It's a podcast you turn to when you oh god.
Why do why do I we don't need the intro you know what you're listening to you don't you don't watch
You don't tune into the latest episode of Call Me Cat on the Fox network and have her explain to you
What's actually you do because yes, she talks to the camera the whole time have you seen that show yet?
Have you seen this folks have you seen this show?
I have only seen the trailers which I think made me impotent and then the
I have a few friends including yourself that have watched it and Joe I believe you said it was the
worst show you've ever seen in your life it was it was real bad it was real bad
Leslie Jordan nice to see him in there nice to see Balik you know I like it nice to see Bialik
Is that a guy who likes Balik my main Bialik who likes her I was a big blossom fan as a kid I watched it but I
mean I take I'd rather have her back than Ted was was directed a lot of broke girls believe in her
I'm kidding I've just it's just a funny name to say I'd rather have her back than Joey Laurence 100 % you know
Ted was actually played the pink Panther and one of the later pink Panther movies yeah it was the one
where yeah I yeah after Peter Sellers died they did one where like he let where Roger Moore at one
point comes in and he's doing a clue so impression and it's supposed to be that clue so had plastic
surgery and now as it looks completely different yeah and then was is like the son of the pink Panther
or something yeah I didn't didn't see that one you really you didn't rush out to see some of the
pink Panther the the even installment in the in the Blake Edwards saga even the original pink Panther sucks
you know I I bought I like a couple of okay there's some funny moments but I bought this giant pink
box set of the pink Panther years years and years and years ago on Amazon and I was like why do I
have this and I sent it it had all the pink Panther movies and then like 20 discs of the pink Panther
cartoon which was never funny never good no no what are you doing and this guy bought this like 10
pound thing for me and I shipped it cost a ton of money I was like boy that was a mistake I've learned
my lesson and then I get the email hey man DVD number 19 of the animated adventures of the pink Panther
does not have the right information on it so I'm gonna need to send it back at your cost so anyway
that's a man that realized he made the same mistake you did as soon as it arrived oh absolutely where's
my out I just bought a pink box that put the singer for my pole dancing classes I admit it's
said to help she's got some good pole dance music I before John knew I was on logged on to the zoom
he was kind of working his cheeks into camera to that I'm coming out so you better get the
ponies not it right yeah yeah you know he was with each beat he was lifting a butt cheek so it
would go right right right left right right you know yeah and I like to add a visual interpretation
of the lyrics to the dance so I'll take my bird out when she first says I'm coming out that's
what I first tease the bird reveal uh -huh and you know that sort of thing I just watched I just
rewatched the sign felt with uh not that there's anything wrong with it that where they think they're
gay yeah yeah and just a great line when he goes I've been out and I wasn't even in yeah that episode
as as tolerant as as a 90 sitcom ever got regarding homosexuality and it's it's a little dodgy but still
I mean man they used to be so rough on that stuff back in the day the sitcoms geez and I was I tried
to rewatch or watch friends and I didn't get far but um years ago when I tried to do it but I
mean every episode they're like you thought I was gay Joey's like she said I was gay it's like guys
this is within my lifetime here did you know there was a married with children spinoff called enemies
that was supposed to be a send -up of friends like making fun of friends who was on it
uh how was it to spin off it was it one of those where they just come visit albundi's house and leave
and then they have their own show yeah yeah it was one of those I think I think Joey Lauren Adams I think
okay but I don't remember it when as far as a pilot stage yeah and that was it um but yeah it was
you know and it was supposed to like just like the way like they're working title of married with
children was not the Cosby's and that show was supposed to be a send -up of the perfect family in the
American sitcom and this was going to be I guess their next attempt at sending up like what was the next
craze which was like all the friends living together and the thing and having a great relationship
whatever um and it didn't go anywhere but uh but yeah I thought that was interesting that it was that
on the nose that it was just called yeah yeah which is like you know that's like a fucking like Leslie
Nielsen level spoof kind of you know what I mean yeah well uh Larry David hated it so in his
movie sour grapes there's like some shots at friends and then they did that whole sign fell about
being a time slot hit how ban you would go up after Jerry and the only reason anybody watched
that was more aimed at like the single guy and all that kind of those kind of shows that
follow shows they were putting on oh really I didn't know that who was on the single guy that
ban you was like I'm killing I'm killing and they're like you're a you're a time slot hit that
was a sign felt thing yeah yeah that's a great one too when he goes up with the suspect he goes I
got to go on stage and he takes off the jacket he's got the rainbow yeah what I had cancer
what was the what was the uh single guy was that John Silverman Jonathan Silverman not a good show
cares Caroline in the city you know Caroline City did well I don't remember it at all you know
but I know it was like sort of a hit at least they always worked at like a magazine or something and
just be these shows of people no shitty shows I mean friends look like a masterpiece compared to
Caroline in the city and and it's ilk friends has I've seen clips over the years I was like that's
pretty funny I guess you know but it was never a show I would watch but like it was you know it was
for that college it was for the college crowd it was it was another sort of sex in the city kind
of which I love sex in the city which by the way news I back coming back without Katrina I mean what
do come on what are we doing here man it's not a show I promise you by season two if it's a hit
she'll be back no they'll have a new they'll have a new sassy brassy show like her daughter like she
like Kim died of cancer or something and they'll have the daughter in there because she did have cancer
on the show I was one of the plots Smith Jared was taking care of her I saw on Twitter somebody saying
like have Cardi B became portrayal you'll get some diversity and you'll get her and I was like that's
it's not a good idea that's not a good idea the show not Cardi B not Cardi B not the most annoying human
on earth oh I disagree with you I don't know that much about the woman but I like her I'd like to
make love to her well I mean what's that saying you fucked an elf mouth until you were 17 or whatever
never came at them I would like to say I wish Leslie Jordan the best he is one of the one of the
nicest sweetest and funniest people I I hate that he is trapped now in the show I blamed the
despicable Fox network and I just didn't get a chance to say that I think the show looks on watch
a bowl and I hope Leslie lands on his feet I think he's doing fine he's just 65 year old man and he's
still working you know it's like well he lives above I don't know why I would tell you where he lives I
just I want him to do well I look I'm sure he's having a great time he gets to run in and be like oh boy
I didn't order the blue ones and they runs out and everybody laughs and that's the end of it like he's
walking on sunshine this guy yeah you know anyway all right we're doing the Friday to 13th franchise
today all of them including I'm gonna touch on the a couple of these movies Pat will be a little
more informed than I am because he's seen some of these a little more recently than I have I rewatched
as many of these as I could in the recent weeks but to make up for that Pat I will take us through the
TV show Friday the 13th oh good so we can really make this a completist episode I never saw
the TV show but I watched in three days over the New Year's Eve weekend Friday the 13th one two three
four five six seven eight nine ten the remake and crystal -like memories the complete history of Friday
the 13th here you're sick man it's sick what you're doing there who's no prop what are we doing waiting
for death I've never seen these movies I wanted to get them done get her done I do uh you know if
you're a fan of the franchise you have to get the the box set it's a little pricey but it's you know
it's everything you could possibly want regarding Friday the 13th except oddly crystal -like memories
which is on shutter and you can find relatively easily but you think they'd spring to get that
documentary on the set but you can also get a trim I just want to point this out to the fans that
might not want to drop a hundred to a hundred sixty dollars on a box set there is a blue race set that
goes for about 20 bucks and they're great transfers and it's the first eight films the only thing you're
not getting is Jason X Jason goes to hell and the remake which for a lot of people you look is it nice
to have a complete set sure do you need those movies maybe the remake yeah I mean you're going
to live you're not you're not going to be like I wish I had a blue ray of Jason goes to hell you'd
have to be a pretty big fan of the franchise or somebody like me who was like I've never seen these
movies and they they come out I've actually sold and made money off one of these sets already when
it went out of print so I kind of paid for it that way the old black more compact set that came out
but this does have each disk is packed with shit there's new 4k transfers of everything I mean a 4k
transfer of the original Friday the 13 still looks like shit I hate to break it to you but
it's a great set if you can get it for that hundred dollar price tag you can't beat it what do
you pay it at that point it's five dollars a movie or something like that you know well don't
don't be shitting on my gift to Emily because you gave her something much worse than mine so take
it easy I gave her a limited edition arrow pressing of reanimator that will be worth hundreds of
dollars as soon as it goes out of print again so we'll see we'll start at the beginning
one start what year did the original come out 78 1980 oh 80 wow okay so basically my experience with
the franchise is I've seen one two or three times and I've never seen anything else except the remake
so this was all news to me and I was sort of blown away by how not good the vast majority of the
franchise is the same issue when I went back to halloween they're just not great movies by and large
the Nightmare on Elm Street series while it has some valleys to be sure is just a much more creative and
visually interesting franchise and storytelling interesting franchise yeah the way they like like
like a plot twist or or or or a new development in front of the 13th is like he's on a boat now
yeah it's got a new mask yeah that's literally as far as it goes it's no like there's nothing they don't
Jason never has a son no there's no you know the sister doesn't come in there's no real he's in
New York well no they they do relatives of Jason you're you're forgetting the really dire entries
around the 7 -8 range they do yeah but I mean it's you know like like in Nightmare on Elm Street 5 it's
like Freddie has is gonna be reborn through Alice's unborn child or you know what I mean they get a
little heady they try to figure out a new way to bring Freddie and they electrocute Jason back to
life about four times in this franchise without without shame without any shame whatsoever anyway it is
front of the 13th the original you know it is notorious really for being an early slasher it's far
when you watch it now I mean the twist is that Jason's mom is the killer but wish you know from
watching scream or or anything but the weird thing about that is the twist is that the killer is someone
you've never seen so it's like it's not that exciting really well that's a big trope not to cut
you off that was a big trope back then with with slasher movies it was like black Christmas does it like
it was it was it was a lot of and Halloween the original Halloween does it it was a lot of POV of
the killer right it was a lot of that back then to keep this mystery going you know so they would tape
like a knife to the camera lens yeah oh who could it be you know there's very little suspense in it
but that is a cool twist and you can't argue with one of the all -time classic endings of okay good
everything's okay stand the shot for an absurd amount of time and then the actual Jason pops out
of the lake now look is Jason just does he live in the lake does he have gills these are questions I've
always kind of wondered but it's an it's an effective twist although even that twist is stolen from
carry it's the same basic deal as carry it's shot in the exact same way of everything's fine the
music's almost exactly the same than the hand pops out of the grape but the so right right right
from the jump it's a it's a fairly derivative franchise and the fact that it had the legs that it
had is kind of amazing because the original is pretty boring in my opinion the kill suck Kevin
Bacon's in it which is kind of fun but I think I think part one is worth the price of a mission for
two reasons the Jason jumping out of the lake at the end is one of the all -time great jumpscares in
horror movie history and the kill of Kevin Bacon with the arrow up through the mattress through his
neck is pretty fascinating done by the great Tom Savini one of the great I texted Joe there's
nothing Jason loves more than stabbing somebody through a mattress he yeah he's in almost every film
yeah yeah and you know what he really likes is a little cabin stabbing yeah yeah so the uh but he
the those two scenes in my opinion are what make that movie worthwhile but you you did leave that one
detail the pop out of the lake is then undone by she the girl waking up in the hospital
that's supposedly like a nightmare she's having or something that's what I wrote here in my little
so you're saying that's why he can live under the lake right but it ruins the movie I think it sucks the
the hospital ending is it just kind of trashes everything that came before and I can only imagine the
audience how much more thrilling it would have been for that audience to go out on the scare then to
go out on that bullshit it was all a dream ending yeah yeah well James Rolf from Cinematica who does
the who plays the angry video game nerd on YouTube he that's his gripe with the ending of the of the
the that film is that yeah why are you undoing this amazing that's arguably the first true great jump
scare in horror movie history there were jump scares before that but I mean if you want to pinpoint
you know one that just that is the prototype for all jump scares to come it's that one in my
carry carry I don't find the carry jump scare as good I hear you it's similar but it's not
I still I don't get tense at the end of carry I still will get a little tense watching that lake
boat scene you know but that's just me I don't I hear you though carry you know but do you
you know I feel like you see the carry one coming from a mile away you don't see the Jason one coming
I don't think you would have seen carry because it wasn't a jump scare world that movie came out
four years before this original that's a good point okay all right fair enough overall though I
agree with you you know the first film a bit of a triumph an independent or low budget at least
filmmaking but overall not a great flick good enough sure passable fine and also something that
I thought was brilliant that they did in the remake which will eventually get to was they summed up
the original movie in like pre -opening credits or during the opening credits it was great I was
like oh that's perfect they do it in several of these like a previously on which was very strange
but I get it especially if they're I can't believe that they even made a slight attempt to continue
the the story throughout the franchise because it's just stupid like just have them out there but the
I mean the previously on's get more and more in depth and you're like am I gonna need to know all
the stuff and and maybe you do maybe you don't it gets kind of hard to pay attention after like
the you know four five six range but um part two significantly better than part one yeah I think
that that with this franchise you know if you look at your three main horror franchises
nightmare Halloween Friday 13th I think everybody would agree those are your three big ones
um they both start with stone cold classics Halloween and Nightmare on Elm Street just excellent
unquestionable horror classics that's why it's so strange that Friday 13th starts with kind of
shit and then has kind of high moments scattered around throughout but um who knew that this movie would
have the life that it's had part two is kind of a continuation the mother the mother's head
and her sweater play a big role that you know he there's this girl the the genny character
who sort of plays his mother and that that's something that everyone kind of figures out throughout
these movie the it's put in the early entries anyway they figure out that you can sort of
convince Jason you're his mom by talking like her I don't know how anyone knows this or what the mom
talked like but when they're like Jason be a good boy it sort of whips him into line um and it's
that's not a great rule it's like it's not a hard fast rule about like how to get Jason or
something it's just something that everyone kind of guesses hey this guy's fucked up about his mom so
I'll act like her and he'll be my friend and it works again and again even though you don't know how
these people know that so you know two is better than one it's a it's a better put together movie the kills
are a little better um but two is not great either you know I like to um you know look I'm not the
biggest slasher movie fan in the world and you kind of don't quite have your footing yet
although Jason is one of the great slasher's in horror cinematic history obviously
um you you're right you don't quite have your footing get into you're not quite fully aware of
what's going on could it be is this really him could it be maybe it's another person posing as him
right right I will say though the visual of him in part two I find very scary uh in some of the
behind the scenes footage uh one of the I believe it was one of the producers said that the reason
so in part two Jason wears a potato sack on his head with one eye cold cut out of it uh one of the
producers uh said that they found that it was getting sort of laughed at uh or considered not scary
because the elephant man came out around that time and people were associating this with that
that to me made it more scary because the idea of what does this guy look like under that hood
you know what I mean like was was it it was much more intriguing to me um that said uh that's why
they eventually switched him out of the potato sack in the next movie but excuse me um you don't quite
as I said have your footing yet with this film you're not quite sure it's definitely Jason you're pretty
sure it is but whatever uh but this movie visually gives you many many more payoffs than the first one
you see the killer throughout uh you see the rotting head of his mother uh you see a lot of great kills
and then lastly another great jump scare at the end of this one when Jason comes through the window
now fully grown with a disfigured face right uh at the at the final girl and uh that's pretty great
I like that ending and I thought it was a great variation on the ending of the first film
agreed uh you know two is is a step up in just about every way I was just kind of like
two was such a letdown that this still sort of felt like it was in the same pack I guess um
three to me is again the same way but three I think it's insane to me that in three they already felt
they needed the 3d gimmick it took it took night run out of street I guess till part six six um
well and that was like six with the gimmick of 3d for night run out of street now six is is in
abomination against man uh but but that gimmick was in three not because 3d was a craze at the time
it was because we got to go out with a bang here right uh the Friday the 13th part three is in 3d
because that was when jaws 3d came out you know the 3d was was making this huge resurgence at the time
yeah so for very different reasons did you ever see any of those old 3d's in the theater I saw
jaws 3d I believe in the theater I saw Freddy uh Freddy's dead in the theater yeah uh
I used to watch him on we had a channel called channel 57 which was the local affiliate where I lived
outside of Philly which eventually became like UPN or whatever uh and they would on Saturday show
3d movies like once every few months it was a big special event they do a kung fu thing or they do
like wizard of gore or something like that and uh where do you get the glasses 7 -11 or something
they would do like these events yeah where it was like you can pick up glasses at these locations or
whatever you know you go get the mean my buddy Scott growing up would would watch those but I didn't see
a ton of 3d stuff in the theater but I missed that it was an exciting time yeah I remember going to the
choose your own adventure movie with Christopher Lloyd that I don't know if we ever talked about
in here but I think we did where in my mind it was I think Zemekas had a hand in it it was choose your
own adventure the whole experience lasted about a half hour but it was a full price ticket I've
never even heard of it um but that was the only gimmick I can recall I don't think I ever did a 3d
theatrically until like Avatar when they made it you know obviously a whole different experience
because what 3d used to be in the 50s uh like with the three stages movies and shit dial em for murder
up to um what they were doing in the 80s there wasn't that much change it's it's all you're not
looking at kind of a three -dimensional world it's just finding excuses to throw a yo -yo at the camera
or like to open a jack and the oh somebody left this jack in the box here and they open it and it
jumps out at your whatever so there's they're not using it really for scares uh the the 3d
in this box that yeah in this third one they do a lot of like oh yeah I look at this pointy stick
and then they wave it around but you know they they well they juggle for there's a long juggling scene
that if you're not watching in 3d you gotta be like what the fuck am I watching there's a yo -yo scene
that was not a joke and then there is 50 occurrences of like an axe handle or a broom handle or some
long handle coming out of the screen so clearly that was the easiest cheapest one to do because they do it
over and over and over but um what I will say is that the redone 3d for this blu -ray set looked great
it gave you the feeling of watching a 3d movie now um where everything has a great deal of depth so
I don't I doubt that's how it looked in theaters I bet this is the best it's ever looked
still the movie sucks I mean it's it's around the same level as part one but probably a little worse
um I will say the 3d is well worth it though because you get to see what that looked like
30 years ago like at the opening there's a scene where they're hanging laundry on on the clothes line
and they're billowing out and it looks kind of kind of beautiful I must say they did a really nice job
with 3d transfer but really I was like how am I going to make it to the end of this fucking franchise
is basically what I thought at the end of part three the movies are short but I was like I'm not really
getting anything out of these I'm not enjoying them at all at that point um which is why I said earlier
it was psychotic that you watched all of these yeah some of them are really fun but I mean man
it's a lot to pack in now I'm not sitting there with with my fingers on my chin staring
intently at the screen for the entire run of the movies I was kind of doing other things but
part three again price of admission is number one starts out with the greatest music in any of the
front of the 13th films it's it's it's opening the credit sequence theme song is like this disco funk
spooky haunted house song it's pretty fucking great I've actually downloaded it oh yeah it's great
and the credits come at you in 3d while that's happening yeah sweet baby yeah so that's fun
and then also this is the movie where Jason gets the hockey mask so this is you know this is a pretty
monumental moment this is when you know okay here's what we're in for Jason is this guy he
lives in the woods he's crazy he's up for vengeance uh because now and this is an interesting plot
point and this really is established in two but now he's a guy that wants revenge for what they did
to his mother just like his mother wanted revenge for what they did to him which is a nice little
full circle you know detail yeah but that all said part four to me is where the franchise really
starts to take shape and take off and I think that part four five and six are a wonderful trilogy
of films much like in the middle of the Star Trek series you have two three and four being a perfect
trilogy uh sometimes in a franchise a trilogy exists within the middle of the franchise and not
as a first three films or whatever which which uh which franchise are you saying two three and four
isn't Star Trek the original okay sure sure as movies two three and four tell a perfect story arc
it's this here it's it's that that should have been two should have been one basically I recently
did that franchise too and I would agree with you there yeah the six is good six is great I enjoy
five people hate five I like five a lot I find it very funny I enjoy it um but my point is a trilogy
doesn't always launch the franchise sometimes it's kind of buried within right in front of the 13th
is a great example where you hit part four and now suddenly you have a story arc of four movies with
Tommy character that plays really well and uh and keeps you guessing and has a lot of fun uh with
what the what the series has led you to expect and where they take you on that journey I was uh
absolutely blown away by part four which is the final chapter I was like oh there there is good in
franchise I thought uh I mean to give you some idea everything that I reviewed from this franchise
hovers around the two star mark on letter box I get the final chapter an easy four out of five you
got crisp and glover um you know kind of before he went irredeemably strange he's certainly
strange and he's got a dance sequence in this that is one of the craziest things I've ever watched and
I can't tell if that's being played for comedy or if white people dance so poorly at the time that
they think that that's how people dance I don't know what the fuck is going on in that or if that
was like a trend yeah you know what I mean like I was like what the this is nuts well you know a guy
commented on here you know about the guy who the boyfriend when he's dying is going he's killing me he's
killing me what while he's being killed and there's something kind of funny about it but also very
disturbing about it um there's you know these scenes where I always laughed even though I realized
it's not funny but whenever Jason just throws somebody I always think that's very funny to me yeah um
so when he throws that woman off the roof of a house and she she goes sailing in slow motion
and then lands on just the side of the car like just like she almost clears the car yeah but then
bashes on the side of it and it's so like just like uncaring about human life you know that I was
I was laughing I was clapping all the kills and this are great Corey Feldman is awesome in it
Corey Feldman talk about you watch this thing you go what this what a sweet heart of a kid this kid was
with the hell god damn it man it's such a bum well the guy who played Jason was like John Wayne stunt
double in this movie is like a real old dude it's not the other people there were so many Jason's that
kind of blew my mind too but they interview that guy on the DVD and he's like he was a little prick I
hated him I really hated him man oh man did I hate him but um he's great in it Corey Feldman
talks about how he was extremely feverish during the final scene where he's actually like beating the
shit out of Jason and and he used that in his performance so whatever happened the movie is like
it's not an 80s classic on a par with a Gremlins or something like that but it it has the same feel
to me I couldn't believe how good it was yeah I couldn't believe that they were so cheap as to not
just bring the director back and keep it going they always bring in new people new writers new
directors and this will start the I'm glad you mentioned that because now starts the trend of that
in this franchise there's a lot of that going on in this franchise where you're scratching your head
why didn't you bring cane hotter back everybody loved him is Jason yeah why did you play have this
was done by Joe Zito who did this movie I watch called the prowler which was kind of a insane I think
it was part of Joe Bob's thing but it was a real great crazy um slasher movie as well and Joe
Zito they interview him and said he's clearly got some weird kind of perversions some kind of weird
sexual hang -ups there's way more extreme and extensive nudity in four which is let's especially
at the time this is what you came to these movies for killing and nudity Zito I think uh does an
amazing job to me they should have just turned the reins over to him all he did after this with some
Chuck Norris movies missing an action invasion USA you know it there are great directors who for whatever
reason get thrown by the side of the other road but I think this guy for the slasher genre he's a
he's a master he gives you the boobs he gives you the kills he gives you a great fucking story and uh
I loved it I absolutely loved it's um for me the best slasher movie I think I've seen
uh if you're not counting Halloween and the the classics of the genre I I think uh I
one of the other things I love about this film is the the portrayal of Jason is very goodness
you've got to determine fast moving Jason he doesn't run but he he's got some speed on him you know
he's just right there he hasn't yet become that mystical I walk at a snail's pace but somehow I'm
always in front of you uh element to him yet uh and I I really like that in this film uh the cast was
great uh the ending is great where uh Corey Feldman realizes that uh if he shapes his head and looks
sort of like Jason did when he died yeah be able to get Jason's attention enough to distract him and
kill him um it's a lot of fun it's a lot of fun and had it been the actual final chapter it would have
been a very fitting ending uh I agree but it is not um I so I immediately was like okay I'm done
you know I finished the franchise final chapter but I still had all these discs
yeah sure enough I I realized that it's uh a new beginning they re -kicked things off and they made
many more um new beginning starts with Corey Feldman returning in the same role briefly uh
watching Jason get dug up oh oh wait one more thing about part four the other thing I love about
it is uh it opens with a classic again this is another eighties trope in these movies the perverted like
morgue worker yeah you know that's the thing that I was it and it's played but the the perverted
mortician is played by the guy that plays the rabbi on Seinfeld the guy that's like that's right
you know it's it's like so weird seeing him in this role but and he's like he does the classic like
he's handling a dead body while eating like a turkey sandwich you know and that puts it on like
the guys like rodded and wound and then you know licks his fingers and touches a bloody stump or whatever
I love that yeah he's like you can go have five minutes whether once I'm done that kind of thing you know
for whatever reason that was a huge trope tarantino did it and kill Bill as well when they actually
try to fuck her while she's unconscious yeah um it's it's a it's a staple uh so five Corey Feldman
comes back at the beginning to watch the unearthing of Jason the digging up of Jason from his grave
and then uh uh uh an older person uh say probably the 17 18 year old kid wakes up in a cab uh and you
realize that this is now Corey Feldman's character Tommy five or six years later whatever it is um
and he's going into a mental institution uh for people that have suffered violent traumas that
just happens to for some reason be in the on the grounds of a summer camp right exactly exactly
you know I don't know why they felt that it had to be they had to be living in cabins uh you know
right they've been a mental hospital we would have went along with it at this point but what I
enjoyed about this is that the the woman they have worked with the mentally disturbed teens
wears a white button up shirt and no bra to work um and then it's caught of course in a
torrential downpour so she spent the last half of the movie just with her tits just freely bouncing around
um yeah there's uh there's a there's a weird thing between her there's a 12 year old kid it's the
kid that played Dudley on different strokes yes at the camp who repeatedly refers to her as his
girlfriend uh she never says stop it that's not appropriate and then there's a scene where
she watches the kid drink beer and I believe smoke marijuana and doesn't say you shouldn't do that
you're a child right uh it's a strange it's a strange set of parameters they have at this mental
institution yeah I mean five is kind of is kind of crazy uh the it it keeps the um high level of
nudity and also the kills there's a there's a sex scene in this in the shower that I found
genuinely erotic I was like are these two in love with each other you know I'm sure a lot of these
kids on the set hooked up and stuff but the girl goes into the show am I is this the right movie I
think it's in five I feel like there's not a lot of nudity in five I feel like the only nudity is
when they're in the woods and they got they fuck on like that blanket oh yeah well then they
they talk in the extras about how they cut the hell out of that scene he was like I just wanted to
be a beautiful sexual scene between a man and a woman they cut five minutes out of it now I was
like well if you had five minutes of them fucking that's a portal movie yeah I think I've also has a
through the mattress killing it I believe it does whatever scene has the girl and the guy like
learning how much they love each other while they fucking the shower I was like four I believe
well again four is per I was fully chubbed up by four but um it's real hard to tell these apart you
know at at a certain point it's real hard to remember which ones you've been watching but um I for
me the highlights of the franchise are four and six but five is right there with them I agree with
you that it's a good trilogy I was unaware that Jason is kind of not a part of the several of these
entries you know it's it's this kid and not Jason um sometimes I was a little confused by the mythology
I think even the riders were confused by the mythology but five is fun it's a lot of fun I'm
as interesting because it kind of goes back to the roots of the franchise with part one it turns out
to not be Jason ultimately turns out to be the father of a child who was murdered at the beginning
of the movie by one of the one of the patient's murders one of the other patients and that's a real
and kind of convoluted setup there for sure it's a little bit of a convoluted setup and it's also
the one thing that the the biggest strike against part five to me and even though I do enjoy it is
they and look I guess this is kind of credit to the writer and director for the detail of this
but when you see Jason it clearly seems to be a man dressed up as Jason and not
at all Jason he's he's very clean his skin is not rotted or weird or you know anything in any way
yeah uh and you go it looks like a guy just put a hockey mask on even the way he moves is kind of
awkward right and that kind of uh you know again that's that's actually a very consistent detail with
what the story is but it does take away from it a little bit for me that said five's a very
enjoyable piece of work in a nice entry into the franchise and sets up what I have said in the past to
me is the greatest of these films Friday the 13th part six subtitled Jason lives they're telling you
right off the back it's Jason he's coming back how is he coming back well you'll just have to tune
in and see the film opens with Tommy driving with another patient of this facility from the facility
now played played by a third actor by the way they've recast him for a third time now right
his friend is played by the guy that played horse shack on welcome back codder whose name I forget every
time Ron polillo I believe yeah and they are driving to a graveyard where Jason is buried because they
want to make Tommy wants to make sure that Jason is actually dead he digs up the grave
in a callback uh or nod to part four he becomes so enraged when he sees Jason's corpse
he repeatedly starts stabbing it with a cast iron bar from from the fence for one of the fence posts
uh this this insane strain credibility for me a little bit I will say it gets this is work starts to get
a little while but I like it uh he leaves the pole stabbed into Jason of course it's a rain storm it rains
constantly at this lake I mean my god it never stops raining yeah lightning strikes the pole Jason
wakes up uh Tommy manages to escape but Jason does manage to punch through the chest of Ron polillo
wherever his name is uh and his hand comes out the other side holding his heart uh one of the great
kills of the franchise and then it cuts to a James Bond spoof of Jason walking into the scope of a
gun actually I actually fell off my couch when that happened I fell on the ground
and he turns to the camera instead of shooting a gun he throws his machete yeah and it was fantastic
this entry is just this is a wild wild entry into this thing this is just it's so self -referential
so self -effacing it was fantastic I love it now like five introduced a little bit a little bit more
humor into the franchise like the characters that he was killing were funny the um the black couple
that's out just trying to get high in the in the winnebego you got the mark maran pot head in five you
know they're they're trying to be a little funnier but for six to come out with that James Bond
thing I mean that's like a genuinely funny creative decision that I was like wow like you don't
even want to give them any credit the movies are kind of so all over the place so six the winks in six
are just kind of a hint of what's to come with your scream and then the eventual
complete comedy horror genre that became so huge but um they do it right they give you a
few winks nobody's gonna believe this they say you know like they they're hinting at they know
it's a little stupid they're having fun yeah I like that a lot uh the director said that he put
a thing in there's a scene where a woman gets murdered and her wallet floats up in a puddle and
her american express card floats to the surface yes of the puddle and he said he put that in there
because the american express commercials were so popular at the time and he was like I knew it
would get a big reaction out of the audience and he said that of course he goes in for sure every time
I watch this with an audience the entire audience scream don't leave home without it when the card
floated up so it's got a lot of that it's got a lot of pop culture nods in it that aren't that don't
really hit you over the head they're just kind of in there and kind of funny if you if you're at the time
this film ends with Jason going to the bottom of the lake this is also the one two
where he gets his face caught in the motorboat blades right and the blood wall comes out and stuff
I think that's seven that might be seven yeah seven is the one with the the telekinesis girl the
fire starter which I like seven we'll get to seven in a second but I mean as we talk about this
what's funny is and it's worth making note of Friday the 13th is the franchise that every
movie about movies has made a joke about yeah like every movie like monster squad like every movie
about a kid that loves horror movies where they go you know well what happens in this one oh well
he's resurrected because you know a delusional priest says a prayer and this is all Friday the 13th
it's crazy like you know like that gag of like well what happens this time and they're all they're
all the same and I don't know which is which or whatever that's all Friday the 13th every joke you've
ever heard in the last 30 years about horror movies that they're in that of that ilk yeah it's about
Friday the 13th because as we talk about this I'm really foggy I can't remember what's happening and
what no and I you know I watched this 10 days ago I mean granted when you watch everything all
it wants it just becomes one long movie but um four and six are and two lesser extent five are
are the highlights I agree with you completely although I think four is better than six seven is
absolutely four is absolutely a better film than six yes six is six is the gremlins two to fours
gremlins sure sure seven to me kind of just sailed off the rails it was um they clearly were inspired by
fire starter and carry you know the movie of fire starter is absolutely terrible and carry
the classic but they bring in which is what this was supposed to be this was supposed to be carry
versus chase was it really not literally but that was like what they wanted to do they wanted to do
right every versus chase I guess it's not a bad idea it's it's just a very strange one it it's strange
to have a um a legendary horror character like this and just throw in another horror trope into the
mix to me I sort of admired how baddie it was her being telekinetic or whatever but um
this this is where I was really starting to lose steam was was part seven the new blood really the
seventh entry in in 16 hours of viewing he was starting to lose steam here yeah do you like seven
I like seven I think seven is no work part of that is just nostalgia from being a kid and seven
was supposed to be Jason never dies again by the same director of six it was supposed to carry on
and once again bafflingly they go no why why follow success we're gonna get to get a new team of
people in here and do a different thing well you know to assume because I was like why okay if somebody
comes in and does this much better a movie than the others why wouldn't they keep them and it's
gotta just be money they know you know all whenever you do something there's an option in your contract
where if they want to do another one with you you get paid a little more um but they they did
the same thing with Jason they're like he's behind a mask who cares we'll replace him then you find
out the fans really do give a shit and you know it bothers people but horror has never always been
about the bottom line making him cheap grind him out and I think this franchise even more than the
others we've discussed so seven is when can hotter comes in yes uh can hotter is a great Jason um
you know so seven you know one of the uh one of the attributes of seven is that uh you know
look at this point in a franchise that's that that's getting this insane I welcome the introduction
of a telekinesis woman right just to break it up a bit I just think they should have left the camp on
this one you know like when I saw they were back in the camp I was like Jesus Christ like how do they
not go okay we need a change of venue not not to bring in carry they need they need to change where it
takes place and this is also one of the first ones that doesn't really have a memorable character
like you remember the telekinesis girl because she has telekinesis but you don't really remember
if for any other reason whereas in six six says that Italian like Travolta type kid who actually is
John Travolta's sister's son I think okay uh the kid whose girlfriend gets her face shoved through the
metal paneling of the RV which is my second favorite uh right at the 13th kill of all time
oh with the face kind of mashes out yeah awesome awesome that kid's awesome the way he's like like he's
just he's wearing the leather jacket in the middle of summer he's chewing gum he's strutting around he's
fucking great uh part seven you sort of don't this is where these you know you could say okay in part
four they had Feldman and and Feldman's sister was great in part five you have grown Tommy who's
interesting and the kid at the top of it that gets murdered is an interesting character and
uh the the Dudley kid running around is interesting uh in part seven it kind of gets back to what
the first three were doing in the sense of like I'm just not really remembering anybody you know
I remember that Kevin Bacon is in part one but I don't remember anything about him I just
remember him because he's Kevin Bacon you know uh and and seven unfortunately suffers from that
Jason and this one gets resurrected well okay from a creative standpoint one of the more creative
resurrections I believe this one is she the telekinetic girl is uh trying to reach out
mentally to her father Jason is at the bottom of the lake in uh from part six a very
poetic ending for Jason at the end of six to go back to the bottom of the lake that's where he was
born from and that's where he dies from uh but then this one you think the guy to buy voices song
back to the lake is about Jason's mental state at that point 100 % okay uh this one the tent I believe
the telekinetic girl goes out to the dock to like reach out to her dead father and then inadvertently
brings Jason back to life yeah the lines get crossed or something
seven I mean I at some point was just kind of coming back to life for the kills I was it seven
did very little for me I got to say I've seen it many times I'm blanking on almost all of it right now
yeah I mean the the telekinesis is just not I think what it is is like they don't know what to do
because Jason can't talk Jason can't do all so it's it is an odd villain to have it's the same
exact thing as Michael Myers but you're you're really you don't have a great character here it's amazing
that they caught on especially because all the iconic Jason stuff doesn't come in till like you
said the third part where he gets the mask and everything but um yeah you you feel like they have
no idea what they're doing with the character during this stretch right um they were not getting fans
of the franchise they were getting just like hack directors to come in and uh when Jason
Jason takes Manhattan to me is as bad as it gets that was the worst offering it looked like an
episode of silk stockings if you remember I can't believe you put Manhattan below hell easily but we'll
get we'll get to it so so Jason goes back to the bottom of the lake at the end of seven yeah
eight here's what I like about eight eight starts with the kid explaining to his girlfriend on the boat
crystal lake and the the murders that have happened here and everything they're kind of looking
right into camera at that point and saying like here it is guys he's leaving the camp he's going to
Manhattan we're starting it out with a kid telling the story that you all know this is the big finale
yeah it feels like the finale it really does as these this couple is sailing across crystal lake
the anchor hits a power line that just conveniently is laying next to Jason's dead body
he is electrocuted once again back to life he comes to the surface he kills these two
and then makes his way onto a boat that is for some reason I guess leaving from crystal lake for a
school trip to Manhattan because you know how every high school has a boat trip to Manhattan
just wouldn't happen just wouldn't happen and where is the is camps crystal lake new jersey
I've never known they don't seem to know okay I've never known I've never looked it up I've never
never had any idea but what is it about look it's not good it's not good at all but what is it
about it that you hate so much for me it there's a genre of television from when I was like
13 14 that would that would it was syndicated shows that would air at like 2 a .m. and I've
always been a very late in night owl what everyone would call it I'm talking silk stockings if you
remember I'm talking red shoe diaries yeah except on it I'm talking things that didn't even have
nudity to offer like the CBS affiliate would show silk stockings or they'd show this whole
kogan on the beach show called like a loha from paradise or something like that
aqua polco heat was one of them they're just bad like cop shows like these sort of detectives but
like Baywatch like we're also exactly Baywatch what was about you as good as you're going to get
for the Baywatch nights of course but like I would hate them I think I hated them in the same way
I hated when mash would come on when I was a little kid because it meant it was time to go to bed it
was like that song kicked in and I was like I always hated mesh yeah always hated mesh to this day I
hate it this looked to me like 80s CBS crime drama like Jake and the fat man you know all these just
shit shows the camera Mrs. King yes yeah I mean Lacey it looks like higher yeah yeah looks like it was
filmed on a cheaper stock with a worse director and a worse cast than normal it looks like
they I you know this was in the franchise was clearly in trouble and I think they were just like
let's not blow any money on this anyone who's gonna come see this will come whether it's good or bad
and that's where I feel like we we lost some quality I don't I don't even know what happened in this
I I hated it I didn't care who lived or died the character sucked the kill sucked I got I got no
enjoyment out of the character sucked the closest you get to an interesting character in this movie
is are the the the asshole teacher mm -hmm who is an unexplicable prick for no reason mm -hmm in the high
school girl that tries to seduce him and does coke like those are the two people that you're like
are kind of sort of interesting in this right and not really at that point but it's a strange
film my biggest gripe with this is it's got its moments it has its moments that's some good kill
it's got a very visceral Jason it again played by Kane Hodder I like that they get him out of the
camp I think that's cool I think the idea of Jason loose on a boat is pretty cool and there's some
interesting moments my biggest gripe with this is the idea that this main character for some reason
is having visions of Jason is his paper thin to me and they don't do enough to validate it or sell it
and then also to when Jason finally does get into Manhattan I feel like they could have done a lot of
really interesting stuff with that it's inconsistent with his character in many ways you know there's
the funny scene and the famous scene from this where the the street gang which you got to love it
every one of these movies from the late 80s as they approached the early 90s like every street gang
was like a bunch of punk rockers gone wrong or whatever it was like kids with like green mohawks and
switches but when that's when that street gang you know tries to like you know roll on Jason because
he breaks their radio whatever and he lifts his mask up and they all they all get scared and they
run away like that's a funny scene and all but it's like that's not what Jason would do right you'd
kill them he murders anybody in his path so I just was disappointed that they didn't do more with
the idea of like well what like we've seen what Jason does when it's him against one other person in
an isolated area what happens when you drop him into time square he should be overwhelmed he doesn't
know what to do he doesn't know who to kill first and that becomes a weakness to him there there was
just so much they could have explored with this and played with and they just didn't play with any of it
they just for some reason had him be like well I have to go find this lady that I want to kill I'm
like why do you get you wouldn't give a shit who cares yeah you would assume budgetary concerns at this
point I mean it is kind of exciting when Jason's in in time square you know but it's all the promise of the
movie is beyond not acted upon I mean they don't they don't do anything with the New York setting they
don't really do anything fun they don't I got nothing out of it the most hated or certainly among the
most hated is Jason goes to hell the final Friday you you can imagine my shock when I saw the great
Leslie Jordan and the credits for this but he is playing one half of a couple that's very similar to
the kind of white trash couple in five who it's this kind of bigger lady and a diner in him who
have a relatively small role in this but it was it was crazy to see him for sure Jason goes to hell
what I will urge you to do beg you to do is at least watch the special features on this one
watch the interviews with Adam Marcus the director of Jason goes to hell and you know a couple
low budget things since but he directed this movie and he was 23 years old to watch him be interviewed
he thinks that Jason goes to hell is one of the best and most misunderstood movies ever he's he freely
shits on the rest of the franchise his arrogance knows no bounds I mean he talks there's a scene in this
movie where one character shaves another and like because you don't have Jason in the movie really
he's in it here and there but for the most part this is Jason as a worm who gets passed from person
to person it's a crazy idea but it is also the movie the hidden which I watched very recently and this
movie took a lot of shit for ripping off the hidden the director and both screenwriters claim they never
saw the hidden but a 23 year old guy who's obsessed with horror movies doesn't see that seems odd to me
so it I never saw the hidden oh okay all right no I'm not saying that to defend them but is the hidden
in the movie the hidden is very cool it's comic locklin and it's the same premise it's a it's an alien
basically who comes to earth and goes from body to body it's a lot like Jason goes to hell and it only
came out five or six years before Jason goes to hell so you know the the movie itself is nuts
there's no other way to put it to watch this guy talk at length about his movie and he so he
talks about this scene where the guy is strapped naked to a chair and he shaves his mustache and like
then puts the worm into his mouth and it's a very home -weirotic and strange scene so they ask him what
was the point of that scene and he goes you know what the point is because I knew that some day
people would be going what the fuck was that and asking me that very question like I wanted to
with the real fear for people at this time it wasn't a guy in a hockey mask it was a fear that maybe
their buddy would be gay you know he he's acting it's one of one of these directors in hindsight who
can't just admit yeah I made a movie that everybody hates and it didn't work and it lost money
he's one of those directors who has to just hang on to it and claim that every decision he made was
the perfect one and that someday people will get the genius of it and it's and so on and so forth
to watch and I sent some clips to Joe I mean this guy this guy was on the rails he's actually
rails he made a couple good points in those interviews and that interview about like you know
I wanted to explain why Jason was able to come back from the dead and why he was indestructible
and all the and I was like okay that all makes sense but the true tragedy of this film to me
is here's where you know look Friday the 13th versus Nightmare in Elm Street it's like the classic
Star Trek versus Star Wars debate like you have got fans who are die hard of both franchises
and people will argue till the end of time which is better and why the one is better than the other
and all that stuff yeah I think it's a real shame about this movie is here's the franchise that's
started first and they're just at this point pulling from Freddy's dead they're just pulling
from Nightmare in Elm Street and why would you pull from a hated movie like Freddy's dead you know
so the only good part of this movie as our friend Pinkstone has pointed out many times to me
is that Freddy's glove comes up at the end of the movie and pulls Jason's mask down to hell
that's the only cool part of this entire movie in my opinion and I just think it's a shame because
this is a movie that really encapsulates why Friday the 13th has left off of so many greatest
horror films of all time lists you know I have a book of 100 greatest horror movies
not one Friday the 13th is mentioned in it and that seems odd because you say well you know who
were the big four it's Jason right ready pinhead chucky yeah or leather face you know whatever you know
four or five you see lists that Friday the 13th has not included on and I think this movie really
exemplifies why because they don't do their own thing they keep at the times when they could
elevate to greatness and do something really original and really cool they end up just being
derivative of something else that's already existed even if that is of themselves and it's a shame
it's a shame yeah I mean for me uh and I really do think that a lot of people remember this and
hate it the most because I think your most intense positive and negative opinions about movies are all
when your age 10 to 30 you know so I think everybody went and saw this one in the theater and we're
excited and we're like god this fucking sucks where's Jason etc when you watch them all in a big line
like this this one stands out a for being completely batch it be for just being something different you
know for me I liked that I liked that it felt like anything could happen in any given moment I liked
that it wasn't just Jason walking around a camp and I thought it kind of had a fun trashy pulse to
it like they're you know it's not good but like any movie that starts with Jason being trapped by an
FBI sting where the where a woman gets naked in a in a bathroom because she knows that it will
lure Jason at the camp and then there's guys waiting to capture him I was like
that's nuts but I love that they went for that I so even though watching this director get interviewed
and I watched an hour of this guy ramble on about what a genius he is and not liking him I came
away from this one feeling like I liked that he did something different with it it didn't quite work
but to me I wasn't like I need to see Jason walk around again with the mask and kill people I had
had enough at that point so I liked the difference which by the way the opening of this is one of the
only redeeming qualities of the film because you know by the time you get to this entry you're like where
are the authority they would have yeah I mean my god you have you have a protest that gets out of hand
they're they're almost declaring martial law in this country it's like you you would have the authorities
come in at some point be like yeah there are dozens of people turning up dead at this camp so
as zany as it was to see the FBI do a sting operation to capture Jason I was like at least it kind of
makes sense yeah but you know it just it just upset me greatly that you know not only did they
kind of follow suit with Freddy's dead where they're like we're gonna retitle this it's gonna be
called Jason goes to hell the final Friday just like Freddy's dead the final nightmare right they
also said we're gonna turn it into an entity that possesses a guy and allows him to these these powers
and these abilities and I hated that about Freddy's dead and I hated it about Jason goes to hell
right which is why Jason X which is not a great film to me was at least a return to some form
and did bring it into this new weird bizarre realm for the franchise and kind of made it fun it was kind
of fun to see Jason okay he's eternally can live forever you can do this can do that let's send him
into the the future two two or three hundred years whatever the fuck it was and send him up into space
and see what the fuck happens you know I was like all right I'm listening I like the swing of it as well
I felt like the vibe of goes to hell was very much like the vibe of horror at that time which was
um I'm thinking of movies like the faculty and stuff like that these movies that weren't great but
are just kind of like nuts and every time I go see a horror movie I was like man how did this even
happen that this movie came together so I liked that Jason X is a much more like kind of controlled
movie it actually makes sense um the space and sci fi elements of it kind of work it's sort of well
written um they talk about how one screen came out they made them add tons and tons of riffs and jokes
and wacky you know like you know there is one funny bit where he Jason stabs the guy and he goes you're
gonna have to do a lot more than that to kill me motherfucker and then he stabs him again and he goes
that should do it you know that's funny um probably not what you'd say while you're dying but it's
funny um I like that they do the holodeck gag of like the naked girls being like hey Jason we're over
here and he can't resist but go try to murder that was interesting because that that virtual reality
element comes in at the very end of the movie and they admitted it was just to get more nudity in
the film and I'm glad they did but um you're kind of like wow well don't introduce this whole virtual
reality thing if that's not gonna be the plot of your movie because it's more interesting than what you've
got here um I liked it to some extent it's nuts that David Kronenberg is in this I learned that the
guy who directed it was a big protege of Kronenberg's and he worked on the fly in a bunch of movies and he
died very young of cancer uh RIP but the movie is not amazing it's not well directed uh you watch
that guy's interviews and he's like yeah I made some huge mistakes uh you know but um but this this
entry does contain the greatest kill ever absolutely in front of the 13th and arguably in horror movie
history and it's when he puts a woman's face into dry ice yeah and then slams it on a countertop
and it breaks into blood ice balls all over the place it's it's one of the greatest effects I've
ever seen ever you know it was a dream kill they they actually on the documentaries go through like
trying to trace who exactly came up with the kill because everyone acknowledges it's the best one
and for the effect to work that well on it is really cool too because it looks great um on the whole
I mean the movie is a step up from softcore porn you know and I don't mean in terms of content I mean
in terms of like the actors and the you know everything it doesn't look great you're waiting like yeah
yeah you're waiting for Sharon tweed and uh for Shannon tweed and Billy's aim to step in at some point
like exactly yeah um so yeah not not not a great sort of ending to this franchise but was it ever
great you know I'd say I Joe and I both agree four five six is kind of the sweet spot um the remake I
thought I had not seen and then realized I did see it uh theatrically and I would rank the remake
kind of around the evil dead remake in that it is well it's kind of an easier job it's not
remaking a true classic it's remaking Friday the 13th but they do a really good job with it and it
doesn't wallow in it like I thought the Texas chance on mask remake did and the nightmare on Elm Street
remake did just wallow and like the misery of it and forget that these movies can also be fun
Friday the 13th the remake is pretty fun the it has the best sex scene in the franchise which this
was clearly one where they were auditioning for like the best -looking people they could find you
know like it's there's some amazing nudity here uh the kills are fun you know when he stabs
that girl through the head and then picks her up and she bashes her head and then it gives you the
group shot it's a great great kill it's it's a funny great kill sleeping bag over the fire is a
yes brutal one like yeah that makes my skin crawl you know like that's well they do the departed
thing of that like it's like a 20 minute side movie before you get to the opening credits even
yeah which is great which is great yeah you know look the remake has strangely unlike the remake of
nightmare on Elm Street which takes sort of a much more boring approach to the original film
this remake kind of looks at the original film and goes okay well how could you have made it better
and they do all that but like I said earlier they they put the whole mother storyline and as like
basically the cold open or whatever right and uh and they just kind of go for it they're just going to
have a fun time with here's a guy loose in the woods going crazy and kennel people and uh and it's a lot
of fun yeah I mean I was I was pleasantly surprised by it the those horror remakes for a while just got
to this place where it was like you know like I didn't even want to go see them because I always
left feeling just terrible and they they they missed everything that was good about horror movies
and about the ones that were even trying to remake this movie uh I don't remember which came first
I believe it this one came first but it almost shares a vibe with cabin in the woods it's not as funny
or as well scripted or as well shot as cabin in the woods but it's got kind of the same vibe you feel
like the people who were making it knew what they were doing at least and this is a franchise where
that's not always the case so I mean for me I will say I I had always thought this whole uh
Friday the 13th should bang like these movies were all suck they all sucked and they were all the same
I'm learning there's actually a big spread in in quality I'm glad I watched them all I actually had
a really fun few days watching them and because I had never seen them um but I think you do have to say
it's it's second tier it's not up there with your with your with your night right now I'm streets or
even with your Halloween's because it doesn't have that a plus classic in it there's not you know for
it for for me was a great movie but it's a great kind of popcorn movie it doesn't there's no classic
in the Friday the 13th franchise except for and it's hard to say that the final chapter of something
an amazing movie you know sure uh you know oddly as we say that uh Nightmare and I'm sure it was
the better franchise I actually thought when they finally did do Freddie versus Jason the Jason
sequences and that were much better than the Freddie sequences uh I felt like they really did Jason
right in those in that movie um which was interesting and they also managed to make much like Dracula
versus Frankenstein they made Jason the sympathetic sort of Frankenstein character you from sorry
for him vote bad for him um which is which is uh you know uh it was a surprising twist for me uh or
surprising detail for me uh in that film but um brother that up because I I wouldn't have even really
remembered to do it and I didn't watch because I had just watched it when we talked about I'm on
street earlier this year I just watched Freddie verse Jason but whereas Freddie verse Jason
feels like a fun add -on to the night of our numb street series it feels like one of the best entries
of the Friday the 13th series and that's not great I agree uh the series Friday the 13th yes made by
one of the original uh I don't remember his name but one of the original people that was on the
the franchise uh was was behind this um I mean look it's a classic thing where like they had the
they had the title they were able to make they were able to use the title to make a series the series
has nothing to do with the uh movies um it's about two cousins uh who don't know their cousins at first
which makes it very odd that the the guy is trying to fuck his cousin uh for the first few episodes
right uh and then even after they find out their cousins I feel like the flirtation is still weirdly
there but uh which is funny the the kid I don't remember the actress name but he left the series because
he wanted to be in movies and then the only movie I remember him being in was uh the final Friday
oh really yeah and then like that was gonna hit yeah but um it's a fun show uh you can pick up the
series on Amazon for I mean like God I've seen it as cheap as $13 for the entire series sometimes
it's 30 sometimes it's 20 the price bounce is all around but the premise is their uncle
was uh an antiquator who made a deal with the devil and there's an antique shop he has and every item
in the antique shop is cursed and what they have to do is basically or he sold I'm sorry he sold
cursed antiques and they have to go out and find these cursed antiques and in doing it in every
episode as they search for whatever the antique is in that episode that's cursed or whatever they're
solving some sort of you know ghostly adventure or whatever um it's okay it's got its moments
we're on a bird director one of those two then I believe so pilot episode is fun it's about a haunted
doll that's always fun yeah um the series was supposed to end with the last antique they had to find
being the hockey mask um it a very cool way to tie it all up that never happened yeah um I'm not
gonna tell you to go out and buy this thing I'm not gonna tell you that you need to go watch it but
if you want some fun sort of you know just sort of rainy day Sunday afternoon fodder uh we're
hotter what's that hotter sunday afternoon hotter yeah where you're not gonna have to think too much and
you know again it's like it's like it's kind of like what you're talking about earlier it's not really
in that Spencer for higher scarecrow Mrs. King uh realm but it does feel like that sort of 90s
horror television thing that was happening at the time like the sort of uh uh uh the outer limits remake
or you know some of the some of the eventual remakes of the or new incarnations of the twilight zone
or something like that it's just got that vibe to it um not bad they show some clips of it in the camp
crystal leg documentary um which is the definitive documentary and one of the great film documentaries
ever made it's six hours long that's why I was amazed by how many additional stories and and
interviews that this DVD box had but um yeah to I watched all them end that documentary and
I can listen to stories of people talking about you know it's still just nice to have somebody
come to me at the mall and tell me they love my kill the most or what you know I can listen to those all day
um it's a blow if you've never watched them I honestly recommend the marathon it was a lot of fun
pick a holiday weekend and go for it uh I'm glad I've checked all these off my list I feel like I'm more
of a horror -efficient I don't know yeah overall my hog is up for the Friday the 13th franchise I
know it probably didn't sound like it through most of this uh review but uh look it's it's it's it's
certainly a piece of pop culture history it's certainly a piece of horror history and it's certainly
worth checking out uh will you be blown away probably not will you enjoy yourself I think so
I think so too uh I'm plugging in I'm at one percent will I make it that's all right we're at the end
here we got the sign off thanks for listening folks that is you everybody Friday the 13th franchise
uh I'm not gonna plug I plugged on the last one I don't need to plug either I got nothing going
on stay healthy stay safe stay in your home if you can uh by all means do not be in one of our
nation's capital or one of our state capitals or nation's capitals in the coming weeks um because
it's just gonna be horrific and dangerous is my opinion stay home if you can uh call a friend
keep your mental health about you and that's what we got we're planning on doing the Hanzel and Gretel
and Hanzel Gretel and Hanzel remake coming up I've actually heard nothing but great things and
I'm excited to watch it yeah and uh I don't know what else we'll be doing probably one of the new
releases but uh thank you all so much for continuing to listen and support check out the patreon I'm
gonna have my usual uh solo corners coming up we'll see you next time and we'll see you in