I'll see you in hell.
Welcome to We'll see you in hell.
Hello, your favorite podcast covering, commentating and reviewing genre pictures, action, sci -fi, horror, splatter core, exploitation, drama, comedy, whatever the hell it is.
I'm Joe DeRosa, foreign films, art house classics, critical darlings. Hello, Joe, good to see you, Patty. How are you?
Good to see you. This is our first zoom podcast, but I feel no magic is lost. I feel none's lost either. You look good. Oh, thank you. I just woke up.
Did you shower or did you just throw us some water in the hair? I showered quickly, but more of a whore's bath.
Tops and tails.
Very good.
When you said, hey, I think when you asked me, hey, can you report on this date? You said like one o 'clock. I'm sure you put New York time, but I just didn't make the connection.
So then yesterday, when you were like, hey, can we do 15 minutes early at 9 .45 a .m. your time. I was like, god damn it. I've been waking up at noon.
Like a college freshman home for the holiday break.
I got to tell you, 1 p .m. my time was a bad time for me because I've been waking up at 715 every day.
Just right out of the bed, dude, and that is it. And then like I always try to take some sort of nap around like four or five.
Like I've earned a nap at this point. And I just can't just throw the horror and the terror. Forget it. It's not happening.
Yeah. Yeah. I was watching some CNN last night, which is always wise before bed. So I got horrible night of sleep.
But I never turn into those news things, but I was like, I guess I got to watch one of our cities burn to the ground, you know?
We're real. It's the world is looking like like the maybe like a Robocop reboot trailer. Yeah.
You know, like a president played by like John Void would be like, when the looting starts, the shooting starts, which is what tweeted last night.
And then they cut to people with masks, you know, throwing things into buildings and blowing them up.
Yeah, yeah. A reporter getting arrested on camera. Yeah. Exactly.
It's a, it's a, I mean, there's nothing funny about it. But you have to laugh it out. Just what a shit show this has become.
Yeah. I'm not even become.
No, the laughter is out of tension. It's only you laugh it like a funeral. You're like, I don't know what to do.
I don't know where to look right now. This is, this is really intense. Yes.
But Pat, I'll tell you, if we're going to talk hard hitting news here. Sure.
I think we need to talk about the fact that Tom Cruise is shooting a movie in space, which is a story you brought to my attention.
Oh, you didn't know about this. I had seen something I think I don't.
The news about Tom Cruise is always so nuts. When you told me, yeah, cruise news. This is a new segment called cruise news.
Is everything about Tom Cruise and about when Joe and I troll public parts for sex. Right. That.
And then also that's about when we take a cruise every summer together.
Not anymore if they destroy our beautiful cruise line industry because of this silly pandemic.
Just you know, there's still a ship with like a hundred people trapped on it that's still in the ocean.
That is a party. And there's nothing funny about that either, but there's kind of something funny about it.
The problem is it's not the idiots that go on cruises. It's the staff of the cruise that's stuck.
Yeah, it's made me that made me laugh so hard a tear appeared in my thinking about being trapped on a cruise ship and how horrible that would be for a hundred days.
I've only ever been on one cruise.
It was the impractical Joker's cruise where I was I was I'm friends with those guys, but I was brought on to perform so it was a job.
So I got paid to go on a cruise, which is a pretty much a dream job. Yeah.
And it was a lot of fun. All my friends were there. We had a great time.
But by the fourth day on the boat, you're like, all right, I'm good. I'm ready to. I can't. I don't want to go this buffet anymore.
Right. The casino is fun, but I've had enough.
Like a hundred days, my god almighty, the fucking that must be taking place on that for sure. Right. Yeah. That's for sure.
It must have just evolved into chaos on that thing.
Do you think buffets are done? Or do you think Trump will step in and make sure we get to keep them?
Something tells me about his shape physically.
Yeah, we're going to have a few buffet. I think we'll still have buffets, but I think they'll all get the law from now on. Have some sort of
patriotism tied into it. You know what I mean?
If we're being real, they always did have some kind of bad.
Like we're Americans. So while you struggle to find food, we will throw away what you would consider a week's meal.
Yeah. Like the bigger. Yeah. I think it will all be called like the bigger is better buffet. And you know, the
take more than you can eat a lot of macho kind of sounding shit. Yeah.
But but before we get into cruise news on the subject of cruises.
Yes.
Which is also fits into our news psycho because it's Stephen King related.
His new, his latest novel that he is not out yet that he's about, that he wrote took place.
This isn't true. This isn't true.
So he just put out this thing called it if it bleeds, which is for novellas.
How much does this man write? It must hate his family.
It's hitting an RL Stein level where I'm like, do you have a staff doing this for you? What's going on here?
I had a big serious thought about that the other day because this is a 75 year old man who is churning out a thousand plus pay for every six months.
And like Daniel Steele, I believe had ghost writers for a while.
You hear about these things. Yeah. His son write a few of them until his son became a good enough writer to take the mantle.
I don't know.
He's got the other son that's the writer too. Owen King.
Right.
The rest renowned as Joe Hill.
Yeah. Still respected writer.
But you do wonder. Maybe Owen King's not putting out as much of his own stuff because he's writing the books for dad or something.
You do wonder. I have sleeping beauties which the Owen King and Stephen King wrote together. I haven't read it yet.
Just because it's a huge book called Sleeping Beauty. It's hard to get the excitement out.
But we're going to be talking about King and our next podcast. So maybe we should save this. But I do wonder if he's actually doing his own ship.
Yeah, it's well, I all I was going to say. I'll finish what I was saying. And then we can get into it.
He wrote his newest novel that is not out yet is takes place on a cruise ship. And he said he had to rewrite it.
Which he said ultimately was a positive thing. Yeah.
But I mean talk about just like sort of kick in the crotch rewrite where you're just like God.
Damn it. You know, the things done you're handing it in. And then it's like, oh yeah, there's a hundred people stuck on a cruise ship for a pandemic.
But why did he have to rewrite it?
Well, I guess we'll find out. It's a pandemic on a cruise ship.
No, no, no. I think because of the pandemic, he had to rewrite it.
Maybe he's rewriting it now as these people on the panda. I know I don't know.
Hey, Stephen, why don't you set the book in 2019 and not rewrite it?
You'd think that'd be an easy fix. Yeah, you think that'd be an easy fix.
He just put out another book before before if it bleeds called the clinic or something or the institute.
Yeah, which is already being an HBO show and they're just come.
But the man has so much money, so much money.
You might be one of the richest people in America.
He's up there. You don't hear about it, but like I mean he gets cuts of these movies.
He gets cuts of the books. He gets cuts of everything.
He's J .K. Rawlings times like a thousand.
And she's filthy rich. Yeah, for sure.
So I also like every day she reveals something about the Harry Potter people.
It's like, just write a book if you want to reveal things about people.
Like, hey, did you know Dumbledore was bisexual?
No, because there's nothing that indicates that in any of the books.
That sounds interesting. I'd love to read that.
I'd like a spicy Dumbledore hitting magical gay bars.
Yeah, leather bars kind of thing, you know.
Oh, and a shots of butter beer and come.
Just like in his 20s, just like going going hard, you know, that's going to be the next reveal.
Do you know butter from beer is semen? No, no, we didn't.
That's weird.
So Cruz is shooting the movie in space.
That was a literally a 10 minute detour that we took.
But yeah, and they just announced the director who's Doug Lyman, who is a great director.
He did, you know, swingers go and then more recently.
Uh, edge of tomorrow.
Very top cruise movie.
He did American made, which was a very average time cruise.
Is that the one with the place the plane smuggler or whatever?
Yeah, yeah.
It was fun. Yeah.
Um, a movie set in space.
It's like, when all is said and done with all the risks and insurance and massive budget of this,
NASA's involved in the shoot.
Is it going to look any more realistic than say gravity?
It's my question.
Probably not.
No, it's one of those things that you do just to say we did it first.
It's like when Soderberg shot the full movie on the iPhone and you're like, uh, okay.
I guess that's a thing you could have done.
And you did it and looks a little worse than your other movies.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's, uh, it's not, uh, did they reveal what it's about?
If it's a, what are the, uh, the genre at least?
I mean, it's, it's sci -fi.
I don't know that we have a genre yet, but you got to get that script right.
You know, they can send it up somebody to do rewrites in a side spaceship.
Yeah.
You know, like a writer being sent up for $10 million to be a punch up,
that script's got to be on point.
Yeah, I can't write a thing.
The pens are all floating.
This is ridiculous.
Yeah.
Tom Cruise Space movie.
I'm bringing it up now, but all it says is that NASA's involved.
And SpaceX Elon Musk is in the mix, which is always a wildcard for sure.
Man, there's a guy that went from.
Like the most beloved and admired individual of all time to overnight people being like,
I think he might be crazy.
It's too much money, you know, it's, uh, you give anyone too much money.
They become awful.
Oh, yeah.
Actually, well, you know what?
With that.
That's, I'm not saying we have to move to it, but that said.
That's what I'm going to, I'm going to base my movie corner this week on that.
Okay.
Uh, well, we're essential.
We're in, we're in screaming and currently.
We are in the news psycho.
Yes.
We're a little rusty folks.
News.
Well, what's it been since we've recorded four months?
I was out there in New York in February, February 15th, when we recorded the live ones.
Wow.
That's a long time.
That is a very long time.
It feels a long time.
Well, the other thing I wanted to discuss, especially because we are the last one recorded,
I believe, was the dark crystal episode.
Is that now labyrinth is getting a sequel after the non -success of the dark crystal show.
They rushed a labyrinth sequel into production 35 years after the fact.
I do wonder if they're not thinking we can do a lot of puppet shooting that won't affect the pandemic.
People are speculating that cruise is going into space because you can shoot around the pandemic.
It doesn't seem like there might be cheaper solutions to these problems.
But, um, labyrinth is being done by Scott Derrickson who did the only Marvel movie I really liked,
which was Doctor Strange.
Yes.
And it will be written by Maggie Levin who it says wrote and directed the My Valentine installment
of Who Lose Into the Dark, which I did not see.
Wait, which installment did she do?
My Valentine.
That's a huge step up from doing a segment of Who Lose Into the Dark to the labyrinth's sequel.
Yeah.
Obviously.
Pretty big.
But we will not be involved.
Um, Connolly could certainly still do it as her as an adult, but we don't have any plot details yet.
And in the past that she wants to do it, like that she's apparently going to be a part of it.
I mean, her as an adult and maybe she's got a kid who gets abducted or whatever.
I'm into that.
I love labyrinth.
I prefer it to dark crystal.
I just, you know, the Jim Henson company is doing this, but it's kind of like,
who is the audience?
You know, who is the audience?
His absence is, is painfully apparent to me in almost, almost every Jim Henson company venture since he has died.
There were a couple.
Muppet things that landed.
Most of them didn't.
Yeah, including the new TV show.
Uh, we've already discussed that dark crystal series at length.
So everybody knows our thoughts on that.
They did that other movie.
That was pretty good.
Um, the one that was all CGI.
Remember that one?
Just called like, um, hold on, let me look it up.
Like mastermind or myth finder or something.
I don't even know if I saw it.
It was, um, oh, damn it.
I recently watched, uh, Muppet Treasure Island, which I always heard was the best of the Brian Henson era and it sucked.
I mean, Tim Curry's good, but it sucked.
Christmas Carol was better.
For sure, but the other anything in the Henson era, I don't like the new Muppet reboots.
The first one was okay.
The second one went off the rails.
Uh, mirror mask.
Yes, I didn't see mirror mask.
Um, you know, and it was, it was a pretty cool movie, you know, it bombed at the box office, but it was pretty cool.
And I did like, they were like, what if we did the exact opposite of what we always do, which is all practical?
What if we went complete CGI?
Right.
Um, I thought that was kind of interesting.
And it did have some of that spirit of labyrinth and the like.
Um, everything else they've done is just really adapted works.
You know, the star is a biblical Christian comedy film, Jesus Christ, about the nativity.
Uh, they're doing Pinocchio for Netflix.
Alexander, Alexander, the terrible horrible, no good, very bad day.
That, you know, that's a kid's book.
Um, and mirror mask was the story of the rise of mirror max pictures and Harvey Weinstein told with CGI creatures, correct?
Yeah, it was about the concealing of Harvey Weinstein's sexual deeds, how they were masked.
Was it planned?
Yes.
Planned words, I thought.
Yeah, I thought so.
Um, yeah, I mean, I just, I feel like, look, a little bonus movie corner here for the people before we've been doing.
I watched Arthur too recently on the rock.
I've never seen him.
The best title I've ever heard for a sequel.
All the rocks is good.
Yeah.
It's great.
It applies to the plot.
It's a perfect title for a sequel.
For the worst sequel I've ever seen.
Arguably the worst sequel I've ever seen.
Um, the Butler's a ghost, correct?
He's not a ghost.
He's, he's a drunken hallucination.
Uh, Dudley Moore is so ship faced.
He, you know, he imagined seeing the Butler.
Right.
It's the only part of the movie you're looking forward to.
You're hoping they reclaim some of the magic of the original.
None of it's there.
Uh -huh.
Gil Good is like, you could tell he cruised in and was just like, you got me for a day.
Give me the fucking money.
Uh -huh.
It was like when Alex Guinness would show up like in return of the Jedi.
And it was clear that he was just like, give me the fucking robe.
I'll do it again.
Christ almighty.
You know, like, yeah.
So, um, you've got another adventure.
Luke.
Yeah.
To cheer you on, Luke.
You scratching is that good on camera.
He looks often.
Was that good?
Or they'll leave it.
Stretching his head.
Uh, yeah.
He's your dad.
I don't know.
Um.
But so, so I watched this thing.
I don't know why I watched it.
Well, because we're in a pandemic.
I just got a hair up my ass.
I was like, I'm going to watch this.
I've never seen it.
Yeah.
And, uh, sat through the whole thing.
Just so I could probably have the treat of watching the original afterwards.
And how great that would be, which is what I did.
And it was.
Um, but, uh, uh, you, I'm halfway through this thing.
And I'm like, I don't under.
I get that this plot sucks.
It's just a rehashing of the original.
I get that this was a sequel that was never meant to be.
I get that they waited too long to do it.
But why does it suck this bad?
There should be more funny moments in this.
Something.
Yeah.
So then I look it up on Wikipedia.
And I realize, oh, because the guy that wrote and directed Arthur died right after Arthur came out.
And he was like 40, right?
Yeah.
So, so the point I'm getting at is this is how I'm starting to feel about the Jim Hanson stuff.
I'm like, so Arthur two feels like people that thought they knew understood the spirit of the original film.
But it just wasn't there.
It didn't have the flavor of the original.
Very few people can do that.
JJ Abrams is pretty fucking good at that.
Uh, you know, he's done it many times.
But, but few people can do that.
So that's what I'm, that's what makes me wary about.
I'm excited for a labyrinth sequel.
But I'm like, are they going to really be able to recapture.
Hanson.
Like what?
It's an undefiable quality that I just don't know that they'll be able to put into it.
Yeah.
And it's very tied to the 80s.
I mean, they just, they feel 80s.
So every, the, the new Muppet movies are so much less technically innovative than the Muppet movies of 1984.
And that's, that's insane to me.
Like they would have the Muppets all riding bikes through a park.
And you watch it now.
And you're like, how the fuck are all of these Muppets riding bikes?
Yeah.
How is it happening?
And then you see Muppet Treasure Island and like you can almost see the risks of the puppeteers.
It's like they went back.
I don't know if that's because they get less money to make them now or what.
But you'd think they would be making advances.
I felt that every Muppet movie since Hanson died with the exception of the Jason Siegel ones.
Yeah.
Or at least the first Jason Siegel one looked like direct to video sequels.
That looked like when they did Cinderella part two for Disney.
Right.
This is Symba's revenge or whatever Lion King too and all those.
And you're like, you made this 60 years after the original Cinderella and it looks this shitty.
How is this fucking possible?
It's weird because people like even five years younger than me grew up being like, you know, they're too young to know.
Okay, this Lion King too is a direct to DVD piece of shit.
I was, you know, 13, 14 when Lion King came out.
Loved it.
But I'm obviously not watching a direct to video sequel when I'm 18 and trying to get laid or whatever.
Right.
So like a young kid who gets Lion King too is like, there's another one and they just treat them as another Disney movie.
Because when you're a kid, you don't make these judgments.
So there's a lot of people who think of Lion King too and Aladdin too, which I think focused on Gilbert Gottfried's parrot.
And they just treat them as another Disney classic and it's like, no, these are what it was.
Did you see what were you able to sense any of that when you were a kid because I feel like I had some sense of it.
I remember seeing Ghostbusters 2 in the theater as a kid and being incredibly excited.
And then afterwards almost as if I'd been touched in the wrong way.
I just felt like something wasn't right.
I couldn't quite put my finger on it.
I just knew I didn't feel right.
Yeah.
I didn't know that it sucked though.
I just knew it wasn't right.
You know what I mean?
Yes.
I had a really good conversation with friends back when we could still do that about what was the first time you recognize that a movie could be bad.
Because like I used to just go, I'd be so excited to go to the movies.
I wouldn't care what it was.
My first few were like American Tale when I was five and then the ET re -release were like the first couple of movies I saw on the theater.
Two great movies.
But it took me till.
I don't know.
What was the first time you thought, okay, this movie is bad?
I'm sure I must have thought it before this because I think I was in like 7th, 3th grade when this came out.
7th grade.
And we've debated the movie on here.
I remember one of the most excited times I ever was for a sequel was Batman Returns.
And I remember seeing it and just being like, I don't like this.
Like I don't understand.
Right.
It just net.
That's the first, I'll give it to that one.
Because that's the first time I saw a movie in the theater where it wasn't just that I walked away saying I didn't like it.
I was sitting there as a kid with that feeling of this is going to turn over soon and then it's going to get rolling.
Yeah.
And it never happened.
And walking out with Scott, my friend Scott, who I grew up with and still one of my dear friends who you've met.
And we were both as kids just like, I didn't like that.
Right.
And I love that, Batman Returns.
Yeah, yeah.
The third song took a step off.
I think watching them now returns is my favorite of those original four.
I think had I seen returns when I was older, I might have had a different appreciation for it.
I feel like it's just too much sense memory at this point.
It's always take me back.
It's just like why I can never see the flaws.
Or very few of the flaws in the original like Star Wars movies.
I know Star Wars, the new hope is not a perfect film.
It's just it will never not resonate that way before me.
Sure.
But that's the first time I remember feeling that disappointment.
And then also the first time I ever felt like I have to see it again.
I must be wrong.
And we're seeing it again and being like, I still don't like this.
Yeah.
But what about you?
Well, you know, my dad took me once in a while, we would usually go to the dollar show.
So like I remember seeing an American tale and then a few weeks later,
because I loved going to the movies so much we saw.
If I'm not mistaken, either a my little pony animated or a care bear is animated,
but something like really kitty and dumb.
And not that American tale is Scorsese version of the immigration with mice or something.
But it is a much better movie.
Don Blue was like a master who gets his no credit anymore.
You know, he did rats of nymph and all.
He's got a new he's got dragons layer the movie coming out for Netflix,
which I'm excited.
I know it's still a lot of.
Yeah, he's still alive.
They're working right now for Netflix, dragons layer the movie,
which the dragons layer games, which dot, okay, just decide step for a second.
The game they play in stranger things too.
Right.
You said you initially thought it was fake because it was a cartoon.
Yeah.
And I go, no, it's a real game.
That's dragons layer.
That's Don Bluth animation.
Don Bluth did that.
Yeah.
So they're making a movie of that, which if you ever played those games,
it will be fucking awesome.
Like classic Don Bluth.
Anyway, sorry, good.
No, no, no.
I mean, I, I love the rats and nymph is incredible.
If you've never seen it, just a great, great movie.
And whatever this was, it was one of those real knockoffs,
real cheapo care bears or my little pony.
And I remember going, this wasn't as good as American tale,
but it took till like 12, 13 for me to get truly down about.
So I remember being very depressed that a movie called,
they used to build things up so much.
I remember being excited for six months to see Stay tuned with John Ritter and Pam Dover.
I was so excited.
And you know, that was a let down.
I begged my dad like, we can't wait for the dollar show.
We got to see this one in a bit of a letter.
A bigger let down around the same time was mom and dad saves the world.
Yep.
If you remember that, that one really threw me for a loop.
But I, I remember I loved John love it.
So I was excited to go see the movie.
And it was so bad.
I remember renting Stay tuned on the weekend.
It was released.
That was when I reserved video bill was my video store.
Yeah.
That I owned and operated as a 12 year old boy.
Video.
And I remember reserving Stay tuned.
Right.
I couldn't fucking wait.
And then I remember watching it and being like, I don't think this is any good.
Like, well, I was like, I don't know this is Wayne's world.
And I was like, they're parodying Wayne's world.
I can't.
But then now that you're an adult, you're like, you don't parody Wayne's world.
Wayne's world is a parody.
Right.
Of a certain kind of person.
You know, it's like those, uh, the date movie.
Um, you know, they did scary movie.
But then when they did date movie, it's like, you're, so you're spoofing comedies.
I don't know.
Yeah.
No, it's, it's pretty dumb.
I remember also seeing, um, and, and later I grew to appreciate it.
But I remember my parents taking me to see the great outdoors.
And funny farm.
Both of those in the theater love them both.
I love them both now too.
Yeah.
When, when I was, I was too young.
I was like 10.
It was two.
Right.
A lot of it was too dry.
When you're 10, you don't get how funny that, at least I didn't, how funny like that Dan
Acroid's speech about the escape mental patients is.
Yeah.
You know what I mean?
But great outdoors has them shooting a bear's ass off.
And raccoons was subtitled.
I mean, that's all for kids.
That's stuff I loved.
But when you're 10, that's few and far between it's slim pickings in the great outdoors.
What I hated was the endless, uh, it's almost a fourth of the movie.
The routine romance.
Ugh.
It's to this day you have to just fast forward it.
And I do remember being strangely aroused by when they're playing pool.
And the pool cue goes up into her mini skirt.
And this is a PG movie.
Yeah.
She's, it's like into her essentially.
I remember as a kid just being like, I'm not supposed to be watching this.
Right.
And I thought it was important so they had him say, uh,
Q stick in the back pocket.
Yeah, it was a bit much.
They didn't go into like the accused or something, but it was, it was a little weird.
Because it does go right into the coach.
Yeah.
It's very odd.
It's, it's also that what always bothered me about that love storyline was it feels a lot like the love story in, uh,
that kicks off lost boys.
For sure.
You know, the older brothers out in the town that he doesn't know.
And he's in this weird CD sort of pool hall.
And he meets the girl that's a little rough around the edges.
It's just, but it, but it doesn't go anywhere cool like it does in lost boys.
But I mean, funny farm.
Seeing that as a 10 year old kid, I mean, forget it.
You couldn't, you don't get why it's funny.
You know, I remember seeing the money pit.
What about the sheep balls?
What about eating the sheep balls?
That part killed me.
Yeah.
But there's not enough of that to sustain a 10 year old farm.
It's like a surprisingly sophisticated comedy for, for Chevy J.
I remember seeing renting the money pit when I was eight or nine.
I love it.
Again, I love it now as a kid though.
Being so disappointed because I thought it was literally about a pit of money.
They were going to find in their house.
I didn't know that that was.
You thought you were writing duck tails.
Yeah.
No, I mean, still I always try to get back in the mindset because I have a pretty decent memory about when I was a kid.
Unfortunately, I'd like to kill them off.
But like when you're a kid and you see like just money pit like Tom Hanks and Shelley Long interacting.
Immediately because I saw the movie when I was probably seven or eight.
You're comparing it to your own parents.
You're like, my parents aren't like as loving as this.
What's going on?
Then you're like, oh, is this what a great couple should be like seeing couples makes you sort of question everything you know.
All you know is your parents around other couples really.
Right.
And then bring out doors, you know, just like saved by the bell for a lot of people.
You're like, oh, okay.
And you think you're learning how to like date.
Right.
But you're not obviously high.
The movie high fidelity goes into a little bit of that about all these movies and songs that give you these fake ideas of love and et cetera.
But really, if your parents aren't talking to you about sex as mine never did to this day, I'm still waiting.
The only way you have to learn is from movies and it depends on what movies you're watching.
But that's what, you know, when if and when I am a parent, it's like.
You have to monitor what they watch and watch it with them not to keep their sensitive eyes, you know, safe or whatever.
But I think sometimes you got to be like, by the way, this isn't how normal people have sex by the way or something like that.
Because when you're a kid, you're just like, I guess that's what it is.
The first time you see sex in a movie or a porn or whatever, you're like, okay, that's sex, which is wrong.
I learned at a young age because our holiday films growing up were nine and a half weeks and the postman always rings twice.
Right. So the thing that the nine and a half weeks of Christmas each year was your big carol.
Yeah. And then last tango and parents eventually made its way.
Sure. That movie got a got a dark re -evaluation when all that stuff came out. Do you remember that?
Yeah, it's a rough. I've always found the film disturbing.
It's a little too much for me.
It's always that I saw that very young and never since, but yeah.
I'm showing up the first time I have sex with a tuba land, a tuba land of lakes.
And she's like, what's going on? We just met, you know, that kind of thing.
Yeah, you're going, I shouldn't call you pig.
Bad.
Wait a minute. You were talking about funny phone over the place.
Funny. The money pit.
A sophisticated comedy.
First time you knew a movie was bad or good.
You said you were like, I didn't find funny farm that funny. You like the sheep balls, but.
Yeah. Now there was something else with that that I was going to, I can't remember what it is.
Oh, well, have you ever seen the, it's like Cisco and Ebert on Carson, maybe.
But they're on with Chevy Chase and they had panned every single one of his movies.
And Ebert gave funny farms like three and a half stars. He loved it.
I used to very carefully monitor his reviews and buy his books and everything.
And three and a half out of four stars. So they're on with Chevy Chase and they're telling him how much they liked his new movie.
But he's carrying so much hatred for them.
And there used to be a lot more smug too, like in the 80s.
Yeah. But he hates them so much for like panning all his movies.
It's a very tense, fascinating clip of late night TV if you've never seen it.
I would love to see that.
It's cool to see like an actor who gets panned a lot sitting on a panel with critics.
Can you imagine a critic now being on like a Jimmy Fallon?
It's so weird. I just rewatched all of the Larry Sanders show.
Which I highly recommend to anybody who hasn't done that recently or who has never done it.
It holds up 110%.
But there's that whole episode where he's mad about the bad reviews Tom Shales is giving him.
And then in the end of the episode when he finally confronts Tom Shales in the restaurant, Tom Shales says, why don't you ever have me on the show?
You know, Johnny has me on and and Leno had me on has me on and letterman you never have me on.
And you're like, I remember thinking, oh, yeah, that was weird.
That was like, like, you would have a critic on as a guest.
Yeah. Well, and in my opinion, and granted, I was a kid obsessed with movies.
But what better guess when they'd have Cisco and Ebert on Carson?
And they'd be like, so what are the big summer movies we got to check out?
Isn't that a more entertaining segment to watch than like some ceilist actress talking about or a new pilot that's not going to go anywhere?
Well, also, too, I would think on behalf of NBC or whatever studio, that's pretty good for your products.
You know, if Paramount owns the network and they're saying get these two on to talk about our movies that are and how great they are, I think that'd be a pretty good commercial.
Hi, Greg.
So we're going to movies. Do you want to spin us down?
Let me take you down.
I shouldn't say the Beatles will owe $50 ,000.
Yes, I watched.
I don't think we've done it, done it on the show, but I mentioned on letter box, which I keep waiting for you to join.
Sorry.
I rewatched because it was on shutter with Joe Bob Briggs, who had tons of really fun information about the movie, by the way.
The extras is three, which I know is a favorite of yours.
And as I told everyone, it was the first movie you and I watched together.
Yes, I mean, do we want to not to step on you? Do we want to save this to review on the show?
Let's give it its own episode. Sure.
I mean, because yeah, I think there's a lot to be said and discussed about it.
I've got I've got much to say. So all right.
But it led me to my first pick, which is the ninth configuration.
So I'm looking into William Peter Blattie, who wrote the book, The Exorcist, which I read far too young.
In the movie, I saw far too young.
My dad thought it would teach me about Catholicism.
So I knew that he had this movie, kind of this notoriously weird movie called The Ninth Configuration, that came out in 1980.
And I only had I never seen it. I'd never really heard of it.
So I saw it appear on Amazon Prime one day, randomly.
And I was like, okay, I got to watch this.
And after Exorcist III, Joe Bob touches on it a little bit.
So I was like, I got to see this movie.
And it's not good, but I think everyone would get something out of it.
It's like so strange.
The first half is like a basically it's about a mansion, a big castle type mansion.
Castle, what's that?
That's secluded almost like where they where they send like Arkham asylum, you know,
at least the one I'm remembering in the cartoon, it was like an island almost, right?
Arkham asylum?
Yeah, Arkham asylum.
Wait, are you asking me if it's an island?
Wasn't it like a secluded island like that nobody could get to, like Alcatraz?
No, it's just the insane, the criminally insane asylum.
And then in one of the video games, they make Arkham City, which is they create a whole section of Gotham City that's chained off as Arkham.
And maybe there's a lot more than Ireland.
I think you're thinking of Shutter Island.
Maybe Shutter Island.
We're up at Treasure Island.
One of those two is what you're thinking.
That's, and that's where this movie is sort of a combination of the two.
But Shutter Island is a great comparison.
One floor of the Kuku's nest is also clearly a big influence.
But it's based on a book of William Peter Blattie, who you can tell in Exodus 3,
puts a lot of comedy into the first hour in the dialogue.
And a lot of like weird dialogue runs.
That Jobab says should be cut, but to me is what gives him flavor.
I disagree.
So, ninth configuration.
The first hour plus is like, it's people with military PTSD.
They've gone crazy due to military service.
And they're all sent to this really secluded island castle, where they're like looked over by military personnel.
Great premise for a movie.
I will say there's ten soldiers in the movie.
Robert Loja, Stacey Keach, all these guys are in the movie that you'll recognize.
All these great character actors, including a lot of the cast of Exodus 3.
Joe Spinal, who portrayed the maniac, isn't it?
But they're all white.
It was kind of funny to me.
Ten speaking parts in this movie, and they're all white.
And it just shows you how times change.
But they're all also kind of similar.
They're just crazy people.
There's an hour of just like people doing crazy things that are not really that funny.
You don't think of William Peter Blattie as a big comedy guy.
Then things get much darker and it's about the meaning of life really.
And whether there is a God and whether a man is truly good or bad
and all these big issues come into play.
And that stuff's kind of interesting.
It all builds to this like 20 -minute bar room brawl where Stacey Keach takes on a room full of biker tuffs,
like something out of Peewee's big adventure.
And then it ends.
And I will say I'm glad I watched it.
It was like notably strange and different and unusual.
But not a good movie by any means.
All right.
I watched and this actually ties into what I forgot what I was trying to remember I wanted to say.
Bright lights big city.
Never seen it.
Kiefer and Michael J.
And this is what I was going to say earlier.
I saw Bright lights big city as a young child.
Uh -huh.
Because my dad took me to the video store.
And for some reason he wouldn't let me rent any horror.
I wanted to rent a horror movie.
He wouldn't let me.
And he insisted that I rent something a little more appropriate.
Yeah.
Which was Bright lights big city.
Which he thought would be appropriate for a young child because Michael J. Fox was in it.
He didn't know what it was about.
Sure.
Uh -huh.
And then he also rented me red heat.
Which.
Belushi and Schwarzenegger.
We thought was that.
But no.
It was just another movie called red heat.
Okay.
That was about women in prison.
Caged heat.
Yeah.
We got the, we got the titles confused.
Jonathan Demi.
I believe directed Caged heat.
Uh -huh.
So the lesbian scenes to me as a child were very upsetting.
Yeah.
Because I never seen two women kiss.
Right.
Little did I know I'd eventually adore it.
But.
Uh -huh.
So, so anyway.
And maybe watching that movie had something to do with that.
You don't know.
Who knows?
You never know.
Yeah.
I, uh, but I, I'm reading the book Bright lights big city right now.
Which is a great book.
And I wanted to watch the movie again.
Because I hadn't seen it since I was young.
Um, it's a good movie.
It's definitely Michael J. Fox's finest piece of acting.
I would say.
Okay.
Um, it's the most serious thing I've ever seen.
You seem like with Mikey.
I, uh, I had a young David Cromwell.
I forgot.
It's, it's a great flick.
Uh, it's not a great flick.
It's a, it's a very good flick, uh, for the time and considering.
Uh, J.
Uh, Maker and Annie.
I think I'm saying his name right.
The author of the book.
A dad.
The screenplay himself.
Uh, you know, the screen.
The, the book is written in, um, second person.
So it's all saying you do this.
You do that.
It never talks about the main character's name.
And it puts you in his shoes.
Um, so it's, it's an interesting, uh, read.
It's very interestingly written.
Uh, and it's quite riveting.
And I think he did the best job.
You could,
it's kind of like Stephen King's adaption adaptation of, um,
pet cemetery to me.
It's like, look, you got 90 minutes.
You got to get it out.
This is as good as it's going to get probably.
Right.
So, um,
uh, I really liked it.
I really liked it.
And, uh, I think Ebert was the one that said.
Uh, Michael J. Fox has a drunken monologue in this.
It's the finest piece of acting he's ever committed to film.
And I agree with that.
The movie is worth the watch just for that scene.
Uh, he's really great in it.
And keyfers graded it.
Uh, a much less substantial role.
The keyfers a lot of fun to watch.
You got, uh, swoozy curts.
Okay.
Is in there.
Uh, you got, uh, Phoebe.
Kate's is in there.
Yeah.
Um, still married to Kevin Klahn.
Still after all these years.
Yeah.
Um, who else is in it?
Uh, oh, and, and then, uh, what's her name is in it?
Um, uh, um,
Oh, shit.
The Helen, uh, the lady from, uh,
Miss later.
Uh, no, no.
The old lady from misery.
The sheriff's wife.
Frances Sternhagen.
Yeah, she's in it too.
Okay.
Oh, and John Lithgauss in it.
No, not, I'm sorry.
Not John Lithgauss.
John, Jonathan Hausman's in it.
Okay.
Uh, from a naked gun.
The, uh, the driver of the.
Yes.
That's all he was ever in.
It's a shame.
He's good.
He's funny on that.
Extend your middle finger.
Yeah.
Jason Robards and Hausman show up in, like, almost cameo roles.
Okay.
Maybe they got caught or something.
Um, so it's, it's, it's worth a watch.
All right.
I love Robards.
Um, that's on Amazon Prime.
Right.
I think so.
Yeah.
I watched on one of those.
Uh, have you seen similar and around the same year?
I think less than zero.
Yes.
And in fact, some of the reviews of Brightlight's Big City compared them.
Mm -hmm.
And the comparison was often it's not a train wreck like less than zero.
But it's, it's not great, but it's okay.
I like less than zero, but I never read the book.
I heard the book is is a very different roller coaster.
I love the book.
Um, and I like the movie.
It's pretty entertaining.
I love the book spader.
I love the book, American Psycho, and I like the movie quite a bit.
And I know it doesn't do the book justice, but I still think it's a great movie.
Never read the book on it.
Never read it.
Seen the movie many times.
But, uh, I remember my mom reading American Psycho when I was like 10 and it shook her up.
Very, I've never seen her such.
I thought she was going to throw up.
And she, I overheard her talking to my dad about.
She had read the part where I believe he puts a rat into a woman's.
The China.
Something like, uh, yeah.
Uh, but my mom used to read about nothing but serial killers and she was just reading that at the breakfast table.
And it was like a very definitive close of the book.
A pushback from the table, like a deep breath.
So I knew that it was, I think I still haven't read it because I was so shaken up by that.
I'd avoided during these times that we're in right now.
Maybe save it for a bunch of real dark.
Um,
I rewatched, uh, which I had not seen since the theater Christopher Nolan's inception.
Still have never seen it.
Really?
Every time I sat down to watch it, I was like, I, I got three hours.
I don't, I can't right now.
And then I would.
Yeah.
It's very long.
I mean, there's, it's a movie with huge pros and cons.
And it's the way I feel about a lot of Christopher Nolan's like his ambition is so great.
His filmmaking is so great.
The way he shoots a movie edits it puts it together cinematography is all, it's always amazing.
But there's something lacking out of all, almost all of his movies.
Where I like them, I'd probably give them all a four out of five stars or close to it.
But there's something that leaves me cold.
An inception is no different.
I think the problem with inception is that the cast, while individually great,
it's DiCaprio, Joseph Gordon Levitt, Ellen Page, Ken Watanabe, Tom Hardy,
it's a stack cast, Michael Cain, all these great actors, and they, they have no chemistry.
It's like the, it seems like they don't know each other or don't like each other.
But for two and a half hours to have this cast where you're just kind of not connected with anybody,
his wife or ex -wife, and it's not even really possible to say in terms of the movie,
is played by Marianne Cochiyard, who's an actor who's very beautiful, of course,
but never did much for me.
I don't think DiCaprio is great in the movie.
I think he's usually great.
So I think that basically no one is just not an actor's director.
He's a director of, he's like Kubrick.
He's a great at directing, set pieces, big, beautiful landscapes, really intense scenes,
but it seems to me like actors kind of elude him to some degree.
So that's my issue with inception, but it brings up so many thousands of interesting issues
about the conscious, the subconscious, about what, you know, every part of the brain and memory,
and can you change your memories and et cetera, that you have to just respect it
in a world where most blockbusters are about people punching each other in tights.
Like you have to respect this guy made a $200 million movie about like inner workings of the brain,
and that it's all very interesting and cool, but the special effects still hold up.
So I mean it's only ten or so years old.
Some incredible scenes in it.
It's still, it's got at least a star cutoff for me,
because it's just like, it never really clicks into something that I'm excited to watch.
Right. Yeah. I hear you. I hear you.
I will double up on, do my second and third simultaneously,
because they're tied together.
And as I said at the earlier in the show, this is based on you saying what money can do to a man.
In theory, at least, is this about Scrooge McDuck again?
Scrooge McDuck. I watched the new HBO Docu series about Scrooge McDuck.
I'm pretty disturbing. Yeah.
I simultaneously watched the Epstein doc.
Okay.
Filthy rich on Netflix, along with the defiant ones,
which I had only seen parts of.
Is the Epstein multi parts or one parts for parts?
Okay.
For one hour episodes of essentially nothing except a guy getting underage women to inappropriately massage him
and do sexual things with him and then the horrors that follow from that.
But you watch this thing and watching it in conjunction with the defiant ones was easy because you,
because you go here on one side here's Epstein.
And on the other side, the defiant ones, if you don't know what it is,
it's the Jimmy Iovin and Dr. Dre document or docu series.
Again, four episodes, one hour each.
Yeah, I loved that.
It's great.
And it's way better than the Rick Rubin documentary way better.
But specifically, you watch these things together and you look at Jeffrey Epstein versus Jimmy Iovin.
And you're like,
Oh, here's how one guy with talent does all the right stuff.
And here's how the other guy uses all of his powers for evil.
Right.
They come from very similar backgrounds.
You know, they're kind of like these sort of street kids that are really savvy and smart.
And you know, don't come from money and get in there and there if they fight and they make it work and whatever.
And then like almost immediately after the first opportunities come,
you see where one guy learns the lesson of you take the hits,
you take the lashes, you work harder and harder and harder and become greater and greater and greater.
And the other guy goes,
Oh, you can just kind of start to lie and manipulate.
And that's how you start to move your way up.
Right.
And they both unfold from there.
Both are riveting.
Both are well worth a watch.
Both are,
honestly, both are troubling at times.
Obviously, the Epstein one is far more troubling than anything you see in the defiant ones.
But even the defiant ones, when it starts to get into the East Coast, West Coast stuff and the tension and the violence and everything that was going on at hip hop at the time.
You know, it's, it's upsetting to see, but.
But they're both.
Expertly made.
Docu series.
I will give the edge to the defiant ones and say that Alan Hughes, who directed it.
This man should be directing every documentary that ever gets made.
I've never seen a documentary made that well before.
I've seen a lot of excellent documentaries.
Don't get me wrong.
But this is Alan Hughes of the Hughes brothers.
I think so.
Yeah.
That thing is edited and cut and shot where it's like, how did he even think?
Because a lot of a documentary is left up to the chance of like, well, we don't know what they're going to say in the interviews.
And we know we've got to do what we've got to do here.
And it'll come together how it comes together.
I mean, there is some aspect of that.
This fucking thing, man, it looks like.
If you scripted this thing, it wouldn't have been done better.
Yeah.
So it's, it's really, really amazing, man.
I can't recommend it enough.
And if you have the stomach for it, the.
The Epstein doc is.
It's a heavy watch, but it's worth a watch.
Yeah.
And I think there's a new one on Russell Simmons on HBO Max, which I don't even know if I have now.
I think everyone just woke up with it one day.
But there's one about Russell Simmons and his, his alleged crimes.
Okay.
Interesting to see.
It's become like, like, to me, and I watched them all.
So I'm part of the problem.
But like, to include a sexual predator documentary as part of your launch.
Like, as like, hey, check out what great content we've got.
Seems wrong to me.
It's a little weird.
But, you know, it's like the people getting paid from something like that are not the victims.
They're people who have decided to profit off it, which is nuts to me.
But again, I watched them.
Look, even even in the.
I don't know the Simmons stuff enough to have.
You know, I know that he was definitely accused of stuff.
I don't know what his stance is.
I don't know whatever he's, but, but just I bring that up to say, even with an Epstein, where this is a guy where it's like, no, no, he's 110%.
Well, this is, you know, like.
Or at least just, you know.
You know, yeah, it's the evidence he's done jail time for is what I'm getting it.
Yeah.
Even with something like that, where they're interviewing the victims and you're hearing, you're saying this is great that they finally get to tell their story and get this off their chest and get treated.
Right.
Fairly and respectfully.
There is still that part of you that's like, is this, I don't know if this is right.
You know, like, there is something weird about it being a form of entertainment.
I couldn't agree more, but the like the Michael Jackson documentary, which was, you know, at times, like, not nauseating to watch.
There is a part of me that's like, well, this is important because there's so many people who are still going to jump up and dance when Thriller comes on at the bar.
And I think everyone goes, oh, yeah, he was creepy.
There's at least 50 % of the American population who's like, oh, yeah, he was creepy and he liked hanging out with kids.
But for me, who has always thought he was a pedophile sitting and watching, because like they basically buried when they rated as mansion a few years back and found huge stores of child pornography.
They basically buried that story.
So like to hear from these people's mouths, here's what happened to us.
To me, it's very important.
I don't know how many people watched it that needed to watch it.
But, you know, it's like, do you want to still listen to this guy at this point?
Right.
And it was the same way with the R Kelly document or not that I was listening to a lot of R Kelly, but they're the R Kelly one.
The weird thing to me with the R Kelly one was they did two seasons.
So that's like with making a murderer where I was like, you're doing multiple seasons.
Like, this seems to be going a little farther than we need to get this story out there.
And it's the same tactic as like a where they now on a reality show.
And it shouldn't be that that I have a complicated relationship with you shows.
But I do watch them because the public likes scandal and I'm no different.
My third choice, and Joe, I figured you would have something to say about this one.
But it is called scream queen scream comma queen exclamation point.
My nightmare on Elm Street. Have you seen that yet?
I did see it. And I'm glad you're bringing it up.
I forgot to add it to my list of things I've seen.
Yeah, so it is a documentary about any.
I was going to tell you as an mark pattern, this is not about basically nightmare on Elm Street, too.
And how the star of it, mark pattern.
Was unaware that it was going to have such a homoerotic subtext to it.
Mark Patton was an is gay. And he seems, and it's it's almost 40 years later, he seems very bitter and angry about this.
And basically he feels that no one made him aware that he was being used as a prop basically for a movie that was a gay movie even though he didn't think it was.
He thought he was just doing the sequel to this big horror movie.
The film that I run Elm Street, too, is strange. It's not really scary.
The homoeroticism in it is pretty obvious, but it's kind of to me.
Oh, I always treated it as it's kind of a campy, fun aspect of it.
The writer has for decades claimed that there was no gay subtext.
But then when he found out that people were reading it in that way and it had a new appreciation, then he was like, yes, I definitely intended that.
Right.
The long Nightmare on Elm Street documentary about all the movies, which is called No Sleep.
Never sleep again. Never sleep again. And it's great.
Excellent.
I thought they did a wonderful job and did not shy away from the gay subtext of Nightmare on Elm Street, too.
I thought that section was such a better documentary than this.
I thought scream queen while I really thought I was going to enjoy it.
I thought it was terrible.
And Mark Patton comes off as, I'm sorry, a complete complaining whiner at this point.
It's like you were the star of this huge horror sequel.
You read the script.
What exactly are you mad about?
And why are you still mad about it 40 years later?
And the truth is, knowing a lot of actors, the truth is he's angry about his acting career not going well.
Like I'm sorry, but that's how I took it.
He's making this huge issue out of the writer doesn't really have to announce to the world that there's a gay subtext to the movie or whatever.
It's a horror movie and it's supposed to be subtext.
You're supposed to watch a movie and think what you want about it.
So for him to act tricked in all this, the whole premise of the movie, I just wasn't buying.
I wasn't buying him at some victim.
And I just feel like his career started hot.
It didn't continue being hot.
And now he's angry about it.
But there's a billion actors with the same story.
The things.
Yeah, I like it.
I quasi enjoyed it.
I wanted to like it more because I'm such a fan of the franchise.
And I'm actually a big fan of part two.
I think part two is a lot of fun.
Yeah.
I mean, look, you want to talk about not knowing the subtext.
I didn't even notice the gay subtext until I watched the fucking never sleep again documentary.
And then I was laughing at how obvious it seemed.
And I remember calling a pinkstone up and going, man, they point out a bunch of shit in this.
I never noticed.
And he was like, oh my god.
Yeah.
So I, I guess I can't blame anybody for not catching it.
Right.
I didn't catch it.
But I also can't blame anybody for not revealing it.
It's been, it's an age old technique of writers and, and filmmakers and whoever.
Just, and, and lyricists and artists of all types to say, I don't know.
You figure it out.
Right.
I'm not going to tell you, you know,
just do that every time they bring out a movie like, right?
You figure it out.
And this day, John Carpenter is like, I don't know.
Maybe McCready is the thing at the end.
Who knows?
You know what I mean?
He's never going to say.
So like.
So I'm not mad at the screenwriter.
You're right about, you know, there were a million guys and girls from that time period,
from every time period in the film, where you're super hot for like 10 minutes.
And then it goes away.
Right.
And like it or not, Nightmare on Elm Street was a big money maker.
So we're the sequel.
So was the entire series in franchise.
But it was not, I mean, for Cry 6, go talk to Mark Hamill.
Yeah.
The guy Walker for fuck sake, the guy couldn't get arrested for years.
You know, it's, it's, it is what it is.
And you, you know, you sort of maneuver with the business or you, or you leave.
I, my criticism of, I'll say criticism and a compliment to Mark Patton.
My criticism was, I did think he was putting way too much blame on this writer.
Right.
I did see, I did think it seemed that he was suddenly far, far more angry about this
than he appeared to be in the never sleeping on documentary.
I was confused by that.
I was doubly confused when he was, when he's on tape saying, I don't blame the lover.
I'm not, I wasn't mad at the lover I had that gave me HIV.
You know, I'm furious at this writer for not telling, I was like, this doesn't make any sense to me.
Like, not at all.
Where are you deciding where blame goes in life and whatever?
You know, and his lover, by the way, it wasn't like, hey, I got it from this guy, but I loved him.
And I took a chance.
I was like, the guy hit it from him.
It was deceitful.
So I didn't know how much of this anger was misplaced or displaced or, or real or whatever.
But in the end.
And I don't think a lot of the people involved with the film understood that either, quite frankly.
But in the end, I applauded Mark Patton that, that when the, when the writer and him finally sit down.
And he goes, look, I'm sorry.
You know, like, I didn't, my intention was not to hurt you anyway, but that he accepts the apology that they hug.
And then he goes, I'm ready to move on.
I was like, because a lot of people wouldn't have done that, especially in this day and age.
It would have been like, no, you suffer more now.
That's not good.
Whatever it is.
Yeah.
So that was a nice turn at the end for me.
But I hear it's, it's also just not a very well -made documentary.
I, you can really tell.
I've watched, since there are so many documentaries out lately, I, you know, I'll watch basically anything about the movie business.
And, man, there's some really bad ones.
There's just, you know, shabbily made documentaries out there.
And this one is particularly bad.
And when, when I found out that it was building to this reality show style showdown between him and the writer of the movie.
I was like, I don't even know who I'm rooting for here.
I mean, the writers seem like kind of a scummy guy, maybe.
But it's like he wrote a horror movie in 1982.
And what are you mad about it?
It really drove me nuts.
And then when he's at the reunion with his fellow fellow cast members.
And they're all sitting outside having drinks and having a nice time.
He keeps bringing the agenda back to this and makes everyone uncomfortable.
But it's also like, they don't deserve to be made uncomfortable.
They were also actors in a movie.
That's why I say I feel like everybody wasn't necessarily on board with the director says.
It was the director of the producer says because the next day when he goes,
if I could have said one more thing to Mark last night, it would have been, what are you angry about?
You know, like, sure.
Anyway, um.
But, you know, like, another quick, quick side point is like, think of the thousands.
And I mean thousands of actresses in 80s horror movies alone, who showed up.
And we're like, oh, I didn't know I was going to have to get fully frontally naked in this movie.
And they're like, well, you want the part?
I bet that would happen thousands of times.
These are people who were genuinely exploited.
This is a guy who read the script showed up.
People took it a different way than he thought it was intended like the room or any number of movies.
What's happens?
And is now furious?
It's like, I found the whole thing complete bullshit.
And I really hated the movie.
The nightmare and I'm sure two are the documentary.
The documentary.
Okay.
I had this whole premise.
We've gotten Mike Harrington with us today.
He's helping us record Mike's a wonderful producer from guest digital.
He produces the podcast current Fisher and I do together.
Thank you.
Without a country on guest digital, he just messaged us here in the sidebar.
There are two things.
Arkham Asylum is a large island in the middle of Gotham Bay.
Boom.
I didn't know that.
Thank you.
And we're at an hour.
For the episode.
So let's get to our movie.
Let's get to the movie.
Yeah.
Do us the honors.
Sure.
The movie is the lighthouse.
I saw it in theaters and I rewashed it last night.
So it's fresh.
The it stars Robert Pattinson and Willem Defoe.
As two guys assigned to man a lighthouse for a period of like four to six weeks.
Willem Defoe is the old sort of surly salty man of the sea who's been doing this for decades.
Robert Pattinson is new to the game coming to it from logging different industry.
And they have this relationship that starts out very kind of like I'm in charge here.
And all that.
And over time, it evolves into both men due to being trapped there.
Or maybe due to some power that the lighthouse has.
Slowly going completely insane.
Perhaps you want to talk about gay subtext.
I mean, this movie is.
Drenched in gay subtext.
They may fuck.
They may.
They seem to form sort of a master slave sexual dynamic.
But anyway, that's essentially the plot of the lighthouse.
Two men go insane in a lighthouse.
It's done by Robert Eggers who did the witch which Joe and I disagreed on,
but which I after rewatching this, I definitely want to rewatch the witch.
Because I had such expectations for the lighthouse.
It looks so cool and so scary.
And when it checked off none of my expectations when I saw it,
I left feeling kind of like eh, it looked good, but who cares.
And when I rewatched it, I fucking loved it.
I really did love it.
All right.
Okay.
So yeah.
So I rewatched the witch.
Yeah.
And was painfully bored on the second watch to the point that I sold my Blu -ray.
Interesting.
I actually gave my Blu -ray away to my buddy Ari's girlfriend for her birthday.
She wanted more horror movies for her collection.
It's interesting because that's the one when I would get on the Facebook page or whatever,
where they would say like, Joe was right and you were wrong.
Usually it would be the other way, but they were like, Joe is right about the witch you were wrong.
I got to be honest, well, I think I'm wrong right now and not liking it.
I'm confused because it's well crafted.
It's well done.
But second, well, on second watch, I didn't think it was bad.
I just was bored to tears and I didn't care anymore.
Yeah.
So that was that the lighthouse said to say
I only did one watch of it during the pandemic.
I mean, you want to talk about a movie that's going to get in your head during a fucking pandemic.
Absolutely.
Two guys stranded on an island, you know, like you said,
you don't know if they're going to fuck if they're going to fight,
if they're going to murder each other.
What's real?
What's not?
And what starts to hate everything Willem Default does?
Like, I'm sure for people with roommates, it's probably hits very close to home during this time.
Willem Default is farting constantly.
You know, he's drunk constantly.
He's just like an annoying roommate until it turns darker.
And spoiler alert.
You know, basically one thing that you I don't think that you mentioned is what happens here in this film is there's a power shift that does happen because it starts with the foe being the boss.
Really poking patents and character a lot in the chest.
You go do this boy and all that kind of shit.
Eventually the dynamic of power shifts, you start to realize that as you said, you know,
perhaps Willem Default is in love with Robert Pattinson.
And then the stuff about patents and sorted past starts to come out.
And you realize that he's the lunatic, probably not not to foe.
And where's this going to go now?
I thought it was beautifully shot as I did with the witch.
I thought it was beautifully written as I did with the witch.
Much like the witch, I had to really focused to understand what they were saying at times.
Subtitles made a monumental difference.
I watched it with subtitles and I felt like I got it so much more.
And ultimately in this, despite the picture ask direction and the cinematography and the wonderful acting jobs, they both delivered as they always do.
It just wasn't enough of a payoff for me.
I'm confused as to how aggers.
Because with a guy like what's his name that did a.
We've the guy we fought about the mid summer.
What's are he asked her are you asked you.
You say, well, how did this guy get to make whatever movie he wants right off the bat?
And it's like, well, he had a movie that went insanely viral on the internet and proved his worth as a filmmaker.
With aggers, he didn't have anything that went viral.
As far as I know, he was able to make the witch based off of just like whatever short film he was shopping at the time.
Right.
It's a pretty big fucking leap, man.
And now he's proving himself absolutely he's able to do the job.
But that's a pretty big fucking leap that you're letting this guy two times now make these movies that are movies that like PT Anderson would have made like six films in.
I mean, these are such sort of bare bones character studies with such there's very little plot.
There's very little, you know, there's you're not going to get any real twists and turns out of these things.
And pay off is very, you know, sort of metaphoric at the end of these both of these movies.
I just the second time around for me, you know, at least the payoff in the witch, you got a couple good witch scenes.
You got a couple good disturbing at the payoff for this to me, I was just like, I don't really give a shit about eat.
There are no stakes really set at the top of this thing like there are in the which in the which you see that a family is banished to the wilderness because of their values.
There's something to sort of rest set your drink on at that point with this it's literally just we have a job to do and it's a weird job where we're isolated and it can make men go crazy.
It's like, okay, but I don't really fucking care if either you go crazy, but I don't really know what it what I'm fighting for for either of you.
So in the end when there's not really a big payoff, it's just kind of like all right, it looked nice, you know, this is kind of felt to me like one of those movies that should be playing in the room at MoMA.
As you walk around and you go, oh, you know, if you go in there, there's a real weird black and white movie playing, you know, that you can watch for a little while.
Yeah, I would say I completely agree with you on everything on my first viewing of it in my second, I thought, hey, the cinematography looked better on Blu -ray.
If some reason it was like so grainy in the theater that it bothered me, I don't know if Blu -ray just cleaned that up or what.
But yeah, any any still of this movie you could put on your wall, it's one of the most beautiful movies I've seen in quite some time.
Yeah, almost like a silent movie at the time. There's some really cool horror visuals near the end that I think you have to assume are the delusions of Pattinson going insane and not reality.
But the second I thought Willem Dafoe should have won the Oscar watching it again. I thought he was incredible. He's got some amazing monologues.
I thought Pattinson was fucking awesome and they're great. They play off each other. You want to talk about like a cast who has chemistry as opposed to inception earlier.
These two guys are like on fire together and apart. And this time around I was just more willing to say, okay, you're not going to get satisfied or scared in a traditional way.
You're going to have to do some work. And normally I don't get to that second viewing to do that work. I'm like, that sucked, it was boring, whatever.
This time in doing it had a whole different experience. I love sort of connecting the dots when when Pattinson's refusing to drink up front, you know, you're like, okay, I bet he was a recovering alcohol.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You know, like it makes you do a lot of the lifting. But to me it was way worth it on the second viewing. And then afterwards going to the Wikipedia page and reading about what the director has said huge paragraph about the homosexuality in the movie.
Huge paragraph about the alcoholism in the movie. It just it made it into a much more special movie than I gave it credit for first time around. I loved it.
I brought it up from like a three star to a four and a half.
It's something I didn't I was disappointed, but I didn't hate it. So it's something I would rewatch gladly to see if it gets me on the second try.
Yeah, to first try for me, felt a little more like a Sam Shepard play.
Yeah.
And something I maybe would have enjoyed a little more on the stage.
But who knows? Sometimes that gets that grows on you know, like, you know, American Buffalo is a great example of that.
American Buffalo in a stage format is pretty, you know, pretty riveting.
When they made the movie with Dennis Farina.
Yeah. No, sorry, Frank, which one's the fat one?
That's France.
France.
And Dustin Hoffman.
It's it's it reminds me of this in the sense that it's very well shot, not as well shot as this, but impeccably acted.
Yeah, beautifully written.
But at the end of the day, it's ultimately two guys and two two earth and then there's the kid to yeah in a room talking.
So, um, but after multiple watches, I grew to really appreciate American Buffalo.
So that maybe could happen with with this as well.
So I would revisit it.
I would give it a hog sideways for right now.
My hog's definitely a formerly sideways.
Your poll time is Anderson comparison.
I wouldn't have thought of, but now that you mentioned it's the perfect comparison.
There will be blood was a similar thing where I was just like, wow, that was something.
I have no idea what I thought about it.
It certainly didn't move me in any way, but that was something.
But I watched it again and again and loved it more and more.
Lighthouse is very similar, also very similar and almost inventing a new way of talking for its characters, you know, with Daniel playing viewer.
So there will be blood I think is a really good comparison.
It's not up to that achievement, but I thought lighthouse was awesome on a second viewing.
Joe, do you have plugs for everybody?
Yeah, just Joe to Rosa comedy on Instagram and Twitter, Joe to Rosa comedian on TikTok and Facebook.
And check out without a country on gas digital myself and current Fisher.
Take five four news stories as they are covered by hard left and hard right media outlets and try to find the gray area in between the two.
That's it.
Awesome.
The next one I'm going to need you to explain to me what TikTok is.
I'm not even sure what it is.
But I'm on Twitter and Instagram at the patch wall.
I was a guest on my buddy, Bridger's podcast.
I said no gifts.
I was a guest on my friend, Miel's podcast, punch up the jam or we discussed.
Hey, jealousy by the gym blossoms.
And I was recently on Lizzie Cooperman's podcast.
She does weekly podcasts while we're quarantined at home.
Check that out as well.
Thank you everyone. We'll be back with a review of the outsider, the Stephen King HBO series.
Yes, and also thank you.
Yes, all of you that have stayed with us.
Whether you stayed on the Patreon or not, just the support from all of you period is means a lot to us.
We know these are tough times.
We know these are times when the least important thing in the world is listening to a podcast.
So there are certainly bigger fish to fry.
We appreciate the fans more than ever.
We hope you're safe.
We hope you're sane.
And you know, just you guys are the best.
Complete that.
Thank you everybody.
We'll see you next time and we will see you in hell.