Huff, puff, and spin the house down at Golden Nugget Online Casino.
Right now, new players can deposit just 5 bucks and get 500 total spins on Huff and
more puff.
The slot that's blowing players away!
Download the Golden Nugget Online Casino app and use promo code Nugget1.
That's code Nugget1 to enjoy 50 spins a day for your first 10 days.
All on our players' favorite game of the summer.
Now's the time to score daily bonuses and spin for all the bacon on the game everyone's
hoffat about!
At Golden Nugget Online Casino!
Gambling Problem Call 1 -800 -Gambleer Please play responsibly, 21 and over, physically
President Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania, and West Virginia only, Void and Ontario.
New customers only, nonwithdrawable casino spins issued as 50 spins per day for 10 days valid
for featured game only and expire each day after 24 hours.
C -Terms at GoldenNuggetCasino .com slash promos ends at 11 .59 p .m. Eastern on August 31st, 2025.
Very Christmas. Happy Holidays. Happy Hanukkah. Happy Kwanzaa. Welcome to another holiday edition of We'll see you in hell this podcast is part of the Fingoria Jingle my keys like Jingle Bell didn't
Sounds good. Sounds terrible. Yeah. This is a part of the Fangoria podcast network for more
information about the network, including other programs and how to follow the show and find
past episodes. We'll see you now. Please visit Fangoria .com. Now on with the show Ho Ho Ho. It's another
Christmas movie today we do black Christmas this is Joe Derosa and I'm Patrick
Walsh I gang Joe your your heart really wasn't in that intro it wasn't it just
sounded just like you were done I thought it sounded okay it wasn't Mary I know
that but it was Mary what I don't know I got nothing Pat what do you want for me I'm
some sort of a whiskey haze right now I've been drinking ever since work
ended last week. That's what people do. That's what the holidays are all about.
It's not going to slow down at Christmas either. I had to struggle right now not to crack
a whiskey open at 12 30 in the afternoon. Why don't you? Because I got to do a show
tonight where I see I have a show tonight where I sing the goddamn comedy jam which
It's a really fun show here in LA and you do a set that you sing a song and the song I'm singing is spirit of radio by rush
Okay, so I got to keep these chords
Lucy Goosey today like a karaoke version. Well, no of the live band. Oh, okay, and they really nail it
So I want to I want to bring it on my end. How does spirit of radio go?
I know the vocals are incredibly annoying. I know that much
all right don't blow it yeah but there that sounds pretty good the only one I
really know is close it to the heart that's a great one yeah that's their big
head that's sort of there well that's not their big hit it is an amateur
rush listener would assume such thing that that's what makes it their big hit
whatever the amateur listener knows that means that your big Tom Sawyer is a
bigger hit than closer Tom Saw is a good song limelight I would argue is a
bigger hit than closer to the heart. Well, we can look in the charts. The charts don't lie,
but closer to the charts. Hey, how about that? That's right. See, a lot of my friends in Missouri
were deep into rush when I was in high school, and I just never got into it. I mean, I love it so
much. They'd be like, just listen to this one song. And then like three hours later, they'd be like,
this is the same song you're still listening to the same. I'm actually gonna
tell the story tonight at the show but my friend Mike Robinson who was a
stand -up comic for some time we started out together he once described rush as
music that you do your calculus homework to yeah and I was like that's the
that's a perfect set that's a perfect description of rush so I called him the
other day and said like hey man I'm doing this show where I have to sing a
rush song can I can I can I say that I'll give you credit for it but you know
it's just such a great description and he was like yeah of course you can say it
and then he said uh you know man it's weird did you actually like rush and all
these years I've never asked you that and I go I fucking love rush and he goes and
Then we're done here.
Yeah.
Ready to end it.
He's about right.
10 -year friendship over it.
I mean, I'm not going to go that far, but I couldn't go to a concert.
I would go to a concert if I had pre -ticket.
They're amazing.
I've seen them live.
They're one of the greats.
That's great.
I have all kinds of games that I like to play, like on a long drive, and one of them is,
would you see X, artist X, not the band X?
Not, I would always see X.
I love the band X.
Would you see artist X, Y, Z, if you were given free tickets?
Because like free tickets really changes the playing field. So like in Vegas, I was like, would I go see Celine Dion for free? No, no, what I see Britney Spears? Yeah, and I did. And it was free. No, I paid for it was for my girlfriend.
All right, let's fire it up. Black Christmas. Black Christmas. I've never seen this or the remake.
The remake is shit. This is the original. Karen Allen. I think Karen Allen's in this.
Karen Allen might be my all -time number one that I would marry other than Holly Hunter.
Indiana Jones, Karen Allen's your number one of all time.
Scrooge.
If you're talking about like a wife, I'm not talking about like...
Yeah, she's lovely.
Who Jamos wanna, you know.
Karen, it's either Karen Allen or Margot Kitter in this.
I can't remember which one it is.
She went and sang Margot Kitter.
I always get them to those two mixed up.
Anyway, it's Black Christmas.
It's DVD this week, guys, because we didn't have...
there was no Christmas shit on Netflix again. We wanted to do a real Christmas movie so
did I have Santa Paws? That's not a horror movie or is it? It should be. So get
your black Christmas ready if you got the DVD, pause us now and get it all set up
and let's count off this play thing. We're on the home screen now of the DVD. Get
your play highlighted here we go one two three play and it's booting film funding and association
with vision four presents am I correct that this was directed by Bob Clark I've done zero research
I believe it was director of porkies and a Christmas story I believe it was actually if I'm remembering
incorrectly. Here's a bit of interesting movie trivia. Oh, I'll be the
do it. Oh, it's Mark O 'Kitter. I thought so. I didn't think it was Karen. I'm
Superman. The star of this film whose name they just showed and now I already
forget it. Oh, Andrea Martin from SCTV. I like that. Yeah, she's in this. And Larry.
Yeah, and I never John Saxon. There you go.
Nightmare Noem Street fame.
Anyway, the one of the girls in this movie
was also in Romeo and Juliet.
She said she met Steve Martin once.
He said you're in one of my favorite movies of all time.
She thought he was going to say Romeo and Juliet.
He said black Christmas.
Really.
Yeah.
I mean, it's a quality film.
This is a really.
This is not a cheesy hack and slash goofy Christmas film.
This is a dark, slasher movie that just happens to take place at Christmas.
I watched it with you yammering in my ear.
Well, maybe if you took this podcast more seriously, you would have watched it before.
Well, we were supposed to be doing Jack Frost, which I have seen, and would have been very
well -versed in, but we don't have it.
Jack Frost, not the Michael Keaton version, which is just as bad as the horror version, it's
just terrible.
Just as frightening.
Yeah.
It's really, really an awful movie.
Michael Keaton dies and comes back to life as a snowman and then it's like Mrs. Dalfire, but with a snowman
Right, they're like Mrs. Dalfire wasn't quite unbelievable enough
Let's push it a little further now is there a scene where Michael Keaton has to run back and forth between B Michael Keaton
And dressing up as a snowman. Yeah, like in Mrs. Dalfire and he throws a piece of charcoal at the back of Pierce Brothers head
He does because it was a run by calling. Oh, that's right. A run by fruiting. Yeah. Is that what's this down fire?
I don't know. Maybe it's just that I saw when I was 13 when I watch it now, and I'm like, yeah, this is still great
But I don't know if it is have never liked it. Like if it came out today, and I went to see it
I just don't know. I never liked the film. Uh, I was about 15 when it came out. Yeah, I don't agree with people that it's hilarious
I don't agree with people that it's a classic. I mean, it's a classic by money standards and popularity. It's got some laughs. I believe the writer of it follows me on Twitter.
I'm not a fan.
I mean, I don't know what else you wrote. I might be a fan of him. She's a woman, Joe. Interesting. You know, interesting that you couldn't wrap your mind around a woman writing a screenplay.
Oh, it's a woman. Yeah.
is it or is it is the question um and she was at that the 100 greatest comedies are
hundred funniest movies because you didn't even you didn't jump on that bit I
didn't hear you you said she's a woman who wrote Mrs. Delphire I said or is she
I was telling Joe in the horror version of Jack Frost which I somehow saw when I
there's Gene Charlotte somehow saw when I was 13 years old the snowman and this
This is not a joke, rapes a woman with a carrot, and when he takes the carrot out of her,
it is steaming.
Yeah, that's, I like that a lot, not the rap part, the steaming part is funny to me.
I mean, can you imagine being on set with that?
Now I believe the director and writer were going for a social commentary on the Bill Clinton
and Lewinsky cigar scandal that could be.
There's a lot of political commentary and check.
Is Jack Frost a comedy, like a dark?
Is it supposed to be silly?
No, it's part of that.
It was like a string of holiday themed horror movies
that had like holograms in the cover.
Uncle Sam, once you dead.
Yeah, that's my favorite tagline ever.
Jack Frost, they did a series of things.
That's Uncle Sam, we talked about that
during Minneapolis cap, it's the same director.
We did. Also, before I forget for you, we'll see you in hell heads. My buddy Jeremy Murley, a lifelong friend texted me this morning, and he listened to the Gremlins episode.
And he said he believes that him and I saw the choose your own adventure movie together with Christopher Lloyd. And he says that it was film converted to video.
they played it on a laser disc player. They did tabulate the amount of votes
that each one got and that's what selected the next chapter that you would
watch on that. If anyone cared, not a single person asked me about it and I thought
maybe a lot of people would remember this and I guess no one did. But I'm glad you
brought it up again because I don't have it's not yet out of my system doing the
impression of Christopher Lloyd telling the audience he needs their help. I wanted
do more of that. Yeah. Now we need everybody to come together. The story's in your hands.
Only you can predict the outcome. It just sounds so bad. When you see Chris Floyd
interviewed now, he only talks about like wanting to get back to like the theater. Like he's a little
pretentious. He seems like a cool guy, but he seems a little like he's he's
above film. And that's an odd thing for the star of piranha 3d to say here on
it. I've never quite heard it pronounced piranha. Well, I mean, maybe he just
wants to do theater. I mean, what's pretentious about that? Does he say film is a
lower medium? They're just like they're asking them to in the back the future
documentary and he's like, oh, you know, I never wanted to return to to Doc Brown. My
heart at the time was on the stage. I understand people liked it, but I thought, eh, well, why
do you like it? It's just a lock. It's not, it's not a quote, but it's just that was the gist.
What kind of theater is you want to do specifically? Is the real question? I don't know. Like Shakespeare?
You know I feel the exact same way and I know writers aren't supposed to say that but I don't give a shit. I went to a fucking Shakespeare in the park three years ago, something like that.
I, and it was an abri, a heavily abriaged version. If somebody had come up to me with a gun, like hour two, I would have killed myself.
It's just that it's so boring. They it just doesn't apply to today. Yes, the story tools are still used and yes, that's great
It's very innovative. It doesn't mean I got to sit there and listen to this shit and the people with the smug laughs
Oh
Go fuck yourself like hey everyone. I get what what's being said. I understand these words that you don't
Yeah, it's it couldn't be further removed from anything. I give a shit about it's like
Hey, let's go see this play takes place in a time period. You're unfamiliar with a
Culture you don't care about yeah, the language you can't understand and oh also. It's a three -hour poem. Yeah
Fuck you. I don't care now. I tried man. I tried watching I mean, I figured the Mill Gibson version of Hamlet
It was probably as watered down as I was going to get Shakespeare wise outside of the Romeo
and Juliet with John Lombard and Leonardo DiCaprio, which every girl age 20 to 35 is crazily
obsessed with.
Yeah, I tried.
I tried to hit them all the time when their loins were starting to quiver.
Yeah.
I didn't care for either film.
but the uh this is uh do you hear this going let's get to the film let me
lick your pussy yeah this guy is really it's a really creepy uh these calls are
really creepy in the film the serial see bomb I believe so the uh the serial
killer in this film print calls the women uh you know who he sounds like is
screen yeah he does so extreme except you know that killer is in the movie
scream whose name was Jack scream was his name Jack scream come on I don't
know I didn't I didn't you know we do the first one podcast right sorry sorry
as I said it's been steady and really the the character's name was Jack
scream I don't ghost face that's his name yeah go for a second is that where
Ghostface killer got his name. We discussed this on the podcast and the answer is no. I think it was probably the other way around they named the scream killer after Ghostface killer the rapper. I don't know.
I know he has a ghost face and they probably started calling him that on set.
That Wu Tang was out in 93, I think, yeah, it's a good point.
So anyway, the killer in this film makes very disturbing phone calls, much more disturbing
than the ones in scream, and it's a lot of heavy breathing, it's a lot of like noises
like that, a lot of like really perverted stuff, he says to them, all right, it's a pretty
rough flick.
It's dark.
It's dark stuff.
Duty?
I can't remember probably seeing this one in a while it's strange that black Christmas, which is you know slash removing I assume we're about to see plenty of boobs and then porkies, which has just a shocking amount of nudity full frontal nudity, and then they're like, hey, do you want to direct a Christmas story?
Well hold on let me look up what's his name Bob Clark Bob Clark he also speaking of
Christopher Lloyd directed a little film called baby geniuses which ran him out of
Hollywood. It's weird that that's that's what didn't mean here's just trying to make
a nice movie for people about babies for geniuses yeah guy tries to do something
decent he gets run out of town I never really understood that baby geniuses makes
Snow money is widely considered one of the worst movies of all time for real and then they made baby geniuses, too
How did these things happen?
Did they just have a lot of babies sitting around on set that can talk?
I mean it must have made money
Kim Kattrell was also in baby geniuses by the way Kim Kattrell is also in porkies full frontal as well
Really? She's the woman who like barks when she orgasms
Super babies
baby geniuses two was his second to last movie do you want to know what his last movie was I do
the karate dog bob before that a young hella joe osman appeared and I'll remember April
catch a falling star can you imagine you're at a dinner party you know I assume Bob Clark has some nice
friends well to do friends like Bob what are you working on buddy um currently directing
uh the karate dog like come on well here's he didn't deserve that he's a good director he
directed from the hip which uh now oh that's not good uh loose cannons hackmen in acroix
saw gene hackmen and dan acroid we're in a movie together it's not good oh boy uh
Ryan Stone. Oh, this guy. He did Porky's too, all right? He did Porky's too. The next day after a Christmas story. Same year.
Uh, Ryan Stone is Dally Parton sliced along. Yeah. Oh, Death Dream. I actually own this movie and I haven't watched it yet.
It just seems like it could have been a little choosier, you know. Yeah, but I remember I bought Death Dream right after I saw Black Christmas.
and said like I'm I'm game to see whatever this without this guy did and that's
as far as I got it he keeps scrolling up to see all the other things. It's weird
now that that movie like and I think the same thing about Jeremiah Cheechick who
was a commercial director whose first movie was national ampune's Christmas
vacation Bob Clark directs Christmas story these movies now are like everyone's
favorite Christmas movie. Every home is watching them at least once every single
year. How did they not get back in the movie game? Bob Clark died. So that's why he's not back in
the game. Yeah. He died in 2007, unfortunately. And old cheat chick. I mean, he did Benny and June,
and I don't know if you ever direct it again. I love Benny and June. I was okay. What's Benny
and June about again? I always mixed that up with Gilbert Grape. It's John Depp. You might know him
is Johnny and Mary Stewart Masterson and he's like a disturbed it's a very
weird premise or she's disturbed and he's like he's obsessed with Charlie
Chaplin I don't know why I like the movie so much but I remember it being a
really good romantic comedy and what's the one you mix it up with? What's eating
and a fantastic movie.
But Johnny Depp's also in that.
Juliet Lewis, who was that?
For some reason, I think I always picture Johnny Depp
with Leonardo DiCaprio doing that role thing,
the chaplain role dance.
Yeah, but that's not it's the other movie.
And DiCaprio is the handicap kid and color crap.
Your boy, Chi -Chi, he could still in the game.
He's directing a lot of television.
Oh good, any big shows?
That's where they go now.
Rogue South of hell criminal minds, you know, all right. He's your mainstream fair part of Dixie Chuck
The glades. Yeah, he did a lot at warehouse 13. Yeah, he's all right. I'm glad to hear him burn notice eight episodes
gossip girl
I
mentioned
Juliet Lewis. I haven't shared the story on the podcast. I had a
birthday housewarming party about a year ago and
And I say it's going to start at 8 o 'clock, but you assume nobody will show up till 9 -9 -30.
Sure. So I got a bar and a bartender and I'm getting everything set up, and my girlfriend's still like getting dressed and stuff, and they're doorbell rings.
And I'm like, ah, geez, which one of my nerd friends showed up at 8 sharp.
And I open the door, and I'm face to face with Academy Award -nominated actress Juliet Lewis, who knows shit, and I am not just saying this because she came to my home.
Has always been one of my very favorite actresses, and I'll see anything she does and I love her always have been like I've had a
Weird kind of creepy thing for her back in the Christmas vacation days also in the
Cape Fear days of course
She's just standing there. I I didn't know what was happening. There was no even like alcohol out
I was mortified and I realized she's dating a buddy of mine who was there early
So I'm like, hey guys, come on in. There's not a single person here. And they were both kind of like little awkward. I give them the tour of the house. It's fine.
Julia Lewis makes a beeline for this Martin Scorsese book I have and opens it to Cape Fear. A movie that she was in. Right. Yeah. So she's sitting on the couch, like reading about Cape Fear.
Um, and I just thought that was kind of nuts that she walks into someone's home and it's like, oh, there's something about me here
Not that she's a narcissist or something. I don't know. Most actors are. It's kind of weird though
But I was like, yeah, that's a little weird. So cut to 10 drinks and three hours later and there's a lot of people at my house
And it's really loud and busy and some buddies of mine are over and we're standing at the top of the staircase
And I start saying to them I go
Oh, hey, it's the craziest thing.
But Juliet Lewis was here earlier.
They're like, oh my God, that's crazy.
I go, yes, she came in, she made a B -line for this book,
opened it to Cape Fear, and they all kind of laughed.
And I was like, can you believe that?
Walks right in and opens it to a movie, she was in.
And then coming from a bathroom downstairs,
where I didn't think anyone was, is Juliet Lewis.
And she goes, oh, you guys are talking about me?
Oh, boy.
How now how high and paranoid are you at this point? I'm high and drunk. I
Tell you it was really rough and my friends kind of laughed and here was my cover
Which I think went over, but I said no, no, no, I wasn't talking about you and then it kind of hung in the air
Like well who the hell else would you be talking about and I said no John here my friend John right his daughter when she was at the house
Daughters never been to my house
Went right for the book and was reading up at all this violent shit, right?
That's what we were talking about and she goes, oh, okay, she seemed totally fine with it. She knew we were I was lying
I think why I would even attempt such a desperate lie. I don't know. This is what I would have done
I would have said no, no, no, no, no, no, I was talking about the time Julia Roberts was here
That's what I would have done. Yeah
It was pretty bad, but she's she was a cool lady. She was delightful
I immediately like was like is the music cool enough like when she walked in
And I was like, do I need to put on cooler music?
Do I need to do this?
It's very nerve -wracking.
What did she say?
No, I didn't ask her.
I was thinking these things in my head.
Oh, I think you were asking me.
You should ask her.
That would have been a good little conversation piece.
Yeah.
That was, honestly, for me, when the first time
I ever had a birthday party at a dive bar here in L .A.
And old Rob McElhaney from it's always sunny showed up.
Yeah.
I was just texting with him.
He showed up with two the churn and boys, two of my writers friends that write on the
show and my buddy Bill Burr and I saw the churn and and I was like, Hey, you guys made
it.
And then I saw Bill and I was like, Hey, you guys made it.
And then I turned and there was a guy and he's like, hi, I'm Rob.
And I was literally shaking.
I was so excited to meet him because I love the show so much.
He's kind of like when you met me, a former writer for the show, you felt the same way
Yeah, yeah, except without the shaking or excitement. Well, he's very different. I mean, like he'll he'll he'll look you right in the eye. He gives you a firm handshake. That's always a real.
Uh, kind of trigger for me. And if I may, I'm very uncomfortable. I mean, if I may say so.
Well, he's a good looking kid, and turned out we had a mutual close friend, a guy that
I grew up with that he ended up going to high school with and was good friends with and
we talked all about it, our mutual friend Bill Graham, and we had a lot to bond on, it
was very nice.
Yeah, good guy.
and then he left and that was it didn't embarrass myself with some insulting story about him at
the top of the stairs just appreciated his presence I did make her laugh though we were in my bedroom
and I was whoa I was like don't say this is where the magic happens don't say this is where the
magic happens don't say this is where the magic happen and then her boyfriend goes I guess this
is where the magic happens and I was like okay you took that one I should have said it because she
left and then I go yeah she goes your bed's the perfect height by the way just so
you know I'm like padded the bed she's like your bed's a perfect height the
hell is that mean I don't know Joe that's whore talk as far as I'm concerned now
and I said well if you like that let me just drop another nugget on you she's
a temper -peatic and she left and I came in my pants look it was it's harsh it's
It's hard to be funny when you're sweating as much as I was sweating.
I hear you. Look, I bombed once in front of Inspector Deck from Wu Tang Clan, and he left the show, which that hurt.
But now he follows me and we follow each other on Twitter, and Deck, if you're listening, I'd like to say you're my favorite of the Wu Tang Clan.
I mean, that's sincerely. We've come a long way. Maybe one day we'll meet.
Michael Henning always talks about he was cast as lead in Tigerland, which was the movie
that completely broke Colin Farrell and he got the role and it was like the part
ever young actor wanted and then like two days before shooting they were like we found
this guy Colin Farrell and he's going to play the part so he was devastated then he gets
cast in Wonder Boys as Katie Holmes boyfriend which was like the fourth lead of the movie
or something. And if you've seen Wonder Boys which is a great move with Michael Douglas you'll
know there's no Katie Holmes boyfriend character because he goes to the premiere of this thing and
they completely cut out his like 45 page story completely cut out of the motor and that's what got us
always sunny basically because he's like I'm not getting in there as an actor I gotta do it on my own
or inspiring tale. Oh my god yeah that's a very heartbreaking story. Well until you realize that he's
created a show, it's been on the air for 12 years, and it's about to direct a major
motion picture.
Woo, what's he directing?
Are you allowed to talk about it?
He was announcing the trades.
He came up with like an ET style story, like a family adventure that he's going to direct
and it's like a massive budget and yeah, pretty exciting.
That's great.
Or you know, certainly a bigger budget than always something.
Congrats to Rob Beckley.
Congrats as always.
Now can we call him a friend of the podcast since you're friends with him?
I know he's never listened to it, but yeah, we can call him that.
I'm a huge fan of that show. I just watched the Christmas special yesterday.
I was right out there at that time. I watch it every Christmas.
It's a pretty good Lamborghini Cooontosh.
Yeah, it's the bad.
He and Dennis really, I mean, everybody hits a home run in that, in that episode.
But he and Dennis.
Well, Davido.
Shindler. Really the couches. Pretty spectacular. Also Davido's choice to make grunt noises
in almost every scene, like when he's trying to get out of the kuntash, he's just going
and then he does it again when they put the fog in, he thinks it's the, when they're going to do the
ghost thing and he thinks it's a fire. Yeah, I remember shooting that, because they had Huddleston
It was the actual Lebowski. Yeah, I know. But they shot that thing where they blasted
them back with the power of wind or whatever. The stobe machine. Crazy shot. They did
it. It's like slow motions. They had to keep doing it over and over. Dennis goes over
in a way where it's like, how did he not just break his neck? Yeah, it looked pretty painful
to me. Yeah. Right. Zerr story here. Yeah. This chick's gonna get an abortion. That was
kind of a big thing in these movies. A catty shack has that whole abortion subplot. Yeah.
Well, you know, these women need to be more careful back then.
Caddy Shackman, I guess they thought they needed to target the fucking youth market.
But man, when they cut back to Danny and his girlfriend, it's just death, it's just death.
For a movie to be that funny, and then also just not realize that no one gave a shit about
that story.
There is zero.
I forgot it was even a story in the movie, so you just said it.
Wait a minute.
Is there a David Huddleston story here?
No, he was on set.
That's it. I don't have a story. He was nice. He seemed kind of with it using blazing saddles as well.
Kind of was a little out of it.
Kind of with it would imply kind of not with it, but he was doing all right.
He's probably 75 years old.
Oh, good. Yeah, that's good.
All right. Well, good. I think he's very funny in that episode.
Sure.
I like at the end of the graveyard where Dennis is like,
you are useless you bring nothing to the table just screaming at him because he's
not he's not grasping the idea of playing a ghost in there like play all right great show it is
I love it I really do love it folks welcome back to this commentary on it's always sunny and Philadelphia
look at that shot right there I don't think we've we've ever talked about a movie less than this one
That's you say that almost every week I really do and the leprechaun was the least we've talked about anything
I mean, you know black christmas. It's a great. It truly is a film. I you know
I think there's a difference between a movie and a film and I think this is truly a film
And I think this is a very well done film
That being said it is a slasher movie so it's a little you know
There's a little less need to pay attention to every detail
We kind of know what's gonna go down here
girls are going to get murdered. There's going to be a little loose tit
shown. Well, this girl's already in the robe. Like she should have been putting it
on. This is the this is the girl from Romeo and Juliet. I forget her name. I
mean, she'll be a hussie. Strikingly beautiful. What else was she in? My bed room.
Olivia Hussie. I told her you know that last name is one letter off for being a
Perfect word. Oh, why not just go with Hussie like a slump
Cuz pussy I was do I know I know pussy thing we this is why
We we don't have girls with us here. We have a dog sitting between them. Yeah, but the dog is sucking our dick
Both of our decks. Yeah, we can both fit our decks into a dog's mouth wide dog
I wanted to ask you, did you finish watching Trumbo, which I consider one of the worst movies of the year, couldn't get through it, and it was sent to me as an Academy Awards for my consideration, couldn't get through it, got about 30 minutes, 35 minutes in, it's so bad folks, and it's gotten really good reviews.
I don't understand every character that walks in announces their name and occupation. That's how lazy it is
I already talked about this on here. Yeah, I don't remember. They'll be like hi. I'm Otto Preminger the film director
Is how a character will enter a scene?
Listen, the thing that bothered me most when I said this to my friend that I was watching it with I go this is the dialogue in this is
Written like it's a movie from the 50s and not a movie that takes place in the 50s. Yeah
You know, it's really cool. This is where we shut it off
The the his daughter goes daddy. Are you a communist and the girl?
My friend she yelled I
Can't take it turn it off. Yeah, that was the breaking point. Yeah
And then they did the thing. I hate when movies do this
You got a guy playing John Wayne
Do you got a guy playing auto -premger? Yeah, you got a guy playing Dalton Trumbo?
don't then splice in real footage of Ronald Reagan get a guy to play Ronald
Reagan pick what you're gonna do yeah then they also had like well Kirk Douglas
you didn't even get to Kirk Douglas but he comes in and I I'm pretty sure
they were switching back and forth between actual Douglas footage and the actor
it was a real botched job then he got John Goodman comes in screaming about how
much pussy he gets. And you're like, what movie am I watching now? What is his role in it?
He's playing his exact same Argo character. I think they use the same set, the same like
office with movie posters that he was in an Argo. Right. I think they just rolled over the same set.
And he is playing, that's the one part I liked actually. He plays like a Roger Korman type
who hires Trumbo and he's like, look man, if you can make, you can make as many movies as you want
for us as long as they're cheap. So then he keeps giving him scripts and
Goodman's like, now he needs more tits, needs more this needs more that. And
then he winds up asking if he can write like a really great small budget movie
for them and it winds up becoming an Oscar thing. That stuff is cool. And he got
his good. No, it's that I don't know what it was because he wrote and directed
that film. It was something about a boy. It was about a boy, the Hugh Graham. Way
ahead of its time. We also, what other screeners do we watch for the big
Oscar movies. We watched Carol, which is a 50s set lesbian love story that I very much enjoyed.
We almost went for Carol, but we went for Trumbo instead. Carol's a slow burn. It's just like a
perfect looking movie like every shot looks like it looks like your screensaver here actually.
It looks like a Norman Rockwell like 50s. Very nice magazine cover. It's really great. I peeped
That spotlight film I really like spotlight. It was terrific. I said Mark Rufalo doesn't get nominated for an Academy Award
There's no justice in this world. Well, it should have won for Foxcatcher. As good as he isn't spotlight
He was better in Foxcatcher. He's doing he's doing a slightly different version of the same character. I think he's better in spotlight
Well, let's fight about I mean it down to this that weird way speaks in it. Yeah, every part of it
It's like, yeah, this guy is, I know this guy.
This is like the anxious guy that I know.
That's how he was in a, you can count on me,
which I think he got nominated for.
If he was incredible number.
Incredible, they were calling him the next brando.
I wouldn't argue it.
He just kind of keeps on acting.
He's in like three movies a year,
summer good, summer bad.
It's great.
It always made me mad in a, the kids are all right,
that he gets the sort of shit
into the stick at the end of the movie.
What happened so much?
Well, it's about, uh, it's, who plays the couple in it?
Julia, Julia and more and more and more and more and more.
And then at Benning and then Julia and more has the affair
with Mark Rufalo, but then she kind of gets forgiven
and he just gets like ostracized.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
It kind of always bum me out.
I feel like it was confusing for everybody.
I'm sure he's fine.
That's the only movie I remember them like trying to sell Ruffalo as like a heart
prop kind of stop doing that. Well he's a sexy man. All right y 'all. Good
looking guy. Yeah. I think I agree. You have to come on here and kick the guy
down. I tried watching Phantom Menace the other night. I got about 10 minutes in. I
prefer Phantom Men to attack the seas. That's rough. I like attack of the
I like from from the point and attack of the clones where he kills the sand people on I really enjoy the first half has got some
Difficult stuff for me in it. I like the Django Fet scenes
Phantom Menace to me looks a little more like an actual Star Wars movie. It's not too carried away yet with the CGI
But I enjoy that whole opening sequence
Where the jet I have to bust out of the trade Federation planet and or ship I mean and
I like when they go down into the underwater city, and I like the lightsaber battle at the end very much
Potterace is pretty cool. I'm still gonna watch them before somehow before
This weekend when the movie comes out. I don't need to watch them again
I've seen those movies. I saw each one seven times in the theater. Oh the the prequels. Yeah, holy shit, Joe
And crystal skull seven times. I don't even know what to say
folks joke out in a fight with some guy the other night about Kim and the
Crystal School. That was one of the more heated arguments I've ever witnessed
up close. And I saw both sides he was being a complete jackass about it. He was
being very smug and annoying. He was right and he's also like won't all your
point was which I completely agree with Joe was like yeah it's not perfect
Yeah, they're stupid shit in it, but you can't say it's one of the worst movies ever made. And he's like, no, I think it's the worst movie ever made. It is. It's the worst movie ever made.
And then he left seconds after the argument. I think it kind of drove him to leave.
He's any well the part that was your I mean that's what's he kept saying
Bill warned me about bringing this up with you. So why do you do it? Well then why'd you bring it up? Yeah, you know, I'm seven whiskey's in
You know, let's like bring it up my parents divorce or so my parents are divorced. I'm just saying right for example
You know, well, how do you want me to react to this? Yeah, that really bothers me
I have a joke in my act about how people it's called defending George Lucas
And it's about how people say Fandom medicine kingdom of the critical skull crystal skull or the worst movies
They've ever seen. It's such an absurd premise, right? It's so insanely absurd and his polyshores got like eight movies under his belt easily
And you're gonna you're gonna say those are technically better. It's fucking ridiculous. It's not an lies
I'm bad, but I think like what he was trying to say and not saying well was like
because the other movies are so great, the fourth one has to be way better than your average movie.
She's a stupid argument.
And yes, stupid. It's not really a great argument.
That's that classic nerd hated crystal school.
That's that classic nerd argument.
My friend Jared always, Jared doesn't, my friend Jared doesn't like the movie, but Logan.
Yeah, but he always talks about how like it's a good point.
He talks about like the nerd argument where he's like,
He's like, oh, I'm sorry was the movie not what you had in your head, right?
You know, and it's like that to me is like what it is with that movie. It's just like
It's like oh, it wasn't made the way you thought it needed to be made like yeah, okay
You know, I just bought the sequel to the dark night returns
Frank Miller's classic graphic novel the dark night returns the third one is the first issue the third
Part of the trilogy was just released
So I said, you know, I never read the second one because it got such bad reviews and everybody said it sucked so bad
And then I was talking to my friend the other day and he's like he goes it's good, man
It's not the first one, but it's good. It's worth reading. There's cool stuff
And I was like, you know what?
This is exactly what happens. People are like it needs to be exciting in a bottle again.
Shut up. Yeah, you go write something. Yeah, people will do that. You know, they'll be like, why would you watch like we always bring up
Norbit. Why would you sit and watch Norbit? What's wrong with you? And I'm like
Because I'd like to decide if I think something's good or bad on my own. Norbit has a lot bigger laughs or more laughs
Than most comedies unfortunately. I love Norbit. It's I watched the fun and
Properly hilarious. Yeah, I mean, it's not it's racist or I watch the
Ridiculous six this weekend the Adam Sandler movie and everyone's like same thing worst movie ever Adam Sandler is
is murdering comedy, worse film of all time.
And all I ever do every time is I'm like, okay,
there's 25 people in this movie that I think are funny.
And Adam Sandler has been in some really funny movies
long time ago, but I'm gonna sit down and watch this.
It's got Norm Mcdonald, it's got Nick Nolte,
it's got David Spade, it's got Steve Zahn,
it's got Will Forte, it's got John Terturo.
How's Norm Mcdonald?
Steve Bishemi, Norm has two lines, unfortunately.
How's Will Forte, Furny?
Jimmy's really funny. Wilfort is really funny. Swarsden's funny in it. Okay, there's love shorts. I'm not slapping my knee folks and it's two hours, which was way too long. But there's a
like John Turro plays the guy who's inventing baseball. And it's really a really really. If it was a UCB sketch, people would be gizzing all over it or an SNL sketch. Right, John Turro is nothing to do with the movie. He's creating baseball.
ball, and basically he keeps changing the rules to suit him. So he says there's two strikes
a piece. So then Sandler pitches and he gets two by him. And I was like, all right, just
one more pitch then. He said it was two strikes. I didn't. I invented the game. And I said,
it's three strikes. And he just keeps changing the rules. So he's like, he'll steal a base.
And I'm like, but you said you can't run unless the balls hit me. He's like, unless you're
stealing a base and you just keep changing the rules and it's a that scene I was laughing and it's a really really funny scene
And that's how you have to look at it. There's terrible stuff in it
There's a donkey who sprays projectile diarrhea out of his ass four or five times in the movie. Okay, you know, that joke
Maybe isn't for you that jokes for your kids kids like Adam Sandler too and kids are gonna die at a donkey spraying
diarrhea.
Any kids that didn't, I wouldn't trust him.
Yeah, exactly.
I wouldn't trust him.
Now here's one issue I did have with it, people are claiming it's a little racist.
There's a little dodgy stuff in it.
Most notably, Rob Schneider in light brown face, just playing a Mexican character who mentioned
several times throughout the movie that he dreams of someday finding a taco tree.
That's a little problem.
Now folks, nobody steps in
However on the whole am I glad I washed it? I don't even know. I'm not glad I spent two hours on it
All I'm saying is I'm trying to make the point that is not the worst movie of all time folks
You can't say that and there are worse comedies that come out every day also this argument of anybody any one person is able to ruin comedy
Yeah, exactly is it's an absurd statement you're doing you're ruining comedy more by saying things like that
Yeah, in a comic you don't like doing something they think is funny
It's also you know like you'll read I read more tweets about
How shitty ridiculous six looks than I did tweets about any of the great movies that are coming out and
None of these people have seen the movie so that's all I'm saying if I'm gonna make a joke about something
I'd like to have seen it and then I can confidently say it's really terrible. I got really mad at a
once when the Clone Wars movie came out the cartoon one I saw it like opening
morning I walked down to the theater in Manhattan and watched it and I was
coming out of the theater and there was a girl there from like a YouTube thing
and she was like did you just see the Clone Wars and I was like yeah and she's like
can I interview you about it and I said yeah and she's like okay how bad did it suck
not come on and I go I go did you see it yet and she's like no no of course not
And I was like, so you're going to sit out here, you're going to interview people about a movie that sucks that you never saw
And I go, no, it's fucking cool. You're like, bye. I was a real contours
Yeah, anyway, it's just, you know, and look, I like making jumps too. Yeah, I mean these people
Everything can't be the worst of the best folks. It just can't and everything's not genius and everything's not brilliant
You got to learn what these words mean and start using them appropriately. Yeah
Worst best a brilliant genius. The word amazing needs to be retired. Amazing. Well now everyone speaks like these clickbait articles
Like try, you know, they got to have a really strong opinion so that you you know
You'll keep listening to them or something, but saying something was the best or worst
They they're really can only be one of those so don't say that I agree Pat. Am I disagreeing?
You're not am I saying no? You're not. I'm telling you the truth, right?
Tell me the truth. Well, that's what the hell I'm talking about now. You know what I mean?
When it's like you you won't believe these crazy facts we found from the set of Uncle Buck and you're like, no, I'll believe them.
Like one of the facts is that McCulley Colken's in it. Yeah, I believe it. I know. I've seen it. Well the things I hate are like are like, you know,
10 ways the girl from the big bang theory is a problem.
You know, then you read the article. It's like yeah, it's like you mean problematic like for feminism or something
Just a general. Yeah, it's like a thing I read and it was literally like
She sent her boyfriend to drug rehab even though she apparently drinks wine occasionally
Hypocrinical, it's literally shit like that. Why are they attacking her?
They attack everybody. What is she done? These are pig people. Yeah, let me just say this if you're part of the press
Yes, you're probably a pig piece of shit.
Now you may not have always wanted to be, but by now you are.
You're most likely a pig piece of shit.
That's why spotlight, that was sort of my favorite part of it, is showing you kind of the
last gasp of like true quality journalism because there's no place for it anymore.
They might exist, but those people have been excised because they're not willing to dance
for the monkey.
We just had a great death on screen just to mention something about this movie in over
a 40 -minute period. Husky lady just got a hook through the mouth. Yeah, yanked her up into
the ceiling. Husky lady. That's a nice eulogy for her, Joe. Oh, what are you gonna say? I just
want them to know who we're talking about, right? That's something it always bugs me too. Like,
you know, like, you have to say somebody's characteristics if you're gonna know who they are.
That was a big thing on curb all the time be like this fat lady and then it's like whoa whoa whoa so
what are you supposed to say what do you mean there's a big thing on curb he always had issues with
that too there's 19 people in a room and one of them is fat how are you gonna single that person out
right right yeah it always bothers me I never know what to say I always just feel trapped of the you
know the um the lady um in the over in the blue dress yeah lady over there in the blue dress
And it was always it was always something I appreciate it about
Remember a friend to race to do a joke about it. He would say black people aren't he was a black comp
He is a black army. It's hey
It's a black people aren't racist. They're just more honest than white people. Yeah, and you'd be like
You know because a black dude will be like, you know, hey man. You seen John John John John the fucking white boy
I always appreciated that like
like the most about like starting in a black room.
Look, I'm like stuttering right now over it.
It's like somehow it's gonna be race.
It's not, I'm saying like a nice thing.
Like I was a white guy.
I started in a black room in a black neighborhood
and it was a different culture
that I hadn't experienced fully up until that point.
I really enjoyed like the honesty aspect
or the candid aspect in the dialogue that I,
because I hadn't seen it and the suburbs it was very you know it was very sort of you know
polite and you and you don't say certain things and whatever and you know that's why I always
thought it was weird like when I started to do different types of rooms in comedy and start to
hear like the arguments about like women uh -huh or four women and the comedy was unfair to women
because I found then the black circuit the female comics were like the most celebrated right and also
So they would just be like, go fuck yourself and not take any shit, you know, I get that
too.
I also get that like, you know, I'm not saying it's wrong, I'm not the kind of person
who can be like, go fuck yourself either.
I'm like, you shouldn't have to be if you can be funny and kind of quiet and reserved.
Yeah, I'm not saying that sexism doesn't exist.
I'm just saying it was a, it was a, it was a new thing for me to experience when I got into
other types of rooms.
Yes.
So anyway, we're at a time now where if I, I go to a
party I almost don't know any topic that is okay to discuss it feels like well
like in a low spiel is area it's of California let's trick them know where we
are yeah but I always hear people like really arguing about something and I'm
like what in God's name are you doing like we're all do we're all doing our best
aren't we and is anyone really out to like leave the house and like really
getting your face and offend somebody I don't think so and this is what happens when
you can't discuss real issues or have real debates anymore.
You end up drunk at a bar screaming at somebody about the fourth Indiana Jones
movie because it's your rage is all impacted.
And it comes out in an appropriate time.
It's the only thing you can fight about anymore.
It's a shame.
It is.
The art of conversation.
Am I right?
Well, you are, Joe, but I think we're proven weekend and week out that that
art is still alive and well.
Um, I just saw the timer on the VCR.
I mean on the DVD I heard you the timer on the DVD player. It's we're at 40 the 45 minute mark. I
mean, I was ready to fall asleep about 15 20 minutes ago. Not because the movie or you. I'm just I
thought we were going to be at about 90 minutes. I was just about to say I think we're creeping
up on the end here. And unless it's an hour long movie. What if it's a two hour movie? We need more
We need more hour long movies. What is this bullshit? Well, I like a tight 90 minutes. Look, I like a tight 92, but I'd love an hour. Yeah, well that'll never happen. They can't release that. Why I actually they'll actually criticize it like that movie grand
with Lily Tom will be like they'll criticize the running time they should have criticized everything else about that
Oh, but it was 78 minutes and they're like is this even count as a feature film. This is like a pilot for Netflix or something
It's like well, okay, but movies no one ever said a movie has to be two hours
I don't know that I could have gone much deeper than 78 minutes with it. Oh, I hated it by the way, but I didn't hate it
I just was like I watched I felt like outside of Lily Tomlin
and I was like, nothing about the movie intrigued me.
And comedies, you know.
And do I like Sam, what's his face to?
Oh, Sam Elliott.
Sam Elliott.
So, that's what started our Sam Elliott impression.
I forgot, give me a kiss.
That's all he wanted.
Yeah.
And then he, oh, that's right.
Because we started the food thing
because he goes, I just made some corn.
You want some corn?
Good odd.
What would I do?
I liked it.
But I liked it too, but I liked the touch.
He was the only one in the movie who felt like an actual person to me.
I thought Lily Tomman was great at it.
All right, Joe.
I'm not going to sit here and disparage an American institution.
I love her.
I thought she was annoying as hell, mama.
Well, I think that's kind of the part, the point.
Yeah, she's not supposed to be a wholly likeable character.
She's supposed to be something that's a little grating.
I liked when she was dripping the coffee on the floor.
Say, and there's your fucking drip coffee asshole.
Yeah, you actually told me about that scene going in and I hated it. You did it just hated it
I don't know what to tell you this guy by the way in black Christmas is this not Frank azz
It's not Frank azz. It's got an azz. It looks like Frank azz
By the way never saw Andrea Martin so bangable in my life
Really, I would say this is the
least attractive she's ever looked I think she looks super like cute like
alternate chick bangable I guess that was a sort of condescending thing it's
great but SCTV is my favorite I like when she plays like the like wild
dancing woman on SCTV yeah yeah yeah she looks sexy when she does it for my
money I'll tell you what's her face on SCTV I mean that's
Catherine O 'Hara, this is good as it gets.
No question.
Could you imagine dating Catherine O 'Hara back then
and her being that fucking beautiful and that funny?
I can't, my former boss, Dave Thomas,
who was on SETV kind of dated and I think she kind of dated,
not to imply she was sleeping around,
but I think she kind of dated a lot of the people involved
with SETV and they all just like Martin Shorten
and they were all just like, I just, I love her.
Like, no one had anything negative to say about me.
How could you?
Had a great time.
She put some back.
I know that much.
Does she?
Yeah.
Really?
I love her as the mom and home alone with...
I mean, I had the exact same hair as the mom and home alone
when I was 10 years old.
A big, big swoop.
She, uh, she's a gorgeous woman in that.
But Beetlejuice, I always found her.
Oh, sure.
Terribly attractive.
And I like that she's like kind of demeaning
in Beetlejuice that turns me on, it's not a art lady. I like that. I think her best
acting role though is in a for your consideration. I think she hits a fucking grand slam in
that movie. She's rough in that movie. Yes, that's a rough part and a pretty rough movie.
It's my, it's probably my least favorite of his even though I do like it and she was definitely
the strong suit for sure. It's my favorite of the guesties. She was, they talked about nominating
her for that it came up a lot and I know the reason she didn't is because every actress was like
that's hitting way too close to home. I couldn't believe she didn't get nominated. She was
fucking great in that move. I can't believe Levy didn't get nominated for Mighty Wind. I thought
Eugene Levy was incredible in a mighty wind. Yeah Levy's grown into tears. Levy's great in
a comedy. He's great in it. That mission when they when they're singing to each other and like yeah
it's rough. He's still in love with her and they have to do the kiss. Yeah it's brutal.
It's brutal film. But yeah, for your consideration is my favorite Christopher Gus movie and my favorite Christopher Gus character is
probably
I always forget the guy's name focus and Claire
Waiting for no no no and it's in it's in it's in it's in for your consideration
Really you like that a lot more than I know the guy that you know the guy that plays like the backer who's in the producer
Yeah, I know you mean it wasn't the apple in the tree
Yeah, but the pair on the ground was the trouble. I mean that guy is so fucking amazing. Yeah, he's actually
Close tie for first place. Other favorite guest character is that guy in best -in -show
Playing Michael McKeon's boyfriend
His name is
John something Michael Lynch something. Oh David Michael Higgins. Yeah
He is super funny. Yeah, he's funny in the breakup also. He's great in the breakup. It's great and everything. Yeah
My favorite part in best of shows when he's at the deli counter and he says
Give me that pepperoni stick. I just want to hold it
Yeah, he's incredibly funny and best of show
Yeah, for me the funniest is is Guffman and for me the best is mighty wind
person. You didn't ask but I'm telling. I don't mind here in it. I love
Guffman. Guffman is a close second place for me. Parker Posey and Guffman. Yeah.
She's great. She's great. I think Posey is better in Best and Show. I agree with
my favorite part is when she's trying to find that busy bee toy for her dog. Yeah.
And the guy holds up the black and yellow fish. And she goes this is the least
like a bee of any of them like screams and it's fed pet adult braces entire sequence gives me
anxiety like I can't tell you yeah it's it's makes me so uncomfortable Fred Willard and Mighty
when talking about the show he was on Fred what happened yeah Fred Willard and Mighty when this
fantastic. Fred Willard, Fred Willard and everything is fantastic. To me, his, his, you know, his, his, his shining performance is
government. He was, well, and the announcer and Buston, shall, and the announcer, Buston, shall, went after her like she was made out of
hand. Oh, yeah, as the couple and the swish, swish pantsuits. It's amazing. Hey, Doc, give her some caramels. Future customer. No, I'm kidding.
Yeah, he's he's so good. He's so fucking good. I also have a best in show where he goes on about the bass and how now he wants to put the pipe in its mouth. Mm -hmm. And the
Like it's the most original idea that anybody's ever had. Yeah, and then they got a perfect straight manager just sits there looking disgusted with him.
Just great. Jane Lynch best in show. Home run. Yeah, and Coolidge. My favorite. Coolidge. Yes. Coolidge is
When they all say they're gonna do a hum in mighty wind to honor the guy who died is like, I always remember he had the
The sweetest hum and I'd like to ask for a quick moment where we all just hum in honor of the late great whatever his name is and they all are going
and humming and then it goes around to
Coolage and she's going like
Like whether like face contorted like an alien of some kind
Real real fun
I love it. I love it. Coolidge in for your consideration, similar to her character on
broke girls. Am I wrong? You're not wrong. Yeah, that very same party with Juliet Lewis,
about 145 in the morning. I'm like, well, it's about time to start winding down and into
the party comes Jennifer Coolidge. She said she was going to take off. I said, no, please
stay. Yeah. And we had a nice little drink. Quite a bit of whiskey with bonus hour at the party.
Yeah. And your couch. Yeah. A lot of drinking. I'll be honest. I was going to try to put some moves on
Coolidge. She's a single woman. I couldn't I couldn't breach it. I was just too nervous. She was making
me too nervous. She is just such an incredible delight to be around. I had a great time talking to her.
I loved her. I loved her presence. Yeah. She can make, you know, she can make just any line that you
I have funny lines that you don't think are funny.
You should mix funny.
That's what that's how Julia Louis Dreyfus got.
Seinfeld, did you know that?
I've seen all the stuff, so probably.
Seinfeld said he wanted her to read for Elaine
and he said he remembered her from SNL
and he said he knew that she could make any,
she knew how to deliver any line you gave her.
Did you know that Rosie O'Donnell nearly got that role
of Elaine?
Rosie O'Donnell.
That's interesting.
Definitely in the mix like she was down in the fine. I could have been funny. That could have been very funny Larry and her friends
I think that could have been funny. I think it would have been too much like having two George's though
I oh Rosadonna would have ruined the show wouldn't have been a hit
We're ruined it. I'm gonna grab a drink right back. Keep talking. I don't think she would have ruined it
I think they wouldn't have been ten seasons. I don't know. I mean it's but you know
I think I think they had a nice dynamic with what they went with
but I like a Rosie O'Donnell.
That means for a moment as Pat's gone.
Pat, take your time.
I mean, the guy's leaving the podcast
to get a drink, he's stopping and reading things
as he leaves the room.
My favorite, my favorite Rosie O'Donnell film
is a little picture called A League of Their Own.
I'm sure all of you are familiar with that film.
Tom Cruise, or Tom Cruise.
Hey, let's imagine A League of Their Own.
Oh, Tom Cruise.
Tom hangs in that movie.
Maybe it's it might be the funniest time Hanks were all ever created and it's his last.
I think like it's like kind of his last like tried and true comedy after that he I think
he did sleepers in Seattle and and then like other than that he did a you know he's done
some stuff that had humor in it like the terminal.
But he hasn't he hasn't done an out and out comedy since then and it's just you know
I got he's so funny in that movie. I want I want Tom Hanks to do a comedy again so bad
I'm happy Murray is finally back
Kind of doing like straight comedy again
Like what are you referring to rock the Caspa look I heard it wasn't great
But I'm just glad that he was kind of back doing a bill Murray thing again like that
You know, he's great in these dramatic roles, but I was just happy to see him back doing something like that again
Here's what it is even a Murray Christmas like I appreciate
I didn't like it, but I appreciate it that he was trying to be funny again.
Here's the problem. He wasn't trying that hard in the Murray Christmas, which I did kind of enjoy.
I'm nominated for a knocking in comedy way.
Emmy. I think. Well, sure.
Here's what happens, Joe. Here's what's wrong with the entertainment business.
These people
start
forgetting about anything else and just focusing on these meaningless awards.
They they get all wrapped up in it. They maybe they got a friend or a couple friends who were like,
I'm nominated for a whatever the fuck and they start thinking like I got to get me some of that so then they abandoned their true pure
Gifts and start doing things that aren't even in their comfort zone and
They won't stop until they get that Oscar so they take roles that they shouldn't be doing I just watched the big short
Which I liked right I thought it was a
So I saw a view that said it was the movie wolf of Wall Street wanted to be okay
It is such a watered down version of Wolf of Wall Street. Now I hated Wolf of Wall Street. Did you?
I hated it. Oh, I didn't even know what to say. I thought it was just a completely masturbatory
jumbled mess of shit like I hated it. I think almost intentionally because it was about the excess
Look, I appreciate it aspects of it
But I think I've said this before possibly on this podcast. I don't need a five -minute improv scene
Where I'm supposed to believe that these economic geniuses are too stupid to understand you're not allowed to throw
Little people it's stupid like I'm not saying they didn't have the dwarf throwing contest
So I'm saying like having Jonah Hill sit there like I just can't look him in the eye because they get angry
It's like really come on. I don't need this shit like give me the fucking move. I want to see
I had forgotten about the minute tossing. I'll agree with you on that
But I would have only shaved maybe 20 minutes off a wolf wall straight
And I still would have wanted to see those deleted scene. I saw that three times in the theater. I'll watch it again
I loved it. My point is the big short was a movie very clearly modeled after Wolf of Wall Street
You know that in the pitch it was like this is Wolf of Wall Street about the housing market
Right, so I really hate when I see a review like that where they're like this is what you know come on all right
Anyway, my point is
Steve Carell
Is playing a role in this movie that he's not right for now. I heard he was great at it and well
Yeah, people rave and they encourage them and they keep doing it. I don't think he's right for the part
I don't think anyone was really right for their part by the end. I started to like Steve Carell
I don't you think he was right for the part
He just
When I can't even really put my finger on it from the second I saw him. He's wearing like a bad to pay
I'm like you can't have Steve Carell in a bad to pay playing a serious role, right? You can't do that
Because you're just gonna it's gonna you're gonna think it's supposed to be funny right so for like 90 minutes of this two -hour movie
I'm just kind of like it's like a sketch with no jokes, and it's not supposed to be it's a drama
Right, and then at the end I kind of started buying his character a little more. I thought Gosling was pretty good in it
It was a solid movie. I liked it, but it's like Will Ferrell doing these indie movies
that he'll do and
what it boils down to is
is we're not going to get these great comedic movies
that these people should be making with their prime years.
Who might have told these people what to do?
But like Jim Carey started doing it immediately.
Like I said, it's been sure I was like,
this is the craziest thing I've ever seen.
This guy is doing things I have never seen before.
And within about three years time,
he's doing movies trying to get an Oscar.
He's one of the majestic.
The problem is it always starts good and then tapers off.
because nobody would argue that Jim Carrey wasn't brilliant in man on the moon.
Nobody would ever say Steve Correll wasn't brilliant in Fox Catcher.
Of course, nobody would get it right.
Right, but I'm saying like it's to me, it's like when they keep doing it.
I think Will Farrell does a good balance of it, like where he'll do like a couple
ridiculous movies and then he'll do an indie thing and I'm like, all right,
I think I once said, you know, you got to cleanse yourself and do the stuff you
want to do too. Yeah. Um, it's also too. And he's never bad in those movies. It's just those
movies are never that well done. Like they're just never great movies. Yeah. But I liked him a lot
in that movie where he played like the angry guy that was selling all this shit that had to like
live on his lawn or something. They must go. Um, it was all right. I mean, but the movie itself wasn't great
but he was good in it. He's fine. I just find myself wishing he'd be funny. And by the way,
I wish you'd be funnier in the comedies.
I go see them in these days too.
All it really is, is what we're talking about
with Crystal Skull.
You want these movies to be better than they are
and they're not and it makes you sad.
And you look for reasons.
You go see get hard and it's like,
oh yeah.
I mean, again, these are, that's just a bad movie.
Yeah.
But that's like, I was really bummed at that new,
that one with him in Wahlberg that's coming out.
Would you have dads or something?
Or stepdad or something?
Dad in any case or daddy's home. I'll see I was I was look great
It doesn't and and I think the other guys is one of the funniest films ever committed to celluloid
I could not
So agree more you're out of your fucking mind. I was so excited to see that
That was when he was still in the pocket. You're out of your fucking mind. I think it was funny at all
I'd argue that it might be the funniest will Farrow movie
Well, yeah, I'll walk out of this podcast. You I'll never do it again. I don't even understand how you couldn't think it was
Keaton
Farrell
Well, everybody hits Cougan. It's like it's like home runs across the world. You're talking about except from Walberg
You're talking about some of my favorite comedic people. Keaton. Farrell Cougan. I didn't think anything was funny
I'll watch it again. I'll try it again. I
Didn't think anything was funny. You didn't think it was funny when Michael Keaton is addressing the staff at bedbeth and beyond
and says there's a rapist on the loose and then he goes I'm sorry wrong job you
don't I don't remember that I'll watch it again all right incessantly
quoting TLC was the movie the desktop thing I look I'll watch it Rob
Riggle Sam Jackson I see narrating the film I mean it's a masterpiece all right we
We should watch it again to the two of us.
That sounds good.
I can't win.
I just remember being like, man, I've been 15 minutes without a laugh here.
That might have been a case where my expectations were just too high.
I was laughing hysterically almost from the beginning of the film.
I think my problem is, because I realized as I was talking, I'm a little anger about this
and I even realized.
But like Anchorman and stepbrothers, I've never laughed harder, and it's almost like
when you take a drug and then you're chasing that high again. So when I go see a
get harder or whatever else, it's not just like, yeah, that movie sucked. I'm
chasing those laughs that like blew my mind apart. Like stepbrothers, I was drunk.
I saw it like a midnight show, me and my buddy were like scream laughing.
Yeah, stepbrothers is hilarious.
You know what's funny is I didn't think it was going to be funny when I saw the trailers.
Yeah.
I was like, can this looks okay.
And then when I saw it, I was just like, oh my god.
It's honestly just madness.
Yeah.
I mean, the scene still will Ferrell's reaction when Marystein virgins like,
you guys need to get jobs.
when he just starts screaming, this is fucking bullshit.
I mean, it's such unbridled rage.
Richard Jenkins, who I love.
Richard Jenkins should have nominated,
speaking to these worthless awards for Bon Tomahawk,
which is a great disturbing horror movie
that we should do for this podcast, maybe.
So Western horror with Kurt Russell,
and it has unquestionably the most disturbing death
I think I've ever seen on film.
I can't believe Quinterantino didn't produce that movie.
I know.
I so look I I knew what Bontamok was I didn't know I didn't know this death scene was coming
When this happens and like you know that you know the guy's gonna die here, but you just don't know what's going on
I'm sitting there watching it kind of head -and -hand like I'm enjoying myself
This this was one of the most unsettling things I've ever seen in my life and I immediately like search the internet
And there's like 8 million tweets of people like holy fuck just got to this scene in Bontamok
Like it's it messes people up. It's really it's really hard to watch this one scene. Now is it because of what you see or what's implied. It's I mean, you see it. You definitely see it really. And then Pat
Nozwell was tweet. He like did a live tweet of the whole movie and he said he looked away and he's like, he wished he had and because what he was hearing was worse because the sounds are pretty graphic.
It's just really this is really it's intense. They sent it all forward to see it because they sent it as a for your consideration screener. I'm just thinking as a person who's seen so many horror movies. I'm wondering how bad the death could be. I mean it's bad. Maybe now that it's been built up. It won't be. That's what happens. I'd like to see it.
Um, back to the movie, uh, stepbrothers, we're just guys still, I always try to go back to black
Christmas for a minute, uh, we're down to about one girl at this point, uh, is left.
I don't know if you've been watching, Pat, the cinematography in this film, but I mean,
the shots, the artistic shots and the editing, it's, it's, it, it, it, it truly is a film.
It's hard to believe that the guy that did this made baby geniuses.
it is not hard to believe the guy that made this made a Christmas story yeah the movies people make
when they're young and hungry are usually a lot more care in them than me well you know I don't
think it's just that I think it's also that when you're a young filmmaker you're probably working for
more independent venues and you're allowed to be a little more expressive and then you get into
that mainstream studio system and they say by the book by the book and then eventually your spirit's
broken and you just start to crank them out by numbers you know that is part of what
happens with a lot of the actors of like what we were talking about like it's not just
that they it's not just that they get an urge to do a certain type of film or whatever.
It's also like you probably they probably just get to a point where they're like I'm tired
of fighting the battles like yeah what's the easy thing to do you know yeah I don't
I look like every other man that being said. I don't think there was one movie
Drama that Bill Murray was ever in that he wasn't good in. Oh
Of course not of course not, but it's like did a ton of them. That's all yeah
It's like that first time they dipped their toe in the water like he had made a few dramatic things before but like lost in translation
When saw that and I was like boy. That's what a perfect use of him. That's somebody who wrote that movie for him
If it's like a part that was gonna be played by
Christian bail and then
and Paulie Shore takes over, that's not gonna work.
Sure.
Yeah.
Well, that's something that happens every day in this town.
Well, I said, I mean, Christian Bell and Steve Correll
were in this thing.
And I know these people are talented actors.
And Correll, like Correll to me,
gave a better dramatic performance
in 40 -year -old Virgin and a comedic performance.
He did it all in that fucking movie.
And the office, he was an amazing dramatic
and comedic performer.
But I think it's gotta be a character.
Like Foxcatcher was definitely a character if it's just them playing in every man
You're just kind of annoyed that they're not being funny. I look forward to watching the big short
I have the screener in the other room and I'm gonna watch it
But because I I heard quite the contrary from a friend of ours
She said that he was oh brilliant our good friend Karen Kulgera. She said he was brilliant saying Steve Karel high praises
Who that was that was the that was the name she mentioned? I said I didn't watch the big short yet. She goes oh my god
you have to. Steve Carell is amazing in it. And then she said, I just wish I hadn't watched it
alone, because she said it was kind of depressing. It was. Like watching this thing about like
the crash of the housing market. I love Karen. She's maybe making me a reconsider. But I will, for me,
I see him walk on the screen in a two pay. I'm like, start making me laugh. Right. Now are you buying
Andrea Martin in this movie? Yes. By the end of the big short I had come around to his character,
For sure this is a very big dramatic part for Andrea Martin nothing funny in this thing. She's not doing it
I'm not doing a Greek accent or anything like that
Are you excited for my big fat Greek wedding, too?
I wouldn't say excited, but I like I guess everyone else in the world thought the first one was pretty cute kind of funny
Right, I love that scene when he's
The phone
He's talking on the phone and it yanks back and he falls over that you made me laugh
She does that she does that. Yeah, she's on the headset. She runs and falls back. That was funny Kevin Smith
I love clerks too, but it's an almost exact mimic. Oh, yeah, and I don't know if it's supposed to be a nod or if you just didn't realize
They did this in my big fat Greek wedding. I
liked it. I'm really excited for clerks three. I need to see Jason Mew's back in action. Again, I wouldn't say really excited
But I found clerks too to be like a real nice surprise. I really like clerks too
The bonus footage on clerk of clerks too is stuff that I'm like, why did they cut this out of the yeah
Why did they cut this out of the movie again? That's a two -hour comedy you can't have no, but they had like alt scenes. Yeah
There's a whole thing like in the beginning with J and sell Bob where Jay starts doing
The shining
And he's going red rum with his finger and he goes look at that silent Bob. I'm your little friend that lives in your mouth
And then he holds his fist up and says I bet you love me to live in your mouth
It was a lot like the first one where he's like tell a silent Bob
He's gonna suck his dick and then he calls him a queer immediately. It's just funny
Yeah, it's a crazy way to behave with another man
Yeah, I and I believe that those characters are gay deep down. Oh, sir. Do you believe that? Sure
Where is Clark's three? What is the deal? What is it about?
Kevin Smith is referred to it as the Empire of
The clerk's franchise
Apparently, it's pretty epic apparently. It's pretty dark
And it's supposed to get made a mirror max passed on it or I don't know if mirror max or Weinstein company
but it was passed on and so then it you know fuck them which I don't get here's what I don't get
he's making he was as much a part of making that studio as anybody right fuck them for doing that
and he's he's making it but what I don't get is he somehow got funding for the for the the the
the tusk trilogy and mall rats too they're not doing a tusk trilogy are they they're doing two more
movies with the Johnny Depp character. I'm excited. That can't be true. It's
absolutely true. They just finished shooting the one. But everyone hated the
Johnny Depp character. Apparently not. I love the Johnny Depp character. That's
madness. Here's my he doesn't care anymore. Here's my point is they're doing three
movies in that series and then he's doing he more rats too is like shooting
already. Is that all the same character still hanging out there? They're all coming
back. It's called mall brats. I think it's going to be about them bringing their kids to the mall.
My the aflac. I wouldn't be surprised. I think mall rats is pretty fun. I love mall rats,
but it's called mall brats. My my theory is it's going to be the characters from the original
bringing their kids to the mall and they're being some kind of conflict with shitty mall kids. But
Jay and Silent Bob of course will still just be hanging out at the mall. But how did that get funding
before clerks three. Well, I guess they have a they can point to clerks two not doing
very well, but they can also point to malrads not doing very well in his prime. No, just
follow up. I don't know. I just made this crazy mixed up world we live in. I'm now scared
that I quoted the joke where Jay says queer in the in in. I was called a talk show. You're
in clerks couldn't remember the name clerks thought it was called talk show for a second now a quick
Little subject going back to stepos for one second Tom Sharplin who I love and listen to his podcast every week three hours
The best show. I don't know why I keep promoting it on here
but he was talking about scenes and movies that make him and only him cry and
It was a kind of interesting conversation topic, but he said when Peewee who is deathly afraid of snakes goes back into the pet shop
He saves all the animals and then he goes back kind of the patch up to say the snakes and runs out holding them screaming
It makes him like break down and sob every time
That was kind of fascinating and then he said at the end of stepbrothers when Will Ferrell is singing that song
Said he sobs every time and like his wife came in and caught him sobbing and it's an odd thing to sob at
I mean it's supposed to be a beautiful song
Yeah, but it's supposed to be a certain there is a lot of like kind of sadness and anger undercurrent and stepbrothers
And that maybe that's bringing it out of him
But I was like those are really weird choices and I was trying to think if I had any like that
You know what part makes me a little a little misty
In old school
Okay, in old school after the funeral when his wife says she wants the divorce and will Farrow goes
I used to argue with people about that where they would be like that's hilarious and I was like that's not supposed to be funny. Yeah, that's supposed to be a guy that like doesn't know how to express himself. Yes, quoting of cheesy song like he doesn't know what to say. Yeah, when those movies, which I think especially that McKay ones and the early.
Todd Armstrong ones. Scott Armstrong, sorry. When they...
No, Jesus Christ. What am I trying to say? Scott Armstrong wrote,
co -wrote them, old school and hangover on that shit. Todd Phillips, Jesus Christ.
Who are you always mix up with Todd Salons? Don't make that mistake at the video store.
They all have a, I think, a very smart dark
undercurrent to them, kind of treating these characters not as heroes, but as kind of pathetic.
Well, there's the great deleted scene. I completely agree with it. There's the great deleted
scene from old school, which is very edgy. And I'm surprised that, I mean, I think it's probably not
in the movie for that reason. But there's the scene where it's on the bonus features where Luke Wilson
goes to Vince Vaughan's store and he's in a panic because he's fucked his boss's daughter.
And he's like, she's in high school. I could go to jail and Vince Vaughan says,
for what being awesome. It's a really edgy joke. And that's dark.
I thought that was in the movie. Now, there's a, there's a, there's a similar joke in
the breakup, I think, where Vince Vaughn's younger brother in that is like the real
coxman guy. He's like the real pussy hammer. Right. Right. And he goes, you're gonna get
arrested. And the guy goes arrested for weapon, being awesome. I think that's in the
breakup. I'm pretty sure he has moved it over. I would say although Royal Ten of
is a movie with a lot of darkness and frown and sadness in it, but I kind of
embarrassed myself crying at Royal Tenamons in high school and Ben Stiller just
says one quick line like the suicide attempt nothing made me cry in the entire
movie and then at the end Hacman goes over to Ben Stiller and he's like it's been
a rough year dad. Yeah tosses it away. Yeah no that's brutal. His wife's dead and
everything I was bawling at them. Well it's the first time if I remember
correctly that the stiller character and the Hackman character show vulnerability yeah and it's
like the you know the understatement of the years it's been a rough year yeah it's yeah it's it's
it's uh that's not yeah it's it's brutal it's brutal uh what gets me is always in grumpy old men
after jack lemon has the heart attack and uh uh uh Walter Matthew finds him gets in the hospital
and goes in to see him and they say family or friend and he doesn't know how to answer it yeah and he
starts crying and he says friend yeah very very sad yeah watch that movie my folks had to get up and
pretend to blow my nose I got a wispy right now just saying it I've been the guy almost choked me up
yeah if you sprinkle those moments into a comedy sometimes they even hit harder like what will never
make me cry is when you're just big and me to cry. And the violins are playing and
everybody's acting their asses off that will never make me cry. It's always got to be
like a small little toss. I'll tell you a final scene and something that'll get you
right in the gut is that Danny Collins movie. I'm excited to watch it. Final scene if that
doesn't get you, you're not a human being as far as I'm concerned. All right. I'm excited
To say it we as we've discussed about playing strains and automobiles private. Sure. Sure. You're not a human if you don't cry that I also can't
Cry in a movie unless I like truly and deeply love the character and
That's very hard for me in a movie. I often am like I don't give a shit about these people in their pathetic problems
Now have you ever cried at a horror movie?
At a horror movie, I would
Oh
No, I don't think for any reason any emotion. I don't think so. I
Mean, uh, no
Polter guys when she's really excited when she feels her daughter go through her that may be the closest. Yeah, I've come to when she like
No, she's still locked she rushes through her body. Oh, yeah, that part. That's pretty emotional. Yeah, but no, have you?
Not that I can think of
Now, it's been mostly dramas, a couple of comedies here and there, you know, I think I've
mentioned it before.
The end of the untouchables always gets me when Sean Connery dies, yeah, that's a brutal
scene.
But it's worth the brutalness of that scene for the awesomeness of the scene when Kevin
Costner throws Frank Nitty off the roof.
And he goes, did he sound anything like that?
Yeah, probably. I just got chills. It's a great, it's a great scene. My friend once
said, the touchable is the only movie to ever make Kevin Costner look like a bad ass.
Yeah, we definitely have discussions on it.
On here or just in life?
Pat, I got to tell you, I need to close my eyes for a few minutes here. It's 1 p .m. I didn't
sleep very well last night. Well, we only have 15 minutes to go. How do you know
it's 15 minutes? I have checked the running time when I got up when you
scold me for not moving fast enough. Maybe I go get a drink now.
I'll go ahead and you take the home. I mean, Pat goes in. Folks, for those of you
at home that can't see us right now, Pat is two brusquies and a tootsie roll pop
deep. It's part, baby. It's the holiday season. Now, you work tomorrow.
tomorrow. Tomorrow is my last day and then I'm off for like three weeks, three weeks. I've
been off on script all week, relaxing, getting there done. You go in tomorrow, you shoot, you're
not shooting your script tomorrow. No, different script. Then a little holiday party at work. And then
I am done for three weeks. Yeah. Going to Missouri, going to Vegas with the lady for New
years. I saw our good friend Ian. Yeah. And I said, what do you do for New years? You said
dinner thing. He said, what's Walsh doing? I said, he's going to fucking Vegas. Yeah. I said, I
can't. I've done broken up about that. I wish I could see the guy. He said, why don't you go to
Vegas? I said, it's him and the lady. I don't not go on to Vegas. If you bring a date, you can come,
but you can't tag along. Does my friend Jesse pop count as a date? Jesse pop is probably the least
date like of any of your friends. I love just. Well, our buddies, Jesse Vincent, Georgia are going to
Vegas for Christmas. Yeah, which is a ballsy move. I really respect that. I love it. I don't know if it'll be dead or crowded, but it'll definitely be fun.
Vince has me excited. I wasn't supposed to be back till after New Year's, but I'm now coming back on the 27th. Vince has me very excited about how easy it is to drive around the city.
The week of Christmas. He said you can get to the west side in 20 minutes flat down right down at the beach. You're coming back early to enjoy the drive.
No, I'm just coming back early now because I'm moving, but I'm excited that a perk
of coming back early will be no traffic, you know, going to get some nice amoeba records
runs in that week, some Christmas deals.
No, I'm going to get Christmas movies for Christmas.
Why do I need to buy things?
I'm really part of this consumer culture.
I get really annoyed now when I go home.
I'm just kind of at this age.
I never thought about it with my aunts and uncles, but you get to this age.
I'm 34. I am just not given any gifts by anyone. They're all like you're okay. You know, the older people are like he doesn't need a gift. He's 34 years old. Sure. The kids don't have any money to buy me gifts. Sure. I get gifts from my girlfriend. And that's essentially it. We do an exchange at work. Parents don't give you gifts. Parents tend to go like cash or you know, like me like a photo album or something. But last year I go home and maybe it was two years ago.
So my dad's remarried. So Christmas Eve, I got to go over and spend Christmas Eve with my dad, his wife, and all of her children and their family. So it's no one I know at all.
And like, she's technically my stepmom and they're technically my stepbrothers and sisters, I guess. But I'm never there. And I have hung out with them like twice in my life. So they're essentially strangers. And I spend Christmas Eve just like sitting with people I don't know. Nice people.
Showered you with gifts nice people funny people just where that's going no believe it or not it's not
So I'm coming home. They're like we're gonna meet our our prodigal son here
And I come home and they do this giant gift exchange. I bet there's 800 packages in the middle of this floor
And that they go around if somebody's playing Santa handing out the gifts and I don't receive a single gift
From anyone and I'm like all right. I guess you just kind of got to accept that, you know
So what your mom bought presents for the stepkids, but not for you my mom's not not there. You're dead
My dad had presents for them. I he had probably, you know, sent me a check of her $100 like in a Christmas card
So I'm sitting there and I'm not getting any gifts, but I'm like that's all right. It's fine and
Then out comes a wagon full of gifts for the dogs
wagon of gifts
For the dogs
I was like well
Okay, I guess I see where I stand. Oh, it's fine. I truly would not have complained
I would have been like oh, it's kind of a bummer that everyone's gonna unwrap gifts for an hour and a half
And I won't have one until I saw the dogs the hole for the dogs
I almost asked if I could open one for the dogs just to kind of have the little thrill
Jesus Christ at the end of the night. I was six egg nox deep fighting one of the golden retrievers for a bum
now do you get drunk on a night like that or do you keep it clean? I can't I'm
not really allowed to with my dad is is a little weird about drinking he just
told me he celebrated 30 years sober this weekend congratulations I'm sure he's
not listening to it but you know I don't the past few years my sister and I will
definitely go to a bar down the street and slam a cup before we head in I can't
believe just before you head in and you don't go back to the bar later.
Now, I mean, look, I could, I could pocket a whiskey or something in my pocket.
It's just kind of like, you don't want to go up and like hug your new stepmom
who you see once a year and your breath wreaks of whiskey or something.
No, I'm saying you, you slam a few before you go in.
Yeah, do your time.
And then you go back to the bar with your sister at the end.
Oh, yeah, close up the night.
We just want to get home and get it over.
I'll see if the drive everywhere and snow and ice
Now we everyone gets real drunk on Christmas day my mom's side of the family are big drinkers. That's great
I never drink with my family. I never feel right doing it. I tell you I'm glad my dad sobered up
But I wish if he's still drunk the the stuff we could get off our chest me and my mom never had any problems really at all
But now when we connect over like a couple of beers or whatever, I find out some things about my childhood
Blow my mind. I'm like holy shit. Why did you never tell me this now? Did you now? Do you do your mom? Does your mom give you presents?
My mom too is always like
You know if they give me something big I have to carry it back on my suitcase
So she's like, you know, I hate to just give you cash
But is that okay? And then they'll give me something nice usually like a little my mom and her husband
I don't get me a little something to unwrap.
Can table my mommy and daddy do?
Yeah.
Go to my Amazon wish list.
Oh.
Just run right down that thing.
That's nice.
And then they ship it all to me after.
They let me open it on Christmas day,
and then they ship it all to me.
Well, do you have the Amazon wish list just as a Christmas list?
I just make a wish list through the year for things
I want that I eventually buy or don't buy.
Right.
Come Christmas time.
They say, peep the wish list.
That's not a bad idea. My mom's going as far as me is to say give me more stuff. Right. There's not enough on here. That's that's great. Sorry, buddy.
No, it's it's all right. I mostly look forward to seeing my friends, but like I don't I've never had the kind of friends that
necessarily give Christmas gifts. You know, I for me, the gift is you don't have to go buy a gift.
You know, like who wants to run around buying more shit on this?
Well, I'm thankful. I don't have to do that for everybody in my life.
But I exchange gifts with my friend Jim, who you've met.
Yeah. And then we do, then he and I and three of our other friends have, have a big,
the night before Christmas Eve of a big party night together, right?
So on that night, we do a, you like a polyanna thing where you get one, not a polyanna,
but you buy for one person, right?
Like a white elephant or just it's just like you get every, you know, this year I have
this guy and he has this guy and, you know, whatever.
So we, so those are, that's two people and then I exchange with my manager, that's three
And then I do my parents. It's my niece and my nephew. It's not crazy. It's just enough. I have some friends. I do
um
our work
Secret Santax change when I first started this job our boss their our bosses were multi millionaires
They'd be like, so yeah, everyone just get a gift. That's like, uh, what do you want to say 500 bucks? Oh my god, and we did that
the lowest person the person who on the lowest person on the on the ladder the staff writer on the show as
As well as the showrunner. Everyone's gift was $500
$500. Yeah
It's crazy. This year it's 250. It's gone way down
But like and then the idea is like okay, if we're all doing this you all better bring in some good fucking gifts
Because I wanted to be like I spent $500 on myself and for the most part everybody brought in some really awesome shit
And we did this thing where you could trade your
You know you swap the gift if you want somebody else doesn't celebrate them
Well, what, like, what was, what were the gifts?
Um, my gift, which was kind of considered the highlight that year was I had a full bar.
All every single kind of alcohol you could ever imagine, um, bottle of Dom Paranjan and
there for New Year's Eve, a couple of weed candies in the mix, just like a, a, it was
a, a bar and I wound up getting it myself.
I eventually was like, I like my gift better than anyone else and I stole it back and I had
a beautiful bar that last to me the entire year. Wow, that's a good gift. Another year
I got the top five books of the year, the top five albums of the year, the top five
DVDs of the year, you know. Right. I like to have a nice little theme. This year I have
roughly 24 hours to buy a gift and I don't have anything yet, so I need to get on it.
You know what I would do? What? If it was still the $500 one, PS4, a couple of games.
people yeah people brought game systems in stuff like that that's just never I
Know I don't need another thing sucking my time or else I would have definitely taken that
Well, what about another thing sucking your dick? I could always use that
If not talked about this movie one bit and it's proud
We're talking about Christmas and that's fun
Arguably one of the best movies we've done on the podcast and we haven't watched it
I just missed who the killer is I'm gonna bring it home and watch it
I think the killer's the guy that bashes piano earlier. I don't remember the movie that well. I only saw it once. I'm gonna watch them
What can you think of the $250 that I should buy for this exchange?
Well, let me think for a second to 50
I'd go get that new Nintendo 3DS that just came out
Well, it's just it's a adult heavy staff, you know, yeah, but I mean they have kids
It's it's the new 3DS. It's the it's the best one they've released. So if I go get that in some some fun games
Where how much is the system to honey? I think the system itself is like a buck 70. Oh wow
And then you can you stack if two three games on top of that you got a nice two fifty dollar little gift basket there
Maybe I'll do that. So I would do that. I would do I
Would go to amoeba do like some like classic box sets
That's as I sit here looking at the velvet underground box that I have, you know some stuff that contains rarities. Maybe that Beatles album box set that you have. Yeah, that's pretty awesome. It's pretty awesome.
It's just you can't know what like the it's a very wide ranging and diverse group with different interests. It's hard to pick. That's why you can swap things. That's true.
Look, I'll tell you this. I'm not a Beatles. I'm probably the least Beatles fan in the world
If I got that box that I'd be pretty fucking happy about it. I tell you it makes those songs
You've heard a billion times sound like completely new things, you know, that's really awesome
I don't know one Beatles album. I don't give a shit about I've sergeant peppers on vinyl by like accident, right?
So my point is is like that's that's a cool fucking gift no matter what yeah, so
How much was it? It was three
I've been on to go a little over I bet you can get that at a me but for just under three.
One year this is how it can go wrong.
The gifts that were flying around were like the other bar thing and the game systems all
kinds of different ship and Morgan Murphy my coworker who you know as well.
She brought in as her gift and she was so excited about it and I get it but she brought
in a $500 giant antique map of the world that would cover easily the an
unentire wall of someone's home okay and everyone that God I was just like
are you fucking kidding me? People were so angry with her. That's what would you do
with that? That's all I know what I'm saying. What are we gonna do with this
market? Like people were so angry with her and she was so hurt and I get it. She
thought I've got this really cool gift and they just shut her down you can't
it's too much real estate you can't you can't give somebody something that has
to cover the entire wall I agree that's insane I agree sorry Morgan I love
you but that's not a it's a bad gift choice and then we were like was in the
right place you take it and she's like I would love to have that and everybody's
like please take it did she take it no she didn't take it now who got stuck
didn't want it I don't even remember
I guess the killer is still at large, it's gonna be the killer is still alive even though you think everything's okay.
So I wish you could have seen my Christmas tree this year, it looks beautiful.
Got it all set up.
I didn't even set up a tree this year because I'm leaving so early.
I leave tomorrow.
I'll also be dead when we come back, probably.
Yeah.
House burned to the ground tremendous fire hazard.
I'm trying to think of another good.
I had one more idea for you for your polyanna and I forget what it is or I've never heard it called a polyanna and all my all my life
Secret Santa whenever the fuck you want to call it well secret Santa makes sense. Pollyanna does not
Well, Pollyanna is
The thing where you put it that what you're doing is a polyanna everybody buys a gift and then you get a gift and you pick
Numbers or whatever right and then you get a gift and you can change it for the next number if you don't like it or you know
that's that's Paulianna okay you know sorry to break it to you do you think
the killers in the attic with this 45 -second stagnant shot on the attic leave
how long they're staying on the shot it's uh so what's happening well I mean I
remember it being pretty cool but you know we paid such a little goddamn attention
the killer so I it's me Billy hey I'll watch tonight and then I'll give you
guys my cell number and we can talk about the movie afterwards I'm in
bearish to have a little discuss the film I think especially from kind of
interact with people online I don't know that they care neither do I which is
but folks again because I asked last week too if you're annoyed that we're not
doing these along with like a movie on Netflix or whatever let us know like if
you watch along with us and that was fun for you let us know but no one has come
forward and said they're doing that. I think people just kind of treat it like a regular podcast.
Yeah, certainly all my friends that listen to it do it that way.
People said we could announce, somebody said we could announce what movie we're going to do next.
That's a good idea. So that way the person can go buy the DVD if they want.
Yeah, we don't know right now unfortunately but that is a good idea.
Maybe that's a thing we'll start in the new year.
I like it. You know, I like it.
It's about to be 2016, Pat.
It's the credits role here.
It's the credits role on 2015.
I'm seeing you on KL.
You're the one.
We thank you for joining us for another episode of We'll
See You In Hell.
Podcast is always brought to you by the Fangoria podcast
network, it's produced by Thomas DeFaio.
So executive produced by Ken Hanley, a Fingoria entertainment for press opportunities
advertising, inquiries and information about, we'll see you in hell, contact Ken at Fingoria .com.
This will probably drop, I'm not assuming pretty close Christmas week.
So if you're a Christmas celebrator, Merry Christmas and if you're not happy holidays, happy
Monica happy whatever it may be I am at the Patrick Walsh Twitter by
Instagram Joe is at Joe DeRosa Comedy and I just I hope you all have a great
holiday. Have a great holiday and if you're in California I'll be touring the
northern cities San Fran and whatnot in January so keep an eye out for that we'll
See you next time.