I'll see you in hell.
Folks, it's We'll see you in hell.
Oh, Joe DeRose of Patrick Laws here today to talk about a little picture called barbarian.
We said we were going to do smile, but that will be the next episode.
We're going to do barbarian instead today.
Yes, because barbarian drops today on HBO Max.
So if you didn't venture out the theaters and catch it, you can catch it now or or ranted
or whatever you need to do.
If you don't support HBO Max, maybe you had a lot of excitement about Batgirl.
And when they pulled the plug, you pulled their plug.
I understand.
You people love your stupid cartoon shit.
I realize, you know, we're going to get to barbarian here.
What the hell does the title mean?
Nothing.
I mean, am I crazy?
Well, the only thing I got from it was, it's on a street is called Barbary Way or whatever.
That's true.
I was like, so that's a play on the street name.
Paul Z moved though to name the whole movie after that, but you know, it says a member, a
barbarian is a member of a community or tribe not belonging to one of the great civilizations
i .e.
Greek, Roman, Christian or relating to ancient barbarians.
So to me, neither of those things applies to this movie at all.
I think, or excuse me, barbaric is an act that is either brutal or cruel to the point
of savagery.
And you got that here, you got that here for sure.
Yeah, you know, obviously, I was like, this is a, you know, the title is because it's sort
of, well, it's about a bunch of savages, actually, number one.
But so I got that part.
And then the street name, my buddy saw this movie.
And I thought he put it best.
He goes, I don't understand what the fuck the point of the movie was, but I loved it.
And I was like, yeah, it's kind of how I felt like it's just, it's a nutty, it's nuts.
The movie is nutty.
I don't always need a point for my movies.
I don't often need a point for my movies.
So I enjoyed it.
We'll get there.
What's happening in your life, Joseph?
Well, I told you a bunch of stuff off there that I don't know where I'm talking about on
air.
Thank you very much.
John lost his dick, everybody.
Just woke up one day and it was gone.
I'm looking to move apartments.
I'd like to get a bigger apartment.
Okay.
I am on street easy right now.
So I get notifications from them.
You might like this one.
The one they sent me just before we started recording is located directly next to Bellevue.
Bellevue mental hospital, which I didn't know this.
Did you know Bellevue is not just a mental hospital?
I thought so.
I always thought too.
Is it a wing?
Yeah.
I guess they had a famous like, like not loony band over at Bellevue.
I mean, the only time I hear it is like Uncle Junior or something being like, what do
you do?
I mean, she should be up in Bellevue.
Yeah.
Where's it?
I've ever heard of it.
I assumed it was like Arkham Asylum.
That's how I always heard of it.
It would be like a punchline on Maude, you know, but yeah, I think it's like just a normal,
but it's, it is a, it's, it's hands down.
And I'm going to go, I'm going to say this.
What are you drinking there, by the way?
Kombucha.
Looks like a whiskey.
Oh, Christ, do I wish it has gumbooch.
It's the hands down.
And I say this without knowing even a tenth of the names of hospitals around the world.
It's the funniest hospital name of all time.
Bellevue?
It just, it just has that ring to it.
It's just, it's just funny.
It's a good punchline name like it just is.
I love, you know, like Lakeview conjures up a, you're, you're looking at a beautiful
lake.
Bellevue, you have a view of a bell.
Is that what it is?
Lakeview is also very funny to me because I picture a man at a straight jacket being forced
to look at a serene lake that he can't like partake in it anyway.
That was another, these home invasion movies are always impossible to name.
I'm thinking of Lakeview Terrace with Samuel L. Jackson is another one.
You know, just a bad name.
It doesn't conjure up any sort of evil or scares or anything.
I think in that movie, he was a black cop, obviously a black cop, but he was, he was harassing
white tenants.
It was very strange like he's mad that I believe it's, he's mad that Patrick Wilson is dating
a beautiful black woman.
Oh, I agree.
I think it's that, I think that's the racial angle of it.
I definitely saw it, but I don't remember anything about it.
By the way, isn't that James?
What's his face?
James.
That's a plan, doesn't it?
No, that's not mangold, that's not mangold.
The guy that did Lakeview Terrace, it's something else very interesting.
That was actually weirdly directed by Neil Le Butte of the book.
That's who it is.
Yeah.
What else did Neil Le Butte do though?
Well, Neil Le Butte did in the company, a man, your friends and neighbors.
Yeah, it made, that made no sense to me.
I guess this was like, hey, I'm going to go for a Hollywooder.
Yes.
And newly, what, and he's done a few of those, none of them really work.
Yeah, that is what it is.
A widowed and longtime LAPD officer, he makes comments about his smoking, his listening
to hip -hop music and his race in relation to his wife, Lisa.
All right.
Neil Le Butte.
Yeah, the man that has made the sickest movies ever made has also made the maker of in the
company of men, your friends and neighbors and the shape of things.
Three of the most disturbing movies I've ever seen in my life.
For sure.
That are not horror in any way related.
Yeah.
He also directed the wicker man, the cage one, yeah.
Lakeview Terrace, the death at a funeral remake insane.
It's insane like he got all those jobs like what he does well is three character intense dramas
about interpersonal dilemmas.
He shouldn't be making the wicker man.
His newest picture is called House of Darkness.
It's an American comedy reimagining of Dracula starring Justin Long and Kate Bosworth.
What the hell, what the hell, how many reimaginations of Dracula we're going to do here by the way, thousands?
I mean, there's been thousands, it's enough with the Dracula, especially if it's just
and long.
And as we'll talk about him, Barbarian, I like Justin Long.
Well, not as Dracula, not as Dracula.
I feel like Bosworth might be the Dracula in this.
I think that's where the maybe the reimagining comes in, yeah, but you look copulas, did the
be all end all Dracula.
That's it.
Yeah.
In terms of modern versions of it, yeah, there were great versions in the thirties and there
was one definitive version of modern times and I think we're good.
It's, it's the Legosi.
It's the first Christopher Lee and it's the Coppola.
That's it.
That should be a box set.
That should be a Dracula trilogy.
You don't throw in a Herzog Nosferratto.
Oh, it's funny.
Yeah, I would add that and the original Nosferratto.
So you got to if that is a, that would be a killer box set, speaking of box sets, speaking
of box sets, the other day, I'm on Amazon.
They, they're doing, you know, it was some sort of prime day sale or something and I see
4K, giant box set, everything you could ever want the evil dead.
I put it in my cart, I'm getting ready to order it and I go, you know what, why don't I just
look and see what's in it just to be sure.
I must fall for this one too.
Doesn't have army of darkness.
It's a trilogy.
You're missing one of them then you don't do the box set.
That's how it works.
The box is the first two and then all of the series, all of the series.
I was just like, which makes sense if you didn't see army of darkness and you're calling
it like the complete evil that, no, it isn't.
There's three movies.
You don't have one of them.
You're not complete.
That's shit, that's shit where it's like a definitive collection.
You see a giant box, you get all excited, yeah, then you realize it's in a giant box because
there's like a neco action figure in it or so, you know what I mean?
And you're like, oh, fuck off.
Who cares?
I want action figures.
I'll go look at them.
This is like I'm buying this for a movie, man.
Give me a neco wafer, give me something I can at least enjoy.
This tar, this tar picture, oh, it was funny, I was talking to my niece the other day.
She's very excited to see tar and I know nothing about it except that it's a lady me too.
That's all I know.
And it's two and a half.
Oh, so she gets me to, she gets me to, yeah, all right.
And she's supposed to be amazing in it.
I'm excited to see it.
Uh, what's it called?
Oh, my niece.
Wait a minute.
If you don't have a brother or sister, how do you have a niece?
Well, my cousin Danielle is more or less like a sister and her kids call me uncle.
All right.
Fine.
So my niece.
She, I don't subscribe to labels also.
No, my niece, she's turning into a budding young lady.
It's very fun to watch.
I guess she's like 13 now, Jesus.
Well, it's wild.
Anyway, I called her on her birthday and I was like, what did you go do?
And she's like, I went to the movies with my friends.
It was very fun.
And about, you know, mm hmm.
I was like, what would you see?
She was like, wild, wild crocodile.
It was so cute.
I had to be like, that's great.
That movie looks great.
Even though, you know, I want to be like, what are you?
And any of it.
Yeah.
Nothing better to say.
Nothing.
You didn't see tar.
That's what I thought you were going to say is her and her friends saw tar.
I was like, all right.
That would be fucking crazy.
But yeah.
Anyway, wait, that's, that's the whole story.
I just thought it was funny because you, you left me a voice memo about, well, that's the part I left out.
I forgot the people at home.
Didn't hear the voice memo.
You sent me about Lyle, Lyle, crocodile.
It could be the most angry.
I've ever heard a man.
But what did I say?
Exactly.
I don't even remember.
You were screaming into the phone.
It was a lot.
Yeah.
Let's be, let's be clear.
It wasn't about Lyle, Lyle, crocodile.
No, there was probably something else going on.
Shaw.
Well, the movie was Sean Mendes, who is, I assume, a pop star of some sort as the voice of Lyle.
Javier Bardem.
In a, like a clown costume.
And then is it Blanchette too?
No, it's the lady from fresh off the boat.
Oh, yeah, Constance Wu.
They look alike.
And then worry.
That was an racial joke.
You just know.
Lyle, Lyle, crocodile also has Brett Galman portraying a character named Mr. Grumps.
And I was talking about how Brett Galman once had a meeting scheduled me and canceled it the last minute because he looked up my credits.
That's.
My agent was like, I don't know.
He looks at the credits and said he didn't want to meet with you.
And I was like, oh, that's incredibly insulting.
I don't know why he told you that or why you told me that.
And now he's playing Mr. Grumps in Lyle, Lyle, crocodile.
So I get why he'd be snobby.
I get it.
You know, he only makes really great films.
I think that made it into the voice memo.
Uh -huh.
I'm sure that probably was the source of a lot of my anger.
Um, the.
These guys, like I need to meet fucking Brett Galman.
Hey, I, I, I try to get a movie made.
I need a queue list actor to star in it.
So I'd love to meet him with Brett Galman.
Thanks.
He's always looks the way he looks right now like that.
Yeah.
He looked like that.
He was a guy like when he was 21.
I wanted to be like, do you have that disease where you look like an old man?
Like I'm in birch.
Kinds disease.
Uh, no, he, um, he did.
He did a funnier die thing called night of a thousand cats that is one of the greatest sketches I've ever seen.
Beyond that, I have no use for the man.
He's a funny man.
He's a funny guy.
But a lot of the guys, it kills me from that scene.
Now, look, we all grow up.
We get older.
Everybody can be a caddy.
Little angsty 20 something year old.
And then grow out of it.
Fine.
But there is an uncanny.
And I mean uncanny amount of people from that scene when you look at the comedy scene from 20 years ago.
That scene, meaning what was called the alt scene, and then you weren't supposed to call it that because you weren't cool.
If you called it that, you didn't know.
But anyway, that like graduated into making.
Not that they don't ever do good stuff, but some of the shittiest stuff out like everything they mocked.
And made fun of.
Yeah.
One of the own, honestly, I don't pick the money and still make fun of it, which I'm like, you can't do that.
David Cross with Alvin in the chipmunks.
Exactly.
You don't get a million dollars in the neck like you're above it.
And I don't, I don't say this just because we're, we're, we're pals, but like I really do mean it's, I feel like.
Patton's wall is one of the only guys that found huge success.
And I'm like, most of what he does is pretty good.
Like he, yeah, you know, when he's in a movie, it's a pretty good movie, you know, like he's, you know, look, everybody's going to everybody.
All of us will have the doozy here or there, but like, are you looking at a guy like Dana Gold who was like the sort of Godfather of that scene.
He kind of stuck to his thing and like made the stuff he wanted to make that he respected and whatever, you know, like.
But so many of those guys where you're just like Jesus Christ, man, it's always children's cinema too.
Yeah.
Now there's a bunch of them and then there are these guys who, you know, you can be introduced to him 25 times.
They act like they have no idea who you are.
They act like it's a stressful pain in the ass to have to shake your hand.
And that's a big part of the LAC and I have a lot of names in the tip of my tongue that I am holding in, but.
Yeah, it's these guys.
You get five seconds of heat and then you think you can be an asshole for the rest of your life.
It's like literally no one knows or cares who you are.
Dude, or do that.
I got an interesting thing to post here here.
Yeah.
Ticket to paradise, which is the new George Clooney, Julia Roberts movie.
And then triangle sadness, which is the new Woody Harrelson thing about the rich.
Great.
Yeah.
Similar titles.
Ticket to paradise, triangle sadness.
Same so almost the same syllables.
Okay.
Both start with a T, both three words.
Second word starts with an O.
Oh, sorry.
But you get my point of sure.
And both movies that are about people getting on boats and going to tropical areas and both are comedies.
Yes.
Could one movie look more excellent?
And one movie look more like the worst thing to ever crawl out of the devil's asshole.
Triangle sadness looks so good.
It looks like such a work of art.
Ticket to paradise.
I'm like, did George Clooney get hit in the head?
What the fuck, man?
Like Julia?
She just did the TV show of um.
Homecoming.
Yeah.
Like they both do amazing stuff.
They do quality quality stuff.
It's like, what the fuck guys?
They knew.
They knew those two together would be a hit.
It's already made $100 million.
I don't know anybody who's seen the film.
Um, moms, I presume.
And their friends.
Um, the trailer does look absolutely horrible.
It's jokes that would be bad in a sitcom from the 80s.
You know, like really bad stuff.
Like he goes at one point.
She goes, oh, how long were you guys married?
Some, some like flight attendant.
And he goes 19 years.
And she goes, oh, it was only 10 years.
And he goes, oh, I'm talking about the trauma or something along those lines.
And it's like, no, if you're going to make that joke as an actual man, you'd just say 20.
You wouldn't say 19.
It's like, they don't even understand basic joke construction.
No human being would say that to set up.
You know, it's just absurd.
The whole movie looks like forced.
They have kids who fall in love.
It's the mama Mia sub plot.
Here's how they got him.
George, Julia, you guys love each other.
George Clooney looks at her when his wife's in the room as though his wife is, is not present.
He stares at Julie Roberts with lust and ignores his wife.
And he's been doing it.
It's real life.
Real life.
He's been doing it.
He's been doing it for 20.
I mean, he, he clearly they, they have, they have fucked or they want to fuck.
The wife knows it.
It's all over her face.
Amal Clooney is always like, alright, can we wrap this up?
Julie, Rob's never did it for me.
It passed pretty well.
I mean, obviously delightful, but I was never like, I had the hots for them.
But they said, hey, Julia, George, you guys are friends.
You guys love to flirt.
You want to hang out in a beautiful island community for three months and make 20 million dollars.
And they said, sure.
I think I'm going to see Triangle of sadness tomorrow.
I don't think I'm ever going to see ticket to paradise.
I'd have to be on a plane, a long plane flight with no other options.
I want to see Triangle sad and it's very badly.
It's two and a half hours.
So star.
And the, I just, I'm getting older and the idea of planting my ass in a movie theater seat for two and a half hours.
Being that close to the public in a situation where the public is probably going to piss me off.
Yeah, because people will be having actual facetime conversations during the movie.
It's just the last movie I went to.
It's a lot.
And then also it's a comedy.
And you think, well, I want to see it in a theater with other people.
Nobody's going to be seeing Triangle sad.
I'm going to be alone in that theater.
I was just watching my house.
Well, I keep hearing it's an art house movie with like something about Mary style gross outs and laughs.
Which is fascinating to me.
The guy who made it did force measure, which is one of my favorite movies, the last 10, 15 years.
Very sad.
I'll tell you what I'm dying to see is this new in bruge guys thing where he's got feral and, uh, and, uh,
Lee Sinback together.
Can't wait and bruge is incredible.
I love everything this guy's done or at least enjoyed it.
The trailer sort of leaves me cold.
I have no idea what it's about.
The entire trailer is Colin Farrell is playing a guy who's, you know, maybe mentally handicapped.
I can't tell.
But he's like, I thought we were friends.
And Brennan Gleason's like, we're not friends anymore.
Get away from me.
But we were friends just yesterday.
That's the whole trailer.
Well, it starts with Gleason saying I've had this guy's plague me for 20 years.
I'm tired of it.
I'm finally cutting him off.
And then he cuts him off and Colin Farrell can't handle it and does understand it.
And then it seems like it's probably going to escalate to a very dark place, which is what in bruge does.
But in bruge, in bruge, one of the greatest lines of all time is, is Ralph, Ralph finds love them in that mood.
Screaming at Brendan Gleason.
You take that comment back about my cunt fucking kids.
Yeah.
It's a really great movie.
And I really like seven cycle paths, which got no play.
Loved it with Rockwell and walking and all them.
And Rockwell walkable boards.
Tom waits.
Yeah.
In seven psychos.
But yeah, I'm excited for this.
It looks very much like in bruge, like a spiritual sequel, because they have a similar dynamic in that, where Gleason's sort of the strong, minded one.
And Farrell sort of the flannel.
Yeah, he's more of the hot head, though.
And this one, he seems to really be like kind of just a simple guy.
I don't know.
The trailer both looks intriguing and also I'm like, man, if it wasn't the talent involved, this would be the least appealing movie of all time.
It does not look that interesting.
Then they bring in like a wisecrack and go halfway through.
Okay.
All right.
That's not helping me any.
I love.
I really enjoy Farrell when he plays the weaker guy.
I like that a lot.
Cassandra's dream is a terrible movie, but I thought I thought he deserved an Oscar for it.
I was like, he's so good at this.
I like Farrell a lot.
Yeah.
In Gleason.
Oh, yeah.
Speaking briefly of Chris walk.
And let me take you to the movie corner.
I just watched a very interesting vampire film on arrow films that I'd always wanted to see.
Called the addiction directed by able Farara.
Who's, you know, did bad lieutenant and all kinds of shit makes some very strange films.
Some very memorable films that he did a lot of like grindhouse shit in the 70s and 80s.
His movie is the is the shy love buff movie.
Yeah, he's notorious for working with whoever is unhierable at that moment in time.
And the thing, it looks like they shot it on video.
It's like a period.
I mean, I respect the shit out of able Farrell.
He's true artist.
Truly doesn't give a rat's ass.
No.
He's made some great shit.
He's hung in there for, you know, 40 years of making movies.
The King of New York with walk in, Bad Lieutenant, Miss 45.
I recently watched the driller killer, which was, you know, he's done some great stuff.
But the addiction stars Lily Taylor, who is an actor.
I was so thrilled when she popped up in the conjuring because she used to be a character actress in everything.
And then in the conjuring, I was like, Oh, great.
She's back.
And then I never saw her again.
It's like she's just kind of pops up every few years.
She's great.
And she leaves like Parker Posey sort of in the addiction, which is a movie shot in black and white.
It's beautiful.
It's 80 minutes long.
Another win.
And it's like a.
The combination vampire slash philosophy movie.
So Lily Taylor is playing a philosophy student in New York.
The movie's got a huge New York vibes.
It's got a great early 90s hip hop soundtrack.
That is awesome.
All very New York East Coast stuff.
She is in classes, philosophy classes with a young Edie Falco.
Cool to see her at a young age.
You also got Christopher.
Michael and Perioli playing a small role.
You got Chris Walken.
And Annabella Ciora, also from.
Sopranos.
So clearly they shared a casting director or some of some kind.
Well, Christopher Walken's wife was the Sopranos casting director.
So that makes sense.
But basically.
It's not a perfect movie, but it's really interesting.
It's all about vibes.
There's a great like orgy of blood sequence where there's like this fancy New York book release party.
And the vampires are like locked the doors and start biting everybody's neck.
So you got Falco chopping down on next.
It's wild, you know.
It's interesting.
It's not perfect.
A lot of the philosophy talk.
Might fascinate you if you're into that shit.
Might seem a little heavy handed and boring if you're not.
But for a new twist on a vampire story.
I thought it was a lot of fun.
And it's on shutter right now.
I watched the.
Where wolf by night.
Marvel.
How was it?
You know, I.
For well, it's straight from the Marvel formula, which I liked.
You know, somebody said recently.
I think it was James Cameron, actually.
First thing James Cameron's done in years that I liked.
He said, I don't like Marvel and DC movies.
They all talk like they're in high school.
I just read that.
I'm not correcting.
I'm telling you because I just read it.
It's like they all act like they're at college, which I think is right.
Just like.
Yeah.
There are none of them have personalities or lives or attachments.
So you don't care about them.
It's exactly what we've been saying.
Yeah, and everybody's a smart ass all the time.
And you know what I mean?
It's just.
Yeah.
But.
Where wolf by night sort of straight from that.
They paid tribute to some of the lesser.
Well, one of two of the lesser known Marvel characters.
The where wolf by night.
And man thing.
Which.
You know, it's arguable what came first man thing or swam thing.
Who ripped off who.
But Marvel historically is ripped off DC far more than DC is ripped off Marvel.
So.
How is it arguable?
Isn't it like whatever one made it to print first gets it or what?
Man thing and swam thing came out in the same year.
Oh, that's a real tough call that one.
But.
Is man thing by any chance come from the swamp?
Yeah, he's like a plant made.
Yeah, then I have some questions.
Swam things way cooler because swam thing is like.
Swam thing has pain and he desperately wants to be human again.
And he can't and it's swam things awesome.
Anyway.
Um, you know, it's look it's it's a TV special it's got a TV special feel when I first saw the trailer for it.
I was like, this is like an interactive video game or something like this isn't a T because of the quality of it.
Yeah, and you'd see what I mean if you if you watched it, but it doesn't look bad.
It just has you know, it feels like it feels like it's not a theatrical thing.
Um, the lady that played Phoebe on Frazier isn't it, which is great.
And she's amazing in it.
The whole cast is great.
The guy from the secret science of sleep is the lead.
He plays where we'll find out he's great.
Everybody's great.
Um, who was Phoebe on Frazier?
I mean, BB.
No, Phoebe's his agent.
I think that was BB.
Oh, BB.
I'm sorry.
Yes, BB.
Excuse me.
Yeah.
She's that lady's awesome.
She's.
She stole licorice pizza.
She had that one scene and she stole the whole movie.
She's like, you know, like show me a female theater actor from New York.
Yeah.
That's her.
You know, yeah.
Um, anyway.
It's, it's a lot of fun.
It's about the world's greatest monster hunters are assembled to hunt down a monster.
Uh, so they can get there.
They, so the, the greatest of them can be clean, uh, can be crowned.
And then that person can obtain this stone of power of some kind of whatever the fuck.
I don't know.
But, uh, it's a fun thing to watch.
It's like an hour.
You're in your out.
It's got a universal pictures vibe to it.
Um, especially the way the werewolf looks.
It looks very much like a long chaney style werewolf.
Um, versus like, uh, an American werewolf and London or something.
So it was fun.
It's endearing in a weird way.
And, um, I enjoyed it.
I had, you know, I had a good time watching it.
And it was perfect for Halloween.
Excellent.
I, uh, I kind of, I'm kind of intrigued by it, but I don't have the plus.
I did, as I talked about on the movie corner, regate Netflix for a month.
And just trying to watch some stuff while I got it.
It's been the struggle.
I will say, you know,
as much as you can enjoy, uh,
Dahmer, I got to say Dahmer, I thought was a very well made.
Uh, many series, you know, I, I kind of missed those old.
My mom used to be obsessed with whatever the CBS movie of the week was,
you know, true crime, whether it be Jean -Bene, or whatever.
I'm sure they made Dahmer movies back then too.
I never saw my friend Dahmer, which I know people really loved.
I don't know if that's the Jeremy Renner one,
but I know Renner did one where he was Dahmer.
Um, and I realized I didn't know much about the man,
because my parents were so troubled by it,
they wouldn't tell me in my sister anything about it,
and they changed the channel every time it was on.
So, which is probably as much about him being gay as it was being a cannibal.
But, um, I didn't know anything about him, you know?
Like my mom, my parents let me watch all the OJs shit and had no problem with that.
But something about Dahmer, they were like, I don't want my kids knowing there's this evil in the world.
And, um, I get it.
Dahmer did a bunch of fucked up shit.
This movie doesn't show them to you, you know?
It's not as graphic as I had heard.
You get the occasional shot of him like talking to a severed head or something like that.
But, um, there's not like him, you know, sitting down with a knife and fork
and tucking in a napkin and eating somebody's stomach or something.
Or why the hell not?
What am I watching?
What was really cool about it is I was like, boy, this was really well directed, extremely well directed.
And who did every episode pretty much?
But the great Carl Franklin director of devil in a blue dress, one false move,
and a variety of other films.
They also got Paris Barclay.
So two black directors.
Paris Barclay did don't be a menace.
I did a movie called The Cherokee Kid with Sinbad.
So, like, these guys are getting a second chance basically.
He hadn't directed in 20, 25 years.
Comes in and just really kills it.
I mean, these guys have been TV directors for a while too.
But, um, the first one, I think, is the best.
It follows Dahmer basically at home board.
Goes out to a bar, a gay bar.
Starts buying guys drinks and it basically follows almost in real time.
An evening of Dahmer like going out to get a victim to bring back to his house to kill and eat.
So it's like a real time first date almost that you're watching.
But you know the danger that this guy is in.
And the first one actually winds up being the last.
The first episode winds up being the last, uh, Dahmer incident before he gets caught.
This guy escapes.
Go, yeah, I'm only spoiling the pilot, but guys escapes, get some cops, brings them back.
The cops aren't believing the guy because Dahmer lived in a very poor black neighborhood and only brought home poor black men thinking correctly that nobody would miss them and that the police would not investigate and they wouldn't care.
So there's a lot of race stuff in Dahmer that I was not expecting, but it winds up making the movie really fascinating because you see how he got away with it.
He positioned himself, uh, and his victims.
As people he just knew nobody would care about or you know nobody in power would care about.
So, um, I watched it basically in two days.
It's a 10 hour thing.
It's depressing as hell.
Richard Jenkins, who I did not even know was in it, uh, is clearly gunning for the Emmy here.
I mean, Richard Jenkins coming into a role like what if you were the dad of Jeffrey Dahmer.
I mean, he's, he's really good in a very, very dark, dark role.
Also, the dad because he can't connect with his son and he can't talk to him about sex or anything.
He's just like so closed off.
They to bond. He starts taking his son out.
They pick up roadkill and dissect it out in the garage.
That's what makes Dahmer who he is.
Like that's what they found.
I believe the dad is trying to sue to be like, I didn't do any of this.
Now, if he didn't do any of it, that's different, but there's a lot of people pissed at the show.
I'm sure the victims, families are furious.
They're like, you know, stop fucking drudging this up every few years.
I'm sick of this.
Look, all sorts of moral issues with the show being made.
Don't get me wrong.
But I think for me, I've seen a variety of Ryan Murphy's work.
I really like Nip Tuck beyond that.
He's just not a guy who stuff really works for me.
Except the stuff that he produces where he's recreating real events.
I thought his OJ show was brilliant.
I thought the Miami killing show was brilliant.
I thought the impeachment show with Clive Owen was brilliant.
And I, you know, Dahmer's not up to those standards, but it's really, really good.
And I'm glad I watched it.
Also a great comeback from Molly Ringwald as Richard Jenkins, new wife.
And some extremely dark comedy of Richard Jenkins,
bringing his new girlfriend around like to lunch to meet his son Jeffrey Dahmer.
You know, there's some like dark comedy in there.
I dug it.
You know, I guess, you know, to market, this is like a Halloween watch is a little sick.
It's all a little sick, but you know, it was well done.
I.
I was going to say something that I got thrown by the Molly Ringwald.
She's great in it.
She was in the bear too.
She had a great role in the bear.
That's interesting.
Yeah, no, that's why I got distracted.
I was like, oh, I didn't know she was back.
Yeah.
I can't remember.
Doesn't matter.
Anyway, I watched the new Stephen King.
Short story adaptation, Mr. Harrington's phone.
Yeah.
I think it's Harrington, right?
Maybe.
Oh, I know it's down Sutherland's in it.
I haven't watched it.
Donald Sutherland is wonderful in it.
The kid from it.
The new it.
The place.
Billy.
Or William is really good in it.
Will.
Everybody's really.
Well, they're the they're the main whatever.
They're very good in it.
And then the kid that plays the bully in it is great.
You know, I've said it before on the show.
We've talked about it.
At least nobody writes a bully like Stephen King.
Sure.
The bully is just such a fucking asshole.
You're just like, God damn it, man.
But the little extra flavor in this one is the bully is clearly damaged.
And the kid that plays it.
He's a child actor who's growing up.
He was in some other stuff.
I can't remember what it is.
But he plays it really well.
Like, you know, there's scenes where he's going to hit the kid.
And he's and he's got no good reason to hit the kid.
But when he does it, he'll be like, see what you made me do.
And like he's like on the verge of tears.
Like it's a very damaged portrayal of the bully.
It's very, very good.
Yeah.
So those three characters are really the standouts here.
But the sorry, the plot is.
Don on Southern one plays the richest man in this tiny, tiny town in Maine.
Uh, he is not very well liked by the citizens.
He does not really have any friends.
But he is impressed with this kid in the town played by the guy from it.
And well, eventually there's a younger version.
And then that could place the older version.
But anyway, he hires this kid to after seeing him speak in church.
He hires him to come and read to him.
And eventually the kid buys when he gets older and cell phones become a thing.
He buys Mr. Harrington his own cell phone.
And Mr. Harrington is against cell phones.
But then.
Find the device very curious and interesting.
But also very dangerous.
And it could, you know, he basically lays out how this device could destroy us one day.
Okay.
Uh, when Mr. Harrington dies, the kid buries the phone.
He puts it in the coffin.
Uh, as a farewell, whatever.
And then he starts to get calls for Mr. Harrington after Mr. Harrington is dead.
And the phone becomes their phone connection becomes a way for this kid basically to.
To seek revenge on people because that's one of the things that was the dark side of Mr. Harrington.
He is rich and he's not a terrible person, but he has done terrible things.
I should say it's Mr. Harrigan.
I did.
Harrigan, sorry.
But the final piece of advice before he dies, he gives that he gives to the boy is.
Promise me that if you when you encounter your enemies, you will dispatch of them with great haste.
And never have regret and whatever.
And he's basically saying anybody that stands in your way, eliminate them.
Right.
And then that becomes quite literal.
Um,
There's a, and there's a great line.
The kid asked Mr. Harrigan, Harrigan, Harrigan, yeah.
Can money be cruel or is money cruel.
And Donald Sutherland says it can be if used properly, which is a very great, good, very good line.
So that's your plot, but it goes nowhere.
It, the kid executes the, this thing, this power two times.
It's almost almost justifiably so.
And then he decides it's the world, it's bad.
And it, and he throws his phone in the river.
And that's the end of it.
And that's how the movie ends.
It just, it goes absolutely nowhere.
It's an interesting little short story.
It is not a movie.
It, at best, maybe could have been a short story, like an episode of creep show or something.
That's what it sounds like.
But, and even then, it would have been like one of the boring ones.
Uh, I would say it's worth a watch.
To see the acting between the two main characters, because that's really the whole first half of the film.
Right.
And it's really, it's really enjoyable watching Donald Sutherland in particular.
But other than that, it's just not, it's just not a movie.
It's just barely, there's, there's barely acts to this thing, let alone three acts.
Um, so.
I can't say I would recommend it.
Um, when I, it's in the book, if it bleeds, I have the audio book.
This is the first story in the book.
And when they said that this was the one they were going to make a movie of, I was like confused.
Like, what are you talking about? They're like, how?
So, yeah, I think they just know they can put a Steve, based on a Stephen King on whatever and it'll have an audience.
And I think sometimes they go for a feature length when they definitely should not sound like that was the case here.
I have if it bleeds, I haven't read it, I haven't listened to it.
But, um, any short story he's ever made will be made into a movie at some point.
They'll find a way, even the ones they thought were unfilmable.
They found a way to do Gerald's game and, you know, they'll make them all.
Yeah, well, there you go.
Uh, I, from my final here, sore a movie.
I think the hellians would love called spider baby.
I know it was on shutter for a while.
I think now it has moved over, of course, to to be where you can see it.
Um, I have an arrow, Blu -ray of it. That's awesome.
I've been watching a lot of arrows just because I had so many of them never opened.
The deal with spider baby, it came out in 1967, which would put it about.
You know, when, when, uh, Texas Chainsaw Masker was what, 74?
73, 74, yeah, something like that.
So yeah, it's about seven years before Texas Chainsaw.
And I don't know whether Mr. Tobay Hooper referenced it as an inspiration.
My guess is he did. There's a lot of similarities, a lot of similar ground.
It's not as troubling or as disturbing as Texas Chainsaw.
But for a 1967 movie, it definitely is the 70s.
Obviously, you know, we're able to make things a lot more sort of depraved and, uh, insane.
But spider baby does a really good job of creeping you out on a very low budget.
And be at a time when you couldn't really show a lot of graphic gore and disgusting ship.
Directed by Jack Hill, uh, he wound up doing a lot of great black exploitation movies.
Really the two best Pam Greer black exploitation movies coffee and foxy brown.
He directed all kinds, all different types of movies.
The big bird cage with Pam Greer as well as a great sort of women and prison movies.
So clearly he was very close with Pam Greer.
Spider baby is a family of cannibals.
Again, kind of a theme this week, who live there.
They are led by, uh, Lon Cheney Jr.
The great who portrayed the wolf man.
And he has three insane siblings, one a depraved rapist cannibal,
who was obsessed with women.
And like if a woman comes around, he's going to attack her.
That is played by Sid Hig or Hig, who was used, uh, very often by Rob Zombie in recent years.
Also played a judge in Jackie Brown with Miss Pam Greer.
Yeah.
Um, Sid Hig is, you know, you get to see a very young, he's a very odd looking dude.
He sort of grew into looking normal, but as a young man, he was very strange looking.
And then you got the two sisters, one of whom was obsessed with spiders.
They're both clearly sexually wound up.
Um, and these relatives show up because they want the house.
They think there's an inheritance to be had.
And they're like, oh, we'll just roll in and get the house from these weird freaks that live here.
And of course, it does not go as planned.
And they are tormented and raped and assaulted and attacked and presumably eaten and all sorts of stuff.
But on top of all this, the movie is a black comedy.
It is a horror and a thriller, but there's a lot of comedy to it.
Just a super bizarre tone.
The movie is loved by a lot of great big names, you know, Joe Dante and all these kinds of folks at great.
Um, it's really cool.
And you can, you can feel its influence on Texas Chancel in a really great way.
They took the ground here and obviously took it in a much darker and more disturbing direction.
But I really admired spider baby.
It's also 80 minutes.
And even that is padded by a guy doing a little corny narration at the beginning and the end.
But, um, I really dug it.
Check it out.
It's well worth watching.
I just added it to my to be.
Yeah.
Great watch.
And yes, Joe, you have one more.
Barely.
I watched Willard on to be to be once again.
Yes, everything.
The newer the old, the old.
I think they have the new one on there too, but I watched the old one.
I've never seen it.
I say barely.
I sort of was in and out.
Like I was kind of watching it tonight before bed and watching it in pieces.
But I did watch it.
It's a fun little weird movie.
Ernest Borg nine is.
Is great in it.
And then Willard is played by what's his name.
From.
Oh, God.
Damn it.
He plays the senator in the X -Men movie.
It turns.
Bruce Davis.
Bruce Davidson.
Yeah.
It is.
And it's funny that Ernest Borg nice in it because there is a marty quality to it.
It's about a guy that's very awkward who lives with his mom.
And his mom's really overbearing except except.
This is a disturbing version of it.
And, you know, he befriends a rat named.
Willard.
Well, first is first.
I think the first rat.
He befriends is Memphis.
Stop a lazy names.
Or Socrates.
That's what he named it.
The second rat.
He befriends is Willard.
And then the third rat.
He befriends is Ben.
Ben becomes the.
Abstructive.
Antagonistic rat.
Willard is his companion.
But he trains the rats to kind of do whatever he wants them to do.
And particularly to to exit exact revenge on Ernest Borg nice character who was friends.
And I guess partners with his father his father died and Ernest Borg nice character sort of stole the company out.
From Willard and the people that should have inherited the company.
And then he treats and the but but Ernest Borg not had promised Willard's mother he would always take care of him.
So he can't fire him.
But he hates Willard and he abuses him all the time.
And you know, there you go.
Apparently the crisp.
Crispin Glover one which I never saw.
Lean.
Lean's much heavier into.
The like sort of sinister.
He's it's based on two books.
There's two books.
I think one's called like the story of ratman or something like that.
I don't know.
But anyway, Willard.
The remake apparently leans into the horror elements of it.
This this one doesn't.
I get I don't know if it was made for TV, but it feels like a made for TV thriller from the, you know.
The seventies early seventies late sixties wherever it is.
But yeah, it's fun.
It's fun enough.
You know, I don't know if you need to own it, but it's fun.
Pretty sure I saw both versions.
I thought the Glover one was pretty decent too.
And then what was the show on FX Wilfred.
Always get that confused with Elijah Wood.
Yeah, that's the man with a pretend dog.
It is it is for a guy for another thing about a weird guy with the animal thing.
Wilfred.
Yeah.
It's too close.
Anyway, our movie for today.
Well, a movie is barbarian.
The movie was written and directed by a gentleman I've known about 20 years and I'm Zach Kregger.
He was in the widest kids you know.
Sketch comedy troupe who of course had their show on IFC with the great Trevor Moore, who was friends with Joseph and myself.
RIP.
I used to see them do live stage shows in New York before they had the show.
So I've known Zach a while.
I didn't know him near as well as Trevor, but he's made this pivot here from sketch comedy into horror.
And he's done a really great job.
The movie looks great.
It has a vibe and energy all its own.
There are light comedic touches here and there to it that never detract from the suspense and the horror.
Really good balance.
I think probably that comes from being a comedy filmmaker trying to do horror.
You don't want to lean too much on your special skills of comedy.
And then suddenly you're just making another comedy.
So it works as horror.
And I thought as a as a clever black comedy.
It's really a movie in three sections.
The first section is a woman showing up at an Airbnb.
She can't get in.
There's another weird guy already in the Airbnb.
Who is Bill Scarsgard from it.
And he lets her in.
They wind up getting along fine, but they realize they're they're not alone in the house.
There is a naked, crazy woman.
Basically beneath the house and beneath the house.
There's this crazy world of like, you know, it's not just a basement.
There's like passageways and stuff.
Then you start part two of the film, which is just as long as a actor who at first you're completely on his side.
It sounds like he is shocked that he is being fired from a TV pilot because of a me too situation.
And very quickly you realize this guy is just a complete misogynist asshole who probably did it.
You never find out, but it seems very likely that he did it.
And that's sort of he no, no, he admits to it eventually.
Well, when he's talking to Zach Rager at that bar.
Yeah, he's like, look, it started out.
She didn't want to, but eventually she did.
You know, he's making it seem like it's a gray area.
But I think no, no, no, no, but then at the end he gives that speech.
Oh, you're right.
I'll wait until you'll get to it.
But yeah, he more or less.
And then it proceeds to do.
This is one of the weirdest things on this movie.
You, it's a character that you know for sure has assaulted somebody.
It is horrible.
Who you're still laughing when he does some of the horrible stuff.
I don't know how they pulled that off.
I'll tell you how by casting Justin Long, you know, he is a guy who is immediately likable no matter what he's doing.
You've, whether you've ever loved him in anything, you've liked him in a hundred movies over the course of your life.
And they play off that goodwill.
He's great in this movie.
He's, he's always reliable.
But I think he's really great in this movie as playing what, what a lot of these guys are really charming likable guys who have horrific secrets and do fucked up things.
So he's great at that.
And that's, and that's essentially you see through some flashbacks later on that this woman under the house is actually you find out she's actually the daughter of a man that lived in the house.
Yeah.
Who is a serial killer and was taking women into the house impregnating them.
I guess disposing of them.
And then they had sineuate fucking the daughters, I think.
And they don't ensignuate.
They flat out say that too that he, he fucks the women he kidnaps.
And then he also fucks the daughters that are created.
He's got a giant video collection like Dennis Reynolds style of all these women that he's brought back to the house.
Yeah.
So, yeah.
So, so this movie really is.
And then that guy on the surface plays a nice suburban.
Yeah.
You're introduced to Justin Long for his, you know, 20 minute segment.
And then you go right into a flashback segment of this guy 20 years ago.
Pick, you know, going into a supermarket to pick up a young woman to bring back.
Chatting with his neighbor played by a very welcome surprise.
Mr. Kurt Bronner and a pair of pleated khakis.
Who.
Boy, was he designed to play an 80s dad and a pair of pleated khakis?
It was so funny to see him play that.
It was funny to see that he.
I called Kurt after I saw it because.
I called him and I said, well, I have a voice memo and I said Kurt.
I just saw Barbarian.
Yeah.
And I said, you know, I said it was fun seeing you in there.
That was a nice surprise.
And I go, hey, you know, when this happens, like you're watching a movie and you see somebody you're not expecting to see.
And you turn to the person you're with and you go, is that, is that, is that.
I go, the guy next to me, or a couple seats down for me, did that when you came on screen.
Uh -huh.
The weird part is he was by himself.
And he just out loud was going, is that, is that.
That's funny.
That's nuts.
Yeah.
But it was, yeah, Kurt was born to play that guy.
I mean, it's perfect.
Yeah.
Like, just the way he said, you know, the wife thinks we're going to have to move.
It's just the, the wife was perfect.
It was everybody that came over to talk to my dad whenever he would get off of work or whatever.
Yeah.
And it's, it's, it's a great little scene because Kurt's character is saying we're getting out of the neighborhood.
It's just not the same around here anymore.
And then like when you see that's going to hell, which is even better.
Yeah.
And when you see that neighborhood in modern times, it is, it's a war zone.
There's nothing there.
It's, it's, it's Detroit.
I don't know if we said that already takes place in Detroit.
So it's one of those areas in Detroit that's like so abandoned.
It's like inhabited by like wild animals and shit.
It reminded me of where don't breathe this set, which if don't breathe wasn't set in Detroit, it was, it was close to it.
I know they shot it like in, you know, the third world.
But yeah, it reminded me a bit of the setting of don't breathe.
But that's also interesting too because the guy, the killer guy likes that that's happening.
He takes advantage of it.
He's like, Oh, great.
I'll be here all alone to do whatever the fuck I want.
Right.
He doesn't say that, but that's obviously what he does.
And then, and then his daughter in modern times has, has sort, well, she's not, she's not a.
The daughter is not a killer because she's a sinister killer.
She's a, she's like crazy.
Like she's like a can't, crazy can't, again, cannibal sort of, right?
Oh, no, you get the feeling of cannibal.
She wants a baby.
Yeah.
You get the feeling, I mean, you can create any sort of dark scenario you want.
But this was probably a woman who was born in the house.
So never got outside.
And then started getting fucked by this old man all the time.
But maybe never had a baby because she couldn't, she didn't, I don't know.
But you can sort of create your own scenario, which is kind of the dark fun of the movie.
She's got a video she watches about a mother.
Yeah.
A baby.
And that's like all she knows.
Very serving.
It's really one point tries to breastfeed Justin Long, which is pretty funny.
I mean, like when, when I, when she first goes into that abandoned room in the basement and sees a disgustingly stained mattress with a camera pointing at it and a shit bucket,
I was like, oh, no.
This movie is going to be discussed.
I thought it was going to be like, you know, really what it wound up being, except you don't see any of it.
It's just kind of alluded to this old man had sort of a fuck ranch, kind of like the one and once upon a time in Hollywood.
But it is, you know, the movie never goes there.
It's not disturbing in that way.
It's just really kind of fun.
It felt sort of 80s, you know, people talked about how it seemed too much like its influences.
I didn't see that.
All horror is indebted to its influences.
I thought in its structure, it felt extremely fresh and innovative.
The movie re -starts, you know, four or five times.
And it all comes together.
I think in a really cool, satisfying way.
I would be down for a sequel.
It's a, it's an interesting, it's an interesting film.
What I was alluding to earlier is.
I guess that's what the title is about.
It's about people that are just irredeemable.
Right.
You can't.
They're barbarians.
You can't talk sense into them.
Just in long plays.
You know, you've got the original guy that's killing people in the 70s and then, you know,
and bringing them back to his house and doing all these horrible things.
He's a monster.
He in turn creates a literal monster by the, through the incest and all this stuff.
As the, as a old unhoused man says, you know, you keep making a copy of a copy.
It's worse and worse.
And then he puts in a, a, a haggard, worn copy of multiplicity to explain his concept.
We found this really disturbing tape to sort of explain what's really going on.
So she can't be reasoned with that woman.
Right.
The main character who's innocent and a decent person, the main woman, like her, she's great.
In a way she can't be reasoned with because several people, including the homeless man and the woman she's interviewing for the job with.
Yeah.
And they say, get out of that house.
Right.
It's not safe in that neighborhood.
And she doesn't listen.
And then has to act savagely to end up surviving.
Like so that she's almost like her own, of own sort of poetic take on, on the concept.
And then, of course, Justin Long's character, who, you know, seems like a decent guy, you find out then he's a terrible guy.
He then comes to terms with what he's done by confessing it and saying, I'm just a good person who did a bad thing.
And I have to make up for it.
And you're like, wow, this guy gets it. He's going to do the right thing.
And then seconds after he says that and swears to like protect this woman and get them away from this monster that chasing them, he throws the woman off the roof.
Yeah.
And then says, I had to do it. I had no choice. I had to protect myself. She was coming at me.
And then Justin Long ends up dying. His head gets crushed by the monster lady, which is wild.
I feel like as we explain the film, if you haven't seen it, you're probably going, what the fuck are you guys talking? This doesn't track.
It's a weird movie. It's all over the place, but it does make sense. And when you see it, I understood what my friend meant when he said, I don't understand what the point of it was, but I loved it.
I don't think he was necessarily saying, you know, what's the message? I just got like I was like, I know I don't understand what the through line was. It was just, it was just a crazy story.
One thing I picked up on and I do think I'm right. So Zach directed a bunch of comedy movies before this that all start Trevor.
And well, I know about Miss March. I don't know if you did a bunch, but there were, I think you did two. I think you did at least two.
There are moments in this where I was watching Bill Skarsgard and I was like, that's supposed to be Trevor. That was going to be Trevor. He's Trevor.
They kind of look alike. They're acting alike. This is the kind of part you would have Trevor play where he makes sense. He's weird, but he's like charming. And in the end, he's a good guy.
But you're not quite sure. I really thought that that was a nod to him. I really did. And I was, you know, it was, it was, it was heartwarming and bittersweet and all those things. But I think this is a great first outing into horror for this whole crew.
And I hope, I hope everybody that worked on it together works on something else again. And by the way, my hat's off to Bill Skarsgard doing barely a supporting role in something like this because clearly just because he thought it was cool or whatever, you know.
Yeah, I saw his name in the credits as a producer. So my guess is he just got slipped the script loved it and and came on board to help out, which is awesome. And the true surprise here is that he got very rich off it more than likely.
If he was a producer on a movie that probably costs $2 million and made 50. Then odds are he wound up cashing out big time. But I would not be surprised if we saw us equal to barbarian. I would love it if Zach became a big horror guy because he's clearly got the chops. It's shot in a great way.
The the 80s flashback where the house looks very Edward Scissorhand style and the neighborhood looks really like perfect is awesome. The shots kind of tracking behind the guy as he walks through the the grocery store, you know, each segment of the movie has its own vibes and its own style and it's all really well done.
Spence works, the Gore works, it's just a, you know, like you said, it's a great first outing and I hope we get more.
Hogs up, hogs up for barbarian. We are still definitely going to do smile and other things. We just got kind of bogged down with all these Halloween releases of horror, which is great. A lot of good stuff.
Yes, Miles coming up and some other things. I'll try to see terrifying or two if I can stomach it.
I want to see it. I think they've added more show times, but it's also being released on Blu -ray in like a week or something. So I'm like, maybe I'll just buy it in good faith. There's like a terrifying one and two package you can get.
But anyway, we'll be back with a bunch of other things. We'll see you next time and we'll see you in hell.