Welcome to We'll see you in hell, it's a podcast.
Talks to you about these genre movies you people seem to like so much and by you
people, I mean it religiously or racially, you take your pick. Hello, everybody.
Today's episode is sort of a Halloween special. Halloween is coming up. There's
absolutely no way to tell. I bought a pumpkin just to have some sort of holiday
spirit. It didn't work at all. It's just a pumpkin sitting on my counter rotting.
There's I don't see any lights. It's it's 90 degrees here. The airs. It remains poison.
But happy Halloween. And we will be talking about you be Halloween. Sort of the Santa
Claus of the Halloween season. And also Pat, happy Hulu Ween. I think that's an important
part of every. Yeah. You're right. I mean there's that. That Hulu, Hulu Ween on Hulu was
my only, only even faint sign. Yeah. And then also I went into Trader Joe's recently. And
I got like there was a good display for apple cider. Okay. And then I went down a candy
aisle and target. This is the third one. And they had like the big bags of like, you know,
candy corn and stuff like that. Right. Well, I don't think we can even do trick -or -treating
here. It keeps, it keeps, we get an email from the governor who's like trick -or -treating
is off in the next day. It's back on. But to me, it seems like a pretty terrible idea with
cases on the rise to have children going door to door. But what do I know really? At least
you don't have problems getting people to wear masks during the Halloween season. Yeah. But
they are actually have been think pieces about a Halloween mask doesn't count as a COVID
mask. Right. Well, it depends on what you got. Solid rubber now is not strong enough
to prevent, you know, a finely woven cotton cloth is somehow better than solid rubber. But
I don't know. After Hulu Ween, of course, comes Chris Flix because all the holidays are
just strictly now streaming service base since that's all anyone does. And then they'll
be Amazon Prime giving. Yeah. I almost bought one of the big bags of candy because I got
swept up in the moment and then I immediately snapped out of it. And I was like, there's
going to be nothing sadder than a giant bag of the candy, a variety of candy corn on
your counter. Yeah. It's just use, you know, you pick at it as you walk, but it's very
sad. Yeah. I mean, candy corn for me, it's always like a couple pieces or I prefer the little
pumpkins, which are made of the exact same material. But I mean, you to me were like chewing
on like an array. It was so much of the one thing. Well, you eat more than two of anything
made of that material. You feel deeply ill. But they are good. I mean, I can't deny that.
I do, I do like candy corn. And I never questioned it. And then Lewis Black had that, you know, like
28 minute rant about candy corn. And I was like, wait, does it suck? Yeah. Because you know,
he's like, candy fucking corn. And his fingers are shaking and shit. Right. It seems to me that
candy corn is one of those foods that would live inside of your colon for like 28 years. Yeah.
Coming out of the bag, it looks like you found it under a couch cushion. Yeah.
What was your favorite? Like I always knew the worst candy to me was always the black and orange
wrapped caramel, maybe, but they, you know, they were way cheaper than getting a mini candy bar.
But it was like that. It's almost like a zag nut, except it was a circle wrapped like a peppermint
and either black or orange wrapping. And they were huge. Like it was really for people who just
didn't give a shit about the kids at all. But I always used to get at least half that because I
lived in kind of a rundown neighborhood. I don't remember a rip your teeth out. I don't remember
those. I do remember the peanut butter, more peanut butter than caramel. Yeah. I don't remember
those. I remember the like made for the season generic candy where it'd be like a like a
silvery cellophane wrapper of like a pumpkin or a witch. Those are always sucked. Those are my
least favorites. My favorites, though, where I loved when the people that went rogue and gave you
like the weird shit, like the people that give you like the wax bottles that had the like candy liquid
in them. Yeah. Or candy pack of cigarettes or whatever. Anybody that did like the zany candies for
me was the was the was the number one. I like the big wax Dracula teeth. You know, those were pretty
cool. You can't eat them or anything, but you just scare somebody with them a little bit. Yeah,
no flavor. Yeah. It's candy corn without flavor. And then if you eat it, I think it's potentially
dangerous. Oh, sure. It's wacky. My best friend growing up was at Jehovah's Witness in one year.
My mom, yeah, there's no way as mom listens to this podcast, but my mom snuck him out because we
felt so bad for him. And we snuck out and did the trick or treating. And then he buried his bag of
candy under his deck. And he would go out every day and take out like five pieces. But there was
always a sense of adventure to Halloween that you don't get with the other holidays that I like.
Trick or treating feels dangerous. You're out after dark. Yeah. Halloween was was kid bar hop.
It was like you were allowed to like be a grown -up and go out by yourself. And yeah, no shaperones or
anything. And that's all gone. It is. It is. Good. Yeah. The thing I never got was destroying like a
beautiful handcrafted jack -a -lantern. Like the handle is something that never it never made any
sense to me at all. Like it just kids ruining something that like a family put their heart and soul
into is just so needlessly cruel that I never got it. I remember my buddy Jim had a jack -a -lan
and carved on his he was that we were older at we're in our early 20s. He was living with his
girlfriend who's now his wife. And they had a carved jack -a -lantern on their stoop in I guess
he lived in Roxboro, Pennsylvania outside of Philly. And we were shit -faced like shit -faced. Yeah.
And I was like watch this fuck face. And I just took my dick out and pissed all inside his jack -a -lantern
and watched the piss come out of the eyes and mouth. And then he ran and kicked it as hard as he could.
And as it was soaring through the air his girlfriend came out and saw it happening and goes
we carved that together. I hope you learned your lesson. I didn't. I mean I never did it again but
not because of any lesson learned. I just never had the opportunity. I gotta be imagining the smell of
your piss and pumpkin innards and I'm getting sick. You're giving my piss too much credit. I mean
your piss at that point is water. We were deep into the night of drinking. It was coming out
clear. Okay. That was point. But did you do a when you did carve? Did you do a
a standard face or were you one of these guys who went a little more advanced with either
an interesting face or maybe one of these people that carved a witch? Sure.
That I can't remember you ever carving. I know my dad would do it and I'm sure I would like help him
in some way. Yeah. And I'm sure sometime in grade school I carved a pumpkin in class. But like
I can't remember the like it's seen when I look at it when I see a pumpkin in the store and I think
about it for a second. Now it seems impossible. I don't understand how you do it. I don't get how
people are able to cut through it with any sort of precision. So I just I'm very out of touch.
Well, you know, we the one I got Heather is pushing to make into a pumpkin pie and I'm like
that's going to be disgusting. Like the the innards with the the goop and the seeds and all that
is so gross you just got to get the can if you're going to make a pie in my well can I can I give you
some my advice? What do you do? You piss in it. To kind of loosen it up for baking. Oh no not for
baking. I was just going to say just when you're ready to just have have a night where you piss at
it. Yeah, both of you. You know, Heather can sit on the top part that you pull off, you know,
yeah, where you put the candle and then you can piss in the eye part. She has started taking an
online Spanish course. So all day she is wearing headphones and talking loudly in Spanish and boy,
that will be what leads to the divorce. Unquestionably. Yeah, yeah, you got to sit in a guapo. Yeah,
oh, it's raw. I can't think of any Spanish things. We used to do, you know, always just the two
triangle eyes and the mouth with the teeth just a standard. And then you try to light it and you got
a candle sitting in there that falls over and yeah, and I got to tell you at this point in this
society culture, heightened sensitivity culture, I feel like anything you're carving into that
pumpkin feels vaguely racial. I just want to stay away from it at this point. Yeah, sure. Well,
I do. There was a guy in my neighborhood who did a was trying to do a laughing pumpkin like, you
know, where the eyes are half closed because he's laughing boy. And the problem boy, oh boy, did it look
Asian? And it was mocked and it didn't feel right to me. It felt very cruel. I'm sure it wasn't
the intent, but you know, I would like to think of, I mean, I know we've been off of it for a while,
but I'd like to think of more streaming holidays like, you know, I don't know, Shutter's Times Day.
Okay. I mean, Hulu, you can't even be mad at him. It's too perfect. The other way, Chris
Flix isn't bad, you know, for I would say Flix miss though. I wouldn't say Chris Flix. I would
say Flix miss because that's the word. That's the thing that rhymes with, you know, but I Chris,
Chris Mix, I don't, I don't hate it. I'm not mad at Chris Flix. I don't hate it. Hulu,
is the, I'll save it for the movie corner, Christ. They never, they never look good. You know,
like I was like, oh, sweet, Hulu, and then you look through 50 titles, old and new and you're like,
now, now, it's yeah, it's literally like, it's like, it's like, it's an expression I heard Vince
Avril use once. And it's a great expression. But he said, he called something inviting the neighbors
over for leftovers. And that's what I feel like Hulu. Ween is they just take whatever the
fuck is lying around on Hulu. Yeah. And like try to pull one over on you, like they've created some
event. Yeah. You're like this, earn a scared stupid spit on here for, for years or whatever it is,
you know, or they'll put like, you know, some movie that isn't even remotely scary into the section
just because it like, you know, has some vague tie to the season. But I did finally watch children
of the corn, because when you and I did it on maybe our first episode. Yeah, it's number one.
I hadn't seen the movie. So I did it, you know, I was doing the commentary just cold, which is insane
that for our first movie, I was doing a commentary and a movie I'd never seen. But I mean, we know we're
near making a dime on this thing. We weren't taking it very soon. Who knew? Do you remember our shock
when we started getting messages from people saying, yeah, we were like, yeah, what? Yeah, it was
really just an excuse to hang out. But the, the movie children of the corn is, I mean, it's bad,
but it's insane to me that that one hasn't been rebooted. I mean, you could make that so terrifying.
I think they did it for sci -fi maybe. And maybe that one's better. But I was just like, man,
you've got all the tools. How is this, this bad? It's terrible. There was a remake. I do think it
I think it was made for sci -fi. Like you said, it also sucked. There's been 89 sequels. Yeah, they've
had every fucking opportunity to get this thing. It's the same story, basically, every time. They've
had every opportunity to get this right. And they have fucked it up every time. As even going as far as
in part, like, I don't know, it might be parts, what part six was, of course, called
children of the corn, six, six, six, I believe. Yeah. But one of them was the return of Isaac.
That fucking kid from the first one comes back. Yeah. And you're like, and they fucked that one up.
Like, they, they, they, I'm starting to think the story itself maybe isn't that good. I never read it.
I didn't either, but the story, even when you're watching it, you're like, the story is all there.
And Stephen King wrote a draft of it that they threw out at the Wikipedia page. It was hilarious. They
said that his draft, the first 45 pages were the couple talking in a car. And they were like,
what's wrong with you? Like, I think this was probably during his Coke days, but
you know, the opening scene of them killing everyone in the diner is awesome.
The kid actors are all very creepy and good, but it just doesn't work, man.
That's that's one of the best openings ever to a horror movie. And nothing lives it up to it. And
then you see it the end of the film when the budget runs out. And he who walks behind the role
rose is clearly just some sort of air pump in dirt. Yeah, they're running under the ground or whatever.
They're using the tremors thing. Tremors did it much better. But yeah, I mean, same exact special
effects. Yeah, it's just terrible. But the kids are good. You know, what's that guy? I forget
the actor's name. He looks kind of like a wolf. Yeah. He's good. Linda Hamilton's good. Peter Horton.
Yeah. I posted to Instagram. I was watching it with subtitles on. And I had a real good hard laugh
because the, you know, they put the actions up. It put up parentheses. Corn howling, which just made
me laugh so hard. What does that mean? What does that even mean? Like the wind in the corn?
It was exactly what was happening. And you're watching it. And the corn's going like,
which for anyone to think that would that would scare an audience is very funny to me.
Yeah, it's it's a shame, man. It's a shame. It's not a very good, it's not a very good film. It's
you know, it's real hit and miss, man. Did you ever see the trailer for Maximum Overdrive, which
is has gone down in history as the arguably the worst Stephen King movie ever? And he directed it
while blazingly high on Coke. Yeah. I've never seen Maximum Overdrive. I've never seen it either.
I tried to watch it once. And I was like, I don't give a shit about this. Like who cares? You know,
like Christine, like scary cars that are alive. Like Christine was as good as that was ever going to
get. And that's an awesome movie. But there's just that's really waiting. And then then the cab from
Hoofram Roger Ray. Right, right. But yeah, in the Nintendo game, because I always know that the
lamest Nintendo games, then the cab was like it, you had to jump into him and drive around. And it
was a lot of fun. But that's yeah, that's not a very well -liked Nintendo. But it's just because I love
Roger Rabbit. Yeah. But anyway, so there's a trailer for Maximum Overdrive where it's Stephen
King addressing camera, Hitchcock style. And there's like all this crazy, if I remember correctly,
like it's all these like really hard primary colors like red and green behind him and stuff.
And he's like trying to be sinister. And you can tell that he's fucking rocked out of his
fucking head. One of his eyes is is cropped crossed inward, which she's not a thing that he has.
So God knows what's going on. And he goes, you know what they say? If you want something done
right, you got to do it yourself. Oh boy, it shows footage from the movie. Yeah. And you know,
that movie sucks, man. Well, I shouldn't say it sucks. I never saw it. But I can't imagine it. We could
do it for the pod. I mean, it's got its fans. I think just because of how crazy it is. I've seen
the famous scene of like a vending machine shooting cans at people. That's pretty cool. Like it's a
cool idea. Yeah. But it's like, I don't know. I've never been a big fan of, you know, the machines
are taking over. It's just not that scary to me. Like, yeah. Like in a terminator sense, it could be fun
to watch, but like, it's not scary to me, you know, like, I don't know. It's kind of boring.
Agreed. I mean, I guess, I guess what was that movie, though, was kind of chilling. Not scary,
though. It was just kind of chilling. Uh, uh, Das, wait, Machina, what the fuck was it called?
X Machina. Oh, I loved X Machina. Yeah. That movie didn't scare me at all, but very well done.
The end left you disturbed, but yeah, not, not afraid. But anyway, what can you do, Pat?
What can you do? Nothing. Maybe the machines will come for us soon.
I think that's happening. The AI is advancing. Uh, while speaking of which, I just have, I mean,
this is a strange coincidence because I've skipped this news cycle for the last few episodes. But
did report that Henry Cavill was chosen as the next James Bond by AI casting program.
Wait, does that mean he's doing it? No, it was just more an article about like they have an AI
casting program. Okay. And it's selected Henry Cavill because these people want to do even less
fucking work. Yeah. At their jobs. Uh, Richard, he got 92 .3 % Richard Armitage got 92 %
Idris Elba got 90 .9%. Okay. Okay. I mean, these fucking executive cocks suckers. I mean,
I swear to God, do they do anything? They're just worthless. Um, I, I mean, who would you cast as Bond?
I think it's time to do an Idris Elba or something of that nature. I mean, we got to shake it up.
Who would I get? Well, I'm cursing them because of the program. Yeah. No, I know. Oh,
it sounded like you were, you sounded like you were maybe saying that I was cursing them for black
casting. No, no, no, no. Henry Cavill is a white man. Yeah. No, I thought you just when you said,
because you said it, it's about time we shake it up. Uh, I don't know. You know, I kind of like,
um, I don't care enough about James Bond to give a shit either way.
So, sure, I mean, same. Yeah. I don't really care. I would be more like, but, but however,
if they can't, if they did like another solo movie and they didn't cast somebody that looked like
Harrison Ford, I'd be upset because it would, it would fuck it up for me. Right. But Bond, I feel like
is, Bond's almost like Sherlock Holmes where I feel like it's, you know, that's so much wider net.
It's kind of like Dr. Who, who is currently female, which I thought was a cool, uh, choice
for that show because it's a doctor that regenerates. I mean, if you want to accept a female doctor,
sure, but I think a lot of people are going to have an issue. Well, it's a science fiction show.
My wife's a doctor, folks. Shut up. You said they're a doctor. I didn't know.
He's a P .A. P .A. position assistant. All right. Let's slow down. Same schooling. You know, you
scream it in about a review I saw. And I think this is a particularly interesting, uh, review for
fans of horror. Now, horror, much like comedy for years and years and years has been
shat upon. They, you know, when you look back at all the classic comedy, all the classic horror,
they never get a fair shake from critics. And I think what it is is that comedy is a young man's game
and critics are usually 50 plus young woman, young man's game. And the horror franchise,
a lot of people just hate horror. I mean, like Vince or a good friend won't watch a horror movie. And
there's lots of people like that. So when they're asked to go and see these things that that terrify
them and that they don't enjoy, they give them bad reviews. They can't look at them objectively and say,
well, that was a good movie. They just talk shit because they don't like being scared. And you shouldn't
be a critic, frankly, it is one of the top five genres of film that you can do. So I'm, I'm trying to
find this here and can't. Um, so, but what was the, what was the, the haunting of blind manner? Yes,
which I hear is not great, but I haven't seen what you did in the haunting of Hill House, correct? No,
too sexy for me. Uh, this is supposed to be sexy as well. Yeah, I'm just, I'm not into it. Um, but
anyway, um, but regardless of whether or not blind manner is any good, it does not excuse this review
by any stretch. Okay, I got it. Okay. So my, I, you know, uh, a good, a good, uh, a coin, even though I've
never met him. It's just one of, you know, a lot of times in this day and age, you say for Andy,
even though they're just Twitter people, but Scott Weinberg, one of the all time, uh, great authorities
on horror, one of my favorite critics, my former boss at a cinematical and a great follow on Twitter
for any fan of horror, but he posted this review of the haunting of blind manner gives it two stars.
And here's how it starts this review. I am no horror fan. I am quite frightened enough in and by
real life, thank you. And I stumble to over the large obstacle presented by the fact that ghosts and
their ilk do not exist and therefore cannot be scary in all caps. The horror of humanity begins a
long way before man's worst efforts. The supernatural doesn't even make it over the fear horizon.
Halloween is the most boring time of the year. Now that person should not be allowed to be a critic.
Plain and simple. And Scott very kindly because he knows that his fans would have immediately
attacked this person who wrote this. Does not tell us what the person's name is, but you can Google
and find the review. I mean, and Scott, what is Scott's link to the project? He's just a critic who
thought this was disgusting. His caption was also a critic. I thought you were saying he was
I'm sorry, I miss. And his is handled by the way is Scott E movie nerd. Him and Drume McWaney
formerly of Anna Cool did my favorite movie podcast other than this one, which was 80s all over,
where they reviewed every single movie that came out in the 80s. But they only made it to 85 and they
canceled the project. It was two time consuming, which sucks because I absolutely loved it. But
I mean, Scott is somebody who's devoted his life to horror, reviewing horrors.
He's slowly getting into horror production. I think he's very right to be furious about this.
A lot of people were steamed about this. If you want to be a movie critic, you can't hate a genre
of films. Plain and simple. Or then don't review that genre. I mean, I don't know. I mean,
at the very least. But look, I'll tell you why I think it's great because it's going to keep these
dumb mainstream critics away from the genre, which is what I want. I don't want this genre becoming
more homogenized. I don't want this genre becoming more mainstream. I don't want it to become
a consistent Oscar contender. I was thrilled that after Get Out One, the Oscar for Jordan Peel,
and I think that was awesome, that that happened. And I think that that was a necessary step forward
for particularly black filmmakers in movies period, but specifically the genre of horror.
So I think that was a great thing when it happened. I was also thrilled that it was not repeated
in the following years and didn't become a trendy thing for horror itself to get nominated
and to be contender. I like that every 30 years or so, one of these movies breaks through enough
that silence of the lambs, then before that was probably the extra system. After that,
our silence of lambs was Get Out. I don't want their hands on this. This is a great gift that
this is untouched. It's had its flare -ups in the mainstream, but horror should remain like
heavy metal for the real fans that get it and not for the people that don't understand it.
You know, well, the new term they use now for a movie like Get Out or basically any horror movie
that reaches critical acclaim is elevated horror and fans of horror really hate that term as well
because it's like, how do you decide what's elevated horror? You know, I just think it's gross and
basically it's like, well, you know, these movies tackle bigger themes through the guys of horror.
So do most horror movies. You just don't look for them. You find the gross outs too gross and you
throw it to the side, you know. Yeah. Or you're too dumb to get the message. Yeah. Now, famously,
the Twilight Zone, most of its episodes were able to air the way they were written because they wrote
the messages over the heads of the executives, right? So, you know, a lot of the time they don't get the
message. So good. And I do think elevated horror is a gross term, but good. I'm glad they have it.
I'm glad they look down on my favorite genre. I don't want them involved in it.
Period. I watched some, I think it was on the special features of a Cronumburg,
Blu -ray, but they talked about it early on in his career. There's this critic who just
sat on every single thing he did and it was a local Canadian critic and he met this guy on some
talk show or something and pulled him into a back room and was screaming at him. It was just like,
not only is what I'm doing different than what you claim that it's not intelligent or has no
worth, but you don't like horror. So I don't know why you're reviewing my movies, but why can't you at
least open your mind to see this is good for the Canadian film industry? This is good for, like,
you're Canadian. Like, why are you shitting on this and being so snobby? And I sort of get it. I mean,
when I was a film critic, I had to go watch Saw Five or something. Whatever one where they
whatever one was just particularly disgusting. And I had to step back and say, okay, you're grossed
out by this, but does it work as a horror movie? And even though I was never really a proper critic,
you know, I reviewed movies for sure, but I knew enough to say, okay, or if I'm going to see say
a kid's movie, it's not up my alley, would a kid enjoy it? Would it be good for a family? Etc.
You know, I just don't understand why some critics can't open their mind to that. It makes no
sense to me. And I think it leads to the only movies that get good reviews are movies that up till now,
middle -aged white dudes have enjoyed, because they are the vast majority of critics. And I think
that sucks. And it's reflected on Rotten Tomatoes as well. Well, speaking of Rotten Tomatoes,
shout out to Mark Alice, buddy of mine, big film guy, a lot of stuff on the internet, film -related
content on the internet reviews, whatnot, discussions. He's got the first ever Rotten Tomatoes podcast.
He's partnered up with a woman who I'm unfamiliar with, which is the only reason I'm blanking
on her name. I've known Mark for a while, so that's the only reason I remember his.
But they're doing a new podcast over there, and it's called Rotten Tomatoes is Wrong.
And basically, the premise is that they're taking on the biggest criticism that Rotten Tomatoes
gets, which is that it's wrong. Yeah, that's consensus is wrong. And doing a podcast about it, I assume
here, let me - It's not pulled out by Rotten Tomatoes, though. No, it is. Oh, it is. Interesting.
Yeah, Rotten Tomatoes, you know, looking the, staring down the barrel of the gun.
Jacqueline Coli is the woman's name. She's an editor at Rotten Tomatoes, and then Alice is,
you know, he's a comic. I know him from doing Doug Love's movies together. And he's also
contributing editor for Rotten Tomatoes. Anyway, excuse me, but they're doing this series where they
basically challenge. Let me read this episode, drop every Thursday, what do critics - what did critics
make of a cult classic before it earned cult status? How does the afterlife of a movie impact how we view
it? In this weekly podcast, the hosts and guests go deep and settle the score on some of the most
beloved and despised movies and TV shows ever made, directly taking on the statement we hear from so
many fans, Rotten Tomatoes is wrong. So episode one is Spider -Man 3, episode two is Mortal Combat,
episode three is Indiana Jones, Kingdom of the Crystal Skull, episode four is Sister Act Two.
They're doing an episode on Venom, so it's all polarizing movies, right? People really hate or
really like. That sounds cool, all right? Yeah. So anyway, yeah, that's pretty cool. I will check out.
Joe, I'd love to take you over to Pat's movie corner if I could. Pat, I will follow you to the end of
the earth. Okay. And I mean that. I'm gonna start since we're talking Hubey Halloween today,
which, you know, slight spoiler, I know you like more than I did, but it made me sort of go back and
watch a movie from Sandler's real golden age. And I remember, you know, Billy Madison, I saw
on an empty theater, laughed my ass off, happy Gilmore, you know, these movies all Tommy Boy 2 at the time,
all felt like very young dude movies, you know, everyone in the audience was this 10 to 20 -year -old dude
at the time. And then Wedding Singer hit. And I remember being like, wait a minute, this movie sold out
on a Friday night and I couldn't get into it. And it was huge. Then came Water Boy, which is
not good. And kind of a companion piece, I think, to Hubey because he's using the same sort of style of
voice. But Water Boy was this massive hit. And I was just like, oh, people just fucking love Adam
Sandler. Wedding Singer brought this whole new audience. Right. And really when he became like one of
the biggest stars in the world, like on a gym carry level, was the next movie Big Daddy. And I watched
Big Daddy on a Sunday afternoon, which is the exact perfect time to watch Big Daddy. And I was just
like, okay, how's this gonna hold up? I know that Gilmore and Madison have such a weird sense of
humor that they're always gonna be funny to me. They're so unusual and so funny. How's this one
gonna hold up? Because I remember that he had two gay friends, a gay couple. And I was like, I have
feeling these jokes are gonna be rough. Sure enough, I look it up. This movie was nominated for a
glad media award for outstanding film. Really. And Adam Sandler, who is, you know, kind of the hero of
frat guys at that time, even though he has a much weirder sense of humor than that,
that's treated very respectfully. So the first time you see the gay couple, and I remember the huge
scream it got when the two guys kissed each other, which is already a big swing in those days.
Right. They kiss each other. Actually, you know, I think I've told this in the pockets before, but I
saw in and out, which is a hilarious movie in the theater. And when Selik kisses Kevin Klein,
everyone in the audience left. Left? Everyone in the audience left. And it wasn't in and out.
It's a hilarious movie. But so Big Daddy, these guys kiss and Sandler's buddy turns to him. And he has
one friend who's really only function in the movie is to be like a little grossed out by his
friend's turning gay. And he turns to Sandler and he's like, oh god, they, you know, I'm fine with it,
but man, when they kiss, it's still really weird to me. And Sandler's like, what do you care?
And then he's like, what do you got a clan meeting to go to after this? And it's the first time they
address it. And I was like, wow, you know, it was surprisingly progressive. They make a couple
gay jokes throughout, you know, and they get some humor out of Sandler being a little uncomfortable
with them like being into each other's bodies and stuff. But it's funny. And it's how a guy like
that would react to it. It's actually probably a lot nicer than a guy like that would react to it
in 1999. But Big Daddy, to me, was a delight. The story was written by a different guy. And then
Sandler and Hurley, he clearly added all the comedy to it. Sandler and Hurley, he also wrote
Hubey Halloween. The difference is there's another guy credited on the screenplay and as writing
the story for the movie. And I think that's what these direct and netflix Sandler movies are missing
is a story. They are so sloppy and all over the place. And Big Daddy, the story is emotional. You
connect to it. You root for Sandler and the kid. It was hilarious to me how little John Stewart cared
about his child. I forgot that John Stewart is the father of the kid that Sandler is raising. And he's
like what? And just stays out of it. He doesn't even come home when he finds out that his son showed up
at his house. But Big Daddy is really funny. You know, you could have issues with some of it. He
makes fun of Leslie Mann the entire time because she used to be a hooters waitress, which is a little
slut Jamie and etc. But by and large, I thought Big Daddy was just a great, great comedy. The likes
of which we don't get anymore. And it confirmed to me that Sandler needs a little more quality control
in his movies. I mean, they are just kind of this loose string of jokes now. And all those early
movies, even something as dumb, quote dumb as Billy Madison or happy Gilmore, have strong stories.
They're cliched, you know, but they're strong storytelling. And I think that's what he's missing
now. Big Daddy to me held up in a big way. I laughed a lot. Buscemi is fucking hilarious. And when they
asked Buscemi why he is homeless in the movie. And he's like, I don't know, you know, all my friends were
getting into, you know, football and stuff. And I just got really into mushrooms. And you know,
let me put it this way. I watched Fantasia a lot. I mean, it's fucking hilarious. Buscemi is great.
The old drunk guy is fucking hilarious in the movie that keeps threatening to kick Sam was ass.
I loved it. I love Big Daddy. Carry on, Joe. I watched
books of blood on Hulu. I'm not going to make you watch this to review it for the podcast, Pat.
Didn't appeal. It sucked. It's not involved at all. It's based on his a few stories from his
books of blood books, which are higher anthology books. He put out sick volumes of these things.
It's not the first rendition of books of blood. There was a movie called The Book of Blood
that starred Doug Bradley amongst others that was released in the 90s. Or no, I think in like
2009, that actually was well received. I've never seen it. It's referred to as erotic horror,
which is not a surprise because Clive Barker does a lot of that. This one was not erotic horror.
It was just supposed to be horror. It's an anthology film. It is based on three
painfully boring Clive Barker stories that have certain moments, very fleeting moments of
seeming like they have direction or are moving somewhere. Yeah. And then just meander and go nowhere.
The construction of the film doesn't make sense. The way the stories are split apart doesn't make
sense. It's confusing. The first story's resolution comes at the very end of the film. The wrap -around
story resolution comes before that. The middle story is just the middle story's the only one with some
sort of like kind of a payoff, I guess. It's just a nothing film. The direction is fine. It's generic.
The writing is as bland and generic as you could imagine. The acting, the performances are fine.
Some of the actors are very good. Some of them are passable. It's just a fucking boring movie,
man. There's nothing to it. It goes on for way too long. It's every second of an hour and 45 minutes.
And I mean, by an hour and you're like, I can't do this, man. I was really struggling to get
through the end of it. But the conclusion I've come to, I think Clive Barker stinks.
I mean, because honestly, any adaptation I can think of outside of Hellraiser one and two,
and I've read the Hellbound Heart, the book, the movie's better than the book, I think.
I think he stinks. There's been so much made from his source material and it all sucks.
Now you could, we were talking about Hellraiser. No, not Hellraiser. But I mean, here's the thing too.
You know I love Hellraiser one, and two, and four. Hellraiser four out of the three of those is the
only one that even makes remote logical sense. One and two make no sense when you step back from them.
We've discussed it on here. I like the movies though. You know, it's another way these things like
Pinhead was never, you know, he gets all this credit for Pinhead. Pinhead was never supposed to be
the icon. He was never supposed to be the focus of that first movie. The fans loved it. So then
Pinhead became the foot. So he can't even credit him for having the foresight of creating an
amazing character. Yeah. His, in the book, Pinhead is not even, he's to the side. He's not even the
head centipede. You know, midnight meat train, boring, Lord of illusions, boring, nightbreed,
painfully fucking boring. I never saw raw head wrecks. I mean, it just doesn't look great to me.
Candyman is based on Barker, but from what I understand, I never read the source material for that,
but well, it seems to me from what I've read about the source material. It seems Candyman seems pretty
derivative. It doesn't seem like it really, wait, am I using derivative, right? It seems like it
goes a little more in its own direction. I might be wrong on that. But, you know, broken clock
is right twice a day. You know, I just don't know that Clive Barker, I mean, I read the Scarlet
Gospels. It was one of the worst books I've ever read from a writing standpoint. It was so,
sorry, that's okay. It was so poorly written to the point that there were rumors in the,
there were rumors in the horror community that he didn't even write it, that he was so sick,
that it was written for him. He released illness. I mean, there's a lot of different speculation. He's
claimed repeatedly that he got some sort of, I guess, septic infection from this dental procedure he
had done, and that, you know, reduced him to almost nothing, and nobody saw him for years.
If you see him now, he, from what I've seen, he's always seems to be sitting down and he does,
he doesn't look, he doesn't look terrible. He's a 70 year old man, but he looks a bit sickly.
There's some, there's some a speculation as well. Well, there's, the only reason there's a speculation
is because his ex -lover or husband, I think it was, has publicly said he gave me aids. Like,
that guy has made that claim. But that, it's crazy. If you go on Clive Barker's Wikipedia,
there is not a fucking stitch of any of that. It is gone, dude. He buried that stuff. So, look,
I don't know if there's any, you know me, I'm always wanted to say, you know, guilty or innocent
until proven guilty. I have no reason to not believe Clive Barker when he says that this is
bullshit. But there's a lot of speculation is that there's, it's a fact that there's a lot of
speculation. My point is, I could say in here, toxic shocks syndrome, which usually women get from
leaving tampons into long, but it says it was triggered by a trip to the dentist, which unloaded
a spillage of poisonous bacteria into his bloodstream. Yeah. And children, Isaac's return was children
with a corn, six, six, six. And you lobbed it to him right over the plate with the six, six, six,
yeah. And the return of Isaac and they still fucked it up. But I don't know, man. I mean, obviously,
the guys are capable writer. Like, I remember reading the hellbound heart and thinking it was very
well written, which is why I sort of believe the speculation that his, that scarlet gospels was not
written by him. Also, because it didn't deliver on any of the things he said it was going to deliver on.
But it's also just a sort of repulsive book. It's, it's, it tries so hard to shock, like, by the time
you get to a demon spitting in its own hand and jerking off to something, you're like, what is this?
You know, so I don't know, man. I don't know. I know Clive Barker is considered a horror icon,
but so is Dean Coons. And Dean Coons, in my opinion, couldn't write his way out of a fucking paper bag.
But phantoms, bro. He was the bomb and phantoms, bro. That's my favorite line, hands down and
gentle, but, but, uh, no, but, um, I don't know, man. I just don't, uh, I'm starting to, I'm really
starting to be curious. It's, it's a lot like a Danzig who will discuss on the next episode.
Oh, well, where the more Danzig gives me, the more I'm like, I don't know if you have talent.
That one thing you did was a fluke, but we'll get, we'll get to that. Yeah. Anyway,
don't waste your time on books of blood. All right. For my next two, I am going to talk about
the two best movies I have seen this year. Are my two favorite movies I've seen this year?
And I know there's not a lot of competition. It's basically Scoob, Bill and Ted three. I don't know
probably my favorite of the year is a documentary that is new to Netflix, Netflix called Dick Johnson
is dead. Um, should you watch that, John? I haven't yet. Okay. Uh, yeah, I freely wept watching
this movie. I was so thankful to be watching it alone. Um, I think a big part of it is I'm doing
sober October. I've had no alcohol, no weed and I don't have anything numbing me anymore.
But man, I just was falling by the end of this thing. And Dick Johnson is dead. It is
a movie, a documentary, basically about a woman whose mother passed away of complications
from very severe Alzheimer's. And had I known this was about Alzheimer's, I wouldn't have watched it.
I don't, it's a big fear of mine and I don't like watching anything to do with Alzheimer's. But
um, as I showed you, Joe, the movie has the worst poster I've ever seen in my life. It is,
it is this man Dick Johnson's head on two crossed bones. It makes no sense. It makes it look like
a stupid comedy, which it isn't. I don't get it. But Dick Johnson's dead is done by Kirsten Johnson.
Kirsten Johnson, excuse me, Kristen Johnson is lady from third rock from the sun.
Anyway, uh, basically what she decided to do was, okay, we all had to watch
your, her dad's wife and her mother pass away through Alzheimer's and it was miserable.
It looks like her dad Dick Johnson is going to die of Alzheimer's as well. He's starting to have
signs when the movie begins. He's slipping a little bit. Let's try to not make this the miserable
experience that our mother's death was and what she decides to do is stage increasingly inventive
almost final destination style death scenes with her father in them and he agrees to do it.
So this is like a, you know, a 75 year old man and they are using a little film crew and stunt people
creating these kind of insane deaths for him and you'll be watching this documentary and then
something horrific will happen to this old man and you gasp and then remember, oh right,
they're doing this kind of for fun. So it's not going to be for everybody. I recommend it to my dad
and he was infuriated by it and he was like, it's very different for a 65 year old man watching this
than somebody who's 40, you know, like you shouldn't have recommended this to me. It got all angry with
me, um, but, you know, he's also criminally insane. Uh, this man is so adorable, so sweet, so funny.
I'm talking about Dick Johnson, how my father, uh, I love this man so much and it's clear that his
daughter loves him so much and he loves her so much. And the fact that he's willing to go along with
this, she's like, my dad has always supported everything I've ever done and basically I don't want
to spoil anything so I won't, but it's a standard documentary basically of a guy, you know, it covers
the span of about five years and you see his condition getting worse and worse and it's very sad,
but it's also balanced out by these increasingly crazy, funny, interesting sort of death reenactments.
And the takeaway for me really is like, death doesn't have to be this really sad thing. We can have
some fun with it and it was really her only way of coping and grieving and I was blown away by it,
frankly, they wind up doing, you know, certain things that I think people might have an issue with
as his condition gets worse, he starts to have kind of issue with having to reenact his death again
and again, but I've never seen anything like this in my life. Uh, it was a complete original. I love
this man. I love their relationship. Uh, and if you're not crying by the end of it, I would go get
yourself checked out or get on some sort of meds, but it's my favorite movie of the year. It blew me away.
All right. Uh, I'll continue on with a theme of movies I didn't enjoy.
I finally watched for the first time of my life start to finish. Robin Hood men in tights.
Oh, Christ. I watched it recently too. It's one of the worst movies I've ever seen in my life.
Terabyte was cringing through the entire thing, cringing. It opens with a rap
of six black guys dressed up like Robin Hood. I guess they're supposed to be the Mary men,
but they don't seem to be around for the rest of the movie except for in the rap numbers,
which pop up here and there. Uh, and, and you think it's going to kind of tie into Dave
Chappelle's character because Chappelle does very much play like a sort of like, you know, out of,
what am I, what am I saying? Like, uh, he's like a street -wise guy. Like he's, he's, he's way too
contemporary for what the movie is and that's the gag of it all, right? Uh, so you think somehow maybe
he's going to tie in with like this hip hop crew. It's not, it's just in there because Mel
Brooks, I guess, thinks it thought it was funny and clearly wrote the rap himself, right? Oh,
like I could write a rap, you know, uh, uh, guarantee Mel Brooks has never listened to a rap song
start to finish never. Yeah. So, um, it's just this whole thing, not one joke is funny, not one
part in the movie makes sense. Uh, none of it is well done. Everybody bombs.
I tell him he's doing a godfather spoof 20 years after the godfather.
I, I hated it so much. I hated it. I had to watch it in chunks because it was wearing me out.
It was wearing my spirit out and I had great admiration for Mel Brooks. You know, he's got an
incredible career and he's done a lot and I've been become friendly with Max's son over the years
and Max does a lot of great hard work. Max is truly impeccable and you know how I feel about
and bankrupt. I mean, and the film that so. And I said it on this podcast before, that so is a better
film than anything Mel Brooks has ever done and rewatching or watching Robin Hood Minotites and then
not sure. I love young Frankenstein. Uh, but that's really a collaboration between him and June
Wilder. Mm hmm. I watched life stinks recently. It's terrible. I've seen Dracula dead and loving it.
It's terrible. I rewatched space balls. It's enjoyable to a point. I would also classify
space balls as terrible having just rewatched his whole catalogue. Uh, the producers really funny
until like the 35 minute mark and then I'm like, I don't care anymore. As soon as they go to Mr.
Belvedere's house and he's like in the dress, that's what I'm like, I don't care anymore. Yeah.
Gene Wilde is great written with five people, including the great Richard prior. Right. And even
saddles for me is it's half, you know, a halfway point. I'm like, I don't care anymore. Yeah.
Young Frankenstein really is the only one straight through. I've never been a high anxiety fan.
I never had any interest in silent movie. Um, it sucks. Uh, man. And I'm, I'm like sitting. I
know Mel Brooks is funny. I'm just like, wait, and he's a great producer. He produced the elephant
man. He produced the fly. But I'm just like, what? See, not good at making movies. Would I miss
something here? Or was it just so of a certain time that I like his, I like about half the history
of the world, I rewatched it sucks. I think a lot of it is the palest scene, the
palest scene with Dom Delewee's in history of the world is, yeah, it to me is, is tour de force
funny. And then I'm going to be, I'm going to be doing all of his movies. I just watched everything
he's ever done on a, on a Pat solo corner. Um, but I was appalled by almost everything. I watched
the 12 chairs for the first time. You know, it's a mess. Uh, yeah, I, I watched that recently
for the first time too. I wasn't into it. Um, anxiety. I, you know, as a, as a hitchcock obsessive,
I was like, okay, I'm going to love this sputanope. Uh, you know, it's all pretty weak. And I don't
know. I guess it's just of its time. I barely. He's also one of the first people doing these
celeb cameos in lieu of jokes, you know, which is now a lot of what comedy is. You know, he's kind
of the pioneer of that. And apparently, um, the story when the ambankroff was, I, I think, I think I
think I have this correct, that she just kind of got it out of her system with FATSO. And then just,
you know, was cool and was like, I want to be a mom and whatever, which is a shame because I think
for that to be her one effort as a writer director, there was so much more there that she could have
done, I think. And I would have loved to have seen. Uh, and her acting it is tremendous, you know,
but, uh, I think that's the thing that I like about that film versus what I dislike about
many of the male Brooks movies. Like, if you're going to make something
that is essentially without heart, I mean, you know, it's in, it's in, the comedy of it all is sweet
and funny and endearing, I guess. But like, you know what I mean, when I say without heart,
like, these are not real people were watching. These are not real, you know, we're not relating to
any of this. It's, uh, Woody Allen once said in the most, uh, arrogant thing I've ever heard of
him being said, say my early films were merely armatois upon which to hang jokes. But you know what I
mean? And it's why I'm like, abattoir? Abattoir. What did I say? Armatois, sorry, abattoir. I was like, what,
I was like, maybe that's a word I don't even know. I listen, when I heard him say that 15 years ago,
and I did, I was like, what the fuck is an abattoir? I had to look it up. Uh, but anyway, so I
fucked it up. Anyway, can you believe by the way that James Cameron is making five new abattoir movies?
Thank you. But I hate the early Woody Allen movies for the same reason. There's nothing to
cling to. There's no, but then you get a movie like Annie Hall, and you go, now there's something I can
sink my teeth into. And these other things are very of the time. And, and they don't, they don't resonate.
They don't hold up. So, but what's interesting is that, you know, people who get much less acclaim,
Zucker, Abraham, Zucker, naked gun is still lentlessly fucking funny. Still, and I wonder if, but
what scares me is did we see it at the right time? Well, when I show it to people, it still hits.
And I would never even show somebody some of this male brook shit.
You know, I feel bad. The guy's a legend. I really admire him. He worked with Sid Cesar for
Christ. Like, I just, I don't get it. I don't know. I don't know. I, I used to love space balls.
It's bad. When they say, let's comb the desert and they cut to that giant comb, I, I had to pace my house.
The only, I told you this and you disagreed. The only character that still makes me laugh in it is
Colonel Sanders. And it's mainly for the part, when, when dark helmet is shooting the guy in the
dick with the laser beam. And it cuts away to Colonel Sanders. And he's, he's like, he looks like he's
coming in his pants. He's like, like that. Yeah, like that's really funny to me.
The part is really funny to me when he, when Michael Winslow won't stop doing like the noises.
And he like, like, he gets so, Rick Moran's gets so mad at these smashes the intercom unit.
There are, there are moments that really, really make me laugh in a lot of his movies. But overall,
I guess what I'm saying is is, I don't know that I think he's ever made a really good movie. You
know, the producers, young Frankenstein is a masterpiece. But I think, yes, I think you have to
acknowledge that that was more than half wilder. You have to say clearly, I mean, his performance is
what is what really sends it over the top. Did you know they were supposed to follow that up with
Jackal and Hyde with Wilder doing, I mean, it would have, it would have melted my brain. Yeah.
To see Wilder shifting from like the suite to the crazy, I wouldn't, I don't think I'd be able to
sit through it. I'd be, I'd be dying laughing so hard. Yeah. But well, young Frankenstein in addition
is just a beautifully shot and, you know, like everything about it is perfect. Whereas, you know, like
these other movies just are, are kind of trash. And I don't know when he just started deciding
Dick Van Patten was hilarious. The scenes of Dick Van Patten in Robin Hood and Space Balls are
enough to make you impotent. Yeah. I've never liked Dick Van Patten in anything. No.
I mean, you get a Dick Van and then, and then it's the patent and not that you're like,
oh, Christ man, you got to be kidding me. Look, having watched that movie, the comic with Dick Van
Dyke that Carl Reiner did, I'm prepared to say Van Dyke might not be great either. But my, my last
pick is just an amazing movie that I am so glad I watched called Swallow. I heard that was great.
It is so good. It's on showtime right now, or, you know, you can order it or whatever, but
it blew me away. It is essentially the directorial debut of this duty as a couple other kind of
minor things in his past. But Swallow, the star is this woman, Hailey Bennett, who I think,
if they push her and they won't, should and will get nominated. They won't do it. But she gives
such an amazing performance. I don't know who else they're going to nominate for Best Actress this
year. What are we talking about? The movie is basically, it feels a lot like Cronenburg,
which is always a good thing. It's kind of, it's kind of body horror, but you also couldn't call it
horror. It's not scary. It's not even necessarily a thriller. It was just a very sort of tense,
unusual look at basically how men feel they control women's bodies, which also makes it
have some similarities, of course, to, like, handmaid's tail or something like that. Rose Mary's
baby. But basically, this woman, Hailey Bennett, is Mary. She's a beautiful young woman. She is
kind of a kept woman. Her husband makes all the money. They don't really tell you, but he appears
to be some sort of stockbroker. They do tell you, but I just forgot. He's like a stockbroker
type guy. Total douche, you know, very concerned about his body, his clothes, his appearance,
and just wants her to kind of stay at home, but also punishes her for that. And at some point,
and you don't know why she's doing it, and then eventually you start to realize it's because it's the
only way she can control herself. She's pregnant now, and she doesn't like having this guy's baby
inside of her. It gives him more control. So what she starts doing is swallowing objects around
the house. This, from reviews I've read, I think some people have real issues with this,
and some people didn't bother. It didn't bother me. But she, like, at first she swallows a marble,
and then more and more of the objects she's swallowing get sharper and more dangerous. And I think
some people have a real, real tough time watching that kind of stuff. It didn't bug me. But it's her
sort of taking back control of her body through swallowing these things. And as her husband,
and her husband's parents, the dad played by David Rache, who was a sledgehammer, you know,
the guy who was the funniest part of Burn After Reading. Right. But the parents are just perfectly
cast, and they don't like her doing this. I mean, they're like your nuts, you know, they try to
basically assert their control over her. And what she's doing is nuts, but it just sort of in her mind
is like the only way she can control her life. I know that's a very strange setup. I don't know how it
was pitched, but this movie is shot, written, and directed so well, and has such a control over it.
It's just the work of somebody who knew exactly what he wanted to do. The guy's name is Carlo
Mirabella Davis. It's definitely somebody to watch. As has Haley Bennett, she gives my favorite
performance of the year. I think, you know, if I'm comparing something to Kronenberg, it's pretty
fucking good. And I think it earns the comparison. It also is similar to Safe, the really great Todd
Haynes movie with Julianne Moore, where you're just sort of inside this woman's head, and it's not
necessarily the most fun place to be, but it's really good. The third act takes you into some strange
new places that I won't go into. I just completely loved it, and I urge you to check it out. I'm
intentionally being a little vague about it, so as not to spoil it, but man, I was, I'll say hypnotized
by a joke. All right. For my third and final film, and I'm just going to kind of use this as a
transition or a segue, I sort of went back and admittedly skimmed, so this isn't really a review.
Admittedly skimmed through all of the happy Gilmore, or sorry, happy Madison films on Netflix. Yeah.
The doover, the sinister, or this ridiculous six father of the year, those three. All of them,
not good. All of them bad. Yeah. At one point I texted you, and I said, I don't understand, like Adam
Sandler is still hilarious. We know he's still hilarious. David Spade is hilarious. We know that
why are these movies so fucking bad? Why? I don't understand. Why aren't they funny? Nothing about them
is good. And I kind of did this as preparation for QB Halloween. Thinking, this is where we're at
with these movies. I admire that he's doing things that he's having a good time with his friends.
I think that's cool. Anything that's going to keep a guy like David Spade working, or whatever,
help keep a guy like that working, that makes me happy because I'm a big fan. I'm a big fan of a lot
of the people that are tied into these movies. Fred Wolf. I don't know if he's worked on any of the happy
Madison ones, but he works with Sandler sometimes. I like this crew. I really do. I just didn't understand
why these movies are never fucking funny. They have one or two moments that get you, and that's it.
You know, there's a great line in a, in a father of the year where they're asking, they're like,
dad to David Spade, they're like, do you remember that kid so and so? And he's like, no, I don't
remember him, man. And they go, yeah, you do. You used to throw batteries at him and tell him that
Christ did it, which is a funny fucking joke. Yeah. But then like, that's it. Like, that's it. Like,
the scene in, uh, doover when David Spade smells the key that was up the guy's ass, and then pukes
immediately. Yeah. That's really funny. But then like, that's kind of to a great puke joke, and
he'll be Halloween. Yeah. It made me laugh. Yeah. So anyway, we're, we're, we're, this was all
prep for hubi Halloween. And like I said, with the theme of my movie quarter, it was have these
people that I admire so much lost their stride. Uh, and I will say, and Pat gave a bit of a spoiler
earlier, our film today, hubi Halloween, I watched it expecting to hate it 100%. I agreed to review it
only because I thought it was going to be something to make fun of. Uh, and I'd be sitting here going,
oh my god, what a train wreck. Uh, I will say right out of the top. I, I really enjoyed it. I
really loved it. Uh, there's going to be a lot of spoilers right now. But the thing opens
immediately with Ben Stiller reprising his role from happy, happy Gilmore without a joke. Um, yeah,
I mean, it could have been a bit funnier, but I thought it was still fun. I can't believe they got
him to come in for a role that wasn't funny. It's like he's so funny and happy Gilmore,
so funny. Right. Um, but that, that excited me. And I was like, okay, like maybe we're going back
to the roots a little bit here. And I still didn't know, think that I was going to like it, but I was
like, okay. And then I don't know, I found myself around the 20 minute mark having had laughed three or
four times. And I was like, I think I think this movie is funny. Uh, one of the things making me,
you know, like you said, the intro to cubius him on the bike and I forget somebody throws something
out of me throws up immediately. He, he puts the raw eggs in his thermos drinks them and that's right.
That's right. An immediate puke is always very funny. Yeah. Um, yeah, I, I have watched all of these
happy medicines. They're wrong. Missy, you know, and murder mystery. The last one, I've watched them all.
And the ridiculous six, you know, they're all hovering around the C minus range.
Um, and I guess the reason I watch them is I miss comedy. The only person really making
comedies, uh, in, in the traditional sense is Sandler now. The other ones don't really get made.
Rogan will have one now and again. But they've almost been wiped out. I've talked about this before
on the pod. It's very sad to me. Um, and I love that Sandler tries. I like everyone in the movies.
I'm rooting for them. Um, you know, Rob Schneider by all accounts of despicable person. Kevin James
by all accounts, even worse person. But they can still make me laugh. I mean Schneider is hilarious
in, uh, in big daddy, for example, even though it's as usual, he's playing a foreigner and it's a
little rough. But, um, I thought this movie was just such a mess. And it's written by Sandler and
Tim Hurley. So Tim Hurley has written on most Sandler projects and wrote some of the funniest,
SNL sketches ever, usually with Sandler or Farley or whatever else. So these jokes pop up and you're
like, whoa, that was a weird, really well written joke. And that always happens, no matter how bad
the movie, there'll be some little moment that's really funny and interesting like you're saying.
But for me, this just didn't work. And people really love it. So maybe I'm wrong. But like,
a Sandler is in his early 50s. And for him to still be doing this, let's be honest, mentally handicapped
character and voice. And then everyone to be making fun of a guy who's clearly mentally handicapped
is weird. And I don't understand how Sandler gives himself no comedy. In this movie, Sandler is
in every scene, but he's not funny. I don't think he's playing. I didn't get the mentally handicapped
vibe. I got that he was a very, you know, sort of sheltered guy. And maybe he had, you know, some,
he suffered some traumatic experiences in his life, you know, but I didn't take it as a
but imagine you meet a 53 year old guy who lives with his mom who talks like that and is obsessed
with like policing Halloween. And carries a, carries a Swiss army thermos around. Right, right, right.
You'd go this guy's mentally handicapped. Right. Well, I think that was also kind of the point
of the movie is is that everybody bullies him. And then he, it's like you said, in big daddy, he's
the guy that shows you that's not cool, you know? Yeah. So I think that's, you know, but but I know,
I didn't agree with you on that because you, you would say that to me before about Sandler,
because I said, why can't he just do like another Billy Madison or something? And you said, or,
no, I said it about Jim Carrey. Why doesn't Jim Carrey just do another fucking funny movie, man?
Like I rewatched Ace Ventura recently. I was crowning. Yeah. And you were like, he's too old.
It's a young man's game. I was like, I look, Jim, if Jim Carrey did that now convincingly,
I would enjoy it. I don't have a problem with it. You know, he's kind of like I saw him do as
fucking Biden again on SNL. And it's just rough that you hit an age. I think where that kind of
extreme physical comedy is rough. It just is. I don't know why. But Gary Lewis went through the
same thing. Here's where this is the only reason I disagree with you about Carrie. Because he keeps
doing it a step short of what it is. Yeah. Don't do a version of it as Biden because you want to
prove to us that you're able to act and play by just do the thing. You know what I mean? Like
with Sandler, I do agree with you on this. Like just be, if Sandler was running around that movie,
doing like the whole, we saw it on a special like he was doing the thing again where he's like,
and it's fucking funny still. You know what I mean? So it's like just do that. Do a movie of that.
Stop wrapping it in this fucking other thing where it's like, oh, but he's a secret agent.
And he's actually pretty cool. And he does get the ladies. Just play a fucking idiot again. It's
funny when you do it. And to me, Sandler is not a character comic. You know, like he is so likable
in Big Daddy or Billy Masner happy. He's playing idiots, but he's not doing this. The the weird
voice. And in this one, he's clearly trying to do a different voice from the water boy, but it's
kind of exactly the same. It's also very little Nikki. These characters don't work for me. And
especially the older he gets where this movie kind of shines is in some of its supporting cast,
but it's not in the big name supporting cast. Like I was excited to see Boshemi. Boshemi doesn't get a
joke. Um, he's got amazing jokes in all of his other Sandler movies. I think and Liotta shows up.
Liotta, I thought was hilarious. Liotta, what these movies need more of is somebody telling him
what an idiot he is. And Liotta does that pretty well here. Liotta, Liotta is lying at the end when
he's like, when I was in eighth grade, I was diagnosed with dyslexia. Yeah, I was just dumb.
Yeah. And he really tries. And he's still acting as if he's in like a Scorsese movie, which is
fun to watch. June Squibb, best known for her role in the pilot of CBS is living biblically.
She's very funny. You know, next to me, by the way, yes, alongside me. She says that whenever she's asked
about. Yeah. You know, my wife laughed at every disgusting shirt that June Squibb wore. I did a
Google search for I shaved my balls for this. I would I want the shirt. I want to get the shirt.
You could probably get the shirt. Yeah. Um, but time and time, I get like, you see,
Keenan and immediately I perk up. Keenan has never failed to make me laugh. He's not given funny
things to do. Kevin James is wearing a truly ludicrous bearded hair combo that doesn't match. He's
one of your Hershey kisses. No, I only have 30 left. You know, there were some funny lines.
Uh, I thought I told you this. The joke of the movie for me was the Schneider piss joke. I mean,
Schneider funny. When, yeah, when Boshemi goes, nobody pisses like you and he just goes, I'm pissing
right now and the camera pulls back and he's I was like, you got me on that one, man. The dog eating
its own shit made me laugh really hard. Uh, I think stuff like that's really funny. I didn't think
Sam, what no, Sam, we had a few funny. See, he was that that one scene is really funny.
When he's talking to Kevin James and Kevin James, like giving him the protocols, being the undercover
and he's like, no, don't get excited. And he goes, huh? And he goes, you're not going to talk to me.
I'm saying that that was really funny. I really liked that character. I thought it was really sweet
and endearing. Again, I'd prefer a Billy Madison type, but I think it's really sweet and really
endearing. Uh, he was, he was, he was touching. Uh, so I liked it and I was watching this film going,
is he our finest working actor? The fact that I'm believing him as this character right now,
right after uncut James is astounding. That's astounding. Yeah, I mean, I can't believe he did
this after uncut James, but he said he was going to. I wish there are, there are so many out of work
comedy writers right now, myself included. I mean, like, I just wish they would let somebody else
into the mix. The guy who wrote murder mystery wrote zodiac. You know, like,
Sam learned early, he can sprinkle all their funny and weird shit on these movies,
but they need the base of a story. So like, Bishemi and Schneider, that story is disconnected
from the movie entirely. You know, it really has no relevance or point at all.
Well, it's the, it's a misdirection plot. You know, it's, it's, you know, I can't, he wants his
friends working and I get that. You know, but like, George Wallace, oh good, George Wallace,
oh good, Keenan, and then they don't have anything. I see, I, let me jump in. I disagree.
Wallace's thing really was funny, when he goes trickle -treat, give me something good.
Okay. It's funny. The thing is, here's the thing. I, I hear what you're saying. The,
the way I saw it was at, there were so many cameos. Everybody got one good one off. Yeah,
there was like off to the, then Tim Meadows got to do his thing. Then my Rudolph got to do her thing.
That's what I was building to is that Meadows and my Rudolph are funny throughout and I get the
feeling they might let them improv a little bit. But yeah, I mean, when my Rudolph goes, she's,
her line is, you be, do be careful. She goes, you be a doobie. I mean, I was cackling at that.
But Rudolph and Meadows, when Meadows came up with that hair, I go, is he wearing a wig? Because it's
Halloween or is this supposed to be his hair? And when you learn that that's his hair, it's like,
guys, what world are we living in? And same with Kevin James' hair. I did it. I said to my friend,
Phoebe, I was like, it's the first wig comedy. I've seen it a long time. Yeah, I was, I liked it.
It was you know, I love Kingpin, the all -time masterpiece of wig comedy. Yeah. But this was too much.
I, I liked that it kind of, I liked that it kind of harkened back to some earlier sandwiched
stuff. You know, including the wig thing made me laugh. Like I liked that it had characters in it.
I was watching clips from Little Nikki and I never wanted to see Little Nikki because I don't like
that character at all. But the clips in that I was like, this is kind of funny, man. Like there's
like a funny danger field thing and stuff. And I was like, maybe that's funny too. But you know,
I liked that this Ted characters that were reminiscent of like, Farley as the bus driver.
I liked that the bully was also, oh, Doyle was one of the, he was related to the, I liked all those
little Easter eggs. I just hadn't seen him do anything like this in a long time. You know, for,
dude, for, for 15 years all we got was like, 51st dates Adam Sandler. Yeah, where you're just like
Christ on the cross, man. I remember little Nikki being unwatchable. But along this kind of movie
lines, I think his most underrated is you don't mess with the Zohan, right, by him and Smigel.
That movie's pretty fucking funny. But for me, I put this, you know, unfortunately right in the same
bin as all of his other happy Madison stuff. But people love it more, you know, I get it.
It certainly has a charm. There's a lack of Halloween comedies. I mean, in a world where I used to
watch Ernest scared stupid every year, like we need more of these. It's better than Hocus Pocus. But
I think as a Halloween comedy, it's one that I'll watch again. I might even watch it again this
Halloween. But I liked out of all the out of all of the happy Madison movies. What I liked about
this one was he was finally again, I kind of wish he would just do it all in instead of under the
guise of a voice and whatever. But he was finally just being funny Adam Sandler again. Yeah, he wasn't
playing a mercenary that was like actually really cool. And because he was so cool, he couldn't be
funny. Even in ridiculous six, he's playing like the white man raised by Indians, but like he's like
the he's the cool guy. He like knows his way around well a knife. And I don't want to see that
like in an Adam Sandler comedy. I don't want him being the backbone. And also the straight man.
You know, I want fucking, you know, I want to tell you what, thumbs me out. Why? And it's got to be
his choice. Why is Norm McDonald not in any of these things? It's definitely got to be Norm's choice.
I think Norm has become a very reclusive hermit who doesn't like leaving his house. And he doesn't know
how to drive. But he tours doing stand up. Yeah, I think that's to sort of keep alive. You know, I
don't know. I think he hates how he looks and doesn't want to be put on. I don't know, but he's a weird
dude. These movies definitely need Norm McDonald, though. You're absolutely right. They miss him.
They miss him almost as much as they miss Farley. Jesus Christ. Yeah, I don't understand why he's
never in these. I mean, his delivery in Billy Madison, when he's like that when it just cuts to them
shit faced. Yeah, at the pool. And he goes, where's Billy? He's at school. Don't you remember? And he
just goes, oh yeah. Yeah. I mean, it's a nothing line that he makes hilarious somehow. Yeah. But
anyway, my hog's up for Hoobie. Hoobie. Hoobie. Hoobie Halloween. I liked it. And my hog is down,
but I mean, I will say I get why people like it and his movies just generate a lot of good feeling
even when they're bad because you can just tell that he's a good man surrounded by people that like
each other a lot. The best scene probably is the same with Shaquille O 'Neil and Betsy Sidero, which is
I actually won't spoil it. It's it's well worth because I just sat with my jaw on the floor.
But yeah, that was that was I was really laughing during that scene. Yeah. That got me.
You're not going to be furious with yourself for watching the movie. No. No. And I think like you
said, closing thought for me is enough Halloween. I think it could even even if you don't think it's
the funniest movie or whatever. I think the Halloween charm alone could carry you through it.
Like I think it's it's you know, it just gets you in the spirit. Certainly. And it's nice seeing
people on camera like having a Halloween where you're just like, yeah, as you stare out your window
with a fucking mask on. Anyway, that's it for the show today. Folks, up next, another Halloween special,
we got Dan Zigg's Verotica. Oh, strap in for that one. Strap on for that one. Oh boy. Oh boy.
Um, I joderos a comedy on Twitter and Instagram. Joderos a comedian on Facebook.
I don't really have anything to plug right now, except for the without a country podcast with myself
and Corinne Fisher. Reviewing the news, trying to find some sanity and middle ground amongst all
the tribalistic outlets out there. You can find us on gas digital. Use couple to use promo code
WAC to get yourself a free two weeks of the network. I have the Patrick Walsh on Twitter,
Instagram and letterboxed if you guys are going insane in the home. I think all all social media has
kind of lost its charm for me except letterboxed. If you're listening to this, you're probably a fan of
movies. So sign up. It's fun. It's a good way to kind of it. I don't know. As I've said before,
it's the only social media app that doesn't make me want to die. Um, we will be back next time
with Veronica. We will see you next time and we will see you in hell.