I'll see you at hell!
When the sun and your screams break out of pain on my dreams you know I'll say
hey, hey.
I'll see you at hell!
Folks, it's Will see you in hell with a special themed episode.
My name is Joe DeRosa.
My name is Patrick Walsh.
Hello everybody and welcome to Will see you in hell.
Joe, what are you drinking there, a little spin drift.
I got a water -loo, sparkling water strawberry flavored.
Water -loo.
Zero calories, zero sugar, zero flavor.
No, but these things like the zero calories, zero sugar flavored waters, it just tastes like
there's the idea of the fruit suggestion, not even a suggestion of the fruit, but a suggestion
of the starburst version of the fruit, like a faint breath of it at the end of the
memory of a skiddle you once had when you drank it.
Yes.
What are you drinking on your end?
Well, now that I see you, I weirdly have one of those things that you're drinking because
somebody brought them over the other night as mixers.
But I'm going to grab something now, you can, you'll do what they call vamp while I grab
a beverage and what better place to vamp folks than a horror podcast.
I'll be right back.
Vamp was, of course, the movie starring Grace Jones where she played a vampire that was
forced to go out and stretch when TV shows needed extra time.
Folks, you got Joe DeRosa here, flying solo for a second while Paddy Walsh gets himself
a water -loo beverage, I am drinking a water -loo because I drank way too much alcohol last night.
That's what I did.
I met an old friend of mine at a steakhouse in New York called the Strip House.
And we were in reunion mode.
We started out with pre -dinner cocktails, hit the bottle of wine during the dendin, went
to the bar, third friend met up with us, and then we all went to karaoke in a private
room.
It was a scene, babe.
Wait, when I went to go get my beverage, you were talking about Grace Slick.
This was an evening with you and Grace Slick out doing karaoke.
I was talking about Grace Jones.
You missed my great, Grace Jones bit where I said vamp is a movie where Grace Jones plays
a vampire who is, whose job is this is to stretch during TV shows when they need extra time.
It's a double play on it.
But no, I said I'm drinking the water -loo because of last night I had too much alcohol because
I went out with some old friends I hadn't seen.
And you know, here we are.
I got to, after this, I got the new episode of Obi -Wan came out today.
I'm very excited because spoiler alert, it has been confirmed that today's episode contains
not only Darth Vader's return, but James Earl is back doing the voice.
So that's all I know about the episode.
I'm very excited to watch it as soon as we finish recording here.
And then I got to go to the bar.
This is James Earl Ray, the man suspected of murdering Jonathan Kennedy.
James Earl Ray is chucky, I believe.
Who am I thinking of?
Jack and not Jack.
Well, Jack Ruby.
Jack.
Pat and I was walked.
Lee Harvey.
Yes.
So what did I say?
James Earl Ray is chucky is the guy, the character that that becomes chucky is James
Earl Ray.
No, wrong.
James Earl Ray was a he assassinated Martin Luther King Jr.
Well, who the hell's chucky then?
What if Charles Lee Ray is chucky?
Charles are we later.
What if they weirdly name chucky after the man who killed Martin Luther King Jr.
Like as a weird political statement?
I mean, that does seem like there's a reference there.
I think it's Charles Lee Ray anyway, but then I got to go after this.
I got to go to we're having a what they call in bar terms in the world of bars.
Pat, it's called a spend.
And what happens is one of your sponsors comes in and spends a little money at an event
that features their product.
So you always end up drinking at that.
And you know, I'm back to the I can't drink tonight.
They got to go on TV tomorrow.
All right.
What are you going to be on TV for?
I'm doing the Greg Gutfeld show on Fox.
Everybody calm down.
I've known Greg for a long time.
And I'm going on to do a segment about Joey Roses and the sandwiches.
Oh, nice.
But bliss for us.
But but that's not really picking me up to 1 p .m.
You know, you're drinking right now.
You just look down and realize you're drinking.
Yeah, I do that.
Okay.
No, you're going to wind up drinking.
I can hear it in your voice.
It's very obvious to me.
I'm drinking the white claw right now.
It's literally 12 11 p .m.
So we're just into the.
Not even I guess technically afternoon, we can call it.
But it's in that new hour.
It's in the air, man.
It's sunny out.
Yeah.
The shorts are getting shorter.
Days are getting longer.
Yeah.
And the baby's getting horny air.
She said, yeah.
Something's getting harder.
Something's getting wetter.
There you go.
Come on, Joe.
I said something.
I didn't say what.
I.
The other day,
while Memorial Day,
I was going up.
I had 80 nothing.
All day.
It was about 9 p .m.
And I was high.
And I was like Pat, you're stoned.
You're starving.
What you've been doing this.
Keto don't go messing everything up.
Stick to the plan ahead.
Get yourself road to history chicken.
Get the fuck out of here.
So I walk in and what do they have but those amazing, you know, they're like, I guess you'd
call them shortbread cookies with like icing on top.
They do them for each holiday.
Yeah.
Jesus.
I do.
I mean, just the most, almost like melt, like melting in your mouth, like, like, they, but
they actually do it.
It's not just my expression.
Baby come to me, starts playing in your head, and then for some reason, who's that lady?
Because I'm sexualizing it.
No, but so I haven't really with, you know, with a couple of very mild actually, but only
a couple of little slip -ups here and there.
I've been on this kettle and I was just staring at it.
Like I stopped at my tracks staring at it.
Then I looked to the left and I saw something that got me even more engorged.
They had, they were offering a 410 red, red, white and blue with the cake frosting, which is
my favorite food, like, like grocery store sheet cake frosting.
Yeah.
So what's that mean?
What's that mean?
What am I trying to say?
You know, like a snack pack, the four puddings together.
So this was like that, a plastic container, but it had four holsters.
Okay, I got you.
And each holster was filled to the brim with icing, red, white, blue, and then the fourth
was sprinkles.
Oh, Jesus.
And it was a two -ford deal where you would get that, and then a plastic container of the
plain shortbread cookies so that you yourself could cover them with the frosting and the
sprinkles, maybe push two together to make a sandwich.
I'm sweating in the store.
I had sweats pouring down my brow.
Would you do?
What I finally did was I said, Pat, it's Memorial Day.
Make an exception for the holiday.
And I bought one holster of plain white frosting and left with that.
I was like, it doesn't have all the weird chemicals and colors and shit.
My crap's not going to be red.
Did you get the cookies, though?
I left the cookies, Joe.
That's what I'm saying.
I was like, I was like, that's what you do, unfortunately, is you're putting dessert on
a dessert when you're putting icing on top of cookies.
And I'm like, I'm not going to do that.
I'm going to enjoy plain icing.
And my God, it was delicious.
It's like having sex when you haven't done it in two years or something.
The problem then the cravings begin immediately.
And I'll tell you this, folks, and I'll tell you this.
I always associated, I had occasional heartburn, occasional, you know, like you keep some
tums in the house, whatever, like everybody else has.
But I always associated it with drinking and usually drinking tequila.
But when I took sugar and carbs completely out of my diet for like two months, although
I had drank, I had no heartburns, so I was like, well, I can't be the alcohol.
Then when I ate this frosting, my heart felt like it was being stabbed for the next eight
hours.
So clearly, I must have some aversion to sugar.
What is it?
Am I gluten intolerant?
I don't think it's that necessarily.
I think it's your body saying you haven't put this shit into your body in a long time and
your body's having a better.
I get that with, I've cut way back on dairy.
And the less dairy I eat, the more amplified my dairy weird reaction is.
Now I do have a bit of a dairy allergy, but it is heightened, the less I dairy.
I still was slipping dairy in on an almost daily basis with cheese on a sandwich or something
like that.
Right.
And I didn't notice it as much.
A gallon of milk with breakfast, yeah.
And now like the other day I had an egg and my ear was itching and I was like, oh, Jesus
man, like it's, so your body adapts quickly, it changes.
So and probably for the best, I mean when you watch those things of like those things
like when a diet coke gets poured on a steak or whatever and you watch it like destroy
a steak in 24 hours, it's very disturbing.
I didn't get me off the soda.
I'm sorry.
That's my one.
I'm sticking with that.
I'm pretty off it to be at T .B .H.
I was doing the celtis, that's supposed to be terrible for your teeth and your insides.
Nothing to be good.
Right.
So I was doing the Keto the whole time and they had this delicious because I just do whatever
they have at work, but they have these delicious, they're called, hmm, something ice.
They're a thin, but almost like a dildo shaped bottle.
And it's like a crystal light type thing.
It's water and I'm like, oh, sweet, flavored water, no carbs, way better than the croix.
So I'm pounding these.
Then one day I happened to Google, hey, is it Keto thinking of course?
And they said, it's horrible for you and diet soda is horrible for you because the chemicals
get in there and jigger up your whole insides and everything.
Yeah, it's not good.
But hey, you got to die or something.
Oh, sure do.
And when it's approaching sooner than you think.
Today we're doing our top five comedy television episodes of all time.
Yes, we're each going to do five.
We're going to get straight away into the theme.
We don't do segments on these episodes.
And I'm excited about this.
I thought about this for a while and I think I, it was very hard, but I think I did come up with.
A fair five.
I really do.
And I've got some honorable mentions for shows that I did include.
I think surprisingly to some of the listeners, but I can explain why.
Okay.
Now are you doing yours in order because I personally would just rather not.
I find it hard.
I used to love nothing more than ranking things.
And now I hate it.
It just makes me sad for some reason.
Okay.
We can go back to yours ranked.
I ranked mine.
Okay.
Yeah, but you don't have to rank yours.
I can rank mine.
You don't have to rank yours.
Thank you, Joe.
You're welcome.
I want to talk my honorable mentions, though.
Yeah.
So these are shows.
That I almost included episodes of, but then I didn't for one main reason.
Because these shows I'm about to mention are shows that I find hilarious.
And for some reason to me work a little better as a whole.
Because I'm not that the shows I picked episodes from weren't character.
Focused.
But these to me work just a little better as a whole versus plucking out an episode.
So peep show was one.
Sure.
I feel like you got to be on that whole journey with those guys.
I feel like it all sort of builds on itself.
I couldn't pick a favorite.
I watched them all over like a four week period.
And I just loved the whole thing and almost felt like one big ups.
Yeah, I agree.
Married with children was one.
Even though I think the show becomes painfully unfunny at the halfway mark about season six or seven.
You know, seasons two to like five, whatever it is where it's really in the zone.
Yeah, you love it because you wait every episode for the part where Al Bundy starts crying at how horrible his life is.
And you know, like that's the stuff you love about the show.
And there are episodes that I love.
But I again, I felt like the show that's more about the experience of knowing that family.
And how dysfunctional they are.
And without that, it's kind of hard to single out the moments.
The honeymooners.
Another one where it's like you're there for that Ralph.
An Alice dynamic primarily.
And then you're there also for the Ralph and Ed dynamic.
And if you don't know their relationship, I mean, imagine watching a snippet of the honeymooners.
But like this man's threatening to beat his wife.
You would have no idea, you know, like so without that overall arc of what the show is.
I feel like it's it's very hard to pick out one episode that encapsulates what the show is to me.
And then lastly, and this is in my top.
So it's people show, but this is my top five sitcoms of all time all in the family.
I couldn't pick just one.
It just builds so much on itself every episode is bleeding into the next with the themes and the struggles of the family and everything.
You can't again, it's about being there and experiencing things with that family and those specific people.
You can't just pick out one isolated thing because it doesn't it just doesn't resonate.
Yeah, it's hard on those sitcoms.
And I never thought this would happen.
I mean, you just get too much stuff in your brain at some point, but I always had favorite episodes, top 10 episodes,
favorite favorite top 10 movies, whatever of things.
And now I just don't it all just sort of blurs together.
I guess in a way.
Yeah, hell of a way to kick off a list episode.
But that's why I came to the cling to the list because I'm like, there was a time when I cared.
Yeah, I mean, my, my picks for what you're describing very briefly are shows like arrested development.
Probably my favorite is the Martin short one where he is being carried around by a giant because he doesn't have the use of his legs.
And he keeps yelling at the giant swoop me and the giant swoops him to grab him so that he can grab handfuls of chips and dip from the table.
A giant swooping Martin shorts body to grab handfuls of snacks.
That stands out to me as some of the hardest I've ever laughed, certainly at a network comedy.
But that show too, it's very, when they're serialized, it's hard to pick out.
And when they're just kind of your standard classic sitcom, your cheers, it was hard.
I know I love cheers, but it was hard for me to pick out a favorite.
I always thought my favorite was cliff on jeopardy until I rewashed it recently.
And I was like, this isn't good at all.
I like the jeopardy.
It's just it couldn't it wasn't as funny as the golden girls jeopardy episode or the mama's family.
Yeah, the golden girls jeopardy one right as the one where the guy is like nobody will like you.
Right?
Yeah, they couldn't have her because she was so I'm like, yeah, very funny twist at the end.
Yeah, Dorothy is like Rose, don't ever press that buzzer again.
But cheers is that way for me.
Even and I know I would hope that Joe's got Frazier on his list, but Frazier is that way for me.
I'd have to really go through and do a full rewatch.
I got through about two seasons during the pandemic.
But yeah, it would definitely be one of the farcical ones.
It would probably be the one with the sword fighting at the cabin.
I think that when I was a kid anyway, I used to watch that all the time.
I recorded it and saved it.
So that would probably be a favorite.
Frazier was hard to hone in on one was hard to hone in on one.
I'll give you another honorable match.
The episode of King of Queens, where he discovers the Italian restaurant that he's not allowed to.
Amazing.
He, Leah Remney gets like chief for Bidson from going ever again, because they're rude to her.
Yeah.
He's there the next day with two full on trees shoveling ziti into his mouth.
Yes.
And he goes, whenever the lunch special was yesterday, bring it.
Because he has to catch up on all the days he missed.
I mean, it's so crazy.
Yes.
Look, it feels good to shout out these, these, these diamonds and the rough, because you can find them now.
They're all streaming.
You can find any episode when I was a kid.
I used to watch sign fell, which of course is going to be on my list, but.
Oh, yeah.
I would watch sign fell when it would air at six six 30 when it would air at nine and nine 30 every day.
I would watch the Simpsons before that.
Two to three times a day.
And then I would watch two to three mom and his family's every night.
So, but you, you'd get them in the order they decide to serve them up to you.
Some episodes never air.
Some episodes of sign fell still never air weirdly.
You never see the port of reacon digs.
It's very controversial.
But sometimes terrible episode, by the way.
I don't remember the word.
It's the worst sign felt episode.
Well, there's, there's a few duds in the mix.
Don't get me wrong.
But it was always just like you watch what we want to give you.
And some just fell out of the rotation and so forth.
And it's nice now.
To be able to have them all at your disposal and to be able to find these classics.
If you don't want to sit through the whole run of a show.
I, I, yeah, married with children.
I was gonna almost, I almost put it in.
It's a wonderful life.
I'm a sucker for a sitcom Christmas episode.
I've talked about the episode before in the show.
The fact that he dies and everybody's life is infinitely better.
To me, it's just brilliant like sitcom writing.
It's just perfect.
I'm trying to think of other shows we, we look.
There were hits all through the idea.
It's funny.
I didn't, cheers didn't even occur to me.
But cheers is all time great.
Obviously, the Cosby show has a shadow looming over it now.
But it's an all time great sitcom.
But I don't remember any of those episodes, to be honest.
I really have blanked on that show.
I've blanked complete night court is one where I might have been able to pick.
You know, but again, it's like, no, it was, you know, I think the five I picked here are the five.
Okay.
You know, I feel good about mine too.
I just, mine, mine are not going to be in order.
I'm going to just say them as they come to me.
Say them as I feel.
Joe, would you like to start?
I will start with something unexpected.
But God damn it.
Front to back every time I watch it almost in tears.
Three stooges.
Malice in the palace.
Which is the one where Shen out now already.
I have issues.
Well, this is the television show.
Where did you see the three stooges?
Would you go in your knickers to the theater?
Went to my local Nickelodeon.
And I put down my nickel.
Joe, I mean.
Yeah.
It's a TV to say one of your favorite episodes of the television show is the three stooges.
It was not designed for television.
I was, I was a little.
I went back and forth on it.
And I was like, no, I think most people recognize the stooges as a TV show.
Well, look, I gave, let's put it this way.
Let's let it slide for one reason.
I gave a shitload of honorable mention.
I mean, it wasn't like I was, I didn't do my homework here.
But I really wrestled with this.
But the thing front to back, it destroys me.
It absolutely destroys me.
Low, low Larry and champ.
For some reason, run a restaurant in a tent in the middle of the Middle East.
A couple of sultans come in.
There's a whole thing through the beginning where the sultans think that they're slaughtering cats and feeding them.
To them.
At one point, he makes champ eat his own food and he doesn't want to eat it because he's now convinced it's a cat.
He goes to bite a piece of chicken that the leg of his share goes down on the cat's tail by accident.
The cat goes, wow, chances he bites it.
He does a classic like, wow.
And they go on a run to find a jewel and they end up in a palace of a sultan and they all get on each other's shoulders and pretend to be a demon that guards the root and tuton diamond.
The whole thing, it's ridiculous.
I'm saying it.
But it destroys me.
It destroys me front to back.
Every single time I watch it, I am in hysterics.
Okay.
I mean, yeah, there's didn't know that we picked things off with a short film.
All right, I'll tell you what I'll tell you what.
It's like when Scorsese and Ebert did their top 10 movies of the 90s.
They go, Ebert's like, I'd like to turn it over.
Of course, I defer to the legendary Marty Scorsese to make his first pick for one of the best movies of the 90s.
And he goes, well, first off, I cheated a little bit. This was made in 1987.
I was like, what?
What the fuck are you doing? Like you had 10 years.
All right. Then I'll do, I'll do an extra one just to make it fair.
I will, I will pluck a, I will pluck a married with children.
All these but goodies is an episode I was going to put it into my top five.
And that's the one we're out here.
There's a Kenneson Christmas.
Well, I already talked about it. I'll do another one just so you see I'm not bullshit around here.
I know my stuff, but
always my goodies is the one where out here's a song on the radio and can't remember the name of it.
And it's complaining that every time, you know, like he's trying, he's listening to the radio trying to hear the name of the song.
And the DJ keeps being like, that was number six in a, in our constant 500 songs.
I don't know.
You know, the radio.
Yeah.
And he can't figure out the name of the song.
And he's going up to everybody throughout the entire episode going, mm -hmm, him.
And he just keeps singing that over and over to people.
He finally finds a record store where they can name any record.
Of course, his song is the only song the guy doesn't know.
And Al Bundy has the greatest breakdown in the history of the show where he falls to his knees and says,
why God, all I want it was a stinking 45, the record or the gun.
I'm going to watch that today.
It's a great episode.
There's a great line where he goes, he then he hears the song.
And he's like, thank you, Lord.
Thank you, Lord.
And he knows the name of it now, whatever.
And he's like, thank you, Lord.
Thank you.
I swear, I'll never ask you for anything again.
Well, maybe one thing, it involves a lightning bolt.
And then he secretly points to peg, which is a funny old.
I hate my wife, Greg.
But it's a great episode.
It's a, it's a really fun classic, you know, it's just a classic married with children.
It's just a really great episode.
I've been toying with getting back in there.
I've bought the box set, which sells on Amazon now for like $20 for all 12 seasons of the show.
So maybe it's time.
I think it might be time.
I honestly, I wish they sold a box that was two seasons two through six.
I would buy it.
They're sold about own in those extra seasons that I don't want that bothers me.
Oh, you just won't even have them in your house.
It's, I've gone back repeatedly and tried season seven is where it gets bad.
I have repeatedly gone back and tried to give it a chance.
And every time I start season seven again, I'm reminded why it sucks.
And it's in the first episode where they inherit a little kid from like, you know, he shows up.
It's like Peggy's nephew.
And now suddenly there's like a kid on the show.
Oh, wow.
And they kept it till the end.
Bucks.
No, he just eventually sort of disappeared.
It's one of those like, and then an episode whenever he went upstairs and never came back down again, they just never mentioned it.
But it just sucks.
And then like in the season after that, her mom comes and lives with them.
But you never see her.
The house just shakes as she approaches.
Because it's a fat joke.
And then is it?
Yeah.
And then the mom just let her for me.
The mom just lives upstairs.
And you just hear her scream from upstairs.
It just, and then like after that, it's just.
It's just terrible.
It's just, it's just so it's, it's, it's, it becomes a parody of itself.
It's just bad.
You can tell they're not really having fun with it anymore.
It's not funny.
It, you know, but season six is the last good one.
Which contains the line when Peggy says she's pregnant.
And the first episode of that season, she says I'm pregnant.
And how it's like, how could this happen?
And then she goes, didn't you notice I was gaining weight and he goes, well, yeah.
Yeah.
Okay.
Wait, wait, we didn't even discuss that they're doing them.
Is that hammering?
Is that me?
Uh, they're doing a married with children animated show now.
I guess like it didn't quite make sense to me at first, but then I was like, oh, I guess they're trying to do it like a family guy.
Like that's the idea.
Yeah, they're just like they couldn't, I guess apparently David Faustino pitched a reboot believe it or not years ago.
Well, couldn't get the cast all together, but they'd all come together to do voices.
So I'd love to see a live action and see like, you know, I think that'd be great.
You mean an animation?
No, I watched the animation.
You want to reboot a lot.
Yeah, I think it'd be fun to see.
I think, you know, but, but whatever.
I mean, you know, look, you need them all in the same house and all that stuff.
So it's, you know, do the, whatever.
So anyway, you go now.
I'm just going to go out with the big guns with Seinfeld and I decided as I was thinking about this this morning.
As I was driving over and I told this Joe last night I went to buy a suit last night at Nordstrom.
Hi, I'd like a black suit.
We are out of the black.
The men's suit department of Nordstrom.
Just thousands of, it looked like, you know, De Niro's closet and casino suits jacket as far as the I can see.
No, black, we are, we do not have.
Anyway, I went down to get a tailored this morning and I was thinking get a new suit, get a tailored, et cetera.
By the way, you got to go to a 50 year old business now.
This old guy comes hobbling out on a cane and I was like, this is where I want to be measures me.
Actually, he didn't even need to measure me knew exactly what my size was.
Didn't even have to measure me puts a suit on fit beautifully tailored it in house.
Told me stories about the old country when he first came out here.
We got a great deal on it and believe it or not, they had black at the suit store.
But you got to go to a to an institution now.
Yeah.
Support these old people, help them.
They're the only people doing good work anymore.
I'm just becoming an old rant and ranger.
Ranger.
Anyway, I would like to shine a light on.
When I was driving around this morning, I thought to myself, a later episode of sine film.
All the praise we've heard about.
And, and deservedly so about the masturbation contest.
My favorite for many, many years was the Keith Hernandez episode.
But now when it pops up, I don't like that it's an hour long.
The, the hour sign, the assign felt always start to feel a little draggy.
Especially like the serial killer one in LA.
I hate the serial killer one.
I've never been a fan of the Hernandez one.
It's too heavy on the Elaine Hernandez romance storyline.
I'm just like, I don't care about this.
I want to see them all doing funny stuff.
So people and I looked this episode up said David Sims, who's a critic.
I know a bit and like quite a bit.
Consider he wrote at the time that it's representative of a subtle drop in quality that sign fell experience in its ninth season.
And that's usually the party line in the last two seasons because Larry David left.
But as George became a more screaming version of himself.
As Elaine became a more like screaming almost evil version of herself.
As Larry became more, I mean, sorry, Jerry became more vicious.
Kramer became weirder and weirder.
And really they were becoming always sunny.
They sort of morphed into that show.
That showed us kind of took the reins over and started at that extreme point.
But I love the accelerated sign felt.
And that's why I got to give it to the dealership from season nine.
And I don't consider this episode of drop off in quality at all.
And actually when I want to laugh, if I need to like snap out of a funk rope, quick and laugh.
I either go to Jimny Glick, my old go to.
Or something in this dealership episode, probably something involving George and the Twix candy bar that gets stuck in the vending machine.
Yeah.
I mean, you line up.
The candy line up.
When he's face down on the floor, trying to get the thing out.
You had time to make the signs, you know, like all the bits about how stupid George is being as it heightens and accelerates.
That sort of story.
That multi -cam sitcoms generally do is the hardest story in the world to do where you just like.
There's not much going on.
George gets a Twix bar stuck.
How do you make that into a compelling story?
They just keep ramping it and ramping it and ramping it.
The guy when the guy's eating the candy line up.
That's a huge laugh when George is screaming at everybody that they're all out to get him because of the Twix candy line up.
Now, we haven't even gone into David Putty, who in my eyes rivaled Newman by this point as a reliable big laugh getter.
Putty and Elaine breaking up and that fucking up Jerry's car is great.
The only thing that isn't great is Kramer doing the drive.
Yeah, that's I've never been a I like the episode.
I've never been a huge fan of it because I find that the candy thing is the is the meat of it that I like.
The Kramer thing I've never enjoyed that like that's not very good actually, you know, but.
But you know what?
I'll go out of order here.
Yeah, my number one is a sign felt and it's a later season sign felt.
So I'll do my number one and then I'll go back and do my fourth three two.
Or I'll just go my number one I'll go backwards order rather.
But my number one is the burning episode of sign felt, which is the episode where Kramer called the burning because Kramer is doing the thing where he has to pretend, you know, he gets the gig.
He has to fake a medical reality for the for the medical students to guess and he keeps getting gone.
That's Kramer storyline.
Feel like that's one that rarely airs.
Well, that's got your favorite line of all time in it.
It's the devil.
It's the Jesus fish putty storyline.
Oh, yeah, that's the episode with feels like an Arby's night.
Feels like an Arby's night is the hardest that me and my friend have ever laughed.
It's not literally fell off the couch.
The whole storyline with Elaine and putty in that episode is first of all, the whole storyline with Kramer is incredible.
With him going in and him doing the monologues about the disease is, you know, he's smoking the cigarette.
But she was a coquettish have a dash and we danced that whole thing is so funny.
The Elaine putty storyline where he thinks she's going to hell.
It's putty and Elaine at their best.
Like it's putty, you know, when he's like, why don't you go get his newspaper?
Why don't you go get it?
Sorry, Elaine, thou shalt not steal.
Well, why is it okay if I go get it?
You know where you're going.
Yeah.
You know, she does the devil horns.
The devil horns thing is amazing.
The Jerry storyline is great where he's dating the blonde that has the tractor story and he doesn't know what the tractor story is.
Yeah.
And then arguably my favorite storyline on the whole show is George getting out on a big laugh where he keeps going, that's it for me.
That's a big episode.
I can't deny that.
It is a, in my opinion, a grand slam like Seinfeld episode.
And it's final season.
Yeah.
I commend you.
It's a good choice.
It's a fine choice.
I would love to single out an episode of the comeback.
Done by my former boss, Michael Patrick King and Lisa Kudrow.
So I think, and I enjoyed the second season, I'm glad they rebooted it 10 years later, whatever was fun.
But the first season is the American masterpiece of discomfort comedy.
The British have, of course, the office, which spoiler alert will appear on my list.
They have really heartridge.
I had a hard time picking the office and extras too for the reasons that I was talking earlier.
I had a hard time singling one out.
Sorry, I was able to remember for sure, but Alan Partridge, you know, toast of London, whatever they do.
They do uncomfortable comedy better than anybody else on Earth.
The Americans, look, I love the American office a lot.
I think it's super funny and about as good as it could have been.
But the comeback doesn't get what it deserves, especially the first season of it, which is just masterpiece.
My favorite episode of the entire run is not many others, but it's this Palm Springs episode.
And it is her husband who is the hilarious guy who Brian Unger who plays the lawyer on always sunny of Brian Unger.
And he plays her husband. Have you ever watched the comeback, Joe?
No, not for any reason. I just never, please do yourself. You'll be hooked HBO Max.
It is the darkest fucking show so ahead of its time.
But episode eight is Valerie relaxes and Palm Springs. And it's the one where in theory, you're going to get away from the insane backstage fame drama that Kudra was caught up in and her husband is excited.
He's going to have some alone time with her and get her away from it, but she is being driven insane and making calls back home.
Every morning, there is a group of people that beat her to the beach chairs around the pool. She does not get to the pool chairs in time each morning.
And that starts driving her insane. And this whole relaxing weekend in Palm Springs is like a horrible ticking time bomb.
And it's a great episode. I love that. I mean, I favor kind of comedy is that super painful awkward comedy. But it's great to because it really shines a light on as sex in the city did, by the way, which Michael also did.
How difficult it can be when people are in very different careers.
And just she can't shut that side of herself off. She's obsessed with it and it's driving her husband away and he can't connect with her.
And it's just fascinating on a thematic level because they don't point it out to you. She doesn't know she's doing it.
But to me, that is one of the best written episodes of a brilliant, brilliant show that not enough people have seen. Check out the comeback.
Alright, excuse me. I'm going out at order here.
I got to go sunny.
Patty's next top billboard model.
The episode is there for that one. I was.
It just destroyed me the first time I saw it. It destroys me every time.
The highlight being the fact that the, you know, they have a modeling contest that Dennis is going to, I mean, that Dennis wants to compete in that Danny DeVito is moderating.
And then Mac does his side like be does like the bachelor, whatever is version of the bachelor in the bar.
But the highlight, the highlights are Danny DeVito doing the modeling competition stuff where he's like, you know, sometimes in modeling, you'll be asked to model a theme.
Today's theme is barnyard.
You know, that thing, he has them posing his animals, Dennis, you're mule is shit.
Yes.
And then just an amazing Mac line where he's like, where he's like, he's got the three finalist girls and he goes, Kelly, you banged me.
Sydney, you also bagged me, but more importantly, you banged each other.
And then he gets, he makes the one girl think she's going to win, then he gets it to the other two girls.
And the girl they tricks, he's like, I tricked you, I totally tricked you.
Which he goes, you're an asshole and he goes, yes, and that's what I learned.
It's just a great episode. I honestly don't really, oh.
And then Charlie and D are doing the, that's the birth of the introduction of green man.
That's right.
That's the episode where green man comes in, that's where D is doing the hard, all of her horribly racist characters trying to go viral.
It's a great fucking episode of the show.
I mean, it's just everything you want in the show that they'll probably never do ever again.
But you know, this is back when they were taking some real chances.
I think one of my favorites is the one where they're trying to rob.
I don't even remember why, but they're trying to rob a house and Dennis and D are stuck in a closet.
Just figuring Glenn is so on fire in that episode.
Just, and Glenn, they give him two or three episodes of season where they just let him go.
It's always wonderful to behold.
But that one would just like when he's trying to keep the, I keep a lid on the rage.
There's really a few better at doing that kind of act.
Slow burn if you will.
He's, he's amazing. That episode, he's amazing in the, in where he makes the fake sitcom about the moms by planting the cameras in the house.
He's amazing in the hurricane episode.
The meltdown he has on the women in the store.
Yeah.
When he invites them back to the bar for shelter.
And they're like, can we bring our boyfriends?
And he's like, how did you think?
And I invite you back.
It is not to bang you.
And he starts screaming shoe at them.
Show.
He's, he's, he truly is just a gift.
He's a gift that guy.
All right.
I got to do, got to do the Simpsons.
Okay.
And for them, I got to do.
Conan O 'Brien's.
Episode.
Marge versus the Monterey.
Is probably my favorite.
Because.
It's really got everything.
And it's written by Conan, which is always fun because you see how much of his personality makes end of the episode.
Although, you know, in any kind of writing, he could have had nothing to do with it.
Who fucking knows.
But it's part of the legend of the show.
But you got a real tour de force performance by Phil Hartman, a musical performance by Phil Hartman.
Now, my favorite character of his on the Simpsons is Lionel Hutz, the lawyer.
Who has probably my favorite line ever.
Which is this is the worst case of fraudulent advertising I've ever seen.
Since my lawsuit against the film, the never ending story.
Which I'm sure are written much better.
I'm not trying to remember it off the cuff.
But him as Lionel Hutz, the lawyer is as good as the show ever was.
And really, though it's not fair to say.
The Simpsons never recovered from losing Phil Hartman.
And I kind of stopped watching when we lost Phil Hartman.
But this is really a showcase for him.
This was one where he wasn't playing one of the many characters of Springfield.
They wrote him like a very juicy guest star role.
It's a spoof of the music man.
A guy coming to town pitching Springfield on a monorail.
But he's actually, you know, a swindler, a Huckster, etc.
Huge, huge laughs throughout.
Phil Hartman is amazing.
Leonard Nimoy is very, very funny in it.
Just a lot of big, big laughs.
And if you want to later Simpsons, that to me is kind of where I put a pin in and go.
That was the last great episode.
It would be behind the laughter, which was a season 12.
I believe a full episode parody of behind the music.
I remember that.
And just really a masterpiece with just amazing jokes.
Again, I can remember one is Tim of the best of my abilities, which was.
The Simpsons were riding on a wing in a prayer.
But the wing was on fire.
And the prayer had just been answered by Satan.
Amazing.
I'm very, it's a, it's that like 12 credited writers on it.
It's a very joke dense episode.
The Simpsons is one I've been meeting to revisit.
That's when I used to watch several episodes a day.
I miss it in my life.
And again, I don't want to watch the new ones.
So.
I thought it was a shame that.
After they had lost to Harman that Albert Brooks didn't become a bigger regular part of the show.
Because I thought he was a great.
I felt like when I saw the movie, I was like, I bet Phil Hartman would have been this character.
Yeah.
And Albert Brooks is a great.
He's just, it's just a great voice.
He's great at playing those very white bread characters.
Is that the episode where the James Bond parody where he's the villain is another true, true classic Simpsons.
And he is so funny in it.
He's the funniest part.
He played a lot of characters, but you're right.
They never really made him a part of the fabric of the show.
I mean, I mean, maybe that was his choice, but.
All right.
We go to the golden girls.
This was a tough.
This was tough.
This one.
This was a real tough call.
But I had to go with the episode that made me buy my first golden girls DVD set.
That I was more excited to see again than any other golden girls episode.
And that to this day has the greatest golden girls gag of all time in my opinion.
Ladies of the night from season two, where they go to see Bert Reynolds.
Get arrested because the cops think their prostitutes.
It's just an amazing episode.
And it ramps up real hard once they get into the jail.
Line after line.
You know, Sophia comes into bail them out.
She goes arrested for prostitution.
I can't believe it.
Dorothy goes, mom, we didn't do anything.
And she goes, no, I can't believe these dumb cops would think anybody paying money to sex with you.
Just scathing lines.
You know, are you here to bail us out, Sophia?
No, Rose.
She brought a Manacotti with a file.
I don't like it.
Yeah.
But the greatest, the greatest, in my opinion, like in the 80s, they did a lot of those celebrity walk on guest star things.
Just cameo things.
And the greatest one ever is in this episode were Bert, you know, Sophia keeps talking about how she became friends with Bert Reynolds at this party.
And none of the girls could go because she left them in jail.
And they don't believe her and they're furious.
By the way, heavy on the Charles Nelson Riley jokes, who was one of Reynolds best friends, which I was surprised Reynolds was cool with.
But anyway.
But they don't believe her.
And then the doorbell rings.
Who is it?
It's Bert Reynolds.
It's just such a weird left wing.
And then the greatest button on the end of a sitcom episode ever, which is.
And it's by the way, it's Reynolds looking like he's doing the impression that Norma Donald did of him.
He's got the hair piece.
He's showing the gum.
He's got the mustache with the open collar.
And he goes.
He goes, these are roommates.
And Sophia goes, yeah, and he goes.
Which one's a slut.
And then they all go, I am.
And then that's, you know, on the music play.
Right.
It's just an awesome, awesome ending to an episode.
And it makes me laugh every time I see it.
I love it.
And it's one of those things where you're watching you go, that's when it was showbiz, baby.
You know.
That's when that's when Bert Reynolds could call three elderly women slots in front of.
That's a beautiful time.
That's what I meant.
But no, no, it wasn't.
I don't agree with you.
He's strolling over on his way to Carson.
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
It's just the whole.
It's everybody's in the same pool.
It's just.
God damn.
Uh -huh.
The business back then.
Anyway.
I got a shout out.
He's bounding down.
The later seasons of the show.
Often hit me in very unexpected emotional ways.
In addition to being very funny, I thought the show was just fantastic throughout.
Truly one of the all time great comedies.
And I think it might take a few more years for it to.
Get that status locked in as it should be because people just think it's stupid.
And it's not.
But.
Yeah, I cried several times.
I rewatched.
I rewatched the show numerous times.
I get more into it every time.
And I think it looks fantastic.
And I think dynamic brides work there is.
As good as it gets in that role.
That's where you want him.
I got to give.
If I'm.
If I'm signaling out one favorite.
I got to single out.
The.
The episode.
The episode five.
Of season one.
I think that they just called them chapter five.
Then so you can't really say what it's called.
But it's when can.
Can he powers decides to give up.
This is before he winds up leaving his wife at a gas station and just abandoning her.
Driving off to pursue his dreams in episode six.
But.
Keeping him in town.
Is a rivalry with Ashley Schaefer.
The owner of Ashley Schaefer BMW played by Will Ferrell.
Oh, yeah.
Being so excited that he was going to be appearing on this show.
Because comedy was still very exciting.
This was like, you know,
a few years after anchor man, whatever he was definitely the biggest comedy star there is.
And he was going to do a guest spot on this sitcom based on HBO.
It was very exciting.
But.
So incredible him Craig Robinson holding his own as well.
Dynamic bride.
And then.
The fact that that scene led to the bloopers that have brought more joy than almost anything else.
I got a shout out that episode is one of the greats.
I also want to put a spotlight on Andy Daley's work in that first season of Eastbounded down.
So especially that cold open that starts with him.
You in the point of view of him fucking you him missionary style fucking you.
And that's the whole cold open of one of the season one episodes of Eastbounded down.
That I just remember being blowing my mind.
Rachel.
There you go.
Where how many how many have we done here?
I have one left.
We each have one left.
All right.
Yeah.
By the way, another honorable honorable mention Larry Sanders.
Jesus.
Couldn't pick one.
Yeah.
I would have done the habitat for humanity episode with Hank's car.
But and that's the Vince Vaughn episode.
That's a great episode.
So all right.
The moment you've all been waiting for you know it was coming.
Frazier.
Frazier green.
I got to go.
This was a tough one because I particularly love the Frazier Christmas episodes.
I watch them every Christmas with my parents.
It's always a really nice moment.
During the holidays we all laugh together.
They're the screaming stops for five minutes.
But I didn't pick one of those.
I went with door jam, which is the episode where they.
Mistaken Frazier mistakenly gets an invite that was meant for his neighbor
and nemesis.
Right.
To a new something that's opening.
He doesn't know what it is.
And he's so riddled with jealousy that he pretends Cam Newton is the is art rivals name.
He pretends to be.
Cam Newton.
And he goes down.
Actually, no, I'm sorry.
Niles pretends to be Cam Newton.
Cam Newton's a black guy with a very deep voice like a Dennis Hayesburg voice.
So there's a scene where like.
Frazier's like well, he's like trying to sneak into this thing.
And he's like I cam is a friend of mine.
And he's like lying to try to get in.
And they're like unless Cam is here.
To vouch for you.
I can't let you in.
And Niles walks in it.
And you know when like.
It's like like Niles walks in, but he's not in on the scheme.
And then Frazier's like.
You know, he's like, he's like, hi, Cam, wink, wink.
And Niles starts trying to imitate the neighbor by making his voice really bassy.
Sounds ridiculous.
It's a very, very funny scene.
Anyway, they, they scheme their way into the place.
It's heaven on earth.
And they're just so happy until they realize there's a.
There's a silver door.
And they need to know what's beyond the silver door in this day spa that they've gotten into.
And.
I don't remember if I said day spa or not, but it's a day ends up being a day spot.
They want to get through the silver door.
And they're told they're not allowed.
They're just bronze level.
They can't.
They're such a leadest stops.
They can't live with the fact that they're being reduced to bronze level.
They then eventually scheme their way through the silver door, which is a serenity garden.
Now they're at the silver level.
And then they see a platinum door.
And they can't get through the platinum door now.
And one of the people at the spa says, sir, you're not allowed through the platinum door.
You'll just have to enjoy your time in the serenity garden.
And the greatest Frazier line of all time is when he goes.
Niles have cruel words have ever been spoken.
I mean, it's it's just classic farcical.
Frazier, it's there.
It's just everything you love about the duo.
Are you seeing how big a presence.
Twitter's having an in meme culture on Twitter these days.
Frazier is a lot of great Twitter memes out there.
Our own beloved that was my shoe dragon cross the concrete by the way.
Can Hanley has on his account.
A great Frazier meme.
I don't remember what it was, but look it up.
And help us out.
Send it to jump.
But there's a lot of great Frazier material.
Like people rewrite scenes about like things going on in the news today between.
Fringer and I have seen those.
Those are always great.
Yes.
Anyway, very funny episode.
Frazier.
And your final, sir.
My final.
Has got to be a curb.
I.
I forgot it.
I just.
I couldn't.
Couldn't do it.
But I forget.
Picking one was very difficult.
My old go to was always crazy eyes.
Kill up, but you watch it now.
And it, you know, aspects of it are a bit dated.
Don't feel as real.
Perhaps.
I love.
When Catherine O 'Hara played.
Funk.
I was crazy.
Sister.
That was a very dark and sane, wonderful episode.
But what I kept coming down to.
And I just.
I think it was remembering.
My life at this time was such a glorious period of time.
I had just moved to New York.
I had been in New York.
Right out of college.
But I had finally found the page program and found my people.
And was just having a great time.
And.
It was the.
Table read episode.
Of the Seinfeld season.
Yeah.
With.
Of course, the famous joke being told by funk house or.
About the woman leaving her vagina in the sink.
And Seinfeld dying laughing over it.
Just amazing episode.
Yeah.
So many amazing scenes.
I love it.
I love everything about it.
But.
And seeing everybody together was amazing.
Seeing everyone kind of just say, OK, and accept.
Michael Richards back into the fold.
There was something kind of beautiful about it.
Even though they didn't let him off the hook.
Right.
You know, they brought him back, which I thought was very nice.
Another favor was opening night.
The end of the producer season where you, we actually like.
It's almost like a full length hour long where it's basically like Larry performing in that big Broadway musical.
Time in the whole season.
Some really brilliant stuff in that.
I love that producer season.
Maybe because I was living in New York at the time.
Also, it was airing with sopranos in real time, which was always just.
The best night of television.
But I got a lot of great memories with the curve I realized.
And there's.
There's really not a bad season of the show.
There's lesser seasons.
But.
That quality has has been there for about a hundred episodes of an amazing amazing show.
Yeah.
Same season.
I believe if I had to pick an episode, my all time might be the black swan where they murder the black swan by accident.
Hilarious.
All those scenes in the in the club.
With.
Richard kind and fun calzer.
When when he keeps ordering those onions and he's going not burnt, but not too crispy, you know, and he's there.
And, and, and fun calzer when he's just like, can you stop shoveling that disgusting shit into your face?
So we can play cop.
When fun cat, when, when, when.
Richard kind starts saying he's going to, he's going to tell his wife because he can't live with the guilt.
Yes.
David is best where he's just going, you shut the fuck up.
I can kill you.
Like.
It's so amazing.
That whole, that's, that's what you, they got the whole crew together in those scenes.
Those are just great.
Yeah.
If you go back now as I do every couple of years with, with this and sopranos, it just gets funnier over time.
Like they have such a repeatability to them.
Those, and you know, I'd say I wouldn't confine it just to the first ten seasons.
There's still great stuff going on in the show, but for a while, there was just nothing better.
And now it's just, it has to just settle for being the only funny show on television, but.
Man, it's just a, it's amazing how the quality is kept up, especially with him being as old as he is.
And never seeming out of touch.
Occasionally, seeming out of touch, but.
Well, folks, and I hate celebrity culture.
That's, if there's one takeaway for American comedy.
It's that even though I praised them bringing Will Farrell on just five minutes ago.
And I'm a complete hypocrite.
That's what, that's what to me brought down comedy in the end is that people, not only.
Started loving it, laughing at it.
They started demanding it and expecting it.
That there'd be giant celebrity cameos and movies that there's no reason for them to be in.
Giant celebrities, plans, stupid games on Jimmy Fallon.
Nothing special anymore. You ruined it.
You blew it up. You made it.
Let's keep it positive.
That's our episode.
There's your god damn top five.
What a great episode.
I enjoyed this very much.
We also don't usually plug at the end of these theme episodes.
So there's your show.
We'll see you next time.
We'll be back with probably the sadness, possibly man.
I don't know.
We'll figure it out.
But we'll be back later in the months, folks.
What else do we got?
We're not going to do Doc Strang, right?
What's the big one?
Oh, you know, we've got to do top gun.
We're going to do top gun.
Couldn't care less.
We're going to do everything everywhere all at once.
That's possible.
I'm not saying no to top gun.
I just never saw the original.
I'm like, yeah, I don't know.
You know, like, I guess I should go see it.
Everybody's waving about.
I don't want to.
I don't care about jets.
I'll give you that.
I don't care about jetty.
I'm going to see it.
Yeah, we'll be back with some good stuff, folks.
Thanks for listening.
We thank you all.
We thank your support.
We love you for your support.
We love you anyway.
Wash.
Take us out, baby.
Folks, we'll see you next time and we'll see you in hell.
See you next time.