I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, and when the sound of your screams becomes
a thing of my dreams, you know I'll say, I'll see you in hell, you know I will, I'll see
you in hell, you know I will.
Folks welcome to a very special We'll See You in Hell.
We're here in the final week of August.
It is the 10 -year anniversary month of this podcast, and as always, me and Pat Walsh are
bringing it to you.
We're hitting you with all four episodes late in the month, but you're getting all four
of them this week, and it is a special episode, not just because it's the 10 -year anniversary,
but also because, well, it's over.
There's no easy way to say it, let's rip the Band -Aid off.
It's not that I don't love you anymore, it's not you, it's me, you know.
I'm sleeping with your mother, I'm sleeping with your mother and your sister, we've all
said these things during a breakup, you know.
But, yeah, it basically boils down to, it had been 10 years, you start thinking about
that for a second, you're like, we started this in 2015, which seems, honestly, like
a century, it just seems like an impossible amount of time ago, five years prior to even
the pandemic, and 10 years of anything is a long time.
I've had one relationship in my life that lasted 10 years.
My careers lasted about 17 years, you know, 10 years is a long fucking time, and I think
Joe and I just, I wouldn't say we're sick of it, I wouldn't say we don't feel like we
still have things to say, I would just say, after 10 years, you're kind of done, you know.
You just kind of hit a point where you don't have fascinating commentary on every single
movie you go see.
You don't want to go see a movie and be thinking the whole time, what am I going to say about
this on the show that's funny?
You want to just start to relax and live your life a little bit.
For Christ's sake, give me some room to breathe, yeah, no, I got to a point.
I started to sense that it might be time, about two months ago, I realized I hate every
movie I am watching, every review we do, I'm saying this sucks, I hate it, and I'm like,
I don't even know if I'm watching it through the right lens anymore, man, I'm just, I don't,
do I hate it, I think, or am I just aggravated because I had to watch it?
I don't mean had to, like it's a burden, but you pick these movies every month that we
think will be good for the show, and on a subconscious level, then it becomes this kind
of work duty, and I started to think, I don't even know if I hate this movie or not, I might
just be aggravated at it because I'm watching it in between two other work things I had to do
today or whatever it is, and I thought, well, maybe that's a sign that we've done a lot,
we've talked a lot of movies.
There becomes a homework quality to it, and if your life's pretty chill or if you have some
downtime, it's not a big deal, but when your career's going and your family's going and
your love life's going, then it does start to feel a little overwhelming, and we just felt
we've done it enough. The other issue that's probably apparent from listening to the show
is that the only times Joe and I communicate with each other are regarding the podcast,
so instead of Joe DeRosa popping up on my phone and me going, oh, it's my friend Joe,
I go, ah, here, you know, here's another, we gotta, I guess we're scheduling tomorrow,
now I can't do this tomorrow because I gotta record this, whatever else,
and you start to sort of dread communicating with your friend because it becomes only about
business, and we were just bickering the way we used to, and we had gotten past that,
and it wasn't feeling good, and I think we're doing a healthy thing. We caught it ahead of time,
we caught it before, you know, Yoko's in the third box criticizing what we're talking about,
you know, where we're doing too much blow, and we're communicating with a mediator between the
two of us, you know, we didn't want to go that far with it. No, no, and we greatly, greatly,
greatly appreciate the fans, I don't even like to say the word fans, the supporters, the family.
Benefactors, really, Charles Dickens word.
Yes, the patrons, the Hellions, the non -patrons that are also Hellions,
you know, I'm out traveling, you know, quite a bit, so I get to meet, I get to meet some of you
very randomly sometimes, and then other times, it's because you came to a show or something like
that, but, you know, the love is apparent, and it's appreciated, and that's the other part of
it too, like we, you know, you don't want to get, you don't want to be, you don't ever want to be
the sitcom that went one season too long, you know, and we didn't want to do that, we, there,
there are TV shows I watch now, where it's funny, my sort of latest reviews or opinions of TV shows
that seem stagnant now, that were once great, I say they're treating it like a podcast, they're
just showing up, and they're just making money, and the fans are built in, and they can just do
this as long as they want, and whatever, and we never felt that way about this podcast, we never
treated it like a podcast, it, we, we treated it like work, and any kind of work, you're going to
have your moments of going, oh, Christ, we got to sit down and do the thing, but we never, we never
looked at this as a paycheck, we never looked at this as, hey, why not, we're making a few bucks,
we always looked at it as a thing we enjoyed doing very much, which is why for so many years
we did it without ever making any money, and then it became a family with the fans, and,
and again, sorry, I don't mean the fans, but you know what I mean, the Hellions,
you know, and it became something, you know, bigger. Off the mic usually refers to you as
on, so be glad you're getting fans. I've also, in my defense, I've also said Philistines, Barnacles,
but my point is, is it became something bigger than we had ever anticipated, and something that was
much more special to us, and to people that were listening than we ever had anticipated, and it's
always been very enjoyable, so when it got to a point this year, which we didn't even realize it
was the 10th year, but we were already feeling, oh man, like this, we're gonna start mailing it in,
and we're gonna start just not being present, and we're gonna start getting on each other's nerves,
and we didn't want any of that to happen, we wanted this to go out on a high note,
and we thought there's no better time than when we found out that it was the 10 -year
anniversary this month. Well, that seemed to make perfect sense. We're sorry to abruptly break this
to you. We did consider going on an extra couple of months, and kind of teetering off, but again,
let's start how we, let's finish how we started. White hot. That's right. And rock hard. That's
right. You know? You can't finish and start rock hard. There's gonna be some
blood flow loss once we've come, but we'll get right back up again, I think is what we're saying.
Yes. And by the way, this is not to say there's no chance ever of us
doing something again, you know, of, you know, potentially a, you know, a live show or whatever.
Who knows? But just for now, it's time to hit that pause button indefinitely. For right now,
we're pretty pumped because Steve Coogan and John C. Reilly are playing us in the film adaptation
of We'll See You in Hell. Still with the fat suits, which I find really insulting.
Were they Stan and Ollie, right? Stan and Ollie, and now they have the new one coming out where
they're an even lesser remembered comedy team by the modern days. Or Barry and McGee or something
like that. Yeah. No, yeah, we're, we can't thank you enough. We have, I think, thanked you
excessively. Maybe we thanked you too much. So I'll take that back. We can thank you enough.
But I don't remember exactly what the date was or what the year was. We've lost all concept of time.
But some point, I guess, pre pandemic, when did you move to New York, Joe?
From LA. 2019, December, and then the pandemic started. So yeah, pre pandemic.
We were going to end it, you know, Joe's moving. We weren't even in the same city or side of the
country anymore. And we basically presented you guys with our dilemma and you kept us afloat.
You kept this thing going for six years longer than we expected it to. Who expects a podcast
to last longer than a year or two anyway? So let's celebrate what we have and not gripe about what
we don't, you know, we had some great times. We met some great people, some great friends.
Yeah, we're gonna some technical talk. If you want to keep the episodes of the show,
Joe, do you want to walk us through that process? Well, for my understanding, I can, I can pause the
subscription charging. So I can pause you. So in other words, in September, you won't be charged
because I can pause the tiers. I wish I could pause the tiers.
But you'll have access to the tier content still. But so we're going to do that for a month.
Yeah, if there's any opportunity to download the episodes that you want to keep.
Yeah. If there's any issue with that, let us know. Yeah, just let us look, message us if there's any
issue. But that's what we're going to do. Because I mean, look, if you haven't downloaded them by
now, you probably don't want to download them. And if you did want to download them, you probably
did. But the point is, is there will be the month of September to download, you should still have
access to your tier. And if that for whatever reason doesn't work, we will pivot and figure out
another solution. But that but that should work. And it should be fine. Yeah, messages, DM, and
please, folks, we try to kind of gently say this about the commenters, but like, know that we are
never trying to fuck you over. That is not our intent. Maybe there are podcasts out there who
are trying to do a money grab on the way out the door that we're trying to do the opposite of that.
So if you do wake up on September, whatever, and you're being charged and the podcast is over,
think to yourself, are Pat and Joe trying to fuck me out of my money here? Or is there some
sort of billing issue that I can reach out to them about? We will handle it, we will always take care
of it. We're not trying to piss anybody off. When a show ends, it's like, well, then what happens?
What are we going to do? We're here for you. If you have problems, let us know.
Yeah, but yeah, even the old episodes that are on iTunes, we don't really know the future of them
yet. But if you want, if you want these things in your permanent collection, download them and
keep them because it shouldn't be a surprise to you that the internet is not a permanent
home for anything. This stuff can all go away. Yeah, also to you know, there there could be
Patreon related issues. So of course, yeah, we don't know anything about Patreon really. Yeah,
we ask kindly that scrutinize the issue you're having before hitting us up to determine whether
it's a Patreon issue or something on our end. You know, on our end, all we can do is go, which is
what I'm going to do is go in and pause all charging. And according to Patreon, it says you
can still access your content. But we're only doing that for a month because you have to reset
that every month. And I got to be honest, people, there's too much margin for error there that I'm
going to forget to keep pausing it every month. So I think 30 days is a solid amount of time to
download whatever you want. And that's it. We'll see you next time. Kidding. No, there's an episode.
Yes, of course, there's an episode. And, you know, there's always a negative way to view
any situation. That could be another another name of this podcast, a negative way to view
every situation. We know that there's a negative way to view every situation and that this will be
devastating to some and it will be upsetting to some and it will piss some of you off.
But it had to end at some point, you know, we're trying to make it as easy and painless as possible.
But we love you guys. And certainly getting to meet some of you and hang out with you and
do those zoom rooms over the pandemic. That was the coolest thing seeing you guys become friends
over us. Yeah. It was just really cool to see actual genuine friendships take place out of
people thinking we're funny, entertaining. It was great. It was nice. What's new with you, Joe? Your
condo in Austin right now, it is a disaster zone. We had I had flooding in here,
which led to water damage, which led to the need for repair. But then there were also things that
I needed to change in here. When I bought it. You know, the appliances were were 20 plus years old
and not functioning properly. And the bathtub was kind of a wreck and blah, blah, blah,
things that happened. So when I while I had the contractors in here, I said, You know what,
let's let's just fix all this right now. And they're doing a really nice job. But I don't
know if you've ever had contractors do any remodeling in your home. But it's insane. It
starts, you know, I found my body wash inside my hamper. You know, the mirror from the bathroom
is in the kitchen cabinet. My Nike slides are on my chopping block. It's like, you know, they just
start, they throw shit anywhere, because they're trying to move fast and be efficient. Yeah. So
right now, my place is is in quite a state of disarray. They said it's going to be done this
week. I wasn't going to come down here this week. But then I was like, You know what,
let me go down for the final week. They said the apartments livable, which technically it is there's
a refrigerator, there's an oven, there's a bed and a shower and a toilet. So I was like, it'd
probably be good for me to be there for the final week. That way I can make sure everything is good.
And if there's anything else that needs fine tuning, I'm there to see it. And because that's
the other rule with the contractor, once they're gone, they're gone. So like you got to be there
with when they're there to be you know, to make sure it's all getting done. Anyway,
it's a good company and whatever you call a contractor contractor is like anything around
the house and they have a set hourly rate or what what is a contract? You know, no, they're guys
are these guys are I forget the name of the company. But I think they're called American
coatings or something. I don't know. You know, they're, they're, they're, they're, they're
carpenters. Yeah, a lot. There's all kinds of contractors. I mean, you could be a contractor
in business consulting or whatever. But in this sense, or in this work realm, they're, you know,
they're usually carpenters with plumbing experience and whatnot. And you know, you say,
you know, this big open space, how do we put a wall here and then have a door and what
you know, and they're like, here's how you do that. And they know how to fucking do it. So
these guys are good. They're straight shooters. And then they give you an estimate, or not an
estimate. They say this is your out the door price, some guys will give you an estimate,
I would never have a contractor work on an estimate. Because they can just go Oh,
sorry, we're $10 ,000 more than the estimate. Yeah, exactly. So they come in with an initial
estimate. And then you say, Okay, scrutinize it now. What is the final price? And then you know,
so that's what these guys did. And they're really good. But I threw admittedly threw a lot of them
at once. So I think that's part of why the apartment is insane right now. But yeah, that's
that's the that's where my my life is that I just got back from I did Chappelle's summer camp last
weekend, which is the thing he does outside in Ohio in that field. He started that during COVID,
which was nuts Shane, I was with Shane to do Milwaukee with him at whatever the arena is
there. And he was like, let's go to Chappelle's first and we went and good to see Dave. It was
fun to do the shows. I saw a lot of old friends out there. Santino was out there and Marina
Franklin and Rich Voss. And it was really fun. And now I'm back in Austin. That's that's where
my life's at. Oh, and my girlfriend is nevermind. I'll stay away from that. Not my Kurt, my ex
girl. I forget it. You know what, that's bad. That's the first time hearing of this. My ex
girl. I was gonna tell you something. What I'm talking about. See, we only communicate on the
air. Sick. I'm not going to bring it up. The ex girlfriend. Everything is good. Life is good.
Okay, how are you? How are you? I'm okay. I'm getting ready to put in a new deck. So that's
why I'm asking about contractors. It's kind of my first big house project in 10 years living here.
But it's time by my deck is sinking. So it's like it's almost like a Titanic vibe. When you
go out there, you go out and start walking downwards sort of. So we're getting that
looked at. And the other thing, I get a printout in my mailbox. It's got two pictures of my home.
I thought it was like a lost highway situation. This guy typed up a letter to me. It says, Hey,
neighbor doesn't know my name. But then it's like, I noticed this sewer pipe that appears to be on
property is leaking onto my street, the street below mine. Can you please get this fixed? It
shouldn't be too expensive or time consuming. I'm showing a few friends this are like, why is this
person speculating on the cost? It just seemed weird that the typed up nature of it in the
printout when he could just knock on my door. But so I called a sewage place. Now I pay a monthly
fee for sewage that's over $100 a month. They don't do anything. Right. It's just a fee you pay.
So now I'm like, okay, well, now I finally have a sewage problem. Now I'll get what I'm paying for.
I call they go, Oh, no, that's that's your responsibility. We don't handle that.
Okay. So you call a sewage place. Yeah, I would have no idea who to call.
Me neither. You Google it. They call us call this sewage pipe repair place. So the guy goes,
I'll send my guy over. He'll jet it. That's going to be 550 and we'll see where we're at.
Said, what is jetting? This is my least favorite thing about dealing with these people is they use
their lingo, talk real fast and think you're going to get it and then seem annoyed and roll
their eyes when you don't. I don't jet sewers for a living. That's not my job. It's yours.
That's why I called you. If I went down there to jet the sewer, it would blow up my neighborhood.
Yeah, no. Yeah. Yeah. My contractor one book is I had to I had them put this Murphy bed in.
And it was white and I wanted it to be black. Yeah, the black one wasn't available. So he's
like, you know, don't worry, we'll order it and we'll paint it. And so two days ago, he goes,
I don't even remember the word he used. He goes, Murphy bed installed,
going to blast it Friday. And I'm like, what the hell does that mean?
You're gonna blasting paint? Yeah. And then he goes, paint.
And he wasn't a dick. But I'm like, just say that just say it.
I hate people that use their lingo. It reminds me of Waiting for Guffman when
Fred was like, strike it. We know all the terms going in. We've done shows with Corky before.
It's that it's no one's impressed. I don't know. And I'm telling you, I don't know. And I don't
think you're cool, because you do know. So just tell me what it is. But they come over, they jet
it. The guy comes up, he goes, um, you only have one welcome on your sewer pipe. But he but I'm
trying to be polite, but I couldn't make out a single word this man was saying. The accent was
so thick. I don't even know what accent. But after multiple repeats, which makes you feel
like an asshole, because you're going, what are you saying? It always makes me feel terrible.
But if you don't know what they're saying, you have to say that. So we keep going back and forth.
And then I turned to his buddy, his partner. And I'm like, Can you help me out here? That guy does
not speak English at all. So I'm like, they're calling a guy who does speak English, the foreman
or whatever. They're putting me on the phone with him. And he's like, Yeah, I'm gonna look
the video they took of your sewer pipe. And then I'll tell you what we need to do from there.
I said, when are you going to call me about that sometime next week. So I've given this guy, you
know, 550 bucks to quote, jet my sewer, which took five minutes, then they leave. And I'm just
assuming this guy is going to call me back. I hate this. I hate it all. And you never know if you're
getting screwed or not. You know, lately, I call at least a second place, because when I got broken
into, I called that second place. And there was like $1 ,000 difference between boarding up my door.
But it sucks. No, it's my arguably my favorite Seinfeld joke is the when they're talking about
the mechanic and George's like, of course he's ripping you off. Nobody knows. Oh, you need a
new Johnson rod. Okay. Yeah, no, 100%. Yeah, 100%. I just got a new car. I lease every three years.
I'm incorporated. I'm a corporation. It's what you're supposed to do in my business.
And then the accountants like you got to lease a new car every three years. It's a free car,
he says. Now I still pay the payments. But he assures me it's a free car. Anyway,
I wanted to get the it's a fully electric car. My ex had a Elon car. The worst car I've ever driven
Tesla. We pay the money to get the plug set up in the garage. Yep. So now I get the new car.
I plug it into that plug. It doesn't work. Now. Yeah, Tesla is infamous for that.
Well, just like the fucking iPhone. They know if they change the plug every two, three years,
you got to get a new fucking car. I don't have a Tesla. I have a different kind of car. But I'm
what is that? So the whole point of electric cars is to help save the world. Like we're killing the
world by blasting it with exhaust and we're just going to keep doing it. And we're already past
the point of no return. So then you say I'll do this. I'll be one of these good people that
gets an electric car. And then they just fuck you again and again and again. So the guy comes in,
he looks at the plug. He goes, Yeah, I can I can get you fully updated and it'll charge
your new car for about a thousand bucks. Does that work? I go, Yeah, we finish it. He's there
four or five hours. I plug in the car. It turns green for three seconds and then red, which was
the original problem. It means it's not taking a charge. I go, This didn't work, man. He goes,
I thought that might happen. Okay, we're just going to have to do plan B then. I go, What's plan B?
He goes, Well, plan B is more expensive. Unfortunately, it'll be about four grand.
Jesus Christ. On top of the one, I go, am I getting a rebate on that thousand that I dropped? He's
like, No, unfortunately, we had to try that, you know, but if it's not working, there's not
much we can do. I finally got him to split that cost in half. But it's like, dude, he goes, Well,
I was still here four or five hours, you know, you're not going to get in the screaming match
with somebody in your garage. Yeah. But it's like, God, damn it, you're always getting fucked.
Oh, and this deck is going to be, you know, I don't know how long those projects take, but
at least a week, you know, so you got to figure out how many problems is that going to drag up.
Yeah. And God forbid you complain about this to anybody. Yeah. And you have a home.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. What's what you get for going electric.
You can't even say that used to be like libtard shit going electric. Now it's not anymore. It's
like, it's like an alpha male thing. Like the electric cars. Very weird. It's like I'm
unquestionably doing the right thing. And just you just feel like you've fucked up time and time
again. Shall we hit that movie corn? Yeah, please. Speaking of which. Yeah. No, I did. Well, I got it.
I think I got a perfect one here. All right. If you don't mind. Not at all.
I've been waiting to talk about this for a while. So I rewatched.
I actually, this sort of is along the lines. I don't even know if it is. I don't know why I
thought this was I just, you know what it is? It's, it's the hypocrisy of it that I think
you were talking about. You try to do the right thing with the electric car, then they fuck you.
And they're supposed to be the people doing the right thing. And they're not. Yeah. Which makes me
think of hypocrisy, which makes me think of my first movie corner. But I rewatched.
Has there ever, you know hip hop better than me. Has there ever been a rap album called Hip Hop
Chrissy? I don't know, but I wouldn't be surprised. I feel like that has to be out there somewhere.
Should you and I release a hip hop album called Hip Hop Chrissy?
Yes, and then do a sequel. Hip Hop Chrissy, like an idiocracy. We do, you know, that too.
Can we do it where we're back to back with our arms folded like Bugs and the Tasmanian devil?
Of course. Of course. Then it's a double pun because you got hip,
hippity hop Chrissy because Bugs Bunny. That's the third one.
That's the third one. All right. This is why we're ending the show everybody.
By the way, shout outs to a track star, the DJ who I've met and hung out with twice now
from Run the Jewels. He's a very nice man. Oh, all right. Anyway. Oh, so I rewatched the
final season of Roseanne. Sure. And I enjoyed it very much. You know, at the time it didn't seem
that great. It seemed like fine. And on a rewatch, I was like, this is because everything is so bad.
And I was like, this is a very solid piece of work. And it was just nice.
The OG Roseanne where they win the lottery, right?
No, I rewatched the reboot one. Oh, okay.
Like the when they came back in 2015 or 16, whatever the hell it was.
And it was just nice remembering a time where things were, you know, before everything was
war of the tribes and whatever the fuck and blah, blah, blah. And I enjoyed watching it.
I thought they did a really good job of tackling issue. You know, they really take it head on that
she's a Republican and a Trump supporter in the first episode. And they have Jackie wearing the
pink pussy hat and all that stuff. And I was like, this is great that there was a show where they
attacked this and Roseanne's jokes about the left are getting laughs and Jackie's jokes about the
right are getting laughs. And this is what it should be. Like we should be able to do this.
And it was refreshing or that's probably the wrong word because it's old. It was nostalgic
to remember there was a time where that was possible. And hopefully we get back there.
But I did enjoy watching the show again. For that reason. I also thought, my God, what a what a
terribly missed opportunity. And I said this when it all happened. But when Roseanne got in trouble
for that tweet, I'm like, you take it onto the show, man. She apologized. Now take it onto the
show. And that's your opening episode one of the second season. And you address it. That's what
they used to do with her in real time when she got in trouble all the time. So I thought what a
missed opportunity for us to have a conversation through comedy on a TV show. But whatever,
people's opinions are their opinions and all that stuff. But in watching that, I decided,
you know what, let me give this Connors a try. I've got friends on the Connors.
Meaning, oh, see, I was confused for a minute. You're talking about I forgot that Roseanne came
back for a Roseanne season. And then when she got canceled, they did the Connors with Jay Ferguson.
Okay, got it. Yeah. So so I'm like, let me give the Connors a chance. You know, I worked with
Sarah Gilbert on your show, Biblically. And she was very nice to me when I got thrown off of that
show. She was the first person to text me. And Ferguson is, you know, an all -timer, man. So I
thought, let me give this show a chance. And it's not a bad show. It's not for me, because
you're watching Happy Days without Ron Howard at that point. You know, it just feels weird.
But episode two of season one of the Connors, let me repeat that. Episode two of season one
of the Connors is an episode about cultural appropriation and approved of Halloween costumes
that children can and cannot wear at a Halloween event. And at the center of this
is Darlene's son, who is dressed as a I believe, a famed Hispanic woman,
because he admires this woman. And the principal of the school is saying you are not allowed to
wear that into the party. It is not appropriate. That is cultural appropriation. And then Darlene
does this big speech of it's cultural appreciation. I get it. We're not supposed
to offend people. But this goes too far. It's too much. It's this. And I'm sitting there going,
guys, you literally, literally just three months ago fired the woman that you're all there because
of. This show wouldn't exist without her. You throw her out without any, you didn't even give
her a chance to talk through it or whatever. And now you're going to do an episode about
how cancel culture has gone too far. Calm down, guys. You're not the platform for this. Just
move on. Just don't address this issue. Yeah. Well, it's a frustrating thing because
the Roseanne of the 80s, the Roseanne that my parents wouldn't let me watch anything. And when
that show first started, it was like, it's important for us to watch this. They wanted us
to see another non -huckstable, I don't mean black family. I mean, essentially a white trash family,
a family with no money that fought all the time where the mom and dad were always at each other's
throats. I really think my parents were like, we need them to watch this so that we don't seem so
bad. But they'd have these arguments. And you didn't hate the characters for you disagreeing
you. It's the same problem as the world at large. Roseanne should have been, especially when it
became the Connors, a show dealing with these thorny issues, because that's what multicam
sitcoms are supposed to do. But they have an actual issue that they ignore in favor of some
fake my kid wants to dress up like Don Quixote. It's wild. And I'm sitting there going, all like,
I was already thinking you've missed this opportunity. Yeah, it's like you could have
dressed this, it would have been iconic. You know what it should have been too is exactly what
happened. Roseanne saying, I'm allowed to speak my mind. There's free speech in this country,
right? And then somebody's saying, not if you're racist, not the things you said were racist.
Well then, okay, that's a fascinating episode of television, where both sides have passionate
arguments and blah, blah, blah. Exactly. But we're never going to get that.
Yeah, no. And it's just the last thing I'll say is, is I just, I've got a real issue when
it's like, look, man, do the thing that you do. That's okay. I don't have to agree with it.
But then stick with it. Don't turn on your heels and then start preaching the other side of it.
It's like, look, if you're a Trump fan, okay, that's your business.
But you've got to admit it would be odd if suddenly Trump was walking around going, you know,
we don't say grab him by the pussy. Not correct. And sir, I've got a problem with you saying grab.
It's like, buddy, you said it. Shut the fuck up. Let somebody else be the person who says we
shouldn't say that. You're not the person to be telling us that. It's like when I bitch about
Disney, Disney is not the company that should be preaching to us about what is racist when they
have been the committers of the most racist. It's like Disney. Song of the South, Disney.
Song of the South, which is in like school textbooks under racism. Song of the South,
they reduced or removed the images of John Boyega from Star Wars The Force Awakens posters in China
because Chinese moviegoers would want to see it less. It's insane. It's insane. They're doing
that as they're telling people like, we've put a warning on this show because, you know, it's
guys, just don't be racist anymore and shut up. Let somebody else who's never fucked up that badly
be the teacher. That's all I'm saying. I agree. But I got no beef with the Connors
theoretically. And I got no beef with Roseanne. I've never met any one. I've never met Roseanne.
I've met some of the Connors. I watched the first season of the Connors and it felt
almost like a little morality play each week. It wasn't it wasn't a knee slapper. It just felt
like they were trying to do little small stories. It just wasn't it was like a little one act play
every week. I admired it. I just didn't really laugh a lot. I watched new to Netflix fit for TV
colon, the reality of The Biggest Loser. I was not a huge fan of The Biggest Loser. I've definitely
seen it. But this was a part of that kind of crazy era of reality TV where you couldn't believe what
you were seeing sometime. I was trying to talk to my girlfriend about this show called Moment of
Truth. And we want there are episodes on YouTube. But they ask you these questions and you can keep
going and going and going. But you run the risk of losing more money. It's a deal or no deal type
pyramid. But the questions get harder and more exposing as it goes. So the one the random episode
me and my girlfriend watched, they asked this woman, you know, have you ever cheated on your
partner? And the guy is sitting there in the audience. And she's like, Yes. It's like, have
you cheated on your partner with more than one man? Yes. Are there any secrets that you'd never
told? And like, so you think it's all about cheating. And then you come to find out her dad
was a pedophile. And the dad and mom are sitting there on the dais, hearing it being revealed.
This was in prime time network television a while back. So The Biggest Loser comes out.
And this is my problem with people today is they can't, they can't accept that the landscape was
different. So they'll watch American Pie and be like, how has this not been criminalized?
Yeah, how is this moving? And you're like, because everyone in the world accepted it at that time.
It was the number one movie in America for months, weeks. So The Biggest Loser is this mocked up
outrage. It's people who are, you know, three, four, 500 pounds. And then the trainers are doing
really extreme tactics to get them to lose weight. And they're interviewing these people today,
and they're talking about how abused they were. And it's like, guys, like the worst thing you
in this thing is that they were given caffeine pills. There's people, for the first time,
I completely sided with the evil television network, a three hour documentary. And I'm like,
they're right here. So they're like, can you imagine you have a show under the guise of trying to help
people lose weight. And one of the challenges is a temptation room, where there's cakes and pies and
cookies. And we have to go in there for five minutes and not eat any of it. That's torture.
Okay, that's not a game show. No, I'm sorry. That's 1 million percent a game show. Us watching you
learn how to eat better is not no one's gonna watch the fucking show. You're not going to be
able to win a million dollars because they're not going to have it because nobody's going to be
watching it. Also, too, I think that's a I actually think it's a great exercise if you're trying to
get over something, you know, if you're million percent, that's going to be your life. The second
you leave this show, it's like an alcoholic being able to go into a bar and be like, Okay,
I can, you know, I can't be here for two hours, but I can, I can be here for 30 minutes. And then
I got to go. It's exposure therapy. It's what you're supposed to do, really, that the sob
stories of these people, and then so many of them had put the weight back on. There's a guy who
went from like 500 down to 200. And now he's being interviewed, and he's probably 700. And he's like,
you know, it's because of my abuse, the PTSD I have from the show that the weight came back.
No, man, you're a big fat dude. Your life is always going to be a struggle. That it's always
a struggle for the fat people. It's unfortunate. But this show was trying to help. And a lot of
you lost a bunch of weight. But they're like, we'd be we'd work out four hours a day. Yep.
Who's watching this in shock that you agreed to it, you signed up, you're going to tell me there
weren't a million forms that everyone had to fill out. I guarantee when I used to do drunk history,
I would fill out a million forms, I had to do a physical, a full physical to make sure that if I
didn't drink a bunch, my heart wasn't going to stop. You you you do it. Because you want to be on
television. I hate that shit so much when it flips. And they're like, No, well, now I was abused.
Or now I want money. And all week, they've been dragging that trainer Jillian Michaels through
the mud. I don't know anything about her. She might be a nightmare person. But it's like,
she was a fitness trainer. And I'm sure NBC was like, we need results. We can't have people losing
a half pound every week, or nobody's gonna watch the fucking show. It was one of the most frustrating
documentaries I've ever seen. I hated it.
I watched it sounds very fucking frustrating. I watched
right on topic the mad about you reboot, not reboot was the you know, when they did the new
season. Yeah, I remember it. I rewatch that just on the heels of the Roseanne thing.
I just really, I don't know, I got I really like mad about you. I like the original. I like the
original show to an extent it gets it gets too fucking I don't know, it just gets too maudlin.
Once they do the thing where, you know, they they almost have the the each of them almost
cheats or whatever. And then it I don't know, it becomes kind of a bummer after that.
Larry Charles season, I just read that he came on to fix the show. And that was his idea that he
put them through that affair. Well, you know, what's funny is they, they, they promoted that
as a very special episode. And Ellen, or Ellen, Ellen Barker, I think you always get Ellen Barker
and Helen Hunt confused. Helen Hunt said, not too long before that, she was like, I really hate
special episodes of sitcoms. And then the next year, they made them do that, that episode. It's,
it's, I, I get why it's relevant to the subject matter. But it's just too much of a bummer. And
they don't even really do anything. She kisses a guy at a party. And he almost cheats. I don't
know. And I enjoyed it. It is a great, it's down, but it's, but it's solid. It's solid enough. And
it's a nice return to all the characters. Which weird is, it was on God Almighty, I don't even
remember what streaming service it was on. But do you remember, that was the first time they ever
did that. When they announced that, we were all like, wait, what? Yeah, they're doing another mad
about you? Wait, what? Like, it didn't make any sense at the time. Now it's common, whatever. But
it was on like, you know, it was on like, a swatch watch original, the mad about you service. I don't
even fucking remember what it was. But anyway, yeah. Um, I enjoy to what a burger plus. I enjoyed
what it was on. It was a spectrum originals. That was the only spectrum original ever.
Yeah, I think it was. Um, but one thing they did that I thought was so perfect and put such a
wonderful button on the series. The show, if you watch the original show, it starts a few months
into their marriage. In the first episode is about how they haven't had sex in a while.
And she's worried that now that they're married, they're losing their chemistry and their spark
and their spontaneity and whatever. And it's a great first episode. And it really sets up the
show. This is a show about a relationship and the ups and downs and the challenges of it.
Um, the last season, they now have a grown daughter and the grown daughter is going off
to college. And they're heartbroken about it. But she's only five blocks away at NYU. And then at
the end of the season in the last episode, the daughter says, I'm actually going to go out onto
this ship in the middle of the ocean and help do garbage collection or something or other. And I
won't have a phone. You have no way to contact me. I'll see you in a year. And she leaves. And at
the very end of the last episode, they're there for the first time in 20 years, back to being
just a married couple again. And trying to figure out, okay, like, let's start our married life
again. It is a perfect full circle ending to this series. And I was like, I didn't catch that the
first time I watched it. The second time I was like, holy shit, man. They brought that full
circle. Like, they're not just going to have empty nest syndrome. They literally can't contact their
daughter. So it's almost like their daughter doesn't exist for a year. And they have to go
back to just being married again and figuring out what that is at this age for the first time.
It's a fucking brilliant ending. Um, and it was, you know, again, it was a fun enough watch.
I enjoyed it. I recommend Mad About You if you've never indulged.
And again, I've ever seen an episode. It always seemed too adult to me. I was
into Friends and Seinfeld. That was my parents' ship. Do you know they're the same universe?
I did, because doesn't Kramer appear on Mad About You?
He goes to, yeah, he goes to, Paul Reiser goes with Kramer to his apartment. They go to the
yeah, Lisa Kudrow plays the waitress, the airhead waitress. And then in Friends,
Phoebe says, like, I have a twin sister who's a waitress. And I think she even appears in the
episode as both characters. Yeah, one of the one of the great in person meetings I've ever had was
Paul Reiser. He was one of the fun in person, one of the funniest people I've ever met. He was such
a treat. And I was meeting on the Paul Reiser show, which was his curb that lasted five episodes on
BC. I'd love to meet that guy. He seems like he seems like he'd be like everybody's favorite uncle.
Yeah, well, I mean, I expected an asshole. I expected one of these guys. Like, honestly,
how you sort of view Billy Crystal is as a bitter old man who's like, fuck this. They don't know
what's funny anymore. But God, he was just like, No, I'm going to be the funniest person in the
room. And I'll show you what's funny. I watched another new Netflix documentary called Devo. It
is about a band that I love called Devo. I'm going to see them with the B 52s here at the
Hollywood Bowl next month. And I'm pumped. They still put on a great live show. This documentary
was weird. You know, I think the worst documentaries in the game are on Netflix, they, they always find
a weird POV. Yeah, they're, they're edited badly that they're just, it's always the guys sitting
down in a chair adjusting them the lapel mic. Are we ready? We ready to get started every fucking
time? Anyway, Devo is weird. It's it's Chris Smith, who was a great documentary director,
he did American movie for starters, one of the great documentaries, and the recent Mr. McMahon
about Vince McMahon. This people love that Mr. McMahon one. I like Yeah, it's a great study of a
complete sociopath. Especially for a guy who doesn't care about wrestling. It was just kind
of like, wow, this is like watching a documentary about one of the world's most evil people.
Devo showed me things I didn't know about Devo, which I appreciated. I didn't realize how
political they were, because they're so goofy. They dress so goofy. But they were formed in
Kent State shootings in 1970. And their entire thing, it might be I didn't realize this because
I didn't grow up with MTV. But they're very, very political. And Devo is about the devolution
of America of American values of American society. Okay, I didn't know that. Yeah, they're they were
really passionately political. They just happened to talk about their issues in kind of goofy ways
and when the clothes and the you know, everything else they did covers. So you don't think of them
as being a serious band, you think of them as being a novelty band, more like the B 52s. Now
the B 52s is not fair to call a novelty band either. They're some of the most influential
new wave music of that era, as is Devo. But that aspect I liked learning about the political side
of Devo. But I have never seen a more joyless music documentary, there's no fun in it.
There's no like, look at this great live performance of them. And I know there's great
footage of them. It was just a really funless portrayal of a really fun band. And then at the
end, they start trying to tie it into how far society has devolved today. And you're seeing
like clips of January six and things like that. And you're like, guys, now we've just lost the
plot. Yeah. You know, everything does not have to come back to this. Yeah. But yeah, it's it's yeah.
No, Nick, Nick, who's a guy who works with my management team, he texted me, we talk a lot
about music. And he texted me last night. He goes, this Devo doc is interesting, but they seem like
a tough hangman. He was like, they are just not fun at all. Like, so it's funny you say that.
It's not just that they're a tough hang. And they do seem kind of because they actually seem to have
kind of this wicked glee with how they're fucking with the mainstream. They remind I watched that
Zappa documentary, even though I'm not a fan, and they seem to have a big dose of that, you know,
they're always fucking with the interviewer. They're always winking at each other. They're
always have a private joke that the guy interviewing them doesn't get. But so I do
think it's a fault of the documentary, the documentary decided it wanted to be this very
serious political thing. And ultimately, I think anybody coming to this to learn about Devo is
going to be like, boy, what a what a serious, solemn band, which is like not the whole story
with that band at all. So I didn't love it. All right, I got I'm ready to move to the
movie of the day if you are. Let's do it. This is one at least privately Joe and I have been
discussing for months fearing. I read a few. Well, obviously, if you've been listening to the show
for the last 10 years, the naked gun movies are very important to me and Joe and huge parts of
our childhood. And we quote it and talk about it all the time. A huge, huge part of the naked gun
success is Leslie Nielsen. If you watch airplane now, you're missing Leslie Nielsen when he's not
on screen. You totally get why they decided to devote a whole movie to him and a whole franchise
to him. So how is Liam Neeson going to fit into that? That was always the big question. I got an
early copy of the script. I read that opening scene with Liam Neeson in the Girl Scout uniform
and I said, I'm not going to like this movie. I'm pissed. They didn't even get the tone right.
Frank Drebben is not a shape shifter. He can't become a little girl. And it really pissed me
off. But I went in, I forced myself and I really worked hard. I waited until I was in a good mood
to see the naked gun and I went in like, here we go, baby. Come on, come on.
We'll get there. I'd say my big overall statement of the movie is it was
not as good as I wanted it to be, not as good as the originals, but better than I expected,
but not way better than I expected. That's the area I'm in with this movie. I didn't hate it
and I thought it was an admirable attempt, a very admirable attempt, but they got a lot wrong for
sure. They got some stuff right and some good jokes and I laughed more than I expected to. How
I actually thought they didn't get a lot wrong. I was actually shocked at how much they nailed
the tone and the jokes and I laughed out loud far more than I thought I was. And I was in a pretty
full theater and the theater was uproariously laughing. So all of that was a nice pleasant
surprise. And I thought Neeson did a good job. I thought Pam Anderson did a good job. I thought
that, what's his name, Paul Walker Jr.? Paul Walter Hauser. Yeah, Marty Paul Funkhouser.
One way to tell Paul Walter Hauser apart from Paul Walker is that one is one of the best looking
men that ever lived and one is one of the worst looking men that ever lived. Yes, and one is dead,
right? Paul Walker. Yeah, one's a big fat guy, one who is alive and one's a real skinny guy who is
dead. But yeah, so I thought that everybody did a really good job. I thought the gags all worked.
The coffee gag really made me laugh that every time they walk into a scene they're being handed
a new cup of coffee and it keeps getting more ridiculous. And it made the car joke make sense.
Like when he gets handed the cup of coffee through the, then I was like, oh, that's actually very
funny. Out of context in the trailer, I was like, what the fuck is this? That's stupid. Anyway,
so all that I was fine with. The plot I thought worked. You know, I like this at the beginning
when you see the little device and it says plot device on it. Well, the older I get, I'm more
appreciate the villain work in one from Ricardo Montalban, but especially in two with Goulet.
I think Goulet is hilarious in that movie. And Danny Houston, who is an excellent character actor,
I hadn't seen in a movie in a long time. He was in every movie in the 2000s, the early 2000s.
He's a great villain. He gets it more than anybody else in the movie. I think he was the
funniest part to me. Yeah, he was great. But I'd say he nails it better than Liam Neeson for sure.
Neeson was, he wasn't pushing, he wasn't mugging, but he was trying to be funny in a way that
did not make the gruffness is right for Drebben. And when he made me laugh is when he was
Dirty Harry, which Drebben always was kind of a parody of when he was a racist or a loose cannon,
or he shot that guy, you know, because to make the line go faster, he shoots that guy or whatever.
That's the stuff I love. And that's the stuff that is timely and political. So I don't know
why they only had little driplets of that unless they didn't want to get the bad reviews of I guess
this is a movie that thinks police brutality is funny, which I'm sure they had to really
Yeah, walk a line with that as a major studio release. Definitely. If this was like a gym,
who's the guy that did Wolf of Snowholler? Jim Cummings, right? I was gonna say if this was
like a Jim Cummings movie, they would have been much more free to, you know, to do a more dangerous
commentary or whatever. But anyway, my problem with the movie solely relied on the direction.
I felt like, first of all, the beginning, you know, when he says Frank Drebben police squad,
and he's standing there with his undies, you know, you can see up the skirt and he's wearing
like girl panties, whatever. Yeah, no balls like you predicted. Yeah, I'm like, guys, hit me with
the music and they don't do it. It does like this action movie opening credit sequence, very short
credits week sequence. And then at the end, they do do the this siren gag, but they're literally
just replaying footage from the first movie, which confused the shit out of me. I also
know. Confuse is mild. I mean, it is so fucking cheap to do to send a second unit out,
you come up with the bits with the funny people, and then you send your second assistant director
out to drive through a car wash with a camera on, or to, to, you know, be the arrow going to the
target of the archery thing, you know, that doesn't even have to be the director's responsibility.
It's easy. It's cheap. It's funny how they missed that opportunity to give us a fresh new set.
I don't know, unless they thought, well, we'll never beat the original. But then why are you
making this movie to begin with? Also, too. They do the freeze frame gag from police squad at the
end. Yeah, which I love that gag in police squad. I hate that they updated in this, where they do
freeze frame gag, but Liam Neeson and Pam Anderson aren't frozen. And they're looking
at everybody else just standing still. And they're like, what's going on? What's happening right now?
It's like, it's so much funnier when the every actor, the best in police squad, when Ed,
the Ed character, I forget Ed's last name. George Kennedy, yeah. Ed Harkin. What's that? Harkin,
right? Yeah. Whoever played him in police squad. I can't remember. No, no, no, Kennedy plays him
in the movie. Oh, I know you mean. Okay, got it. But they do the freeze frame in the office. And
he's like, he freezes on like a fake laugh. Yeah. And he's got his coffee up. Yeah. And he's just
standing there forever. And then the dog comes in and starts licking his nuts. And he's just
standing there still. He's like shaking from the dog, the coffee spilling. It's so funny. It's
that's a perfect gag. Just do the gag. Like you don't have to don't fuck with it. Don't don't put
a hat on the hat. Yeah. So anyway, again, my issue with the movie was direction. It was it was a very
you had pointed this out with the trailers. It was a very colorless film.
It felt it felt like a modern action movie in a terrible way. Yeah, it felt too action movie ish.
And it just there's no brighter movie in comedy hit movie history than the naked gun series.
For Christ sakes, the font is hot pink. Yeah. I mean, these movies were bright. They were bursting
with color. And this is just like, I didn't like that part of it. And that was the part of it
that took me out of it. Because visually, it evokes a sadness. There's a bluish bluish hue
to everything. And blue is not a chipper color. Blue is a very kind of cold, you know, color.
Yeah. And it just didn't have the the vibrancy, or vibrance, whatever the word is, but that the
original films had so so your eyes are saying I'm watching something sort of somber and serious,
but then your ears and brain are hearing jokes. And it was just a weird contradiction for me.
I just feel like if you're going to do it, do it, go for it. And you know, and I won't talk
too much now about it, because I'll review I'll do it in the movie corner. But I watched Superman,
for instance. Superman, the new one. Yeah. And, and the, you know, I knew they were going to
use a bit of the John Williams Superman music from the Reeve movies. Yeah. But I thought
here or there, they'll put it in as a little sting. And it's just kind of a wink to camera.
It's it's almost the main theme of the movie. Yeah. Yet, the movie doesn't open with the classic
Superman opening with the music booming and in space with the logo. I'm like, guys, if you're
going to do it, do it. Like, go for it, man. That would make everybody happy. And instead,
you're doing this sort of passive version of it where you're sort of doing it, but you're not
really committing to whatever. And that's kind of what I felt here. I'm like, guys, you're going
forward in every other area except visually. And just go for it, guys. Make the fucking naked gun.
That's clearly what you wanted to do here. Why are you pulling back in the quick because some suit,
some suit and some skirt said, you know, behind a boardroom meeting table said,
young people won't go for the brassy music. It has to start like, you know, whatever.
That was already parodying something from from 20 years prior. So at this point, it's 50 years old.
I mean, it's it was already kind of a relic when it came out in the 80s. It's a weird thing to
update what I might have done. And I think I might have enjoyed the movie more if they came to me
and were like, you're rebooting this. We'll do whatever you want. Why not make it a parody
of this entire new genre that Liam Neeson has invented, which is dad action, you know, do a
take a full length taken parody along the lines of spy hard or Jane Austen's mafia where you're
walk hard, where you're parodying the biopic, but parody the specific thing. Because to me,
this didn't really feel like the naked gun. It felt like a parody of something else.
All I can really judge this on is it's jokes. I mean, that's what the naked gun is. And for me,
I wasn't dying laughing at any point, but I laughed more than I expected. And I just I think in terms
of comedy as a thing now, it's better than most comedies we've had in the last five years. Sure.
It's still just unfortunately, just an average movie. Yeah, this is what I would say. Pam Anderson
doesn't get a single moment. She's got that scatting bit, which sort of felt like death to me.
My theater was very quiet. And that's tough on a comedy. I sometimes it just can't be helped if
theater sucks. The movie is going to not really play that great. Sure. But I just I don't think
we'll get a sequel. I don't think it did well enough. I think I think there'll be a seek.
I mean, the reviews were great. It didn't make money, though. It didn't make a lot of money.
No, it probably broke probably break even. I rewatched as you were talking about the direction.
I rewatched Pop Star last night. Never stop, never stopping. Pop Star is a way funnier movie
than the Naked Gun reboot. And it's it's in a very, very similar style. And they have the same
director and co -writer Akiva Schafer. So it is odd to me that Pop Star was directed brilliantly.
It works both as a music documentary and the thing it's you know, the thing it's parodying
the parody. The Naked Gun. Yeah, every choice seems off. That may just be that it is so much
harder now to get anything of quality made and they had to fight every step of the way. I don't
know. But yeah, the Naked Gun, I guess I'll say it could have been a lot worse. It could have been
a lot better is where I'll leave it. Yeah, my hog is straight out, not up. If they make a sequel,
I'm open to it. I'd be open to watch this again and see how I feel on a second watch.
And that's about where I stand. We'll be back with another legacy sequel.
Happy Gilmore 2 in the next episode. Folks, we love you and until then, we'll see you next time.
And we'll see you in hell.