🎵
It's will see you in hell.
I'm Pat.
Walsh!
You know, you're not. I'm Pat Walsh. You're gonna do it.
Well, sir, not good at the interesting start on that one. Folks, today we are talking about the 39th film in the Halloween franchise Halloween
Kills directed by David Gordon Green written by Danny McBride, David Gordon Green and some other guy starring in a cameo role, Jamie Lee Curtis,
Anthony Michael Hall and others. We will get to Halloween Kills as we always do at the end of the show.
Blumhouse strikes again. Here we are. Taking out a thriller spec soon. I'm not gonna talk about Blumhouse.
Got one out there now. You know, you're the the mortg saw of whatever we're doing.
I'm actually gonna take about Blumhouse movie. I liked in the movie corner to it. Okay. All right.
Was it the new Amazon one? No. Okay. I didn't see that. Blumhouse is always dropping movies on Amazon that I guess didn't quite make the cut or something.
They made for Amazon. I don't know. Yeah, I didn't see that. I got a quick scary stuff. If you want to collect as Pat and I do these types of films.
We so often discuss in this show, check out the label blue underground. They're doing some really cool stuff.
Very similar to a vinegar syndrome or what Vestron is doing now or arrow or any of these places.
Blue underground. Some very, very cool titles fairly priced and worth checking out.
That's it. Excellent. Now, Joe, let's get to the issue at hand. Why did you tell Alec Baldwin to do what he did?
I mean, that the guy else, you know, I'm so unshakable now, like I'm just like everything hits me.
He just like complete numbness because of the events of the last every years.
And when I woke up to see Alec Baldwin had shot, she died. I know it's not funny people, but I'm just talking about the world as it is now.
Of course, my heart breaks for this woman and her family and everyone who knew her.
But God, it's just every day is a new and sane thing happening. Do you see this video of hilarious and Alec pulled over with some like paparazzi yesterday?
No, it's a must see. It's riveting and you get to see it just how I mean, it's no surprise, but just what a ticking time bomb Alec Baldwin is.
He, the video is this. There's some paparazzi following him and his wife who is still using the fake Hispanic accent in the video.
And finally, Baldwin pulls his car over, gets out, walks back and he's like, what do you want to know? Okay, what do you want to know?
My kids are in the car crying. What do you need to know?
Ask your fucking questions, ask your question. He looks so intense and frazzled. And then hilarious is filming with her cell phone, the people who are asking him questions, the paparazzi.
And she keeps getting in front of Alec Baldwin while he's trying to do his little impromptu press conference.
And he looks like he's going to hit her on three different occasions in this three minute video.
And he's like, could you just get away place?
Wow.
And he's like, excuse me.
And he's doing this with paparazzi there. I imagine that home relationship is a tense one.
Oh, my God.
Did you hear the rumors that apparently on this movie set, everybody had walked off the day before because safety regulations.
And then I mean, all the producers are like, sorry, we weren't there. We had nothing to do with it.
I mean, I honestly, I think the director, this is another landest type situation. I think the director certainly is going to face potential jail time.
And I think Baldwin could in theory, you know, the only thing that could possibly get ball went on would be in voluntary manslaughter.
And I don't think, I mean, I don't even think he has to get a high powered lawyer or anything. I think he'll be fine.
The director, I guess I see it as different from land is because land is was screaming, get the helicopter blades closer to them.
You know, on a coked out uncontrolled set. This seems like just a terrible situation all around. The crew was not well equipped. Now the director hires the crew.
But sometimes that's a production manager's job. Who knows?
I mean, if you're directing a movie, I would think I would think if you're directing a movie and your crew walks off over safety regulation, there was also another story that crew members were taking the onset guns.
Yeah, particularly this one and like doing like target practice with live ammunition. Who the fuck is allowing this to happen?
I know. And why the fuck is there a real gun on set for Christ sakes?
Just no clue. I so my experience is largely in sitcoms and then the rare occasion we have a gun, which does happen.
The they announce it like a king entering his court. Like it's like a huge announcement. A guy holds up the gun. He shows you each chamber of the gun. It is boring and dry and exactly what you want when you're bringing a gun onto a set.
It's the fact that none of these precautions were done is rough. But I mean, this guy's the director's career is probably done. It's just a sad story all around, you know, it just seems like this girl, the girl who was the armorer, which is a person in charge of guns on a set had done a podcast interview where she talked about how she feels like she's not ready sometimes like they're going back and getting stuff like pulling it for the for the trial.
It's like, you know, I really felt like I wasn't ready. And I was unprepared on my first set. And I didn't know what to do. And I like just things people have said in their everyday life. We're going to come back to haunt them now. It's a tragedy. It's a terrible situation.
Jesus Christ. And I don't know when hilarious video is something to watch. And of all of all people of all people bald wind. Yeah, it's like, hey, buddy, where's your
Your gun concern seemed to go out the window when it's time to shoot a movie. What the fuck, man?
Well, I mean, look, and it's not just because I like Alex, well, I've heard the man's a monster don't get me wrong, but I don't think he's under any responsibility here at all.
No, but I'm saying if you're going to be a guy that, you know, he made fun of Cheney for the friend of the face thing, he hates Trump, he hates Republicans, he clearly is a proponent of gun control.
And that sort of thing. I would think a man with his policies and his political persuasions would say you're not putting a real gun on my set.
That's not how I do it. I'm just shocked that the place making the most noise about gun control is still utilizing real guns. I mean, I can't think of a more careless thing you could possibly do.
No, it's crazy where we just watch Dune. Yeah. And you know, it's like, what are we doing here?
They also talk about how now in most of these big action movies, Dune, I'm sure included, they do it just how they would have done Star Wars, you know, with the pew and the blue laser coming out of a gun, they just put in a little white flash and the noise in post coming out of the gun.
It's so easy and cheap to do that there's just no reason to be still using blacks and everything else.
I mean, Brandon Lee should have should have been the the upset that caused big change. And I don't remember at the time, if they talked about changing protocol, but truth is, everyone in Hollywood is obsessed with getting the most for the least money.
And that's always going to be at the cost of safety on a low budget film. That's not something that they're going to prioritize.
Really gross. It's really gross. It's bad and terribly sad for this woman and her family.
It is. It is. Yeah. And the and the paparazzi, of course are like, you think you'll ever act again, Alec.
Oh my God.
And you know, he exudes intelligence even when he's incredibly pissed off. He has good answers to all their questions.
But anytime they ask something that isn't directly related, he's like, there's nothing to do with this investigation.
I mean, they're like, they're like, do you have to stay in town or you and he's like, I'm cooperating, but I don't care for the way you're suggesting that I should be scared or that somebody's going to come after me. I don't care for that.
He, I mean, Jesus Christ. Yeah, the it's just wild. Nobody lower than a paparazzi. Nobody disgusting.
And they took pictures of him morning, like a minute after it happened, they were like up in his face, taking pictures while he's like yelling into the phone. I killed somebody.
Terrible. Apparently all he kept yelling after it happened was, why was I handed a hot gun? Why was I handed a hot gun? Very valid question.
I mean, yeah, I don't understand. I just I briefly thought it was because he's considered, you know, I've heard tales myself of him being a complete asshole to people on set.
I was like, was somebody just really pissed at him, you know, and I don't think somebody pissed at him would want him to kill an innocent person.
No, but I did briefly go to these dark places. I mean, I'm a bit of a no, it sounds like it just to me, it sounds like it was not a well run set.
No, nobody knew what the fuck they were doing crew members were getting away without rageous behavior regarding firearms.
Yeah, and something terrible happened. Yeah.
You know, and they're going to need a fall guy and the fall guy will be the director. I promise you, you might be right. You might be right.
I promise you, speaking of, and getting out of something also not funny, but I guess time has made it funnier.
I told Joe, you got to watch this coming to America. It's the movies that made us on Netflix, which they hit and miss. It's all about how much you like the movie.
If you like the movie, you'll probably like these. They're our line specials. They're kind of like VH1 style pop up documentaries about some of your favorite films.
The home alone ones good. There's some good ones in there. But I watched the new coming to America one.
And I have never seen outside of like these Dick Cheney documentaries or Trump documentaries. I have never seen a documentary filmmaker with more disdain for who they're doing it about.
That these people hate John Land is so much. So it kicks off with they go, all right, would you just tell us who you are and and how you're related to the movie.
And he goes, really? Did anyone else that you interviewed for this thing make you do this for you? Did they say their name, other directors?
And it's like, have you ever heard of a, he made a documentary about Don Rickles? Yeah. And then it cuts.
It cuts to every director they've ever interviewed doing the exact thing. It's no problem.
It's, he really does not come off goodness thing. If you're told that you're going to be in a documentary, the very first thing you have to do, even if you're a Barack Obama is say, hello, I'm Barack Obama, you know, it's, it's 101.
And he's such an ego maniac. So throughout there's all these people, they, they go to talk to George, George Folzy, one of the producers of coming to America, who's now 90 and like sitting slumped over in a chair.
And anytime land is comes up, he looks like he's going to be sick. He's telling this story and they go, well, actually, that's not the way John Land is told and he goes, well, he's a fucking liar.
One point in his eyes. He's got one of those high pitch gravely voices. And at one point, he goes, they go, that's not how Land is said it. And he goes, oh, no, fucking.
Yeah, it almost seems like that got me out of the way for movies due to working with Landis. They tell the great story. I recommend googling the Playboy interview with Eddie Murphy, where he talks about how he choked out John Landis, which is amazing.
But they go into that story. Landis is like, oh, is that what he said? Oh, that's not really what happened. I don't know, you know, like he's, he's clearly everyone hates him and every time they cut to him, he's like, oh, that's not really wasn't that bad. It wasn't really that he's in denial.
His wife was the costume designer on coming to America. She gets one moment to shine and she's talking about these dance shoes and how in the big dance number, the women all had trouble dancing in them.
And she's like, well, yeah, I mean, not dance shoes so much. They were really kind of like these really like jazz shoes. Can you hear this voice off screen go, well, those are dance shoes.
And she looks over and she goes, excuse me, like he's talking over his wife's interview.
The whole subject of the movie is about him and he can't give her one moment in the sun.
It's really a, it's so much. And then go back to that moment again and again, where he won't say his name, the documentary keeps breaking the fourth wall to shit on landis.
They get into the twilight zone thing.
They say that they think landis was in that state of mind, because he was pissed that nobody came to his defense. Yes, when that happened.
But who knows Eddie Murphy in on the Arsenio Hall show, they reference this joke. They don't show the clip says after they wrap coming to America.
John Landis has a better chance of working with Vic Marl again than me.
That is, that is that cuts glass.
I wanted to see that clip so bad. Maybe that's on YouTube, but like Murphy, Eddie Murphy, everyone knows the man is a brilliant performer and a brilliant stand up.
But when I heard that, I was like, oh, he's also like a fucking nasty roast comic bitch too. Like that's a great joke.
You forget that he's like a kid from Brooklyn, you know, like really, really wild.
I guess I can tell this. I think I can tell the story. When I met Norma McDonald, he told me, I don't know why the hell he told me this. It was odd that he opened up this much.
Because he didn't know me. We were just hanging out. He didn't barbecue. And he goes, he told me the story of Eddie Murphy, like going after David Spade, because David Spade made that joke.
A look at the phone. Yeah. And he said Eddie Murphy kept calling David Spade at 30 Rockefeller Center. David Spade kept dodging the phone calls.
And he said, and then finally the secretary or in the office goes, Eddie Murphy's on, you know, on the phone. And he's like, just tell him not here. And she goes, no, no, no, you don't understand. He's downstairs on the phone. Like he's in the building. Yeah. And he said, Norma McDonald said that they picked up the phone to listen in.
And he said, Eddie Murphy said, David Spade, you're afraid of me because I have friends in high places. You better be afraid of me because I have friends in low places.
I was like, Jesus Christ.
Yeah.
Yeah. I mean, that, that story is him, is him choking John Landis because he put his, he put his money on main. Basically, he, there's these writers on set that Eddie Murphy's company hadn't paid and Landis was like, Hey, when are you going to pay these guys?
Next thing, you know, Murphy's got him in a chokehold. And he's like, you don't talk about my money. Like tell him what happens when people talk about my money.
And this man at that time was the unquestionably the biggest box office draw in America. Like that's nuts. Yeah. The, it was a different time. You could get away with something like that back. Yeah. Yeah.
The, you know, there's the great recurring thing in that episode with the one writer when he says he comes up with the idea to make the two homeless guys.
More or more in what's his face from trading places and like Landis keeps saying, if you bring it up again, I'm going to fire you. That's the dumbest idea. And then it cuts back to this guy like 27 minutes into this thing.
And they're like, but there was the problem of the homeless men. Who would play them and it cuts back to that guy. And he goes, they ask me again. And I'm like, you fucking know who I think should play them.
How many fucking times I gotta say it. Yeah. I love that dude. That old dude. Just classic old Hollywood grumbling. Yeah. Just people were, it was, it was a fiery.
And, you know, Eddie and Arsenio are not in it. Yeah. It reminded me of how funny Arsenio is.
Because they played the clip from Amazon women on the moon, where he's the guy having the worst day ever. And I was like, I forgot how fucking funny Arsenio Hall is, man.
Yeah, I mean, he's great in the first movie. It's weird that they couldn't get him to do this documentary. I get not getting any Murphy, but I feel like he's probably like guys. I have to be careful that like my whole legacy isn't coming to America.
That's true. That's true. He was one of the best interviews I heard on Stern. He was awesome to listen to. And I've never cared that much about the man to be honest, but he was great.
They don't interview any of the cast as a matter of fact, except John Amos. He's the only one. Like they don't interview the wife. That's true.
Did the sister, did the hot sister who's like always horny in the first movie. Does she come back in the second one? I can't remember.
The hot sister who's always horny.
Oh, I don't, I bet she was in there for a quick cameo, but I don't, I don't recall specifically.
Yeah, John Amos is the only actor they interview.
And then the Frankie phase on stuff is all just brilliant, but we've talked about that on the show. Yeah, yeah, you're conscious.
Are we ready for the movie corn? Yeah, well, I mean that almost was.
It was, yeah, but go ahead. Yeah.
What I'm going to do is I went to the new Beverly all night horror fun.
So you went, you were saying you weren't going to go because your, your soul was dead or something like that. I did go and I'm glad I went. It was the, you know, the one Joe and I went to here was at the Alamo and it kind of sucked.
You, what were the other movies that were in it?
Cubes, which was currently streaming on Netflix. Yeah.
The house on Haunted Hill, starring Chris Catan, because the curator said when I was, I don't know, when I was 12, I just love this movie. It freaked me out.
Yeah, we're not here for nostalgia trips, sweetheart.
Terrible. Just a piece of shit movie.
And then they played that fucking like shot on video movie by the guy that did green room who said I'm not going to stick around so enjoy the film.
That's how much he didn't give a fuck. And that was streaming on shutter at the time.
I don't know how we even stayed till the end of that. That really, and it was really expensive. So no, there were two here.
There was one at the arrow in Santa Monica that really did go seven to seven. And then I found out the new Beverly one was just four movies, seven to three. That's why I wanted to go as I was like, you know what, I can do that. That sounds fun.
Hit me with the flicks, babe. Would you say, well, they came out. And similarly, everyone was like, you heard this groan go through the audience because these two guys were like, okay, I thought I might be Tarantino there actually, but it's just two kind of right hand men who are great.
But they were like, we decided the theme tonight was going to be movies you have never seen and maybe never even heard of.
I'm like, you can't do that when we're here till three a .m. Like you got to have some, I mean, it doesn't mean you got to play gremlins or some shit, but like, I don't know. So they didn't tell you till each movie started what it was going to be actually didn't know till the credits what it was going to be. And that was really fun. I liked that a lot.
But here they are. The first one was and I'm going to, by the way, sorry, I'm cutting you off just for a second. The fourth movie at that thing was the it's so bad it's good.
Horror movie from Canada of like the people trapped in the house trying to find the money.
Like it was like it was literally like an irony like isn't this so terrible. It was like a room kind of movie. How did we stay the whole time because we kept thinking because they again, they didn't tell you the movies we kept thinking it was going to get better.
Fucking ass was a rough day, the rough day.
The first one up was called nothing underneath. And it came out in 1985.
It's a thriller set in Milan, Italy, where a serial killer uses scissors to assassinate top models, a yellow stone park ranger.
But it was probably not what you thought the next sentence would be a forest ranger who works in yellow stone park in the USA has a twin sister who has become a jet setting model and he claims they have had a psychic bond since childhood.
But there's a lot of him like touching his forehead and then he can feel what his sister in Italy is feeling.
It was ridiculous. It was sleazy. The music was by Pino Denagio who scored a lot of Brian de Palmas movies. And the music was great. It was so trashy. It felt at many times like it was going to go into hardcore porn. But it was mostly just a soft core.
It's a new day and age. I mean, I saw eyes wide shut in theaters had no problem with that. But something about sitting in a theater where people are having sex in 2021, it does feel weird. I don't know why I guess because we're also sanitized now.
But I don't even know where you would find nothing underneath. I don't know where they got a print of this thing. It's not streaming anywhere.
My cat is attacking me. It's, it's well worth checking out, but it was kind of a so bad. It's good. And there you go. It was nuts.
I said, I review a Blumhouse film. I actually liked. I finally watched my Blu -ray copy of Ma written by our friend Scotty Landis. Yes.
I was riddled with nerves, turning it on, thinking God forbid. I hate this. God forbid. What am I going to do?
But I thought it was great. I thought it was a really solid, fun little thriller. Scotty's a great writer.
Octavia Spencer certainly elevates the whole affair.
And I enjoyed it. It's basically a fatal attraction type scenario, except it's about a woman who becomes obsessed with teenage kids because she wants to relive the childhood that she was that she never had because she was mocked and at the
a bunch of like very cool pranks were played on her in high school. And the people she went to school with now. She's hanging out with their kids. Yeah, trying to recapture that, but also in a weird revenge kind of thing. And I enjoyed it. I enjoyed it.
I thought the alternate ending was cooler than the ending that was on the movie.
Okay.
The movie just ends with the house burning and you don't know what her fate is and it just cuts to credits.
There's an alternate ending where you actually see her in walking through the veterinary clinic where she works and the back of her neck is burned.
Okay.
So interesting.
Yeah. So I was like, oh, that's a, that to me is a cooler cliffhanger, like to set up the next movie.
The guy that directed it is a little bit of a numb nuts. I don't know. He directed. I think he directed the help which is odd that he went into horror after the help.
He also did get on up, right, which I liked.
Yeah, I like it.
Anyway, I read an interview with him where he talked about a sequel and he's like, I want to have her killing a bunch of white people and Mick mansions.
It's like, you tell me white guy says something. You just sound like a fucking moron. But anyway, I agree. I agree.
I liked the movie quite a bit. And I hope Scotty does another piece of horror.
Yeah, I think we initially didn't do it on this show. I saw it in the theater and I think we didn't do it because you were afraid.
We were like, what if we, what if we don't like the movie? I think it was a lot of fun.
I liked it a lot. But I mean, what are you going to do integrity wise? You can't, you can't have a review show and then go, well, my friend made it.
So I liked it. Right. You know, we've, we've, you know, I'm going to panic the other night.
I was talking about Peretti's dropping me lines. I'm like Christ almighty.
And does the man have any idea?
I liked, I liked mock quite a bit. I thought the kills were like wild and like went to some crazy places and was very fun.
And it is a female horror lead, you know, every time I've mentioned that I watched to somebody say every first sentence every time.
Dude, would she hits that lady with her car? I was like, yeah, that's wild.
Yeah. And it's what's her face. It's, um, missy. Isn't it missy pile?
Missy pile. Yeah. I believe. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I, I, I dug the picture.
Um, up next for me, I'm going to do this one in five seconds and then move on to the next one because there is four. We're only doing three.
The vampire in the ballerina was up next black and white 1960 putting in a, a black and white movie at one of these things late at night is always dangerous.
And luckily it was short. It's a bunch of beautiful dancers who find themselves trapped in an old castle and there's vampires in the castle.
I have no idea why the man thought this was some lost gem. It was boring as hell.
Quickly, let me get to the ruins, which was our next picture. And this is where everybody burst into applause because I was shocked.
Oh, applause. This movie sucks.
I thought you hadn't seen the ruins. Wait a minute. The ruins where they go to the place and the plants are alive or whatever.
The violence. Yeah. Terrible. I own it. It's one of the only horror movies I've ever gotten rid of that I bought.
I saw it in theaters. I liked it a lot. I actually remembered a brief moment of nudity in it that I was stuck in my head forever.
I rewatched it recently. So when it came up, I was like, God damn it. But I love the ruins.
Seeing it on the big screen, watching everybody squirm and freak out at all these gross out moments, it's vines going into legs and into sides and et cetera.
It's short. It's nasty. It's gruesome. I completely disagree with you, Joe, because I think this is one of the best of those like 14 horror movies that they are, you know, 14 age kids or whatever go to an exotic place.
I think it's one of the best. I love it. It's down and dirty. I love the book. It's based on the guy who wrote the book wrote simple plan as well. And he wrote this screenplay.
I would check it out again. There's some really effective scares, some very effective gore.
Already incredible on the big screen. It really did. I'll revisit all I remember is a lot of CGI vines that I didn't find scary.
And I also remember being very disappointed that the horror was a plant. Yes.
When I bought the blue ray on blind faith, because I thought it was going to be people going into ruins and encountering, you know, I don't know, fucking skeletons or something.
Yeah. And when I thought it was going to be like the descent, like that kind of thing. And then when it was plants, I was like, God, damn it.
All right. I'll revisit. I finally watched when a stranger calls, never stand up.
Carol Kane.
It's a great little movie. I mean, you know, it's funny. I always thought this movie was her babysitting the whole time. I thought that was the whole movie.
Yeah, so did I. It's not always heard great opening. And then it tapers off the big twist of the calls coming from in the house. That's that's in like the almost the cold open. Right.
But it's a pretty brutal cold open when you see what transpires. And then it goes into it. This is funny because this relates to our movie today with Halloween.
I mean, in one of the problems with it, it then jumps forward 10 years. And the guy that this crazy person is released.
And he's back on the street. And will he strike again. Charles Durning is the detective. And this is like the case that broke him.
And he's now a private investigator, but he gets brought back in to pursue this guy, because he knows there's probably a threat.
Probably not a lot of foot racing going on with. And then eventually it circles back around to Carol Kane's character who now is married with her own children.
And is moved on with her life as anybody would.
Versus creating a militia training center in your home, instead of just leaving the town of Hattenfield where you're convinced this guy will come back one day to kill you.
So I liked it. It's, I think it was a theatrical, yeah, it was a theatrical release, but it's got that made for TV vibe.
Yeah, of a 70s made for TV. I enjoyed it. I think it's worth checking out.
I'd love to. Have you ever seen the little girl who lives down the lane? That's another one that's kind of a TV feel that I've never seen.
I own it. It's one of the ones I haven't opened yet. I need to watch it.
Yeah. And my last one is fatal pulse. I had never heard of it. So they came out. They asked who here had has not seen the ruins in every hand, but mine went up, which was shocking to me.
You've figured they're horror fans. The new Beverly usually gets obsessive film fans. Nobody had seen the ruins.
So no one had even heard of fatal pulse. And the guy apologized over and over and over. He's like, you're going to hate me. He's like, I'm leaving so that you guys don't beat the shit out of me and the lobby afterwards.
This is one of the worst movies ever made in the history of time. And so they ended with a so bad. It's good to I the older I get have less and less desire to watch something that's so bad. It's good to make fun of it.
I don't I don't get into it anymore except for fatal pulse, which is weird and bad in such an alien way that to me, if anyone knew about this movie, it would be on the same pedestal as the room.
Okay. It came out in 1988, the director directed one other movie. That's like a foreign movie. This it feels like a movie that was made by somebody not who wasn't from America, but somebody who wasn't from Earth. It is completely insane.
It's it's 10 sorority girls. A girl is killed and raped minutes after fighting with her boyfriend. Jeff is the assistant of professor called well at the university and he wanted to return with his old girlfriend.
The girl lived with another five girls, including Lisa. All these girls begin to be killed one by one in strange ways. The main suspect is Jeff.
That is the an alien wrote that that is the synopsis they have available for fatal pulse. I don't know how to describe it to you. It's chock full of nudity as well. I don't know where you can find it.
But if you are a fan of the room, if you're a fan of so bad, it's good, or if you just want to see something that blows your mind and is fun to watch with a group of friends, I do recommend fatal pulse.
Finally, a double speech. I rewatched Halloween four and Halloween five. I won't talk at length about these. If you've never seen them, Halloween four absolutely is worth a watch. It is a very, in my opinion, solid solid sequel and entry into the franchise. It is a perfect sequel to part two.
Pleasants, the whole nine. It's good stuff. I enjoy it. Five is too much more of the same. It's not very good. It's not good. It's not as bad as six. It's not as bad as resurrection. And it's also not as bad as the film we're discussing today.
Halloween kills the latest entry into this franchise that people will not let go. I mean, my God, I just don't get it.
We've got a what's the last one going to be called Halloween lives Halloween ends. And there's a four year time jump.
Okay. Why? I wish I had known how much this Halloween kills was going to continue the story of the Halloween that came out a couple years ago that Joe and I did on the live show.
Because this thing's starting and I'm like, they expected me to remember all these plot points from the new Halloween.
Like, and they really do. I guess that's fair. That's what sequel is always used to do. But I was confused. I'm looking at Wikipedia. I've actually now watched Halloween kills twice, which I can't believe.
Just because the first time it was so hard for me to even pay attention to it. I thought it was so dumb. Weirdly, I liked a little little more in the second viewing as with noon.
What were your thoughts, Joe? I feel like they're negative.
It's.
When I first thought I said, this is the worst Halloween. I don't feel that way anymore. I don't think it's, I think it's equally as bad as resurrection and six.
Six.
Okay. So let me, let me do a little history here. Yeah. Yeah. You'll know, I've seen them all, but you'll know like how this connects because the opening is a weird prologue in the seventies.
And they're taking completely unnecessary legend, but not some other stuff from the legends of walk us through.
So point part six is called the curse of Michael Myers. And it's a real shark jump. It would ended the franchise for a while because it was about how there was a curse and a tribe.
And he was not human and all it's just stupid shit because they were grasping at straws to try to explain. How does he keep coming back to like, why can't he die or whatever, right?
Terrible. That movie's main character was Tommy played by Paul Rudd, who they tried to get to reprise the role in this film. Big surprise. He said, no.
Every interview they go, he was tied up with Ant man and the wasp to or whatever. I was like, yeah, I'm sure that's what it was.
You know, anyway, so that's so that's a mistake they made in the in the sixth movie. Yeah.
The seventh movie, I'm sorry, the seventh movie was H2O, which this has retconned and doesn't count anymore as a true sequel because H2O follows the original storyline that Laurie Strode is his sister.
Right.
So that's off the table. Make just make note of these details and pointing out resurrection, which is worse than part six is the sequel to H2O, which is terrible because for some reason, Michael Myers needs to get kills Jamie Lee Curtis at the beginning, which is the point of the whole thing.
And then he keeps killing why because it's not about Jamie Lee Curtis. It's that he has to get back to his house. What the fuck, right.
And all of these sequels that I'm talking about right now have been essentially erased because John Carpenter has had a stick up his ass since 1980 that he made them brother and sister and that the studio wanted a sequel of this movie.
So as we've discussed on here, Danny,
Eastbound and Downs, whatever's name is McBride and Green, David Gordon Green and Blumhouse said, well, we're going to restart.
We're going to make a true Halloween sequel, and they do the Jamie Lee Curtis one from two years ago, which, oh, by the way, I forgot the Rob Zombie movies, which are terrible. I don't really count those.
But in the Rob Zombie movies, one of the things I hated was that he made Luma's evil.
He made Luma's like exploitative of Michael Myers and not somebody that cared about the fact that Luma's in those.
Malcolm, the guy from Clockwork Merge, was it?
Yeah, yeah.
Anyway, anyway, I'm going through all these little plot points for a reason.
We get to now the David Gordon Green, Danny McBride version of Halloween, which is supposed to now be a direct sequel to the first movie.
Right away, we're in trouble.
We've already talked about this on the show. I already mentioned it earlier today.
You take away the brother sister aspect. It makes no fucking sense that Michael Myers is obsessed with this woman.
Another huge mistake they made in that movie, which was already done by Rob Zombie, was they made the doctor pursuing Michael Myers actually evil.
Stupid, stupid, stupid, stupid.
A lot of the elements of the first Halloween in the reboot were weaker, lesser versions of what they already did in H2O.
Agreed.
It was all completely just derivatives.
And on top of all of it, we've talked about.
And they're raving about how this new one deals with grief and trauma and et cetera.
And that was all taken from H2O.
And I feel like they did do it better there.
She was having drinking problems and et cetera.
Because in H2O, she did what a person would do in that situation.
She moved away.
Yeah.
And hid.
Right.
And was struggling to forget her past, but moved on in some way with her life.
She didn't sit in her backyard doing target practice for 40 years.
It's so crazy.
Anyway, now we get to Halloween kills.
They are sticking with the fact that they're not brother and sister.
They address the fact that Michael Myers doesn't give a shit about Jamie Lee Curtis.
Because why would he?
Why is Michael doing this?
The kills are a straight line back to his childhood home.
Okay.
So now you're doing resurrection, which is awful.
Even Buster Rhymes, a friend of mine met Buster Rhymes.
It was like, I like Halloween resurrection.
And Buster Rhymes was like, that movie sucks.
It does.
It's terrible.
Yeah.
So they do that.
They beat, shoot.
Whatever the fuck, Michael Myers.
So many times in this.
And who's leading, by the way, sorry, who's leading the charge in this movie?
Well, it centers on Tommy.
So now you're doing part six.
Already been done somehow better in a piece of shit movie like part six.
They somehow did this better.
Yeah.
They beat Michael Myers in this.
They shoot him.
They do everything.
They do it.
It doesn't make any sense.
This is a 66 year old man.
I did the math, which is older than real Michael Myers, the comedic actor.
Yeah.
It's the same age as Dana Carvey.
Strangely enough.
You're telling me if Dana Carvey was terrorizing your town, the town couldn't handle it.
You know, yeah.
So anyway, well, I mean, it goes back to the old thing.
Is there a supernatural element to Michael Myers or not?
Is there never really unkillable?
Well, at the end of the movie, Jamie Lee Curtis says,
you can't kill him with brute force.
He's pure evil.
Right.
Bullshit.
He's not.
He's a kid who killed his family.
And he lived in a fucking institution ever since.
He's not working out.
So he would not be superhumanly strong.
Yeah.
If there's no supernatural element to it, and I'm glad there isn't, then what goes on in this movie is, is absolutely absurd.
It's the kind of stuff that happens in Marvel, but that's because the person is a superhero with superpowers.
And he can beat up 50 people at a clip and not break a sweat, you know.
It is a terrible, terrible movie that starts mildly interesting with the flashback to the 70s.
Don Pleasants.
But I knew we were in trouble when the little kid who you meet later on as a grownup says,
who, who did you, the cop kid says, the kid, who did you see?
And the kid says, the boogie man.
And I go.
It's not known that he's called the boogie man.
Like, this isn't like you, the kid wouldn't say that's like a thing that the fans know.
Yeah.
So everybody in this movie acts the shape.
Everybody in this movie acts as if they, they're people that have seen the Halloween movies.
The way they talk about him.
Then you get a CGI.
Pleasants coming in.
Right.
Like, guys, for Christ's sake.
Hold CGI Pleasants because in that first movie, nothing underneath.
I forgot to mention that Donald Pleasants is the cop.
He's drunk or stoned throughout the film, slurring almost dozing off during one exposition scene.
And you can see it.
And I think because the director was an American, he didn't notice how bad the performance was.
There's a scene where they're approaching a crime scene.
And it's two cops up front.
And Donald Pleasants was supposed to be in charge of the investigation in the backseat.
Looking out the window like a dog with a big smile on his face.
And they're, they're coming to like solve the crime.
And in the funniest scene of the movie where I had tears streaming down my face.
They discussed the harrowing details of these rapes and murders.
At a 80s salad bar with a giant Wendy's sign in the background.
I guess this is when Wendy's had a salad bar.
Giant Wendy's.
They go and sit down.
They're, they're putting salad on their plates.
And they sit down and have this intense conversation while the one guy eats salad.
And Donald Pleasants eats a giant bowl, which was not available at the salad bar.
Of sauceless spaghetti noodles.
No, that was available.
It was three things.
The Wendy's before.
Yeah, it was salad bar, taco bar and, and, and noodles and spaghetti.
To have pleasant eating these noodles and discussing murder.
I mean, it was one of the funniest things I've ever seen with Wendy's in the background.
It's like product placement in the middle of this.
Anyway, Don Pleasants.
Apparently it wasn't CGI.
It was a lookalike or they combined to look alike with the CGI.
Whatever the fuck they did.
It's, you know, so you're like, okay.
But I'm still at this point invested enough in the movie that I'm like, all right.
Where are we going with this?
Maybe this will be interesting.
And about the 25 minute mark.
Anthony Michael Hall pops up.
I was excited to see Anthony Michael Hall.
I always, I'm on his team.
Yeah.
He.
First of all, looks as if he actually lives in the town.
And his drinking at that bar every night.
The man is, I mean, looks like a young Rodney danger field.
Like he's aged, you know, he's not going to look like he looked at 16 candles.
I know.
But he's pretty good.
He's, he looks like he puts him, puts it away.
Who am I to talk?
He's had a drink.
Yeah.
Who am I to talk?
Anyway.
He gets up on a stage at this Halloween party at a bar.
And tells the legend of Michael Myers, the boogeyman.
He starts calling him the boogeyman.
Everybody's calling this guy the boogeyman.
Is if this is just common knowledge.
He tells this story.
It's just ridiculous.
And that, that like, we're going to fight.
And we're going to be ready when he comes back.
And all that.
This is not what you would do.
And it's like a standup night.
It's going to open mic night where he takes the mic and gives this big lecture.
By the way, says we're going to be ready to fight when he returns.
And this is the night where he could all, you know, we have to be aware that he could return.
And then he goes to the bar and gets shit faced.
Yeah.
That's correct.
So, I mean, you know, it's, it's just lazy bad writing.
Anyway, Michael Myers sure enough strikes.
They get word of it in the bar.
Tommy is like going to lead the charge.
There's a couple that are a doctor in a nurse.
And they're also dressed as a doctor in a nurse.
I guess it's a joke.
They're literally fleeing from the bar to go home to get inside where it's safe.
Because there's a killer on the loose.
The boyfriend goes, hold on.
I forgot my stethoscope.
And goes back into the bar.
I mean, the writing in this thing is nuts.
Like it makes no sense.
Yeah.
It makes no sense.
Turns out the person at the bar they think is Michael Myers is just another escaped patient.
Who ends up at the hospital and everybody at the hospital, by the way,
which is now grown into an angry mob of people hanging out in the hospital.
By the way, whole thing takes place in a hospital.
What else took place in the hospital?
What else had Jamie Lee who occurred as in a hospital bed the whole time?
Halloween fucking two.
You know, the one that you said sucked and we got to fix it now.
It's crazy.
The amount of shit they're pulling from the other movies that they're,
that they're trying to cancel.
What's there to is I saw this, you know, floated as like,
there's a lot of fun nods to the other Halloween for the true fans.
And it's like, no, I really think they just kind of use a lot of the same ideas.
They didn't feel like homages to me at all.
Yeah, it's worse versions of things they already did.
And they're saying they're trying to make a better sequel.
It's terrible.
He's going to do this with the goddamn exorcist.
I guarantee it.
The exorcist is another one of these franchises with like one good sequel
and a bunch of do'sies.
And he's going to somehow make worse exorcist sequels.
Well, you love three.
I love three.
Three is amazing.
But I'm saying to Mike, he's going to somehow outdo like the Stellen scar scar.
Like Egypt one or whatever the fuck that was.
You know, I never even saw that one.
But David Gordon Green.
I, well, I love like all the real girls.
His early indie movies.
I obviously love his work with Danny McBride.
Yeah.
I love pineapple express.
I love a lot of what I love.
I don't mind him mixing genres.
Some comedies.
Whatever.
But like this just does not feel like the man's strong suit.
In terms of his writing or his directing, it's it's a miss.
For sure.
He once again, and look, you know, I'm always on here bitching about PC,
culture, run a mock and all that stuff.
But once again, he's got a black lady in this black character.
And the first one it was the little kid.
Kid was funny in the first one.
The kids funny, but it's like, okay, so second time around now you have a black character.
It's Lenny Clark's girlfriend.
Yeah.
And it's the same like gag of like.
Like like she's talking like she's in like what's happening or something?
And it's like it's awkward man.
It's fucking awkward.
It's a little weird.
Like you're like.
And it's an it's an equal opportunity killer.
But for some reason watching like a 60 year old black woman gets stabbed in the throat.
I was just like, okay, this is not.
You know, it's.
Well, she was carved out as any more of a cat like if she was an actual character,
it didn't.
It doesn't.
It wouldn't feel weird.
It feels weird because you feel like like this stereotype character gets thrown in.
Right.
You know, like, you know what I mean?
You're like, you don't have Lenny Clark being like, you know,
where's the beans?
I'm from Boston.
You know what I mean?
It's like why?
Like and they did a pretty sensitive for those guys anyway portrayal of a gay couple.
That was big John a little John.
Pat Strange edition Michael McDonald from Matt TV and Scott McArthur,
who's a very funny actor.
Pat big John and little John big John a little.
I did not find this to be a courteous or or or or flattering portrayal of a gay couple.
I thought it was outrageous.
I'm saying that in their portrayals, I would say that they were they weren't as swishy as
perhaps they might have been in a movie from ten.
They were wearing satin robes.
All right.
Good point.
One in one part, the guy smoking weed and dancing alone.
Yes.
And they call each other big John and little John.
It's outrageous.
And they live in the Myers house.
Yeah.
I mean, they just live at the house.
That's it.
They're kind of the first first gay appearance in all the Halloween.
I mean, I guess.
So I for some reason, it didn't bother me that much.
And in both movies, what I liked the most were I liked the the black kid that their
baby sitting in the first one.
And I kind of liked the gay couple in this one.
They're the elements that they introduced.
Everything else where they're trying to kind of do a mullage of what we've seen before feels
wrong and ridiculous.
Essentially, you realize at some point you're watching a Judy Greer movie,
which I liked Judy Greer.
And she's she's just bailing it right in.
I mean, she couldn't be less invested in this thing.
They killed Toby Huss in the first movie who was one of the only like sort of interesting
yes characters.
They got they got Will Patton and Jamie Lee Curtis.
Again, two of the interesting characters bedridden through the entire thing.
There's a there's a sexual tension between them.
Remember I kissed you.
Oh, I do remember that.
What?
So what you're watching here is an Anthony Michael home movie with Judy Greer in a supporting
role who by the way, Curtis isn't in this thing.
She's just not in it.
She narrates it like the old like an Edward Scissorhand.
She's like an old woman who lives in a castle narrating the story.
And by the way, when she goes.
Judy Greer's daughter goes on leaving the hospital.
Stay with grandma.
Judy Greer goes, where are you going?
She goes, I'm going to go join this vigilante mob to hunt down the killer.
And her mom goes, yeah, I wish you wouldn't.
But you know, but then she goes and does it and the mom doesn't go.
I need to go find my daughter.
She's going to get herself killed.
There's none of that.
Anthony Michael Hall leaving leading the charge of evil dies tonight is horrendous.
It's embarrassing.
Them all like what an odd thing to chant evil dies tonight.
It's like, okay, that you can put them on your poster.
But I don't buy a group of people chanting evil dies tonight.
Then it's really building quote from like a previous what I mean.
Like they're like, they're like, they'll know each other.
Another fucking Halloween movie.
Yeah.
It builds to what is a very clumsy statement on mob justice.
Cancel culture maybe is in there too.
I don't know, but they all get hot and bothered and think they found Michael Myers.
And they break in this guy jumps out of a window and kills himself.
He's not Michael Myers.
They've got the wrong guy.
It's supposed to be making some sort of point about mob justice.
It does not really work.
And then I think we're supposed to be rooting for Michael Myers as he kills 50 firefighters in the street and everything else.
You know, I've seen the kills kind of raved about in this one.
They're well done.
There's none that stick with me as being particularly noteworthy.
They were fine.
They were not.
And this is, you know, this is when I often say horror is like porn.
It's not enough.
Right.
You're not going to say this.
This porn was good because I saw some fucking.
Yeah.
You know what I mean?
Like you're not going to say great script.
And hard does the same thing where it's like you think the gratuity is going to is going to carry the story.
It's not.
The kills were fine.
They weren't anywhere near interesting enough to carry a movie.
It wasn't that kind of movie.
It wasn't like a fun ride rock.
Like there was nothing fun about it.
It was.
It had the kills.
I was talking to Pinkstone about this.
The three best kills in horror movie history are Jason Voorhees putting somebody in a sleeping bag and bashing it against a tree.
Jason Voorhees slamming a woman's face through an RV door and the RV door making the imprint like loony tune style on the other side.
And Jason Voorhees dipping a woman's head in dry ice and then like slurpy splattering it on a countertop.
You're never going to beat those.
So you know, yeah, how this.
What did you think of the mob justice subplot and all that?
Did you think that the themes were coming through or at all?
No, I thought the themes were.
As usual with Blumhouse completely heavy handed.
Right.
I was very confused as to which side they were.
What the commentary was because Curtis in an interview said that the movie has like a BLM analogy.
And I'm like, I don't understand.
Are you saying more for that?
Yeah, I'm like, are you saying that BLM is bad?
Or the mob is, I don't understand.
At one point she's screaming at them.
It's the wrong person you sheep.
Nobody's listening.
By the way, lady, sorry, everybody's riled up after you've been like lurking around the town carrying a shotgun for the last 35 years.
Telling everybody this guy's going to come back and murder all of you.
You might have had a little bit of a hand of that.
But you know, and then it made Anthony Michael Hall's character so ridiculous and also so unlikable.
Yeah.
He's almost the villain in this.
Which I didn't get.
You are sort of rooting for Michael Myers.
If it's going for the theme of like mob justice is always bad or whatever.
Well, this mob is trying to kill the man who's killed everyone in this town 38 times.
That's not a bad mob.
Then they have to get their message across by making the wrong guy jump.
But it's like it's it's very murky what they're what they're doing here.
It doesn't work.
Although because it is short and I watched it the second time on the peacock, which actually made me laugh out loud as I pushed play.
There's just something funny about it to me.
I don't know why something streaming on HBO Max isn't funny, but something streaming on peacock is funny.
But that's just the way it's because it's like there's like the thumbnail of this next to like 30 rock.
Doesn't make any sense.
Also, I signed up for peacock to watch it without ads.
And I now every day I get an email like, hey, there's some movies you might enjoy on peacock.
And every day I click on the email and it's just a picture of Halloween kills.
That's that's their algorithm.
You liked this movie.
Maybe you'd like to watch it again.
Yeah.
But it's not great.
I liked it more on a second viewing.
I think just because I was able to just sit back and enjoy the kills and I wasn't trying to follow the convoluted plot and the timeline and everything else.
But I really hope that three is the end of this.
It won't be.
We're going to get the real.
I'm already said he's open to doing more after this next one.
Yeah, at least get Jamie late.
Let Jamie Lee go to bed. Let leave her alone.
It's, it's, they also too with this thing where it's like the timeline doesn't make any sense.
Up until so when Jamie Lee does her big speech.
Yeah.
About like he's, you can't just stop him with this.
He's pure evil. He's this and that whatever.
She makes that speech.
Of two hours.
After he was burning in her house.
And after she said, so, so, so her entire life.
She's known Michael Meyer.
She's not an idea of Michael Myers is X Y and Z.
Right.
And then suddenly two hours later, she comes to this realization of he's walking pure.
What?
It doesn't make any fucking sense.
It's stupid.
There's a part where she even says like the end of the first.
Oh, oh, oh, this is huge.
I can't believe I almost forgot this.
She's laying in the hospital bed.
Yeah, we got him.
We got him.
And she's so happy.
We killed Michael.
Yeah.
At the end of the last movie, you're in the truck screaming no as the firefighters are approaching to put the fire out.
Why are you so positive?
He's dead all of a sudden.
It doesn't make any sense.
No, it really doesn't, Joe.
It really doesn't.
It seems to me that a lot of these guys, once they get success, they are able to do like five projects a year.
And the quality just suffers.
And as I said to Joe, I don't know this.
My theory, my thought is this movie was written by these two guys.
Stoned one afternoon.
And then they bring on a different third writer each time who maybe tries to make some sense of what they do.
But that's my guess is that these guys put very little time into it.
They're rushing these movies out.
The next one is going to be the same.
Are we are we carrying over characters from Halloween kills into the last one?
We have to have a Curtis showdown or what are we doing?
I assume that the end will be Curtis finally like dying at the hand.
Like they'll kill each other like one of those things.
Okay.
It can't be greer.
I mean, we can't just be watching.
They they've done a terrible job of giving you new people to care about.
They give you some funny new characters here and there and then they're quickly killed.
But like they're not they're not building the franchise out in a way that we could keep going with.
We don't care about Greer.
We don't care about Michael Hall.
We don't care about any of these people except Curtis.
And you got her sitting in a bed.
I don't know if that's because she said I'll only do the movie if I can do it in a week or something.
I think a lot of times actors do that.
But it's like.
But also two.
We're here to see Jamie legal up against them.
She's sitting in a bed.
Also two dude.
It's like.
The cops.
I love the scene after scene where the cops are sitting around as the mob is plotting.
Yeah.
And they're just like, yeah, whatever you guys want to do.
Are they living in the same America?
They got they got goddamn machine guns in Union Square Park every other day at this point because they don't know if somebody might break a window over there or something like.
Yeah.
What the fuck is this?
Speaking of the cops, why are you introducing an obese black man and a cowboy hat as like the town sheriff and then not doing anything with him.
As soon as he walked in, I was like, oh, this is going to be a good character.
It's barely in the thing.
The cowboy hat was so confusing.
I didn't understand.
Yeah.
It's like, okay, this is a you can't have that character walk into frame and not help us out.
Not give us something about the man or what why he is wearing cowboy.
And they brought back like, I guess Braddock from part two and.
I don't know.
Two hogs way down.
Well, my hogs way down.
I can't speak for years, but mine's way down on this movie.
I think it is as bad as Halloween resurrection.
Redeemable only in the fact that it has a few more potentially interesting kills.
It is a terrible, terrible movie.
My first viewing was this is the worst Halloween ever.
My second viewing was able to really take a step back and and file it somewhere in the lower middle of a franchise that isn't good.
I think it's.
How do you compare it to the other David Gordon Green Halloween?
I didn't like that, but that was the leagues better than this one.
Like it was better.
I just.
Yeah.
It's a it's a missed opportunity.
I feel like Halloween is the worst long running franchise that there is.
I mean, there's so few great movies in the franchise.
There's in my opinion, there's one.
I know, Joe.
I think there's only one great Halloween movie.
I think the original is great.
And I think that there are scattered decent Halloween movies.
I think one, two and three are perfect.
I mean, I'm sorry.
I think one, two and H2O would make a perfect trilogy.
I think four is a solid entry, as I said.
I love three, even though it's, but it's, you know, it's completely off base, right?
Yeah.
But yeah, but I think after that, it becomes, you know, five, six resurrection.
Right.
The zombie.
I mean, look, you, you really fucked up when Rob Zombie's Halloween movies are better than your Halloween movies.
Yeah.
I got to say they are.
I didn't mind them that much.
So all right, folks, that's our show.
I'm not going to plug.
We've plugged already.
We've plugged.
I have no idea what we're doing coming up.
The eternal is getting shot on.
I guess that's a possibility.
But we don't have any plans.
We'll let you know.
Maybe possibly.
I thought maybe, maybe eventually we do the new curb season.
Maybe that might be fun.
It might be fun.
You watched the new one.
Yeah.
I don't want to say anything.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
All right.
So we will let you know.
Thanks to all.
Happy Halloween.
Of course.
Thanks to Emily for all of her hard work.
I think you will for the new art.
Well, thank you.
Well, for all the art that you guys do for us.
And just that's fun to check out on Instagram and so forth.
Thank you for supporting us on Patreon.
Thank you to my agent.
Thank you to my mom and dad for believing in me.
I wish they were here to see this.
I do want to say.
I don't know if Joe got on the the Thursday night talk.
But I said I would be there and I wasn't.
I apologize.
I do fully intend to be on there.
And hang out with you guys.
I promise all I love that everybody's doing that.
And I promise I will stop by it at some point.
I'm just getting the ever living shit kicked out of me right now between getting the bar open.
And doing shows at night and doing two podcasts.
And I went and saw the stroke.
Yeah, I wasn't on.
Anyway, I'll see you guys soon.
We will see you next time.
And we'll see you.
And hell happy Halloween.