I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, and when the sound of your screams becomes
a thing of my dreams, you know I'll say, I'll see you in hell, you know I will, I'll see
you in hell, you know I will.
Folks, we'll see you in hell is back, back, back, back, to Unite as we discuss the film
of a divided country, Civil War, whereas Pat would saw it, War -er -er.
Civil War.
Or would say it, I said would saw it, damn it.
Written and directed by Alex Garland, a man I am rapidly losing respect for with each
passing film, the new A24 joint, did you see it in IMAX Joe?
No, I did, I like IMAX for kind of a weird reason, on a movie like this where there's
no reason for it to be in IMAX, it's just there because there's nothing to put in theaters
right now, you get to hear great songs on the best sound system imaginable, like in
this movie they play Suicide, which is a band I love from the late 70s, early 80s, and to
hear one of their best songs like blasting with the IMAX sound is pretty cool, I saw
one of the shitty Spider -Man movies that I did not like at all with Zendaya's boyfriend,
and they played Isimbra by the Talking Heads, and I was like you know what, that almost made
it worth it to hear that great song and this great sound system, one of the best things
I ever did in IMAX was go to see a Soundgarden concert, a three hour Soundgarden concert that
they just played live after his death, not live obviously, but yeah if you ever get a chance it
winds up being an amazing place to hear music, like Stop Making Sense was awesome in IMAX,
little tip for you, anyway. I can't remember the last time I was in an IMAX theater,
I don't really enjoy the visual experience of it, it's too big. Yeah I mean like people will tell
you, you sit in not the first three rows obviously like the ones that are on the floor, but you're
supposed to sit dead center and then like pretty close to the front so that your entire field of
vision is screened, that's where you're supposed to sit, and I find that to be a little overwhelming,
especially with these movies being three hours long. I like to sit like in the back row of the
IMAX and just have a giant screen to look at, but I see everything I can in IMAX because out here in
LA you can see a regular movie for like 15 or you can see an IMAX for 25, and since I have an AMC
Stubbs that enables me to see anything, I like getting that bargain and getting more for my money
going to see the IMAX, or a 3D but they barely make those anymore. Do they make them anymore?
It's amazing man. God it went away fast. Like it does every time. It was supposed to bring us back
theaters and it kind of worked. Yeah, I'm glad it's done. I was like all right with this stuff.
No, I hear you. I got sick of doing it for sure. I started choosing the non -3D option,
which I never thought I would do. I saw this at the Little down in Pennsylvania,
not Little, but there's a classic movie theater from like the 90s that's owned and operated
privately now. It used to be I think a Regal or something, and it's like 10 bucks a movie,
and you go in and it's like a fucking time warp. There's video games in the
lobby, and there's cheap concessions, and the seats aren't great, meaning comfortable, but
I go there a lot. I'll find myself out and about running some errands, and then I'll be like,
you know what? It's a nice day. It's about to be dusk. I got that feeling I used to get when I was
a kid and it was summertime, like I'm going to go to the movies, and that's how I saw Abigail and
both just on a whim, and it was really enjoyable too. That experience is very enjoyable,
but we'll get to it. We'll get to Civil War. I can't believe it. We're going to have different
opinions. Are we? I think so. I'm basing out on what you've said so far. We haven't discussed
it yet, but I have a feeling we're going to have different opinions. Well, I mean, we may. I
definitely didn't expect you to love Civil War, but we'll get there, or like Civil War, but we'll
get there. Yeah. I got a new psycho or two. Please. Well, first of all.
Is it about how Tom Selleck might lose his ranch when blue blood goes off the air?
No, no. I don't understand how that's possible that he could lose his ranch. He's got the money
to have bought it by now. I don't understand. I read the article. They're like, but so blue
bloods, there's no scenario in which he isn't making a half million dollars an episode of blue
bloods at this point. And that's roughly $12 million a year, 11, 12 a year. He's got savings
from the movie career, the TV career, the 40 year acting career. And he's got this California
ranch and he's like, I can't believe they canceled blue bloods. I might not be able to hang on to my
ranch. I'll be fine, but I might lose my ranch. And I'm like, are you looking for sympathy, Tom?
Yeah, they all do. I have a, I have a very famous friend who has a sort of famous wife
and he's always complaining about money. And I'm like, you have so much money, dude.
And he goes, no, the problem is we started living like we had money.
My wife started living like we had money. So now we feel all the time, like we're poor again,
because we're trying to keep this lifestyle going. And you don't have to do it guys.
Like when I started making good money, I bought a house and nothing else. I didn't like start,
you know, go on a clothes tour or show up in a Porsche or buy a California ranch.
This is not a business where you're always going to be rolling in coins. There's going to be
down times. You got to plan. I don't know why I'm lecturing Tom Selleck on, on financial planning.
I shouldn't have to, Tom. Well, yeah, I mean, you know, it's the problem probably isn't the house
payment. He's probably paid off the house. The problem is, is you need a $50 ,000 a month staff
to run that house. Yes. When you have a house of that size, it's like,
you know, dude, you have, you have grounds that need keeping from wild animals and shit like that.
It's like, you know, there's, there's a lot that needs to be done. You can't just like let that
house sit there. So that's probably what he's referring to. I've had friends who were like,
I'm putting a pool in, you know, I don't, I truly have, I don't even have an estimate of how much a
pool might cost, but let's say 20 grand. Okay. I don't know. Maybe somebody just laughed at what
an idiot I am, but it's LA. Maybe it's 20 grand. Then you're like, okay, we've got 20 grand. Now
we're going to have a pool, but you've forgotten that you'll need someone to tend to your pool,
to take care of your pool. You need chemicals, you need a heater, you need this, you need that,
you need a cover for your pool. It really is. People just don't think stuff through. It's like,
I have enough to do this. And that's the end. They don't think about how they'll have to maintain
it and keep it up. I was going to put a hot tub in my backyard in Pennsylvania. I've been thinking
about putting one on my deck. I love a hot tub. And I talked to my friend, Jamie, about it for two
seconds. And he goes, don't do it. Don't do it. I did it. Don't do it. Yeah. Tons of maintenance.
You got to change the water. You got to clean it. He goes, don't do it. And I was like, say no more.
You, I'm not doing it. Yeah. I'm not doing it. I had a similar friend who helped me out. Just
talk to somebody who has it. They'll usually tell you the truth. So, so my new psycho, well,
I have two here. The first, well, this is really the new psycho. The other one is sort of not really.
Martin, this is from movie web. Martin Freeman hits back at outrage over gross intimate scenes
with Jenny Ortega as Miller's girl leaps up the Netflix charts. I just watched that movie.
So I'm curious what he had to say. It's an erotic story where 51 year old Freeman
gets close to 21 year old Ortega and some people were not happy. You know what? That's what the
movie is about guys. The movie is about an inappropriate age gap and a power gap with a teacher.
But here's the thing. It's not an inappropriate. I'm not getting mad at you. I'm getting mad at
society. It's not an inappropriate age gap. That's why the law says it's not inappropriate.
Well, he's also a professor. He's also a professor. Fine. That part's fine.
Yeah. But it's only Anna essentially without the assault element of it.
But the gripes are not about the teacher thing. It's about that he's older than her by 30 years.
Right. And this fucking thing.
It's not. Hold on. And he had this come out and go. We're not saying isn't an age appropriate.
Isn't an age gap romance great? He goes, that's not what we're saying.
People said gross and troubling sex scene between the two leads. Now here's the thing.
It's barely existent. There's no nudity and it's a barely existent sex scene.
Here's the thing. This is yet another one of these articles that claims there's a lot going on here.
I'm not even going to get to the other thing. Well, you know what? No, I will get to the other
thing because it's linked to this and these fucking people. OK,
this is yet another one of these articles that is claiming there's this huge outrage and backlash
and yet there's no examples of the backlash in here. So this is something now that these studios
do. They plant these concepts and these news stories of this outrage. By the way, the movie's
poorly rated. Terribly rated. Produced by Seth Rogen also, which is odd.
This is what they did with the Rings of Power. They came out and they said, oh God, everybody is
there's this huge backlash by racists about how the Rings of Power, the Lord of the Rings show was
cast. I went online. I was like, well, what are they saying? I couldn't find anything. Then you
look at the ratings of the show and the ratings are terrible. It's not being well received.
Oh, well, the controversy makes people want to see it and support it and whatever. So that's
probably there's probably some truth to that happening here. But this concept of the age
inappropriate, whatever. Guys, if you want to have a real discussion about this, talk about the laws
needing to be changed. Don't say it's gross for some two adults of age to be together in a fake
setting. Yeah. Okay. And by the way, how come when it's fucking Timothy Chalamagne
and Army Hammer, it's fucking beautiful? I always question that one as well. But I think,
you know, we know the answer to that one. This, well, this is one of those things that makes me,
it makes it sound like I'm being like, how come when the gay guy, I don't mean it like that. It's
guys, get your shit together. Be consistent with this. And by the way, go ahead. And I'll say the
second part. Sorry. No, go ahead. This is what bothers me. It's, you know, Chappelle had many
specials ago had opened up with the thing 15 is 15. Yeah. He's like, if we're going to persecute
R. Kelly for hooking up with a 15 year old. Okay. This is way before R. Kelly went to and years and
years. If we're going to, it was when the Pete video came out that was bootlegged everywhere.
So we're going to persecute R. Kelly for doing freaky shit with 15 year olds. That's fine.
But then like, and I'm paraphrasing, don't turn around and put Britney Spears on MTV
with her tits and ass out when she's 15. 15 is 15. We either treat it like it's not a sexual age
or we don't. And I think that that's a very fair point. It's not me saying 15 should be sexualized.
It's me saying that I'm so tired of everybody talking out of both sides of their mouth with
every cause. It's gross when it's this, but it's not gross when it's that. No, no, no guys. Gross
is gross. Violence is violence. Wrong is wrong. Right is right. There is no justifiable version
of any of those things. There's no such thing as justifiably wrong. There's no such thing as
justifiably right. It's your right or you're wrong. That is it. Now there are degrees. Okay,
fine. I agree with that. But, you know, as I'm bitching about this, the other thing I had in
my notes here for New Psycho was the new Twisters trailer that opens with the 25 year old lead
actress being called in by the tornado committee or whatever the fuck it's called and saying like,
we're going to need your help because this is the expert. Right. A 25 year old. This is the expert
in the field of tornadoes. And she goes, can't do it. I don't chase anymore. So they want us to
believe that a 25 year old can be a grizzled hardcore veteran that has lived life, that has
seen life, that has been down the road. You know what I mean? When AOC talks, it's like, isn't the
youth great? And we should be listening to them. And they are now I know AOC is not 21. But my point
is the fervor around it is we should be listening to the youth. Okay, fine. That's fine. I'm with you.
But then you can't turn around and also say, it's disgusting if a 50 year old hooks up with a 21
year old. Well, why is it disgusting? We're saying they're adults. We're saying that we should be
listening to them. We're saying they're part of the conversation. We're saying they're legal in
every single way to vote, to drink, to do anything, to go to war, to die. Why is this gross? Like,
oh my God, it drives me fucking crazy. Um, I hear you. I mean, I think people are allowed to say
it's gross, just like you're allowed to do it. I mean, uh, it's, it's a lot of it's jealousy,
I think a lot of the time. Um, there is an odd double standard that if a woman dates a much
younger man, everybody celebrates it. If a woman likes older men, everybody thinks that's hot. If
a girl's got daddy issues or whatever you want to call it. Um, they criticize it. They're saying
it's gross. The guy is gross. They're saying that's what I'm saying, Joe. They celebrate.
Sorry. They celebrate the woman in that circumstance, but not the man. The man is the
lecherous old predator. Um, and the truth is situations are just much, much, much more
complicated than that. And human beings are much, much, much more complicated than that.
I had gone my entire life, never dating anyone who wasn't within five years of my age.
And when I got single as a 42, 43 year old man, whatever your palette changes, not, not, not my
taste change, but on these apps, you wind up some girl likes you and she's in her twenties. Some
girl likes you and she's in her thirties. Some girl likes you who's 50. It's just kind of the
beast. And if, if someone's approaching me, you know, if I felt uncomfortable when I met
them, that would be different, but it's, it really is case by case. People are different
and people have different tastes and, and you gotta kind of celebrate them all. I understand
what you're saying, Joe. It's never a comfortable thing to be passionately arguing for,
for this topic. I hear sort of feel like, you know, like this, this movie in particular,
I think they're trying to drum up controversy just because nobody was watching the damn thing, but
I don't know. I feel like most people, certainly people our age don't give a fuck.
People coming up here, these terms like problematic age gap and all that stuff
on Tik TOK as they grow up. And that's all they know. Their parents don't talk to them about that
stuff. So it's like, they just form their morals from Tik TOK on a variety of issues.
And it's like, well, we'll see what happens when you get older and you're actually out there dating,
you know, people change, people are different. Here's the, here's the, here's the,
where I would say somebody would have a point in this department. Yeah. Now, if you want to talk
about some guy in his fifties or forties or whatever, who only dates 18 year old girls,
which was a lot of guys, when I first moved out to LA, anytime I met a guy's girlfriend,
I would be like, are you fucking kidding me? Every time that's changed. That's gone a little
bit. So if you, I remember I was having a discussion once with, with a burr about this
and he referred to those types of guys as pressing their nose against the glass.
Yeah. He's like, they're trying to get right as hard up against the line as they can.
Right. I agree. And that's the turn on for them. Probably. Yes. I agree that that's weird. I agree
that if there's a pattern in behavior, it's weird or could be a telling sign of something,
but I'm just sick and fucking tired of hearing about every time there's some age gap romance
between an, a man and a woman in a movie, in a fucking movie, there's gotta be these stories
around it that are questioning the morality of it and all this bullshit. Meanwhile, every fucking
a studio head and producer and whatever. I mean, I love that. These guys are all running around
with fucking, you know, 23 year old girlfriends and whatever. Nobody's questioning any of that
shit. You know, it's, it's, it's, it's the characters in the movie. We have to question
once again, fighting the fight with the most benign fucking path you could possibly fight it with
not doing anything about it. Do something. If you think it's weird to fucking start a movement,
to have the age of consent up to 22. But I mean, this shit here, it's like saying it's,
it's inappropriate for a 22 year old to get drunk. No, it's not. They're of age. They're of age.
Yeah. I mean, if this movie really had the, had the balls to like talk about this issue,
which it does not, I've seen it. It would have been, the girl would have been 16, 17, you know,
something that is illegal. It is kind of a strange thing to be moralizing on something
that our country has deemed. Okay. However, you know, I think we should do away with
guns also everyone's dying too, but that's also on the books. It's clearly time that if everybody
wants to change the morality of the nation or, and they're not going to be able to do this, but
make some fucking amendments, change the law is how this conversation started. Like
you got to change the law. You can't get mad at people for not breaking the law.
And as you're saying, Joe, the people who are pushing against it are weird,
but they're also not breaking the law. So it is hard to, I don't know, you can't really
moralize against what's, what's allowed, you know, I shouldn't get as wound up as I do,
but God, it makes me mad. The, the one, the complaining, I know that's ironic coming from
the complaining annoys me people. That's all. That's all. But anyway, and, and, and a Martin
Freeman and a Jenny Ortega, two seemingly sweet people just trying to make their fucking way in
the goddamn business, you know, like leave these people alone. They're two of the act, few actors
I don't have a problem with. Yeah. Okay. Anyway, good. Um, I got a couple of myself real quick
ones. Number one, yes, Russell Crowe made the Pope's exorcist. Yes. Now he's making a movie
called the exorcism and not two weeks later, we have learned that he is also making the Pope's
exorcist too. Yeah. The scooter is back. It's all back. He's going to make three movies in a row.
The Pope's exorcist, the exorcism, the Pope's exorcist too. That is one of the more insane
career paths I have ever seen. And by the way, if it does well, he will make the exorcism too.
There's a chance he'll be the Liam Neeson of exorcism movies. And you know what? Find your
love it. Um, I'll be watching it. Of course. Then we also have the first teaser trailer
for movie. We've talked about a bit on this show, Megalopolis, the new Francis Ford Coppola picture.
Now I'll say this. I know it was very, very expensive. He's it's, it's Adam driver, bad
haircut. He steps out on a ledge in like a futuristic world. He looks over the edge. He
goes, time stop. It's very reminiscent of the matrix or inception or a lot of these things we've
already seen. And then he's kind of looking over the edge. The effects look good. The world looks
cool, but not like awesome. And it shows us really nothing about the movie. I don't have high hopes.
Joe, what did you think of the teaser?
You know, well shot. Nice to see the big scope of it after Twixt, which was Coppola's last movie,
I believe, which was the one with Val Kilmer. And it bums me out, but that was one of the last
times we got to see Val Kilmer, um, in his full capability before this tragic sickness took his
from him and everything. But, um, Twixt is, is confusingly bad. I mean, Twixt is shot like,
it doesn't even look like it shot on iPhones. It looks like he took the
laptops and shot it with the cameras on the laptop. It's like crazy.
I did not understand Twixt at all. Um, I couldn't understand how a man of Coppola's capability
made something like that. It's, it's the only thing more confusing to me is Argento's Dracula,
which I re tried to rewatch again. I mean, this fucking it's, it's astounding how bad it is.
And so this with Megalopolis, what a terrible title. Uh, it's, um, you know, I was like, cool,
it looks like a big shiny professional movie. Like this looks like it could be epic.
Wasn't crazy about the time stop thing. I love Adam. Yeah, it sounded kind of dumb.
Look, I love Adam. I'm a big fan of Adam Driver and I, I actually have watched interviews with
him and I love that he's like a real, seemingly a real human being like that, that takes the
work seriously. He was on a burrs podcast and he talked about how he hated. He's like, I don't,
I hate phones on set. Don't bring your fucking phone to set. We have one chance to do this.
Let's do this. Let's be present. Let's, you know, he seems like a great dude. He does a lot of
really amazing charity work. Like Christopher Nolan doesn't allow phones on set either.
And he's a great, you know, doesn't allow phones on set. He's a great actor, but, um, uh, so,
but, but I am getting tired of him. It's like, all right. He's, he's another Canna Valley where
it's like, dude, please take a week off. Let me have a breath here. No idea. The fact that he,
somehow in the middle of all this, he was in like 10 Oscar movies in five years. And then he also
made that like Jurassic park movie that nobody saw. He was like, he did a fighting dinosaurs movie
that nobody watched. Yeah. Um, so look, scope of the film looked good. He's got a good actor
in the lead, even though I'm a little fatigued. The device of the scene was stupid, but let's see
how they use it. Uh, you know, that was my take. It didn't look bad. It just was like,
okay, let's see what we got here. Now reviews, uh, are not kind. The early screenings are saying
like, this is a mess and well, they're saying it'll be impossible to release, but somebody did
take the rights. So it is happening. Um, all right. I saw Miller's girl. Let's go there.
This is a bad movie. Um, it's, it was written by a woman.
Probably the only way this kind of thing gets even made. Now it is a hot button topic for a variety
of reasons, the power dynamic, et cetera. Now, when they did this kind of thing, the teacher,
female student, uh, weird sexual power play dynamic thing in David Mamet's only Anna,
uh, that was a much darker. Look at this with like assault, sexual violence, um, a lot more
going on to the story. This is kind of just a simple story. The two don't have sex in it outside
of his fantasy. She writes a creative writing story. That's like about him. He jacks off to it.
It turns him on and they're, they're playing with some degree of inappropriateness. But
as you're saying, Joe, you know, even though these two do not look suited for each other
she looks like a young girl and he looks like a creepy old man. They are age appropriate. So
it's really about the power dynamic of a teacher and student. The guy loses his job. She feels bad,
you know, not much happens in it. It's not like one of these where like the scandal terrorizes
the town or anything. It's just kind of a, almost a lifetime original movie look at a slightly odd
relationship. Um, an inappropriate relationship depending on your view, um, between a teacher
and a student, there's not much to it where it annoys me and where it becomes kind of a chore
to sit through is it's got that like, and I like some for work, but it's got like that Diablo Cody
style dialogue where everybody is. They look, they are English, they are in an English school
and he's a teacher and everything, but everybody is talking in this like arch fake dialogue that
just makes my head hurt. And, you know, like, you know, you know, the Diablo Cody dialogue just are
like Buffy, the vampire slayer of the show. Everybody speaks in whips. Everybody speaks in,
um, too flowery language or something like that. Just not how human beings communicate.
That's odd that this type of movie would have that.
I agree. I agree. She has, um, you know, a female friend who comes in and
they have this kind of like lesbian relationship that goes on. It's just, it's like, it's trying
to sort of shock, but it doesn't go anywhere near to me. Shocking territory. The dialogue,
as I said, is a real struggle. Um, there's nothing exceptional at all about either of
the lead performances from Ortega or Martin Freeman. And I'm sort of confused as to why
Jenna Ortega did this unless they could, she could have shot it in a week because I know,
you know, there's always, if you're doing a Wednesday or something or a stranger things,
and you want to break out and do a more adult role that's been going on since the dawn of film.
You know, I understand that instinct, but to do a little indie with Martin Freeman,
I don't get it where you're like a Lolita figure. It was an odd choice for her. I'll say that
since she's kind of like weirdly one of the biggest stars on earth right now.
Um, not a good film. And I think I liked it even less because I bought it for 5 .99
and it appeared on Netflix the next day. That's what you get.
Uh, have you seen Wednesday, Joe? I haven't seen it. No, no, no interest really. Just
I'm not an Adams family guy. Oh, see, I, you didn't like the movies either one.
I just could care less. It just doesn't those movies are sort of like, especially for that
time period, the ideal TV to movie adaptations. I mean, I heard great. Yeah, I heard they're good.
I just, I never liked the TV show, so that was kind of, so you never saw either movie.
I've seen, seen them or seen parts of them or what? I don't know. I just don't care.
Like I just, I have zero interest. All right. The characters don't interest me.
Sequel is way funnier. Adams Family Values is actually way funnier and Crumb Holes is great
enough. Yes. I've seen the Crumb Holes scenes. Okay. Um, I watched, uh, the, well, I went to see
Phantom Menace. Yeah. For the re -release 25th anniversary. I saw it yesterday in the theater
at like 10 55 AM. Uh, it was a really enjoyable experience. I, I remembered when that came out
again, summer, I remember the weather and the excitement and the feeling of going into the
theater to see it. Uh, I saw it many times despite, uh, by finding it a bit problematic.
Yeah. Uh, I did see it many times cause I was very excited that Star Wars was reigniting and,
and all that stuff. And, uh, I will say this was probably my most enjoyable watch
I've ever had in the movie. I think 25 years has, has done it well. Getting that level of
two plus decades where your expectations and the pressures of what it needs to be to you are gone.
Yeah. And you just go in and just kind of watch it as a Star Wars movie.
It's flaws, which some are very glaring are much more forgivable. Um, you're not caught off guard by
anything. And then the awesome parts are awesome. So, uh, I really enjoyed it. I really enjoyed
watching it. Um, and that's really all there is to it. And then also to just seeing that stuff on
the big screen again, I saw it at the Regal Essex in Manhattan, which is the, in my opinion, the
best theater in Manhattan. It's brand new. It's state of the art. The sound was nuts. Like the
whole pod race scene in the theater was awesome. Like, you know, and, um, you know, the thing at
the end when Darth, when the doors open and Darth Maul's there and the, and Obi -Wan and Qui -Gon are
like, we'll handle this. And they all drop their cloaks, like ceremonially and all ignite their
lightsaber. I was like, this is fucking awesome. This is like what you, this is what you watch
Star Wars for. So I enjoyed it. Uh, I enjoyed it. If you can catch it while it's still in the
theater, people are complaining like, why is this the only one they're re -releasing? It's not, they
are re -showing some of the other movies elsewhere, but Regal, well, it might be more than Regal,
but, but it's the 25th anniversary of this movie and it's, it was just May the 4th. So it's AMC too.
And if you are an AMC Stubbs member, I urge you to check every day. If you're, if you're home and
bored, like, and you think there's nothing out, AMC is always showing two or three old movies,
you know, like yesterday I was going to see something. I actually, I sent Joe the picture
of the no ticket sold auditorium of Phantom Menace, but that day they were also showing
Field of Dreams and Steel Magnolias. I didn't go see them, but like, that's cool. You know, if you,
if you were looking for something to do with your mom or something, go see Steel Magnolias.
They are, they're good about that at AMC. They keep stuff popping. They're usually only five
bucks, even if you're not a member. Yeah. Regals, Regals does that too, to, to an extent. And then,
yeah, like this, I got rid of my membership because I just, I wasn't going enough, but
this was eight bucks. It was like, yeah, great. Let's do it.
I saw Challengers, the new film by Luca Guadagnino, who did Call Me By Your Name,
which we discussed earlier on this film and the excellent Suspiria remake. I like him as a director.
I watched his HBO show and I watch a lot of his movies and I wonder about him sometimes because
he does seem to have an obsession with young sexuality. I don't know anything about him as a
man, but that was like the Larry Clark deal. Remember in the nineties, like kids and bully
and all that. And then you realize he had 20 years of photography of underage kids. And it's like,
we're letting this guy make movies still. What's going on? Is he still working Larry Clark?
No, I'm sure he's a hundred years old at this point. He was old then,
but Bully is I think an excellent movie, his masterpiece for sure. But yeah, those movies,
I saw them all when I was 17. I got to imagine watching now. I'd be like, yikes. Challengers.
And it's interesting that we're talking about this today because Challengers and I saw with
a buddy of mine and we both had the same reaction. We're getting older. Everyone in the world is
getting older. But when you'd go see American pie or you'd go see, um, you know, one of the many,
many sex comedies of that era, super bad, whatever you were, or we were, I was 17, 18 years old.
American pie came out when I was a senior in high school. I was the same age as those kids. So I'm
naked girls who are my own age and it was hot and it added to the fun of the movie and it was a big
part of movie going for a young horny teenager. Now I go see this movie and me and my buddy,
the first thing we did when we left, we're like, how old were these three? Like it makes you feel
creepy. You know, Zendaya is, you know, one of the most flawlessly beautiful people in our existence.
She is, she's gorgeous. And I really, really like her as an actress, but I think of her
as a kid. You know, I think of her as like a child just because I sort of watched her grow up,
I guess. And in this movie, she's not naked, but close enough. You know, there's a lot of,
there's not, there's not as much sex as the trailer would have you believe.
And that scene that looks like you're about to watch this really hot threesome
doesn't actually happen. That was a disappointment for a lot of the audience
on the way out because there was two guys. Well, sure. I mean, I like sex. I like watching sex
and having it, you know? And I was like, this is a movie about sex. And I was pumped. That scene
is a blue baller. They kiss for a few minutes and then she leaves, no clothes come off. You know,
it's like sex, even, even in a sex movie like this, where you go and you're like, I'm going
to see some sex. You kind of don't. And it's, it's a weird, weird time in American culture.
It's almost like the fifties all over again. But that said, this movie is hot. It's very sexy,
almost for what it doesn't show. Zendaya, much to my relief and my friend's relief is 27 years old.
The guys, I don't know their, their story. I hadn't seen them really. Josh O 'Connor and
Feist, I don't think I had seen them in a lot of shit or anything. And if I did, they didn't leave
any impression, but that was an interesting call. They didn't go with like Freddie Prinze Jr. and
Paul Walker as the guys. They're kind of like not technically attractive dudes even, you know, and
maybe women out there are disagreeing with me, but they have great bodies. Of course they're athletes,
but they're just kind of like guys and Zendaya makes them feel special in much the same way.
We had this exact same dynamic and it's weird. I don't see anybody mentioning this movie, but
it's Bull Durham. It's the same exact dynamic. It's a sexy woman who controls and pits against
each other to men who are playing a sport. It's weird that this movie has not been compared to
I think it's the exact same thing, but as the movie goes, I'm not going to say there's like
twists galore, but you just keep learning more and more about who these three people are,
why they need each other, how they drive each other to be better and to compete, be that sexually,
be that as athletes, et cetera. I was able to compare it to my own life and how competition
can drive me in good ways and positive ways and also in terrible and obsessive ways.
It's a very, very, very smart sports movie and you know, I don't give a shit about sports,
but it, you know, Bull Durham is hailed as this big classic. I rewatched it recently and I think
it's very overrated. This movie is doing what Bull Durham did a little better. I got to say,
it's a really sharp movie with a kickass soundtrack from Trent Reznor and Atticus
Ross who do amazing film scores. They mix the score so loud in the dialogue scenes that sometimes
you can't hear it and I think that's sort of the point. I saw it in IMAX as well and I just
recommend it. If you can see it in the theater, IMAX, it's like a really cool audio visual,
sexy, smart experience. I'm realizing as I talked, I liked it even more than I thought. Joe?
Your only disappointment was not seeing enough tit on the young people you were
disturbed for being attracted to. Am I understanding you correctly?
No, I'm not even complaining about not seeing the nudity. I'm complaining more about
there not being real sex scenes. The sex scenes in this movie are like Zendaya straddles the guy
they make out. You're like, wow, this is hot. Okay. All right. And then they cut away.
It's just a very different time. I know you're kidding, but it's a different time.
And have you experienced that where you're watching a movie and you're like, am I allowed
to find this girl attractive? It's just a weird part of aging. Of course, you're allowed.
It's just my mind.
No, I hear you. I get confused sometimes. I'll get a bit confused sometimes because
when there's a movie and it's a person who I'm not sure if it's supposed to be like,
well, you don't know if they're a senior in high school or a freshman in college. They're in that
weird and then they're putting them in sexual scenarios. And I'm like, not even that I'm
feel like aroused and don't know what to do. I'm like watching it. I'm like, I don't understand.
Is this supposed to be like sexy or am I supposed to think that this is wrong? I don't know what's
going on. I hate to use these terms, but it's because the gaze changes. The male gaze
changes as I was saying. I was like, where is he going? No, the male gaze changes because when you
are, let's say when I was 10 or whatever, let's say when I was 10, I watched Vacation. I see
Beverly D 'Angelo's giant jugs in the shower. One of the great all -time flashes. Amazing. And my
parents were under the impression that Vacation was PG -13, the original, because all the other
ones were PG -13. That was the one movie I managed to slip through the cracks. So I saw Beverly
D 'Angelo's breasts 50 ,000 times. The tape came off the spool at that part because I would pause
it. And Beverly D 'Angelo was like my mom's age. So that's weird when you're 10, you're looking at
a 30 -year -old naked woman and now you're suddenly looking at your mom's friends and your male gaze
changes. Then suddenly I'm 18. I'm looking at Shannon Elizabeth in American Pie. I'm like,
holy shit, but she's my age. It's appropriate. Now suddenly we're on an even par. It's not creepy
like it was when I was looking at a 30 -year -old woman as a child. Now it's on an even par.
That was a weird thing too. But hang on, Joe, because then I was going to push it further.
It's creepy as a kid looking at adult women naked. For a brief window when you're 18 and
they're 18, it's normal and everything's great. But then when you get to be 40 and you're looking
at an 18 -year -old naked woman, then it's creepy again. And all of that is how it should be. And
yet you can't help what happens. You can't help what you see. Yeah. No, I hear you. I hear you.
Yeah. And I think too that American Pie was a weird one because I was in college when American
Pie came out. I remember the Shannon Elizabeth scene. I remember thinking she was the hottest
girl ever. I remember loving the nudity. But at that time, if you had said to me as a college
student, would you date a high school girl? I would have said, absolutely not. I would have
been offended by the idea. So it was a weird time because it was okay to see it on screen. By the
way, at any age, maybe it wasn't okay, but just speaking about society, at any age, nobody
complained. Maybe they did and we just didn't hear it because we were young, but I don't remember
there being any backlash about American Pie. I always subscribed to Premier, to Entertainment
Weekly. I always subscribed to a variety of movie magazines and nobody complained about teenage
nudity in those movies ever. And the critics were all 50 year old then. So you get why they didn't
complain. It's interesting. It is. And now as we were talking about with Miller's Girl, a completely
chased movie is so controversial now because we're in Pilgrim times again. Yeah, it is very
interesting. It is very, very interesting. I also feel bad now that I made the joke that
you like the threesome because it was two guys. I didn't mean to make it sound like
there was anything wrong with that. I feel bad. Have you never watched an MMF porn? I surely have.
I just didn't want it to sound like I was being like, that's gay, ha ha ha,
which I guess was kind of the joke, but I feel bad now and I don't think like that.
Well, it's the same. It's on this thing. I feel like I could fashion this into a TED talk. I'm
all lit up about this now, how the gaze changes. I don't know why I started talking about this,
but I'm watching The Roast the other night. Now, why The Roast of Tom Brady was three hours,
I do not know. Over three hours, I do not know. But there were some great performances,
some brilliant jokes unquestionably, but this tonnage of jokes about like,
you're gay, dude. The amount of people who were like, you're gay as the punchline,
it was half the jokes. Then Affleck comes out looking like a wolf. His face is made completely
of plaster now. It looks like he's wearing a mask. He comes out to close the show,
makes you realize how difficult standup is as he does a horrific job. And it closes with him
saying like, this should have been you to Bill Belichick to Tom Brady. Why were you so mean to
him? This should have been you. And then does like this long graphic dick sucking thing to end it.
And I'm kind of like, you know what? This is wrong. This is gross. I don't want to be associated
with this kind of comedy either. Here's what people don't get about the roast. They think,
and the best people to do it do get it. Honestly, Nikki Glaser is one of the best doing it. She had
a fantastic set because she gives really smart, creative, clever ways to say you're gay, you have
small dick, you cheated on your wife, whatever it may be. That's all it takes. The old adage,
as long as it's funny is true, but also there's an as long as it's smart to it. Too many times
for comfort, the punchline was you're gay. And then people were bringing back the F slur and the
R slur and mass. And you're kind of like, you know, like a little bit of progress is fine guys,
you know, like you're not, and too, too often the laughter was the word. If you're going to say the
word, give me a beautifully crafted joke that justifies it. Don't give me a lazy joke that
I've heard since the sixties and then say a slur and get a big laugh and woo woo woo,
because half the forum is full of, you know, monsters. That's all. It's been a weird,
because I resist change like anybody else, but also there's part of it watching this. And maybe
it was just the tonnage, the three hour nature of it, but I was like, yeah, this is getting a little
gross guys, you know, don't show the whole event, edit it for television for sure.
Livestreamed it because that's Netflix is going to start doing that now. Yeah. But I mean,
yeah, I can't, I can't even speeches with shaky hands and shit. Like, I mean, it was too long.
Sorry. I can't in good conscience. This is not a criticism towards you. I'm just saying for myself,
I can't criticize any roast jokes or anything. I've been, I've been a part of plenty of podcasts
and plenty of roasty situations or whatever you want to call it, where I've said things that would
offend certain people. Other people have said things that would offend different people. I've
laughed. Of course, of course. But then I also have my own lines that I draw. I'm of the belief
that once you start, if you say, if I say as a comic, you can't do that, but you can do this.
You're, you're getting into some dangerous territory, but I would agree that at least
my own personal approach. Yeah. If I am going to use a word that has a lot of weight behind it,
you know, a slur or whatever in a joke, I am going to try to make sure that there's a nuance to that
where you get what I'm, there's, there's a, there's a point or a purpose. It's not just
the joke is the shock of the word. So I don't, I don't disagree with that, but, but if that's
your thing, then that's your thing. And that, you know, do it, go ahead and do it, you know,
even if it's not for me. Right. It's what, it's what Chappelle said, you know, like when he walked
away from Chappelle show is like, what are you laughing about? Like the white crew, he started
looking around and he was like, now I think that your laughter is racism and it's, it's coming from
this weird place. And that, that sort of stuff can change quickly. You know, like you're sort of on,
on that line, Joe, where you, in a great way, where you can hang with the alt comedians and,
and be hilarious. And you can hang with the, you know, the fingerless glove comics and the
Legion of skanks or whatever. And, and, and both, in both instances, you'll be great and be hilarious.
That's, that's a skill that many don't have. Well, thank you. That's very nice of you, Pat.
Most don't have, most people are in one lane or the other and they stay there.
Well, I feel as a, as a, I'll lob it right back to you. I feel as a writer,
you also walk that line very nicely. And most writers don't, most writers are either,
I'm going to jam an agenda down your face, or I'm going to be the most callous, psychotic,
you know, inhumane, whatever. And it's like, no, there's, there's a middle ground where,
you know, you know, you, you get, you get a, you get an Arthur Miller type of person or whatever,
or whatever. So we're a good comedic writer, like, like many of our favorite comedies.
And I think you walk that line nicely yourself. I appreciate that, Chuck. Thank you. Let's get
to our move. But no, I didn't even finish why I brought that up. I wasn't just complimenting
you randomly. What do you think of the phrase? I was saying, like, you can hang in both worlds.
But there must be a point when you're in the Legion of skanks type world,
where you're saying something, you're saying these jokes and the tenor,
the tone of the crowd starts to change in a way that you yourself start to kind of not like the
vibe. I will say it's, let me take it away from skanks. Let me say you're at an edgier Vegas type
show. Yeah, no, no, no. I will, I will say absolutely. It is not, and this is not me just
taking up for my friends. It has not happened to me on Legion of skanks. I find that that crowd
doesn't get the credit it deserves for their nuance and their understanding of irony and
all that stuff. I think they're great fans. And I swear, I'm not just being diplomatic.
It's happened to me, though. Absolutely. It happened to me on my own show. It happened to
me two weeks ago. I was in Delaware and I have a joke or thing, whatever you want to call it.
About young, you know, everybody criticizes the young generation.
My only criticism of the young generation is they have no fear. You know, your parents
gassed you guys up to think you're heroes to the point where you're committing crimes
and being called heroic. And then I give examples. I say, Greta Thunberg, skip school. It's truancy.
It's crime. Kyle Rittenhouse, you know, ran out. I go, I make the gun noise and I go,
good shooting kid. Good shoot. And this guy in the back was like, yeah, yeah. And I, I,
I went like two more sentences and then I just jumped out of it. And I go,
that guy was cheering for the wrong reason. And then, and then the crowd like laughed at that.
And I jumped back in, but it's like, yeah, dude, it, that happens all the fucking time.
It's rarely though, I will say this in my experience, I might be
on my own in this take. I find it's rarely a bunch of people laughing for the wrong reason.
I find it's a couple people that are way too amped. Most of the crowd gets here.
It's not hard to tell though. You do feel it. You're like, oh, there it is right there. That's,
that's not right. You know, I've changed shit over too. I've been like, Hey, I'm not gonna,
I gotta reword that or I'm not gonna do the bit that way anymore. Cause it's getting the wrong,
I don't like that. Yeah. Yeah. But it is frightening how, I mean, look,
all you gotta do is go on Twitter. Questlove said, he posted a thing yesterday about hip hop is dead.
He's talking about the Kendrick Drake beef. Yeah. Yeah. And he goes, this,
this battle wasn't about skill. This was about winning at all costs and being extraordinarily
personal. True. At the expense of children, all this stuff, right? True. I don't disagree with
them. I, I really enjoyed the, the, the, I enjoy a classic rap back and forth battle, but he did
make a point and I didn't disagree with it. And he said, these people cheering right now are the
same ones that'll be writing the RIP posts and acting like they had nothing to do with it.
And I thought it is intense, you know, and maybe a little dramatic, but
I thought he had a point. And, and the reason I bring it up is because you, you read comments
on the internet, you read Twitter X threads, whatever, you know, whatever. Yeah. You see how
easily swayed and, and just, just one tick left. It can go where it's like, no guys, that's not what
it was supposed to be. Now it's over here. It changes very, very quickly. People will respond
to things you write, you know, you'll, you know, you'll put something out that says,
uh, or, or, you know what, I have a joke about, and it's a clip that, that's done,
that's gotten a lot more viewership than most of my clips where it's talks about, um,
the changing of the genders and ethnicities, the complex characters. Now, the point of the joke is
I'm offended that Hollywood started most of the racism and now their way of fixing it.
And now they're going to fix it, by the way, which offends me that the place that started
most of it is going to be like, we'll fix it. Um, and it also offends me that they won't
put any effort into the solution, or at least to the extent that I think they should, they just
make these alterations to existing, uh, content and characters and go, there you go. And to me,
that feels like a bandaid fix. It feels disrespectful to the cause. That's how I feel.
There are people that will see that joke and understand 100%. That's what it means. And
that's what I'm saying. And it's, it's offensive. Then there are people on, by the way, this,
this switch I'm talking about, it goes either way, the wrong cheers, right?
So then there are people that respond to go, I'm tired of this diversity shit. And it's like,
that's not what I'm saying. That is not what I'm saying. But then there are people on the other
side that are like fucking white male doesn't racist. And I'm like, that's not what I'm saying
either. And it's like, God, man, it can gentle breeze will push it one way or the other real
quick. Very, very unnerving, to be honest with you. Well, and there are people, generally
younger people these days who I think spent the last three, four years locked in their houses on
Tik TOK, which is going to, I think, be a big societal problem going forward, but they're
reading every single encounter for you, for you to fuck up. Yeah. They're reading every word you say
in every situation, whether you're at the grocery store, mining your own business or whether, you
doing. Sure. They're just waiting and dying for you to say something that they can go,
oh, wait, that's fat phobic or whatever it is. I was told the other day, and I won't go into the
situation, but I was talking about a weight loss goal that I had for myself. So I want to lose
X amount of pounds by whenever. And I was told that that was a fat phobic thing to say.
Wait, what? And I said that you're saying weight loss goal. Yeah. I was like, you know, I, you know,
let's say I said, I wanted to lose 10 pounds by summer, whatever you're, you know, something
everyone says at a barbecue or just something, you know, shooting the shit. And this lady told
me that I was being fat phobic. And I said, what do you mean? And she said, well, you don't need
to talk about how you need to lose weight when there might be overweight people around you.
And I started to engage and honestly turned away and took a deep breath
because I'm becoming an adult. But like, I was just like, nah, no, I'm not doing that.
What was the, I know you don't want to get into it, but I mean, just tell me this much,
was it a party like social situation or was it? Yeah, yeah, yeah. Okay. And were there
people around you? She was heavy set, you know? Yeah. All right. But I wasn't talking to her.
I didn't know she was even there. I was talking about what I would like to do for my own health.
But then even saying that it's healthy to want to lose 10 pounds is fat phobic. And, and look,
I think that's nuts. I guess I'm allowed to say I'm sorry, but I think that's nuts.
I'll just picture it. You hear it. You hear it from her shoulder. That's fat phobic.
What you turn around, she's holding a chunk of egg. How dare you. Yeah. Crumbs flowing out.
Bucket of chicken under her arm. Yeah, exactly. Um, no, it wasn't like that.
That, that here's the thing, man. This is what drives me crazy about it. And then we can move
to the movie. My mom, I said this 10 fucking years ago to Jen Kirkman. Yeah. Who, if you know,
Jen Kirkman, she fights this fight pretty hard for like whatever the, you know, the, the, the,
very outspoken sort of virtuous left leaning fight is she's pretty outspoken or was I haven't
heard from her in a while. And I liked Jen, but I said to Jen Kirkman, 10, 12 years ago,
we were sitting in a bar at a comedy festival and it was when the fat phobia shit first started
coming out. And I said, and this applies to a lot of things, but this is just an example
that crystallizes it. I said, you know what, Jen? She wasn't like challenging me. And we
were just talking. I said, you know what? My mom has struggled with weight issues her entire life.
I feel terrible. I've always felt terrible for people with a food addiction because it's a thing
you have to put into your body is the worst addiction to have to beat. Yeah. It's terrible.
Nothing makes me sadder than when I see an overweight person eating by themselves in public.
It makes me sad in the way you'd feel sorry for watching a person drink alone or something like
that. I go, and I don't need a bunch of fucking liberal people to tell me suddenly that it's
wrong. The audacity of these fucking people to preach to me now that it's wrong when by the way,
last year they were the same people walking around talking about how America was fat and
they cranked their fucking rage against the machine records. Like fuck off. Fuck off.
Yeah, no. I mean, all growing up, the amount of like anti -fat stuff in schools was like
constant, the presidential fitness test and all that. And, you know, that you do pushups in front
of your entire student body and pull ups in front of the entire student body. I don't know if that
still goes on, but it's like, are we saying that kids are not supposed to be physically fit?
Is that what we want to do now? Like maybe the other one was a little too army based for my
taste. I didn't necessarily like having to do all that shit, but it does instill in you a belief
that physical fitness is important. And I just don't think that that's a bad belief for anyone
to get early on. Like, no, it's, you got to take care of yourself and, and of course,
or you don't have to, and I won't shame you for that, but let's not pretend like,
let's not pretend like doing a bad thing for yourself is somehow a positive thing.
Yes. I don't want you to, I don't want you to wake up sad. I don't want you to cry yourself to sleep.
I don't want you to look in the mirror and hate what you see. I want you to love yourself. I want
you to celebrate yourself. And I mean that if you overeat, if you're an alcoholic, if you smoke
fucking crack, I don't care. Whatever your thing is to get through this huge trade, you didn't have
to pick three things I do there. Whatever it is to get through this putrid, horrible fucking
existence, this, this awful pointed fucking world that we live in every day. This it's, this it's
awful. Whatever you have to do, as long as you are not hurting yourself or somebody else. And I know
this is where the gray area comes in with hurting yourself. Well, if you eat too much cake or do too
much this or what, I get that. But my point is, is I would go as far as to even say, as long as
you're not hurting anybody else. And I don't mean emotionally the people around you even, I just
mean like you're not doing illegal things with underage people. You're not assaulting other human
beings. You're not committing crimes. You're just, you're doing your own thing on your own time. And
that's how you deal. Then God bless, man. I don't care, but I'm not also going to go right on, dude.
Heroin is good for you. It's like, it's not, it's not, it's not a thing to celebrate. It's just,
I'm also not going to shame you, dude. Do your thing. That's okay. Yeah. So, you know, that's
anyway. All right. Speaking of shame and a broken society, Civil War, starring the power couple,
Jesse Plemons and Kirsten Dunst. We've been waiting for this reunion on screen,
not since Wilder and Pryor have we. It's true that the chemistry is just electric.
This was a very drained performance from Kirsten Dunst. She just looked exhausted, you know,
by war. A much flashier role is had by her husband, Jesse Plemons, who really lights the
movie up for his one scene cameo. And of course he's heavily featured in the, in the trailer.
But, um, yeah, Joe, what's, what's, what's the plot? I mean, the plot we, we know is basically
this, it weirdly focuses on journalists as they try to get to the white house to interview the
president in a country sieged by civil war. I will begin by saying, uh, I will begin with a,
with a thing I have watched, uh, the red letter media guys do a few times at the very beginning
of a review and I will do this here. Uh, I've seen the guy, Mike, on that show say,
you guys are going to hate me, but I love this movie. Uh, I don't, you guys not meeting the
audience, Pat and I look, when I first started watching it, I was like, uh, all right. I, you
know, I didn't quite know how to feel the more distance I got from it after I saw it, the more
I understood it. And the more I was like, that was really good. Um, look point a to point B plot.
Like we keep fucking saying, yeah, countries siege by civil war. As Pat's debt said, uh,
California and Texas have seceded from the union. Um, the president is under fire and there is a
siege about to happen from the, from the revolution that's happening in, in the United States,
where it's basically the, the, the revolutionary army against the government's army. Um,
and the revolutionary army is going to siege, siege the DC and kill the president. Basically
that's what they're trying to do. Kirsten Dunst plays a war photographer, journalist,
photographer, not journalist, a photo journalist. Um, and her partner, she and her partner have to
get from wherever they are at the beginning of the movie. I think they're in Texas or something. I
can't remember. And they have to get to DC because they're going to try to interview the
president. Uh, they are warned by Nick Offerman. Yes, which is an interesting choice. Um,
I would say a bad choice. It's, it's, it's, you know what? He's not bad in the role. It's just,
he barely has a role. It's distracting. It's distracting. Um, and I thought them casting
Megan Mullaney as the vice president was ridiculous. Well, lolly, lolly. Anyway,
yeah, it's actually, this has a very similar setup to like a 28 days later, which was also written
by Alex Garland in that it's kind of a makeshift family trying to make their way to a goal across a
war torn. Well, except in that movie was zombies. It's funny. I was going to text you and say,
and say when I was watching this, this third zombie land is really dry because it does kind
of feel very similar. Yeah. Um, anyway, a young, so they are, yeah, they're in, uh,
at the beginning of the movie, they're in Brooklyn.
All right. So they're in New York. Oh, that's right. They say you can't just drive
like to DC directly. You have to go like around through like Charlottesville and stuff. And then
that there's like, like, uh, Jesse Plemons is wearing like red sunglasses and that that's
about as, as political as it gets as these illusions to, okay, this really racist character,
it has red ties. We'll give him red sunglasses. Um, it's not, it's weirdly a political,
which we can discuss of course, but, um, yeah, there, I thought that this was going to be
Trumpers versus non Trumpers, you know, like, like I, I thought this was going to be a very
disturbing look at what could quite possibly, uh, happen to some extent in our future,
in our near future, regardless of the outcome of November. And everyone's just kind of forgetting
that that's coming up, but it's coming up. And in actuality, there's no mention of Trump. There's
no Trump figure. That's certainly not what Offerman is. The problems don't really seem to
be the same as ours. And the only real like ugly American racist character we see is Plemons in
one scene. Um, the other fighting and bombing, we're not necessarily sure what's going on a
lot of the time. Well, I'll say, um, excuse me. They, uh, they do say at the beginning,
like journalists will get shot on site at the white house. Yeah. Um, the president's foreign
policies against other countries are very much questioned. It's not, it's not like his foreign
policy in, in, in, in forming an allegiance with such and such places is criticized. It's like
his absolute cutoff, uh, and, and, and outward, uh, antagonism of other countries is, so there
are things that are, and then, and then they show Offerman rehearsing his speech at the beginning
of the movie and he goes, they are already saying it is the greatest victory ever in military,
you know, and you're like, but it's clearly supposed to be a Trump. Like, okay. Maybe,
maybe it was too subtle for me. I also missed that opening speech because I came in a little
late, so that's part of my problem. Yeah, it's, it's, they, they, they define a lot of that at
the beginning of the movie. Okay. Now they don't ever say he's Republican or not,
but the way they counterbalance that, I do think it leans definitely in the direction of like the
conservatives are the evil people, but the way they counterbalance it is, is they start to show
you the inhumanity of the other side of the fight and how disturbing that is to certain people.
And they really encapsulate that with Kirsten Dunst's character where she is saying like,
I'm not here to help anybody. I'm not here to save anybody. I'm here to document what's going on.
And even the other journalists are like, Jesus Christ. Yeah. So I think the movie scene where
these journalists talk in the lobby of a hotel that I swear to God is 15 minutes long.
They're, this conversation at the hotel, that's what it got me off to a real sluggish start,
them having that, that just seated conversation. I was like, what are we doing guys?
And what that led me to, in addition to some curious editing choices later on in the film,
where like characters are introduced in very bizarre and confusing ways a couple of times,
I learned that this movie was originally three hours long. So I don't know if that
version will hit 4k at some point. That would be kind of cool to see. I always like that when
it's a drastically different cut, but I think they preferred, I don't know about preferred,
but the original version of this was three hours long and it barely clocks in at 90 minutes.
So we have characters like these two guys in a truck who come up upon them and start
kind of challenging them. And you think that they're a threat, but then they're their friends
from what would have been an earlier scene in the movie that we just don't see. So you kind of play
theater, looking around like who the hell are these people? So there's some choppiness to it
that I think might be corrected by a longer cut. Maybe it was more political. They were,
when I saw this in IMAX opening week, they were heavily asking audience members on the way out
their opinions, their political beliefs. They were having them fill out forms in a way I haven't seen
in ages there. And that was all A24 reps. So clearly they were concerned about the box office
performance. Maybe a bunch of political stuff was removed because they said the makeup of the
audiences were equally conservative and liberal. So everybody went to see the movie. It was a big
success for A24. And I think that only happened because they stayed on a very narrow, we're not
taking sides political line, or at least not in a way that would offend people.
I think it walks the line well. I think that at the beginning of this thing, you're supposed to feel
that a lot of wrong is being done by the conservative party. And I feel like by the
guys in quotes are doing is disturbing. And I thought they did that well. There's a great scene.
I forget the actor's name, but he's the guy who was in Fences. He's great. He was in Tower Heist.
There's a great scene where they're on the road and they're documenting a shootout that's
happening between the soldiers and the uprising or whatever. And the uprising gets the upper hand
and they capture the soldiers and the American soldiers and they put them in hoods and they're
gleefully taking them out to a field to execute them as it plays Say No Go by Dale Assault. It's
a very well shot scene. And it's like good vibes as they're going to go kill these people. And it
cuts to that guy's reaction and he's disturbed. He's disgusted. He's like, this is not the way.
Like, this is all awful. We've all lost our humanity. And that's really what the movie becomes
about is a loss of humanity. Does it really matter who started it or who's going to finish it? We've
all lost our humanity. It's a lot of what we're seeing right now overseas with this current
conflict, there's a loss of humanity that is taking place. And at the end of the movie,
this is spoiler alert. So if you want to see this, don't listen to this part. First of all,
the whole final sequence is awesome. The siege of the White House is fucking awesome. It's like
you're playing Call of Duty. It is a fucking intense scene. It's great. And when they finally
get into the Oval Office, the president's there and he's cowering and begging for his life and
they just fucking kill him, like very cold bloodedly. And then it cuts to, and that's
preceded by Kirsten Dunst jumping in front of a bullet to save the young girl photographer
who she is mentoring basically throughout the movie. And as Kirsten Dunst falls to the ground,
girl takes pictures of it and you see that this girl now has lost her humanity as Kirsten Dunst
once did. Kirsten Dunst regains her humanity to save this girl and dies doing it and becomes
just another picture of a dead person, just like she has been the capturer of for this whole movie.
And then the final shot of the movie after they kill this cowering man and it's kind of disturbing
is them, the soldiers all smiling, like standing on the body like we did with Bin Laden.
And it's like, Jesus Christ, man, like this is horrible. Like this is about a loss of
humanity. And I thought the movie was very effective in that sense. I thought at times
it made me angry. It was emotional. And I think that I could easily see somebody who was very
hard left or very hard right watching this and saying the other side is completely wrong in the
whole thing. Yeah. Well, that was sort of my issue with it. That actor's name, by the way,
because I hate when we don't mention a great actor because we don't know their name,
Stephen McKinley Henderson, who I didn't even have any idea that was his name. He's one of the
character actors working right now. Stephen McKinley Henderson. He was in
Devs, which was Alex Garland's FX show, which I did not really like, but that's the first time
he really popped to me and I noticed him. He's in Bo Is Afraid and other stuff. But the movie to me,
and I think it might benefit from a second viewing, hopefully from the full cut of the movie,
I would like to see. But to me, as I'm watching literally five or six four minute segments that
play out essentially like music videos, I talked about loving hearing that suicide song as they're
driving around because I love that song and the sound system was great. But there's so many drone
going overhead, really cool song pumping on the soundtrack, but just like music videos in this
movie, that's, you know, I'm not complaining that it's too short. I would never do that, but
there's not, there just wasn't a lot of meat on the bone to me. I'm watching musical montages
while I'm just generally confused about what's going on in the movie. And the De La Soul thing
that was an interesting juxtaposition of song and visual, but yeah, I guess it made me,
it made me sort of lose my humanity or something. I was like, this is not working for me. Whatever
is happening here, I get it, you know, that the mixture is trying to unsettle me or whatever,
but I'm just, I don't, I don't know what to feel, which is not a bad thing for a movie to do.
Maybe it just sort of may be uncomfortable, but I found it really hard to just dig into anything
and care about anything or anyone. I was just sort of as dead as the protagonist of the movie.
What kind of scene did you come in on? I mean, I gotta say, and I've never said this to you,
I think you're a little unfairly, you missed like a very key thing in that movie. Like you need to
see that opening speech and opening sequence. I came in like in the middle of the speech.
So like he was giving it, I might've missed two words. I might've missed, I heard some
speech and I had my Wikipedia, but yeah, I think a lot of times when you're, when you're expecting
a movie to be one thing and it's another, it requires a repeat viewing because you're spending
the whole movie mad at it for what it's not. And I've been guilty of that. You've been guilty
of that, whether you'll admit it, Joe, but you go in and I think in this movie, I was like,
this is going to be a really unsettling and political look at these troubling times.
And it was, but just completely not in the way I was expecting. And that might be on me and I need
give it another look. I will say that from this standpoint of, of visually and musically,
it looked really cool. You know, it's got those, the vibes of that every movie of this studio,
you know, they, it looks cool. It's flashy. The music is synced up perfect. You know,
they got a great team over there, but what, what am I watching? You know, I just felt like
I wanted more depth from the movie is, is what I would say. I wanted more insight, even though I
feel like it must've been a conscious choice to keep these characters sort of muted and keep the
details, the specific details of what's really going on from us. I just found that kept me at
a distance. I think that was the absolute strength of the movie. I think anything at this point
that's coming in from a specific political perspective is in my opinion, foolish
and short -sighted. I think anybody at this point that thinks there's a good team and a bad team
and that one team is not flawed and the other one is all evil or vice versa. And
not putting too hard a stamp on either side of it. I think they were probably editing in real time
with, with the Israeli Palestine thing happen. I mean, look what's happening now. We're watching
people. We're watching people who absolutely said the people on the left, who absolutely said the
Michael Rappaport is the best example. This guy would Dick Stain called them Dick Stain, Donald
Trump, the fucking weasel, whatever, video after video. I know Michael Rappaport is a little nutty,
but he just said in an interview, voting for Trump is on the table for me now because I'm pro -Israel.
It's like, so you're seeing people that are taking wild swings from one side to the other.
And I'm not saying you need to do that. I'm just saying we're living in a time where I know
for certain seeing people that I know personally that said I could never align with a Republican
for any reason or vice versa. I could never align with a Democrat for any reason. Now aligning with
them based on, based on, well, this overseas conflict is too important and now it's changing
my perspective on all that. I feel like they were probably editing this in real fucking time and
like, no, we've got to keep it vague and just make it about, look what this is all doing to us.
Forget who's right or who's wrong or getting into which side is what. We're losing ourselves.
It's gone. Our souls are going away. That was my takeaway, which is why the further I got from it,
the more I thought about it, the more I liked it. But I hear you. I thought for certain from the
trailers, it was going to be a very like, there's the red state Republicans and the blue state Dems
and they're all fighting, you know? And it wasn't that. It wasn't that. And the closest we got to
that style of character was definitely Jesse Plemons who's wearing the red glasses, probably
because they thought the red hat would have been too on the nose. But he's super, yeah, he's really
good. He's really effective, but you got to wonder he's a big name. The movie lost an hour and a half.
Did he play a bigger role in this one scene? Who knows? But no, I think that was literally
Kirsten Dunn saying, can Jesse play this part? He'd be into it. And they were like, fuck yeah.
Yeah. Look, the other thing is kind of like when things come out, if this had come out right after
when I was like, oh, this Alex Garland is the shit. I probably would have liked it more. I saw it. The
last one I saw of his was Men, which I hated so much. I hated that movie so much. And I might have
gone into this with the wrong attitude, but basically I just saw it as like a cool audio
visual experience and not much more. I didn't really get anything out of it. Your take on it
interesting. I like your take on it and I would watch a full version. Didn't hate.
Let's say I liked it more than Abigail probably, but as a movie didn't quite work for me, didn't
quite land. My Hog is way up for Civil War, much to my surprise. And I'm very happy to say that
because this was one I was rolling my eyes like, Oh Christ, another fucking thing about how
you know, I just, I was like, Oh, another politic, whatever. So I loved, I ended up loving it.
I think it's a very good movie and I think it, My Hog is up for Civil War.
And I would also like to see an Uncut. I'd be very curious to see, you know,
Uncut Hog, an uncircumcised Civil War. I'd be there for it. Folks, we'll be back at the end of,
not at the end, but sometime later this month with two more episodes. We're not sure what we're
doing yet. Who knows? Not sure what's coming out. TBH. I guess the Fall Guy. I don't know.
Fall Guy, I'm open to Tarot, which I can't imagine. I'm not seeing Tarot. Good. Thank you.
I was worried you were going to want to see it. It doesn't look good. What about this Nun one?
I haven't seen any of the Nuns. You mean the Sydney Sweeney Nun picture? I'd watch that.
Inconceivable. No, I think it's, I think it's called basically that. Yeah, I want to watch that.
Is it on streaming now? It's got to be. It's out of theaters. Immaculate. Immaculate. That's it.
Yeah, I would see Immaculate. Sure. We'll be back with something. Maybe we do a
and I did. I loved it. I started watching it. It's great. All right, maybe we'll do that too.
All right, folks. Hell of a 4k. You should, by the way, just buy it if you want to watch it before
the episode. If we do it, we should do it. All right. We'll see you next time. And we'll see you in hell.