I'll see you in hell.
Folks, it's will see you in hell, we're back at it again.
This time talking about road house, it should have that in it, yeah, road house, the original
star Patrick Swayze and Sam Elliott, favorite here at the, we'll see you in hell podcast.
This one has Jake Gyllenhaal and Connor McGregor.
We'll get into it, but a pretty fairly true to form remake, I don't think it strays too much from
the formula, the first one. I haven't seen the first one in quite some time, but I always thought
the first one was, when I did finally see the first one, I was disappointed because I thought it
was going to be like a goofy romp. The first one's much darker than you think it's going to be.
Well, it's got the reputation of being like the room, but it's not bad like that, it's a little
cheesy in the way of a lot of great 80s action movies, but it does take itself seriously, which is
why it's great. And you got Ben Gazera in that first one too. Yeah, that's right. Anyway,
what's happened in your life since I last saw you? I ate some broccoli.
I saw you five minutes ago. How was the broccoli? It was okay. I hate to do this all the time,
but I hate starting my day with a vegetable. It's a bad start. It's like the stomach doesn't want
that first thing, but I do it. Yeah, it's terrible. Yeah, if you're mixing in with eggs or something.
No, just straight. By the way, yeah, we got two. They released. Oh, Jesus, God. Oh, no. Oh, no.
Oh, Pat, I'm so happy this happened while we're on the show. What's this? They released today.
First image looks of Christian Bale's Frankenstein. Oh, really? He's a monster. He didn't know he was
the one that's different than the one with the Lordy. Well, that's what I saw the headline here,
because I was going to movie web to see the news stuff. And I saw the headline and what I was about
to say was how many fucking Frankenstein movies are we going to get? This is the third now in a year
or a Frankenstein. This is ridiculous. Then I just watched Lisa Frankenstein. Yeah, which we might
do on the show. Then I then I clicked on the picture of the first look. Yes. And that's where the
oh, no, came from because oh, wow. He's Mickey Rourke and the wrestler, but with a tattoo. You see
the tattoo on his chest? No, I'm just saying what's on his head, which is like barbed wire. He's
the Frankenstein in oh, it's Maggie Jill and Hall's movie. Wait, does the tattoos say hope? Yes,
it does. Oh, no. Frankenstein's wearing a tattoo that says hope. Yeah, he's got a tattoo.
Has no hope? It's so that is so fucking stupid. A lonely Frankenstein, he's also pulling his shirt
open to reveal it like he's, you know, in a in a gas jeans ad. Well, it's brighter Frankenstein,
so he's showing that he has hope for love. A lonely Frankenstein travels to 1930s Chicago to seek
the aid of a Dr. Euphronius in creating a companion for himself. The two reinvigorate a murdered
young woman and the bride is born. She is beyond what either of them intended igniting a combustible
romance, the attention of the police. And here we go, Joe, a wild and radical social movement.
Oh, for the love of fucking God. Yeah. Oh, here we go.
If that echoes Oscar winner poor things, rest assured that this bride is not at all like Bella
Baxter. Jesse Buckley told IndieWire that the film is chock full of gill and halls twisted imagination.
That's what I've always said about Maggie Jill and Hall. Don't worry, everyone. The movie's going to
be chock full of Maggie Jill and Hall's twisted animation. And not what did I just say?
Imagination. Sorry. Crazy. This is on the heels, by the way. This is on the heels of the announcement
that there is a remake of war of the roses happening. You know, I saw that I really, really,
really love the war of the roses. It may be too painful to revisit, but Benedict Cumberbatch and Olivia
Coleman. So it's kind of a smaller scale British movie, I guess. I don't hate it. I don't hate it.
I don't need. I don't need it. Well, look, it might be fine. As we sit here, getting ready to talk
about a roadhouse remake. I didn't need a roadhouse remake, either. But, but yeah, I just,
oh, God, they're making another blob. Another blob too. Remaking the blob.
These are all headlines in a row on movie web. MCU Blade Reboot finally gets an update.
Jesus Christ. Did they even finish making that? I don't know. Super natural is potentially getting
a revival soon. This is all just on the front page. Folks, I was asked about a year ago if I wanted
to reboot wings, the NBC show wings focusing on Tim daily, the straight man. They were like,
we've got daily. I passed a year later. They came to me and said, we're looking to do a wings reboot.
I said, yeah, you came to me with this a year ago. It's with Tim daily. They go, no, Tim daily dropped
out. We want to do a Tony Shalube -focused wings reboot. I laughed on the phone, but I'm like,
well, look, I like Tony Shalube. I don't know why you would spin off just his character who,
if memory serves, was an immigrant who like lived in the airport. It was like the terminal with Tom
Hanks. I said, I assume you have Tony Shalube and the answer was no. We're doing a Tony Shalube
focused wing reboot. We haven't yet asked Tony. That's what the business is right now.
And then if I said yes, then that's a year of my life developing a show. Then we go to Tony.
He says no in five minutes, and I've wasted my life. That's how the business operates right now.
Yeah. Well, I mean, he is the most relevant of that cast. Oh, yeah. Yeah.
By far, after the fact that with the mustache died, yeah.
You know, and I guess that could be funny. He'd be like doing like a sign felt thing where Kramer is
the, you know, you go back to the building and Kramer's still there or something like that along
those lines. But did you watch that first round of sign felt spin -offs? The Kramer is a
as a private investigator. I've tried. The Kramer one is the most
worthwhile. Yeah. But no, I hated. I thought, well, I take that back. New Adventures of Old Christine
was the best of those shows. Yeah. I didn't, it was, I could recognize that it was a good show.
I didn't like it. It wasn't for me. It was a little too sterile. Sure. And then at the Kramer
in Alexander shows, the Alexander show is Jason Alexander has said this is great disappointment.
Yeah. That he thought it was a good show. And that it could have been, if they had a better shot,
they could have made a good, they could have become a really good show or whatever. But
I think it's terrible. He said also too, they actively tried to make like an extension of George
Costanza without making us, Costanza spin -off. And I don't see that at all. I see no connective
issue between. Yeah. He was a motivational speaker that had nothing to do with George.
But also too, just the energy of the character. And like he's not expressive. He doesn't, you know,
well, Elaine also had that show that was like, it went backwards with Stephen Colbert.
What? Didn't she? I'm going to look her up because she had a show very short lived
before Old Christine. You got a show.
After sign fell. Because she, yeah, people forget. They think it was just Old Christine and
B button. No. She was, oh, yeah, she's essentially scrubbed us from her, her resume. I got to go deep
in the IMDB. But um, did you want, so you told, you directed me, Joe, towards that Larry Charles
documentary about the failed comedian? Yeah, I can't. She was very depressing as you, as you promised,
it would be. But then that led me to Larry Charles introducing his first post sign fell pilot
with Wayne Knight. Have you seen that? Yeah.
It's a multi -cam pilot with Wayne Knight as like a dad. It, I made it five minutes. It's so
fucking bad. And for Larry Charles to be like, I thought you guys would get a kick out of this. You
know, it's a great show. I'm like, no, it isn't, man. It's, it's really bad. But um, it's interesting.
I hope they put more of these failed pilots online. I love watching them. I'm a fan of Larry
Charles. I wish he would step in with some of it. I mean, maybe he doesn't want to. Yeah.
I wish he would come back and I really wish he was involved with this last season of curb. I just,
I went back last night and rewatched the original curb, the documentary, the fake thing where he was
going to do the special that started the whole show. Yeah. And yeah, I was just like, oh yeah,
this used to be really fucking funny. Yeah. Oh yeah. And by the way, similar, similar dilemmas
as the new season, he just, oh, actually, one of them, he redid. He's, he read us so much on curb.
Some from science felt some from curb, but he, yeah, he read us a lot. What is the thing he
read? Did he read it a thing? And I was like, well, the happy ending massage he's already done.
He did that. But no, no, no, no, it's the, oh, God, damn it. There was a joke in that,
and either in that episode or in that documentary, or in the very first episode of the first season,
because I watched both where I was like, that's the joke he does in the latest season. Is he,
is he purposefully like just giving like an homage to the past jokes or something? Like,
I don't think so, no, but I don't know for sure. Um, the show was created by Julia Louis
driver's husband, Brad Hall, and it was, it was called watching Ellie. I did watch it. Her husband
was Steve Carell, and it wasn't told backwards. It was told in real time each episode, a linear 22
minute slice of Ellie's life. I remember that. Yeah, apparently I went two short seasons.
Two seasons ain't bad for, you know, I mean, no, that's a bad day for Julia Louis drivers.
There's two full seasons of a sicker. Yeah, yeah. So, uh, Julia Louis drivers and Steve Carell though.
Come on. I bet some of those are funny. They got to be. I, uh, let's take us to that corner.
I saw
in sendies a movie I have long wanted to see. It is Dennis Villanoves movie prior to prisoners,
which is his masterpiece in my opinion. And I completely see why this got him prisoners. It is
awesome. It is a excellent story clearly and cleanly and beautifully told.
I was, you know, I was surprised. I've watched so much junk lately. I was like, what a, what a
beautifully put together movie. It is a movie about, I don't want to spoil anything, but it is about
two twins who are at the wheel reading of their mother who has just passed away.
And they're in sort of a war -torn Lebanon -esque country that is left intentionally vague.
The twins are given instructions that you're going to get your inheritance from your mother
if one of you finds your long -lost brother, okay, like what? We don't have a brother. And the other
one of you has to find your long -lost father who I told you was dead, but who is actually still very
much alive. If you do this, then I will tell you what your inheritance is. Now, like, fuck you, mom.
Like, but of course they're curious. The brothers like fuck this. I'm not doing it in the leaves,
but eventually he joins the search as well. That's about what I can tell you. It's these twins looking
for their family, but it was, as I said, a really, really well -constructed screenplay. Great characters,
great twists. You've got to pay attention. But Villanoves, the shit, man. And I looked at his IMDB.
I'm also going to talk about the movie he made prior to this, but it goes this movie, which is
excellent, kind of his indie, into prisoners. He did a rival. He's doing all these cool, interesting
movies. And then it's Blade Runner 2049. Dune, Dune 2, Dune 3. And just another heartbreaker for me.
You know, there's so many of these where you're like, Matt, see you later.
Yeah. Oh, well. Oh, well.
Guys gifted. And there's so many people right now going, dudes, the masterpiece, go ahead, go ahead,
enjoy it. I'm just saying I think his talents would be better used elsewhere, like this movie
that I'm talking about. He also did Sicario, which is fucking excellent.
Um, okay. Yeah, I'm not, I love prisoners, but yeah, it's all over the world.
Gives Sicario a watch. I watched, well, you know, a movie that you said was good and that everybody
said was good. Uh -huh. It's not good. It's a bad fucking movie. I read three. I was at my place.
And the internet went down, yeah, because it was raining for the 87th fucking day in a row.
And I just, you know, I was like, I had a screener of Creed 3 sitting there that I had never watched.
And I was like, you know what? Fuck it. I put it on.
Um, uh, it's bad. It's a bad movie. It's, uh, it's, you know, is it not better than two?
I guess it's the same goddamn story again. It's the same fucking thing. Yeah, I, I, he wins a
flight. And I thought, and I don't know why you told him to do what he did and ended his career.
But I thought that Jonathan Majors was such an excellent villain that he up the game of three
and made it better. Jonathan Majors was amazing in it. He was amazing. But the character is so,
okay, let me first of all, they do the thing with Creed 3 that they have to do with every movie
when they start running out of ideas. They have to add lore. Yeah. So now all of a sudden
there's this whole backstory of when young Creed was a, was a young boy. He had a friend who was
supposed to be an Olympian boxer. Uh, and that's the reason that he wants to, by the way, we're,
we're, we're, we're dipping now into the plot of this week's movie. Uh, uh, roadhouse. Yeah.
He had a, you know, so he doesn't, it turns out he didn't want a box because of his father. He
wanted to box because his friend was a boxer and his friend was going to go on to the Olympics and
do all this stuff. And what happens? Well, things go wrong for his friend and he goes to jail over
an incident where he pulls a gun on a bunch of guys who are beating up Adonis. And, um, and because
he comes to Adonis' rescue, he gets arrested and goes to jail because he goes to jail. He doesn't
get to box because the kid is a theory, theoretically, a bad influence. Creed's mom hides the letters
that he writes to young Creed. And it is revealed later that this gentleman thinks that Adonis had abandoned
him. And so now he's out of jail. Adonis is retired. Again, he's not going to fight another fight
again. Um, and just like in a bunch of the Rocky movies, again, uh, and now the plot is is that this guy
wants a title shot and Adonis potentially has the ability to do that. Adonis, of course, is like,
this is absurd. I can't get you a title shot. So the guy
Drago, young Drago is supposed to fight the champ. Right. And this guy then has young, pays a guy
to beat up young Drago. And you find out that it's so obvious that that's what's going on, but they
reveal it 20 minutes later. And you're supposed to be like, I didn't see that coming. Which you see
it coming from a mile away. And the way they reveal it is the guy that beats up Drago, uh, the mom finds a
picture of the jailed guy and the, and the, and the assaultor of Drago shaking hands from when he was
in prison that he said, it's all just so sloppily fucking written. It's all completely unbelievable.
The dialogue is corny. The heart is corny. You don't give a fight flying fuck about the,
so what happens, of course, everybody Adonis has to, because now
there was string of events. This maniac from prison beats up the fucking, uh, he does have to,
he does get the title shot. He does fight the champ. He almost kills the champ. Oh, we've never seen
that before in a rocky movie. Um, and then because of all that, what happens? Adonis has to save
the day. The only way he knows how by getting in the ring to make a bunch of money for a bunch of
people and he has to fight his old mentor slash best. It is so fucking idiotic. It's idiotic. It's
fucking idiotic. It's so out of the realm of any possibility of anything sports related. And it
takes its so into the zone of like superhero. It's crazy. And yes, it is glaringly obvious that
not only is still well not in the movie, they don't even mention him, which is a weird spiked thing
that the studio is doing. It truly lacks the Stallone presence. I mean, here's the heart and soul of,
obviously, the franchise, but also of creed. I mean, him and him and creed was incredible at this,
for the first one. First one's awesome. And the first one makes sense. Yeah. And they don't even
mention him. It's like, what are we doing, guys? What are we doing? By the way, you're going to hit me
with flashback sequences in a fucking creed movie. Oh, here's an idea. Maybe you could have done a
flashback with Carl fucking weather as a young, de -aged creed, which they could have done. And you could have
seen a really cool fantasy sequence between him and the son he never met or something like that.
You're wasting my time with a young Jonathan major. What the fuck off? Fuck that movie. It sucks.
I remember enjoying it. Everybody did. I think we were still hot off the heels of COVID. I feel like
it was not. Yeah. I watched first time female director on the Roku channel. Okay.
What is the number one viewed show or movie on the Roku channel? Two broke girls. How much
money do I get from that? Zero dollars. Same fair to you. It doesn't seem fair to me. Anyway,
first time female director is written and directed by Chelsea Peretti, a comedian who has never
been nice to me. I'm afraid I try not to hold that against her. She is the wife of Jordan Peel who
makes a funny cameo appearance. You forget that he's an actor. The movie is a ripoff of waiting
for government to such an extreme degree that it hissed me off because that's one of my favorite
comedies. And here that a recent movie that ripped off waiting for government theater camp did it,
but also brought a whole bunch of its own tricks and a whole bunch of its own comedy and a whole
bunch of its own style. You could say the same about like Hamlet 2, the very funny underrated
Steve Cougan movie. It brings its own stuff to the party. This is just so fucking lazy. It is the
homeless man's waiting for government. Forget poor man's. It sucks and it's got a funny cast.
It was clearly shot like they they had a school for a weekend. It looks like it was shot very quickly.
It's really badly directed. It's like you're you're I'm not trying to be sexist. Your husband is a good
director. You could have ran a few questions by him. It's really it's really poorly directed.
And that's what it is. It's a woman who's kind of a mess. It's like a screaming loud broad
performance from Chelsea Pretty, which is not her wheelhouse. She is directing a local play.
It's got Andy Richter. It's got Amy Poler. Kate Berlant. Blake Anderson from the Workaholics,
Megan Malali, Max Greenfield, Tim Heideker, Nick Crowell. There's a bunch of like quick funny
cameos. Actually, Brad Hall, the creator of watching Ellie has a cameo in it. Legero Guy,
Bronham, you know, you know, a lot of these people from comedy. We're hitting a point now. It's
like we're talking about earlier. The comedy for the masses is not funny and the comedy for the
alt world is not funny. I don't know where to go for my laughs anymore. But this really bummed
me out. It's like all these funny people coming together. Okay. If you want to do kind of a loose
improvie, we'll do our waiting for government. Fine. But that movie, a they had mapped out the story,
Kerber enthusiasm style, b they worked forever on getting those perfect characters right. No one in
this movie is playing a character. They're just themselves. Right. It's weird because
Ferretti is obviously somebody who knows her way around a joke and can be very funny. I don't know
why anybody let her release this movie. I mean, it's a it's a fucking disaster. Joe.
Yeah, I hate to hear it. I like Chelsea. I think she's funny. And I was interested in seeing this. I
can't access the Roku channel, though, unless I'm on my laptop. It seems like Sam. Yeah. So it's not
it's not everywhere. I don't know why they would not make an app for this thing. It's ridiculous.
But anyway, it's there's their second kind of big comedy release. They also did the Weird Al movie,
which was decent. Well, my only other entry today, but it is very funny in speaking to where to go
for your comedy. Alan Partridge live from the Oosthouse podcast, which is available on Audible.
It's just huge fan. I'm on his latest book about the he is trying to build a lighthouse big
it's called Big Beacon his latest book. I listen to them all. They're so funny. The pod is if
you've never heard it is it's basically his radio show. Yeah, where he's at some sort of event
or partaking in some sort of task on air or interviewing people about whatever, but it's very very much plays
like a local NPR radio show, which is what? What was the what was the not aha? What was the single cam
Alan Partridge, Tridshow? Where it was it was, you know, every episode would start in the radio show
that it would you it would go into like into his life. It was like a, you know, that's I'm Alan Partridge.
Yeah, yeah, it's that show from I'm Alan Partridge, the Mid -Morning Manor or whatever. And I'm I
it's it is scripted. I was like, how does he this funny? This is crazy. This is perfect. But then
at the end, they're like, this was written by and they name like seven people. You're like, oh,
okay, that's it's a script. I think the podcast has a has a staff, but his books are written by
these two guys who must just be fucking hilarious. And then he comes in and lays his own sauce on it. But
anything the key thing with the Alan Partridge books and there's no week there's no week link. They're
all perfect. I partridge is the best probably, but you have to do it audio book style. I mean his
his vocal performance is what makes the thing. It really is. He's so funny. Yeah, the there's a
there's an episode I was listening to. It's about a funeral or he's buttering bread for the
funeral buffet. Yeah, which is such a funny just setting or whatever. And it's just the way he keeps
coming back to it. He's talking so the story about a guy. He's like, he's like, he's like, I ran
you know, he he he was out and about probably shouldn't have been because of lockdown. It was
lockdown. He shouldn't have been out of the house. And he keeps telling the story and he keeps coming
back to again, should have been home lockdown. But but nonetheless, not to judge, but it's so fucking
funny. He's criticizing the cooking of the women at the never a bland of food tasted that had a funeral
buffet. They don't want to spice things up too much. Yeah, it's it's it's amazing. It's amazing.
Yeah, like it's it's it's a real human being you're listening to. You're like, this is this is a
person. This person exists. And and I wish I knew him even though it might be annoying if you
actually knew Alan Partridge, but you know, it's like a like Jimmy Glick or any of these other
great characters. But anyway, give it a listen. Alan Partridge live from the host house. I don't
had to look it up, but it's like a summer home kind of thing. Okay, he's got two seasons of that now
of the podcast. And they're great. They're like, you know, it's it winds up being like five hours of
stuff. Okay. I rewatched I think for the first time since theaters last action hero in glorious 4K.
Uh, the movie I had tried to watch on TV for whatever reason. This is a movie that has looked like
absolute shit in every incarnation on home video. And I think it's probably because they lost so much
money with it. They were like, fuck it. Just dump it out on a piece of plastic. Get it out of my sight.
But to see it in 4K, uh, it looked fantastic. It looked like all the classic kind of 90s action
movies. Um, it's John McTaren and director of diehard. There's great action in it.
There's great comedy in it. The first half of it, I think, is a really solid, entertaining spoof
of the movies of the time and who better to do that than Schwarzenegger. There's stuff in it that's
really weird tonally like there's, um, it's it's realistic. People are dying. But then when they go
to, it's almost like Roger Rabbit. They go to the police station and they're partnering up unlikely
hairs. Like there's a Nazi and a rabbi are paired up as funny cops, you know. And you're like,
oh, that's funny, but that's a hot shot, Joe. Like it just can't decide what movie it's making, you know.
Then, so while I'm still sitting there thinking that was an odd tonal choice, you know, to have a guy
in full rabbi gear, do that bit, then they're pairing a guy with an animated cat. Like MC
cat cat is coming up. And the kids like, see, we must be in movie world. There's an animated cat over
there. Now, sure enough, when you look online and you're reading like the Wikipedia page and some
red, it's about the most complained about moment of that movie is the animated cat. And that seems
to where most people went. Oh, fuck this. Like what world are we even living in? But you've got
to look at this movie. Yeah, I thought it was kind of clever too. It's a, it's an notorious flop.
So people have their guard up about it. But it's super entertaining. I think it goes on too long.
I thought, wow, this is definitely like 20 minutes too long. And then the editors at the time were
like, I don't think Cisco Niberg get to tell us it should have been 10 minutes shorter or whatever
else. We were editing this movie the night before it made it to theaters. And you see that sometimes
there's some shotally done effects, you know, in around this movie, that's like a massive big summer
blockbuster. And everybody says if they had just not come out like the same weekend as Jurassic Park,
the movie might have had a chance. Schwarzenegger begged them to not release it. But they did. And
everybody hated it. And it doesn't deserve that. It's not a lost masterpiece. But there's a lot
of really funny stuff in it, particularly in the first half. There's all kinds of great cameos. Like
like Sharon Stone standing outside the police station smoking a cigarette. You barely see her.
The T 1000 walks out past Arnold and the kids like, wait, did you see that? Kind of like the Wayne's
World cameo. But it's that kind of movie, you know, there's just a million great little
in jokes, some tonal issues. But it's a good action comedy. If you never saw it because of its
reputation, I recommend checking it out in the 4k. Joe. Yeah, I always liked last action hero. Tom
what's his name? Tom Noonan. Tom Noonan. Yeah, he's great. And then you also the the one liners are
great. Like Arnold's up to a guy and he goes, hey, are you a farmer? And he goes, what? And he
goes, you want to be? He goes, what? He has a couple of acres. And then he kicks him in the nuts.
I thought of acres. I think it was I think it was two meta. Yeah, for the public at the time. I think
everybody wanted, you know, this is big follow up to last, I mean, to a terminator to, you know,
and everybody wanted another terminator. And they got this instead. But this was the beginning of
the end. I'm just looking up. I mean, Schwarzenegger obviously is still highly relevant. But I'm just
after they were to race or actually no true lies was after this. And that was a big hit.
But then it's like junior, eraser, jingle all the way. Batman and Robin. Yeah, end of the day is
yeah, six to the six day. Yeah, the lateral damage. And then I remember when he terminator three was
coming out, they were like, all right, here we go. Arnie's back. I really like terminator three,
but it did not, it was not well, it made $433 million. Jesus Christ. Yeah. So it did, it did just fine,
but but people didn't like it. No, and then that was it. And then he became governor and you didn't
see him again till the expendables. Anyway, speaking of ass kickers and one liners. Yes, roadhouse,
starting director of the twistedly imaginative Maggie Gyllenhaal, brother of the as we all know her
as the director of the twisted visions, Jake Gyllenhaal, just boring old Jake Gyllenhaal. No twisties
and imaginative things here. It's just old Jake old Jake, he's playing Dalton, you know,
it's the same role as in roadhouse did find it out that they're like, they keep or at least one
person tells me as a girl's name. Have you ever heard of a woman named Dalton? No, the fuck was that.
Sometimes like there's when if you see any line of dialogue in a movie, 50 people stood around and
heard it, you know, and there's people hired to go wait, that doesn't make sense. They're called
script supervisors. I these things get into movies all the time. It doesn't make any sense. There's
yeah, I don't know. I've never heard of it. Yeah, I've never heard of a man named Dalton.
It's a weird name. They're out there. They're out there. But, uh, yeah, it's directed by Doug
Lyman. Lyman, you know, started with swingers and he's done a lot of really good action movies,
uh, edge of tomorrow or live night repeat. You know, he's he's good. This movie was very controversial
because they put all this money into it. Lyman was like, I think this is the best movie I've ever
made. He's wrong. And they couldn't get a theatrical release out of Amazon. Now, I mean, while I'm
at a movie last week, I'm like, well, fuck, I came to the movies. There's nothing to see. I don't
have anything to watch. Why aren't you releasing Road House into theaters? We're coming off strikes.
There's no entertainment. Why did they dump this on private? I never understand the decisions that
go behind whether they do it or they don't. Um, my guess is they thought it seemed like a direct
to DVD movie, which is how it's felt to me. It's the Road House story, you know, uh, essentially the
same thing. And this version, it's it's Jill and Hall was a MMA fighter with a, you know, scandalous past.
And he's brought in to kind of clean up this bar in Florida that really looks like a set,
like really looks like a back lot set. Well, let's start there. Let's start there. It's, it's, he's
approached by a woman. It's the lady. I know Phoebe, but I never met the other girl from two dope
queens, but it's her. She doesn't have acting now. Uh, she approaches him at an MMA fight. No,
I'm not an Emma. I'm sorry. Like an underground like fight club style. Right. You know, where he
where he's supposed to fight post Malone just for Williams. Yeah. Post Malone, by the way, I was thrilled
to see that he's got a slubby Bobby body with man tits because post Malone is like one of the coolest
dudes alive. And I'm like, Oh, he's kind of got my body. That makes you feel you'll be devastated to
learn. He's lost all that weight. Well, throw Zemper. Doesn't matter. Which he claims was giving up soda.
Well, fair enough. Anyway, yeah. Uh, she approaches him. She says, I've got a problem. I've got
these ruffians that come into my bar and kind of fuck shit up every night. I'll pay you five thousand
dollars a week, which is insane. If you have a bar, folks, I've got a bar. If you've got a bar that's
struggling for any reason whatsoever. Yeah. You don't got to have. Yeah. A week. A week.
Anyway, I'm like, okay, that's clearly going to be a plot point where she can't pay him or
something. And they know they don't do anything. Whether it's just she just got that money.
He goes down to the roadhouse. This is why I interject it. He goes to the roadhouse and the roadhouse.
It's not really a roadhouse. It's like a beach cabana teaky bars. And that right there is trouble.
I don't mind, um, take, I want you to take some fucking liberty. I don't want
the Gus Van Sant Psycho remake where we're doing it beat by beat. Change some shit.
Put in a movie called Roadhouse, folks. Why are you not shooting this movie in a roadhouse?
That makes no sense. My theory is that Jake Gyllenhaal said, they probably did not go to Jake Gyllenhaal
first. Let's be under Rousey was doing it first. Okay. That makes a lot of sense, actually. Yeah.
But for whatever reason, they end up going to Jake Gyllenhaal. And Jake Gyllenhaal comes back and says,
you know, guys, I'm not against it. I'm open to it. I just don't really want to spend
six months of my life in the fucking backwoods of Alabama in like Splatland. So makes them.
We do something about that. And they go, you know, we could do it in Florida. And they go,
yeah, all right. I don't know. We're getting somewhere. So I think that's probably what happened.
That's my guess. But because it makes no sense, it's it's bright and shiny and beautiful. And
there, there is a, the plot as you eventually find out is that the rich asshole in town is sending
these thugs into the bar every night to fuck things up. Why? Because the woman that owns the bar
won't sell the bar to them. Yeah. I want you to sell the bar to them because her father, a black man
opened it in the 60s during racial turmoil, whatever, and succeeded and put a stamp down
in this place where everybody was against it. And he succeeded. And this is their legacy. And she's
like, I'm not going to just sell it, you know, especially to a bunch of these rich guys that just
want to own literally every part of town to control everything here. It's a strong enough motive
for her not to sell the bar, but it gets to a point where I'm like, I feel like you would have
just sold the bar at this point. I feel like you would have just like, give me, give me X amount
of dollars and I'll leave because I don't want to be around people like this anyway.
I don't know. It gets a little convoluted. You know, Jake Jellin Hall does show up. He does start
kick and ask what CGI asks. Like, can I just say the thrill of these movies, the John Wicks and
stuff, which you CGI, I'm sure in these fights, he's don't get me wrong. But generally in a fight
movie, the thrill is watching people fight. You know, I know they're not making contact, but that's
what this always was. Swayze trained and people trained in martial arts and so forth. And
this, you know, yeah, Jellin Hall is an amazing shape, whatever. But the vast majority of these
fight scenes are very obvious CGI where they don't seem to be needed. Like when they throw a guy
and he crashes into a table, you're watching an animated thing do that. It's very non -exciting to me.
It looked real to me. I didn't, I don't know. It didn't make to me. Well, I'll say this. Let's,
let's talk about a different aspect of the fight scenes. Jake Jellin Hall is very good. He plays
the part very well. And he's very good at being, you know, the whole thing. Like there's that great
scene when he, when he first gets to the roadhouse and the, and the assholes come in for the first time
and then he takes them all outside. And he's like, he does the whole thing where he's like, guys,
before we get started, is there a hospital near here? And he's not saying it like a bad ass. He's
telling me there's a hospital close by. We're all going to have to go. And it's very funny. He beats
the shit out of all of them. I like the way they shot the fights where you're seeing like first person
stuff. But they're, you feel it. Like they're, there were hits where I was like, I, I felt that,
that felt like it really hurt. And I felt like I was in the fight. And there was a lot of humor in
the fights, which I really liked. But, but after that first fight scene is when, in my opinion,
the movie's problems start because this is where they now start introducing too many characters.
So now he goes to the hospital and there's a nurse there that thinks he's an asshole because he
brought a bunch of damaged people in and that's getting in the way of people that actually need help.
And these are just a bunch of drunks that fight. So then she sort of becomes the love interest.
But then there's the woman that runs the bar and you're supposed to care about her. But
then there's people that run a bookstore. And there's a little girl that works at the bookstore.
And you're supposed to care about them. And I'm like, guys, combine some of this shit like me, the
fucking bar owner, the love interest, or, or make her the mom of the daughter and get the bookstore
out of here. This, you're bringing like way too many. There is so fucking dumb. And that girl, she goes,
oh, it reminds me of like an old Western. You're like one of those Western characters who comes
in to clean up the town. Guys, what, what has happened to subtext in movies? We all know that this
is a Western style setup. We don't need a girl to say this is a lot like a Western or a girl
beyond her years. She's like, yeah, well, you're like, what 12 year old talks like this? You know,
I'll 12 year olds love the old black and white Westerns. Just outrageous. By the way, by the way,
not a video store where she would have watched Westerns. And it would make sense a bookstore. She's
reading books. Yeah, fiction novels about the old West. I can tell, by the way, you're talking,
you enjoyed this quite a bit more than I did. I hated it. I thought Conor McGregor was
super annoying to then have Billy Magnuson, who's a very funny actor as the villain play essentially
the same character as Conor McGregor. They're just two crazy guys who kind of look alike.
I didn't care about anyone or anything in the movie. It's over two hours.
I liked Billy Magnuson, my favorite, some Sandler character. I liked Billy a bit. I thought Conor
McGregor was a little green in his acting, but I thought he did a very good job of making me nervous
and feeling like this guy's out of his fucking mind. So I bought that. I liked that.
But again, this is where the movie starts to get convoluted. Why is Conor McGregor in it? Well,
because the bad guys fail so many times at intimidating Jake Gyllenhaal and get the shit beat out of him,
so many times by Jake Gyllenhaal, that the dad yet another character, the dad of Billy Magnuson's
character, who you never meet because he's in jail for life, hires Conor McGregor to come into town
to kill the bouncer. Yeah. Why guys at this point, are you not just killing the owner of the bar?
We got a real terminator situation on our hands here. Guys, stop trying to kill John Conor.
Go back and kill Linda Hamilton and the whole thing is solved. Yeah. Why are you focusing on this,
it's crazy. So that happens. Then one of my all time favorite tweets, and I wish I remember the word
of it, but it was why aren't more people talking about Sarah Conor, raw dogging a stranger at the
height of the AIDS epidemic? It's not quite exactly it, but I just thought I love when people have a
different take on a movie. It always makes me laugh. Anyway, go ahead. Then the brookhead sheriff comes
into it. Yeah. And all the cops are supposedly brookhead. Yeah. But they're not some of them are
some of them are. Then you find out the sheriff is the dad of the girl that works at the hospital that
he's in love with. It's like guys simplify this fucking thing. It's a roadhouse where you're having
problems. Make the problems fucking make sense. Again, even their motivation is very convoluted. You
guys are this concern that you don't own one single piece of beachfront property in the entire
town. You're you're concerned about that. Yeah. In the original one, if I'm not mistaken, I haven't seen
it a long time. Gazera is the one bad guy. And he wants the roadhouse because isn't it on top of like
where there's oil or something? I believe so. Yeah. It's something where you're like that's very
concrete. Yeah. It's like killers of the flower moon. There's oil under the land. These people occupy
the land. The assholes are going to try to kill them now to get the western. Yeah.
It's like a western. Yeah. This whole thing goes around and circles my favorite line in the original
roadhouse is Sam Elliott goes, you know, this reminds me a lot of one of the old Western pictures with
the gal boys. And I'm because that's not like something Sam Elliott would say. I've been in those movies,
Mojito. The other thing, can I get an ETA on that mojito? I ordered Mr. Jill and ho. Yeah.
There's also that weird. What is that weird detail at the beginning of this when he first gets
to the roadhouse? And he goes, he goes, can I get a coffee? And then he's like, we don't have coffee. We
know. And you're like, well, sir, that's going to come back later. Whatever the fuck that ridiculous
pointless scene was. Nope. Yeah. I thought like it was going to go time to the heritage of the people
that own the bar or something. There's nothing. I was like, okay. The, the, yeah, he, it's weird.
Nothing really bad ever happens to any of the staff of the bar. The only bad thing that happens to
anybody is they, the daughter and the father that have the bookstore get hospitalized because they
get attacked. Right. And then that is what motivates him now to not leave town to stick around and do
what he's got to do. And you're waiting for the line to come. He says at one point, I'm very scared.
I'm more afraid than you can imagine. And then you know the follow up to that line is going to be coming
very soon in the movie where he's going to say, I'm not scared of what's going to happen to me. I'm
scared of what I'm going to do to other people because they establish at this point his shady past is
he murdered a guy in the in the ring at UFC. And that's why you can't find anymore.
You're waiting for the line. It finally comes when it does. It's awesome. He brushes a guy's
trachea by punching it. And he goes, you're, he's broken. You will not be able to breathe. He's telling
the guy's going to die. And he goes, he goes, somebody asked me the other day if I'm afraid.
You know, and he says the line, I'm afraid of what I'll do because now, now I can't stop. And I'm
like, I'm like somebody told me the other day that this reminded her of a Western. It just keeps
going with it. Yeah. I didn't get it at first, but now that I think about it, I see how I represent
the cowboy and you, the Indian. Yeah. And I never noticed the roadhouse does have swingy doors on it,
which it does. But at that part, I'm like, awesome. Here we go. Now he's going to go John Wick.
This is going to be awesome. And he sort of does, but not really. And he still makes a lot of jokes and
things. And he's still kind of nice guy, Jill. And I'm like, and yet a cool chance they're to
really turn this over into like a wild thing. I also thought too at the end, when Billy,
whatever his character's name was, when he betrays everybody, including Connor McGregor. Yeah.
I was like, Oh, what a finale. Now Jake and Connor McGregor, yeah, who wanted to kill each other
are going to team up and bring like the ultimate come up into to the bad guys. And now they just
fight to the death and Jake ends up thinking, well, you know what, sometimes I don't know this,
but sometimes what happens with stars is that does happen. If something that you would, you'd think,
oh, wow, that would have been a much better ending. How did they miss that? Sometimes that'll be in
a script and Jill and Hall or any actor will read it and go, Oh, no, I want to be the sole hero at the
end of the movie. Cut, cut McGregor out of this and just ruin the movie so they're more of the
hero. Stuff like that happens all the time. Well, they want to look better and they don't care
how the movie around them looks. It's funny. I'm making that up again. Maybe it wasn't him. Who
knows? But it's funny. You mentioned that because the, I've watched a lot of YouTube videos with
Conor McGregor and Jake Jill and Hall interviewing after this because I wanted to see what the
report was like. And they have an amazing report. They have great chemistry. They seem very
friendly. They steam. They're, they're ball -wash in each other through the entire thing about how
much they admire one another. Yeah. Kind of McGregor, by the way, seems like the nicest man on earth,
which was a relief. Probably not true. He's, no, he's very like, he's very like, a lot of those UFC
guys are like his, I mean, he has sexual assault charges. He does. I think so. Let's shouldn't
put this up. I can't imagine he's starring in roadhouse with
won't face sexual assault charges in Miami. These were recent. But he's not facing charges.
All right. I pull it. Okay. All right. Well, that's a bummer. That happened. Anyway.
I, I, I, I, I'm just surprised. They just seem like they, they enjoyed one another. So
yeah. He's definitely, there are a lot of interviews with him though on YouTube where he's like
twitching and shit and people are like, oh yeah, he looks super cucked out. They got something here.
But then he also has been punched in the head a million times. Might have something to do with.
Yeah. Okay. Wait a minute. Florida robbery arrest.
Okay. So, so he was, there were sexual assault charges in Dublin.
Um, March 22, the high court made a pre trial discovery order against McGregor in the case.
The order requires guard day. Who's the accuser? I guess to disclose certain information and documents
gathered by them. So that doesn't sound like that's over. Yeah. Uh, the Florida robbery arrest.
Okay. He was arrested in charge with strong armed robbery. Yeah. Okay. He grabbed. Okay. Well,
that's he grabbed a, a cell phone from a fan who was taking a picture and smashed it. And that's,
that's what counts as strong armed robbery. Holy shit. Yeah. I accept that. I would do that if
somebody had my picture all the time. There's then a Dublin pub arrest. Uh, Corsica
arrest alleged attack on Francesco Batchy Nettie. Uh, Gregor's pub targeted with
petrol bombs alleged attack on yacht Miami related incidents. It's the whole section by itself. Yeah.
All right. Yeah. Now there's an alleged sexual assault in Miami here. Okay. You know what? You were
right. Well, I misspoke. Uh, uh, anyway, the original roadhouse is considered a, a modern classic,
you know, it's like like showgirls or like Starship Troopers. It's one of those movies that has its
tongues so perfectly in cheek that you don't quite know how serious they intended it. You don't know
quite how funny they intended it. But the, the mix and what hit the screen was perfect. It just
they, they got the perfect tones that it didn't become the room, but it also didn't become John Wick.
It's its own weird, beautiful tone. That's kind of campy, but also works as an action movie.
This movie for me plays like any other modern action movie. I like that it's human beings and not robots
or, uh, superheroes, but it just felt endless to me and the fights had no personality or, or
character or color to them. That I disagree with. I agree with a lot of what you're saying. But
I thought the fights were very well done. It just, it didn't feel like visceral or real in a way
that you want a roadhouse bar brawl movie to feel. As I said, my problem started right at the beginning
when I said why is this movie not set in a roadhouse? I just felt like it was kind of a missed opportunity
because you can have a lot of fun with something like this. And I felt like they just didn't.
It seemed like you had some fun with it. I had no fun. I would say my overall recap is it was dumb fun.
I enjoyed it. Uh, you know, I didn't walk away going my god. What a picture, but, but I had a good time.
Uh, and I did enjoy the fight scenes quite a bit, which, which will make or break the movie for you.
If you don't like the fight scene, you're not going to like it. See, I think in a post, in a post
wick world, these kind of fight scenes can't compete. I, I'm not, yeah, it's weird. I had a very
different take on them. I, I did think they felt visceral. They felt, I felt like I was getting hit.
I thought they were really interestingly shot with the first person perspectives and stuff, but,
but it's okay. It's, it's, it's like I said that I think that's a real interesting takeaway of the
movie. If you like the fight scenes, this movie is good enough. And if you don't, you're not going
to like it. Like, but I do think that they are, it's like, it's like, if you like the car chase
scenes enough, you'll like fast and furious. That's it. You know what I mean? Sure. Um, my hog is,
I wouldn't, I don't know if I'd say up, but it's ready to fight. Um, it mines way down. It's
out cold. We will be back with probably Lisa Frankenstein and definitely late night with
devil, which is coming to shutter, but in theaters now, I want Instagram at the Patrick Walsh,
we are on Instagram at see you in hell pod. We still have our Facebook page up. Yes. And we thank
you all for being our Patreon supporters. We love you. Joe. Thanks, folks. As always, check out my
website. Come to see me in a show. I plugged them all in the last episode. Come to Joey Roses.
I plugged that as well. We'll see you next time. And we'll see you in hell.