Summer is here, and Bed MDM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer.
Or check out our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz.
Only available at Bed MDM Casino.
Spin on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 fortunes, Mystery of the Lamp, Raken
Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand!
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action!
Bet MGM in Game Sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 plus to Wager, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and West Virginia
only, games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as non -mustrable site credit slash bonus best unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
The football season is full of guarantees, and here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October, if
your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning or winning money back in fan
cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
Winning hits different here.
Monthly 21 -plus, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamberler, offer not available in all states,
term -supply, see Fanatic's fourth book out.
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to another edition of Will See You In Hell, the podcast
now part of the Fangoria Podcast Network.
You know that, because I say that every week, for information about the network, you've
heard this all before too, including the other programs, maybe you want to follow our show,
maybe you want to find past episodes of Will See You In Hell, or any of the shows on this
find network visit Fangoria .com. You've heard it all before. Now on with our show this week we're
talking greed. This episode we're talking greed. This is the sixth of the seven deadly sins.
Our next edition will be envy and then we're done with season two of the podcast and on to a
Cisco and Ebert style format as discussed. Good news everybody. Yeah. We made the official decision.
and we are returning back to an all movie format.
We won't be watching the films and providing commentary
during them.
We are going to be discussing a film every episode
for about an hour or so.
And Pat and I often agree and disagree.
And you know, it'll be like a mean Cisco and Ebert.
Yeah, which the fans seem to like.
And that's good because they were.
Like, have you seen that YouTube video where they're trying
to record a promo and they're just biting at each other.
No.
I will send it to you.
It's one of the best things you'll ever see.
They're just shooting a 15 second promo and it starts out, they're like gently ribbing
each other and then it starts to get so cruel and nasty and cutting and by the end, because
they get really angry, but by the end they're both laughing and friends again and then good
naturally ribbing each other and laughing at each other's jokes.
But you really see the whole relationship play out.
I love it.
Uh, as usual, Pat and I sitting here with alcohol, I have a St. Pauli girl, Joe in my hand.
Has any beer ever tasted and smelled more like marijuana than St. Pauli girl?
It's my first ever St. Pauli girl.
It's weird.
It's like skunk weed.
I'm smelling it.
You're right.
It's Heineken smells like that.
Yeah, exactly.
I don't like Heineken.
It's stink.
It does.
It's going to taste like Heineken?
an Amsterdam every bar like the on tap is Heineken and yeah that's like their Budweiser
earlier yeah I just got so sick of it because it was always like you can get a Bud for
five or you can get a Heineken for a dollar yeah I'm not a fan of Heineken and and Heineken
is the only beer in my experience that makes your breath reek like beer like it's the
one that you drink where everybody makes sense that makes sense which I don't care
I like a sneaky alcoholism sure see that's it's a scary thing for me. I've I've I've had
a couple of friends in my lifetime whose breath is
just
chronic and terrible and
You don't know whether to tell them. I would hope my good friends would always tell me if I have a single issue or a permanent issue
It's a tough tough topic tough subject. It's a bridge
It's tough to bridge, but you got to have a friend close enough who's gonna be like your breath fucking stinks
Yeah, you know, you have to have that and I hope you will do that for me in a fun way that makes that breath
Stank if they said it like that you'd be like, oh, that's fine. Okay. Yeah, or offer you a mint and then you do the thing
Like, oh, do I need this and then you can go yeah? Yeah, yeah, you got a little beer breath or whatever
That's it. And then you go you do asshole. Yeah, I think I'm offering Vince because you're hungry
I've never offered you a mint in my entire life. So if I'm doing it now take the hint
I get a little annoyed sometimes like I'll be with like with a girl and like we'll be spending some couch time together for the first time
And I'll say hey, and we've been out of the bar or something. I'll say hey, you want some gum and with oh without fail almost every time
Look, why do I need it? No, just we're clearly about to make out. Yeah, I'm just we've been out pounding shots of Yeager Meister
Yeah, it's the way an American summer thing is somebody offers you a piece of gum that means you're about to make out take it
Yeah, it's just like, you know, it's not, I'm not saying your breath stinks, you know,
we just ate onion pizza. I think, you know, we've known each other two, three years at this
point. I, I'd never known you to have it. And I think the only, only once, and I heard about
it second hand was that our buddy Vince was like, Pat, were you okay last night? And I actually
wasn't. I felt really, really terrible at some bar and left. And he was like, well, he had Joe
said that you had the sick breath. And I was like, that piece of shit, why wouldn't he tell me I
I had the sick breath.
But I think it was just that something was going wrong
and I felt terrible and it was reflected in my breath.
I don't even remember that, to be honest with you.
I'm sure at one point when you were leaving,
you got close to me, probably, and said I'm leaving
and I thought, oh yeah, I can smell he's got some sick on him.
Yeah, because I always, and not puke breath,
but just like sick breath.
I always breathe into my hands.
I'm always very conscious.
I'm big into all toads and et cetera.
And what I can say and hope that a couple of people in my life
who have this problem, who I'm not close enough
to breach the subject with. He'd the advice. Get it checked out. I think it's a big thing with
former alcoholics. Their insides are so destroyed that it's sure. And I think whiskey is a big
factor. Uh oh. I'm in trouble. Hello. Joe was telling me the other night that he was doing shots of
scotch, which every time I thought about it for the past several days has made me so sick thinking
about doing a shot of scotch.
It was, I only did one, and it was disgusting.
I was out with, I was at L. Sid, which is, if you live in Los Angeles,
or if you don't live in Los Angeles, it's an outdoor bar,
beautiful Mexican restaurant kind of place.
They also have an indoor space, but you go there mainly for the outdoor.
And the upper patio of L. Sid was having their first night of,
They were doing some new thing up there where like it was a different menu and it was a different drinks and whatever
And it was their first night to the hostess who was quite lovely said
Guys if you'd like to go up to the upper patio, it's free booze and food up there
We just want people up there so it looks like it's happening. Yeah, great. We went up all we could get was wine
But I had mr. One Bill Burr with me bartenders knew who we was they were like Burr
You want something? You got it. Yeah, he said me and my friend Joe would love some whiskey
They took that as scotch, which God love them. They were giving us free booze
Yeah, they poured a couple Johnny walkers and then they said apparently to bill
We want to do a shot before we leave so Bill said we got to go do a shot of those guys
And we went in them. Fortunately the shot they poured was
Scotch yes, nausea
I mean it was and I was chasing it with more Scotch. It was it was a rough shot. I don't I mean
I mean, we've discussed this before.
You used to be very adamant about me doing shots.
You've gotten 100 % better about it.
I don't do them anymore.
And I think it's why I haven't had a hangover
in several years.
I can't stand them.
I don't see the point.
Put a couple ice cubes in it and sip it.
You know, I drink pretty quick.
I just don't need to jam it into my system.
I hate it.
I do it as, yeah.
I usually do them now as a kickstarter to the night.
Like, if I'm doing a beer night,
my first I usually will have a shot or two kind of up front right or somewhere in
that first four or five beers to kind of just get it going yeah I didn't
really write last night I was at our good dear dear friend Vincent Georgia's
place great watching payback the rest give some oh okay yeah and we were drinking
beer and then Vincent one I was about four or five beers in and Vincent do you
want some whiskey. And I said, you know what? Yeah. Had two quick pops of it with with our
dear friend Jesse pop who better to pop with pops with the pop. And then I was like perfect.
I was just like, yeah, now I'm just going to sip another beer to smoke a little reef. Yeah.
We put on UHF. Oh beautiful. We were the anticipation. We always got to talk about movies in some way,
even though we're not officially back on movies. But I think we should. I think people want it from us.
the anticipation of just Vince started talking about UHF and how much he loves the movie.
I started going, I love the old guy so much. He goes, what do you mean? And I go, the guy that's
like, you idiots. Right. Yeah. Bad guy. Vince and I start laughing hysterically. We're drunk. We're
puts the movie on and it's about a 25 minute take until you get to that guy right and he
was just counting it down in the best way he's going oh man we're not far off. He's coming
soon. Seeing hits opening line is you idiots which I didn't really remember that and I mean
that exchange between him and weird hour he accuses weird house stealing the mail and then weird
Yeah, no, I don't I don't work here. Yeah, he goes, ah, trespassing.
Which I just magic or Kevin McCaffrey is his name and he's been in quite a few twilight zones.
Kevin McCarthy or McCarthy's and was in the original invasion of the body snatchers as the lead.
When I was a kid, I was very obsessed with Weird Al and was probably my first big comedy love.
I had all the cassette tapes. I followed him through Alapalooza, the one with Jurassic Park on the
cover oh you hung in there that long I did but I was a bit younger than you so
yours last one might have been smells like teen spirit or what it smells like
nirvana I was out after dare to be stupid I was out okay see I was so you know
but no even worse was my last one yeah we did fat that's pretty great yeah I was
so young that I really loved that weird I was going after nirvana I was like
11 and I was like yeah fuck them you can understand a word they're saying like
Like I wasn't old enough to be like, obviously I love Nirvana, that took a few more years.
But my intro to Nirvana was definitely weird now.
And I used to be obsessive about UHF, and I had his VHS video collection, which I watched
until it ran off the damn spool.
The man was a genius, as well as I'm concerned.
Well, I used to love when Weird Al used to do the MTV takeovers, and it would be like,
out TV the whole day.
Yeah.
Those were fucking amazing.
I didn't have MTV, but I actually ordered a VHS dub of an LTV best of off -off lines.
That's what you had to do in those days.
Right.
If you wanted to...
There was no YouTube.
You know, I'm going to sound like an old man, but you had to go find some shit.
There was a whole store at the mall, which was bootlegged concerts on VHS.
It's amazing that that was a viable business for many years, and I miss it.
Illegal.
It's got to be illegal.
Yeah.
They used to have a big...
still well moved but right near the where I grew up there was the Valley Forge
Convention Center and they used to have a music show there every black
Friday and it was just table after table of guys selling like bootlegs and
wordies and whatever and eventually they weren't allowed to sell that stuff
anymore and then that moved downtown to Philly and yeah but but I used to live
for that I had I mean we started at MTV I remember I didn't know what Weezer
looked like and they were one of my first like CD music obsessions. You see the cover of the
box or whatever you want to see them move and perform and I would buy these like boot legs of
their concerts. I was like God damn these guys are so exciting and energetic and it set me up for the
fall when I saw them on the green album tour and they acted like first they came out three hours late
like they were guns and fucking roses. They played only the green album and they would not move and
And I was like, well, wait, I saw this video where you guys are doing backflips, practically.
What happened to you?
Really?
And still you go see a Ouija, they barely moved, they're boring as shit.
Yeah, it's a shame.
That new album was sort of a return to form for them.
You know, 50 people have told me that.
And the album sucks dick.
It doesn't suck dick.
It's just not, yeah.
But here's what sucks is a guy came in and wrote it with them, like they got a, like there's
a guy that like helped them write it because he was like, no, this is how you write a
weasers song.
Sure.
So it's just kind of a bummer.
It's just kind of a bummer.
How did Michael Richards perform and hold up as Stanley Spadowski?
Amazing.
Yeah.
It's still hilarious.
Because that was my introduction to him when I first started watching, so I felt season
one because that was a big TV guide obsessive.
Yeah.
And I was like, oh, they got the guy from UHF and this.
No.
He's hilarious in it.
And I mean, in my opinion, one of the great feats in cinematic history is we're now making that Twinkie
He makes that Twinkie hot dog where he cuts. Yes. Twinkies the bun the hot dogs in the middle and then he puts cheese
Was on it. Yes, and he fucking commits to it man
He dips it in milk and starts eating it. Yeah, and there is not a break in the edit
It's so yeah, I think I would have no problem eating a hot dog Twinkie cheese was
Well, it wouldn't make me sick. It's one thing to eat the twinkie cheese was hot dog
Yeah, another thing to soak it in milk. Yeah, odd move for sure. It's the grossest
Combination ever and like any sticks to it. Yeah, I appreciate all right. That's fair
I saw UHF at the drive -in theater in Missouri, they would do double features, but it wasn't
always of two new movies, they would show, when I saw Batman there, probably two years
after it's released they all they paired it with Beetlejuice like they kind of had interesting
pair and it was great but why I really love going to the drive -in is because if I did it
suddenly I could turn my head and see the R -rated screen which would often contain tits.
Why are we not going to the drive -in we have out here? When I started dating my girlfriend I went
all the time and I would love to go anytime you want to go it's so fun yeah we'll put a cooler in
the trunk get some weed. It's like a half -hour drive tops. You see a double feature, but
I was seeing a couple of movies with Heather there, and we turned around and like, this
one has four screens all across this parking lot, like giant four screens. So on one of
the screens would be literally like Cars 2, an animated movie. And on a screen in the, honestly
So in the same viewpoint was that 302 and just like a graphic 10 -minute sex scene, I'm
sure it's been an awakening for several children, but you see two movies for the price of
nine bucks.
It's great.
And they used to let you switch screens, so I would see three, because they had a seven
and nine in a midnight, but now they watch it very carefully.
So that sucks.
So now you got to pick which two you want to see, right?
And that's the problem there as if you don't like the pairing tough ship
But is one of the movies on both screens?
Sometimes they'll do that. Generally, there's a popular one that they'll
You know, they really seem to be because the line was always so long and it was so crowded
They started really kind of fucking with people. Oh, I want to see that but that's actually a nice segue into our topic
You got greedy and you can't get exactly greedy with it anymore. Are you greedy when it comes to that sort of thing?
I used to do that in New York. I used to go in. I'd buy one movie ticket. And I call by the way. Yeah. Oh, that's not a bird.
They're a dog.
They probably can't hear it at home. The mics aren't picking it up. There's some sort of honk. It's a guy that honking toy. It's a guy that sells like churros out of his shopping cart.
And he just honks that horn going up. It's like his version of an ice cream man. Yeah, it's annoying. Yeah, I know.
So he's he's set up camp here. He's not walking up and down the street. He's walking up and down. It's just you can imagine pushing a cart up this hill. Yeah, I can't imagine, you know, I walk up this hill. I feel like I'm going to have a stroke.
I know.
But anyway, I used to that in New York. I would go what I would do is I would figure out like, okay, there's these two movies I want to see playing at the AMC.
whatever. And I would call them, I would say. I'm coming to the theater today. What's,
and I was always the second movie I was going to go. Yeah. What screen is such and such playing
on it for 30 because that's so weird that you would even ask why would God go because I'm meeting
some friends there and we're going to be very pressed for time and I want to be able to tell everybody
ahead of time like it's in this theater. And they would go, oh, that's playing in 15 or whatever.
And then so suspicious and like a needless I'd so I go in I'd buy a ticket for the first movie and go see it
And then I know like okay when the credits start rolling. I've got three minutes to get to 15 to see the other thing
I'm amazed we never discussed this because I can do you one better and
We did a two -bro girls episode about trying to sneak into five different movies in one day
That was a great episode, but I
When I lived in Missouri, I used to do it constantly, but I started a tradition the day after
Christmas that still goes on to this day where it's called the day after Christmas movie
spectacular.
Great title.
Yeah.
And I mean, I would step over the red rope at the West all of 16 theater, pass the ticket
and go make the international, I got to make a phone call thing to the ticket ticker, walk
over to the pay phone, which maybe there isn't even a pay phone anymore, so maybe it's not
possible.
But I would now I would go got to run of the bathroom mouth that and go into the bathroom
Then you're in your pass the ticket taker. It's a day after Christmas so they're packed
What I used to do was pretend to be on the phone make my call talk talk talk till the guy had his back to me
Hang up the phone go into the men's room
Waiting the men's room a couple of minutes come out walk with a purpose, which is very important to my theater
I would point to someone who wasn't there and go like oh over here over here then go into the theater
You'd buy no ticket. I bought not even the first ticket
Then how did you get past the guy that tears the ticket? That's what I'm that's what I just explained to you
Oh, you would you have to go to the bathroom and then he wouldn't he'd forget that you went in
I'd say I had to go to the phone then by the time he turns back to me
He assumes I'm gone, but I'm in the men's room when I come out of the men's room
He doesn't even he just thinks I'm a guy come out of the men's room now. He's taking tickets
We would get the running time of each movie add 10 minutes for trailers and time it so it was bang bang bang
See five movies every year the day after Christmas for free
I had some friends who had a guilt would buy the first ticket or they'd want to go get launched and I'm like
Well, that's stupid because then you got to buy another. Yeah, what would you eat this whole time?
I would bring in some food in my pocket
I know my whole goal was to never spend a dime
So I guess that is great or just being cheap. I had no money
Then around the time I got to New York when I had even less money and a lot of free time I would do the exact same thing
I would see five movies for the price of one one year after my it was my birthday
And I had no friends in the city one of the saddest days of my life. I go to that AMC
Times Square theater 42 42. Yeah, and
I said hey, what's the longest movie you got playing? And they said cold mountain. I said great
I go and I watch cold mountains. It would kill the most time. I came out and snuck into something I didn't even want to see
like, you know, soul food or some movie.
No interest in.
Just whatever killed the most time,
I would spend whole days at the theater.
I had girlfriends do this with me in New York
who were never enthused about it.
It sounds terrible.
And as I told you yesterday,
there's this restaurant called Cozy,
which is kind of like a Chipotle,
but with salads and sandwiches.
Cozy is shit.
I like their Thanksgiving sandwich.
I really loved it.
The bread there was great.
What was on the thing?
Let me guess turkey, you know what's up thing cranberry sauce. Maybe a little cheese meal gravy
But I ordered it and there was a big line at the cash register and I walked right past the cash register
Where you would pay sat down at a table and ate my sandwich and no one even glanced at me
So for the next year I ate lunch there every day and never paid how filling was this Thanksgiving sandwich?
Oh, it took care. It was a I mean, I I was I weighed nothing at this point. That was my meal of the day
And I would go over and eat it in the restaurant because that's a little tip if you want to steal
They never expect you to just steal something and eat it there who would be that stupid
And it's that confidence that gets you away with it also in New York. No one cares
No, and what people don't realize because now I don't sneak into movies
I work in the entertainment industry that'd be a little stupid of me, but I
Will say
Hey, it's generally a 16, 17 year old who doesn't want to be there who hates what they're
doing.
I used to be a movie usher.
Never in a million years if I saw somebody sneaking in, would I run over and be like,
wait, wait, they don't care?
Right.
Nobody cares.
No.
It's a miserable job and they're probably happy you're ripping off their fucking bosses.
Yeah, yeah, I got really mad once because one of the things I would do in New York, because
even when you're in New York, you got to have your little hustles, you got to, I mean,
it's just, it's necessary, it's an expensive city and if you're struggling, you got to have
your little hustles. Well, a great one that my friend, my dear friend Joanne Grigioni
taught me was not so much a hustle, just a great tip. Yeah. Always buy your beer at
the drugstore. Drugstore everything is. Of course. It's this cheap as it can be. Yeah.
So, you know, you get stuck in New York going to these bodegas by six packs. You're dropping
13 bucks. bodega adds three, four bucks. Yeah. You go into the, you go into the, the
Dwayne Reed. You're getting a six pack of Corona's for like 6 .99 or whatever. And a stop and
shop's even cheaper if you can find one. Yeah, but but one of my things was I
would go down to the theater on a 14th Street, the Union Square movie theater,
which I like quite a bit because I'd find myself over there frequently during
the day with time to kill. I'd always buy a senior ticket. Sure. You buy it on
the kiosk. Yeah, I'd buy a senior ticket on the kiosk going up. You're in. But I
remember once, man, this lady, she called me out and she's like, you got to go
back and get the other I'm like what do you care I know you're not getting a
commission on tickets what do you care I myself when I got a little too old to
be just like sneaking in every time I did the same I used to get senior tickets
and I had the same thing a lady was like oh you bought the wrong one I was very
apologetic but part of me is like it's wrong with you help help me out a little
bit who gives or not coming out of your pocket a rats patootie as they say they
deal. Well, I guess that's sort of greed. I'll tell you what I think I'm greedy with, is
I don't know if this is greed or not, but I'm not a big like I need more money guy like
or I need more or more or more, but I am a guy that does like to buy things and I have noticed that
I never have enough records. I just want to buy records constantly. I have a huge collection
and it's just never enough. I don't know if that's greed or not, but
I've always been that I don't blow my money on you know
Cars or women or whatever else I but not women there not prostitutes now
But right sometimes you you do enjoy fast cars and fast, which well who doesn't right, but I've always bought
I like a big blu -ray collection. I like a big you you know was cassettes
Then it was CDs now it's back to vinyl which seems kind of stupid
But I like a big collection to put on display
Let people know what you like. It's a conversation starter. I like having the physical tangible thing
It's really my only indulgence too, but I that's a great fun
To stand at a you know, see you're over here on a Friday night. You're looking at my record rack
It's this cabinet. It's full this whole thing's full
It's fun to stand in front of this thing with a few beers in you and a little weed on your breath
And yeah, they go want to pick something out and you put it on and everybody says oh great choice. I agree and then you know I
Uh, you know, I am making some money.
I've heard.
I love making money.
I've been reading the trades.
I just made $13 ,000 in Las Vegas off of video poker.
For the second time in six months, which is amazing.
And I can attest people, loyal listeners,
that is absolutely true.
And I want now to go with Pat to Vegas
so he can coach me rainman style.
I will to win at the video poker machine and the thing is you know
They come over and they're always baffled by it and they put their key in the machine
They're looking a little skeptical. There's no way to fuck with one of these machines
It's not like counting cards or something. I've just kind of found a way to make money at it
and you can tell they hate it and
They keep giving me more and more. They'll put me up there for a week if I want to and a nice one bedroom suite
My movies my dinners my steak dinners my drinks everything's comped because they think I'm gonna fuck up and give them the money back
But because of I wouldn't say great
I'd say it's being smart with money if I lost even a grand I'd be like well, I'm done gambling for this
Trigger is a lot of money, but when I'm winning it all goes my pocket I put everything in the bank my whole thing is
You know, I'm making a good living. I can add this supplemental income in Vegas
is I just think back to my dad, you know, working day in and day out, back breaking physical
labor, trying to break even. And I've kind of, you know, it's, it's talent, sure, but
I've, I've looked into this great money situation for myself. I'm not going to fuck it up.
I don't spend it on a bunch of crazy shit. I'd say if anything, it's being thrifty. I tip
Well, I you know, I I go out with friends and have a good time
But I want to go a guy who's throwing around a huge chunks of yeah, I want to go make this money
Which of course it won't work for me. I'll lose everything and it'll be miserable you never know
But if I were to make this money, I would come home
I'd just buy something crazy. Yeah, which I would love it. Why not? It's fun when I was walking an envelope of
13 ,000
dollars, all in hundreds, into my bank of America.
Hey, I'm thinking, if somebody robbed me, this would be the best hit of all time, like
outside of robbing a bank.
I was a little scared because when you win the jackpot, there's a red siren that goes
off and makes sound, alerting everyone that you have just won a large amount of money.
Then they come out and give it to you in cash and it displays on the screen exactly how much
you've won.
No, do you want to let any listeners know when you'll be in Vegas again?
I mean, people and some shady characters will stare at you, especially when you win after midnight.
Yeah, some guy that just put his deed to his house down at the black check table.
I'm sure he's exactly on happy for you.
And you think about these little old ladies there who win these jackpots.
You got to go up to your room alone and I asked somebody once I was like,
look, has anyone ever been just hit and hit hard?
Winner one of these jackpots and they go you know where you're in trouble is if like I stay at the cause of Paul
If you hit it big at planet Hollywood then you got to walk back to the Cosmo right at two in the morning
Somebody might follow you and hit you while you're out in the stream
Fairly certain you could request a security escort. You probably could yeah, but they'll go you know
If you're here at the Cosmo and you're going upstairs
There are 18 cameras on you every step of the way and nobody is stupid enough to rob you and no one has ever tried
Now, I'll tell you who does approach you is them prostitutes.
They come out of the goddamn woodwork when they see that you've won a nice chunk of money
because they figure you're looking to spend it.
It's a rough one.
For me, I just put it in the bank, you know, I don't have any big purchase that I need,
but I should definitely at some point go, yeah, I'm going to take 5K of this and buy something
stupid.
Yeah!
But then...
I couldn't literally...
A part of me is like, I should give it to charity then.
You could buy a used car.
That's true for like 10 grand like a little fiat or something. He's like, yeah, no, I have this or a moat
True, you know when when things get really shitty is unless you hit
$1250 without $1 ,000 $250. They don't lock your machine
So a lot of things you get four aces or whatever and it gives you $800
You know that doesn't lock your machine. They don't come out with the w4 unless you hit $1250. So it's tax -free money, too
So you can win a couple of these jackpots of like $1 ,000.
I always sit next to this guy who never hit the jackpot.
He never had anybody come out and lock his machine and give him the tax form.
But he had put together about $3 ,600 in the machine.
And he's like real kind of slurry, and he's like, oh, fuck, yes, kind of drunk, right?
And I kid you not, he just kept hitting the button, boom, boom, boom, plan, plan, plan.
Then I look over again. He's down to like 2 ,800 from 36 and he's down to
1 ,400 and you never want to
Talk to a man about his money when he's drunk, right?
I lean over and I go buddy
You might get mad at me now. You won't be mad at me in the morning
I would cash that out and take it upstairs, buddy. Put it in the safe. Go to bed. You wake up tomorrow
You got $1 ,400 that you did not come here with, right?
You should listen to me and he goes fuck you man because I've been winning all night
I'm going to keep winning of course immediately angry kind of in my face
But fuck you really immediate fuck you like don't tell me what to do
Within five minutes. He's just fuck and he's down at zero and he stumbles up to the room if he had listened to me
He would have woken up because that's the thing you wake up the next day with money
You're like oh shit. This is great when I win money
I walk it straight up to the safe in my room and I put a post it on it in case I want to get drunk that says Pat no
Well, when I go up there and see that post it. I'm like Pat
No, you know what would have helped with that guy is as he was stumbling away. You should have went told you so
Oh sure that would have he would have stabbed me in the throat probably with a bottle
Buddy, I just I told you so yeah, just maybe next time you should listen when somebody tries to help
Yeah, you fucking idiot
I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you,
I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you,
I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you,
All of them, gluttony, you're being greedy.
Yep.
Pride, you're being -
You want attention.
Yeah, you need to be objective.
Short -sighted, greedy.
Envy, why don't I have that?
That's being greedy.
Lust, I want more.
Right.
What else is there?
Rage.
Yes.
Even in its own way.
Like it's all of them applied to some sort of overindulgence,
which is what greed really is, or the want for more.
So sort of a, what's an irrelevant sin on the list?
Because it kind of is a subcategory of all the other ones.
I agree, and did who came up with the seven sins?
Was it Jesus?
Who decided those are the seven deadlays?
I don't even remember.
Or no.
I have no idea.
You're talking to me like I put some sort of preparation
or work or effort into this podcast.
Yes, you show up and I fix a drink and we kind of go at it.
Yeah, I know which my beer is empty.
Do you need another one?
Yeah, I'll take one, Joe.
All right, you won't talk to the nice people while I get you
on.
Sure.
Greed in seven the movie, I forget what it was to be honest with you.
I guess it was, I think the banker at the beginning
where they just didn't really know what to do.
And they just found him dead at his desk.
Vanity was one in the movie maybe. I don't know.
Joe's just talking to me off screen him. And then of course, on the lighter side, you
have greedy with Michael J. Fox and Kirk Douglas, which is a movie I really loved a very
funny movie. Phil Hartman is hilarious in that. And he has one of my favorite insults ever.
He walks up to this guy and gets, I think it was Michael J. Fox. He gets in his face and he
is you know something I didn't like the Beatles and I don't like you. It's a great, great
line. We talked in the last one about how much we miss Phil Harman. But yeah, I think
the only area I might be greedy in is like, you know, you sell something, you sell a pitch,
whatever it is, you want to get as much money as possible. And that's really just being
smart. I think, you know, if you're going out of the way, if every decision in your
may, every decision in your life is motivated by money, that's greed. But simply wanting
to be compensated and wanting to get the most money you can, I wouldn't put that as a
sin. Maybe they're saying it's holding on to it, not giving it up charity, etc. Sure.
You know, I make a nice living. I try to throw out some money to charities throughout the
year. I try to tip well. I try to remember when I was a you know a movie theater usher or whatever
it may be. I try to tip a dollar or two even at the places where they're simply handing you
something. I mean I would say that any one of the seven sins to a certain extent, having a certain
percentage of that in your sort of daily makeup is good. Yeah. You kind of need a little bit of all of
these, but I guess the whole point of where they, or that the turning point at which they
become sins, access, yeah, is the, is the indulgence in one versus the necessary usage of it.
Yeah, if you will. So, I mean, of course, you need a little greed in your life because
without it, you don't, I mean, it's just, it's, you know, work at that could be defined
as greed in certain ways. You know, yeah, that's sad. I mean, like, you know, Leonardo
Articaprio probably has six houses and he fucks a bunch of supermodels and he has whatever
he wants private jet private helicopter.
Is that greed?
I don't know.
And maybe because that is greed, he, well, he's just being compensated, but he also does
a bunch of work and charity work and shit like that.
I guess maybe they're saying is if you have a tremendous amount of money to pay it forward
and pass it along.
Well, also to this is a very old school sort of Christian Catholic
Belief system. It's you know, they're like a more progressive Christian belief is that
You know, for instance a priest could live in a mansion or drive a BMW or whatever
Yeah, because the idea that you need to be poor and starving in destitute to be a truly truly a man of God is
It doesn't apply as much as it used to yeah
Well, and then you know a big part of a most churches really is the concept of TIEVE I believe it's pronounced
I'm not sure
TIE I think maybe a G in the mix as well
But just that you give 10 % or whatever you can afford of your income to the church and
When I think about these families pulling in
$30 ,000 a year with three children
Giving three grand to the church. It honestly makes me a little upset. Yeah, I know I agree with it
And my dad always dropped, you know, we never had any money growing up.
My dad would always drop a 10 or a 20 in the basket.
And I would be like, what are you doing?
It's like we see major improvements in the church or something.
It always upset me in defending your life when Riptorn says to Albert Brooks.
He goes, did you get into charity?
And Albert Brooks goes, I gave a lot of people on the street.
But you don't really get a receipt for that.
And Riptorn goes, no, like he just gets no credit.
Yeah for having give it and it's affected my giving change to people on the street, right?
I won a little credit
The things that start to affect me with that are like, you know, it's been done in a lot of TV shows
But it's done because it's true. I've done this so many times where I will hand my leftovers to someone and they will open it and go
Yeah, and try to give it back and it's so infuriating that it makes you never want to give again
I went up to a guy in a public park once and I said he was he was clearly homeless and
writing in a book or something. Right. And I went out to say,
hey, man, sorry to bother you, but I involve this food if you if you'd like it.
And he looked at me and he goes, I'm working.
Sorry. And they're crazy. Yeah. What can you say there is at the
intersection before I get on the five highway right by my house is you're
sitting there a long time. It's a long light. You're trying to make it.
You try to get on the highway. And there's a guy who has like a
wishing well set up with a bucket he spends all his time like really carefully grooming the
little area he's got a nice little racket and he comes up to each car window and we'll stand
there until you either turn your head away right which you have to do because he's there every morning
or you know half the mornings I roll in the window and give him a buck but one morning and I see
this guy every day I know he doesn't remember me I know he's crazy but my window was down I didn't
and frantically roll it up,
because that's always a terrible feeling
when you have to do that.
Right.
But he comes up and he's standing there
and I said, I'm sorry, man,
I don't have any money on me.
And he goes, screw you.
I was like, I've given you over the past year of my life,
easily $30, $40.
And now I want it back.
Then that's when you have to take it back.
Yeah.
I mean, I don't know.
It's easy to forget these people are crazy.
And then of course there's the people who are like he's just gonna spend it on booze. I'm like then good
Yeah, I don't know I don't have a problem with that. I always like this sign where it's like I'm gonna be honest
I want it for beer. Yeah, it's always nice. Well, I saw a great sign once I said can I please have some money for booze or drugs
Dot dot dot. Hey, at least ain't bullshit and yeah, and he put the apostrophe on bullshit
Which I thought great. Yeah, but I mean, I don't know I the that never affected me giving to the homeless or the
parent homeless, I don't give a shit if they're going to spend it on booze or whatever.
The thing that didn't stop me, I still do it, but I mean the thing that hindered me
from doing it more frequently was the fact that I started to read articles when I lived
in New York about guys that were like, that had houses that were professional beggars.
That started to really bother me.
And it made me start to look for, I always called it window shopping homeless people.
You would look for clues to be like, you're not really homeless.
Yeah, like you're your outfits too nice. I see you have out here every day
And you're always wearing a different outfit and it's always clean like you're not homeless. I read a couple articles like that
It's it's a real dark place to start thinking like that like all these homeless people are doing that because that's definitely not true
But no not at all. It's just that's why I say window shop. You got a you find the guy and you go now this guy's clearly homeless
Right, I read an article about a guy who's a professional
Jack Gallifonakis from the hangover in Vegas and he stands in the strip every time you go to Vegas
I thought you see him
But now you actually see the other 30 guys who do this now, right because they read that this guy was pulling in 60k
Year and then people are like everyone goes to Vegas because they want to recreate the hangover
I don't you know people from other other other
Other lands do where it's a big vacation an exciting trip for me. It's a four -hour drive
but
But, you know, they're like,
oh my God, it's a guy in the hangover,
they want a picture he charted his five bucks.
The guy made $60 ,000.
Now, there's one in front of every hotel.
A guy dressed like this.
It's kind of sick.
Yeah it is.
But then again, maybe he's smart.
Anyone making money, I'm like, good for you.
I don't know what to say.
I mean, smart, greedy, lustful, erotic.
Yeah.
Gluttonous, hungry.
Who the hell knows?
I don't know anymore.
You got anything. Well, it's too far out to plug because we don't know when this one's coming out, but so just your Twitter, I guess, right?
Yeah, Twittervine Instagram the Patrick Walsh. I don't I don't I think this will already have happened on doing a standup show in New York.
Sunday May the eighth at UCB East.
Other than that, keep listening to the podcast folks keep giving us those reviews. I hope you enjoy it.
Me, Twitter, Vine, Instagram, Joe DeRosa, Comedy, and I'll be at the Wild West Comedy Festival in Nashville, Tennessee, May 19th and 20th, so come out for that!
Pick up Ken Hanley's book, The Iron Evil is our executive producer, it's a very funny book.
Yes, it is very funny, and we should have been playing it this whole time, and we just started plugging it, because this brainfarts, but that's about it.
But yeah, go go get that book. It's great. Yeah, Pat. I'm gonna miss you and I you. I hope you're well
Well, I'm alive still I'm fine