I'll see you in hell.
And when the sound of your screams becomes the thing of my dreams, you know I'll say.
Ho ho ho, folky folky folks, it's...
Damn it.
Leave it.
Leave it in.
I was going to say ho ho ho, folky folk folks.
Uh huh.
Not Joe Joe Joe.
You already missed a pretty good opportunity there.
Well, maybe do a Christmas on with the Joe, except as ho ho ho.
What song?
Oh, yeah.
Uh, and now on with the Joe Joe, the missile Joe, hung where you can see.
Somebody waits for me.
Kiss her once for me.
Right?
Yeah, there you go.
Burl Ives.
Have a holy, jolly Christmas.
I always found it a little creepy that Burl Ives is singing.
And the way he says it too.
Kiss her once for me.
Weird, Burl, you're like 75.
Have you ever seen the episode of Night Gallery that stars Burl Ives?
I'll tell you no, I've never seen any of them.
Does he play Santa?
I own the Night Gallery, I've never opened it.
No, he plays a quite sinister man.
He's awesome in it.
And I was like, it makes it even cooler because it's Burl Ives.
It's a great episode.
It's an awesome episode.
Maybe I'll start with that one.
And is it Christmas themed?
No, not at all.
Oh, okay.
Not at all.
I thought maybe they didn't let Burl Ives out of his house if it wasn't Christmas time.
I never saw him do anything that wasn't Christmas related.
You know what?
I'll tell you the episode.
Spoilers, everybody.
Because it relates to the last thing we were just talking about.
It's about a guy who, a prominent businessman, who you find out early in the episode is having an affair
with a woman who is going to basically try to blackmail him.
And he's got a problem now.
So he's receiving these letters that are saying,
We know what you did.
Meet us here at this address at this time with this amount of money if you want this to go away.
So you're like, all right, well, he did something real bad and he's in trouble.
So he goes.
It turns out that it's some house in the middle of fucking nowhere.
He has to ditch his car and like walk through brush and brambles and all this stuff to get even to get to the house.
And he gets there.
Burlives is there.
Burlives.
Oh, here I thought Burlives was this fuck machine.
No, no, no, Burlives is the guy at the house and he's talking about.
He's talking about I forget the other character's name.
So -and -so is coming.
So -and -so has got a real bad temper.
And he's making the guy think he's got a way out of this.
And then it's revealed very quickly that he doesn't.
And he tricks the guy and traps him in this awful cellar where there's only one way into the cellar to trap door.
And the guy stuck in the cellar.
And then Burlives, who's talking about the purse, you find out that this woman was Burlives' daughter and she was a stripper.
And this guy had an affair with her and then killed her because she was going to talk.
And Burlives keeps telling the guy, you know, don't worry, there's one way out of that basement.
Like there's a way out of that basement.
And this person who's got the temper finally gets home.
You realize it's a little kid.
It's the son of the woman.
And he just wants, he wants revenge.
And the guy's like, you lied to me.
There's no way out of here.
That door is too high.
I can't climb up to it.
And he goes, I didn't lie to you.
There is one way out.
And he throws a bullet down.
And the guy's got an empty gun down there.
And that's the end.
I'm not doing a total justice, but it's a fucking great episode.
And Burlives really, and that's what I mean about the apology.
Somebody's done a horrible thing.
Either ramp this up where you're like, this is wild.
Like what a fucking scene this is.
Or take it terribly seriously.
Apology to one or the other folks.
Burlives was in Cat on a Hot Tin Roof, which I forgot about.
He's great in it.
Big Daddy.
And he was in one of my favorite Westerns, which not enough people have seen.
The Big Country.
And he won Best Supporting Actor for it.
So there you go.
And the Burlives appears to be a drink.
Okay.
So let's see what's in that.
I can't imagine eggnog isn't one of the ingredients.
It says the holidays came burly this year.
Scotch, sweet vermouth, creme de cacao, bitters, and an orange peel.
Sounds like an old fashioned with Scotch basically.
Well, the creme.
I knew there'd be some cream element to that thing.
Yeah.
Burl was a man who liked cream with his drink for sure.
Why have we been speaking about Burlives for so long?
Oh, have a holly jolly Christmas.
Yeah, that's my favorite Christmas song by the way.
Have a holly jolly Christmas.
I'm here in Hotlanta and it's cold.
It's getting to be like at night times like freezing weather.
I go to Missouri next week for the holidays.
I want to see some fucking snow.
That's what I want.
Well, you might, who knows?
I'd like to see a little snow too.
And that's not a euphemism, people.
I mean actual snow, talking about some wild bite.
If it's getting plowed by a house key, all the better.
I got some news psychos here.
Yes.
Because I only have one thing for the movie corner.
And people, it's not that I don't care.
It's not that I'm just having to spend time watching the things we're reviewing
and I'm not having a ton of extra time to watch additional stuff.
A lot of my TV watching over this last month has been taking place right before bed.
And I don't think any of you want me to do a rewatch review
of the Married with Children episodes I'm falling asleep to
that I've talked about a thousand times.
Did you see the Beverly Hills Cop 4 trailer?
No, it's out.
It looks good.
It looks like, what was even happening with part three?
Why would they even green light that pile of shit?
Which I just saw recently for the first time.
But it looks almost like a Bad Boys for Life type reimagining of like,
it looks like a Michael Bay movie or like the classic 80s style.
Huge explosions, giant budget.
Riser's in there with the gray hair.
They bring back John Ashton.
Everybody, Balky's in the mix. They're all there.
Does it look funny? Is there like a couple good like...
You know, it's more of a teaser.
I think it was really just probably put out to show you like,
this franchise is back to spending like $200 million again.
And for me, I thought John Ashton was long since dead.
So I was very excited to see him again.
No, John Ashton does like, I think sports radio somewhere.
What a dream job.
I mean, I don't care about sports, but what a dream job to be like,
you know, I bought a ranch in Montana
and I do a small little local radio show.
Yeah, for sure.
And I make...
That's probably what he always wanted to do.
Yeah, I make 85 grand a year.
Yeah.
And I lead a simple life out of it.
Great to see him again.
I'm going to be watching that.
I got a plane on mute here and already it looks very quality.
On the other side of the coin,
I watched the Garfield trailer in between recordings today.
Like, did you ever even just read one Garfield comic
before making this fucking movie, you fucking clowns?
Do you think the only interesting thing about Garfield is that he eats a lot?
First thing we see him eating is a piece of pizza.
So already it's like, oh, so he doesn't just love lasagna.
It's all Italian cuisine now.
He doesn't do or say anything rude, crude, negative, mocking.
He's just an adorable little cat.
Well, wait, are you talking about the teaser where John...
That I think is just when he finds him as a kitten, I think...
It's a two -minute trailer.
He finds him as a kitten, he moves in, then I guess his dad's also moving in.
He then looks like Garfield after that, though, after that opening, I think.
No?
But he doesn't act like Garfield Joe, and that's what's bothering me.
Fair enough.
I mean, this whole thing...
By the way, I can't wait till we get into people online that have a problem with
how is a black cat the father of a white cat?
Because Sam Jackson is the...
Why is Sam Jackson's character not an actual black cat?
I guess everything's about race now, isn't it, Garfield?
No, I couldn't care less about that.
I'm saying...
No, I know.
In a two -minute trailer, you have thrown out every piece of Garfield lore
that the fans have come to know and love,
and you've taken away his attitude, his spirit.
Garfield is an asshole.
You want to make a movie about a cat who's easy to get along with?
Go make Heathcliff, nobody's going to go see it.
No, Heathcliff's a real piece of shit.
Heathcliff is an asshole.
He eats shit, but I don't remember him being an asshole.
He's an alley cat, he's tough, but I don't remember him being an asshole.
I hated Heathcliff, I felt like it was such a fucking sad excuse.
Awful.
Heathcliff is, to cat comics, what Marmaduke is to dog comics.
You can't just have a big dog and that's the end of your character.
There has to be something else going on.
That's the beauty of Garfield.
Garfield is a depressed person.
He overeats to self -medicate, he sleeps all day,
he's disgusted with everyone around him because they are happy
and he cannot understand that happiness.
I related to Garfield the same way I related to Charlie Brown.
They're depressed.
When you're a kid, you're like, oh, okay, I think this guy feels like I do.
You can't suddenly make Garfield an adorable little cat who likes pizza.
Ninja Turtles like pizza, you fucking clowns.
Well, I guess the cuisine was a necessity given the fact
that he's finding the cat on the street and then going in a restaurant.
Like, a guy's not going to order a pan of lasagna.
Why not?
You just have the chef come out and go,
you know, I made one of the too many pans of lasagna.
Explained. It's explained.
I like that that's the detail you've got a problem with.
No, there's a million details.
I could talk for the full hour about it, but I won't.
I saw and I hate, especially since you're a comic
and I would love to give this guy a shout out.
I'll jot it down and do it on the next one,
but you know how you're on TikTok and you're not paying attention.
I saw the stand -up do a bit so funny about the Ninja Turtles.
And it was like, you know what I find weird about the Ninja Turtles?
Do they need the masks?
Do they really need that?
I mean, you wouldn't say, you know, there was a seven foot tall man
who just came in here with a shell on his back.
And I, boy, I wish I could give you more details,
but he had this mask on his face.
It's a really funny bit.
You know, I'm laughing at that.
And then he slides in with the funniest part of the bit, which is,
and we're making two or two to three of these Ninja Turtle movies a year.
Why are we cracking down on everything,
but we're still comfortable with that splinter voice?
He only does it for like 10 seconds because he knows he's on thin ice,
but he goes, you know, everybody's so woke and everybody's so concerned.
All of a sudden this rat comes out of the back and goes,
Oh, hello, Turtles.
We've been allowing this since we were kids.
It's a really funny bit. I'll find the guy's name.
He's a not unknown.
I should be known at some point. I just didn't know who he was.
That's very funny.
I'm not going to read the whole article, but one of my,
this is a little bit of a cheat because I'm combining segments,
but one of my news psychos was Rex Reed has reviewed Thanksgiving.
Oh, boy.
Does he call it a turkey?
Does he use Thanksgiving puns?
I'm going to guess.
I'm going to read the headline and then the opening blurb.
Okay.
A Thanksgiving horror movie is exactly the hack job you'd expect.
This is, Rex is really,
despite the appearance of such veterans as Gina Gershon and Patrick
Dempsey, did you ever think you'd hear Gershon and Dempsey
referred to as veterans?
She's Shelly Winters or something.
The acting is uniformly mediocre.
The really bad and intrusive pop music only prolongs the agony and nobody
in this miserable Thanksgiving ever eats so much as a single
cranberry.
He's mad that there isn't seeds that people eat.
Come on now, Rex.
That's not what you're mad about.
You're mad because dad didn't love you, buddy.
Jesus Christ.
You got to get to therapy.
He's, uh, oh boy.
It's just, that's just so funny to me, man.
It's so fucking funny that he's mad about that.
Oh God.
Uh, love Thanksgiving.
You had a new psycho.
Uh, yeah.
Well, uh, that was one of them.
Um, the other rest in peace to the great, the great Andre Bauer.
God, what a loss.
I'm so sad about this.
We brought him up not a month ago talking about the mist and how much we
love Andre Brauer and he, uh, yeah, gone too soon.
I, I never watched Brooklyn nine, nine.
Almost everybody I know says it's a really funny show.
Um, and I heard he was great on it, but I always say like, why don't we see
him in anything?
But he was on that show for like nine years, so he was working.
Um, yeah, I got, I'll recommend the mist and I'll certainly recommend
homicide life on the street where he played this, uh, detective who slowly
started losing his mind, like having mental issues.
It was one of the most riveting stories I've ever seen on TV and he was so
fucking good.
I, I don't know if he got nominated.
I would assume.
I mean, it's a performance that still gets talked about, but what a great
actor.
Um, okay.
Yes.
Rest in peace to Andre.
Uh, I'm very sad to hear.
Apparently it was a very short bout with lung cancer.
Uh, I guess recently diagnosed and very quickly fatal.
Very sad.
Gone before his time.
Uh, and also, you know, rest in, I didn't know, but rest in peace to Kenny
Deforest.
Uh, I didn't really know Kenny, but, um, he was a comic and my God, the
outpouring of love, uh, from the comedy community, uh, shows how well liked
and adored the man was and loved.
And that's sad that he, that he passed.
So rest in peace.
Um, I didn't know either, but, uh, what I've seen the past couple of weeks
has been really funny.
I guess he got hit, hit by a truck on a ball, riding a bike.
And it's just, that's, that's essentially what I just spent the last several
months watching was on the six feet under rewatch.
I mean, every show starts with someone dying abruptly, horribly,
unexpectedly.
It's a great gimmick.
It gives you like a little movie before the show starts, but man, as you're
watching it over time, that show really just started getting to me about death
and how like it just, it can happen at any time, anytime.
Um, on the heels of the Netflix isn't funny or whatever the hell the fuck it's
called that festival they do.
Um, that is just a ball washing of every famous fucking comedian they can think
of.
Right.
They, uh, are about to also drop.
Uh, the latest masturbatory jizz on himself fest from Zack Snyder, Rebel Moon.
Yeah.
Part one.
Oh, great.
Zach.
I love when you promise us there's a part two coming, whether you like it or
not.
Uh, a child of fire is the subtitle.
Uh, it comes in now, early reviews with a 23 % on Rotten Tomatoes.
Is anybody surprised?
Is anybody at all surprised?
This, this is interesting to me.
Disney has royally in all their indulgence and gluttony, royally fucked up
Star Wars and the Star Wars universe.
They fucked up Marvel years ago, as far as I'm concerned.
Uh, I love that just now people are going, I think Marvel's getting to be a
bit much.
Oh, okay.
Literally like saying like eighth hour of the buffet.
I'm starting to feel full.
Okay.
Yeah.
Um, Disney is really fucked it up.
And I love all the fervor that was around this stupid Rebel Moon movie that this
was going to save Star Wars.
And this, and because this was a Star Wars movie that he was in development, he
was making, he was developing.
Yeah.
Uh, and then they ditched it and then he went to Netflix and Netflix made it.
Why?
Cause they'll make anything that Zack Snyder wants them to make because they'll
do anything that a famous person wants and they don't care.
Anyway, so they made this movie, uh, and everybody thought it was going to be
the answer to what we've all been looking for for Star Wars.
And no, it fucking isn't.
And big fucking surprise.
I love this concept that the other big bad studio is going to rectify the
damage that the other big bad studio did people for gods.
This is just like when meta came out and everybody started being like, see you
later, Musk, I'm going to Zuckerberg's thing.
You think Zuckerberg's a good guy?
Are you insane?
The guy we accused of colluding with Russia to spread propaganda through
Facebook, right?
What, what, everybody's an idiot.
Everybody sucks.
None of this stuff is on your side.
Rebel moon has a 23%.
Is anybody surprised?
The guy that makes movie after movie where it's just fucking computer graphics.
Here we go.
They'd say, well, they won't.
Well, they definitely won't give him $300 million again.
But then you remember baby.
Wait, you cut out.
It's two steps.
He's already making part two.
He's already got his next project lined up.
He's going to make another shitty one.
That's going to get a 14%.
Zack Snyder hasn't made a good fucking movie since dawn of the dead.
Well, I really liked his justice league movie when he got to do his director's cut.
The black and white one, not the Joss Whedon one that got released.
I like the black and white.
Whatever.
I thought that was really good, but that was also a project of extreme indulgence.
And, you know, but if you want to just go, if you want to just go.
On.
Well, you can't because there's movies that he did that have been higher.
Look, Justice League was good because I knew the mythology of what was going on.
And I wanted to see it played out in that movie.
Had I not known any of that, it does not stand alone extraordinarily well, in my opinion.
I liked Batman versus Superman.
People hated it.
It's critically panned.
The recut of Justice League was obviously terrible.
Army of the Dead was fucking awful.
Awful.
Can't believe I saw that.
Just for the show, I saw that otherwise.
Army of Thieves.
Yeah, I didn't even watch Army of Thieves because it's like, well, it's like Army of the Dead,
except without the, it's a prequel, so there's no zombies.
I'm like, what?
Yeah, just hanging out with the characters.
The great, great characters that Zack Snyder always brings to the table.
Man of Steel.
You know, I guess, I guess a sort of passable Superman movie, but not good.
I fucking hate Watchmen.
300 was a one and done.
Yeah.
You know, does anybody on planet Earth ever want to rewatch 300?
The guys who I knew back then who were obsessed with 300, I was like, just say you're gay.
Like, you're obsessively watching the best looking men with the best bodies wrestle in oil,
and you're watching it over and over and over and saying it makes you manlier.
I'd argue quite the opposite.
More power to you and your choices, but come on.
Let's be real.
I didn't see 300 part two, 600 or whatever it was, Rise of the People.
300 part, 300 Rise of an Empire with a terrible title.
That got critically panned.
I did not see it.
I didn't have zero.
That was like why I didn't see Sin City 2.
I was like, guys, we did it once.
Like, we're good.
Yeah.
What else did he do here?
He did Sin City 2 sucked.
Sin City 1, I owe that a rewatch.
I fucking loved that when I first saw it.
I was like, this is great.
Grav Regas has got a weird quality control.
He's all over the map.
I think Sin City's a lot like 300.
It's a great one -time watch.
Maybe you revisit it on an edible or something.
But I never had a desire to re -see it, but I enjoyed it the first time.
He also did this Legend of the Guardians, which was a kid's thing.
I didn't see that.
Me neither.
I missed one, though.
There was one in here.
Oh, Sucker Punch.
Sucker Punch is one of the worst movies I've ever seen in my entire life.
Now, it is terrible.
Here's my question.
Sucker Punch comes out on the heels.
Was it after Dawn of the Dead?
Oh, yeah.
Quite a few years.
No, but I mean, was it what he made?
Hold on.
I want to see the order of things.
I'm looking at these on Rotten Tomatoes.
Where's filmography?
Films?
Okay.
Sucker Punch.
He makes that on the heels of Legends of the Guardians.
Wait, is it Guardians of Ga 'Hool?
The Owl movie?
Oh, I didn't know he made that.
He did.
Now, that made money.
That title used to make me laugh so hard.
The Owls of Ga 'Hool.
I love it.
Terrible.
Now, here's what's astounding to me.
Watchmen.
He puts out Watchmen.
Yeah.
It does $187 million at the box office on a $150 million budget.
That is not, in the studio's eyes, that is a massive bomb.
Yes.
He then does Guardians of Ga 'Hool.
That does $140 million on an $80 million budget.
But it's an animated whatever, but it does well financially.
Then he does Sucker Punch.
Sucker Punch makes $89 million on an $82 million budget.
And on top of it gets a 22 % overall rating from critics.
That ends careers.
Yeah.
How the fuck does he get then shuffled in two years later to do Man of Steel?
Man of Steel is poorly received.
They get it in their head.
If you have made a movie at that scale, if you have made a $300 million movie and it was released,
I think they put you on a list of maybe six guys that have done it.
But they're not taking into consideration whether the movies were well received critically or commercially.
It's just like he's done it and he didn't kill anyone, so now he's on a list and can keep doing it.
That's the only explanation I have for Zack Snyder.
What's it called?
Now Man of Steel makes almost $700 million, which is a success.
But here's what kills me, what you just said.
Well, OK, so he's back, right?
In their eyes, he did it.
He's back.
Guys, you could have had a fucking wet dog direct Man of Steel.
It would have made $700 million.
People are walking, $700 million is walking through the door just for the S and the cape.
You make a good Superman movie, it's going to break a billion.
Yeah.
I just don't understand the logic.
There are these people.
I don't know.
It's something sinister.
What is the blood oath that has been made between Zack Snyder and this industry that he just gets to keep working?
And meanwhile, a guy like Coppola has run out of the fucking business.
It doesn't make any sense.
I think it's because Coppola's goals are different.
Zack Snyder's, I don't think he's setting out to make bad movies, but I don't think he's setting out to make art.
Like Coppola, a lot of the times, forget not having Superman or IP or something.
Like this movie he's got coming out.
I just don't see that turning a profit.
Let's be real.
It's all about, you know, in the 70s, and they've lost their hat on that many times.
Look at Michael Chimbano and Heaven's Gate.
They would give these huge budgets to the best directors.
They would say like Stanley Kubrick, whatever you need to make your next masterpiece.
Nowadays, you know, Christopher Nolan is not anywhere near the filmmaker Kubrick is.
They'll do it for him.
But Christopher Nolan is making movies that outside of Oppenheimer maybe scream box office hit.
He makes movies in proven genres.
Look at the Dark Knight trilogy.
Kubrick was making weird up his ass artsy shit, and Hollywood was like, here, what do you need?
They don't do that anymore.
Scorsese maybe, but he's got to have a DiCaprio in his pocket.
They're not going to fund, you know, some no name little thing he's got going on.
No, but I mean, Christ, but Scorsese is getting, Scorsese is getting a hundred, two hundred million to make these movies.
I mean, it's budgets are outrageous, man.
It's just like the Irishman, which I love.
It played in the theater for three days.
Yeah, it's a weird time.
This Zack Snyder movie, whatever the hell it is, is, I guess, not going to play in theaters.
This is the kind of movie that is made for the theaters, regardless of what you think of it, which everyone seems to hate it.
But why are we releasing this giant Star Wars level space opera millions and millions and millions of dollars to Netflix where half the people are going to be watching on their phone?
I don't understand.
And I'm not Mr. Purist trying to be Scorsese like, oh, a film's got to be seen on the big screen with no intermissions either.
I can be that guy, but I'm not being practical.
I'm just saying from a business standpoint, why are you not putting it in theaters?
Then release it on Netflix a week later.
It's like we've proven what models will work, but still every streamer, every release, they just decide at random whether it's going to be theatrical, whether it'll be all 10 episodes in a dump or whether it'll be weekly.
They just decide on a whim.
There's no, you never know what's happening anymore.
Anyway, let's take us to that movie corn.
I saw a picture called Please Don't Destroy colon, the treasure of Foggy Mountain.
This is the new film from the three guys named Please Don't Destroy that do the weekly digital shorts on SNL.
They've gotten some flack for being nepo babies.
Their fathers are mostly big time comedy writers and the SNL or Conan worlds.
But I don't tend to care about nepo stuff as long as they bring the goods.
And these kids, you know, they're no lonely island.
They're not at that level.
They're just kind of like a lot of sketch comedy that was happening in the early 2000s that like adam .com.
Funny or die, crackle, cracked, whatever, all that stuff.
They have a sketch.
They're usually sort of clever.
They put a little smirk on your face and they have access to the biggest stars in the world to act in their sketches because they get whoever hosts SNL to be in them.
So naturally they seem like a bigger deal than they are.
I sort of looked at them as like, well, see, they're too young for me to really hate them and they are they know their way around a joke.
Let's see where it goes.
So I was working on something with Apatow Productions and I got called in to give like notes on the original cut of this, which was over two hours.
And it is like a Goonies parody.
It's three kids looking for lost treasure.
It's like DuckTales, Treasure of the Lost Lamp or whatever.
So imagine a movie like Hot Rod or Pop Star or something stretched to like two hours and ten minutes.
It was pretty rough, but you could see where there was a funny comedy.
Weirdly, they did not make the cuts I suggested.
Not that they had to listen to me, but like I felt they cut some of the funnier stuff, frankly, when I saw the new version.
But it's a pretty in this day and age.
It's a very solid comedy.
There are some good laughs, some big laughs in it.
Meg Stalter steals the show.
The girl from Hacks and online.
She's very funny in it.
Three guys are funny.
Conan O 'Brien has never acted in a movie before, to my knowledge.
And he's the best part of the movie.
He plays the father of the redhead kid.
And he plays him as kind of like an emotionally distant borderline abusive father with a beard who owns the sporting goods shop that they all work at.
Conan is the reason to see it along with Meg Stalter.
Conan is very, very funny.
I miss seeing him every night.
It's just great to have him in something.
I hope he acts more.
Meg Stalter is funny.
I saw a stand up thing she did.
It was one of the worst things I've ever seen in my fucking life.
I have not seen her stand up.
I like her on Hacks a lot.
I think she's a very funny performer.
All right.
And she's funny in this movie.
Something they did cut down is near the end.
It's one of those like, oh, it's like we're going on a journey like, you know, Harold and Kumar or something like that.
And they bump into all sorts of weird stuff.
The third act of this, they find this like rave in the woods.
Bowen Yang is the leader of this cult rave in the woods.
That was like a half hour section in the cut I saw.
And that is widely cut down.
I think Bowen Yang is very funny.
I just don't think he'll ever be a movie lead.
He's got to be like a pop in, give you a quick hit and go.
And he's great in it.
There's enough to recommend.
There's some funny stuff.
There's some stuff that just doesn't work, but I'll keep watching these guys.
You know, I don't know that this movie made a lot of money, but it was very low budget.
And this is what comedy used to be, should be, could be.
Again, give three guys who are young and funny and have a vision a little money and have them make something.
I hope we get more of it.
It was a decently funny, like old stupid style comedy that we don't get much of anymore.
OK.
Go ahead.
What do you got, Joe?
Oh, you got nothing?
You know, I had one, but I'm going to save it because I have another sort of news cycle I forgot about that I wanted to say.
But go ahead, do your three and then I'll bring this thing up.
Fair enough.
Yeah.
I saw Old Joy, which I have always kind of wanted to see.
Kelly Reichardt to me is a very, very overrated filmmaker.
I liked showing up that she did with Michelle Williams this past year, but I like a slow movie.
I like a small movie.
I like like a Manchester by the Sea.
That's that's I love that.
That's that's my jam.
But she this woman, Kelly Reichardt, goes so slow and so little story that I struggle with a lot of her work.
And I've seen several of her movies at this point.
First Cowl was a big acclaimed one from a couple of years ago.
It's a tough sit.
It's boring.
This one Old Joy is probably my favorite of hers that I have seen.
And I owe that to it being 73 minutes long.
If you're going to make a movie about like the tiny minutia of everyday life, I think 73 minutes is a good running time for that sort of project.
This is a movie about two guys in their I'd say maybe early 40s, one of them being Will Oldham, who is Bonnie Prince Billy.
If you know his music, he makes like really dark folk music and they play two old friends who haven't seen each other in a long time.
One is now a family man who's like got his shit together.
And the other Will Oldham is kind of lost in his life.
He's got nothing.
He's a Pat Walsh or Jodorosa type.
You know, there's just nothing going on for him.
And the two of them, the two of them go on a trip, a little like camping trip.
And it was great.
You know, they both kind of realized the ways in which they envy each other, the ways in which they don't envy each other.
You know, just a really small story about what happens to you when you hit 40.
You just start looking at life very differently, looking at your mortality, looking at where you have fucked up, looking at how much time you have left to do the things that you want to do.
And that's what the movie is about.
Very small.
And then the sort of most interesting aspect of it, and I had to hit the Wikipedia page.
Some reviews don't even mention it, but I thought it was kind of the most interesting part of the movie.
The Will Oldham character keeps like, they're getting into like a mud bath situation or like a jacuzzi, but he keeps getting naked in front of his friend and like lingering in a way that I do not think could be anything but intentional.
And it seems to me like he's sort of, and he's not a great looking guy, but seems like he's trying to seduce his friend who is married with kids the whole movie.
And it adds this layer of unease and weirdness to everything, but it's not commented on.
An interesting movie.
It was the first one that made me really get why everybody jizzes over this, Kelly Reichardt.
And yeah, I think short is the way to go when you're going for a movie like that.
Third, I ain't seen much either, Joe.
I watched Night on Earth, which I've always wanted to see, the Jim Jarmusch movie.
I'm prepared to say Jarmusch is overrated as well with everything I see of his.
Night on Earth is early 90s indie.
It takes place in five different cities across the world.
It's like taxicab confessions, but not as good.
Big stars Winona Ryder and Jenna Rollins are in the best of the segments.
Rosie Perez, Roberto Benigni.
I guess not big stars.
That's about it.
But it's five short stories of people around the world and they're not super connected.
Jarmusch's big thing is no plot like he does.
He doesn't even give you the bare bones of a plot.
It's all vibes.
And I don't know.
I never really got into him.
I kind of like Ghost Dog and Dead Man and a couple of his movies, but I don't know if I would watching them now.
I think he's very overrated.
For me, Jarmusch or Jarmusch, however the hell you say it, I respect him greatly.
But I've said this about a lot of the criterion stuff.
It's like A for effort cinema.
Sure.
This guy went out there and did it.
See?
And they're like, OK, but I'm really bored.
And inspired all kinds of people.
That early indie movement with Kevin Smith and everybody.
Like if you ever read Spike Mike's Lackers and Dykes, which is an excellent book about the early days of the indie movement.
And unfortunately, a lot of Harvey Weinstein in there, too.
But they all really looked up to Jarmusch, you know, but especially his recent stuff, I just think is absolute shit.
Speaking of criterion, by the way, this is what I was going to bring up.
I just fucking I just I just bought The Devil and Daniel Webster.
Yeah. How did I buy it?
On DVD, because that's the only way they have fucking offered it for years.
And I sat there and sat there and sat there and sat there and didn't buy it and didn't buy it and didn't buy it because they might release it on Blu Ray.
They just might let me wait.
Let me wait. Let me wait.
After years, literally years of watching this thing on their website, never get the Blu Ray upgrade.
I go fuck it.
I'm buying the DVD.
I buy it.
I receive it last month.
Today, I get an email.
I know where this is going.
The Blu Ray is about to come out.
You know, it just pisses me off.
This is we can't live like this.
We can't.
I can't in good conscience upgrade now to the Blu Ray of this.
I can't do it.
We have to learn how to accept.
Sometimes something's just on Blu Ray.
Sometimes something's just on DVD.
Sometimes you don't need the 4K.
True.
This is just going to keep happening over and over and over again.
It's madness.
I've been doing it my whole life.
I used to go to Best Buy every Tuesday because that was the day they released new movies and records.
Now there's not even a day anymore.
We don't even get that.
They just appear.
Yeah, I am going to, by the way, I am finally pulling the trigger and purchasing the region free Blu Ray DVD player.
You have to find a place that sells them where they are unlocked by a third party.
There's a place in New York.
Is that legal?
No idea.
Don't give a shit.
Yeah, there's a place.
It's got to be like B &H in New York has them and it's advertised on their website.
So clearly it's not illegal.
But what's fucked up is you can't get a region free Blu Ray player in the United States
unless you're going to a place that says, no, this has been serviced in order to do this.
Because the scumbag capitalist pieces of shit that run every inch of our fucking system of commerce in this country
and the sales market and everything, don't allow it.
When I went to Best Buy and I said, you have a region free advertising, they go, yeah, it says that.
It's not.
If you look on the box, it's region A only.
He goes, we have contracts with the studios in order to not allow that.
Like, what the fuck with this shit, man?
It's never enough for these pigs.
It's never enough.
They got to squeeze every dime out of you.
So anyway, I'm getting a region free.
And why am I getting a region free?
So I can sweetly go to that UK arrow sale, for instance, and buy any fucking thing I want.
Yes.
On sale at amazing prices and watch it.
Because I'm giving money to the movie studio one way or the other.
I'm not illegally downloading stuff.
Can I capitalize on a sale?
Jesus Christ, man.
It drives me crazy.
I just have learned to wait for the American version.
For Criterion now, they usually announce like, here are going to be our April releases right now.
And if it's something I have in Blu -ray and it's going to 4K, I hop right on Amazon, sell it for 20.
I bought it for 20.
And then I'm ready for the 4K.
But you might have trouble selling a DVD at the stage of the game.
I don't have the energy to start selling on Amazon and all that shit.
I sell so much that it just is part of my morning routine.
I hear you.
It can be a hassle.
I like it because it focuses my brain early in the morning.
Just something mindless.
All right.
Well, we're onto the movie.
Are we not?
Unless you want to do one more.
Yeah, we can go to the movie.
I did three.
Oh, OK.
What the fuck more do you want?
All right.
I am very excited that Aliens, True Lies and The Abyss are coming to 4K.
Very excited.
I'll tell you that much.
Those are my next three purchases.
If you told me those movies were erased from existence, I wouldn't bat an eye.
Fair enough.
But it makes you happy and that makes me happy.
Thank you, Joe.
Folks, we are talking today about Rare Exports, colon, A Christmas Tale.
A movie that I have been mixing up for a decade with another movie called Joyous Noel or something.
It was something that Joe Bob Briggs did on Shudder.
So I thought I had seen this.
This is where Letterboxd comes in handy.
I had not seen this movie.
The other one, people say Home Alone ripped off.
It's some weird French movie that has nothing to do with Home Alone.
But I guess in theory, but not really.
This movie is actually a very complex or complicated backstory, which I was not expecting.
I didn't know anything about it.
But it basically, you know, creates kind of its own science fiction world as it relates to Santa Claus and is a slow burn.
You know, it's about it's about a 90 minute movie.
But for me, nothing really took off till the end.
Joe, walk us through the kind of interesting plot of this movie.
And where is it from?
What country?
Finland.
Finland, yes.
Well, right away, it's confusing because it starts off with English speaking characters and then switches over to a strictly Finnish.
Always throws me.
And then the guys finished talking Finnish before we go to English.
That's good.
That's very good.
But then but then the Finnish people keep talking about the English speaking characters who have who all have English accents.
Yes.
As being Russians.
So that was confusing.
But whatever.
It's about a Russian dig in Finland.
They're excavating something from a mountain that is very mysterious and very precious.
There is a very rich man who's funding the dig.
You don't know what it is.
A lot of the thing vibes.
Yeah, a little bit of that, right?
No.
Yeah, I felt thing vibes.
Then you meet the main character, which is a young boy and his father.
His father is making a dead fall in their in their yard of their farm or ranch, whatever you want to call it, to trap wolves that are killing the reindeer that they that they harvest and take the pelts and sell.
And that's how they make their living.
The low and behold, the dead fall traps, not a wolf, but a man.
And the young boy is also, while this is all transpiring, looking up mythology of Santa Claus.
And learns that Santa Claus is not the benevolent, child loving, gift giving, mystical person that we've all been taught.
It's actually this evil entity that, I guess, like feeds on bad children and like, you know, something.
It's sort of similar to the Krampus legend, but not.
It's what we find in the trap is like this elderly naked frail man.
Well, that's not Santa.
Right.
Yeah.
The the the trap.
The the the legend is.
Yeah, sorry.
It's a little convoluted, but the old frail man they find in the trap turns out to be one of Santa's elves.
And you find out that Santa's elves are all old men with white hair and beards.
And which was interesting because I was like, oh, that's cool.
They're saying like the elves actually look like this.
And because mythology gets distorted in and and transforms over time and everything, we've come to believe that Santa Claus looks like that.
You know, over the years of passing mythology down, the Santa Claus has adopted the look of the actual elves.
Santa Claus, you see later, has horns and whatever and is actually like looks like Krampus.
Anyway, the plot is, is that these elves are snatching up all the naughty boys and girls in the village.
This kid figures out what's going on and needs to stop it.
They eventually end up in a situation where they find the block of ice that was excavated.
It is a frozen block of ice containing Santa Claus, which you never get to see him actually in their reality.
You'll only see pictures and stuff, but it's a giant Krampus like beast that's encased in a block of ice.
And the elves are thawing him out.
And if they do thaw him out, he's going to murder all the children or something.
Again, it's a little vague.
You just kind of know it's not good, like it's not going to be a good thing if this happens.
So the kid devises a plan with his dad and his dad's friends.
Which, by the way, is all I need. Mission Impossible or whatever. That's all I need.
Tell me the world's in danger and move on with it.
Yeah, I agree. So the kid and the dad and the friends devise this plan to blow up Santa Claus and kill him,
while also leading the elves into the pen where they trap all the reindeer and trapping them there.
And then the movie ends with them all retraining the elves to love children, putting them in Santa suits.
So now the elves actually are Santa Claus and then exporting Santa Clauses to each country in the world,
of course, for a high price tag so they can save their ailing village.
It's a good ending, and I thought it lends itself to a sequel with that ending,
and maybe it wasn't successful enough, but I think a cool sequel could be made to it.
I don't think, I didn't, well, I didn't interpret it that way.
I didn't think that there was this, I thought it was very much supposed to be a very happy ending, and that was kind of it.
Yeah, but one of them snaps. That's all you need.
So yeah, so it's a weirdly cute movie at times.
It's well -made. The guy that made it is the guy that just did Sisu or whatever that movie's called,
and he also made that movie Big Game with Sam Jackson.
His movies are always well -received.
Rare Exports, the favorite movie of Cate Blanchett, I learned from the Wikipedia page.
Favorite movie?
That's right. That's odd.
That weirdly, because I like Cate Blanchett, and weirdly that influenced my opinion.
I was watching it like the whole movie, the whole time I was going, how could this be someone's favorite movie?
It came out in 2010. I thought it was older. It looked really good. I thought it was going to be cheaper.
It definitely looked like a big Hollywood blockbuster. It was shot really well. It was in great locations.
I thought the lair or whatever where Santa is under rice looked really great.
But yeah, something about it just wasn't involving to me.
It felt like a movie directed by a guy, I don't know if he did, but it felt like a movie directed by a guy who came from TV commercials.
The movie has a TV commercial feel. I got no emotional value out of it. I wasn't in suspense or anything.
However, it's short and like you said, it's cute and the story is good.
It almost felt like a kid's book adapted into a movie.
It felt like a book that my mom would have read to me when I was little at Christmas time.
And I might have thought it was kind of neat, but on the whole, I can't say I thought too much of the movie.
What do you think, Joe?
Same thing. I thought it was well put together. I thought it was a really interesting plot, especially since it was a precursor to Krampus and any of that stuff.
I remember when I saw the trailers for it when it first came out, I was very intrigued and excited about it because I was like, oh, an evil Santa. That's cool.
But not one who's like a murderer in a Santa suit, just like a real Santa who's evil. That's really cool.
But then in watching it, I've seen it twice. This was the second time. I don't know. Nothing really happens. It's just kind of boring.
And then everything happens within like 11 minutes.
Couldn't agree more.
It's so like sluggish and what you're looking at looks good and like the kids cute and it's just the story is not compelling enough.
The comedy, if it's even there, is certainly not funny enough.
The effects and everything are great. And like like Joe said, the mythology, the world building, the story is all good.
There's just not enough of that rooting for these people that you need to kind of take you from A to B.
But I enjoyed it. I say with like the faintest of praise.
Yeah, it was it was it was I think it was passable. I'm certainly not offended by anything in it.
I'm not mad about any of it. It was an enjoyable enough watch. I certainly would not purchase it.
It's not something I would want to re -watch a third time.
Did you see Sisu?
No, I still really want to see it.
I didn't say it.
I still really want to see it.
He seems like I never saw Big Game either, but he seems like he gets more wild as he goes.
Like he goes, he gets bigger and crazier.
So that's that's interesting to me.
So I would like to potentially I would like to see Sisu.
But this movie was I don't know. It was I guess hog straight out.
It's just fine. It's like a fine movie.
There's nothing exciting about it.
Yeah, I mean, I'm going to say I'm going to say limp.
But on a good day, you know, there's no there's no sort of lumping or blood happening, but it's hanging there low and proud.
And that brings us to the end of our discussion.
Really, we I think we've kind of hit so many of the classic Christmas movies and they're not making more.
That now we're going into the corners and not finding not finding treats this week in our stocking for either.
Yeah, I think next year it might be worth a deep dive into like some esoteric older offbeat Christmas movies from the 60s or 70s.
I'm sure they're out there.
I'm sure there's Christmas horror movies from the 70s that we have not seen yet and whatever.
But yeah, as far as things that people may or may not have heard of or have access to immediately, like it's it is getting a little tougher because, you know, we can't we can't do an episode on Christmas vacation.
It's we've talked about it, you know, like it's right, you know.
So we'll see what happens entirely convinced we haven't done an episode on Christmas vacation, but we might have.
Yeah, I don't know.
But I want to say a very, very, very sincere.
Happy holidays to everybody that is part of the we'll see you in hell family.
We appreciate you all greatly.
Thank you all.
All all all for being a part of this journey with us and continuing to care enough to make Pat and I put out a show and to allow us to enjoy putting out a show for people that.
That that do enjoy it.
It means a lot to us.
We appreciate what it all means to you.
And I hope you have a wonderful, wonderful holiday season.
And that extends to you too, Pat.
And to you, Joe couldn't have said it better myself.
Happy holidays to you all.
And we will see you next year.
Which will be a better year.
And we will also see you in hell.
Happy holidays.