I'll see you.
Oh, I'll see you.
Folks, we'll see you in hell.
Joe DeRosa and Patrick Walsh, back at it again, here to talk about a movie called Uninvited.
You're uninvited, and there's more stuff.
Oh, you know, I knew that by the impression.
Yeah, it was a big hit, even though it's not a very good song.
Didn't know the song.
Don't know the song, but you did a good enough impression that I got it.
Thank you. I appreciate that.
You're welcome a lot.
What's popping Joe?
Nothing, I got a, I got a head over to the bar today.
We're having a guest, we're having even fight ants, very funny comic and a good friend.
He's guest bartending.
Sure over at Joey Roses.
So I got a head over there and make sure that goes off without any problem.
Yeah, and I also need to try not to drink at it, which is going to be hard.
Any particular reason are you taking some time off as well?
You know, I was saying last step that I need to do a little dry out,
because the stress of everything had me going a little too hard.
The rage.
Yeah, to just, you know, it's, but, but I'm at a point of.
I don't know.
I'm in that zone now where I didn't drink all week and I feel like way clearer and healthier.
And I'm like, oh, this is good.
And, but, you know, I took the month off.
I took the month off of drinking drugs.
Weed and thought phenomenal in every way.
Everything was better.
And then I went to the Palm Springs trip in the desert with my friends from high school.
And everybody was drunk 24 7 and I was like, yeah, whatever.
I'll drink.
And I was back in Missouri for a little while and drank.
And then I came back and went right back to sobriety.
I think I've actually sort of turned a corner.
Okay.
What would that corner be?
The only drink sometimes.
Yeah, turn a corner where I'm not drinking.
And then I, but the thing is, you keep walking and then you come to that next corner.
Every building's got four corners.
Then you just turn right back to drinking.
But I don't mind like a month on month on scenario.
It works for me.
I don't mind it either.
I just as a, as a single man, it, it's just, it's tough.
Cause you're in a lot of scenario dating is dating impossible.
And you're in a lot of scenarios where you're just like, you know, like tonight, you know, fairly busy day today.
Last weekend of summer, really.
I mean, I know that was technically last weekend.
But, you know, I'm just like, God, damn it, man.
Like, you know, let's cut loose.
Let's have fun.
But, you know, that's the problem.
As I always cut loose and have fun, then you're going Christ and cut loose and having too much fun.
That's right.
What really sort of helped put me back off the, the hooch was on this trip.
We're there in the hot tub every night.
It's like 120 degrees in the desert.
And we're all sitting in the hot tub drinking every night, talking, laughing.
Like the last night, I was not drinking a whole lot and kind of looked around.
And I was noticing all the children in the hot tub.
Some in like diapers.
And I was like, this is probably not good.
Sure enough, two weeks later, I developed a bacterial infection.
And I was like, I bet it was from that fucking disgusting hot tub.
And I asked the group of friends via text and like somebody else had the exact same diagnosis of bacterial infection that I had.
So I was like, yep, that's definitely what went on.
So basically I woke myself up scratching an incredibly itchy mark on my arm.
And when I scratched it, it was when it was at its most contagious.
Okay.
So basically my entire left side was a rash.
It's finally cleared up, but it was horrible.
And I was like, I bet if I hadn't had 13 beers that night, I would never have set foot in that jacuzzi.
I've got a giant zit on my cheek that I tried to pop.
And it went sideways.
And now you can see it looks like I just have a wound on my cheek.
It's not, I wouldn't have noticed, but I do see now that you mentioned it a hard sort of lump on your face.
I showed up to be my friend Nina last night.
And she's like, your face is bleeding.
Now it's a zit I tried to pop and popped it too hard.
Got good to me.
Popped too hard.
I don't get them anymore.
I really, it's almost never.
So I feel glad about that.
I think I got it as a result of, well, a couple of things.
I was on a trip and I forgot my face wash.
I was washing my face with, you know, whatever soap was available in the hotel or whatever.
And that's the first coat.
Yeah. And then, uh, and then also the stress, obviously, just the stress of everything right now.
I'm like, yeah, probably made me, I popped, I had three pimples on my face.
I was like, I think that's stress related.
You know, yeah.
So once this damn house is paid is done.
You'll have the skin of a.
Uh -huh.
No, I was just interrupting.
But yeah, you know, you'll have the skin of a 18 year old woman again or something.
I don't know.
I don't know what's considered a baby has good skin.
Yeah.
Uh -uh.
No, I, I think God was like, this kid had enough acne growing up.
Let's just give him the rest of his life off.
And I appreciate it.
Real problems.
Really.
I've always had like this where you get like, yeah, where you get like, not, you know, I used to early high school.
Just like I, I eventually became pretty popular homecoming king.
Thank you.
Uh -uh.
But early high school was when I had braces and the acne.
And I used to be so embarrassed of the acne that I would sit with my face in both hands
like home alone style and act like I was resting my head in my hands.
But actually, I was covering my face.
But then of course, I'm putting my oily hands on my face, which would just increase the problem.
Sure.
So I eventually started taking acutane, which is supposed to cause, uh, suicidal thoughts.
And each pill had a pregnant woman with a line through her belly on it.
So I was like, this feels a little too intense for me at age 14.
It did clear up my acne, but I was also peeling off like face -sized sheets of skin every morning.
You know, it, it dries you up.
I, uh, I took acutane in my 30s.
I had hit, uh, uh, what I would call a rock bottom in the business.
Sure.
I was, you know, all these promising things that you know, then how much further you had to fall.
All right.
Well, you know, I'm not taking shots at your fucking pimple face childhood heartache.
You know, those days are gone.
That child is dead.
No, I, I, yeah, I just, um, uh, I, I hit this terrible, you know, the, the, the, the, it was that zone you get in sometimes in the business like around the 10 year mark, where you're like all the promise and excitement.
And the wild ride of the first 10 years, where it was all going to happen.
That, that sort of has settled.
And now you're going to go through a really hard patch.
And I was there.
And I was so stressed out.
I had a joke at the time, where I said, I'm 32 years old.
I was, oh, that was a 13 years old.
Uh, and I had to, I had to get proactive, uh, the face -to -face.
And I go, that's, and that's not the saddest part.
The saddest part is my dad had to pay for it, which was true.
I was so broken in my dad to buy me proactive.
And, um, it was, but I was so stressed out that I, I started breaking out and full on adult acne.
Like, notice it.
Like, to the point where a guy stopped me in a store once and said, hey, man, let me tell you what I did for that.
Because he knew the struggle.
But that's how bad it was.
I started, I was wearing, at one point I was wearing makeup.
I was wearing foundation or whatever that's called to cover it up.
I didn't hide school too.
I did that school too.
It was brutal.
Yeah.
Also terrible for your acne.
Putting makeup on it.
Well, yeah.
It's not the help.
And eventually just went away, maybe because of the acutane.
Probably.
Whenever the fuck it started.
Acutane?
Yeah.
Acutane, yeah.
Um, I'm glad those days are behind us and there's no more stress in our lives, Joe.
Well, that's what I was going to say earlier was all I got to do is get this whole house deal settled.
And then I can get on to worrying about the mortgage itself.
Yeah.
To give you a little personal, a personal take on this strike, which is now well over 100 days.
And even though everyone hates me when I say this, it is not going to be resolved in 2023.
We are definitely going to be on strike until next year.
Um, um, but I have written for Miss Pat for three seasons now.
And I have not received a residual check.
And my parents were like, hey, it's, it's, it's airing on BET.
They had a marathon of it last night.
I got to watch a lot of episodes really funny, blah, blah.
And we air all the time.
We air on VH1 all the time.
We air on BET all the time.
They're simply not paying residuals via comp paramount.
So I called the writer's guild and reported it.
And they said to other people have already reported this issue from, and I said from Viacom.
They said, no, from Miss Pat.
They were like, forget Viacom Viacom has been sued by the writer's guild repeatedly.
So the writer's guild was like, you're our third complaint from this show.
And all we can tell you is you will eventually get paid with interest.
But it's going to take a long time.
These places don't like to give it up.
These are just people that owe me money.
You know, if this was, if this was straight out of Compton, and I was ISQ
about walking in with a fucking baseball bat into paramount and be like, where's my fucking money?
Because that's what it is.
It's criminal.
And we are out of work struggling.
People, I know people very well with children who are losing their homes.
And they just will not pay up.
It's, it is madness.
Meanwhile, they're selling Hulu for like $300 billion.
Where's that money go?
Where does that money go?
You have it.
It drives me so crazy.
It's like, you know, other time, I'm not always in 100 %
lockstep with the writer's guild and what they do.
I wouldn't be a human being if I was.
But this is just a case where it's like, it's everyone in America versus these assholes.
And the assholes are like, yeah, we're just going to keep being assholes.
And it's that line of thinking that has just brought America into the gutter.
And it doesn't show any signs of improving.
Well, it's a tough.
This isn't a Republican thing, a Democrat thing.
It's just, it's just a bad time.
Yeah, it's a horrible time.
It's just destroyed this world.
It's a horrible time.
But, you know, I, you know, I take obviously I take empathy with the,
with the members of SAG and the members of the writers guild on the member of both.
But, you know, I've said it ad nauseam on this podcast and elsewhere to anybody that'll listen.
You're, you know, the Hollywood is the drug game.
You are in mafia business.
Yeah.
You know, they, they will keep doing this.
They've done it repeatedly.
They will not stop.
Everybody needs to break away and start to utilize these wonderful platforms that are out there for all of us to do our own thing.
I know it's not easy.
It's hard.
It's stressful.
It's terrifying.
And it's not what anybody really initially signed on for.
The people I'm scratching my head the most about are these people that are six months into writing.
I'd be like, fuck this guys.
I'm going to YouTube.
Take care.
I get it with a guy like you where it's like, no, I made a career out of this.
And now it's going.
Yeah.
Very sideways.
So.
But it's not going to change.
And people need to start making some real hard decisions in their lives.
You know, and again, I've said this before.
And I've got friends.
I've got friends in all these places.
But before you want to start casting stones and aspersions at somebody, for example, like myself to speak selfishly because they dared.
Be seen in public with a Fox News host or employee.
Maybe you need to start turning that that venom on some of the people working at these studios and not acting like it's all good.
That's a thousand percent.
So be consistent or don't be.
And you know, it's a shit show.
But this is where we're at.
This is that we've allowed it to happen.
We've allowed this to become this corporatized because.
And I'm guilty of it too.
We're all guilty of it.
But we all go, well, I'll take a shot at myself.
How long have I sat here and bitched up and down about Netflix?
I still watch fucking Netflix.
Now I watch it on my parents subscription because I don't pay for it.
Yeah.
But I still watch it.
I shouldn't be.
I shouldn't be doing it.
But God forbid I miss the Irishman or or the next score says you know whatever the fucking is that I need to see on there.
You know, like.
Yeah.
I pull all the plugs.
I mean, but what I what I feel is when I.
I can't be out there protesting these places and paying them money.
So I did pull the plug on everything except shutter because shutter is just barely hanging on.
And my thinking is, you know, if this killers of the flower moon or something, it's being released theatrically, which is where I'll see it.
But if it was only coming to Apple TV, you know, I would either wait for the screeners or more likely I would pay the five bucks for Apple TV for a month.
You know, I think their whole business model is reliant on you paying for these services for months and months and months and maybe never even opening them.
I think you should use it as an all a cart system, you know, like.
Just like if something comes on that you want, get it for a month or if it's cheaper to buy that one item on Amazon, do that.
But like I wanted to watch the Arnold documentary on Netflix and then I was like, no, I'll wait till I'm in an Airbnb and got time to kill and I'll do it on their dime.
Like I can wait to watch that, you know, that's where I'm at.
No, I hear you.
Not that I'm any better than you.
I mean, I know the arts is all I care about.
It's all that brings me joy.
So I can't say no to it, but what I am doing more way more is turning to my vast collection of movies because it's another thing, Joe.
And I'm sure you're on the same boat as me.
I'm 42, you're a little bit older, you're like, all right.
With my family history, I probably dropped at 75 being generous.
When am I going to watch all these movies that I own?
When am I going to read all these books that I own?
When am I going to listen to these vinyl records that I buy and put wrapped into my collection and forget that I have?
So what I am doing is like, I set 10 albums.
If I'm going to have a writing day, I set 10 albums that I haven't listened to next to my record player and I make sure I'm catching up with them.
By the way, it's a great way to free up shit too.
I don't like this so much.
I'll sell it.
But I got too many movies I haven't watched to be, you know, watching 12 hours of F boy Island or something like that.
Yeah, no, I agree.
I agree.
I'm teetering, you know, one of the reasons I'm excited about getting a house is so I can finally have the collection I want versus the collection I have to have, which is very truncated by my space in New York.
Yeah.
And but at the same time, I do that too.
I have to get back into a zone of going through the stuff I already own versus always going to the, you know,
the new thing that I want to get to or whatever it is.
It's, it's tough though.
It's tough.
You know, that's the plight of collecting, but, but I agree with you.
I do the Alacarque thing too.
I dip in and I dip out.
So I dipped into Disney plus.
Because I wanted to see Asoka, you know, as a lifelong Star Wars fan.
I wanted to see it.
I've been waiting for it for a long time.
Yeah.
And then when it's over, I'll dip out again.
What's the premise?
I've been saying Ashoka.
What is the premise of it?
Well, there's a lot of backstory.
But the simplest explanation is Ashoka.
Ashoka was, they set all this up in the Clone Wars cartoon, the Rebels cartoon.
She was a new character introduced in Clone Wars.
But Ashoka is, was Anakin Skywalker's apprentice during the Clone Wars?
Who eventually becomes very distant as she grows and evolves becomes very disenchanted with the Jedi order and leaves and renounces being a Jedi, not to become evil.
She just doesn't call herself a Jedi anymore.
And then after the events of both those series, we pick up with this live action version of it where they're bringing a lot of those characters into live action.
And the premise is she basically is being pulled back into becoming a Jedi.
Anakin showed up last week.
It was fun seeing Hayden Christianson back.
Apparently, this new episode coming out episode five, the first three, the first two episodes sucked.
It just were, I don't know what it was.
They're just boring.
Like it was just boring.
The third episode got a little more interesting.
And then the fourth episode was amazing.
And I was like, holy shit.
This is like, oh, you want from Star Wars.
They're doing it.
This fifth episode, the rumor is the cliffhanger of last week's episode was Hayden Christianson reappearing.
There's rumors that this fifth episode is going to be a game changer.
And I was like, well, it's rumors who knows they announced the other day they're going to screen the episode in theaters on Tuesday during the day.
If you want to go to a movie theater to watch it, instead of waiting till 9 p .m. to stream it.
So I'm like, they must be pretty fucking good.
Yeah.
So.
And of course, I have to fucking record on Tuesday, son of a bitch.
I am very excited on Monday to be seeing one of my very favorite movies.
The greatest concert film I ever made stopped making sense in IMAX.
And afterwards, the first ever reunion of talking heads live, they're going to sit down and do a big interview, which I'm beyond pumped about interviewed by Paul Thomas Anderson, no less.
Are they going to play to or they just do it in an interview?
They're not playing.
They see the concert film in the in IMAX.
And then they do like the live stream of them being interviewed.
Oh, that's about right.
And I'm hoping there's some tension between them.
Honestly, I would love to see some fighting.
Did you think that Andor was the masterpiece that everyone did?
I liked Andor a lot.
I thought it was very, very, very well done.
It just wasn't my style of show much more of an espionage high stakes, very dire, very dry, very dark show, which I like those things.
But for Star Wars, it's not what I go to Star Wars for.
So I thought it was cool.
And I couldn't deny its quality, but I'm not as excited about it because it's not this, this Asoka is becoming.
And if it continues to deliver, it feels like George Lucas Star Wars.
It's fun and space and dog fights and the force and all that's kind of shit.
I like that stuff.
Right.
Okay.
Anyway.
Let's get to that corner.
Unless you got some something to say.
I got nothing to say.
Okay.
Well, speaking of which.
Speaking of fun adventure space, whatever.
I'm going to put my foot in my mouth here.
I was on an airplane.
I was on jet blue.
Jet blue has some some airplanes that are so shitty that they only allow.
Your monitor doesn't have the in demand thing in it.
It just has live television.
And at a certain time, you can turn to one of three channels to watch one of three movies on the flight.
Okay.
Jet blue, cut in some corners.
Yeah.
And the three movies were Mafia Mama.
Oh, wow.
Yeah.
A movie.
A movie I hadn't heard of, but it was a very heavy drama.
And I wasn't in the mood for a heavy drama.
And Guardians of the Galaxy three.
I chose Guardians of the Galaxy three.
I thought, sure.
Well, I'll sit here and hate watch this because I hate Marvel.
And it'll be entertaining.
But wait a minute.
You like the first two, right?
I like the first one.
The second one was one of the major issue movies I had with Marvel, where I was like, oh,
come on.
Fuck this.
It's a fucking comedy.
Like this is stupid.
Like, but see, I, for me, that them and James Gunn's suicide squad and so forth, which I know
is DC.
But they, they are funny in a way that is not the Joss Whedon.
Everybody has a quip way.
They, they, they tended to be genuinely funny.
I thought I had, I had a good time with both of those movies and adding Kurt Russell helped to part two.
So suicide squad two had gags in it.
Like when the aliens are trying to blow up their ship, it shows the monitors.
The aliens are using as they're like targeting systems.
And it was, and it's playing Gallagher sound effects.
I'm like, guys, come on.
Can you please, like, everything doesn't have to have a fucking punch line shoved into it.
And then, right, I didn't feel there were any real emotional stakes.
I don't know.
I just didn't like it.
This one, however.
Okay.
I found to have great emotional stakes.
I cared very much about the characters.
The premise is that rocket raccoon is in like this.
They've got a rescue rocket raccoon.
He's in like this coma.
Yeah.
And while he's in this coma, he's having flashbacks of how he was created.
And it's just a heart breaking.
Fucking story of this guy that was doing these genetic mutations on animals.
And it's just so sad and beautifully done.
And then Gamora is resurrected from the dead.
And she doesn't really remember anything about her time with the Guardians.
And she's kind of an asshole again.
And she's much more like Thanos, who's her father.
She's much more in that sort of attitude zone than she was with Guardians.
So there's the whole thing with Chris Pratt's character still being in love with her
and being happy that she's alive, but she wants nothing to do with him.
Got a little deeper into Chris Pratt's, you know, what's he running from sort of storyline.
I really, really enjoyed Dave Batista.
He was really funny.
Yeah, he's growing on me a little bit.
And then there's this.
Good. Sorry.
I'm sorry.
I said he's growing on me.
I got to admit it.
You know, I like him a lot more than like the rock at this point.
Yeah.
And then there's this really beautiful moment where like this girl, the girl with the antennas
who has the ability to like erase your memory.
She says like she talks about how like he's dumb, but he cares.
And like he's got this beautiful moment where he's like, you think I'm dumb?
And it's the first time you see in my memory that you see that character be real.
So it just had these great moments.
And the action was fun.
And it was it was genuinely really funny when it was funny because the funny parts were organically funny.
Like to the characters and not to we're going to do some slapstick fucking naked gun style joke
in the middle of this thing where you're supposed to give a shit.
So I really liked it much to my surprise.
And even more so to my surprise, when I ended, I switched over and saw that Mafia Mama was still going.
It is longer than Guardians of the Galaxy three.
I know for a fact that Guardians of the Galaxy three is 230 because it was too long for me to see one day.
And I didn't ever see it.
Well, so that is madness.
Mafia Mama that movie made no head to have lost $15 million easy 20.
Anyway, oh boy.
Great.
Well, so I'm glad I'm excited not to watch Guardians three because those are some of the only superhero movies that I actually like.
Yeah, let's go here.
That was your first one.
I guess.
Yeah, I'm only going to do two.
Oh, all right, sir.
I saw R.
I watched hustle and flow again.
As I have said, I'm pretty addicted to this 4K.
And I hadn't seen hustle and flow since the theater.
And I was like, fuck it.
It's a limited edition 4K.
I'm going to buy this steel book.
I'll watch it again because it wasn't available to rent.
I don't think.
And, you know, then I'll sell it.
And sure enough, I don't know how I forgot that this movie was so fucking entertaining.
Hustle and flow is great.
Similar to like an 8 mile with M &M, but I think even better.
It is as you know, the very famous song.
It's hard out here for a pimp.
John Stewart once famously joked that three six mafia had won Academy Award.
Martin Scorsese had zero Academy Awards.
And I think that that was when they finally snapped out of it and actually gave him one.
But, um, yeah, it's, it's Terrence Howard, who is such a cool actor.
And I was like, what happened to him?
I did a little research.
He invented his own kind of math.
That's how crazy he went.
Yeah, yeah.
He said, he said, I have proven that one times one equals two.
One times one can't equal one.
And that became his life's focus.
He lost his mind.
He also had a lot of assault charges and things like that that I'm sure did not help.
But forget that.
He is, no, I mean, don't forget that.
If you can forget that, he is such a brilliant actor and he is so good in this movie.
Um, you got Teran Manning as his like number one.
Oh, Teran Manning, who has also lost her mind.
I don't know if you've seen her Instagram videos.
But she was fucking a married man.
And he dumped her.
So she got an Instagram tagged him and his wife and started doing these daily videos.
Where she's like, I want you to know that I'll lecture husband's asshole.
Like he liked that.
And I said, I'll do it.
I loved him that much.
So I was licking his asshole.
He demanded it.
This girl was in eight mile hustle and flow academy award and I've rated movies.
So she's lost her mind too.
I can only imagine what it was like directing these nuts on the set.
Maybe they were more normal back then who knows.
But the movie is completely chaotic in a great way.
It's Craig Brewer, who is one of my favorite working directors.
I did not like his coming to America reboot.
But that's that was one for the studios.
I would say he did hustle and flow black snake moan.
Dolomite is my name, which I love.
I just like what he brings to a movie.
And this one is no exception.
It's shot like a seventies movie on film.
And I think those movies look the best on 4k.
I think they get the best juice out of them from the 4k format.
Other than if you're watching Avatar Planet Earth or something like that.
I fucking loved it.
I recommend going straight to a purchase on it.
It's that classic kind of like rocky story, except it's a pimp who runs into his old friend Anthony Anderson.
And he's like, what are you, what are you been up to man?
And he's like, oh, you know, I record music for, you know, like local church church music, a gospel stuff like that.
And Terence Howard goes checks out one of the recording sessions.
The gospel singer makes him cry.
And he has this like epiphany where he's like, I'm 40 years old.
And I'm a fucking pimp.
I'm wasting my life.
I'm just as talented as anybody else.
I'm going to be a rapper.
And just fucking loved it.
Just pure pure entertainment.
If you never saw it because it is one that kind of slipped through the cracks a little bit.
But what a great fucking movie hustle and flow.
Joe.
I've never seen it.
I got to check it out.
It's great.
I, uh, my second movie.
Also a sequel.
A rewatch in light of the release of the new exorcist.
The believer trailer.
The second trailer was released.
I rewatched exorcist two.
Man, it's bad.
It's real bad.
Uh, now it's not as bad as the Paul Schrader one.
Surprisingly.
Well, I was pleased that the other night and never returned.
Never finished.
And finish it.
And then there's the other version of that called, uh,
exorcist the beginning.
That's the reshoot half reshot, half.
Recut that's directed by who.
Who did that one?
I think Ronnie Harlan, who died two and all.
Yeah.
Both of those are terrible.
Exorcist two is a more interesting watch than either of those.
It's not a better movie, but a more interesting watch.
Uh, an exorcist just.
I mean, it's John Borman, who did deliverance and shit.
So it's like a well -made movie.
It's just like, it's, it's like jaws to.
It's just like, what were you thinking here?
Like, I guess maybe just there were in such a rush and so blinded by cash.
I don't know.
Well, he said he, he said, you know, I knew what they wanted.
I knew what the public wanted.
And I didn't give it to them.
Linda Blair said in an interview recently she goes, you know,
that movie that you saw is not what the script was.
Yeah.
They were, the script was actually very brilliant.
It was very smart.
And she goes, and it was the thing that made me say, yes,
she goes, I've denied doing sequels for years to, to that movie.
She said that they were making changes throughout the production.
Um, you know, it just sounded like a fucking mess.
This all said, there are some genuinely scary parts in it.
There are some genuinely scary sequences where Reagan.
I don't even think she's playing the possessed version of herself.
I think it's a different actress, but there are some kind of creepy parts
with the possessed version of Reagan.
There's some interesting stuff with the James Earl Jones character
and the locusts and all that.
It's sort of eerie and strange and odd.
And then you got Richard Burton in there.
There's an exorcism scene at the beginning that's pretty cool.
It's got some, I remember the locust scene as being pretty dope,
if I remember correctly.
Yeah, there's, there's, there's some interesting stuff.
It's not a good movie.
Uh, all of this to say that the trailer won for David Gordon Green
to the actresses believe what I thought was terrible.
The second trailer, I was like, okay, I'm listening guys.
I'm seeing priests.
I'm seeing creepy looking kids that are possessed.
I'm hearing a dubbed demon voice instead of a shitty voice.
Modulation effect.
Yeah.
I like the new trailer.
And they're saying creepy shit.
So let's go.
I want to see this.
I like in the new trailer when the demon goes,
are you looking for Reagan?
She's in hell.
I was like, okay, this, all right.
Let's go.
So, uh, and also this is to say that, you know,
the actresses three is an awesome, awesome movie.
And Legion is also excellent.
The Peter Blattie director's cut.
But, um, you know, these guys don't have too tall in order to make a decent extraceous movie.
Uh, so hopefully they pull it off, but we also thought that about the Halloween sequels.
We're wrong there.
So we'll see what happens.
It's true.
I'm, I'm cautiously optimistic.
It's actually coming out within like the next few weeks, I believe, which I'm pumped about.
Um, after hustle and flow blew me away.
I also wanted to revisit his next movie, Craig Brewer's next movie, which is black snake moan.
A movie that I saw theatrically, and I remember finding it just so bizarre that I don't,
I didn't even really remember what my opinion of the movie was.
I just remember it kind of being a head scratcher.
Um, and seeing it again, much like with hustle and flow.
It's not as good.
It's, it's a far stranger piece of work.
But it's a great movie.
And I think it also speaks to what Joe was talking about in the last episode with semi pro,
is that we just had this tonnage of great movies being released.
So when something was average, you'd go, ah, fuck that as a piece of shit.
Now we would, we yearn for average.
So, you know, sometimes you go back and rewatch something and you're like, wow, okay,
this is way better than I remember.
And sometimes you change as a person and like something more.
So black snake moan is Sam Jackson and what he considers his own best performance.
And he is great in it.
He's doing something a little different than his usual thing.
He plays an older dude who lives alone in kind of a rundown house.
His wife cheats on him with his brother.
She did not want to have kids with him.
It just, it completely devastates him.
She leaves him first brother.
He confronts her aggressively in like a breakfast spot in one of the greatest scenes of the film.
A really beautifully performed and acted scene by Sam Jackson,
where he's like, he just, he wants to go nuts on her.
But he can't because he's at a, you know, crowded restaurant.
But he's, he's at his wit's end, you know, he's a very kind of biblical Christian guy.
And he just can't accept that his wife did this to him.
The parallel story is Christina Ricci, you know, outrageously sexy in this movie.
She's in, she's in her underwear the entire time.
But she plays an infomaniac who is dating Justin Timberlake.
And Timberlake, who's great in this movie too, by the way.
And Timberlake goes off to war or he goes, you know, he gets drafted or something.
And she's like, what am I going to do with this pus, you know, she's like, she constantly needs dick.
And the second he skips town, she just starts fucking Annie and everybody.
And there, there's some graphic shit in this movie that I did not recall.
But she's like, she's calling up people.
She's, she's, she, she, at one point, fucks a kid.
I mean, it's nuts.
You know, he had 13 or something.
Oh, the 13 year old boy, he finds her like, so yeah.
And she fucks up.
I mean, are they stuff happens, but are they showing sex?
I don't show that.
No, but I mean, Jen.
No, no, no, no, no.
But in general, he's showing tons of sex scenes.
Oh yeah, lots of sex scenes, but the kid they cut away.
But it all goes to show you like this is a medical condition.
And then you find you come to find out that as is often the case with an infaminiac, they were, you know, she was abused as a kid and so forth.
And she has her own, you know, graphic backstory.
Her mom is a character in this as well.
But she goes out to some party.
She takes, she gets cross faded, which is where you get super fucked up.
Take drugs and alcohol.
And she basically gets assaulted, beaten, left on the side of the road in her underwear.
And when Sam Jackson wakes up to throw his garbage out in the morning, he sees this blonde girl sitting there.
But a black guy in the South, not exactly going to, you know, he's not going to call the police and be like, hey, there's this half naked white woman in her underwear that I just found outside of my house.
So he brings her in.
And then what he decides to do is chain her to a radiator and cure her of her sinning ways.
And then it's fucked up ways also trying to get back at his wife.
But he's trying to cure her from her nymphomania by like locking her up.
And it is a crazy movie.
It's a hard, hard R just like hustle and flow.
And I really, really hope I'm trying to, I'm trying to get Craig Brewer for something is why I'm rewatching his stuff.
But that's not why I'm raving about the man.
I've never met him.
I just think if he, he's got to get back to that.
Dolomite is his name is the same kind of thing.
It's a 70 style movie, big energy.
It just hilarious out, exciting, crazy.
And when he's in that mode, he's just the best.
But when he's doing coming to America, you know, that's a real heart breaker.
I really hope he's at this pivotal moment that he does not go further down that big budget Amazon comedy.
And he's got a lot of money out and sticks to his guns because those three movies that I mentioned, I think this guy's a really great director.
So check those out.
Even if you saw him the first time around, maybe you'll see something new, but loved it.
Love both.
I got to see both.
I haven't seen either.
Highly recommend.
Cool.
All right.
Let's go to that movie.
Let's all go to the movies.
Uninvited.
Yeah.
Shutter.
We're now.
Shutter original.
Yes.
Joe, when you.
Watch this movie, you mentioned you've been doing a lot of rage drinking lately.
Had you had you been drinking when you recommended this film to me?
No, I was quite sober.
When I saw it.
And I was quite sober when I recommended it.
Look.
I was with Pinkstone.
We were at his house.
We said, let's Sunday night.
Let's watch a horror movie.
We scrolled up.
We stumbled upon this.
He was like, well, the premise sounds kind of cool.
These just couple after a tragedy moves out to the Irish countryside.
And there are creatures out in the woods that, you know, whatever.
I was like, okay.
Fuck it.
It sounds like a Gremlins kind of thing.
We started watching.
They're literal goblins.
Like they look like garden gnome, sort of like little.
Like many red bearded.
Yeah, I had not seen the style of goblin before in a movie.
They look sort of like things you'd see like Dobby or something, but not Dobby,
but like they look like Harry Potter -ish.
Yes, I agree.
Sure.
But the premise is it's a couple.
They get pregnant.
They suffer a home invasion.
The husband has trouble standing up for himself.
But the first time he does stand up for himself, it's to some creeps that hang around his house.
Outside of his apartment building.
And then it results in them invading his home and beating the shit out of him and his wife.
Miraculously, she does not lose the baby.
And this is this happens just as his aunt dies and leaves them a house in the Irish countryside.
They go out to the Irish countryside and they're immediately told by the aunt's friend that the reason the aunt died basically is because she turned her back on these creatures, the red beards, I think they're called.
That live out in the woods and you have to feed them every day or they will turn on you.
Of course they think it's nonsense.
And little by little, you realize it's not through a plot device of the home that they have inherited needs repairs.
A family of rough and tumble people that live in the town who are drunks are the only people they can find to do the job.
However, inviting these people into their home creates a lot of problems. They're stealing from them.
The slow -witted son and large -bodied son of the father who runs the company tries to sexually assault the wife.
The other kids, brother kids meaning they're all like in their 40s.
The brother and sister constantly talk the husband.
It's a very tense situation.
And what happens?
I will, it's calm, calm meaning by the way, who if you're a fan of Irish film as I am, is kind of a legend.
He's from the commitments and looks some of some of the greatest school.
He's actually played on, always sunny when they were in Ireland.
It's always good to see him pop up and so he's just a great Irish character actor.
Go ahead.
So he's sadly probably the name of the movie.
I thought I recognized the lead girl, but then when I looked her up, I was like, I guess I saw her in Ant -Man, but I don't know who she is really.
Ready to play her role.
So these little gnomes that sort of show their face here and there, leading up to this.
What happens climatically in the movie is you think that it's going to be they get home invaded at the beginning.
They're going to have to suffer another home invasion, but they're going to have to fight gnomes.
What you realize is no, it's quite the opposite because they do start to believe these things exist and they feed them.
The home invasion is of the family of contractors.
And the gnomes come to their rescue in a sequence that I just found wildly insane and fun and bloody and insanity.
Yeah.
Well, that's what, look, when I looked on letterbox for this movie afterwards, because I was like, I miss some here.
I felt the way every single review said the exact same thing, which was I had a blast when these red beard goblins were on screen and boy did I not have a blast when they weren't.
And that's kind of how I felt.
I thought it was super generic and dull and the story was not particularly compelling.
I think it's, it's weird to have elements of like sexual assault attempts and stuff in a movie where you also have little garden gnomes who come back.
You know, like, but I think the vengeance that they wreak upon them hits harder because of how fucked up the, you know, the family that's fucking with them is.
I was also surprised to see this referred to as full core because I watched a four hour documentary about full core and I was like, maybe I don't know what full core is.
I got to be honest.
I still don't understand what full core is.
I guess it takes it has to be in the woods.
I still don't fucking totally get it.
I think yeah, woods are a key element clearly is maybe the only thing that holds them all together, but yeah, you know, it's.
Look, I always complain about movies being too long and an hour 44 minutes is not a too long movie, but maybe it is when we're talking about gnomes, you know, cut it back to 90.
I felt the stuff that didn't involve those gnomes really drug on and by the way, these gnomes aren't like great special effects or anything either part of the charm is how shoddy they look.
But the movie on a hole, I bet if it was made in the 80s and I watched it, I'd be like, alright, that was pretty damn cool or something.
There's something about the shutter original vibe that just looks too cheap and too video to me.
This one looks better than most. Don't get me wrong.
I said to Jim at the top, I go, if it says shutter original, we're in trouble and we were commenting at throughout going, man, this is really well done.
Like, like there were moments where he was like, dude, that shot was great for a fucking shutter original. Okay, because I was like, here we go. It's going to be three characters in the same room for two hours. And it was like, no, it's not that at all.
I thought apparently it was it was an Irish theatrical release that they picked up, which is probably why it winds up looking a little better.
But yeah, there are original stuff that just don't put enough money into it. And then when you see them laying off half their staff, it's probably just simply because they don't have it.
I thought this movie did an excellent job of leading you in one direction, which was thinking it was going to be this very somber, very emotional, very, the humans are the real monsters kind of film.
And then they went, nope. And they gave you a gremlins, gullies, critters style, half hour, fucking sequence of batshit insanity violence.
There's a part where one of the gnomes kills a guy. He comes up behind him in the car and stabs him in the neck.
And like, I go, Jesus, yeah, I was like, he just killed him like Charles Bronson or so. I was like, this is wild. And then I was like, okay, you know, the deal is is you have to make a deal with these things for them to really help you to this extent.
The mother, sorry, the aunt, the story was that the aunt had promised them her baby. And then when she resent, reneged on that, the gnomes turned on her in this when the woman needs them to help because her husband is in terrible danger in the house with this family trying to kill him.
She says, I'll give you anything. You're like, oh, well, there it goes. She's going to have to give the baby.
The climax happens. It all goes down.
The gnomes leave. They're like, thank God, we're fine. She then goes into labor and has the baby. And I'm like, okay, here comes the big twist. And I thought for certain what was going to happen was these gnomes are going to come back.
Yeah. She was the husband knows they she promised them something. And the twist was going to be she gives them the over the husband because she doesn't love him anymore because she wants the baby.
That's not what it is. It then goes to a place where they come. They take the baby. She goes to like their layer.
There's a crazy sequence with her in the layer where she's attacking these things and like splattering them. There's a there's an old witchy woman living down the layer. She realizes that's her aunt's baby that that which was a lot like barbarian.
Right. Exactly.
And she gets her baby and she escapes.
Oh, she then she then murders the old lady who tries to take her baby from her brutally with like a rock and then all the gnomes start worshiping her like like return to the Jedi Ewok style when they're all bowing to see three.
They follow her home and it starts pouring rain and she starts dancing pouring blood all over herself and all the gnomes are gleefully chanting around her and you realize no, the end is is that they're all going to be a big happy family together. It is so fucking insane.
And I was seven dwarfs. Yeah, I was like, I'm here for this 100 % these guys went all the way with this thing like this is nuts.
You're not wrong. That that stuff that stuff is great. I just wish the rest of it had a little more life to it or a little more something. But maybe that's the balance. Maybe that's that's why it works is that it throws you off by thinking it's one thing who knows. But I
I didn't love it. Don't let's let's not let's not be too kind here. But what Joe was saying I agree with it had a craziness to it at times that was sort of fun.
I loved it. I thought it was a lot like I do agree the first hour 45 minutes whatever it is is is dry. Yeah, you know, I think a good analogy could be.
The first part of the movie is like watching the TV show back the Mitchell web TV show back which is the latest thing they did together.
You're just like this is interesting and it's got its moments, but it's it's very dry. And then the last 45 minutes is like watching the witchel and meb the Mitchell and web look which was their sketch show which is bonkers.
I like I feel like it was the shift of one thing to another. And somehow they pulled it off. It's usually a thing that's probably one of the other reasons I love this so much. I in my opinion, they pulled it off which you don't often see and it's a thing I often complain about where they try to do this and they try to do that. None of it works.
It's a mess, blah blah blah. They stuck to the rules. It made sense in their world that they established. And in the end, I was like, wow, you you you you landed this plane somehow. So I really liked it. My hog is is pretty far up for for uninvited.
If if a unwell come or sorry, unwelcome, sorry, shooting above it's a by the way, who is title and movies these days unwelcome.
I thought that title made sense. It's about it's it hinges on two home invasions.
Shouldn't we know that there's going to be norms in this movie shouldn't there be some some inclination. How many movies have been called unwelcome you've mistaken the title twice three times in this episode.
That's fair. I was singing an Alanis Morissette song about uninvited. And I was wrong.
Did I also talk about it at the beginning? We've been calling it uninvited the whole time.
Whoops. Talk to me. The uninvited there are several movies called that too, but I saw talks me last night. And I was reminded that there's a Don Cheetle movie called talk to me that came out 10 years ago. I think he got nominated for it.
Like we got to start copywriting these things like we used to anyway. I think I talked to me looks like a good movie. And I hear it's great. I don't like the title. I think it's it's a no. It sounds like it sounds like it'd be like a sex comedy or something or like, you know, or
it would be the title of the the Frazier reboot. Yeah. Yes. They're by the way, they started putting up ads around town for the Frazier. Oh, really?
To do a late in the late in the app grain shots. But yeah. And they say they say like no more callers is the no more callers, but like a same old Frazier or something like that.
Oh, the teasers are up. I didn't see a clips of it. Well, there's a there's two 30 second teasers. One of them is Chelsea, Chelsea, Jesus Christ. Kelsey grammar sitting at a piano. And one looks like it's just a drawing. It's the drawing of the lines.
Like at the beginning when it makes the cityscape.
Well, you know, we're going to be covering that Frazier reboot, folks, unless it's awful. If we don't talk about it, you'll know it was awful because I always gunning for a job on the Frazier reboot. They hired all the old original people. But some tells me they'll have to fire them. And that's where I slide.
And Joe is great to see you. Helios is great to see all of you. Joe's going to tell you about our live show next month. I am on Twitter. No, not anymore. I'm on Instagram at the patch.
Walsh. You can listen to me on good Christian fun. Discuss the movie contact. And that's about all I got. I'm waiting for this strike.
Like I already plugged all the dates on the last episode, those all still stand joderosate .com for all tour dates and tour information. And we're adding new cities every not have some said every day. We're adding new cities as frequently as we should be and more popping up. So please come check the check me out live and we'll see you on the 28th in New York.
And that's it. We'll see you next time. And we'll see you in hell.