Summer is here and Bed MDM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer or check out
our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz.
Only available at Bed MDM Casino.
Spend on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 Fortunes, Mystery of the Land,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand.
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action.
Bet MGM game sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 Plus to Waiter, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and West Virginia
only.
Games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as normal, durable site credit slash bonus bets unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
The football season is full of guarantees and here's another, no other sportsbook has
an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee every single game day from now until October, if
your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning or winning money back in fan
cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
Winning hits different here.
Monthly 21 plus, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamberler, offer not available in all states
terms apply, see Fanatic Sportsbook app.
Welcome to we'll see you in hell the podcast brought to you by the
Fangoria podcast network you want info hey you want info on the network that
what you want you want to fucking info is that what you need yeah you want it
yeah you want to info sorry that was creepy uh don't like it
the uh go go to the damn website that's how you follow the show that's how you find
past episodes. We'll see you in hell. You go you visit fingering .com now on with the show Pat how
are you? I'm all right Joe. As I was saying before we started recording I was just watching the
third and final presidential debate. I'm sick to my stomach. I want to apologize to the women of
America that that this man is representing perhaps half of the nation. It's dark man. He's a
fucking sick sick man well that being said Pat I have a cold yeah I didn't
see the debate tonight because I was sleeping okay so I am sick but it
sounds like you are sick and tired you know you're absolutely right
Joe. I'm sick and tired of being sick and tired. No, it's, it's a bad time, folks.
You know what I know it. So why can't we just talk about some movies and try to feel better?
I'm going to break down what I've seen in the couple of weeks since we last spoke, Joe.
Right. Well, tell me about it. Now, do you think we're going to get a Trump movie eventually?
Oh, no question like a real one because they've done like funny or die. No, no question. I mean his life story
I think you know like very much like what they did with the OJ show, which I thought was so fantastic
I think would be an amazing thing and they know who do you think David swimmer will play in the Trump one Melania?
He'll play Meloni. Yeah, okay
Melania
Melania, I think he said Meloni like he's gonna play Christopher Meloni in the Trump movie
Which I didn't know what the connection there would be you know, so I'm a horror
Tech swimmer. I think it's a fine enough actor, but
In a way that never happened with me with like Julia Louie drivers with the sign fell people
Even though I love that show much more. There's something about the friends or when I see him. I'm just like you're on this this frothy little
Friends show, you know, they never so when swimmer was an app pupil
Which is a fantastic movie Stephen King adaptation who I never saw at pupil
who was really? It's one of Stephen King's short stories. I know. I think you would love.
I know. I didn't have a high interest in it because it was just about the Nazi hiding in the
neighborhood. There was no like monster elements. So it didn't excite me that much.
No, it's an extremely good movie. It's I don't doubt it. Plus, you got your Brad Renfrow in there.
Yeah. I think it was Brian Singer's follow -up to usual suspects, actually.
It was. It's a very, very good movie, but Schwimmer plays the guidance counselor in it,
And it's not a big part, but it was like during the height of friends.
And he shows up and you're like, nope, I just saw him in I just rewatched season four
of curb your enthusiasm.
And I enjoyed Schwimmer's performance in that, but never realized it was weird.
I was watching and I was like, Jesus Christ, guys exceptionally good looking.
Schwimmer at that period.
I mean, I haven't seen him lately.
I'm sure he's still in handsome man.
but he he's a good looking dude man you heard it here folks I wouldn't mind
taking a swim in that pool what movies have you seen Pat let's let's start by
the way let's let's officially make this how we open the show we the movie recap
sure I'll tell you what I've seen speaking of friends Lisa Kudrow had a small
and distracting got to admit it part in the girl in the train which I saw
distracting because it was Kudrow or yeah and and Kudrow did differentiate
herself because now I think of her more as Valor Cherish from the come back
which I think is a genius show. I think Kudrow is a magnificent actress and
deserves. I do as well. She's more the funniest part of neighbors I think by far.
Romeo and Michelle I love. Well yeah she's great she's great in the opposite of
sex. Yeah yeah we're big fans over here she's I'm a big analyze this fan. Yeah me
to not analyze that. But folks, she shows up in the girl on the train and you're like,
oh, it's Phoebe. And you're judging her on her looks because you can see her every night
on television. There's something about people being on TV for that long where you feel like
you're able to judge them and be like, I know who you are and everything about you. I don't buy you
the phone. Well, I just said it inadvertently just said it about swimmer. I was focused completely
on what he looked like over everything else whereas Ben Stiller was on the same season and I was
just like yeah this is Ben Stiller doing a part like I wasn't thinking about you know. It's not
fair. She has a very small part in the girl in the train. Girl in the train I did not read the book.
I was very confused for three -fourths of the movie but I was on board. My friend's wife is reading
the book right now said that the book is utterly confusing and she doesn't know what's happening.
Okay, then the movie I guess was very faithful adaptation, but when they started explaining everything I
was both
Clear, I understood everything that was happening, which is rare for me, and I
Loved it. I thought it was great twists and turns. I was on board. So the movie, you know, I'm gonna give it a B
I thought it was a very good thriller not not at a gone girl level
certainly not at a fatal attraction or a basic instinct style level.
It was a fun movie.
So you didn't see any clam in this picture?
No, you did see a little bit of clam.
You did? Who's?
Well, I honestly...
I tried to talk to my girlfriend about the movie and I found
you almost can't say anything about it.
Because as soon as you start talking like,
well this guy, his relationship to her,
you ruined the movie.
A lot of tabloid heat on Jolie right now.
Well, you know, she divorced Brad Pitt.
I know but all the tabloids are saying that she's that she's slandering him so to speak she's making up stories
But but who the hell knows? I mean I had always heard he had a big weed problem and and him and Clooney, you know that that sort of
Rat -packed drink and you know folks it might be fun on the set of oceans 13, but when you bring it home
When you got
12 kids in the mix
What do you think it's gonna be like on the set of that oceans eight?
I don't know. I love all three of the ocean's movies, even the much -maligned 12 because while
that twist was stupid, I admire that they went for it.
I've only seen 1 and 11 and 13, actually. I never saw a 12. I love there. I thought
Prachino was... Prachino? I thought Prachino was great and 13.
But Gozzy and Anpochino, or now Gozzy and Gould, excuse me, Ampochino, world -right.
Yeah, I mean, it's 11 the original I think is a is a modern classic. Yeah, it's a it's a lot of fun
Yeah, and this is why one of the you know, you mentioned Trump and how poorly women are treated these days. Yeah
Or I said I shouldn't say these days. I should say how shameful it is that in this modern of a society
This is still a thing. Yeah, that's happening. But I mean, you know, you see it too with these movies. It's like
Can the can the women just have their own movie yeah like this the big franchise they get is like just the
It's not even a remake of the
Remake of the all men and it's like the most man thing
Yeah, the rat pack and then it's the modern rat pack redoing it then they give it to women
And it's just not even a remake of that. They're like no, we're just gonna do three prequels
It'll be eight, nine, and 10 now.
Yeah.
And it's like, can send same with those blusters.
You have one of the most beloved comedies ever.
People firmly entrenched in these roles.
And then, you know, now we'll just do it with women.
Why not come up with an original thing for women?
Which they did, and they have done before.
I think Romeo and Michelle's a great example
of a woman -driven comedy that felt very new.
Very friendly movie.
Bridesmaids, of course, you know, everyone always sites,
but you can't really underestimate what that movie did.
but nine to five.
Why, look, if you're gonna remake a movie for women,
if you're gonna force unfairly female actors
to be in remakes, at least remake nine to five,
and stuff like that, why are you making them do men movies?
You know, I feel like that's disrespectful.
I don't know, it bugs me.
Anyway, go ahead.
I just saw Dolly Parton at the Hollywood Bowl.
Hello, Michelle.
I heard she put on a great show.
It was like two hours amazing musical performances and then an hour of like great he -haw style stand -up
She did she did stand -up. She tells so many fucking jokes
So many jokes, and they're all funny. It's like, uh, you know, Rickle style
Very old school now tell me where in the set this nine to five come. It was the closer
But she'll tell us the place just go and berserk of course
She told stories about being on the set of nine to five. She told a very funny story about the set of best little horrors in Texas
She's making out with burnt rannels and she's like and I don't know if murder to appreciate me saying this
But he was starting to go real gray at this point
So before every take he'd smear a bunch of black dye and do his mustache and his beard and his hair
So I go in for the closing scene of the movie to make out with Bert and when I pulled away
I had black all over my face
crowd goes and say. It's kind of a funny story. All right. All right. Um, I saw, we talked
about solely last time. I saw deep water horizon. Another real time ripped from the headlines,
water tragedy movie. I mean, you're just seeing the dad movies at this point. Yeah. Uh,
I mean, Heather, we're joking this weekend.
We went with this couple two weekends in a row.
First weekend, we saw Sully.
Second, we saw Deepwater Horizon.
Do we discuss the issues of the day at brunch afterwards?
And I was like, we're 45 years old.
45.
55 years old.
Yeah, 65.
75 years old.
But Deepwater Horizon, I liked Kurt Russell,
Markey Mark, Kate Hudson,
Skyping in a performance, which is what again is what women have to offer these days folks I'm actually I'm a little envious of that gig
That's a nice. Yeah, it's like a voiceover gig or something. Yeah, that's nice
Deepwater horizons about the BP oil spill. I thought about it exactly as I felt about solely I thought it was
I learned a little bit. It was a great retelling of the events, right, suspenseful, and I liked it. They got in they got out
right
I saw Birth of a Nation, the very controversial Birth of a Nation.
Yeah, that's a tough one because that whole rape controversy popped up around it.
Yeah, they bought the movie at Sundance or one of those festivals for like $20 million
and then between that acquisition and the release of the movie, it came out that the director
and star and writer Nate Parker had allegedly raped someone when he was 18 and been acquitted
of the crime. So you go in, of course, not if I shouldn't say, of course, I just mean
like, but the only reason I'd use the term, of course, is because I said controversy,
meaning from the other side of it, it, there was a lot of argument that he was not innocent.
You know, that was, yeah, because the woman who brought the allegations recently killed
herself. Oh my god, I didn't know that. Nate Parker was on 60 minutes recently and they asked
him if he just wanted to apologize to her or her family and he said, no, why would I? I've
been acquitted, which is not a great response regardless. Oh, it's a terrible response. Yeah,
so you go into the movie knowing these things about the guy who made it. I recently read this disgusting
article I think in the Hollywood reporter where they were like, you know, let's say Woody Allen
Rome Plansky rate who they say they're raped. This is unfortunate, but they've had 50 years
of great movies. So we're very willing to forgive them. Right. And it's part of the
Roman Plansky admitted to guilt. He admitted to unlawful sex with a minor. And it was like
Nate Parker. He hasn't really proven himself to us. So you know, I don't know that people
are going to be as forgiving of him because this is his first movie. Very dangerous and sick
This drives me nuts with Polanski.
Yeah, I understand if you're on either side of it with Woody Allen because there was no,
there was no real closure to the thing accusations were hurled, there's information on both sides
that caused different parties to support either side of the argument.
So we can leave that one out of it.
Roman Polanski admitted to having sex with a minor.
it is fact and that's the part that drives me nuts that people are still so
supportive of them including me a pharaoh yeah which is nuts to me but but you
know it's I hate that he even gets brought up into this like well what how
would we have react well you know how to react we have the we know what happened
yeah with Polanski yeah still you know it's you got to separate the singer
from the song. I don't agree with that. I don't agree with that. And I will say I brought
my knowledge of this guy, which was not a very positive view of him into the movie, which
contained about two rapes scenes for shock value. Rapes are kind of what incites the slave
riot that is the climax of the movie. It's a movie about slavery. It's a movie about a revolt.
Where the rapes scenes in that you say for shock value, were they unnecessary or were they
of slaves at that time.
Look, there's nothing you can put on the screen
that would compare to the horror of slavery.
But there are some very disturbing scenes in this.
The rape scenes are handled tastefully.
They're for the most part off camera.
But for a man to have been accused
and acquitted of rape to include several rape scenes
in his movie, and they're also the events
that incite this very famous slave revolt, my thinking is, what are you trying to say?
Are you trying to say like you're so disgusted by slavery that I'm just, excuse me.
You're so disgusted by rape that you support an uprising and is that trying to clear your
name for these previous offenses?
These thoughts, you shouldn't be having when you're trying to enjoy a movie.
right but you know it was a I didn't think it was an amazing movie but it was
pretty solid it was not as good as two years of 12 years of slave from a
couple years ago two years of slave I prequel I think we'd all prefer two
years to twelve but I have there something happened when I saw birth of a
nation that I think would make the ultimate Kerberanthusia in the
long. You should send this to Larry Davis. I'm sure he never gets these from fans.
Maybe if I if I it'll be my elevator pitch. And then I'll tell you my and then I'll
tell you my curb idea. Okay. And then we got to get to the movie. Yeah. Yeah. About 10
minutes into the movie. So it has army hammer in it, ogling himself up to play a plantation
So he has like literally three teeth, he insulted like the he ha, he inserted like the he
ha style, you know, three tooth, you know, you buy it in a quarter machine at the grocery
store.
Halloween adventure.
Yeah.
He wears that the entire movie to ugly himself up.
It's that kind of movie.
It was not great, but Army Hammer is yelling at this guy like do you think you're better
than me N word and the slave says no sir and this black guy is walking into the movie
theater the visa over here in Los Felos right and he seemed to be to me homeless but he did
get into a movie so I guess he had some money but he seemed to maybe have some mental problems
Okay, so he walks in and he's, you know, making a lot of noise and being kind of a big scene and when army hammer says
You know, do you think you're better than me and the guy says no sir this guy screams up at the screen while he's walking to his seat
You say yes, sir
You say yes, you're better than him screams at the screen. Okay, so I'm like, okay, there's a little intense. Okay
and he sits down and then basically everything that is said so when the white
slave owners are talking of course in a slave movie like assholes for the
slaves he would scream up at the screen okay and he'd be like you don't have to
take that fucking bullshit okay so we're sitting there and you could tell
everyone was very annoyed by it because then even in the quiet more serious parts
of the film you know like more like more intense parts of the film he's still
screaming at the screen and kind of ruining your engagement with the film.
Sure.
But you looked around the audience, which was of course, you know, black and white people.
You know no white person in the audience is going to say to him, shut up, quit screaming
in the middle of this.
You've been screaming for an hour and a half, where we all paid to watch this movie.
And all the pathetic white people in the audience were giving each other this look of like,
like, boy, I wish I could say something here,
but I'm gonna let it roll.
So now, yeah.
And it made a movie that already would have been
very tense and depressing, even more tense.
Like, you felt like when we walked out in the lobby,
like maybe it was gonna like turn into words
because people were getting very uncomfortable.
So your curb episode is Larry David being like,
I can't, it's got nothing to do with race.
I can't tell him that I want it.
Yeah. Or Larry David telling him to shut the fuck up
and then it like, like in the background behind him,
He's making the exact same gestures as like the slave on the movie right, you know like lecturing the guy or whatever it is
But right I thought that could be a very funny episode
my curb idea was always
That in a rest he's at a restaurant and
He's having a discussion with his manager
Jeff green. Yeah, and the waitress comes over like waitresses do and waiters not being sexist wait people
Do and interrupts the conversation. Hi, welcome to such and such. What can I get for you today?
And you know, she walks away and then she comes back again two minutes later.
Here are your drinks. Walks away, comes back two minutes later. Have you decided yet? Walks away. He's like, it's very rude, you know.
Trying to have a conversation, she keeps interrupting. Of course it's managers like, you're crazy. She's trying to, it's called good service.
what are you talking about? He's like just they should say excuse me. Are you ready to speak to me? It's very rude
She comes back in all the time. He puts up his finger. He's like I just I just would like you to wait for a moment
She of course gets very mad. Then he's got to pay the bill. Can't find her
Go to the weight station says I need to pay my bill. She goes can you just give me a minute? He is a meltdown
Oh, when you need a minute
It's fine, but we need a minute. It's not okay. Right. Well, then you just go from there
Well, at the end, it's something that's got to bring what in a cost Larry David pitching these I
I also saw I'm not done. Oh, I forgot. I saw my favorite movie of the year
Manchester by the sea
It comes out around Thanksgiving. I believe I saw like a you know an Oscar -type screaming for it
But it's Casey Affleck Michelle Williams
directed by Kenneth Lonergan, written by Kenneth Lonergan, who did you can count on me,
which is one of the all -time great, wonderful film. Movies, Mark Ruffalo, Laura Lennie,
and he also did Margaret, which is a very interesting movie, but you know, maybe not as great as
some said. This is his best movie, Manchester by the Sea. This thing, don't watch the preview,
don't read anything about it. It's just like, it was a very like emotionally taxing difficult
movie incredibly well written, very funny, Casey Affleck was incredible in it. I don't
know what to tell you. It's the best movie of the year. You should tell it. Just go see it.
It was an incredible movie. Okay. Just like a movie about such like explosive
emotional things handled in a way that never gives in to like the sappy emotion the
Reality sure it was amazing. I loved it sure and my second favorite movie here
I just saw American honey. I walked in knowing nothing it was three hours long
Which I was certainly not aware of it seemed to be kind of improvised. It's shy of buff
I should have hated it shy of a buff and then this kind of nobody actress that no one has ever heard of and
And basically, they go across the country selling magazine subscriptions, and it's three
hours long.
And I know that it doesn't sound good.
Sort of like a Glen Gary Glen Ross kind of thing.
No.
Well, yeah, it was like Glen Gary Glen Ross meets Larry Clark, like kids or bullies or something.
It's about kind of pardon the term white trash kids.
It's set in and around Kansas City, which is very close to where I grew up and I related
to a lot of it.
It felt very real to me.
Sure.
It was three hours long.
I could have watched eight hours of it.
It's a very, very much an art movie.
But at an amazing soundtrack, it was very funny.
It was very interesting.
It was filmed in an incredible way.
I loved it checking out.
Is that it?
That's it.
All right.
I got a couple.
Go, Joe.
My list is not as long as yours.
But I spent some time at the New Beverly Cinema.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
This month, which is, if you're not familiar,
Quentin Tarantino's cinema, it's a wonderful place.
Eight bucks, you get to see two movies at a clip.
Double Features, they play cartoons,
they play old trailers, it's a really wonderful experience.
Fed the whole family at the snack bar for $15.
Went with our friends, Vincent, Georgia and my parents.
So the heart of Dracula, the hammer classic Christopher Lee,
Dracula movie that started it all had a great time.
I'm sure most of you, Fengoria, folks out there have seen it already and if you haven't it's a wonderful adaptation of the Bram Stoker novel and it's a lot of fun.
And I watched Bram Stoker's Dracula this weekend.
I love it.
It's a fucking masterpiece.
I think it's as good as a piece of work as Coppola has ever done.
You know what?
I don't understand.
If you're willing to say like the godfather is like the perfect drama.
And Bram Soaker's Dracula is the perfect like classic horror. I would absolutely agree with you
Yeah, it's a wonderful film
Incredibly cool well -shut. I wound up watching like three hours of documentary footage and how they did the special effects
They did them all in camera. Yeah, they're he didn't want to do ILM
No, so he had his son who was like 25 do all the special effects and he's like yeah
We just tried we put the film on the freezer for like eight hours and so this movie that made like three hundred million dollars was like a
extreme independent movie. I loved it. I thought about it a lot when I watched it
and I thought you know Coppola barely makes movies anymore and when he does
they're very under the radar but I was sitting there watching horror Dracula saying
I mean Coppola the guy knocked out Godfather one and two. A lot of people like
three, a lot of people hate it but so let's just say one and two. Apocalypse now
and Dracula. I mean four of the most incredibly tailored epic films I've
ever seen in my life. But anyway, so I saw that. I went back there last night, saw the
conqueror worm starring Vincent Price, 1968 witch trial movie where Vincent Price plays
the witch finder general. It's a brutal, brutal scenes in it. It quite a, quite a, like,
gross. Well, it's the way they execute the witches and torture them and stuff or the accused
which is obviously, it's a rough flick and a very, very hard commentary on
misogyny, hard meaning hard hitting. And it came out in 1968 and it's
surprisingly jarring especially for Vincent Price movie. But a film we're
seeing and I think the commentary is quite interesting. I have this book growing up
the entertainment weekly guide to the 100 Greatest Movies in each genre and I was a subscriber
of entertainment weekly from like the time I was nine years old and I loved it. It was my
fangoria of the day you would say. You know, not that it was ever hard hitting journalism but at
this point it's a lot more like people weekly. It's not as good a magazine as it used to be.
Sure, but this book was so incredible and they did not pick the obvious choices or easy choices
But they had the hundred best movies in every category and that was my film school from when I was like 10 to 20
I was trying to check off every movie in that book and
One of the only ones I didn't get to because I couldn't find it and I was so much of a dork
I used to travel from city to city go to the blockbuster the Hollywood video of the mom and pop
trying to find these movies, which was a lot of the fun of being into movies at
that time, which now you don't have anymore. Unfortunately, I'm going to sound
even older. Sure. But one of the only ones I could never find was the
conqueror worm. And then you invented, you saw that last night and I was like, fuck,
because I always wanted to see it. But I guess it's maybe now it's on DVD. It wasn't
when I was a kid. It's it is on DVD. You can find it. There's a Vincent
I think you can find it a solo on DVD.
There's a box set that it's included in on Amazon
that I think I'm gonna order.
It's got that in the Dr. Fibes movies
and stuff like that in there.
It was originally called Witchfinder General
over in Europe.
The European version was edited heavily
because of the extreme torture scenes.
When it was released here, it was renamed Conqueror Worm
after the Edgar Allan Poe poem that it's based on.
The Edgar Allan poem.
There you go.
and this the film was restored with the original footage for the most part but I
mean there's some rough scenes man there's a scene where they lower a woman
face first into a bonfire really rough stuff and you brought your pants on
this no I brought my parents to horror of Dracula okay the conqueror worm was Matt
McCarthy Vince A. Roe myself okay and we ate a ton of candy again went to the
counter I said Guy Snacks are on me $15 for all of us the new Beverly's one
favorite places in the world. When I first moved here and had zero friends, that's where I went,
three nights a week. So that was great. What else did I watch over here? Watched
a scarecrow, a scarecrow's, really a lot of fun, 80s horror. Wait, I thought you meant
Gene Hackman, Pacino, a scarecrow. No, it's called scarecrow's, it's an 80s horror movie.
Now, one of the shout factor, screen factory releases,
a botched ice goes wrong, they land in a field,
the scarecrows come to life and start killing people.
A lot of fun, a lot of fun, a lot of grower,
a lot of really fun, gruesome stuff.
Life force, Toby Hooper's life force.
I ordered it, never seen it.
It is, in my opinion, a fucking masterpiece.
I can't wait, I've heard so much about it,
And there's a tremendous amount of nudity, am I right?
There's a lot of nudity, but it's not sexual nudity.
But Dan O 'Bannon, who wrote Return of the Living Dead
and co -wrote, I think he co -wrote the original alien.
Yeah, he did.
He either co -wrote or wrote the film.
Directed by Toby Hooper was put out by Canon Pictures.
It's probably one of the only movies
from the Canon catalog that you can look at and say,
no, like without any kitschy irony,
this is actually really good movie it's just magnificent it's just that the
effects are insane I got to come in this week I ordered so many of the
screen factory blu -ray's and I'm gonna email them tomorrow and try to get them
as a sponsor on the show we should we should so both of those were out of
screen factories library with the re -released factory has and they have a sale
going on right now actually but these things are the best like I'd never seen the
Howling, and I watched The Howling the other night, which is you know
Not as great as I have been led to believe, but I liked it quite a bit and
I want to watch like this 90 -minute documentary on the making of the Howling that I liked more than the movie
I think shot factory does an incredible job. I'm very excited to watch this new print of the thing
I just got and this new print of Carrie. I just got the best they got they got vignettes on the on the
scarecrows DVD as far as I could find these guys. I don't think I've ever made
another movie. Yeah. And then you got interviews like modern day,
and your present day interviews with these guys. Yeah. It's real.
I gave you on demon night. You're going to love. I did watch it. Watch it.
I loved it. Uh, you can have that blue ray back. I enjoyed it quite a bit.
Um, that's the only reason I came to the box. That's not folks is to get my
demon night blue ray back. Look, we're 32 minutes deep here. Roughly, uh,
Well, then we're rambling. We mean to talk about psycho and psycho too. Yeah, we got to talk about the first two psycho movies
And then we also have to get to our new segment at the very end, okay?
So we're gonna book in the show from now on with these segments. You'll see what the new segment is when we get to it
It's time to see your smile, it's time to see your smile, it's time to see your smile, it's time to see your smile, it's time to see your smile, it's time to see your smile, it's time to see your smile, it's time to see your smile, it's time to see your smile, it's time to see your smile, it's time to see your smile, it's time to see your smile, it's time to see your smile, it's time to see your smile, it's time to see your smile, it's time to see your smile, it's time to see your smile, it's time to see your smile, it's time to see your smile, it's time to see your smile, it's time to see your smile, it's time to see your smile, it's time to see your smile, it's time to see your smile, it's time to see your smile, it's time to see your smile, it's time to see your smile, it's time to see your smile
to come out because they must have known.
Psycho 2 is the shit.
It's awesome.
I had never seen it.
I own in a DVD box set.
I got an Amazon for five bucks, by the way.
Psycho 2, 3, and 4.
I have it myself.
So I'm excited to watch 3 and 4 also,
but Psycho, of course, I've seen 50 times.
I went to film school.
You wind up watching it in every class.
It's an incredible movie.
Psycho 2, all I had ever heard about it
was that Quentin Tarantino liked it more than the original Psycho and of course that made me curious
but I was kind of like oh he always says crazy stuff like that. I didn't like it more than the
original Psycho of course but in terms of a horror movie sequel like I think it's one of the
all -time great horror movie sequel. I would agree especially to step up to a classic like that
this is like an original story but like very heavily influenced by the original and it was so
fucking fun and funny. Anthony Perkins was awesome. Loja was awesome. Meg Tilly was awesome.
I think it's insanely underrated and I saw that it did very well at the box office, but
it's not a movie you ever hear about as being any good.
Well, let's talk first about Psycho 1. Let's do it.
Before we get to Psycho 2, you know, come on, Psycho 1, everybody knows it. I, in fact,
just got it. I was up in Toronto. I had a Blue Ray. I mean, I had a DVD of it. I was in Toronto.
They had a goddamn Blue Ray of it at Best Buy in Toronto for $5 Canadian, which was like
$375 American. Is that a Louis? Is that the Canadian dollar?
It's a Canadian dollar. I don't know. That's just as far as I know, it was just called the Canadian dollar.
but psycho one I mean every aspect of the movie is in my opinion is perfect from
the credit sequence to the score. In fact I was just an amoeba and I bought on
vinyl Hitchcock the famous scores of Hitchcock or whatever can you
look at her? Yeah conducted by Bernard Herman with the London Philharmonic in
psychos on there obviously but you know this is this is a great this is the height
of filmmaking in Hitchcock's career would you think of the psycho remake you
know man I'm a fan of pretty much everybody involved in that thing but I just
I didn't think it was bad I just didn't think it was at a point yeah it felt
What kind of like a sort of shitty, not interesting art exhibit?
Whereas I went, I saw it.
I had kind of a fun time because they're doing the exact same movie and it's been spawned.
You know, the only thing they added, I think it was him jerking off but it's a shot for
shot remake of the original and I was kind of like, alright, I guess I'm glad I saw it.
What's frustrating is that I'm sure many people saw it and that's the only version of Cycle
they'll ever see. Right. I believe it was a bad move. I just didn't get the point of it person.
I'm sure as an actor, he never wants to hear this, but I don't want to see Vince Vaughn playing
a creep. Yeah. No, I don't. I like when he's likeable. But have you seen Bates Motel? Yeah.
You know, it's a half good show. Yeah. The storyline involving Norman and his descent into madness
all this stuff is great. That fucking shoehorned in B story like Twin Peaks
thing they're trying to do with the weed is terrible. It's terrible. And I say
that because I like to try to be away before the end of the first season and I
did think it had some good stuff about it but it wasn't keep my interest
percent. Yeah and I also don't like seeing Norman Bates with his and I
iPhone. Right. Yeah. Come on. I agree. I mean, fine,
said it in present day, but his mom shouldn't let him have an
iPhone. Right. She should be crazy. Like whatever. So, but I
would imagine most people listening have not seen Psycho 2. And
if you get nothing else out of this podcast, I urge you to
rent it. But you said you've seen 3 and 4, which I own, and I'm
excited to watch. I have. But I know you don't remember them,
but do you remember them being good or bad? I remember them being
forgettable and I remember well hold on before we get to that the one thing I want to say is I
actually have the book the novel of psycho okay the original novel and one thing I'll say about
is it called psycho yes okay no it's actually it's called crazy town isn't isn't Ed
Gein the inspiration for both psycho and Texas chance on mass I know definitely for Texas chance
and so I think possibly for Psycho but I will say this
about the book and this is gonna lead us into Psycho 2
because there's not really much to say about Psycho 1.
Everybody knows it's great,
it's probably got 100 % on Rotten Tomatoes.
I think it was the one of the first movies
that we ever have in our rating.
You know, we all know the little,
he used chocolate sauce instead of red stuff
because it looked like blood on the black
and we all know that shit but the one thing I will say
before we move on is the book Norman Bates is depicted quite differently in the book
he's in his 40s he's a short bald heavy set man okay with thick glasses which I think
is much creepier I would have liked to have seen like a real like there's something about
him being middle age with the glasses and bald that's much creepier but I got to tell you
I don't think it would have been as scary because, you know, especially watching him
get in too.
He was amazing in part two, but he's kind of like a good looking older dude.
And there's just something a little off about him.
We all know people like that.
And I think that that was a lot more interesting to me than if it had been Paul Giamatti or Steve
Hashem here or whatever.
So speaking of which, I just got an audition for something.
I don't probably can't, I don't know if I can say everything.
You know, talk about anything anymore.
But I just auditioned for something in the in the breakdown. It said a Paul a Steve Bouchemi type except not as good looking.
Well, thank you for that. That feels good.
Anyway, my buddy John Gabriel is one of the funniest men alive. I got him auditioned for a part on the show I write for and he texted me the breakdown from the script.
I had no idea this was in the script
But it described the character that I told him like you're a shoe -in for this role the description of the character was
Slavinly fat
Disgusting semi -colon a real pig
He just sent me a screen grab. I'm like, thanks for thinking of me. Did he get it and he didn't get it
Well, he's a good looking man if I gave us if I may say so gave us is a good looking man
He's a heavy set man, but he's got a slovenly pig no, but he he he would have been much better for the role of the person
We got I assure you so here's the thing so psycho one is is you know, it's slightly different in the book
The story, but it's pretty much it's pretty much it's fairly accurate
Now, but here's my point that I'm getting to as we go into the
psycho too.
And it was a fiction book, correct?
Yeah.
Okay.
But here's the thing that's important about that to me.
You mentioned Tarantino saying he likes psycho too better.
Now he might just like psycho too better.
My theory on that is he's looking at this as most people would argue but part one is based
on the book and the book this and the book that.
But I think his argument might be, but part one actually took a lot of liberties from
the book.
Therefore, we have to judge this not as Hitchcock's master adaptation of this best -selling novel,
but just as a film series.
And as a film series goes, part two is better than the first story for these reasons because
of what we learned of the character.
And one of the first things you notice in part two, and some people mentioned this on
our online questions tonight that they're sending in,
is that Norman Bates returns some 10 or 15 years later,
whatever it is, 20 years later.
And he's quite sympathetic.
You feel sorry for him.
Yeah, I did.
You don't feel like this is a terrible man
who did terrible things.
You feel like this is a disturbed man who was abused
who was out of his mind and has gone through rehabilitation
and is really trying his best to be normal now.
They also really the entire time because a lot of the plot of Psycho 2 without spoiling
anything is are people fucking with Norman to get him to go crazy again, to get him put
back in jail, which is a really ingenious way for the sequel to go.
So you never really know what's real, what isn't, and like it's the kind of movie where
my girlfriend was like walking from our kind of like study room to bed and just kind
of overheard something and wound up washing the last like hour and a half of the movie.
It's like there's something about it.
It's shot in a very it's not hitchcock but it's shot in a very cool way and the story is
fucking awesome and really kind of a should be a lesson to a lot of horror sequels that
It sucks so hard, because it has so much respect for the original, but it's also kind
of balsy enough to go the opposite way of this classic movie and just create some really
crazy shit of its own.
And speaking of horror sequels, hitting it out of the park, just a brief side note, Ouija
Origin of Evil, which is the new Ouija board movie, great reviews, 90 % on Rotten Tomatoes.
I didn't even see the original, but Ouija 2 looks terrifying to me.
Yeah, so and then the reviews that are read said just that this is this is how you make a sequel it
Write it all the wrongs the first one yada yada yada here's the synopsis a psycho to in case you haven't seen it
Uh two decades after the original murders at the bates hotel motel
Norman bates completes his treatment at a mental institution returns home
And he finds that his hotel is run down under the management of Warren to me play by Dennis france who's always enjoyable
Despite a new friendship with waitress play by Meg Tilley and a job busing tables at a
diner Norman begins to hear the voices once again no matter how hard he tries
Norman cannot keep mother from returning a coaxing him to unleash the
homicidal maniac within so that's basically the idea of the movie and as Pat
said it's you know it's one of these things like the town doesn't want him
around. They all hate him. You know, so are they fucking with him? Or is he really hearing
these things? And, you know, it's sort of unfolds from there. I, the movie kept me guessing
told just about the very end. Yeah, me too. It is well shot. It was shot by Richard Franklin.
It looked really great for like when I looked at it was 1981. I was like, yeah, that's a pretty
awesome looking movie for that time. They got the original sets. Richard Franklin also did. He's
done a bunch of movies but he also did the movie Patrick which is the mental telepathy horror movie
from 1978. They remade it later in the 2002 or something like that but the original Patrick is
wonderful. And again, note it as by Tarantino as one of his favorite films. But I truly do think that
I mean, look, what psycho too would have been at the hands of most people was a killer
on the rampage, more deaths and put them over the top and more blood and he's on the
loose and he breaks out of the asylum and yeah, and instead they did this really earnest
character study about a guy desperately trying to get his life back on track and what's stronger
his will to live a normal life or these demons he has inside of him.
Yeah, and then the really cool thing is that it does all that, but there are also really
cool kills in it.
Yes.
Like when the violence started happening, I was kind of like, oh, like I thought this was
kind of a very classy, well done continuation, but then when it comes down to the kills, they're
They're kind of beaten the Friday the 13th crowd at their own game.
They had some really awesome kills in there too.
Now it was also written by Tom Holland, who child's play, Fright Night, Wrote and Directed
Fright Night, Wrote and Directed Child's Play, yes, Wrote and Directed thinner, which we've
done on here.
Has a writing credit on the Fright Night remake, I don't know if that's just for characters
or not.
So, no, he wrote the story, well, I guess it's the same story as the original.
And Tom is a friend of horror podcasts all around.
Many of my friends that do horror podcasts, he's guested on him.
We've never had him on here because we don't usually have guests, but I've had some correspondence
with him on Twitter, and I'm a big fan of the guy.
So yet another cool reason that Psycho 2 is a cool movie, he also, you mentioned already
Robert Loja's in it.
Love Loja.
I love Loja too.
Feats Lamana from the Sopranos, which Joe inexplicably hates.
He plays Feats Lamana.
Feats Lamana, yeah.
That's his name in it?
Yeah.
Feats Lamana?
Yes, he's a great part for him.
It's a wild name.
No, I was actually blown away by Psycho too.
I was very, very pleased by it.
I'm excited about watching 3 and 4.
I think 4 was a showtime movie, 3 was a theatrical release, and the reviews kind of get worse
with each, but they brought back the original writer of Psycho for the 4th one, whatever that
does for you.
Yeah, now I will say this, the Psycho 4, I remember liking more, the reason I don't really
remember three and four is because they were not as riveting and more
forgettable than the first two. Three and four apparently was like I don't
I'm pretending that two and three don't exist. The writer was like I saw
those I thought they were shit so I'm not I'm not doing anything. It kind of did
skip it. The thing I didn't okay here's the cool aspects of four you know that
But they go into flashback sequences with, I think it's Will Wheaton in Psycho4 plays
the young, the young, Norman Bates, I mean, it's a big, good casting of the walls.
I think it is Will Wheaton, hold on a second, let me look this up.
So those aspects of it, I thought were cool, I like that they were showing you some back
story.
No Henry Thomas, that's right for me to, CCH Pounder, isn't it?
of Demon Knight and the Shield.
Yeah, Olivia Hussie plays Norma Bates.
Right.
Before I liked the backstory aspects of it,
I didn't like the whole modern story part
was that Norman is now living like a sort of normal life
and he's married but he's somehow hidden his past
from his wife and he's like about to host
to dinner party or something and he calls into talk radio and he's like, I think I might
do it again. It's a, it's a campier take on it. You know, it's like, oh, he's back.
He's up to no good. I personally wasn't buying that he was living in this like $350 ,000
suburban home, just kind of, you know, with, with, with a flair for the, for the, for the
Artisan foods or whatever, you know, but but it's not bad. It was better than
three. Three, I honestly, I couldn't, I don't remember three at all and I did
watch it fairly recently but I can't remember it. Did you know Anthony Perkins
died of AIDS? I did know that. I'm fortunate. I did know that. I watched the tab
Hunter documentary and he dated Anthony Perkins for a bit. Yeah, I mean we
Yeah, Heather loved Psycho 2 last night as well and wound up doing a Wikipedia on him.
It seemed like he lived a gay life for a while, then married a woman for like
Oh, okay.
And Tab Hunter unfortunately says in that documentary
like yeah, I mean I was incredibly close to this man
and he turned out to be like a Hollywood climber
and was only out for himself and was very selfish
and it kind of sucked, it put a new,
a darker spin on Anthony Perkins than I wanted to have
but whatever, especially a guy who didn't climb that high.
Let's go to the, you gotta take your foot off that
because that's gonna shove that down.
Pat's got his foot on this.
What was a table at one point, and I think it's now been smashed down into nothing.
I'm sorry, but I couldn't focus.
I couldn't focus.
I get it.
I'm just destroying Joe's home.
Let's go into the fan feed, the questions here.
first comes from Josh Brown at the underscore, Josh underscore, uh, brown. Hi, Josh.
Were you able to, is it for the first time without the ending being, I don't know what
that means it's clearly a typo.
Were you able to is it for the first time
without the ending being spoiled for you?
You're being able to see Psycho 2
without the ending being spoiled, I assume?
Yeah, I didn't know what the ending was.
I completely was.
I had no idea what it was going to be
and I thought they kept the twists a common
and I was blown away by it, frankly.
I was like this movie, you know,
especially, 22 years after the original movie,
like our Red Cisco Nebrit's review,
and they were begrudgingly admitting that it was good.
But they were like, you know,
compared to the original, no,
but we have to admit, it's pretty good.
But at the time, it must have seemed
like this kind of cynical cash in,
but now where both movies are just old movies,
it seems like kind of a dream continuation of it.
Like I was actually riveted to it,
had no idea what was going to happen and the movie is like 40 years old.
Next question comes from at C72, M -E -R -C.
Interested in what you guys thought about last shift on Netflix?
If you guys care to review it?
Well, possibly another time. I did watch it based on your last shift.
I think this guy recommended this to us. Somebody recommended that we watch last shift on Netflix.
I think it was him. I watched it. I found it disappointing.
I thought it had its moments. I thought it started with a lot of promise and then got kind
of got away from itself a bit, but it wasn't bad, but possibly in a future episode we will
review it if Pat watches it. Gibbon Wizard writes to us, what's your favorite Hitchcock film?
I'm going to go with Rope on that. Wow, Rope, okay. Rope is a masterpiece.
piece. I love her. My favorite Hitchcock movie by far is notorious exclamation point,
which is one of my favorite movies ever made. And that's the movie about B .I .G., right?
The rapper. Yeah, exactly. I didn't know Hitchcock did that. That's amazing.
No, notorious is obviously a classic but is strangely not often mentioned among his best.
It's Carrie Grant and Ingrid Bergman and it's kind of a Nazi romance thriller. To me,
it's his best movie. I think it's one of the best movies I ever made. My follow -up would
be Rear Window and then maybe Vertigo Psycho. Rob Larrick writes it. Rob often writes to us.
Thank you, Rob. Two thoughts he has on part one and two and two thoughts that are echoing some
things we've already said on here tonight. But Norman at the start of Psycho 2, you know what Norman
is at the start of Psycho 2. Perkins still gets you to sympathize with him.
Great performance. That is true and that is what sells the movie.
Absolutely.
And then also about part one, the degree to which Bernard Herman's score
elevated the horror is rivaled only by John Carpenter's score for Halloween.
I agree and I would also put the
the Anyomorakone Exorcist score
right there with it.
Let's see, here we go.
Brian Jepson writes, Brian Jepson. No Ray, just a Brian Jepson. No relation to
Carly Ray. Then not that I know of. All right. This is very interesting.
Christopher Walken was considered for Norman Bates for Psycho 2. Yeah, apparently
I read the Wikipedia on it and Anthony Perkins passed on Psycho 2. He was like,
No, like why would we do this again? They're like, okay, we're going to recast it. They got very close to signing Chris for walking because the group was so good
and
Perkins was like, okay, I'll do it
He thought they would maybe call his bluff
Wow
Do you think Chris for walking would have been an incredible length of work? It would have been great
I prefer having the consistency of the same actor because Perkins is a truly great actor
Perkins was awesome in Psycho 2. Yeah, he directed 3, I believe
It would have been two distracting I think to have yeah, I have another actor in there
Did either this comes from Eric Lamora did either of you see Hitchcock if so is it worth of viewing absolutely worth of viewing. Yeah, it was fun
Anthony Hopkins was great as Hitchcock Helen Mirin was great as
Mrs. Hitchcock. I can't remember what her first name is
Well, that's a sister's name. I don't know. It's great. I would also see the girl which is the one with Toby Jones as Hitchcock
Unfortunately, the girl basically serves as not intentionally, but it's essentially
a sequel to Hitchcock, because Hitchcock's about the making of Psycho, the girls about
the making of the birds, which was the follow -up.
Hitchcock portrays some of the darker sides of Alfred Hitchcock, the girl goes all in.
I didn't see the girl, I liked Hitchcock.
It's a great movie, but it's one of those biopics where you're like, okay, well, I hate
this guy now, right? Cunningham Holman wrote, so I'm sad for you,
that you had to sit through two. Cunningham. We couldn't disagree more.
This whole podcast episode has been in praise of two. Finally,
Super LB Stowe writes, your rap music sucks like your entire career.
Now, off topic, but who was that for? Super LB Stowe.
This is about to you. Yeah, which means he's named himself after the
The Rob Zombie movie, the adventures of Elb,
what is that, McCartoon?
I don't want that.
But do you have a rap career that I'm unaware of?
I used to do rap music when I was younger.
Oh, so they're just taking a shit on you.
Yeah, so we're gonna go ahead
just do a block on that guy.
Okay.
Why not?
You know, what's his name is deplorable beasto?
Oh God.
Well, if he's saying he's deplorable,
he's a Trump supporter.
Anyway.
right. That's the discussion. Let's get to this final segment, Patty. Alright. Joe told
me about this new segment we're doing about 10 seconds before the show started, so I'm
going to let him handle it. It was just an idea. I just thought it'd be fun as a quick
segment at the end of each episode to select our favorite harsh review from Rotten Tomatoes,
It's a contemporary harsh review of a movie
that's playing in theaters right now,
because some of them are really, really funny.
The movie I'm picking is keeping up with the Joneses.
I'm a fan of many of the people in the film.
I think the film looks deplorable to use that word again.
I hate that the billboard for it says license to kill
and license to chill.
I mean, I am baffled by how a movie with those people in it
Can have not even a smile on the trailer. That's where I'm always kind of like well
You know, it's like daddy's home in theory. I want to see daddy's home
So you see a trailer for it and you're like wait a minute
If they couldn't get one funny moment to put in this trailer
I know what I need to know about daddy's home frankly and then I saw it and it was confirmed folks
So these okay, so these are the two I actually picked two for this because they just they're just so funny
The first one is from Bill's Abeary of the Village Voice.
I apologize if I'm reading it.
You read an actual review.
Yeah, yeah.
You take a bad review and you read it.
I thought you were looking at like customer reviews.
No, like top critic reviews.
They're just funny.
Okay.
I apologize if I said your name wrong.
But here's the review.
Even those of us with a soft spot for dumb, high -concept Hollywood comedies
might be outraged by the limp, unfunny, nothing burger.
Woo!
It is keeping up with the judges.
Yikes.
Nothing burger.
I've never heard that term before.
That's a guy looking to be shouted out on a podcast with that interview.
And then the second one, Alonzo Duraldi from the rap.
Did I say that right?
if I didn't apologize. This black hole of a film is a waste of this talented cruise time,
yes, but it's also a waste of the audiences offering no laughs, no ideas, no fresh perspectives,
comma, nothing, period. Wow. You know, Joe, it reminds me of a critique of a paper I wrote my junior year
of high school. And Mr. Mueller wrote back on my paper, you know, Patrick, having your
own opinion is one thing. But being wrong is just that dot, dot being wrong. And he
underlined being and wrong three times each. Very nice, very nice. You kidding me? Are
you going to do one? I don't have one ready because I was not prepared. But my favorite
All -time negative review of a movie I will give you that is Roger Ebritz review of the village
M. Night Shyamalan's the village
It's one of the funniest negative reviews ever written and I urge you to Google it and check it out. All right Pat. What are your plugs?
I got no plugs Joe. I'm doing great
Follow him on Twitter the Patrick wall at the Patrick wall. Fine Twitter Instagram
We're on iTunes, we're on Fangoria, hit those iTunes reviews, give us some nice ones if you have the time, we'd appreciate it.
I've got the new short story column out, story number four entitled our father just dropped some severe situations, that's available at Fangoria .com.
I'll be at the Galway Comedy Festival in Ireland. Halloween weekend, where we will be doing a live recording of We'll See You In Hell.
unfortunately Pat won't be with me but we've got Mr. Tom Rhodes sitting in as
co -host for that day. He's a legendary comedian. He's a wonderful man. So
Tom will be with us and we're going to talk about an Irish centric horror film
Leprechaun. Well I think actually we might do Bram Stoker's Dracula because a lot of
it was shot in Ireland apparently so we already did Leprechaun so we can't. But I
And then the New York Comedy Festival,
if you're in New York, all of the first two weeks of November,
I have shows out there.
The big one for me, though, is November 3rd,
Gotham Comedy Club, headlining that night doing new material,
because I just shot the hour, and it's time to start rebuilding.
Thank you again to everybody that came out for that.
That was really wonderful of you.
I appreciate it.
And Joderosa Comedy.
This has been a podcast produced by the Fingoria Podcast Network.
You want to know the names of our producers?
It's time to fail.
An executive producer is Ken Hanley of Fingoria Entertainment.
For press opportunities, advertising, increase information about this show and other shows
contact Ken at Fingoria.
What is it, Com?
Yeah, Com.
Okay.
Dot Gov.
Yeah.
All right.
Thanks, folks.
Thanks folks, happy Halloween!