I'll see you in hell.
When the shine of your screams
becomes a thing on my dreams
you know I say, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
you got this new Queen's the Stone Age album, you and I were talking about live from the Catecombs and they're doing a series of performances around the country with alternate arrangements of their songs which can be great and can also suck. I'm also about to go see yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, do that with an orchestra and generally I'd rather your rock quite frankly, I don't need the Metallica with Lou Reed and an orchestra and bullshit. Yeah. But Queen's are a favorite band and I'm very open to
whatever they bring me and a band like that or the strokes or a great rock band at the sphere I think would be pretty amazing but we'll never get it. I don't know.
Insane orchestra thing I've seen and it was the and I'm happy for them. It's it's a cool milestone and it speaks to their prowess as a music group. But the Cypress Hill with the orchestra. It's like guys. It's a gangster rep. I don't want to see B. Real in a tuxedo.
With like a martini wrapping over a string section like I like I want it I want it to be rowdy. It's a mod it's a Priscilla. Yeah, yeah, they're all doing that. Well, Wu Tang did their final shows here in LA. I almost went but I've seen them so many times. Yeah, I get to this this point now where I'm like, oh, I got to go see X fill in the blank although X is a band I've seen 15 times.
And I'm just kind of like maybe I went too much when I was younger I don't get excited anymore. I'm reaching to be honest a scary place. There was a whole South Park about it where you hit an age in your 40s where everything sucks.
And I was like, I'll never be like that but my God. I have to really battle to keep a positive outlook on things I don't like anything I'm seeing or hearing and it's not good. It's not good.
Yeah, well, it's I think that just sort of malaise that everybody's feeling. Yeah, yeah, not alone. Yeah, it's a massive. We're all suffering from a, you know, common psychosis at this point. It's kind of hard to not filter everything through that even subconsciously. Yeah. And just sort of sit back but also to the just that I don't know, man, the older you get.
It's already bad enough that the older you get the more you know the tricks and the ins and outs and it makes things less enjoyable because you know when you're getting gouged on money and you know when you're getting taken for a ride all these things become more and more aware of with each passing day.
And then you combine that with, as I said, the universal psychosis that everybody's suffering and then you combine that with the drop in quality of everything. It's kind of hard to just enjoy anything anymore.
It absolutely is. I get a, a no every day. I'm taking out two very high profile pitches with high profile people attached and hearing things like here's a, here's a direct quote.
This was a pitch that made both the people we were pitching to in the pitch meeting. Cry. Okay. Cry.
Obviously we loved it. You saw how moved we were by it. How excited we were about it. We waited for two weeks and then the answer was at the end of the day. It's just a whole new world, unfortunately, in television. And it didn't feel global enough.
Now yesterday's no was look, I hate to say it. If you had Gerard Butler in a plane, we would have made the thing.
This project has nothing to do with Gerard Butler or a plane. You're just like, what?
So what, what am I supposed to even take away from that? I was complaining to my manager this morning and she goes, pap, Amy Polar just sold a show with Michael sure who sells the show every week.
Because that was the third pilot this year that Amy, Amy Polar has taken out and it got passed on by all networks. So imagine your Amy Polar going into NBC, where you are.
The Queen of SNL for 10 years, then the Queen of Parks and Rec for six years. Everyone still loves you.
And you can't sell a show to NBC. So then where I start spiraling and why I have been having some rough mornings of late is I'm like, I wake up in a panic. I'm like, what point is there of me taking out a show with no Amy Polar?
At that point, it's like, well, then none of us have a shot. Yeah. Like what you used to say was like, God, I could sell this thing if I could just attach some big star like Amy Polar. It doesn't nothing matters anymore. So it's dodgy. It's tricky. It's a horrible time.
But you know, I think talking to people helps because at least everybody is going through it. So don't assume you're alone. I make that mistake sometimes. I'd be like, God, why can't I feel better? Why can't I not be in such a bad mood all day? Why do I feel so down? And as soon as you talk to five friends, you realize all five of them feel the exact same way.
You know, improve your mood necessarily, but it makes it a little easier to deal with.
Well, I would say that the issue for me is I hear you on, you know, as I said here, talking about, you know, the, the, the, the psychotic ties that bind.
The problem is is the, the, the, the stuff that's causing us all to feel like this is in and of itself isolating. So it's hard to stay in the zone of, well, I'm not alone. We're all kind of dealing with this because you are in a position every day where you feel like an outsider because of insane tribalism at this point.
I said, I'm talking to a friend of mine. I go, do you realize we're witnessing for the first time in history, a president who is being booed as own rallies, like his own fans are booing him. Like, what the fuck is going on? You know, I'm watching Tucker Carlson chew up.
What's this? What's the guy? Yeah, it was right. Yeah, Ted Cruz. And you're like, wait, wait, do I, am I, do I like Tucker Carlson? What the fuck is happening?
Well, there, there's such an assortment of Dick Tracy villains running Washington that the former people you used to hate look better. They look like heroes now.
We're just, we're just up for sale to the highest bidder. I mean, I, in addition to everybody else's career anxiety or in your case, Joe, a dose of relationship anxiety and a dose of family illness anxiety, all the worst kinds you can have.
Then we also, and we all kind of joke about it and smile about it. We could be bombed any second. And as I've been saying on this show, why haven't we been?
There's no one, there's no one to wake at the wheel.
Bommas, like I keep waiting. There's a whole, and it tells you where my mindset with these tic-tocks because the ones I get are like, imagine you're out, you're playing with your dog and this video guy and his cute dog or whatever.
And then him and the dog look up and the sky fills with bright white light. You seen these tic-tocks. I don't look at tic-tock at all.
People with their, with their $10 budget showing you what it might look like when we all die of a nuclear bomb. Like, yeah, I think if this is where people's creativity is bringing their minds, we're not doing well.
Well, last time I looked at tic-tock on purpose. Yeah, it was amidst one of my many epic dragings by a group of people I pissed off. But when the nurses, this couple of years ago, and I got the nurses all mad at me.
But my phone, but I was never, remember this very clearly. I was at the stand. I talk about it in the special. I was at the stand waiting to go on stage. And I was aware that the nurses were mad at me, but I was not aware to anywhere near the degree that it was happening.
And my phone buzzed and I pulled my phone out and it was a text from Emily, our matriarch. Yes. And she said, uh, do you, do you, have you been on tic-tock tonight? And I said, no, and she said, don't go on it. Yeah. You're going viral in the bad way right now. And I was like, yeah, wait, what?
So your criticism was that nurses don't do shit, right? No, I made a joke that some nurses, uh, the watch the special, you'll see. I've seen it and I remember it. I just don't know you. I just mean the audience. Listen, I don't want to.
Um, but it was a joke. Uh, you know, if, if you ever get into that situation with nurses again, you can hit them with this fact by a considerable margin.
The profession that cheats the most on their partner is nurses. Oh, I'm not surprised. There's like not even a close second.
The reason I say I'm not surprised is not as a shot at nurses. When you work those hours and you're in close quarters all the time with other people, I'd imagine it gets very hard to stay in the bounds of your relationship at times. And if you're having problems at home or whatever, it's probably a really easy opportunity to cheat, you know, uh, I would say,
certainly if Grayson, Adam, he has any indication for the last 68 years that's been on. They fuck all the time on that show. And I guess you're right. It's probably doctors, fucking nurses, fucking nurses, fucking doctors as opposed to patients. I was kind of like, is it that you're saying turn your head and cough, but while I've got you. Nice piece, but that's probably not happening so much.
I don't think so. Yeah, I think we know a lot. We'd hear a lot more stories of guys being like, I fucked my nurse. You know, guys wouldn't be able to keep that quiet. No, no, of course not. Yeah, my ex was telling me a story wants about some 99% of her patients were females with genital issues or STDs or pregnancy or whatever, you know, plants or plant parenthood. And it'd be the occasional dude.
And she told me about it the first time about and I was like, I was kind of like, I don't know if I love hearing stories of you handling dudes, don't know if you gotta tell me those stories.
And she was like, well, just know that if I'm ever holding a penis, it is covered in sores and legions. And I'm like, you're right, that helps quite a bit. Thank you.
But um, you got now. Yeah, we've all got our thing. Let's hit the corn.
That's sweet old movie call. Yeah, butter it up and suck it down. Well, I would
be in ship. Me too. We were going to do this. We both watch this movie. I was going to suggest this. We both watch this movie. I don't think we're going to do it on the pod. I put it into my corner for today. But should we just discuss the damned as our number one in the corner. We can just talk about it and then move on.
I have not seen the damned. Oh, all right. Well, then maybe I'll hold off on it. I've seen everything that we floated as potentially doing an episode on except the damned, whereas I think you've only seen the damned. Yeah, which I don't think we ever agreed to do an episode.
Well, you you started off. Oh, okay, I'll start one off. I did. Well, I watched graveyard shift.
I bought some of these keynote Lorber 4Ks when they went on sale, including gambling on some movies I had never seen. And in every case thus far, I have immediately flipped the 4K and resold it on Amazon after reviewing.
First was what's the one? Oh, a body parts, which I enjoyed actually, but not enough to own. And then graveyard shift for me was a real let down. Joe said it kind of had a sweet spot.
Probably because he saw it when he was a younger man. But it's it's not much. I know I've read the Stephen King story. I didn't recall it.
I always thought this was a movie about killer rats, you know, and there are rat based scares. It's a guy, a drifter. He needs a job. He he starts working at a like a textile factory. And he's working the graveyard shift, meaning overnight.
He's supposed to clean out the basement, which is swarming with rats. Yeah. So you're watching it. And I'm like, cool, you know, like we actually haven't had a lot of rat horror. There's willered and then and that. But like awesome because rats don't scare me, but they give me that.
So it's like a rat nephobia. I like that kind of fun, almost like a PG 13 thrill ride scare. I like it. But much to my surprise graveyard shift is actually about a large swamp monster who also lives down there in addition to the rats and kills people.
It's supposed to be a mutated rat like in the book or in the story. Yeah, it's like a mutated rat that has grown to I don't know it's got fucking wings or something. I don't remember. But that that's that monster at the end of the movie is supposed to be some sort of rat related mutation.
I think the film is a is a I didn't see it when I was young. I saw it at about 40. Oh, and hated it. But then it was a movie that I would keep returning to it was streaming and at the time.
I just kept returning to it on like those like hungover Sundays when it was raining outside and I needed to put something on where I didn't want to think.
But I wanted a horror movie and I was like I might fall asleep because I'm hungover. Yeah. So graveyard shift became one of those movies that I would go to for that.
And over time, I it just became a comfort comfort food for me. Sure. I think personally, it's it's almost worth the price of admission just for the Brad Dorif performance as the exterminator who's always.
He don't get enough of this in movies anymore. The guy that's chewing so much tobacco that it looks like he has a tumor in his lip from the wild and Dorif is the high point of body parts and this movie.
And he's spitting constantly streams of brown. Yeah, as he talks.
Yeah, this was a great era for Dorif. He was working a lot. I mean, I don't know if he was thrilled about it. I mean, the guy we first see him and like, fuck it. One flow over the kukus nest, one of the all time great supporting performances. He still makes me cry.
But tonight I can think about that movie and tear up. But yeah, once he hit Chuck E. It just became this like he was doing horror supporting roles. And that's about it. He's great in all of them.
His high point, of course, is in the movie that brought Joe and I together the extra sister's part three. But I love him. And I he was on deadwood as well with Jeff Jones.
But we don't get enough Dorif lately. I must say at least I don't see him. Well, he's you know, he's doing the the Chuck E show, which is a hit. Oh, yeah, that's right. And I mean, I'm happy for that guy. He is he's a Robert England. He's another guy who's a great actor.
Yeah. And has is always really good in whatever he's doing. But really stumbled into a nice pile of shit with becoming a horror icon. But he, what's great about him in graveyard shift.
You know, I'm pretty sure everybody on that set. Nobody thought they were making, you know, fucking Shakespeare and love or whatever.
Well, he, but he gives it as all man, like God, the guy you can see that he probably had notebooks filled with the backstory that he wrote of this exterminator.
He comes in. There's a physicality. There's a voice. The man here is everything. He's just, he just dissolves or evaporate or disappears, excuse me into the character.
And I, I tip my hat to a guy that does that, like just sees everything as an opportunity, you know, agreed. And he's only 75. So I hope we haven't seen the last of him. I think he's the kind of guy who could get some, you know, if Guillermo del Toro had him play Renfield in this, he won't because it's going to be probably the guy who played Elvis.
So other hunk Renfield's not in Frankenstein, which would be another issue.
But couldn't we do a Frankenstein meets Dracula type of vibe. Maybe we bring in Abedon Castello. I'm just throwing stuff out.
No, I agree. He's a great character actor. I'm a big fan of Dorif. And yeah, I also, we mentioned this just in a, in a why did you tell him to do what he did.
You guys aware I was not that Ed Gale, the, the little person who portrayed both Howard the duck and Chuckie and the suit is a noted pedophile as well.
Yeah. And there's that wild interview he did before he died where he's got the oxygen tank hooked up to his nose with the little tube. And he's literally just like, yeah, yeah, it was 14 and I wanted to have sex with him. Like he's like saying, he's not even saying it like I made mistakes.
He's saying it just like, yeah, what do you want for me? You're like, this is insane. I haven't seen that particular interview, but I've seen another one where he's kind of in better health. And he's saying the same thing. He's like every time they asked somebody in one of these pedophile videos.
Like what, what was it going to hook up with? I mean, I just wanted to talk to them or whatever. This guy first question. He's like, yeah, I was planning on having sex with him.
I wasn't that clear from the messages. I don't know. I don't know what was going on there. The guy did also didn't seem to be unwel mentally.
He was just like, do you have a fucking problem with me trying to sleep with a child? Do you have a problem? It was like, yeah, we do.
I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean
Well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well
well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well