🎵 I'll see you in hell. I'll see you in hell. And when the sound of your screams becomes a thing of my dreams, you know I'll say. I'll see you in hell. You know I will. I'll see you in hell. You know I will. 🎵
We're talking apartment 7A, which I have called apartment 2A. I've called it every number to Patent Text Messages. I couldn't remember the apartment number.
I didn't correct you. I let you go.
Thank you. And then also Rosemary's babe.
Rosemary. How's your baby doing, babe?
I wanted to say, which I didn't get a chance to say last episode, I told Joe off the mic, but wanted to say publicly.
We were talking about Joe's stand -up and how he didn't get on Netflix or Hulu and was frustrated. Well, fuck that, I say.
I listened to every one of Joe's albums. I had heard some, of course, and been to some of the tapings and so forth.
But one of the many, many beauties of the streaming era, which has its problems too, but one of the many things I love to do in this modern streaming era is listen to all of a band's albums in a day.
Their entire filmography. I do the same with stand -ups. And I did it with Joe while I was doing an overhaul of my movie and vinyl inventory one day.
It took like 18 hours. I listened to every stand -up album Joe's ever recorded, and I laughed and laughed and laughed and laughed.
Well, Jesus, thank you, man.
One of the best to do with Joe, easily. I laughed the whole time. I never felt like I'm getting tired of Joe. I just kept listening to the bits and enjoying and laughing.
And if you've never heard Joe stand -up, go all the way back to the start because it's all good.
I am without words. When you texted me that, it meant the world to me. It means the world to me coming from you.
You hopefully know my tremendous admiration for you as a writer. And as I say to many, many, many people in my life, the funniest guy I know is Pat Walsh.
My God Almighty. The guy is so funny. You're a guy that I'll quote your tweets, your exes, whatever the fuck they're called now, to other people that have never met you.
And watching the other people laugh hysterically brings me great joy. So that's high praise coming from you and also too that you're one of my best friends.
That means a lot to me, man. And that's an endurance test that I could not sit through. So hats off to you there. Thank you very much, man. I appreciate it.
Of course. Did not need you to come back at me, but I appreciate that as well.
Also, important to make note, I don't know if you noticed, for those of you that can't see us, I had to look at the ground the entire time I said that because I can't have an emotional connection with a human being.
I did the same thing and was thinking, Pat, this is pathetic. I'm 44. And that entire time I was talking to you, I was looking at my shoe.
It's just pathetic. We could do it. We can actually say something emotional once a year, but we have to stare at our shoes.
That's pathetic.
That's all right.
Quick update on my life, folks. I was robbed this week. I went to get a massage at 4 p .m.
I've been lifting a lot. I'm sore. I am gone as a 90 minute massage. So I was gone roughly two hours.
And I come home, I open the garage door and the door from my garage into my home is wide open and propped open, which I've never done before.
So I was like, oh, fuck, somebody's in my house. I don't hear anything. I walked through very cautiously, but it was very scary.
Basically, what happened is I have a deck behind my house. These guys jumped up on the back deck, shattered the glass window to my bedroom, came into the house and ran around as according to the cop looking for cash or jewels, which I have neither in the house.
So they emptied every drawer, every cabinet, everything that was put away in my house was dumped out onto the floor, completely ransacked. It looked like a dump.
The only thing they didn't touch, thank God, was my massive movie collection and vinyl collection left on its shelves.
But other than that, they were great because when I was telling pigstow what happened, I was like, I was like, dude, you think I got a lot of movies. If they threw all his movies on the ground like Jesus Christ, I'm happy to hear they didn't do that. Jesus.
These guys, it was weirdly like a best case scenario robbery. They threw hundreds of books on the floor, but I was like, you know what, it's about time for me to reorganize my book collection.
You know, like the movies and vinyl were are always exactly how I want them and they left them. It's almost like they thought, oh, this guy put a lot of work into that collection. Let's leave it alone.
Everything else ripped apart two days later, three days later. Still, the only thing I have found that was stolen was my wedding ring, which no comment, but obviously I was not getting any more use out of that.
And men, they tell men to spend three times three months of full salary on a wedding ring, three full months of your salary. Women spend 500 to $1 ,000 on a man's wedding ring. Honestly, that's that's the cappers like $1 ,500.
So I think my wedding ring, which was really cool. It was gold with black diamonds. So very unusual, but I think it was $1 ,200 and that's my one loss. And as the cop said, that's such a weird ring. It might show up in a pawn shop. It might help.
Um, it was scary though. People being in my house. I went to the guy across the street who had a ring cam and he showed me, we watched for two hours. This car drove pat back and forth in front of my house five times. Yeah.
There's so many people working like construction workers in my neighborhood that I think somebody probably just called a friend and was like, he's leaving. I think that's what happened.
Um, we watched the ring cam. They parked, they put on gloves, they ran in the house. You couldn't make out their faces. You couldn't make out the license plate. The cop, I was like, you guys can't do CSI shit on this. The car's right there. You can't zoom it. They couldn't see the plate.
No, that drives me nuts in all those movies when it's like, and they, I'm like, give me a break. Well, here's the thing that I'm like, we have the perpetrators on camera and there's nothing we can do. It made me question why I have an alarm system, why people have cameras on their house, why you have anything.
The other thing they did was, and this is what really fucked me and Joe over over the last couple of days is they yanked my internet system out of the wall and threw it in the toilet because I think they thought that would disengage my alarm system and my cameras.
And all it did was fuck up my wifi for several days. So I've had a guy trying to fix it and we can't. So yesterday we finally made the connection that they probably cut some wires outside as well.
But they're going to completely get away with it. You know, the cop was like, yeah, you know, insurance might pay for the door. They might not. The ring, maybe, but maybe not. But we're never going to catch them. It's like that Lebowski thing is like, do you have any leads?
And he's like leads starts laughing. It's like, yeah, they know there's nothing they can do. So why wouldn't you keep robbing? You know, yeah, I asked this all the time in a way darker, way darker question.
90 % of people get away with sexual assault. Like, why is anyone having second thoughts about doing it? If you're if you're a criminal, you know, it's terrible. It's terrible people.
The law favors the guilty far more than we would like to think it does. It's terrible. When I got robbed is the same thing. Guy wore. I mean, it was comical. I was laughing about it. The guy used my suitcases to fill them up with my stuff and then stole one of my hats, put it over his face so he could walk out of the lobby discreetly with my suitcases.
The way they found him was this is one of the good things about New York.
There are cameras everywhere in New York. Yeah. So they found him. They picked him up on another camera. They went to all the local stores and they figured out who it was.
But yeah, it's terrible. It's a terrible feeling. I hope that it doesn't ruin your experience of living in your home because it's a very violating thing. And I hope that you're able to get past it. But I'm sorry you went through that.
I'm past it. It shook me up. The reason I was so kind of nonchalant about it was because I looked around. I'm like, okay, they left my VR system. The thing we got over the pandemic. What is that called?
Oh, Oculus.
Oculus Rift. They left that. They left 4K player. I think they unplugged my PlayStation then realized it was a 4 and left it. They left my TV. Granted, you're not going to jump off a deck and run out to your car carrying a TV. I guess that's the reason.
But there's so much stuff they could have shoved down their pants. They didn't take a movie. They didn't take a record, at least not one that I've seen.
And then I'm out talking to the cop and my heart stopped because I went, my fucking laptop. And I ran inside and it was just sitting on the couch. They ran right past it. And I get it. You can find my iPhone and it's an easy way to get caught.
But goddamn, my laptop had nine projects on it that I haven't backed up. So now I've got to back them up. It was kind of a good wake up call. You can feel too safe sometimes. And now I definitely don't.
I'm also not going to set my alarm only at night. I'm going to set it every time I leave the house. It sucks. This happened in broad daylight.
But as people get more and more broke and more desperate, there's only going to be more of it. So I just hope these guys are reporting to their friends, hey, this guy has nothing of value.
That's also to all the devices and stuff that's in the big picture. That's all kind of chicken shit money. You're going to get 300 bucks for a PS5. You're going to get whatever. The laptop, like you said, is dangerous.
There's a lot of reasons they probably didn't take that stuff. The movies forget it. It's worthless. They're not going to start an eBay store.
They're up at Amoeba talking to that guy with the black Afro with the gray hair. And he's like, look, I can do $1 .50 maybe on this pile.
Yeah. It's a tough thing, man. I'm sorry you went through that. It just sucks.
It sucks. It does. But it's over.
At least my house looks like a crack den now with a giant block of wood over the door.
You can use this bit, by the way, if you want. You say, folks, I live in Hollywood and I was robbed, or as we like to call it, snubbed.
That's good. I like it. I like it. That's good for like a Conan monologue at the Oscars. I think you could do that.
Anyway, so yeah, it's sort of a shitty week, but we're glad we got to record.
We were wondering if this was going to have to be the first month where we were like, we're not going to get you a couple of episodes, but we did it.
We did it, ladies and gentlemen. Yeah, we were down to the wire.
We're sitting here recording now as I have to get up to New York, which is never an easy drive from Pennsylvania, especially on a Saturday as everybody on Earth is going into the city to party.
But we're down to the wire. I was like, dude, I got to be on stage in New York at like 7 p .m.
Because of the time difference, we can only record so early. Pat can't record at 5 a .m. his time.
We got it done, though, but the backup I think would have been, and I'm happy it didn't come to this.
If we hadn't for and by the way, when I'm in New York, I'm not going to be able to record.
It's not like I can go and just record. I'm literally slammed morning till night with obligations up there.
So I was just like thinking about it and I was like, well, if it got to the point where we literally couldn't get the episodes done, I guess we would have just done six next month.
To make up for the two that didn't happen, but it didn't happen and hasn't happened yet.
And you're a sport and a champ for weathering this and persevering and figuring out a way to get to somebody else's place so you could record.
You could have easily thrown your hands up and just said, hey, dude.
Well, I felt bad, but also, and I'll have to look at my shoes again for this one, but I was noticing as we were navigating this situation because I felt bad, even though I knew deep down it was out of my control.
I didn't try to get robbed and then the guy who came to get my internet fucked up and he couldn't fix it and blah, blah, blah.
But yeah, just just Joe and I is texting about this was a lot more respectful and kind than it would have been five years ago.
Wouldn't you agree, Joe? Yeah, it was great. You were like, but you in particular, it was like this isn't your fault.
And I was like, you're right. It's not. Thank you, Joe.
What are you going to do? We were both frustrated because the internet.
So what happened was we were supposed to record today, Saturday.
We were supposed to record Thursday.
And then this happened.
And then Pat was like the internet.
And by the way, the internet guy, meaning he had to have a specialist come because he's got an Eros system.
And so it wasn't like a technician from Spectrum who was available, could just come out and replace the thing and leave.
It was a lot more complicated than that, unfortunately.
But you needed this specialist to come out.
The guy was supposed to come Thursday, then he couldn't come Thursday.
You know, like he's coming Friday.
He's supposed to be there early.
He kept getting later and later.
Then when he was there, it was a lot of like, we'll be good to go in five minutes.
Then the guy left and the internet didn't work.
It was a lot of back and forth.
We were both frustrated.
But I also knew like, this is not, Pat did not get robbed.
You know, this is not somebody being careless.
This is like a shit situation.
And I appreciate you for, you know, despite what you were dealing with, also being respectful of the fact that I was like, it was a lot of stop start on my end or whatever.
And you didn't need to be.
And I appreciate that you were.
So thank you.
Thank you.
I came here early this morning.
And then she was like, like going to chill on the bed and read a book.
I was like, oh, no, I'm sorry.
You have to leave.
I'm not going to be able to talk freely for two hours.
And she's like, oh, you're throwing me out of my apartment.
I mean, it was a bad situation all around, but she'll be fine.
It was raining and no, on top of everything else, she's like, all right, I guess I'll go out in the rain.
Yeah, it's raining here, too.
It's raining in the city, whatever.
It's all going to be fine.
I get before we move on, what was I going to say?
Oh, this is too funny.
I was laughing so hard at this and I hope it translates.
It's a quick little story.
But I remember at least five years ago telling a couple of stories about my AV guy.
I had one AV guy who came drunk.
Remember that story?
And he was like breaking tables and shit.
And then I got this new guy who is good, but he had tears in his eyes when he couldn't fix the internet.
He's a little slow.
He's a big, very fat Armenian guy and he's slow.
And his parents are his assistants.
His elderly Armenian parents come with him and he'll go like, mom, Ethernet cable.
And she gives him Ethernet cable, whatever.
They are such characters.
He's not mentally fully there, but he's a savant with electronics.
So when he got there late, his reason was he said, he goes, I'm sorry, I am not a wealthy man.
I had a job, a $50 ,000 job and your job is probably $200.
I could not leave for your $200.
I'm like, I understand, man, I understand.
But it was Gary Doberman, who's the producer of It, which I thought was kind of interesting.
He's a big, big horror producer.
He talked about him at length.
But this guy, since he's a little autistic, he's probably my age, but he's obsessed with the movie Gladiator,
which was also the case of Joey Pants on The Sopranos.
He had an obsession with Gladiator, which I always loved that character trait.
But when he came to my house and was setting up my new 4K player, he's like, well, let's pick out one of your movies.
Oh, good. You have Gladiator.
And then he talked to me for hours until I said, am I being charged by the hour man?
He goes, oh, everything I've been saying about Gladiator, you will not be charged for.
I just love talking about Gladiator.
We just kept talking and talking about Gladiator.
So the second time he came out to do some tune -ups and he's looking at my Blu -ray wall and he goes,
oh, have you seen this? Have you seen this lately?
And he holds up Gladiator and I go, yeah, I've seen it.
And he goes, but lately this movie and he starts going in about Gladiator again.
So this time he comes and we're trying out my Apple TV and he goes to Netflix in a few places and it's working
because it would work for five minutes at a time and then crash.
And he's looking around and he goes into Amazon Prime and he's like,
so let's just pick a movie at random here and see if it works.
And I started laughing before he picked it because I saw in the top right corner,
Gladiator 2 was new on Amazon and he goes, oh, oh, perfect.
We've got Gladiator 2.
He goes to it and starts talking about the problems with Gladiator 2.
I mean, the man is obsessed.
I love him.
If you live in LA and need an AV guy, hit me up.
Also, somebody told me my address was on my Amazon page.
I've been signing a lot of stuff for people and sending them out on Amazon.
That deal is going away at the end of the weekend because now that my house is a target,
I'm not going to have my address available for people to find online.
So if you want me to sign something for you, that promotion is ending, let's say, end of the month.
Thank you. Joe?
Speaking of Gladiator 2, I haven't seen it, but somebody said something to me about Gladiator 2.
It was one of the most insane comments I've ever heard a person say about a movie.
And it was insane because I was like, that's what I would have said 10 years ago about a movie.
And I get now why people looked at me like I was crazy.
But my friend Becky, and she's obsessed with Gladiator 1, and Hans Zimmer, I believe, did the score for Gladiator 1.
And she said, I can't believe he didn't do the score for Gladiator 2.
They ruined that movie by not having him do the score.
And I said, oh, I haven't seen it.
And she goes, I didn't see it.
I was like, well, it's a crazy statement to make.
And then she started laughing like, I know that sounds insane.
I was like, all right, yeah. But I was like, I would have said that same thing 10 years ago.
I hate it. Have you seen it? No.
I feel like we've had that conversation many times on this show.
Gladiator 2, I think you and I were maybe going to do, so I never discussed it.
But if you were curious about what my thoughts on it were, it wasn't very good.
I love Denzel in it. And I think Paul Mascall is the best actor of his generation.
He was completely miscast and should not have been playing that part.
And there's no, I mean, Crowe dies in the first one, but there's no Crowe cameo like in a flashback or something?
No Crowe cameo. And I know he was very offended that they didn't reach out to him.
And then they asked Ridley Scott, hey, so like, you know, Russell Crowe was kind of bothered that he wasn't asked.
Why would he have been asked? He was so dismissive of him.
He was like, why would we have called him? What are you talking about?
Ridley, even if you feel that way, that's crazy.
Did you see the interview with Crowe where he's like, you know, he was like, I was in Greece.
I looked from a hotel balcony across the water at an island.
It's all kinds of fanfare going on. I didn't know what it was.
Turns out they were shooting Gladiator 2. I didn't even know they were making it.
And the guy's like, you didn't know they were making it? Like, are you in it?
And he's like, who gives a fuck?
So just classic Russell Crowe, like, just like, get out of my face, idiot.
There's no amount of age or wisdom that can keep you from being just a jealous little bitch.
Sometimes I do it all the time.
I do like Russell Crowe. He was so exciting when he came on the scene.
You remember that time, LA Confidential into Gladiator, it was like, holy shit, this guy.
Yeah, he was one of those guys where they were like, he's going to be our next De Niro or Bogart, whoever they made the comparisons to.
But I got to say, I think I prefer, this might be my favorite era of Crowe.
Like, I love fat drunk. Give me the paycheck. I'll play a priest again.
He was such a sex symbol that I never would have dreamed that he was going to become our Orson Welles, which is basically what he is.
Playing fat priest after fat priest. I'm into it, too.
I do hope he gets out of this direct to DVD ghetto at some point, but I'm a big fan.
Let's go to the corner, if we could. I only have two today.
Oh, you want me to go?
I was going to say, I don't have much of a theme here. You can go first. I don't care.
Very well. I watched a couple Preston Sturges movies. Sturges did Sullivan's Travels and a lot in The Criterion Collection, Palm Beach Story.
I considered one of the pioneers, one of the greats, the experts of the screwball comedy.
And I have a box set of his that, like a lot of my box sets, I had never opened in 25 years.
I popped it open. I was like, I want to see everything this guy's done.
And I watched a couple of really charming early movies of his. One is The Great McGinty.
He wrote the screenplay. He went into the studio. He said, you can pay me $1 for this screenplay if you let me direct it.
And they did. And very much the Rocky thing, just like the only way you're going to make this movie is if you let me direct it.
They ultimately did not let Stallone direct that movie, but they did let Preston Sturges.
And it's great. It got nominated for an Oscar for Best Screenplay and led to great success for him.
And I always loved those stories of somebody taking a chance on him or herself.
It's really funny. 82 minutes, lightning fast screwball comedy dialogue, character actors out the ass.
I love these old black and white movies, all the old like, you scoundrel, you scallywag.
That's always fun watching that shit. It's a very funny movie.
Basically, it's a guy who helps, and it was timely.
He gets hired by a politician to go out and vote falsely, vote for him.
And he says, I'll pay you $10 if you go do this. And he does it 37 times.
He votes falsely 37 times, so he gets a big check.
And he's such a likable guy that they wind up putting, you know, it's the classic Capra thing.
He becomes a politician himself, and he's like, yeah, I'll just keep being a scumbag.
And then he winds up, they pair him up with a woman because no politician can be successful without a wife by his side.
And his fake wife starts being like, I think you can do better.
You know, I don't think you got to be a piece of shit to be a politician.
So, you know, it's a little, it's a little corny, a little kind of like that.
We can even the common man can make a difference type movie, which is very much Preston Sturges, very much Frank Capra.
And it's a little corny in spots, but overall very funny old classic screwball comedy. Joe?
I rewatched all of the because I bought that Dirty Harry DVD set, the collectible one that I lucked out and got brand new at a half price books for $20.
But I rewatched all the Dirty Harry movies. I already talked about the first one.
The only sequel that I really think is worthwhile is the third movie, which is The Enforcer.
That's the one with Tyne Daly where she becomes the second one.
No, Magnum Force is the second one.
Magnum Force has the best intro because it's the camera zooming in on his hand, holding the Magnum.
Right. On like a, you know, blank background, whatever.
And he's doing a monologue about the force of the gun.
Like it's a great intro, but then the movie doesn't really deliver after that.
But The Enforcer is a good one.
And it's the logical sequel to the first one.
You know, he's pissed off in the first movie about getting a new partner.
There are some racial aspects to why he's aggravated about it.
That they play more for comedy than him being truly upset.
In the third movie, he's teamed up with a woman.
And it's because there's a almost DEI style movement happening in the police force.
Where they want to get more women on the street and he's pissed off about it because he's like, it's not about representation.
It's about, are you a good cop or not?
He gets paired up with Tyne Daly because his chief is spitefully doing so.
And he grows to really care about her.
And she is a great cop and it shows that he was wrong.
Which makes, spoiler alert, when she's killed at the end, an amazing moment in the movie.
It's heartbreaking. And you see a human side of Harry that you don't often get to see in these movies.
I forget who plays the villain in The Enforcer.
I'm going to look it up really quick.
I rewatched all five of those over the pandemic and I thought they were all pretty good.
I didn't, I think Bobby, or D. Varen Bookwalter, that's who it is.
He plays the killer and the killer in this one is a sniper.
He's killing people from a distance.
I disagree, I just, I couldn't.
The second one was like a sort of watered down revisit to me.
This third one got back into the themes that are challenging about the first one.
And it just had the grit and it just felt like a sequel to me.
The other ones, The Deadpool, Sudden Impact, and Magnum Force.
They just feel way more to me like it's Clint Eastwood playing a cop, but not necessarily Dirty Harry.
This felt like Dirty Harry to me. I really enjoyed it.
It made me sad that Gran Torino is not an official Dirty Harry sequel.
Because I was like, if that was the third official movie, that would be a perfect trilogy to me.
But then I actually read up again on Gran Torino.
And it was interesting because I found a lot of reviews that said this is not just a spiritual sequel enclosure to Dirty Harry.
It's also the closure to his stranger characters in all those westerns he played, or did.
He's the man against the town, you know, dealing with the threat.
And I was like, oh shit, I never thought of it like that.
So I think Gran Torino kind of serves as a closing piece to a lot of things that Eastwood did.
But I enjoyed The Enforcer. I thought it had more depth in a character sense than any of the other sequels.
And it's a fun watch, man. It's a good movie. It's a good entry.
I would recommend The Rookie as a movie that should have been a Dirty Harry and was considered to be a Dirty Harry.
But it's him and Charlie Sheen. Raul Julia is the villain.
Co -written by the guy who did Evil Dead 2.
Lots of really crazy set pieces in it. I really like The Rookie, which was really unfairly hated because I think it's as good as all the Dirty Harry sequels.
I watched another Preston Sturges, which was called Christmas in July.
This movie was 67 minutes long, ladies and gentlemen, and it told a coherent story and a romance, and it was very funny.
So I'm not sure why everything needs to be 230 these days, but I like this even more than The Great McGinty.
This was about an actor who I normally don't give a shit about, Dick Powell.
He plays an office clerk who enters all kinds of contests, very similar to Punch Drunk Love with the pudding points.
He's just a guy who loves entering contests.
He enters one where he's got to make up a slogan for a coffee company, and he makes this slogan that makes no sense, and everyone in his life tells him it makes no sense.
But his co -workers lie and tell him that he won.
And the theme of the movie is basically like, if you think you've got some money, and if you act like you've got some money, everyone will treat you as such and treat you with respect.
Great little theme, great little story, really, really funny movie with some funny performances, particularly this guy Raymond Walburn, who's been in a million old movies.
The Coen Brothers try to do this a lot with their screwball comedies, like just give you a lot of really funny, goofy characters in the background.
This Raymond Walburn stole the movie and is one of the funnier supporting performances I've ever seen in an old movie.
Sturges is great, a 67 -minute effective, hilarious comedy. You've got to really admire that, and it's 85 years old, so pretty fucking impressive.
Joe?
I guess my theme is movies about men that portray men in a way that men aren't often portrayed anymore.
Men that I'm sure a lot of modern women, these are movies they would cite as the problems with machismo.
And not to say there aren't problems with machismo, but these characters are a hell of a lot of fun to watch in a movie, even though they might be nightmares to deal with in real life.
But Tin Men, which is a movie I'd heard about.
Oh yeah, funny movie.
Oh, it's so funny, man. Barry Levinson directed it.
I had originally, the reason I watched it was because after I watched Get Shorty, it came up as a suggested title.
And I got confused. I thought for a second Barry Levinson directed Get Shorty, but that's Barry Sonnenfeld.
It was a great autobiography, by the way, with really funny stories about his time in Hollywood.
Nice. Levinson has directed a lot of great movies.
Did the Alto Nights with Robert De Niro in a dual role.
You know, I'm so bummed about that, man. It's like, if he didn't have that harebrained idea to cast De Niro in the dual role.
If that was De Niro in Pesci, you would have seen that trailer. You would have been like, I gotta go see this. This is fucking awesome.
And instead you're like, what is going on with this? I don't understand.
Anyway, Barry Levinson directed Tin Men. It stars Richard Dreyfuss and Danny DeVito and Barbara Hershey.
All of them excellent. But he also wrote this.
It takes place in 1963 in Baltimore, Maryland.
DeVito and Dreyfuss play tin salesmen who are technically competitors because they work at different companies.
And the movie is about their feud. But the feud is not over. This is such a weird premise.
They're not feuding because of the tin sales, the aluminum siding sales. That's what they do.
They're feuding because they get into a car accident in the beginning.
They both think it's the other guy's fault. And they're both such psychos. They're determined to get revenge on the other guy.
And it just so happens they work in the same industry as competitors.
But that never really comes into it outside of the fact that they're dealing with the same plight in their industry,
which is this federal investigation about basically fraudulent sales of aluminum siding.
That really happened. That was a real thing.
Anyway, it's everything you want out of DeVito and Dreyfuss in a movie.
Dreyfuss is playing an unhinged, just manic lunatic in this movie.
And DeVito is playing a charming nut job.
It's Dreyfuss freaking out and having meltdowns in every scene.
And it's DeVito being explosive. It's what you want out of both of these guys as actors.
It is so funny. And it has a tremendous amount of heart and takes a really nice dramatic turn in the third act.
I immediately, I couldn't stop talking about it. I watched it once and I was like, I talked about it for days.
Days and days. Patton Oswalt, not to name drop, but Patton Oswalt and I text a lot about movies.
And I texted him and I was like, have you seen Tin Men, dude? I never saw it. I'm obsessed with it.
He's like, I love that movie. And started immediately, this is what's fun about texting about movies, he'll start sending you all these facts about the movie.
Like you can't stump him on anything. And it was just cool. And then I texted you about it as well and you're like, I love that movie.
And I was like, okay.
Mahoney by the way.
Oh yeah, that's right. Mahoney by the way, playing a very charming, endearing guy and is doing so many things in his character that he did on Frasier.
So it was fun for me. There were so many similarities. It was fun for me to watch and kind of in my head pretend that it was a younger version of that character or whatever.
But anyway, I immediately tried to buy it and it's never been released on Blu -ray, let alone 4K and the DVD of it is like $25.
I own the DVD and I could send it to you, I guess. But if it's streaming, I guess you don't need it.
Yeah, it's a great, great movie and I'm a fan. I'm going to re -watch it today, I think. It's been 30 years since I've seen that movie.
Levinson, you've seen Diner, right?
You know, I'm embarrassed to admit I've never seen Diner.
Joe, you in particular would love Diner. That should be your next watch.
All right, I'm going to pull it up here.
But all those Touchstone movies, Touchstone was when Disney decided they were going to start making adult comedies.
They'd make like three adult comedies a year and they had a lot of good ones.
None of them are available to be found on Blu -ray for whatever reason, so there's got to be some sort of rights thing.
It's like they did Outrageous Fortune with Shelly Long, Big Business, Stakeout. They did all kinds of movies, Touchstone.
And they're all impossible to find.
I think -
Any hoot.
Pardon me. I think Tin Men is well worth the $24 asking price. The only reason I don't want to buy it is because this is Pinkstone heavy this week.
I was talking to Pinkstone and I was like, I was bitching about the Night Gallery Blu -rays being so expensive.
Because they only have the DVDs. And I was like, I'm not doing it, man. I'm not doing it.
The second I buy those goddamn Blu -rays, they're going to announce a 4K.
And I was like, I purchased these things and a light goes off in a factory. And they're like, all right, boys, we're back in business. Let's go.
So I feel like that with Diner, I'm like, I mean, with Tin Men, I'm like, this is going to get some kind of goddamn release.
Keno Lorber or something is going to re -release it. And I'm just going to wait. I'm going to try to wait this out.
Especially with it on streaming. Why not? Sometimes you really can't find something. But if it's there, that's good enough for now.
It is a lost movie. It totally fell through the cracks, which is weird.
My last one or have I done three? I have not.
No, this is your third.
I'll just be quick because I'm at my girlfriend's place. I walked in here and she had Frasier paused on the TV.
It's her favorite show of all time, much like Joe. If I'm at her place, Frasier tends to be on.
Love it.
Her, you know, yeah, she's obsessed.
And I, of course, have seen the show many times. I started a rewatch briefly during the pandemic that I abandoned, but I am now committed to doing a full rewatch of Frasier.
Crane Shots might start making the occasional appearance on the podcast again.
But I'm, you know, six, seven into it.
What I really want to step aside and say is that if you have any interest in screenwriting, and people have been reaching out to me lately with questions about screenwriting, and I think people are getting, obviously it's a field people are interested in.
There is no outside of maybe Cheers by a lot of the same team. There is no finer sitcom pilot.
It's just perfect. It is a, if you're doing a sitcom writing class, my guess is that teacher will at some point have you watch the Frasier pilot.
It's impeccable. The decision to give him a snootier, less likable brother because the character was already kind of snooty and pompous, genius.
It's just, it's perfect. It's just, and the titles before each segment that they do on Frasier make it seem even more like a class.
It's a textbook class on how to write a script.
So that's all I'll say. It's perfect. It's funny.
And it's a spinoff. It handles that perfectly, the spinning off of this beloved character. It does everything exactly right.
Joe?
That's all I got. Let's get to the movies at hand. We got Apartment 7A.
Which is a prequel to Rosemary's Baby.
Yeah. Rosemary's Baby, obviously a classic directed by Roman Polanski.
Books written about the making of this movie, which I have read.
I love the big picture, which is about the making of Chinatown that Polanski did, but of course goes into a lot of stuff with Rosemary as well.
I guess we'll start there since that's the first one.
Rosemary's Baby is considered one of the all time great horror movies and rewatching it in glorious 4K.
Who am I to argue? It's brilliant.
I think Polanski's masterpiece has got to be Chinatown, but Rosemary is right behind it.
I'm willing to put aside what the man did for today's discussion.
It's brilliant. Mia Farrow is an actress who rarely does anything for me, and it has nothing to do with her life story and all that drama.
I just don't love her as an actress. She is so fucking good in Rosemary's Baby. She's incredible.
As is John Cassavetes, and since over the pandemic I checked all of his work off my list.
Now I love seeing him in a part where he's not just an abusive alcoholic as he is in all of his movies.
In this though, he's arguably worse. All the characters he's played in all those movies, those degenerates.
He's maybe more of a scumbag in this as a guy, and what a genius character motivation.
He's a narcissistic actor who's not as famous as he wants to be, so he sells his wife's unborn child literally to the devil in the form of some Satanists who live in the building.
Doesn't even sell the kid. Let's them drug her so the devil can have sex with her.
Quick pause. The wildest scene of this movie, and it was so wild that it made me laugh out loud.
I do think Rosemary's Baby is intended to be a very dark comedy at times.
She wakes up and she's covered in scratches and is like, I feel groggy and I feel bad or whatever.
And he goes, yeah, sorry, you were out cold, but I knew it was prime baby making time, so I just raped her.
And then he goes, I tried to cut my fingernails, but it's like, so not only did you rape her, you scraped her back up, and your wife's like, oh, okay.
Shocking stuff. It's pretty insane.
You all know the story of Rosemary's Baby. You all know how it ends. We've done it on the show.
Oh, we did?
Yeah, years ago. But that's fine. It's worth revisiting, obviously, given the movie we're doing.
But at the beginning of the movie, the next door neighbors, played by Harold and Maude and the other guy, Ruth Gordon and the other guy,
they are approaching the building, and it's right after Rosemary and Guy have moved into the building.
And they're the castavets. That's what it is. Castavets.
They're approaching the building, and there's this big hubbub outside of the building, what's going on.
Turns out a woman has committed suicide. She's jumped out of the building.
The prequel, Apartment 7A, I discovered this as I was watching it. I didn't realize it was so out in the open.
But the prequel is about that woman.
Yeah, I didn't realize that until I watched Rosemary's Baby after the prequel, yeah.
So when it was getting to the end of Apartment 7A, I was like, oh my God, this is the woman from the beginning of Rosemary's Baby.
Holy shit. I didn't even put that together.
So then I went back and looked up Rosemary's Baby, and I was like, clearly they don't name that woman in Rosemary's Baby,
so they were able to make this movie with some suspense that you didn't put that together.
I was 100 % wrong. They name the woman in the thing. They name her from the beginning of this.
They don't do a cheap trick of like, well, her actual name was this, and then you go, oh my God, it's the woman from the original movie.
It's just flat out, this is the story of that woman and how she ends up jumping out the window.
Overall, I thought 7A, for the most part, worked.
It had some really nice moments. It had some spooky moments, some stuff that was genuinely scary.
I thought the director's name is Natalie Erika James. She directed a movie called Relic that I have not seen.
It was okay. But she did some really interesting artsy stuff with this.
This centers on a dancer who becomes pregnant. Why? Because the producer of the show she wants to be in also lives in the building.
He drugs her. She becomes sort of romantically involved with him, and he drugs her, and she becomes the carrier now of Satan's Baby.
The Antichrist. So I thought it was interesting that they shifted it, and she's coming to terms with it where she might be okay with it, she might not be.
There's a little tug of war there. But I thought it was interesting that they changed it a bit and made it less about, in the original movie, it's the husband, he's an actor, he's a theater actor.
He does this so he will have success. In this, it's happening to her, and then she has great success.
So she's faced with the conflict of is this worth it or is it not? Ultimately, spoilers, you realize it's not worth it to her because she commits suicide at the big ceremony at the end when they're all gathered around and the baby is about to be born.
She cons them into thinking she's good with it and then jumps out the window and kills herself so their plan cannot be hatched.
And that ends with a nice little moment in this film where the cast of vets again are walking up as they do in the first movie, and from the behind you see two people that very much resemble John Cassavetes and Mia Farrow.
In this film, you get to learn a lot more about the next door neighbor characters. Diane Weiss plays the...
Ruth Gordon.
Yeah, but what is her, hold on, what is Ruth Gordon's mini?
Mini cast of vets, yeah.
She's great, and in the Sidney Blackmerc role as an actor I was unfamiliar with.
Kevin McNally, I was unfamiliar with him too.
But they both do a really good job of encompassing these characters. I mean, Diane Weiss is doing an impression of Ruth Gordon, but she's great. I mean, Diane Weiss is never not great.
Always great to see her and she is great. Yeah, I wished that I had watched Rosemary's Baby first.
I would imagine most people were just watching it like, oh, okay, yeah, this is a new movie and I don't need to know anything about the original.
But yeah, what's cool about it is that it does nicely sync up with the original, and yet it's not one of these movies where it's like constantly winking to you, like remember Rosemary's Baby, you know.
It's kind of doing its own thing. It's classy, it's well done, it looks good.
It reminded me of like a Ouija Origin of Evil where the period element helps make a sequel to a horror movie kind of better because it just automatically feels more fresh, you know, doing a period piece today.
Because so much horror is just modern day shit. Sure. So I like that aspect of it.
Julia Garner in the Mia Farrow role, look, Julia Garner was so great on Ozark.
She was so great in this movie called The Assistant where she played basically Harvey Weinstein's assistant.
But then sometimes like Wolfman, she's embarrassing and like not even playing a convincing adult.
I thought she was fine in this. I'm still torn on her as an actress.
I'm not sure how great she is or if she's just a good director helps bring out a good performance from her or what, but I thought she was pretty decent in this.
I did too. I thought because we had watched this right after Wolfman and I remember thinking while I was watching it like, oh, she's good. It seems like she wants to be there.
Yeah, I didn't reinforce my take on Wolfman, which was I think halfway through it.
Everybody realized this is a pile of shit. Yeah. And kind of checked out.
But I thought she was I thought she brought, you know, that whole thing at the beginning where she breaks her ankle and she's playing and she gets addicted to the pills.
Yeah, but she was great in all that really conveying the plight of this woman and like her dreams being shattered and I thought that she did a really nice job.
Kind of strange to do evil in the ballet world when we just had the superior remake five years ago, which was kind of the same vibe.
I agree. And this is nowhere near as good, exciting, scary, innovative as that.
But look, I looked at it like this as a Paramount Plus original straight to DVD, whatever you want to call it, sequel to one of the great horror movies of all time.
Pretty solid. I'm going to say my hog is not up, but if somebody was like, is this any good? Should I watch this? I'd go, yeah, if you like Rosemary's Baby, give it a shot.
Not mind blowing, but certainly better than expected and reasonably entertaining, I would say.
Yeah, I'm in a similar boat. My hog is up enough.
This is one of those flicks that exists in that weird zone for me where I'm like.
I wouldn't buy it, but if I was gifted it, I wouldn't be upset about it.
If somebody said, should I watch it? I'd be curious to hear their take because I wouldn't be able to definitively say.
I don't think you'll like it or I'll think you'll love it. I think there are people that will go in either direction with this.
The set pieces were really great. Again, some really artistic direction from the director.
Little slow, little too long, even though it wasn't that long, I don't think.
This is always my gripe with these prequels and legacy sequels and stuff.
It's one of the things that JJ Abrams did right with the Star Wars stuff he was involved in.
I don't like when they don't make it look like the original movie.
I feel like when you do something like this, you've got to put aside your vision.
Tarantino said this about Psycho 2. He was like, that movie needed to be shot like Psycho.
That's what Tom Holland did and that's why it's great.
I felt like this needed to be shot a little bit more like Rosemary's Baby.
It needed a little more grain in the visual.
And just stylistically, some of the fantasy sequences were a little too elaborate compared to the original.
But that said, those were some of the best parts of the movie, so I might be very wrong there.
But anyway, my hog is up. Apartment 7A. I don't think you'll be mad that you watched it. I think you'll enjoy it just enough.
Yeah, it's pretty much exactly that. It's right in the middle.
Not sure what we'll be back with next month or even what is coming down the pike, but rest assured,
we will be bringing you the best in horror, action, fantasy, sci -fi, entertainment.
I am on Instagram at the Patrick Walsh. We are on Instagram at See You in Hell Pod.
Our Patreon is We'll See You in Hell and there's a lively discussion happening in there at all times.
As well as on Facebook, I am told. Jodie, have plugs.
I plugged the last episode. It's all the same stuff, folks.
Joderosa .com for upcoming shows, especially this Tuesday at the Angelica in New York, 9 p .m.
We're showing the special. And then everything else, Jersey and Nashville in June and Connecticut,
I'm sorry, Rhode Island in August and so forth. Joderosa .com for tickets and links and info.
And then come to Joey Roses, JoeyRoses .com. We'll see you next time, folks.
And we'll see you in hell.