Hello everybody and welcome to we'll see you in hell podcast where we talk
about, you know, your movies, your fantasy, your horror, your sci -fi in theory,
but we also talk comedies, dramas, et cetera.
This week we're talking about Megan, the latest film in the killer doll craze
starring Alison Williams, swept the nation.
We'll talk about that soon.
Joe, how are you old friend?
I'm fine, Pat.
I, uh, I rough energy to start us off there.
I, I don't, I didn't know what to say to that.
Cause you know, we recorded back to back.
So I, I, you know, I appreciate the inquiry.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Uh, I refilled my water.
I'm hydrating a good amount today.
Um, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm drinking only once every two weeks right now.
Okay.
Uh, and it seems to be having a good effect.
Good.
Uh, I mean, we, look, we've talked about it constantly.
Who, who, who, you know, I'm better without it yet.
I miss her.
God damn.
Yeah.
Tonight's a night where I just would love to go just sad, sidle up to a nice
bucket, dark little bar.
I was just thinking that.
I mean, like, cause we recorded the first one and then, you know, I was like,
Hey, I don't want to record the second one.
Let's say, let's just say, fuck it and do it tomorrow.
And I was going to go get a drink, even though I'm not drinking.
But Joe, my sponsor kept me out.
No, he didn't even know.
You could still go get a drink though.
You'll be done by Christ almighty.
It's not even, it's not going to be like 7 PM your time.
You're right in the pocket, baby.
No, I know.
I could definitely go get a drink.
I got a day tomorrow where I'll drink.
So I don't need, I don't need to drink tonight.
I'll be fine.
Yeah.
I'm trying to wait.
We're, we're doing a lot of stuff at, at the bar for, um, the super bowl.
So I'm trying to like, if I'm going to, you know, I'll probably have a few drinks
that day and the Eagles are in, so I gotta, you know, I gotta go represent.
So Eagles versus who?
No idea.
Could barely, couldn't tell you one player on the Eagles.
It's just, I'm from there.
So I was excited as I'll ever get about this.
Last time I saw the Eagles in the super bowl was, I was with you and Vince, uh,
Avril, uh, and Jesse pop at the roost watching the game, right?
And then you and I were in Vegas for another super bowl shared a room.
Christ, which one was that?
I don't know.
That was at least five years ago, maybe more.
That was when we saw, um, uh, sticks, right?
Yeah.
I think you did yourself point show and then came, maybe that
was the same trip, maybe not.
I was just talking about that trip.
That's the one time I ever ate blue chew.
Cause I stayed that extra day and I was all hung over and a woman wanted
to hang out with me, so I had blue chew.
Yes.
I remember that.
Uh, and had a, had a hell of a day.
Went to the pot awards.
Yeah.
The cannabis award, cannabis cup, whatever the fuck it was called.
Uh, a lot of, uh, chill people there.
A lot of kind vibes.
Yes.
Uh, you know, we had, we had fun.
We have fun around here.
Sure.
Uh, I'm also trying to eat better, which I'm doing, but you know, when you're
not boozing and you're eating right, it's tough, dude, it's, it starts to get sad
when your big thrill of the day is the bowl of semi salted pistachio meats and
raisins.
Yeah.
It's just, God damn it, man.
Look, here's, here's the best solution that I find sleep as late as possible.
Go to bed as early as possible.
Well, that's the easiest, that's the way to do it.
Like I, I start work now at 11 AM and I'm like, you know what?
I'm going to wake up when I wake up.
I'm not getting out of bed.
I'm working out on my lunch break.
So I don't eat lunch.
You know, I got to trick myself.
I try it.
I can't sleeping going to bed is no problem because I'll sit there.
I'll read right now.
I'm reading Stephen King's insomnia.
How's that off?
As we talk about sleep, uh, it's 790 pages.
The guy could learn how to trim a little bit here and there, but I've got it.
I'll, I don't think I'll ever read it, but I own it.
I'm enjoying it so far.
It takes place in dairy, which is what made me excited about the story.
Um, you know, I'm enjoying it so far.
I'm picturing Tom Hanks for some reason as the main character and it really works.
That's fun.
Um, but you know, going to bed is never a problem for me.
I'll lay there and read until I literally am falling asleep.
Yeah.
Or I'll, I'll turn the TV or the iPad on and watch something until I fall asleep.
King of Queens or something like that.
Comforting.
It's the waking up that's or it's the sleeping late that I can't do.
My body, dude, when I, when I, if I'm, when I am, you know, fairly free and
clear of any booze, meaning a couple of days and eating decently, my body is
like, bro, it is 8 a .m.
This is as late as it's going for you today.
Yeah, let's go.
Like it just, it's just how it is.
So, you know, I can't nap anymore.
I try to go down for a nap.
I have anxiety.
Like, I'm like, what, my phone, what am I missing?
Like, you know, what went wrong that I'm not seeing, you know, it's terrible.
Yeah.
It's terrible, but Hey, I'm awake.
Rearranged my whole apartment.
I'm excited about my new energy in my apartment.
Got it.
Pop.
You got a new Feng Shui.
Something like that.
Yeah.
You know how it goes.
I mean, for me, what I realized is generally my anxiety kicks in when I
come upstairs to start the day.
And I decided to just not do that anymore.
To just come up to start my day as my day is starting.
I give myself enough time to make a pot of coffee and sit down for work.
I did, I did realize how much having a job affects my self -esteem.
It's massive.
Been working three days this week, short days too.
And my, my mood changed a billion percent.
You have a purpose.
Yeah.
Why we, why we need jobs, you know?
Look, I always wondered like, why would you work past a point?
Like, you know, why are people who have $500 million still working?
But I get it.
Got to, got to do something.
It's it.
I was saying to somebody the other day, you know, being in the entertainment
business, especially as being comedians in the entertainment business, the
friend I was talking to was a standup, you know, you, you, you really cherish
and relish in this, this, this sort of unorthodox, non -traditional lifestyle
you've chosen and we were talking to their day where we were like, is
does every, is everybody we know crazy?
And I was like, I think so.
Yeah.
No, we all sit here and scoff at the middle American lifestyle of like,
you know, as Kramer said, these are manmade prisons, Jerry, you know, the
people that get married in their twenties and have kids by their thirties
and, and, and, you know, live in a cookie cutter suburb and go to the
nine to five and punch the clock and blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
You know, I, I, I understand.
I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I don't mean to talk down about that in any way.
I'm not, but there is a part of you that when you go into a certain type of
work and it doesn't have to be entertainment, but anything that it
doesn't involve the sort of traditional trajectory of things.
There's a part of you that sort of scoffs at the traditional route and
goes, oh, it's not for me, whatever.
You know, now I'm in my mid forties.
I'm like, I get it.
I get it.
It keeps you, it keeps you in line.
Yeah.
It's like saying, it's like why you need government.
You need some rules in your life.
It's not good to just have a free for all.
No, my therapist told me a million times during the pandemic, like to
make yourself a schedule.
She's like, set your alarm, get up at eight, read for two hours, exercise
for an hour, you know, whatever it is.
And I was just like, that goes against everything I've ever wanted from my
life is to when I have free time to just schedule it, but you realize that
that has purpose too, like the days that I know what I'm doing always go better
for me mentally than the days where I wake up and I'm like, I guess I'll just
let my brain eat away at itself.
That never works for me.
Sure.
So, um, I'm certainly never going to relax.
I mean, those days are 10 years behind me.
So, yeah, it's tough to, it's tough to relax.
Um, so funny, as we're talking about this, I'm looking at my, uh, screen,
you know, like what Pat, what Pat, what you can see of me and just the endless
amounts of action figures and DVDs filling this fucking room up, you know,
I could really see where my, uh, my depression goes when you walk into my
apartment, you're like, oh, yeah, I have been trying to move stuff out.
I have been selling a lot of albums, a lot of blue rays, a lot of et cetera.
And that for some reason always keeps me in a good mood, keeps me occupied
and making big sales because a weird supply chain ship, big sales.
I just did a thing where I was like, oh, what a fail.
I reorganize my store.
I have a storage closet in my bedroom and I reorganized it and put everything
into actual containers by category.
And I took DVDs and blue rays.
I had pulled off my shelf and put them back.
And I was like, this is not what you want to be doing here.
Yeah.
That's like the hoarder who's like, I need that bag of stamp wrappers
that I've had since 1945.
Yeah.
And you know, like hostile two and three went back to the shelf.
And I was like, well, it's the complete trilogy.
They should all be there together like a family.
And I'm like, I'm never going to watch them.
I'm never going to watch it.
I'm going to watch hostile one and that's it.
I liked one and two is three with an earshot of one and two.
I think three is far better than two.
I hate, I hated to, I, I hated that it got into like the network and how it works.
To me, that was matrix two shit where it's like, now we're going to show you
the city they live in when they wake up.
It's like, nobody cares, dude.
No way cares.
Hostile threes in Las Vegas.
I'll be checking this out ASAP.
I'm sure it's on Tubi as we speak.
I enjoyed hostile three, uh, cause it was more like one again, but I don't remember.
I mean, I could watch it now and be like, this is terrible.
I don't know.
I just, I really didn't like to, I bought two on blind
because I loved one so much.
Yeah.
Oh, they let Scott Spiegel directed who co -wrote evil dead too.
Oh, all right.
Well, then maybe that's why it's good.
I'm going to watch this bitch.
I've never seen any of the American psycho sequels.
I have however, seen all of the wild things sequels.
I've definitely rented all of those.
I never saw wild things one even wild things is excellent.
And the others are good spank material.
If you're in a bind.
Uh, American psycho, I think only had the one sequel, which was part two
starring Mila Kunis.
Yeah.
As that's like the lady psycho, right?
She's like the girl that got away from Patrick Bateman and now she's crazy.
It's it's terrible.
Yeah.
It tries to be like a satire and it just doesn't work.
I missed that man.
I mean, that's there.
There are a million podcasts with two guys in the forties talking about how
much they miss walking around a video store, but Jesus Christ, it hits me
sometimes.
It really does seeing like, because they do it now, you got to just do it through
like looking through Amazon prime.
They still do all the tactics they used to do in the VHS days.
Like, uh, instead of Lord of the rings, they'll have a movie called like God of
the circles with a poster that looks identical to it, you know, they still do
that shit or like instead of Titanic, it'll be like called boat, you know, it's
and they're just shameless.
They make the titles, the font, everything identical, I guess, in the hopes that
people will get it by mistake.
Um, I missed the, the shitty direct, uh, DVD sequels, you know, they would just
pile up horror in particular.
They, they, they did a movie on the new in search of darkness.
Uh, I can't even remember what it was called, but it's from, it was a full
moon movie and the guys like, yeah, this was a, you know, in the wake of alien,
you know, just trying to, you know, we were kind of doing our version of that.
And then it cuts this actor, the one of the actresses from, and she's like,
everybody said it was a ripoff of alien and predator or alien and terminator.
A guy that cuts another guy, the guy goes, it's the only movie that, that
we're discussing here that can't be, that couldn't be found in the U S it was
not allowed to be distributed because there were so many lawsuits about how
much it had stolen from, and then it cuts to, I don't think I'm mixing movies up.
It cuts to a scene of a bunch of people in like the, the wife beater teas, you
know, like sitting around a, a white kitchen table on a spaceship and you're
like, Jesus guys, come on.
This is directly at alien.
And then a guy alien bursts out of his upper thigh.
He did.
He dies at the table.
He starts convulsing, whatever, but nothing bursts out of him.
And he, I'm just like, guys, and then that cuts to a guy with like a
red eye exposed through skin.
I was like, this is outrageous, man.
But it's funny because I didn't know.
I knew full moon was responsible for doing, excuse me, some schlock over
the years.
I didn't know anybody did anything that blatantly derivative until the asylum.
I thought the asylum kind of created mock busters, but I guess I was wrong.
I guess it's been going on for a very long time, you know?
Yeah.
Uh, Joe, did you read the new army hammer interview?
No, is he busy back?
He's back.
They interviewed him and he's painting himself as a victim, baby.
What's he saying?
He's saying he was molested as a kid.
Oh boy.
Uh, and this has led him to act out as an adult.
He said, when these allegations started, he tried to kill himself, but he
describes his suicide attempt as walking out into the ocean and hoping
that a boat would hit him.
Uh, so not a real, not a real pointed attempt to kill yourself.
There are, there are quicker ways to do it.
Uh, and then the wife has come out and said, like, she didn't know any of
this was going on until the pandemic and everything blew up and, uh, just
seems like a disaster.
I, and I don't think people care enough about army hammer to let him come back.
People just don't care.
I, I'm still confused as to how army fame hammer was found.
Like, I, I, I, I'm still confused.
I'm like, he was in the social network where he played the twins.
And then all of a sudden he was like the fucking lone ranger.
And it was like, he's famous now.
And I was like, wait, what?
Yeah.
Um, well, and that still needed Johnny Depp, the lone ranger.
Like, and by the way, talk about a movie that wouldn't happen now.
Johnny Depp and army hammer.
But well, Johnny Depp playing, playing a native American.
Yeah, exactly.
Um, yeah, it's crazy.
It's like, he is a, is he a good looking guy?
Sure.
But like, did he ever give a performance that was even adequate?
Like, I don't think anybody gives two shits really about him.
I saw the lone ranger with my parents in the theater.
We had a great time.
It was fun.
So much.
It was, you know, it was fun watching my mom get all excited because it
took her back to being a kid.
And yeah, it was a lot of fun.
He was, you know, he was good at it, you know, like, and I thought he was good.
You know, I remember finding out that the Winklevoss twins in the social
network weren't actually twins.
It was a one guy.
I was like, oh, that's impressive.
He was good.
Right.
I just didn't understand.
I mean, look, he comes from old, old money, so that's probably what it is.
But
rumored to have bodies buried.
Yeah.
I mean, just when I'll be a cannibal.
When the controversy came out, I just was like, I don't understand
how this man is a household name.
No, like, like this is weird.
Like, well, he's not, I mean, I guess, you know, that death on the
Nile and stuff, but like, yeah.
I mean, the reason my, my mom would know who he is, which is always my
test is the cannibal stuff.
That's the only reason.
Um, well, he got himself out.
I mean, I would love if all this was a ruse to get out of being in
that JLo wedding movie that he was supposed to be in.
Yeah.
That did not look great.
Uh, shotgun wedding, shotgun wedding.
If, if JLo, if you have a script where JLo is getting married.
Rushed into production.
That woman has been getting married in the movies since I was 16 years old.
Dusted off Josh Duhamel for that film.
Oh yeah.
I mean, Duhamel's like on, they are, there's always a list of available
actors when you're trying to cast a movie or like a list of actors who might be
good, he would be on the back page.
Like if you're, if you're getting to Duhamel, you're done.
You just shouldn't make the movie.
There's nobody below Duhamel.
But then the surrounding cast is like a big cast.
It's got, it's got, it's got, uh, Jennifer Coolidge.
Yes.
Is it Rita Marino in it?
I think.
Well, Sonya Broga.
Movies.
I saw a big, uh, bus ad that said Sonya Broga in shotgun wedding.
Sonya Broga from like, uh, you know, one of, I think one of the late dirty
Harry movies, I haven't seen her in anything, maybe because it was in
a Hispanic part of time, they're advertising Sonya Broga as being in it.
I don't know who that is.
I had to look it up.
She's an actress.
Uh, obviously she was an actress in like the eighties, I guess, I assume
she's still acts, but I haven't seen her in anything in a long time.
Folks, let's go to the movie corn.
If I may.
Yeah.
This lady.
Oh yeah.
She's from, um, uh, the cause that's what I know her from the Cosby show.
Right.
Yeah.
That's funny, man.
Moon over.
With Dick Dreyfus.
Yeah.
Can you imagine there was a time in this country where Richard Dreyfus was a, was
a box office leading man for a long time.
Yeah.
Fucking insane.
Uh, in one of my favorite, really ridiculous Clint Eastwood movies is the
rookie, the Charlie Sheen Clint Eastwood movie.
I really love it.
Which randomly is also written by Scott Spiegel of Evil Dead 2 fame, but the
German villains are played by the Puerto Rican Raul Julia and the Brazilian Sonya
Braga, and they're playing German villains and, uh, the Sonya Braga
character, I remember this scene vividly rapes Clint.
How?
Gets him hard and climbs aboard.
And he's going like, no, stop it.
Just leave me be.
Yeah.
I mean, he eventually relents, but yeah, she just hops aboard.
I mean, a guy like Clint, you figure he's always hard, especially back
then he was probably just always ready.
I bet you he still gets it up pretty good.
Yeah, for sure.
Uh, she dated Robert Redford.
Wow.
She was, she was quite easy on the eyes, as they say.
She was, uh, should we go to the movie corn?
I saw dash cam.
What is on Hulu?
Dash cam is another one of these, uh, super low budget flicks.
It cost about $150 ,000 shot during the pandemic.
And I thought it was super clever, but like a lot of these things that it's
just too cheap to really land as a movie.
Uh, it felt like a shutter original through and through, but somehow it's not.
It's on Hulu.
What made it really interesting is that the lead girl is a
hardcore Trumper and anti -vaxxer.
And the plot life or in the movie?
Well, that's what's crazy is she's playing an influencer who's dry.
Her gimmick is she drives around and takes, takes calls and texts on her
little Twitch feed or whatever, uh, with suggestions and then she makes
them into improvised songs and the songs are raunchy and sort of funny
and sort of annoying, whatever, but she's driving around during the
pandemic, making up songs or whatever.
And at some point, this old woman approaches the car who's very creepy
and her daughter comes up and is like, I need you to take my mom somewhere.
So she's going to take this woman somewhere and very quickly into the
journey, this woman shits herself.
And then it's real gross.
They linger on it.
They show it a lot sort of.
Um, but she, and she's in London at this point, the influencer, she left cause
she got sick of America's strict rules.
But this woman turns out to be sort of a supernatural being.
So from there, it's sort of a crazy road chase driving around thing.
It's a lot of honestly really cool special effects on a low budget.
It's sorta got that kind of zombie movie crazy feel.
Um, meanwhile, you've got this character who you never see as the
lead of a movie anymore, or as a person who runs against everything
Hollywood is for, you know, she's a hardcore Trump or she has a
Donald Trump bobblehead and she's not painted as being a villain.
So that was sort of novel about it.
And, uh, I guess the only other attempt I've seen in that way was like the
Matt Damon movie where he's a dad who goes to Iraq or whatever that movie
was that really was boring as hell.
Um, I think it was called still water.
I want to say, but, um, I looked her up and she's an actual influencer
who actually does this, this guy, the guy who made the movie liked her
videos, uh, where she drives around riffing and kind of built the movie around her.
It's sorta works, you know, it's a, it's a fun little horror movie.
It would make way more sense to be on shutter.
And I think a lot more people would find it, but for like this kind of low
budget thing, I thought it, it worked better than most of these
kind of cheap experiments do.
I liked it.
Okay.
I watched, I'm doing all documentaries.
Everything is copy, which is a Nora Efron documentary.
Very good.
Nora Efron, what a body of work.
What an amazing person.
What an amazing artist.
What an amazing writer had no idea that her first husband and mother
of her son is Bernstein of Woodward and Bernstein, which is the
second is the guy who wrote wise guy.
Goodfellas.
Yeah.
Nick Pileggi, which they said leading up to her death with those, they were like
they like the love of her life, which was really wonderful.
Yes.
Um, it's great.
It's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's her son kind of is at the helm of the, of
ship here.
Uh, it's something celebrating his mother and her work and what she meant to not
just writing, but as a feminine voice in writing, because at the time that she was
writing these autobiographical op -ed pieces, uh, on women's perspective and
stuff that were scathingly funny, this, you know, in the six, I guess it was the
late sixties that when she first broke through, this was not happening yet.
So, uh, you know, she, she, and then she of course went on to, to make a bunch of
really classic movies.
Um, I enjoyed this very much.
Um, but at all, and I particularly enjoyed that it does not shy away from her
shortcomings and really highlights her as a fully complicated person that, that
she could be somebody that was a little too harsh or somebody that did kind of
make you feel a little bad about yourself.
Uh, because you know, she would.
Critique you, albeit humorously, but in a way that was, that was, that was fierce.
Um, but everybody said without question that that was secondary to how much they
loved and respected her.
And I, I just thought it was cool that they painted her as a complete person and
not just as some perfect angel who, who is no longer with us.
I think she definitely was gone far too soon.
I think she still had a lot more to offer.
Um, and it's funny.
I did lucky numbers on here a few weeks ago.
That's in the documentary considered that what they call like her dark years,
uh, like that, like you've gotten male.
They were like, here she is, you know, this woman that wrote heartburn.
That was this, you know, again, scathing, hilarious commentary on divorce and how
things don't work out and she starts doing these, everything is perfect in the
end movies.
And this was like her dark period.
And you look at her dark period and it's 20 times better than most people's best
period.
So, uh, you know, I'm not complaining, uh, but everything is copy.
It's a great movie.
Check it, check it out.
Yeah.
I would way rather watch you've got male or even mix nuts, which is another one
that's considered a bad movie of hers.
They really go in on mixed nuts.
They're like, it is bad and it is Nick mix nuts is terrible, but I'll give it
another try.
I saw it twice in the theater.
I mean, I, I loved it twice in the theater.
I mean, for me, it was Sandler, Steve Martin, Juliette Lewis, Parker Posey.
I'll give it another shot.
I remember really enjoying it very much.
Actually my school, my high school did it as a play and I played the Adam Sandler
role.
I tried to stay in front of that.
I'm like, you're, you're drifting a bit tilt, give it a little tilt down.
All right.
There you go.
Uh, I played the Adam Sandler role in my sophomore year of high school in an
adaptation of the movie mix.
Now, what, what did you bring to that role that was different than what Adam did?
I know you, it was probably hard.
You'd delve deep.
You say perfection.
You don't want to retread.
What did you, I wasn't doing an impression of Adam Sandler.
I just played him like a weird guy.
All right.
Uh, the easy thing to do would have been, especially for a high school play at that
time to just do the Sandler impression.
But I brought more to it.
Very good.
Um, yeah, I loved Nora Efron.
And she also did my blue heaven at the same time as her husband was doing good
fellows, which is kind of fascinating because they're two flip sides of the
same coin, no, uh, my blue heaven was based on Henry Hill and was supposed to
be a comedic version of what that guy's life was post Bob stuff, but, uh, they,
they had to change things obviously.
So anyway, uh, I watched starting over on canopy.
This is an early script of James L Brooks, who of course did terms of
endearment and you know, as good as it gets, all sorts of great things.
Um, he was a TV writer at this time, and this actually felt very kind of TV movie.
He, he was always a great writer and one of the great sitcom writers of
all time, but this feels a little more sitcom me than maybe it needed to.
I thought it's Burt Reynolds, uh, kind of at his most charming.
He, he's lost the mustache.
He's clean shaven.
He's just a normal dude.
Um, he is married to Candice Bergen.
Candice Bergen leaves him at the beginning of the movie to become a
songwriter and he's devastated.
So, you know, it's a, it's kind of that forgetting Sarah Marshall or the, you
we've seen it before the guy gets left by his wife and it sends him on some
journey, we see where it goes.
Uh, and this one, it's a very, very simple story.
It's actually so simple that it would just never be made today.
Cause there's no hook to it.
So it's just a guy who gets divorced and he meets Jill Clayberg who is an actor.
So I don't think people even really know these days.
She was big in the seventies and eighties.
Uh, she played Kristen Wigg's mom in bridesmaids is how you might know her,
but she like won Oscars and great actress, unmarried woman, very good act.
Um, so Burt Reynolds and her are amazing together.
They have this great chemistry.
And it's the only time I've seen Burt Reynolds interacting romantically with
like a normal looking woman, like, you know, Sally field is a movie star.
Like he interacts with people kind of at his level of hotness and Jill
Clayberg is a very beautiful woman, but she looks like everybody's mom growing up.
She kind of got Melinda Dillon vibes actually, who just passed away RIP.
Um, so to see great, yeah, to see Burt Reynolds interact with a woman who's
like strange, like just not, not just hitting the standard romantic comedy
beats, she's a James L.
Brooks knows how to write women always has, he writes very interesting female
characters that are always just as well written as the men and, uh, it's great
to see Burt Reynolds chewing on like real adult romance and not like driving
up to a woman in jean shorts and honking his horn and she sits on his face.
You know, um, it's a real adult romantic story and I really enjoyed it.
I had never seen it somehow.
It's directed by Alan J.
Pakula who directed all the president's men and clout and Sophie's choice and
all these huge movies, not a big comedy director and that kind of shows here.
It would plays better as sort of a straight drama, but, um, I dug it.
I really, the only thing I didn't like about it was Candy Bergen.
Joe and I were kind of talking about how we were never huge fans of hers.
The other night, I never liked Murphy Brown much, but, um, she's playing
like a broad comedy character.
She's playing this character who's like always singing that it's weird because
she's a big success in the movie, but the songs are comedically terrible.
So you don't know really what is going on.
And anytime she's in it, you're like, he divorced, you're, you're
getting divorced for a reason.
Candy go away and let bird hang out with Jill Clayberg.
There's never any tension there because you hate Candice Bergen in the movie.
That's the one drawback, but, uh, as a romance between Clayberg and
Burt Reynolds, very charming, check it out.
Uh, this isn't a doc, but it's a sort of, it's a taping of a one woman show.
Uh, Carrie Fisher, Carrie Fisher's wishful drinking, which is my favorite
name ever for a one person show.
Uh, it's great.
You know, I'm a huge Carrie Fisher fan for many reasons, starting of course,
and most prominently because of star wars, but she's wonderful.
She's popped up in all kinds of stuff over the years.
She's got a great role in my favorite movie of all time, Hannah and her sisters.
Uh, she's in the burbs, one of the great unsung comedies of our time.
Deserve a lot more.
She's the one Harry met Sally.
She's great in that Carrie Fisher is awesome.
Uh, and you know, she's, she's got the chops.
She's got those theater chops.
She's got those movie chops.
She's got those writing chops.
Uh, and it's just great.
The one woman show highlights her, basically her family tree and her
life as a product of show business.
And it's Carrie Fisher, she pulls no punches.
She makes a lot of jokes about her mental health.
And the time she has spent in certain facilities and addiction and all these
things, and it's wonderful and you watch it and it puts a huge smile on your face.
She never gets sappy as real as she gets.
She never gets sappy.
Uh, and, and it's from the heart and you know, another person gone too soon.
Uh, you know, too soon, uh, sad that she's not around anymore, but watch it.
It's a great little time capsule of her.
Uh, HBO Max, I believe.
Correct.
That's where I watch both of those.
Yes.
On my dime.
Well, don't blow up my spot.
You know, I want Netflix.
He's going to cut down on that.
So you better hope HBO Max and Netflix can kiss my grits.
I am too.
Uh, I didn't, I didn't ever discuss in the last episode, plain with Gerard Butler.
Um, the movie is what he does now.
He's doing, he inherited the Bruce Willis throne when Bruce Willis stopped doing,
uh, theatrical movies.
And although he was, uh, as we now know, having mental health issues, but, um,
Gerard Butler, I admire the hell out of the guy.
He hung in there.
We all counted him out.
We all thought, okay, this guy's done.
But he makes two to three movies a year.
They all turn a profit.
And he really is our generations.
Chuck Norris or Charles Bronson are one of these guys, um, where just dudes
love him, women like him.
I texted my mom today.
She always wants to know what I saw.
I was like, I saw a plane.
It was okay.
It's like, oh, that's good to know.
Tom will want to see it, meaning her husband.
It's like, you know, guys love taking their wives to see these Gerard Butler
movies, and this is a pretty solid one.
He plays a pilot.
Uh, he is trying to take these passengers to their destination and get
reunited with his daughter, but plane crash happens.
Things go wrong.
There is a passenger on board who is a, uh, a prisoner being transported, who of
course Gerard Butler enlists to help him out, but you know, as corny as that
is as corn, like there's Tony Goldwyn, who's an actor who's been in a billion
movies and you know, like he walks in at this one point and he's like, so, uh,
bring me up to speed.
Like it's one of those movies where just everything is as generic as possible.
There's this bald actor who looks like the poor man's F Murray Abraham, who
you'd recognize in a heartbeat.
If you saw him, um, Joe, I'm going to give you this guy's name and you
can look them up.
I'm looking them up.
You don't have to.
He looks like a poor man's F Murray.
I think I already know who you're talking about, but just,
um, it's a movie where everyone is cast exact, like it's exactly who you'd
expect everyone to be playing.
The dialogue is almost AI generated.
It's just like the most generic shit.
Paul Ben Victor, Paul Ben Victor, baby.
You've also got a Joey Slotnick in this Joe Slotnick, who I, I enjoy
pops up in things, various, you know, very random, but you're always like,
Oh, that guy, I like that guy.
I actually hate that guy.
Oh, all right.
Uh, he was on the Ellen show, wasn't he?
Yeah, he's on something.
He used to be on shows back in the day.
But, um, you know, it's one of those where the passengers are all really
annoying and then Gerard Butler and the, uh, the prisoner go off on this island
and very Rambo style.
So like, you know, this guy on the plane is like, wait a minute, if we
landed on this Island, they have no laws.
They're, they're, they're lawless murderers.
If they, if that's the Island we're on, we're in trouble.
Believe it or not, Joe, they are on this Island.
I can't, the dinosaurs are there, aren't they?
No laws, no police.
So single -handedly, uh, although they eventually get a little help, Gerard
and the prisoner take out these guys and, and get the plane to safety.
You know, it's a, a little bit Sully, a little bit Rambo, a little bit lost.
The TV show and it's perfectly entertaining.
It would actually be a good movie to watch on a plane if it didn't have, uh,
several serious plane crashes in it.
Uh, a solid entertainment, a solid entertainment.
My final installment is Pennywise, the making of it or the story of it.
I forget the exact title documentary about the making of the mini series.
Uh, I love this every bit of it.
It was awesome.
It was awesome seeing interviews with all the kids grown up.
It was awesome seeing interviews with all the actors that are still with us in it.
It was really awesome seeing Tim Curry interviewed where, you know, it's very sad.
He's still is affected by what the stroke, the stroke that he suffered.
He's in a wheelchair still, but he can, he can speak again.
And he's like, he's clear and articulate and all that.
And it was like, good to see him like able to talk and just, you
know, have a conversation.
And I, I was, he seems to have not lost his spirit at all, which is great.
Um, yeah, he's landing jokes.
I mean, he seemed really sharp.
I loved watching, you know, the interviews with the writers, the
director, every part of it, I just enjoyed.
And I will tell you people, it really solidified for me because they don't
even get into the other version of it because I think that's not the point,
but it really solidified for me.
And people made fun of me when the, when the new version of it came out.
This version is superior and it is scarier.
It is, it just, uh, they get heavily into all the stuff about Tim Curry,
about what they initially wanted him to do with the role, what he
said he would do with the role.
They agreed with him because this was back when they let a fucking artist
have a say in something for once.
Um, you know, and not because they were Brad Pitt saying, you got me for three
days and it's going to cost you this much and fucker walk, and it's not to shit on
Brad Pitt, but that's kind of how it works.
A lot of the time it was them saying, this guy is going to make it better
and he's right and we should listen to him.
Um, uh, the guy that plays, I forget the actor's name, the guy with the
mole on his cheek and the glasses that plays Bill William, old William.
From the Waltons?
Yeah, he's, he has the, I think he has the best interview snippets in it.
He's, he's really like, it's very funny.
He's, she's telling a lot of funny stories, laughing a lot.
Yeah.
Uh, you're talking about Richard Thomas.
Yes.
Um, I just, I loved it.
I just thought it was, I thought it was great.
I have always, I, I saw it, I saw it as a kid.
I saw it in real time.
And I remember being like waiting with baited fucking breath for the second one.
Cause I think it was, they were like a week apart.
Uh, and I couldn't wait.
Now there was a mini series, it wouldn't have been a week apart, but it doesn't
matter whatever the duration was between them airing the first part and the
second part, I was like going crazy.
I couldn't, I loved it as a kid.
It scared the shit out of me, but I loved it.
Uh, I own it.
I watch it at least once a year.
Um, it was just awesome.
It was just, it was just awesome.
And it was really cool.
See the kid, the kid that I forget the bully's name, the main
bully's name in it, but seeing the grownup version of that kid.
Cause the kid is such a fucking prick in the movie and seeing the grownup
version of him now saying like, I would, any of these from Canada, I'd go.
And I, I, I, I, after the scenes, I'd go and apologize to the other kids.
Like, I'm sorry.
I don't mean that's not me.
Yeah, it's like, I just love seeing stuff.
I love anything where I'm like, wow, that guy's a different person.
He's a good actor.
Um, I really, really enjoyed it.
It was the first time I can recall really seeing anything truly scary aside from
like Bambi or something that scares you, but isn't a scary thing, uh, cause it was
on channel four and I could watch anything on network television for the most part,
unless it had black people in it, like in living color.
Um, but I was watching it.
My mom had read the book and I was horrified.
I went to bed after the first part and it's the, it's the first time I remember
being scared, walking to my bed, like running down the hall because I was
worried something was going to grab me.
And it's starting the movie with him at, at that level, the level where he
reaches out and grabs your feet.
So for me taking a shower as a kid or like anything where I was, I was
anything where my feet were exposed.
Like when I would get into bed, I had to make sure my feet were covered.
It really traumatized me as I recall.
Uh, and the new one, obviously I saw it when I was 35 and it didn't work as much,
but to me it's night and day.
One movie is made with a lot of care and love and is a classic and one kind of sucked.
The, uh, well, it just, it highlighted like, because they do what they
didn't do in the original.
They do all of that in the, in the new one.
It's like, they do give Pennywise too much prosthetic to not look human in any way.
Um, they, with the makeup, I mean, it's all jump scares and almost no mood.
It's, you know, it's all the, you know, and they captured some of the elements
and, and, and then they also alter the ending in the new one and the altered
ending in the new one is worse than the altered ending in the original.
Yeah.
Uh, and they talk about the regrets of the altered ending in the original, but
whatever, uh, they do, uh, condemn the scene where they all fuck Bev.
Uh, yeah, that didn't make it into any of the adaptation.
Oddly enough, it cuts to child orgy cuts to a producer and he goes, this was one
of the scenes Steven wrote that just doesn't work.
Uh, I put a big X through it the day I read the novel and, uh, you know, I
just said, we can't do this.
Uh, but my favorite story is the kid that plays.
What's the name of the, the, the, the fat kid, the character's name.
Uh, I don't Ben cross.
I want to say, the grownup version of the kid that plays Ben in the movie.
He tells a great John, they all talk about what all they were in of John
Ritter and how they couldn't believe they got to like work with him and, and
how awesome he was and how funny he was and whatever he told a great story of
they were throwing, he was, they would play catch with football, the football.
And John Ritter was like, ah, that's enough for me.
And he goes, and you know, we were all the kids.
We gave him like a bunch of crap.
Like where are you going?
Come on, keep playing.
And he's like, yeah, it's easy to throw the ball around all day.
When you got no hair on your nuts.
I was like, I miss that time when you could make a joke like that to a
bunch of 12 year old kids and they'd laugh.
Yeah.
A lot of times they knew it wasn't perverted.
You were just making a statement.
A lot of times when you're watching these like special editions, like
scream factory or whatever, and they're reminiscing about things on set,
especially when older actors are reminiscing, I'd say three out of 10
times, it's like a sex crime, you know, by today's standards, they'll just be
like, oh yeah, you know, Gary grabbed her by her panties and threw her off
the roof into the pool and we all pointed at her and laughed when she got
out all wet in her underwear.
And you're like, this is, that's not as charming a story as you think.
Then it cuts it.
It'll cut to her.
And she's like, it's the funniest thing that's ever happened to me.
You're like, I loved it.
I loved it.
Yeah, exactly.
Different time.
Uh, anyway, I watched to close the corner or am I done?
I'll be done.
I think you're done.
Oh, okay.
Then there, there we are.
There we are.
We're done.
Um, it brings us to the big horror smash.
They, I saw them on the red carpet at the Oscars or at the golden
globes, they asked Jamie Lee Curtis, who's the next scream queen, Jamie,
who do you think's going to take the mantle?
And she said, I'm hearing Megan.
I'm hearing it's Megan.
Um, could that be because she works with woman?
He's just, I don't know what happened.
You're married to one of the funniest men on earth.
It must be a nightmare at home.
She's just, I've never seen somebody so serious.
She's very serious.
Uh, especially for a movie where she plays a woman who, in one scene
has hot dogs for fingers, literally.
She could probably loosen up a little bit, but, um, Megan is, uh,
the latest from Blumhouse.
I, I hope we can dodge this minefield without hearing Joe talk about it.
We can.
Blumhouse.
Um, it is a story of Alison Williams is, uh, one
of the more unlikely scientists.
Not that there aren't beautiful scientists out there, but she's working
at a toy, uh, company designing or trying to design a new sort of AI,
basically the child's play type, uh, pal for your kid, like a robot that
could be friends with your kid.
Her niece is killed in a horrible car accident at the beginning.
Her parents are both killed.
No, the niece isn't killed.
Just, yeah, just the parents.
Parents are killed and the niece is sent to live with Alison Williams.
Alison Williams, uh, is perfect casting because she just seems like a woman
with no maternal instinct or warmth at all.
And the early scenes of her trying to interact with this girl are pretty
funny because she's just sucks at it.
Yeah.
And she gets the idea.
Why don't I give her a friend and this Megan and Megan can take
care of her while I'm under these work deadlines or whatever.
And of course, folks, Megan turns out to be more than they bargained for.
It's I like, by the way, I got to, I got to backtrack for one second.
Well, I just, my computer screen, I looked up, I still have the
cast list of plane open in front of me.
Yeah.
You want to talk paint by, listen to these character names paid by number.
Gerard Butler is Brody Torrance.
Of course.
Hold on.
These are my two favorites.
Tony Goldwood is scars Dale and, and, and Rebi Adelique as shell back.
Yeah.
No, I mean, and it's the kind of movie where each of those characters is
introduced by another character going, get me shell back, like that's how
they all come into the movie.
Uh, um, yeah.
When I liked, I liked, I liked Megan, so I'm not going to do the usual
because, Hey, Blumhouse is good when they let the movie be the movie and
they're not driving some agenda into your face the entire time at the
expense of the movie, uh, I don't have a problem with an agenda in a movie.
I have a problem when the agenda hurts the quality of the movie.
Um, and this is not that this is made by the same writer director that did
housebound, which I enjoyed, um, and is a very funny movie and scary.
This is very funny.
Uh, Megan is very, very funny.
Uh, and to me, those early scenes of like, it's the, it's the always sunny
reveal, they've done this reveal a thousand times on the show, but it's
like Megan and Alison Williams talking, and then you pan out to reveal that
Megan is sitting there listening to them.
And it made the audience laugh every single time, uh, when they're talking
and Megan's like listening and like looking back and forth at the two of them,
it just can't help but be funny.
And the movie knows it's funny.
I, I don't know if the director is gay.
It's not my business, but the movie had it actually, it says he's married.
I don't know if that means to a woman or a man again, not my business, but the
movie has sort of a gay vibe behind the camera to me, if that makes sense.
How do you mean?
It felt a little campy, you know, and, uh, it is definitely campy.
Yes.
It's becoming a big hit with gays.
My friend, John Gabers asked me to go and he was like, I'm going with like
this giant LGBTQ group or whatever.
Um, when I saw it, I saw it twice, uh, because the first time I just
was super distracted and I realized I hadn't paid attention enough to
discuss it on the show.
So I saw it at the theater and it was so much more fun at the theater.
Uh, but it's already getting that sort of like cat's second life.
Where there were a lot of people there to kind of like talk back to the
screen and cheer and things like that.
And it was super fun.
Uh, I mean, Megan sings at a couple of points.
It's really unexpected and funny.
That's the funniest scene for me is the, the, the little girl is in a terrible
way because she misses her mother.
And it's the day that they have to give the big presentation of her
interacting with the doll to the big executives.
And the girl is having like a meltdown and it's like, Oh my God, this, this
presentation is going sideways because my niece is too upset about her parents.
And I forced her to do this thing.
And I'm a terrible person.
And Alison Williams job is on the line and everything's at stake.
And Megan connects with the little girl in such a true, pure emotional
way and makes the girl feel better.
And it's the moment that the girl falls in love with the doll.
And then the doll starts singing this like Annie friends forever song to her.
And it, it instantly goes from, from weepy to hilarious.
And the fact that they pull it off, I was like, that is like a fucking
magic trick this guy just did.
I don't know how he totally shifted that smoothly, but he did it and
it works and it's great.
It really is.
I mean, we talked about how badly you people was directed.
This movie is directed so well because how many horror comedies have we talked
about on the show that fuck up the balance or horror or action comedies
that fuck up the balance.
And then you're like, well, I don't, not only do I not care about anyone in this,
it's also not funny.
So you're not doing anything.
Well, this movie, even if, if it were just a paint by numbers horror
movie, which it kind of is, it is basically child's play.
There's not a whole lot of crazy surprise to what we're seeing here.
There wasn't even as much surprise as like a movie like smile, which had that
uh, wrapping up the cat birthday scene.
Right.
Uh, there's nothing like that except Megan dancing.
Megan dancing was a wild moment from the trailer.
Her dancing was awesome.
I wanted more of that.
That reminded me of in, um, ex machina when, when, when he jumps in and
starts dancing with those robots.
I mean, the theater, when I saw that was like howling cause everybody's
like, what is going on?
This was definitely, I feel like influenced a little bit by
ex machina, but him, the tone of this thing, he keeps it scary enough.
It's PG 13 horror.
It's not scary per se, but he, all those elements work very well, but he lays
the humor in and it's there and it's really funny, but it never detracts
from the other, he walks a line throughout this whole movie.
And by the way, the script, which is by the girl who wrote malignant, uh, and
I feel like I should shout them out, but, uh, I know her first name is Akilah.
I don't know her second name, but, um, I thought Megan was a lot of fun.
I liked it more on a second viewing.
The writer's name is Akilah Cooper story by James Wan, who's of course,
legendary horror guy from these days.
Uh, and to me, James Wan's always a second tier guy for me.
He's made great movies, but to me, he's always kind of bringing in second tier
horror, same with bloom house a lot of the time.
And Megan to me felt like a real nice B plus it's better than a lot of the junk.
It's not perfect.
It's not great, but I thought it was really fun and funny.
Uh, I, I did not like the child's play remake.
I did not want to see this because the plot was so similar.
And then I read it and then when I realized it was the housebound guy,
I was like, ah, okay, hold on.
Uh, and then I read an interview where he talked about it.
He was like, yeah, we heard about the child's play remake.
And we were in pre -production and obviously we were concerned, whatever.
And then I also remembered that the studio very shittily rushed out that
child's play remake to try to beat the series, which is excellent to the punch.
And I was like, you know what?
Fuck the child's play remake.
I want to see this.
Um, and the thing I liked best about this that I found to be truly chilling.
And it was the same thing, similar thing in ex Machina.
In child's play in the remake, some disgruntled employee programs
the doll to do bad things.
And that's why the doll does bad things.
This played very, very seamlessly and realistically on how artificial
intelligence develops, how quickly it learns, and you see in real time
why this goes sideways and it's great.
And it makes it scarier and it's excellent.
Um, one thing I didn't quite get, which I thought was going to be the plot for
the second was going to be a set for the second movie, there's a disgruntled
employee that's under, by the way, shout, shout outs to Ronnie Chang.
Uh, Ronnie Chang's really funny in this movie.
He's great.
He's been a friend and he's a friend and I've known Ronnie for a long time.
I was excited to see him in this.
It was really cool.
Um, and he's, it's great seeing him play a dick cause he's such, he's
like the nicest guy in the world.
He was a good deck.
He was funny.
Um, but anyway, um, he mistreats his subordinate and his subordinate steals
all the data for programming for Megan.
And the whole plot is we got to get this doll out before the
competition finds out anything.
And the guy is clearly going to take the data to a competing company as a
fuck you to his employers that are mistreating him.
They never fulfill that.
And I thought that was going to be clearly the, actually, maybe
there is a post credit scene.
I don't know, but I thought that was going to be the button at
the end of the movie.
Like they destroy Megan.
We've saved the day.
And then you see there's another company like, we got to get this out and
like, oh shit, here comes an army of Megan's, which is kind of like
the ending of child's play.
That's not what happens instead.
They go, and maybe they will do that in a sequel.
I don't know, but they do go this other route that seems to be the only route
that everybody's talking about in the articles about there being a potential
sequel, which is Megan can transfer her, her intelligence to other devices.
And she, in the very last shot, you see that she's transferred herself into
like the Alexa device at home, which does not excite me because I'm just like,
I don't care if it's an Alexa type device, like controlling the house.
Like that's not interesting.
They know they got to somehow get, get her back into doll form.
They know for the sequel, right?
So, yeah.
So then that's the thing.
I am not, you know, but who knows?
Maybe they won't even do a sequel.
I don't think it needs one.
I think they got done what they're, what they set out to do.
And that's kind of it.
I would say 99 % chance there will be a sequel because of how much money it made
and it being room house and it being cheap and it's easy to get
Allison Williams and et cetera.
But, um, but it was great.
My hog is up.
As welcome a sequel.
I know Megan was shot rated R and made PG 13, which kind of sucks.
It was PG 13.
It was pretty violent.
It was violent.
I didn't know that, but like when she's spraying the lady with the chemicals
and her face kind of melts off, like, you know, like you'll see the face
melt off and there were gore scenes that aren't in the movie as is now.
So my guess is because he's, he's blown me loves the money.
He's going to release an R rated movie to, uh, blue ray and to, to these
streaming services and et cetera, and a sequel and probably several sequels.
And I welcome it.
I would much rather have another Megan than another Annabelle.
I think Megan is a really fun character.
And I hope that they don't make the mistake of going, well, now let's
lean so hard into the comedy.
Now that everybody got a kick out of Megan and ruin it, they will probably.
But, um, that, you know, sometimes it's that delicate balance that they just
happened to get right once and they never do it again.
My, my hope is we get more quality Megan's down the road.
I liked it.
I like Alison Williams.
I like her on girls.
I like her and get out.
I like her in everything.
I'm a fan.
Yeah.
I like Alison Williams too.
I'm very enchanted by her.
She's great.
Um, and I liked this movie quite a bit.
So I hope that, uh, good things come from it, whether it's a
sequel or just, you know, another movie from this team that, that can,
that can do another cool thing, you know?
So, uh, uh, hogs up hogs up G's up hogs up.
My hog is up for this young lady, Megan.
Um, sorry if that sounded weird.
I well, she's underage.
It's a little weird, but what can you do?
I enjoyed the film greatly.
We will be back.
Not sure what with, but we will be back.
We're definitely plotting that special episode, um, of, of sort
of recasting some roles, et cetera, but we will be back.
You know that I'm doing two movie corners this month due to missing one.
You've already got one up and the other one should be up shortly.
I am on Twitter and Instagram at the Patrick Walsh.
Miss Pat show season three is airing in a few short months and
season four is writing now.
Joe DeRosa comedy, Instagram and Twitter again, Valentine's day,
Crane theater, New York city.
I never promised you a Rose garden.
Please come out and see it.
If you haven't, and if you have come see it again, I don't care.
Uh, and then I'm on the road like crazy.
JoeDeRosainfo .com for all upcoming dates and JoeyRosesNYC .com for all
roses info, come hang with us for the Superbowl.
We're going to be having a good time and we've got catering platters.
If you want to bring it home with you.
That's it folks.
We'll see you next time and we'll see you in hell.