Summer is here, and Bet MGM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer.
Or check out our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz.
Only available at Bet MGM Casino.
Spend on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 Fortunes, Mystery of the Land,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand.
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action.
Bet MGM in Game Sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 Press to Wager, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania, and West Virginia only.
Games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as non -mustrable site credit slash bonus bets unless otherwise provided in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
Gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamber.
The football season is full of guarantees.
And here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October.
If your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning or winning money back in fan cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
Winning hits different here.
Must be 21 -plus.
Gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamber.
Offer not available in all states.
Terms apply.
See fanatic sportsbook app.
Hey everybody, welcome to we'll see you and how let's let's skip the the the normal preamble here.
Pat and I are right in the middle of a hot take and I wanted to hit records so we can get into it.
We're sitting here enjoying well not enjoying screw drivers because I'm enjoying mine.
If you remember recently ladies and gentlemen, we had we had screw drivers on the show and there
were some complaints for me that they all they had at the store was the five calorie OJ.
Wouldn't have been an issue if it didn't taste so shitty.
Yeah.
Usually you get the light you're like whatever it's close enough.
This tasted like water with orange food coloring in it.
Yeah.
So then Pat shows up today.
I asked him to grab OJ on his way over so we can do the thing we do drink.
Yeah.
Shows up with 50 calorie OJ and then he sips and he goes this tastes just as bad as the other
cut stuff.
I go well didn't they have regular and he goes oh no they had tons of regular.
Well why the hell didn't you just buy the damn regular.
My reasoning is if now you don't live with somebody you don't know what their buying habits
are but I thought to myself if my friend Joe purchased a five calorie and deemed it not good enough
he must be counting calories but want a little more flavor I'll go with the 50 cow.
My instincts were pure at heart.
It saddens me that you don't remember when I said to you and this was on or off air I can't
remember I said to you I only got this shit because it was the only kind they had literally
the only other brand was mango infused and I didn't want you to die because of your allergy
so I got the thank you you don't even remember that.
We were both looking out for each other.
I don't remember the specifics I remember the mango part of it in a way in a way I'm sorry
I'm sorry these screwdrivers are subpar I got to be honest I just tasted mine it's not
that bad once the ice gets to it and it's like that meat in McDonald's you throw enough
shit on there you don't even know what you're eating anymore did you know that the meat at
Arbise originates as a paste oh that's bullshit it's not bullshit that's bullshit
not bullshit how does it originate as a paste I send in tubes of paste you cut it and it
like congeals into your meat that you're eating I don't believe it it's true this is like
with every once a year they go you know chicken McNuggets have pink foam in them I think
that's true they got that pink slime yeah and then you look it up you you go watch a video
of them making them and there's I don't see any pink slime all the video McDonald's puts
out they're not using a tube of paintmarked pink slime to inject the nuggets I realize that's
a little bit like Nixon being like take my word for it what was on the tapes you get here
it's fine come on but my boy tricky D that a good Nixon impression yeah I like that that's a funny
sort of Anthony Hopkins ask uh commitment I brought to my impression of Richard Dick Nixon
Richard Millhouse next in my opinion to this day an absurd casting choice uh Hopkins is nicks it's
just yeah it just didn't he was fine it just it's just it was very distracting to me he did a good
job but yeah he didn't really suggest Nixon at all I don't I mean if you go with a real Nixon you
be cast in Dan Hadea that guy looks like fucking Nixon he played Nixon in uh in dick in dick that's
right which is a great movie uh he uh I love Dan Hadea he's dead now right I don't believe he is not
at all I love Dan Hadea there's a guy you get on the cool kids I'd love to hilarious yeah what about a
rea problem you get her in there somewhere I do a rea problem we I mean she's in the uh always sunny
family I've met her she's great um Charlie can call her up hey she's very very nice she seems nice
I mean if you'd real shock if you were like what if she's a real asshole that Pearlman I mean you never
know in this town baby Pat and I uh the plan for today was to record two episodes we we're it's
2 2 30 pm we're starting this early because the other night we all made a big plan to like all go
drink together today uh for that for a farewell holiday thing I mean let's be honest it's Sunday and
it's right we'd be doing it whether it was holidays or not sure but it was a big send off I'm leaving for
a few weeks and blah blah blah and which by the way guys but before anybody freaks out uh bonus
apple be up soon for December and also uh the final episode for this year we'll we'll air on Monday I
think it is the 31st actually uh and then what are you doing new years new years right yep
harry conic junior uh and then we will not be doing episodes the first two weeks of January we'll
be back mid -January with with regular Monday apps and a bonus and all that shit all right folks
if you couldn't tell from that vocal performance I am heavily drugged I am in excruciating neck pain
well that's what I was getting at oh okay well go on it was supposed to be a big holiday day so we
started pat insisted we start early because I can't I can't start recording and drinking at four
it's too late we have to start early because I have to go to bed by midnight that's true oh I got
to you know do shit tomorrow morning early which is fair I said okay and he strolls in here today my
neck hurts I can only hang out for an hour no no I'm drinking early for no reason right but look it's
not neck hurts is not doing doing this justice couple weeks ago I was like wow I'm in extreme pain
what's happening how do I get it to stop uh little by little as things improved at my job it went away
then things took a twist and so did my neck and like three days ago I woke up
worse pain in my entire life about three in the morning next two nights I didn't sleep at all
because there's no good way to lay on it you can't fall asleep when you're in excruciating pain
it's miserable miserable took a muscle relax for finally today chasing it with some vodka I don't know
where this day is gonna go I gotta be honest I feel like by the end of recording and a couple
of screwdrivers you might be ready to fucking burn the midnight oil maybe I'm fine you gotta pill
in here but uh it's it's rough I wouldn't got to act you puncture today and then they did cupping
which was the best feeling ever but instead of sticking a suction cup to you they squeeze like a
suction cup to your flesh and then drag it around your back and shoulders to like loosen things up
so it's like a reverse massage where they're actually like pulling tension out of you
Lucy Goosey yeah so she does all this and then it ended and it was nice it was relaxing she was
like how do you feel I said I feel exactly as bad as when this started right and she was like yeah it'll
take a few days to open up so I'm just taking her at her word that's so weird I can't believe the
horse shit black magic needle ritual didn't didn't work well so many people swear by it I was out last
night I swear by a lot of things some people think fruit can cure cancer I mean it's crystals or
whatever else yeah you know a fruit based diet over time can lead to the prevention of cancer but
I'm not here to do a commercial for the the fruit lobby commercial kombucha
uh who am I to say potato patato commercial kombucha um I'm just pulling my phone out here
for when we get to the segments also we gotta do shout outs today great
uh so I want to get those set up uh I almost forgot and it's hard for some reason it is hard to
remember to do those shout outs every month slips the mind well it shouldn't because these people
are counting on us I've never let them down no yeah I'm just saying it's it's I always remember
like the last minute like oh we still got to do our shout outs this month right they're not a part
of every episode see now somebody requested a Christmas on with the Joe and even suggested one
for me and I will do it now okay it's a little uh medley dashing through the Joe on a one horse
jopin slay Joe bring us a figgy pudding Joe bring us a figgy pudding Joe bring us a figgy pudding
and bring it out here chestnuts jostain on a jopin fire wow you know a little fun that was a lot
a little fun that was a lot and it is the holiday season I probably when this airs I'll be in Missouri
I hope it'll be snowing I'll be staying at the casino hotel with my wife perhaps doing a little gambling
it's gonna be nice here's and I'm looking at the patreon right now yeah looking at the the generous
people that give on all three tiers yeah some guy uh or I assume maybe no no it's mr. Alex Alex
low donated chose a no reward donation I didn't even know you could do that he did she chose to
donate and then not accept any of this is that's how I understand I mean look it's not not a charity
we're happy to provide you with a service uh I mean that's that's thank you thank you that's
a very selfless thing to do unless maybe maybe he donated so little they were like we can't even put
you on a dollar tier or something yeah and you look that's appreciated to yeah of course pay
what you can kind of forward I'm gonna but I'm gonna pretend that in the christmas spirit he just said
I don't I don't need a gift yeah what do you give the man that has everything right uh that's
that's I didn't even know that was an option to to resist the uh the get the one it's on a gift
what's it called the bonus I'm just looking at the fucking thing and I reward that's what it is
uh I don't know where you're going Jon's just rambling over there I had a wild night last night
what kind I was at the improv doing the kind that van Morrison and Michelle and DeGaio Chelo
once sang about a wild melon camp by the way John Cougar Melon can but singing the uh
book and playing the Gunk G du G du G du that was Michelle and DeGaio Chelo I'm saying Van Morrison
wasn't there not in that at that time right they both sang about a wild night yeah it's a cover of
Van Morrison right yes um I I'm sorry I'm just figuring it out I had a show at the uh improv last
night very fun did my friend Thomas Dale's podcast upstairs and then I
did a set downstairs uh and you work a little more blue downstairs Dan a little little blue downstairs
yeah yeah had a great time just like really wonderful time then my friend Ben Bailey showed up
when all buddy of mine from New York host of TV's cash cap oh nice that was a surprise I'm not mistaken
the inspiration for beloved comic strip character Beetle Bailey yes yeah it was based on him all right uh
and we had a blast we had a few beers at the bar and then he's like you want to go to this Christmas party
went to this Christmas party met up with his current manager and a guy I used to work with
named Jonathan Brandstun who's one of the best dudes in the world okay uh hopefully at this party
below me on the list but sure yeah you you and I are closer all right uh but he's a great dude and we
were at this party we had a we had a great time hopefully it was great as times that you and I have
that but go on this was a little better I gotta be honest but the time itself all right hung out with
Albert Brooks's wife for a while okay told her repeatedly that I loved her husband with all my heart uh
huh and then we're like and what do you do again tuts no she loved it she's like he's great isn't he
I love him he I love him he's great I'm like you know he's the funniest man on earth right yeah she's
like yeah I know like she was really sweet nice um I wonder if that's how my wife speaks about me
got so drunk it was eating this is one of these big fancy houses up in the hills was eating
chryt cocktail over the bowl at one point uh it just fingers into the cocktail saw some like
licking your hands clean yeah real like a stanza style um they had karaoke face down in it like
beetle juice or in the day oh scene carry karaoke brought the house down with my uh cover of don't stop
me now by queen okay people are freak it out and yeah I believe you're bringing bohemian raps you
to the movie corner today are you not yes I am I'm excited to watch it I don't have it yet uh
spent a little time talking to a very lovely sexy lady oh and then left the party not as lovely
and sexy as me but go on and then left the party and went home and fell asleep the lady no no no solo
fell asleep in the uber okay had to be woken up by the uber driver when we got to my place uh -huh uh but
I was just 17 ,000 sheets to the wind yeah uh but woke up today and you know got back at life
I went to a party yeah went to a party I've taken to wearing a scarf
because I can pull down on my neck which relieves some of the misery this is why everybody
know they wear scarves it's that's why I wear a scarf I don't know about everybody else
um and look it's it's pretty jaunty you know it's the holiday season but uh
Heather and I were taking an uber over to this party and there's a giant tree that has uprooted
the street in my neighborhood like it looks like an earthquake hit it and if you have a
Prius or a low car it always scrapes the bottom and people get pissed the uber driver every time
like don't go that way they go that way they scrape the bottom of the car so last night I'm sitting
there and I just getting my head in the car nicked my head on the roof a little bit and it's set
like a blind rage into my brain like I thought I was going to lose my mind for a minute it was so
painful then we start going and then this guy turfs out on this fucking hill bump Jesus
yankin my head around I was like I'm gonna have to get out and walk to this fucking thing go to the
party had a nice time I saw some old friends but then I got back and with all our bitching about
ubers I wanted to give a shout out to a young man I won't say his name but you ever have an uber
driver where you didn't want him to stop talking this man was a god damn delight now this might
have been cuz I had had 3040 drinks but it's funny last night you were able to have drinks with the
bad neck yeah I know I didn't take a muscle relaxer I just I'm just worried about it because I've
never taken a muscle relax oh that's it I don't know where you're saying my neck hurts too bad my
neck hurts very bad but I thought you were saying that's why you couldn't drink no I didn't want
right but you hung out last night is my point yeah went to this party yeah but I had worked all day
on a script from like nine to nine and I had to get out of the fucking house all right but I mean
just saying maybe you save a little fun for your real friends in this business show I'm going out
with not just the people that paint the pockets green that's going out with you and it wouldn't hurt
you to paint my pockets green once in a while it's all I'm saying
now if I may I guess we should pop on over to path was that the end of the story
I mean I wasn't really telling a story I was telling what I did you didn't want him to stop
talking oh he's no he's just completely delightful like it was the one one of the few times I've
ever had an Uber driver where we were like all three of us genuinely laughing the whole way home
okay and it reminds you there are nice people in the world I I tipped him a $10 bill I you know
good Uber driver that's great lift I should say lifts the better company was it lift or was it
lift okay is left left it was left now over at the movie corner Joe why don't you start today because
I want to hear how Bohemian Rhapsody was I know you liked it more than most I was excited to get it
in the mail it was the first screener I got this year where I was like oh cool every other screener
I was happy to receive it and it was anything from a movie that I said I'll never watch this
to I'd watch this right but Bohemian Rhapsody was the one that I got where I was like man I'm
excited to see this like I followed the story of this film since the Sasha Baron Cohen days right
I popped it in it starts right off the bat right off the bat and you're gonna have to get past
the fact that this man has been accused several times now of molesting children basically sure
it's a very well shot film Brian Singer well we don't know how much of it even did but that's well
yeah it's true too he walked off set halfway but right off the bat the movie he does get the soul
directors credit and right off the bat the movie is very interestingly shot it's it's it's very well
done you know somebody to love kicks in and you're you know you're just you're you if you love
Queen you're immediately feeling it from the first second when they sing fat bottom girls do they zoom
in on a fat bottom of a girl no and what bothers me about that sequence in the movie is they put fat
bottom girls in on like their first tour that now came out like 1980 that's what I've heard and
what it's not like I'm going to have a really hard time getting past that because ultimately people
don't care but the issue is if people do really get into Queen through this movie which a lot of young
people are doing you're learning their history all wrong and I see no reason to not tell it the way
it happened well it makes no sense it's not it's not like it's not like there's an event related to
fat bottom girls or something well it's just not that early I'm not still talking about fat bottom
the history it some of it happens a little out of sequence or or a little too conveniently
where they sacrifice some of the poignantly yeah sure they sacrifice some of the cool aspects of
the story more deserved just a cursory remark it's it's they sacrifice some cool stuff that actually
happened like aides well no that's in there oh they do go I thought they didn't even mention him
that's no no that's all in death or anything I'm going to get to that because I was my big
that was why I was apprehensive about seeing it to begin with the like when they wrote another
one bites the dust it was because the label was saying like you guys are done nobody wants to hear
your bullshit anymore it's all about funk right now and whatever and they were like basically like
fuck you and then went off and wrote another one bites the dust and came back and was like here's your
funk yeah then it went it was like the number one funk record of all time right so like they don't
put that part in it they just have them arguing about like where they're gonna go next and then the
bass player just starts playing it and they're like oh that's a nice riff so my favorite song of all
time arguably uh now you got to get back like weird al's version another one rides the bus who doesn't
I've always felt the weird al versions were superior yeah I agree I had a theory for a while that
weird al was actually doing the original versions of the songs they were that much better sure
I think I heard smells like nirvana before I heard smells like teen spirit honestly and that's
pretty sad uh that's one that's so close that you you probably you probably were like I don't even
mean obviously look there's gonna be a point all right I can't today with the puns but I do appreciate
the effort trying to chime in trying to reach in here right away I can I'm just I'm I want to tell you
about this movie though go on I mean like honestly because I'm surprised at my reaction to this thing
let's hear it's it's it's you're gonna have to get through some biopic bullshit that you hate
right you know there's of court like the first scene is the dad being like Freddie you can't
just be a dreamer you know what I mean like you all that stupid shit is in there um but isn't
it true that Mike Myers is in there and says like nobody's gonna draw of a round banging their head singing
Bohemian reps it emits yeah that's as you say it into camera or to another character uh he actually
goes Bohemian reps the uh yeah sure he does that he breaks into the Wayne character for a minute sure
yeah uh it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's pretty on the nose no way yeah that's what I was
thinking of I couldn't remember what the Wayne thing was sorry anyway um it went anyway and shepherd
how about this movie Damon Wayne's world Damon Wayne's world is it Damon and and Wayne together no it's
Damon Wayne's oh and like a Sean Wayne's or you know I mean that just sounds very generic to me
they're just there I mean you're having all the pun fun today I'm just trying to jump on with
something Damon Wayne's world all right we'll work on it sounds like a mad tv sketch ready to go
in my opinion uh anyway I found the movie to be uh I loved the portrayal of Freddie Mercury
I am a little confused as to what all the controversy was it certainly does explore his homosexuality
and it explore what huh what Freddie Mercury yeah yeah he was gay what but you heard about all the
criticism of the film where they were like it it glazes over it yeah no it doesn't it doesn't glaze
over it at all it tells everything I've ever read about the guy it tells the story that I've always
heard about him and it deals with his homosexuality in the way that a guy in the 70s
who was brought up by fiercely religious middle eastern parents right or Arab parents rather
would deal with it it was not an easy thing for him to to to accept are these people mad that there
weren't like Dallas Byers club but fucking scenes or like there were like doors closing right probably
there's like scenes where he kisses dudes and stuff and it's not you know and then there are the scenes
where it like early on where he's like sort of sneaking off somewhere yeah um it to me it just came
across like this is how this guy came to terms with it and by the end of the movie spoiler alert
he has fully accepted himself his parents have accepted him and it ends with the live aid thing which
I thought was going to be a dumb place to end it but instead it's this wonderful triumphant moment of
the spirit and the guy it's awesome it's I was crying my fucking eyes out I I love the guy more
than I ever did it was it was an uplifting film it makes you want to go out and live your fucking life
the music's amazing and my favorite scene is when he says like when he gets diagnosed he tells the band
and he's like I don't have time to be their poster boy or their cautionary tale I'm doing what I was
put here to do I'm gonna be an entertainer like he's just like fuck you disease fuck all this I'm
not letting it stop me he's like I don't want he says to the man I don't want your sympathy like let's
fucking do this and they do it and it's awesome all right and I was crying my fucking eyes out and then the
movie ends with a credit what during the credits they show in the actual video of actual queen playing
don't stop me now which is my favorite queen song next to another one fights dust and don't stop me now
and I just love the movie man I fucking loved it all right you know and all of it made sense when I
saw it and I was I was an unseen critic for a while the film because I was like I don't get why it
doesn't cover this I don't get why they stop it 10 years before he dies I don't get right and when
I saw it it all made sense and it was just an awesome movie do they go into flash Gordon no
so they did skip some pretty important thing yeah they also don't cover when they did the
highlander soundtrack fair enough Joe I saw another big holiday release borrowed from you as a matter
of fact Mary Poppins returns now well how many similarities to Batman returns are in this film
well they're both disappointing oh Batman returns shit now I was thinking Batman begins I can't
believe that you think Batman begins is the disappointing of those two Batman films I love Batman
returns and I did not love Batman begins that's that's what I'm saying to you hi this Thursday I
have tickets to see Batman returns and Gremlins at the Egyptian theater I might go if any hellians want
to catch me over there catch me outside wasn't that a big meme catch me outside I don't know I'm
girl on Dr. Phil and she was like catch me outside like meaning like I'll fight you I'll fight you
doctor yeah I like that me too anyway Mary Poppins returns synopsis of my first viewing of it
oh oh man Mary Odin go wind this is Lynn Manuel Miranda pay Lynn my boy go round the streets of
London town and then I fell asleep two lines of this Lynn Manuel Miranda so the next night I fired up
all right Pat you got a little sleep in you let's sit down and enjoy this another couple bars
a Lynn Manuel worst British accent I've ever heard of my entire life perhaps worse than the original
Dick Van Dyke's bad accent but at least Dick Van Dyke had some fucking charm Lynn Manuel Miranda
stinks up the joint in this movie something awful he can't sing he is not a good actor and he can't
do the accent he's not funny he's not charming now here's what's good about it Emily Blunt
is awesome as Mary Poppins she does a very good job she's just doing an impression of Julie Andrews
but she does a good job I happen to love the original Mary Poppins I've never seen it I never will see
it I think you'd probably love it too it's all it's undeniable it's a great movie don't give a rat
sass about it it's a great movie and I enjoyed saving Mr. Banks about the about the making of Mary Poppins
but folks I can't stress this enough don't go see Mary Poppins it is terrible when they go at some point
and this was a scene that could have been edited in five minutes they go to visit Merrill Streep who's
like playing like crazy and Dorinda and then she does this whole song like oh crazy and don't
ring that and dances around for five six minutes Merrill Streep like with pink air and the movie was
trash here's why I never want to I've seen it get great reviews too Mary Poppins returns is trash here's
why I never wanted to see the movie it always looked to me like a Harry Potter movie if you took out all
the cool Harry Potter shit and it was just about regular people in a in a hair and Hogwarts or
something I did it's not like entertaining it's in that nice sweet spot of like bed knobs and broomsticks
and all those kind of movies that they take me back to a simpler time I used to love that good songs
in a broom I could sing you any song from Mary Poppins right now name one my pussy aches since yesterday's
mall pussy I'm New York's
stay down in song you got to say me pussy me pussy I
It's almost the melody of Gilligan's Island you were just doing there yeah
it's got that great song feed the beds
Oh
Now Chitty Chitty bang bang is in this movie or is that it's own movie Chitty Chitty's is own thing okay
But that's also I feel driving over to this Christmas party last night bouncing around like my boy Chitty Chitty bang bang
That's how a previous girlfriend and I would refer to anal we'd call it Chitty Chitty bang bang
Oh boy oh I'm sorry is that not as good as a
Queen Viennian or wherever the fuck you said 10 minutes ago I'm just trying to keep this clean
I don't think we need the explicit rating on here. Well you you were the one that's saying my pussy aches
I wasn't me I was giving the lyric
Anyway, it's not good and I don't recommend it this song I couldn't I couldn't hum you one song from Mary
Turns I could sing you all 20 songs from Mary Poppins
It says a lot the animation sucked it all just sucked I've seen people calling it the best movie of the year
Uh
I Pat I watched bah hum duck oh looney too. Oh my christmas Carol
I would bet I would bet it's pretty good
I really like Mickey Mickey's Christmas Carol it didn't carry
You might be surprised to hear it didn't hold the same weightiness that the actual christmas Carol depictions
Donald duck as you might have a man or daffy duck excuse me as you might have imagined a scrooge
He's running a toy company or something
Can you do the daffy duck or a Donald duck never been able to know I can't do either
What what what that's Donald the daffees like the list you know
Yeah, not from suck attached that's uh
I like I prefer looney tunes to Disney except in their versions of christmas Carol
I think all looney tunes movie suck
Actually quack busters was pretty good the Donald the daffy duck car one
I've seen quack busters, but their movies usually aren't good they're better at the shorts
Whereas Disney to me is the opposite, but
Porky pig was was Bob Cratchit sure
Instead of tiny Tim being a dying child
It was just a girl the little girl that wanted a doll that or that porky couldn't afford
Okay, they lined it up a lot
But they did commit to the ghost part which I was shocked so Vester was the was the Bob Marley ghost
So Vester is just a boring character boring character
And death the death ghost was tweety bird was christmas future right character or christmas past right which was perfect christmas present was um
I can't remember
Christmas future was Tasmanian devil
Yeah, it was well cast as far as your looney tunes christmas Carol goes he was a well cast
They they considered the choice. Yeah, but uh
But after that and it was also new -ish
You know, so it's not like it's male blank during the voices. Oh, no, I wouldn't have watched that
You know and you can always tell dad bugs is in it a little bit not too much, but it's probably probably bugs light for
looney tunes film I could go for a nice cold bugs light right now folks
Oh boy, uh, I watched pattington two
Oh
Yeah, because it's the end of the year and certain movies keep popping up on every 10 bus list and you're like maybe they're good
pattington two
Was pretty awesome if you like that like west Anderson kind of fake world
Like that grand booted booted past hotel vibe
That's what this is except it's got a couple of animatronic bears in it. It was very cute. It was funny
Had a sweet story didn't overstay. It's welcome Hugh Grant was very funny as the villain
And it really does create like a very cool
visual world that I enjoyed spending time in
Again pattington pattington always struck me as a west Anderson film without any the incest or inappropriate
sex scenes between children right uh, why am I there?
What am I here for? I
In your trial
Yeah, they're right
My final will be another Christmas tale
There is best of Christmas red Christmas
Okay, it's a movie about a woman getting her period during a shopping spree at macy's
folks oh my god
Oh
My god red Christmas
It's that time of the month for the Christmas sale and for mommy's little visitor
What is going on? I don't know. I'm just being dirty and gross. Uh red Christmas is a terrible terrible terrible horror movie
starring de Wallace of many horror movie fame many I tell you and horror movie film fame
I cast de Wallace this week in the cool kids really but she has to go
Because we're shooting it like Christmas day basically. She had to drop out but I love de Wallace
She had an awesome audition and we want to cast her in the future
I love she still has to audition. She was in ET for Christ sakes. I know. Who do you got a bang in this fucking business?
I know my god. I don't usually see the actress that come in and read for one line parts
You're like wait a minute. This guy's been in every sitcom I've ever seen. Oh god. It's dark out there. It's a sick business
Anyway de Wallace is in this film
She's about the only redeeming quality in it
aside from the
She has a son who has Down syndrome and the actor playing him actually does have Down syndrome and he's very good in it as well
He's very funny and uh
An endearing um, but aside from those two
This is an unwatchable mess of a film. It's it's billed as a comedy. Uh, it's not a comedy in any way shape or form
It's not scary in any way shape or form
It is
It's messages confusing. It's about a woman who got an abortion
20 years ago
But the abortion didn't take and the kid lived
And then it's about the the you know mutilated child who's now 20 or 21 years old coming back on Christmas data to to confront the mother
Okay
So here's why the message gets mixed up
You're like oh wait, so is this some sort of pro life cautionary tale
Right because she's hiding the abortion from people or whatever
But then when the kid shows up and mentions it she doesn't believe him
And she starts screaming that's some pro life freak
Trying to ruin and I'm like okay, so this lady isn't pro life
So why was she hiding that she had an abortion? Who cares? Right then you she turns
One of the six people in the house is a priest it makes no fucking sense
And it's not like there's some debate between the two about the morality or whatever of it
These just there's just a priest character who doesn't say anything on the subject at all
I'm very confused by what this movie was was was trying to say yeah, it for some reason takes place in Australia
So but but then D Wallace is the star and she doesn't have an Australian accent, but all of her kids do
And then a guy that I guess she's dating now because the dad's dead has a southern American accent
But none of this thing makes sense that the aborted kid shows up dressed like literally like death in a black cloak
With bandages all around his face so you can't see his face
They invite him into the house
You tell me a guy like that shows up on your doorstep Christmas or not you're not saying come inside right now
They invite him into the house and then he's he doesn't know what presence are
He somehow was figured out how to track down the woman that aborted him 21 years ago
He's got the insight on how to do that
But he's never heard the word literally never heard the word presence before in his life. He doesn't know what it is
He uh
He uh and then it's this like terrible elephant man ripoff like the voice the guy does where he's like he's like
I've never heard a page before
So he's got an English accent this fucking thing makes no sense
It's a terrible terrible terrible terrible movie. It's essentially
90 minutes for you of you waiting for them to show the guy's face
They show it the makeup is terrible looks ridiculous looks like he's wearing like a fucking
Halloween adventure mask
Ha
It's a real piece of shit. You really maybe want to see this thing
It's and it's got like decent reviews. Yeah, like what I think bloody disc like a year ago. Like
There's a recent movie. Yeah, bloody disgusting. I think it was like it's a fun little holiday thriller
It's like what are you talking about?
This is terrible
Ha ha
Ooh for D Wallace man poor D Wallace
Wasn't she in the hailing also she was in the hailing. Yeah
This is this is one of our great scream queens and she's you know she's being reduced to this
I watched
I rewatched because you and I heard that song
We went out to a bar a couple weeks ago from European vacation
Oh, yeah, I remember like the whole level that's like in a foreign language whatever. Yeah
I can't I don't know the language, so I can't sing they also use it in jackass. Yeah
Uh, and it reminded me that whilst I've seen christmas vacation
Easily 50 times and the original vacation easily 30 times
And Vegas vacation 10 probably
I really never revisit European
You're a you're a mystery man to me you've revisited Vegas over European
I mean Vegas came out when I was like prime age. I was like 14 and very into the franchise. I liked it. I didn't love it
but
European I just never got into
I rewashed it and I wasn't into it again. Oh come on. It's not great
There's very few big laughs in it
There's this weird running gag where everyone's trying to molest his 13 year old daughter
Like you see you see grown men like cropping her at various point it is an odd runner in the film and I looked up that girl
And I'm like whatever happened to hurt dad. Yeah, that's sad, isn't it? I mean I just I was finding it hard to laugh and there's that scene where Williams
Vodka like almost fucks her on like the picnic table right like during the family cookout right
I do like the pig in the poke sequence
uh
I I like it. I like all the rusty stuff. I like that Rusty's like playing this horny little kid
This was the first time I think I'd seen it with all the nudity. It had a tremendous amount of nudity and it was only PG 13 lots of tits in that movie
I like it. I think Christmas is better. I think the first one is better. Yes
It is the the the the weakest link of that trilogy because I don't even recognize I refused even recognize Vegas once
They took national lampoons off the top of it, right? Like this isn't we're not in the series anymore
Well, you know, Vegas vacation is the whole lot better than the next one which I saw called
Uncle Eddie's Hawaiian vacation. No, it was I know what you're talking about. It's called Christmas vacation part two. Yes
Eddie
Takes the family to Bermuda or something absolute horse shit
What makes Vegas vacation? That's why I like Vegas vacation as much as I do is because I've seen what came after
I think that should be the thing you you know when when Randy quay dials on the internet being like you think I'm crazy
You should just you should just show him the cover of that movie right? Yeah, you're crazy. Look at look at this. Look what you made
Yeah, you were in the you were in uh the the last detail for Christ sakes right what this is business is terrible
What it's done to Randy quayton D Wallace
D Wallace is fine. She just that was in a movie. You didn't care for she's not out taking pictures of her asshole and the
Nevada desert is that Randy quay? Yeah, the man's lost his mind
I don't know he posts like sex tapes with his wife
What now he doesn't yes, he does I haven't seen that I've seen the his band don't seek it out the star killers or whatever
Yeah, we like sings about how they're like
You know like how they come after like it's all a conspiracy to ruin celebrities and stuff. Uh -huh. Oh boy
That's a shame old Randy quayde. Yeah, Randy Q
One of the funniest men that ever lived
That I can't give you but I have gotten a lot of laughs from through the years as an actor I mean
I mean there's few people that are as funny as him in
In Christmas vacation kingpin too, you know. Oh christ. Yeah very underrated performance
He also was great in a movie called quick change with Bill Murray that I really love and Gina Davis very good movie um
I was almost watched the man who knew too little the other night
The Bill Murray movie, but I remember it suck. I remember kind of enjoying it
I feel like that's the last time he was straight up Bill Murray. Yeah, like
After that came like lost in translation and that was it. He was he was down that road. Yeah
Um
Well, wait, it's look. It's we're about 45 in which you probably get to the movie, right
Let's do it. You on his screaming ends news psycho. I do have a quick one. I'll drop real fast before the new year hits uh
Uh, very exciting news for Star Wars fans. I would think I know I'm excited, but word on the street is George Lucas
Has been called into assist with episode nine
particularly a certain
What did I say that wrong? No, I'm just enjoying the build up here. Uh a certain storyline
revolving around a specific classic character so I think
The speculation is right one of the Ewok
The speculation obviously is after the
Controversy or or the Contra debate about the last Jedi and the Luke Skywalker portrayal
That they are bringing Lucas in to make sure that they close out the Skywalker story properly
And they give it a bang
Kevin Smith
Was on set for two weeks
Uh, just we're watching and hanging out, but he has been very public about like look. I can't give details obviously
But I wept
It is amazing like
JJ is doing God's work. This is the movie you want and that's what he said about Force Awakens
And he was right about Force Awakens and I don't doubt that he's right about this
Uh, I do like the last Jedi, but I do think
This is the ninth installment of the Skywalker saga at saga. This is it
I want them to end it with a big Star Wars bang. I don't want them
Going off the tracks and trying new shit
Now this is because this is this is all we get with this is it
So I want them to do it right and I want them to bring us back
To to childhood with it and I think they're going to and I've been saying from the beginning
I'm pretty sure that's why they had JJ in there
Again because he's good at that sort of thing
And I am thrilled that Lucas is somehow putting his stamp on this new trilogy somewhere
Because I think that that's not only appropriate but but right and it's what should happen
He created these characters. Let him be part of the final phase
So uh, that's exciting news. I'm excited
You know Joe so am I
There's a there's an electricity in the air
After you talk about Star Wars
Uh, I think you're being a smart ass. No, I'm excited to see the picture
I've enjoyed all these. I like except you know except those prequels but
I've always found them to be
entertaining, but I don't have the obsession
I have the obsession
But I'm also not a psycho
You know, I didn't think that last Jedi ruined my fucking life
Right. I was a little upset about it and then I watched it a few more times and I like it
It's not perfect, but I like it
So I can't wait to see what they do with this new one. There's there's all kinds of crazy rumors
swirling around that like they're they're gonna bring Vader back into it somehow and Darth
Garth Vader actually Garth yeah, yeah, it's another Wayne's world crossover
Was that done ever they must have done that somewhere right they probably did Garth Vader yeah
Uh anyway our movie for today I better use the lightsaber as a boner go ahead as a boner
Yeah, or yeah when he or at least unsheathed and went swing right all right. That's all I wanted to say go
See
Our movie for today folks on this as we as we was it was we barrel toward 2019
Can't come soon enough reanimator, which is appropriate reanimation a new life a change
Resolutions it's the new year, so this excuse me Joe. This is the new year
Did you and I don't feel any different?
You know when we miss a song death cab for cutie. You know when we missed we missed Joe. This is Christmas
No, I've done that one before you did yeah, okay pretty sure
The judgiest Christmas carol of all of all time yeah by the by the least involved asshole who's ever lived
Don't get me started on John Lennon
All right, I am not a fan all right come on
Pat I'm gonna set us up with some new drinky poos. Why don't you set the audience up with what the basic plot of reanimator is
the basic plot I watched it a while ago, but
basic plot is a young
med student
Is really into experiments of the brain and he falls in with a cookie doctor
Who also enjoys such experiments
Next thing you know they're bringing bodies back to life
It's a classic sort of
zombie tale done
You know as as outrageous as it gets done in like a fairly straightforward
Realistic style even as it gets crazier and crazier. That's what I like about it. It's got a very deadpan vibe
Almost like an evil dead type vibe where people deal with the horror and very
straightforward manner. I like it
There's a very memorable scene where a man
picks up a severed head and is going to go down on a woman with
The head and the head at one point starts going down on the woman
And that's the kind of scene you just
Don't get enough of in my opinion. I would recommend if you've never seen it to watch it with the joe bob brings commentary
Again, we are not being sponsored by shudder, but I had so much fun watching all these great movies
Some of them I'd never seen with joe bob. He had all kinds of great reanimator facts
But it was done so cheap steward Gordon is a guy who makes awesome low -budget shit almost every time
I recommend this crime thriller called king of the ants that he did that was awesome
um
Steward Gordon's great doesn't does great director mostly hp lovecraft adaptations. Yes
But you know did uh, and that's what this is as well. Yeah, reanimator
Great performances all around Jeffrey cooms of course
Uh, I have not seen the sequels to reanimator. Have you bride? I own the trilogy. Okay
I'm a big fan of the entire trilogy. I think the weakest is the third one
Because I think that's the one that doesn't involve steward Gordon and and or at least he's not directing it
And his absence is in my opinion noticeable, but coams is still in there
It's a different storyline
It's he's in prison and he is called upon by like the wardin or whatever to start becoming involved in these medical procedures
So I miss that it doesn't have the characters from the first two films in it
But the second one bride of reanimator is awesome. Okay, really awesome
Even fucking crazier than the first movie
My favorite element of the second movie is that the severed head
They reanimate bat wings and and attach them to the head and that head flies
Throughout the movie. Okay, which is a lot of fun. Uh, it's a pretty crazy film um, but I really like it
I really love that reanimator one
It's um
You know, it's a classic. It's it's it's that classic and it was a
Interestingly enough. I believe
It was made by
What's the company um
Son of a bitch the puppet master company
That makes like all the schlocky horror movies. I don't know. I'm sorry
No, you know, we've talked about it and I said I called you once they go they're having a sale and you're like arrow not arrow now
Kino, I don't know
What the hell is the name of the company? This is gonna try me fucking crazy
That we've we've talked I've full moon. Yes. I think reanimators are full moon. Is it not?
Probably yes, I think it is I got the special arrow blu -ray which does really just as good a work as criteria on yeah, they're great
I haven't even cracked it open yet, but it seems like it's got great stuff documentaries etc
So you got the special edition
I wanted that so bad and then it sold out it's like 20 bucks
Uh, well, there was there was a first there were two editions of it. Uh, the initial one was like 40
But it had like it had like a fucking recut of the movie or something on it had something on it was three cuts of it
I mean, it's got everything you could want. I would think why don't you give me that now?
Just give you my DVD. I think I deserve it
For doing what? I think I just as a fan deserve it more than you do all right
But that's just my but I just set him a fan. I just said I loved it
so
All right fair enough. It's a great movie. It's just um
It's an extremely creative movie
They do a lot with a very limited budget and it looks awesome the effects are awesome
Great good scares in it. It's funny
It's a great movie uh big daddy Kane one of the great rappers of all time uh
Samples the film on his second album. It starts with the sample of the guy going is mr. Kane loose in this hospital
Which uh, I didn't know that's what it was from I got that album when I was a kid and then when I finally saw a reanimator
Uh, five or six years ago. I was like holy shit. That's the big daddy Kane sample. That was pretty cool
Uh, and I do remember one of the the third second or third time I ever watched this film I watched it with Pete Holmes
Okay, because he had never seen it and he expressed some interest. So I put it on and during the world
Literally giving the girl some head scene. Yeah
He was exclaiming oh no from the couch. It really he found it mortify. Yeah
um
But that scene is insane. It isn't that it's fucking nuts
Yeah, and I love that like the head can still control its body right but the body is all like clumsy right
Because the head's not attached to it
um
Interesting film fact too steward Gordon was an originally approached to do a vampire film
And he said there are too many vampire films coming out. I want to do a Frankenstein film
and he landed on an adaptation of
Herbert West reanimator
Which is the old hp lovecraft story. So that's how that all started
Recommended my my hog is fully erect
Two hogs way up two hogs way up for reanimator
folks
That's our show and that's 2018
Uh, this is like the New Year's Eve drop
Something like that or like it's like the 30th or 31st. It's right there folks. I hope you catch the 31st though
That sounds right
I think
Uh, if our first ones Christmas Eve, yeah
Um have a great holiday whatever you celebrate celebrate it well
Enjoy your time with your family. It won't be here forever
You know put aside your differences this year if you can
Unfortunately, this comes out basically after the holiday so if you've already squandered it
We don't know what to tell you try to piece it back together make it your new year's resolution
Uh have a big have a good 2019. It's got to be better than 2018
We will be back the third week of January as I said
There will still be at least you know, however many Mondays are left at that point
They will you'll get a new episode each one of those Mondays and a bonus up
Uh, and the bonus up for December should be out by now
Uh, should I do a shout outs here on the patreon? Uh, no here
Here here because if you only pay for shout outs, you you don't have enough to hear them then all right
Because it's only the attitude. No, I don't I honestly didn't mean it with an attitude. Well it sounds
Attitude. I'm very aware of that venom in your moisture
venom
Speaking of stinkers. Did you see that? No, I didn't say that I hear it either. Yeah
All right, here we go with uh
You shout outs. Oh quick plugs um
I'll make Gotham comedy club this coming week and headlining
In New York City if you're around come on out. Uh, I'm also headlining the rec room in orange county in california for everybody
That's always saying when are you doing a california headlining show near la there it is
Uh, that's yeah, it's one show only January 19th
Uh, at the rec room uh, and uh, that's and then oh my hard my fiction stories are officially out in um
Penn house the first one came out or comes out in in January this week or whatever sometime
Uh, so check that out and joder was a comedy on instagram pat anything for you before we
Sure the Patrick Walsh twitter and instagram and the cool kids returns
Within extremely funny funeral episode guest starring jack hay harry nba great rick fox
And the warden from shawshank redemption mr bob guntan together at last
uh, that airs january 4th my birthday is january 5th and i expect gifts
Here we go with shout outs anthony v minito aka party mcfly philip Rashad marcus magehi
erick martina's piv
Jared packwin Christopher muse
Christopher museel
Daniel pescal joe i'm not racist. I was just tired and nervous
nickel will nolton dav kraneski mat reaves mat rees wow i'm really fucking these up today
i'm sorry guys floppy Jonathan sprouls chris simmons
brine scatter scatter shactor
brine shactor
taylor lindie west can't be the real lindie west
tomas kosa dustin collins kevin switzkowitz not
medium rare benedict back dan hepanoids tom holt
hose arquimides ibarra justin tyler edmund agabo omar
alic ma
monagon alic monagon mark who
hyanian god you you fucking with me
these names are getting very complicated how would you say that i'm not making fun of it
mark who and then h y n n i n e n
once more h y n n i n e n
hidden in hidden in it's a lot of ends that's a tough one
stuff nobody says it's not gonna be tough baby bop and barney and baby bops blanky
chris marsh brook atoms david crumholz nice watch the douche yeah
alexander manta rubio matchairs john and bk
martin nicholas
mccalsland zack baldwind derrick dan jar chow rph chrystifer renalds calibsoranson patrick
backster julie baili violet you're turning violet violet
is that from woolly wonka it is michael witsett
anna sam eliet bred her way professor pap smear
funny that's very good patrick wathan truth crab
also funny what is that i don't know baby laugh oh it's just okay i don't know it's a reference
as i think i'm not i'm not challenging you david to wit zack henderson sandy bug
coal rothaker waffles steven calpa a stupid bloated booze bag aka sam michael
andrew telekin or telashon kelly amoroso beth gaston
charifa david denny devlow trever gage joshua christian sin kp flin elvae and reekas
matwheeler lesley coffin welfare dentist jackson c lowmeyer ash augden reign purple peacock sterling
abrigo chrystifer sebella steve murdoch drew tiberius pull monica not from friends
tyler la point steve smith loopay pita piceo tauncy zonjick
mat robin wilfoli kevin regati yeah regati josef christian renalds josh smolridge curt zygler
britney Ferguson shon florin danney rud natalie heartline leo lopez
turn on your hotline emily rook not rock scott through nick mascara davdell greco curt zygler
curie pageit did i start repeating myself i don't know man
that's weird i just had a weird like deja vu thing uh where did i leave off
curt zygler chloe pageit scott birchit dennis ormston travis hinds john wizen gruber
mathew maguire angela poor caro james obryan mathew moon jayfisher shonlil john hollywood
jake mick alivane meridith mick williams Gregory hasel jessie jenickey
mike greenwood briana alkire mat supportive guy oops i said that last one wrong
anthony rudrigas chris passmore kacy jones syngy robert haines natalie hatley will pitman
kevin mick nanny kevin driscoll jenn wessels joehoffman scotsweeney jay miller
Clayton stamper amanda lankister michael ballas ethin garnage oh no i'm sorry ethin gamage
james gui rolamo daryk adams shonhole adam lounsbury
bret frangela vinson francs joseph regusa or regosa steve Burton and a demario bow
aron robberts scot john ben metty kevin eason fucking rich tillman
saracatherin paul murchie scot sweezy cara conini joshua taz bozeman Taj bozeman
chuck andru's tom laverick tucker rouch john smith andru brian belaria will helms jennifer anna
tl mun holen molissa alvarez jake bullock slay bodies not reindeer zero fox trot dot com
maccrofford jennah richer deer lord why aren't these in alphabetical order dimming
brine calls tim drain michael madrigal visit mr suit records in lankister pa
richard howinstein bretten phrasier or phraser shon luke fiziock karen kill garif
listen to my favorite murder shelby l nathan basket gary mmyron dillon laur fill borrell edmund dillon
the black magic ninja scot pauline syrell daphne kellog tristan avry hunk master cent
richard aiman mathieu j brown julia guyer charity Ferguson hank from dan kakes
nick walther alexandr stein emily marvel john bwhat visit zambian's horocrafts on etsy
mori benjamin nickolas burns alex nelson jermy cool
too fat to skate alex shipley shon pinock amanda libson timothy let's go shane nazarian hold on i
gotta take a sip here a lot of people impressive list
daddy got his work juice smelly bubbles samantha kefir i love you
dave bellinger hunter mcdonald justin bohager adam benbenek mani rios demonio rubio
brandon gash jake forote rob lines jika barrett barrett jordan c maxwell ashcroft ryan colar
barb alan rebekah kohen chris bowens mic gibbons danie joys michael Dawson jennifer smith
conner denne he anthony jay guajardo anti johannison timmy kay megan ly brand
scott blickens durford bret wemer tristan karlson
lara sexton anthony guajardo weston thomas vidhill jared blare richie verdugo chris hooper
emily farens our matriarch hello emily we love you shon el
dave comarek abbey manuel kim de angelo jonathan galotte michael mcb steffony power
diago campos stefen moussell zowy blaskevich
aeslie kivinsland dan mccloud lorenz bunganiers alohandro saldaga
i'm sorry alohandro salgato tracy reddington shantamis amanda alzamora
jason wible mike curie drew spindler andru koval koval koval
sam michael aron milanowski scott nolan ben mysties of our moly rustles wort wort
dejanay wilford hello johnny furg michelle gold deniel duer arachlamora kevin marcenick
laran sanderson jared smalridge will potorff natalie cragg kyle kinslin
the man whose name we cannot speak anibaba duc scott paton kevin stickers at pint services dot com
the block watch rage less name sounds asian michael ilo read aesthetic and max unrath
folks i can't think of a better way to end the new year with reading a list of the people we are
most grateful to our fans that is an overwhelming list of supporters and whether you support
on patreon or not we just love the fact that you support by listening uh we thank you we're
we're we're we're touched to say the least uh thank you very much everybody we'll see you in the new
year and we'll see you in hell