I'm here for Betrivers Online Casino in Sportsbook with poker icon Phil Helmiot.
And now thanks to the excitement of Betrivers, I'm also a slots icon.
That's great! And a same game, Parley icon.
Cool, cool. A Blackjack icon, a Moneyline icon,
A Roulette. Take it from Phil Helmiot.
If you love games, Betrivers is the place to play in Betrivers.
Games on.
Must be 21 plus in present at West Virginia.
Void were prohibited. Terms in conditions apply.
Gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gambling.
The football season is full of guarantees, and here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October, if
your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning or winning money back in fan
cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
Winning hits different here.
Must be 21 -plus, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamberler, offer not available in all
dates, terms apply, see Fanatic Sportsbook app.
This is a Headgun podcast.
Welcome to, we'll see you and how your favorite podcast discussing, reviewing and commenting
on horror, fantasy and sci -fi, both contemporary and classic, a very exciting show today.
We are doing, this is a cutting edge episode, we're right on the, the fingers on the pulse
of pop culture.
here. We are about to do a review of Thor Ragnarok, which we have just seen just out of the
theater up at the, uh, the, the Americana here in, uh, beautiful Glendale. So Pat, yes.
Why don't you get us started here? Um, okay. Um, well, how are you doing, Joe, for
I mean, a little romance first before just forcing it in.
I just thought you could say the opening phrase
and then we could get rolling down.
Oh, sure, sure, I know what you mean.
I think you're talking about it.
And then I'll play with your push.
Oh my God.
I think you're talking about getting on with the show
and also on with the,
Joe
Probably you're worst one you've ever done. That was my least favorite for sure
I didn't have anything in the hopper. I just started talking and that's that's what came out and I'm sorry
But I was reading today. There was a discussion on the Facebook page, which I always encourage you to check out
About what the finest on what the Joe's were and they were citing, you know
somebody decided the one from the Christine episode.
I don't even remember what these were.
Sure.
But there was a lot of talk about what were the best
and it intimidated me, frankly.
I was trying to live up to former glories
and in doing so, I created what I would say
is unquestionably the worst on with the Joe I've ever done.
Yeah, you didn't live up to shit that just then.
Yeah, it's that fear of failure.
It'll cripple you.
Yeah, it'll cripple you.
And this is a special episode also because this is our first shout out episode of this month will as we promise do them on the second and fourth episode of each month.
Bonus episode will drop at the end of the month.
Thank you again to all of the Patreon people out there supporting us and all the people up on the Facebook discussion forum and all that stuff.
We really really really really can't believe the support and we love it.
If you want to check out the Patreon, pledge page, it's a patreon .com slash WS why I ate
no shit patreon .com slash WS IYH pod you know I said it right the first time why I oh
Jesus why IH pod we'll see you in hell yes WS why IH pod that's a ease all right so go check
Stone sober folks. We are stone sober. It's like in kingpin when he's throwing up and he's like
I thought you weren't drinking anything. I don't throw up when I drink. I throw up when I don't
That's where we're at the only we don't throw up the only sad line in the whole movie. It is but it's great
Yeah, just great. Yeah. Now Woody Harrelson as we saw at the theater tonight
He's playing LBJ in the new Rob Reiner film. Well
I'm gonna see it my buddy Alan Mendobon produced it. He's a great man.
Just a little shout out. But, I was telling Joe, I fucking hate biopics.
You know, I hate biopics and the more prosthetics the more I hate him, and they got Woody, you know, all made up.
The worst makeup I think I've ever seen in a movie, I got two. I got two.
And I think they probably both either were nominated for or won Best Makeup because Best
Makeup usually the award goes to most makeup, right, which it shouldn't be.
Here we go.
Number one, a beautiful mind when they age up, Crow and Connolly at the end, who daddy?
That's some rough old age makeup.
I don't even remember what they looked like at the end.
It's very bad.
If you're doing old age makeup, just a little suggestion is all you need, you know?
Yeah, yeah.
Um, and then the other unquestionable winner for me is a picture called J Edgar.
That's, that's my number one.
That's when Ace would direct it.
Where every time DiCaprio would open his mouth, like a hunk of wax would fall off like into his coffee.
And they would just keep rolling.
Clint was like, we got the shot.
Yeah, that movie looked like he went to Target.
And there was like a you could be J Edgar for Halloween.
Yeah, it did just it didn't look like a mask and then they like ironed it.
It didn't look good. No, the look like Clint was like here.
I took a picture of my right ball.
Just make his face look like that.
And there's no excuse for bad makeup.
I don't get why I don't get why old people makeup is still so hard to do.
And they can make people have two faces and you know alien heads and all this shit to face for example like to face
Yeah, I know they throw a little CG in there a little sure on screen
But my point is is like why the hell is old people make up so hard to do also
Why don't you just like for the end of a beautiful mind in that kind of situation just hire two old actors sure to play them old
Do they do the saving private Ryan thing? That's not Damon on the book ends. It's an old man in the book ends
well and like okay so raising Arizona easily a top five movie for me one of my
all -time favorites Cohen Brothers there's a brief scene where Nicholas Cage and
Holly Hunter they flash forward into the future while Cage is dreaming it's
the final monologue of the movie and they flash forward to being elderly with a
bunch of children and that movie was made in 1987 on a budget of probably a million
dollars max and the makeup looks fantastic right you can tell it's cage and
hunter but they look great right what went wrong and it's the same with special
effects you know like Gremlins looks great 1984 the effects and they try to do
it now and you're like I see a blue like sheen around these creatures
thought that in the new planet of the apes and as cool as those effects are there
were moments where I was like you thought that was ready to hit the theaters well
So there's different effects, Pat.
I know.
You're talking animatronics versus CGI.
I just like to more.
That's all I can say.
I get it.
There's a little home spun quality that I like.
I get it. There's a word you don't hear every day.
Home spun. Home spun.
I know when I'm, that was my rap name.
What spun a speed?
Huh?
If you're spun, like they made a movie called Spun
with Jason's wife.
Are you on the stage?
It was crank, I believe.
They're not cranky. It was meth, I think.
Meth. You're spun out.
Cranky is a, is a cheat.
I think cranky is meth.
Cranky is a cheap cocaine, like a cocaine alternate that's very cheap, where the high
last, so I think that's what meth is, too, right?
Okay.
Isn't that what meth is?
Or are you smoke?
No, meth's like you smoke it.
Meth is different.
Spawn was about meth, though, because Mickey works trailer blows up at the end.
Yes, that's a meth thing. Not a great movie
Yeah, it was one of those things where it was like watch everybody you love take a dark turn
And it was just wasn't that interesting. Yeah, wouldn't you like to see all these actors on meth? I was like no, right frankly
No, I don't
I will say this about biopics. I think the description for every biopic should be hey
You know how you love this guy?
Yeah.
Well, watch this now.
I've never seen one where you walk away going.
I like the guy more.
Yeah, exactly.
Well, as we get older and it's going to be like, you know, probably Woody Harrelson
again playing Tom Petty in 10 years or something, it's just like, as much as I love Tom Petty,
I don't, I would rather watch a documentary.
If you're just going to be telling me the beats of their life and also fictionalizing it
somewhat as most biopics do and everybody's just begging for an Oscar I'd rather read a book or
watch a documentary they won't make a petty movie it's not scandalous enough well just wait who
knows I hope not what what do you think it'll be called my money's on won't back down obviously won't
back down. Well, or American guy. Well, I mean, couldn't it be stopped dragging me around?
Stop dragging my heart around. Whatever this wildflower, the Tom Petty. Sure. Wildflowers,
the story of Tom Petty. There's a fantastic four -hour documentary that I don't think we've ever
discussed near called Running Down a Dream. Oh, that's a good title for me. If you want to really
learned about Tom Petty, that's the way to do it. Or his biography, which I've been 12 pages
into for roughly six months. What's his biography called? I think just Petty. Petty.
Whatever, this would be a good name for the movie, Petty Bastard. Well sure, and then you do
a play on words through the whole movie they go, you know Tom, just because Petty's a
suiting suitable name for a guy as as you know as as petty as you
I couldn't get another word for petty right, but I you know you do that kind of thing, you know I got it
I'm very tired Pat. I was real tired on the last one, but that was for one in well
It's 11 p .m. On a Tuesday. I mean I'm I'm a little I'm certainly more amped up than I was Saturday night
I didn't know if I was gonna stay awake
there was there were some people that enjoy Monday's podcast but there was a
lot of talk about how we sounded perhaps suicidal and I got to tell you folks
you're not way off it was Pat and I went to dinner that night I don't know if
we talked about this part on the podcast but Pat and I went to dinner with our
buddy David Cremolt I don't think I said a word through the entire meal except
Except of course. Oh, that's right. Except of course not medium rare, not medium rare. Yes.
And then it was good that you didn't speak after that. Folks, I'd like to invite you over
to one of my favorite night spots, Pat's movie corner. And believe it or not, even though
I had nothing a few days ago, I got to stop you. I'm sorry, we forgot to do something before
or pets movie corner, we forgot.
We jerked off together.
Now, now, now, ready?
Get ready to do this.
I wiped it on you.
Get ready to do it.
Get ready to do the sound effect.
Folks, we're coming to you live from the hog house.
Oh, God.
I don't like this bit.
Why?
There's something about, at any time you say hog or pig,
which you do a lot, refer to people as pigs.
It just really rubs me the wrong way.
Well, we're not referring anybody as a pig right now we're just saying the hog we're calling our studio the hog house
I don't like it. All right, when the hog house indicate, especially at this time we should be a little more enlightened
that with what?
with
You know hog house. It's not you would you invite a woman over to a hog house?
What are we talking about? I'm not talking. Yes. I want our female listeners to feel comfortable entering our world of
do you think it's like a derogatory female thing?
No, I don't think that either.
Oh, what do you think?
That it's off -putting, hog house.
Did you just see a movie called Hog House?
I think you're, I think you're being sexist
for thinking it's gonna turn off the female listeners.
They can think, I don't think the men listeners
are loving it either.
I'll tell you what I didn't see one comment on on Facebook,
Hog House.
You will now.
Yeah, now we will.
Put it to a vote, folks.
Do you want the hug house bit to continue or not?
Please don't want it to continue folks. I
Proposed a question to Joe. We were walking out of the theater and there was an ad for some very boring new
Mark Wahlberg Kevin Spacey movie together at last and I think Michelle Williams was in it too
Anyway, I don't know anything about this movie and I think they're pretty much burying the release because of the new
to quote allegations about Kevin Spacey,
although I think in his case, he's starting to admit them.
Well, no, he kind of admitted it right off the bat.
He was just like, I was drunk, sorry about that.
Yeah, also, I'm gay.
Yeah, he deserved the shit he got for that.
Absolutely.
That fucking apology was dark shit.
But I proposed the question to Joe,
what if, let's say Kevin Spacey was a much bigger star,
Like it was the American beauty days or whatever. Let's say it is American beauty and there's an American beauty is about to come out
And in the mood which I forgot about of course, but in the movie he's lusting after an underage young lady
Who he does fuck at one point doesn't he they get closed? They don't fuck he masturbates to her and then they're about to but they don't actually do it
They're real close
She's like six supposed to be like 16. Yeah, he takes her shirt off and you see nipples and everything but
Okay, so let's say today let's say let's say it's that time period. Okay, it's about to come out
Spaces peg to win my pegs a bad choice of words. Spacy is earmarked to win a best actor
American beauty's got a lot of buzz. It's gonna be a big hit and a week before it comes out these spacey allegations hit
Could they could the producers of the film Sue Kevin Spacey for ruining their Oscar chances for
Retainting their great movie. I don't think they can because Tom Cruise didn't get sued when he blew like all the promotion for War of the World
Because he blew that by jumping on the couch. Well, he did that
Then he that was when he started like talking about Scientology everywhere
And yeah, Spielberg was like what are you doing? Right? These are like promotional interviews. You're supposed to be promoting the movie right
But he never got in trouble, so it's weird that you can't there must be some protection
But like that was my other example of like saying I hired a guy to do my taxes and I found out you know
He a costed somebody once and you can't sue him for that you just fire him. Yeah, yeah, yeah
I would think I mean that's my guess. I got to tell you like okay
So I mean obviously this is not the case
But like I might it's been my dream to run my own show. I'm running my own show. It's gonna come out
this will never happen. Somebody in the cast has some allegations. The show never gets released.
They're like, oh, we can't even release this thing now. Put it on the shelf. Of course, I can't sue,
but how do I not just be angry for the rest of my life? I guess go do something else.
Well, yeah, you keep working, Pat. I don't know. This is where my mind goes into worst -case scenario.
Well, I mean, but you know, if you're gonna be mad at everybody in the world that's screwed your life up,
Yeah, where do I start form a line?
Yeah, I don't think, but here's, this is my impression of Mark Wahlberg in Kevin Spacey
on their way to the press junket for the movie.
Yeah.
What?
Why'd you do that, man?
Why'd you do that?
Yeah.
Why'd you do that, man?
That's Mark Wahlberg.
Are you also going to do Kevin Spacey or do you want me to do it?
I don't know how to do Kevin Spacey.
Okay.
I don't barely know how to do a Mark Wahlberg.
I only know how to do him in a house of cards.
I'll tell you, Freddie, this house just got a whole lot of cards here.
I'm going to make a Kevin Spacey biopic.
Alright.
And I'm going to call it Inner Spacey.
Inner Spacey, the about dark secrets of a leading man.
I tell you this.
Here's my impression of Kevin Spacey on the way to that press junket with Mark Wahlberg.
Hey, uh, speaking of pressing junket, zip, young zips, Mark Wahlberg's fly.
Wahlberg beats the shit out of him because he's a notorious homophob and racist.
Not allegedly.
He wants beat an ancient man within an inch of his life.
uh... you hear the other day he said uh... he he renounces the film bookie
nights he didn't say renounce that he said he's advertising to god or that he has
regrets in his career and it boogie nights is a regret
who guy would have a career for wasn't for boogie night
the only time ever really love the guys in boogie nights and then he's been
okay and things before but i love him in uh... the good guys or whatever that
other guys i think is a very funny movie
It's all right
Folks speaking of movies sorry the movie corner let me take you to the movie corner
And I did watch a couple things because I have developed insomnia again. It was gone and now it's back. Baby
Hey, um, Insomnia movie. I like Al Pacino. Robin Williams. That's a good one. Uh, I find it painfully boring.
Everyone finds it boring. The performances are good. I thought I was boring in a theater and I watched it again.
I loved it. And there's nothing funnier to me than how the trailer starts with Al Pacino who plays like Ron Dormer.
And the trailer starts. He wakes up. He looks like he's been to hell and back.
picks up the phone and he goes no more. Yeah. No more. Yeah. Like the worst voice out. I guess
he's like hung over or something. Oh, I remember a whole movie him like taping the windows.
And we're like, I can't get the goddamn light out of the room. Yeah. And then at the end,
yeah, he can't. That's right. He can't sleep. Because finally at the end, the partner, whatever's
like it's pitch black in here. Yeah, yeah, he shouldn't say out whatever his name is
dormer. So what did you watch? I watched the first episode of a show I really thoroughly enjoyed
called tales from the tour bus. And it is on cinematics. I watched the first and half the second.
This is the Judd or not Judd the Mike judge show Judd judge Mike. Yes, Mike judge. Yes
and basically I
Am fascinated by always have been by outlaw country
The country music of the 70s of just like raging alcoholics and guys with like extreme
Coke problems pill problems, etc
making music about getting fucked up and
And it's a genre of music I love, and each week this focus is on a new person, and it's
a documentary.
It's like a behind the music type deal, but they animate it, and then occasionally they
flash to the real people and show you.
So they animate like some of the crazier stories, but also the interviews with the people weirdly
are animated, and they add funny little touches to them.
The heart of it, of course, is all these great stories.
So I watched the one about Johnny Paycheck.
Johnny Paycheck.
He did take this job and shove it.
Okay.
I'm most excited about the two -parter on George Jones
and Tammy Wynette, who are two of my favorite singers
of all time who had like,
unatoriously horrific relationship,
and he would like drive to get liquor on a tractor
because they took his car away and on.
So the stories are great,
and the people they interview are hilarious.
There's a five minute detour
in the Johnny Paycheck one where they all talk about how much he loved to be naked and how
tiny his dick was. And then this one guy's like, boy, I tell you, I was always surprised
because you'd think he'd be ashamed of such a penis. He goes, he had such a teeny -weeny
penis that I always wanted to make fun of it, but I was afraid that if I did, that Johnny
would point out my teeny weeny penis like these guys are just like really really hilarious so these
guys live to tell the tales they live to tell the tales and they're it's kind of moving it shares
a little of DNA with like a drunk history they're just like telling a funny story and then at the end
it's like usually kind of moving because they all talk about how they miss their friend or whatever
but uh it's great the second one is Jerry Lee Lewis who was of course married to his 13 year old
cousin. They're wild, wild stories.
Didn't Barry, didn't Barry the guys work back then?
No. Have you seen that bio pick, great balls of fire?
Yeah. Dennis Quaid, and went on a rider.
Rider? Didn't even meet her, folks.
It's disturbing the scene where they have sex
for the first time, Mr. Derby, and it's got my favorite,
probably my favorite bio pick line of all time in it.
Okay. In, it's when Dennis Quaid goes,
If I'm going to hell, I'm going there playing the PN.
Sure.
Eddie, like has that like rooster walk in the hair
that he struts out of the room.
And at the end of the movie, you're supposed to still like him.
Like it's never like, look at the mistakes this man has made.
They're little blips.
Right.
The movie's PG -13.
Yeah.
I remember.
Any movie released in the 80s and mid 90s, I knew it's rating.
If I'm not.
whether or not I could see it.
If I'm not mistaken, nobody's mad, she's 13.
They're just mad that Jesus cousin, right?
Look, I would say equal issues.
I mean, they're, well, not equal issues,
but there's a lot to be concerned about there.
Well, of course, but my point is,
there's a lot of fish in the sea.
Do they ever say in the movie like she's only 13?
No, they do say that, they do say that.
But I think the bigger concern,
the emphasis that it's is cousin.
Yeah, with different time.
Didn't Rantiquet play as brother in that?
I might have dreamed that.
Randy quaid he might have been it now. I don't think so. I don't remember swatch didn't it a thing on YouTube
Famous celebrities who eventually ended up homeless. Okay, Randy quaid was in there. Oh sure of course
I listened to Chevy chase on Gilbert Godfrey's podcast and he was like
You know, he just was like Randy
You know on all these movies like he wouldn't drink he didn't do drugs like he just didn't know what happened
And it was kind of a sad tale.
Well, I guess it's his wife, you know, but.
I think he seems to be like sort of bipolar or something.
Right, right.
Or is it manic?
I think manic is the term, whatever that is,
where you have like the extreme paranoia
about like being hunted by like the government
and stuff like that.
Yeah.
Because that's all, that's all it is.
Like he's like the Hollywood,
there's a, there's a hit squad in Hollywood.
Like they're framing all these people,
they're murdering people.
I had to leave the country because they set me up right and I think he's just needs medication
You don't know all right. I'm obviously. Hey pet. I'm obviously not a doctor. I didn't say you were
I want to make a quick correction to last week
Because very often I listen and realize we've made dozens of mistakes and I say I'll correct it and I never do
Always double check anything we say on this podcast, but
I claimed to have been in the play noises off, and in fact, it was the year before me, I think.
Because when I really started thinking about it, I was not in it.
I was in something very similar called mixed nuts, which was a theatrical adaptation
of the Adam Sandler and Steve Martin film mixed nuts.
Yeah, that's an unwatchable movie.
I always loved the movie.
That was a time when Steve Martin could do no wrong
and Sandler being in the mix in Julia Lewis
and Leigh F. Schreiber and it's a great cast.
She, I don't agree.
That was the Steve Martin slump in my opinion.
Certainly it slumped.
That was during like leap of faith
when it was like what's going on here?
Well simple twist of faith.
And then he started doing those like tiny dramas.
But mix nuts at least was a comedy -ish.
I think it's an underrated Christmas movie.
I liked it.
And for some reason it was adapted
into a high school play, but it was very like fast pace and people running around.
I wasn't in noises off.
Maybe I wanted to be and imagined it, but I didn't want to lie to you people.
To hell of a mistake to me.
It really was.
You know, I was in a lot of plays in high school and I tried to block
everything pre -18 out of my head because it was so rough.
But I wasn't in it.
Yeah, I was telling our friend Pinkstone today about how you didn't know
what Dragon's Lair was.
Not familiar with it, no.
And his only words were, Missouri sucks.
Well, the only, yeah, I guess so, man,
like that's so weird, like we both were in disbelief
that you had never come across this game.
My mom never would have let me go to an arcade
and throw my money away like that, which is odd
because now she loves gambling as much as I.
But I would play pinball at the bowling alley
while she would bowl in her league.
but I would always get like a dollar to last the night and then she would be like
you have an intent to at home why do you need to do this I never and I never
played any games I just didn't do it you play your Nintendo though I did I
played paper boy I played a game called tuban and I played Mario one two and three
all right well I don't talk to me like I don't know what they are Pat I know the
games I know the guy didn't know about tuban what else you got for the movie
corner. I only have one thing. Speaking of Winona, great balls of fire. I watched the end
of Stranger Things, and I take back what I just said on the last week's episode. I felt
it started strong, meandered the seventh episode that everyone despises was stupid. I'll give
you that, where she like meets her. Well, you know, I'll say meets her and you'll know
if you've seen it and you want if you don't. But the last two were phenomenal, very exciting,
particularly the second to last one. I really loved them both. I thought they were two of
the best episodes of the whole series. I love the whole thing but I already talked about it last
week. Yes, and I don't think we've still not spoiled it, which is good. Other than that, I didn't watch
anything, but that's not bad. No, not at all. I dipped into my cinema cult blue rays. Yes.
That I bought when I was in Australia. Okay. Good day, mate. Just to give a little free plug to them,
cinema cult, great, great blue ray label. If you can find them, check them out. There are no
frills, blue rays. There's no special features, but they're really immaculate transfers and because
there's no special features, they're quite affordable in the packaging. There's always really nice. So
I think they're well worth the purchase.
I have most of them.
I might have all of them at this point,
but I watched, are you ready?
Okay, that was actually on Turner movie classics one night, and I didn't watch it, yeah.
I watched it, okay.
And I liked it.
All right.
I hate that that's the title.
It looks cool on the box, but then when somebody says, what are you watching tonight and you
No, I mean, no, it's not it's not with an H so you can go one for his right. It's just S's
Right anyway
It's a fun movie it stars Dirk Benedict
Who the hell's Dirk Benedict face man from the 18 the original 18. Okay, never seen the 18
So I'm sorry. I don't understand. I'm sorry. You really missed out. I know
Uh, uh, never seen Magnum P .I. and never seen McGyver and never seen fucked those shows.
The A team is where it was at.
All right.
Magnum P .I. was like, the A team for your dad.
Okay.
Janine.
Yeah.
It's your dad's A team.
McGyver was like hipster.
Well, I'll blue bloods as, uh, yeah.
McGyver was hipster A team, you know, he was a hipster.
Well, no, but it was always like, I'm going to solve the problem with a leaf and a paper
clip.
Right, whereas the A team was like they were firing fucking rockets. Yeah, and machine guns and shit
Anyway
Dirk Benedict plays a college student who falls or becomes the assistant of a
What turns out to be mad scientist who specializes in snakes. I can't remember what that term is
For a snake scientist and a orin tholars. I think it is
Orin tholars. I think that's a bird guy
right? Well, I guess fuck me, right, Joe.
shove it up your ass trying to help out.
Hey, if it's not helpful, don't help.
I don't think an oranthologist is a bird person.
Why don't we just look?
Look it up while I describe the goddamn movie, please.
Can I do my turn?
Go ahead.
The scientist is injecting Dirk Benedict
with these, you know, serums,
these venom, sort of serums to make him,
what's that called when you get injected with something
so you're not susceptible to it anymore?
A anecdote.
No, that's fixes it.
Like something that makes you like immune to it.
A serum?
I feel like that's not, I'm saying serum.
Vaccine?
Maybe vaccine.
Yeah, I don't know.
Anyway, he's giving these venom injections
and she's like, look, you're gonna get bitten the lab.
You don't wanna die.
And then you realize eventually the injections
are not to make a dirt Benedict immune to snake bites
but to turn him in fact into a snake with a man's brain.
Does he talk?
When he's the snake man, he's able to talk.
Okay.
But then at the end, he becomes a full on snake.
And then then he can't talk. He's just a snake at that point.
Okay. So sorry if I spoiled the movie.
For all of you, but that's how the cookie crumbles.
I'm surprised you didn't know what it is called because it's called herpithology.
I thought that would be sort of a specialty of yours.
Is that a joke about my dick? Yeah. Herpithology is the study of reptiles and amphibians.
Herpetology, you fucking pervert.
A herpitalogy specializing in snakes
could call themselves a serpentologist,
that's just made up.
Or an ophidialogist.
Oranthologist is a study of birds, Joe.
Thank you.
And can you please tell the audience
that I don't have herpes?
I mean, I don't know.
You can tell them, I don't know.
The amount of times I've raw -dogged you.
Well, yeah, I didn't get them, that's true.
Joe's scary stuff.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, no, I'm still riding the high from getting it right once.
Fair enough.
I don't have anything either because we just did the other podcast two day and a half
ago actually.
So I'm still playing the order 1886 and I've played a bit more since the last show.
And I can't tell you enough how much I'm enjoying the game.
So we can move through Joe scary stuff great and we can get right down to the review at hand
Thor
Ragnarok Ragnarok Ragnarok. Yes. It sounds to me like a like a
Like I always want to go what's that song like?
Rang no rock, so don't stop the rock remember that shitty
the planet rock, the African band bodhisattva.
No, we're falling apart here.
What are you singing?
Can't stop the rock.
It was in like every trailer for a while.
It's not deaf punk, but it might as well be.
Can't stop the rock.
No.
God, God, God, God, God.
You think the rock sings this every day
when he gets ready in the mirror?
Yes, I would.
I would sing it to himself.
Thor Ragnarok, the latest installment in the Marvel phase.
I guess we're in phase three now of Marvel.
Wait, what do you mean phase?
You never heard that like the Marvel movies
are in, they do phases.
So like Avengers 2 was, I'm sorry.
Everything up to including Avengers 1 was phase 1.
Everything from that up to Avengers 2 was phase 2.
Everything after that, till now is phase 3.
Let me real quick see if this has stopped the rock
by Apollo 440 1999 sounds right hang on all right Apollo 440 don't stop the
rock yeah that's it it's like a fat boy slim type song played into the mic
Damn.
Start.
Jesus Christ.
All right.
Who cares?
I don't see it.
It sounds like a downhill.
Well, don't take it away before it kicks in.
You've heard it.
I've never heard this song in my goddamn life.
Never literally never once.
You just said it was in every movie trailer.
It was in tons of movie trailers.
Can't stop the rock.
And everything else I said was right too.
Late 90s, that sounds like Daft Punk, isn't Daft Punk.
That didn't sound like Daft Punk.
That sounded like a Stevie Ray Vaughan.
Got a vocoder, kind of a tune.
Everything that's suggesting off of me listening
to this is Daft Punk.
So it might sound a little bit like Daft Punk.
All right.
The voice part does.
Oh, Christ.
I'm sorry. I'm not trying to be difficult. Anyway, face remarvel, Thor Ragnarok, let's get down to it. Let's just right off the bat. There will be spoilers. Sorry. Pat, did you like the film?
I don't like any of these films. That's not true. You've defended them before on here. I like only I like Dr. Strange.
And by the way, would I ever watch him again? Did I love them? No. I like Guardians of the Galaxy fine, too fine
But I hate the DCs. I hate the Marvels. I hate almost all superhero movies, but I love Taika with TT
Who did hunt for the Wilder people which I loved with Sam Neal and
Then movies that are overrated, but I loved like what we do in the shadows and it's have you seen that one? No
you might like that. I mean, it's a horror comedy. Right. The guys got an interesting voice.
I get excited when they get a director, but really, I shouldn't be because all it means is
then they'll never make a good movie again. They're on this wagon of doing shit. Well, I mean,
the reason they pick up these art house directors is because they just tell them what to do.
Probably so. They're like, we can't bring in a Spielberg or somebody like that to
Right.
Because he's gonna have demands and he's not gonna,
we can't control that guy.
Right.
But you go a wide eyed Tim Burton off of Frank and Weenie
or whatever the fuck you're a direct Batman.
You know what I mean?
It's like they're gonna dictate a lot.
Burton is a perfect example.
I mean, he held on to his vision as long as he could
and made interesting movies within the studio system.
And now, I don't even see his movies when they come.
If you had told me when I was 13
that there would become a time where I don't see a new Tim Burton movie, yeah, I wouldn't
believe that. But, you know, this guy, very long answer here to what I'm saying is, thing
had a 93 % right, critically acclaimed, and I heard that it was hilarious. Like, forget,
like, so, okay, already, I'm like, well, at least it's not as boring as these other two -hour
45 -minute slogs. It'll be funny at least. I didn't crack a smile and answer your original
question. I hated this movie. Yeah, you tapped out even sooner than I did. Pat turned
to me at about the 30 -minute mark and said, this is terrible. By the way, I hated it and
I liked it more than the other two fucking thores. I liked the first thore a lot. I thought
they walked the line in the first thore very well. I thought they did a good job with the
first one. I thought the second one looked like an episode of Xena Warrior Princess and
was stupid. And this one, look, these fucking movies, you know, nobody, look, and I will
pat myself on the back for being somebody that's been saying this for a long, long time.
I told you, these goddamn jokes are going to ruin these fucking movies and they're ruining
the goddamn mood. They're ruined. It's, it's not, well you're saying I told you, but people
I love this movie and it made a tremendous amount of money.
Well, I don't buy the critic response to these things.
I am absolutely convinced of one of two things.
Either A, times are just that shitty that people,
that this is the base sort of entertainment
that even critic film critics eat up.
Or B, there's a pay only thing or something happening
because it's Disney and Marvel and there's no way
this is a fucking 93 % movie.
It's this movie tries to be Flash Gordon, the 80s Flash Gordon.
That's a movie that I own on Blu -ray and I loved it as a kid.
Now as an adult, I own it because visually it's fun to look at.
But if you said to me, is this a good movie?
I'd be like, Christ, no, it's not a good movie, it's absurd.
So nobody is saying, man, it's just fun to look at and who cares about the plot, which
The critics shouldn't be saying anyway, but they're saying this is a great movie.
The people saying that this is hilarious, like I've never seen a movie take so many big
swings and misses at jokes.
People I know and like said it was hilarious, like, so right off the bat and I figured you'd
be sighing and huffing and puffing throughout, but I did kind of prep you and I'm sure you
had read that it was supposed to be a market and as a comedy.
You told me to watch it with an open heart.
I did.
I don't know why.
But at the beginning when he keeps spinning around on those chains and he's like hang on I got to do another spin on the
Chains and I'll come back and talk to you to this devil guy or whatever. I'm like this is like a long
It's awkward comedy which generally plays unlike the office or something. Well, yeah, and he's spinning and I'm watching this and I'm like
He's going they're doing this again. He's going around again for another try at this bit by the way the theater was silent
Yeah, and this is your first joke. So if you're gonna establish yourself as we're like Deadpool now
We're gonna be a straight -up comedy at least your first joke has to work
Then I know you get mad that people are joking in these movies
But to me, I'm like look they're running around in tights throwing hammers through the air and all this other shit who cares, but then I
Have my limits too when I see a villain a henchman
He's calling in a command and they cut back to him
And, folks, he's using a shake weight.
This is two minutes into the movie.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
The two minutes in the movie,
you got one of your main, you know,
he was at least a villain.
It was Carl Irving's character,
saying that he has used the ice bridge
or whatever it's called.
The thing, the thing in Asgard
where they can like travel to any world or whatever.
He said that he's been using it to accrue riches.
Yeah.
And then it shows his riches.
is. And it's all like dumb shit. And he says the line, it's like junk, but he thinks
it's cool. And then he says, well, I think that was supposed to be a spoof of spring
breakers, unless I'm wrong. You know what breakers? Yeah, you know, when Franco's like,
look, check, look at my stuff. And they had the montage where he showed up stuff. That guy
said, look at my stuff in Thor Rangerock. I don't think that that was a nod to spring breakers
at all. Because this is another. There's a movie I love, folks, spring break. This is a
Marvel movies you're dealing with people that live in other dimensions and and galaxies and whatever the fuck you
Want to call them right and they're using words like stuff
How many times in this movie did somebody say like yeah, could you like like like more of like a weird thing?
It's like this is how the guy in Asgard talks
So so that's never gonna. I'd rather that than you know, whatever Anthony Hopkins is doing in the first one
But give me the as guard talk. I don't know but look here's I don't want any of it
But I definitely don't want fucking Thor ranger rock so they have a shake weight joke
Which a is not funny just because it's not well done and then be a soft part was doing them 10 years
Yeah, it's like the hackiest thing ever. It's like that that's a shake weight. Jesus Christ guys
so
By the way two of the things he acquires
You know then this is always the interesting thing I find with the with with what gets attacked one of the things this guy
requires are two automatic rifles, which he then uses heroically at the end of the film
to kill all the bad guys.
And I don't remember a review saying once, sort of an odd thing, we're all kind of saying
we need to kind of watch with these guns and everything, but you know, so I thought that
was especially in a world where they all have powers and guns don't ever really need to
be involved.
I mean, if you can turn into the Hulk and solve any problem, that's what that's why I just don't understand ever getting emotionally invested or getting into these movies at all if the Hulk's involved and the Hulk's heavily involved in Rangarok.
Folks, they eventually just have to keep making the obstacles larger and larger and larger until the Hulk can't beat them.
But everything else, all right, I'll become the Hulk and I'll beat ya.
And is there a sadder career trajectory than Mark Ruffalo?
Go back and watch one of the great performances of
90's cinema and you can count on me. Mark Ruffalo
Incredible the next brand. Oh, they called him and now
Every year
He's playing the Hulk two or three times. Well, he said today
He's like they're like I thought you said you were training and he goes I didn't mean I was trained to fly an alien
spaceship. That's how he said the line in the movie, not in it, not in real life in
the movie. It was one of the lamest livers I've ever seen. And especially now that I'm
editing episodes, I'm like, I guarantee they were like, oh my God, see if we have another
take of that. And I guess they didn't. Well, let me say that I don't agree with your overall
take on Mark Ruffalo. I think he still does amazing work. I just think like he was fantastic
Classic in spotlight that was only last year whatever that's true. He still does great stuff
But it breaks my heart to see him in these films because he's because of the route they've taken with these movies
Uh -huh, where everything is supposed to be funny now. You've got everybody trying to be funny
God rat God love Mark Ruffalo. You're not funny. You know, I mean like he's not a funny guy
So then you have him now playing nobody last funny
instead of playing like instead of playing like a sincerely like mentally unstable David
Bruce Banner like he did in the first Avengers movie which was very cool he's now kind of playing
it for Yux and it doesn't work you got Kate Blanchett doing jokes in this fucking thing I mean
these are bombs yeah one of the most talented and stunning human beings on planet earth she is one of
my favorite actresses she's gorgeous and she's gorgeous in this movie. She can't deliver a god damn
joke. And she's the goddess of death and they got her up there going. I need you to be my
executioner both to kill people and carry out my will. But mostly to kill people you know she's
doing terrible. All these jokes from the shake weight on down are jokes folks. I think are probably
out of the mix on like a good multi -cam sitcom.
Like they got Kate Blanchett going like,
did I say that out loud?
This kind of stuff.
Like stuff that a room would be like, come on,
we can't do that really, can we?
It's, I don't blame Blanchett
because I thought she was a rare bright spot
probably because I just thought she looked great.
But.
Did she or her husband?
No.
I looked him up during the movie.
I was like, I gotta see Kate Blanchett's married too.
She might be the most stunning woman I've ever seen.
Yeah.
Yeah, this guy looks like he's a playwright.
I mean, it gave me hope.
I'm not gonna shit on the guy.
But he's not who you think Kate Blanchett
would be married to.
Sure.
It gave me great hope.
I was like, all right, like, you know.
She gets better looking with age.
Ruffalo, folks, is bad in this movie.
I want to stress that.
It's weird.
And then the, you know, here's my biggest,
I got a harp on this comedy thing for a while.
When jokes are being made every three seconds,
and then also you're bringing characters back
from the dead, Loki back again, Hulk back from the dead.
First line, Ruffalo system, we thought you were dead.
I mean, first line, Thor's system, we thought you were dead.
And then on top of that all, them very carelessly,
or effortlessly is a better term, getting out of every single situation they're ever put
into. There are no stakes. There are no stakes. That's what I was trying to get out with
the Hulk thing. If you can do that, there aren't stakes. Yeah, it's just there are no stakes.
When they... This is the end of the movie, so this is a big spoiler. As they watch Asgard crumble
in flames, and the entire population of Asgard is on this ship because they're gonna have
to go find a new home or something.
By the way, the entire population of Asgard
is apparently a 78 people, so they're all in this ship
watching their home crumble in flames.
And it's supposed to be that's really sad.
It's a devastating, you're watching your home,
to be destroyed.
And no, you can never go back.
And as that's happening, they have this rock alien guy go,
it'll be fine, it'll be fine.
If the foundations good we can rebuild it and then the thing crumbles he goes no foundations
Go on strike that and it's like you're making a joke now
At the like what's supposed to be the emotional climax of the film. What are you doing?
It didn't work. It emotionally
comedically
Action a couple decent action sequences, but but decent as as far as I'll go and
and I couldn't follow the plot for the life of me.
I kind of, I understood what was going on.
I mean, it was just, it was muddy
down by a lot of bullshit that didn't need to be in there,
but like, I understood what was happening.
And here's in other criticism I have.
I really fucking hate now that Jeff Goldblum
is in on the joke.
I don't like it, it's not funny anymore.
It was funny on Tim and Eric for some sketches,
But now everything Jeff Goldblum does it's him being like look at me. I'm Jeff Goldblum
And it's it sucks
It's like it didn't laugh once at Goldblum. It's not interesting. It's suck
He now he's like hamming it up and being weird just to be weird and it's like he's doing what walking eventually did
Yeah stop just stops kind of I mean I was excited to have Goldblum in it
I haven't seen him in a while and I was just like no, no
It's bad. We spent a lot of time on like Goldblum's plant
There's a lot of non -thore material for this to be a Thor movie where I mean, you're there'll be five minutes go by on
Blanchets planet or I didn't even know it was going on
You really didn't because we were never on Blanchets planet in this film
But I had I consider it intelligence, but maybe it's a problem
But if if I'm watching a movie no matter how complicated it is if I get the people if I get there
emotions. If I understand the characters, I'm completely on board. I understand it.
LA Confidential, first time I saw it, completely followed it for two and a half hours. It was
never confused because I got all the characters and their motivations and what they were doing.
I understood them. I liked them. I cared about them, etc. But these big, and maybe it's not being
a comic book guy, but like these Avengers -type deals, man, I just don't give a shit. I don't know
how anyone does, there's nothing to care about.
No.
You can't see your white male, you can't see your white male, you can't see your white
male, you can't see your white male, you can't see your white male.
And you know, look, I guess this is what everybody wants.
I'm not going to go down the Batman V Superman road again.
Thank you.
But I will say this, you know, everybody goes, it's too dark.
It's too dark.
Well, as opposed to what fucking family matters in space, like Jesus Christ, I think Justice League might hit it up the middle.
I feel like they're gonna find a balancing act. I'm excited that it's Joss Whedon, when he was involved with the Marvel stuff,
it was fucking great. Tonally, it was great. Did Whedon direct the Avengers and he directed Iron Man? No, no, Favreau directed Iron Man.
Yes. Or is it Zack Snyder? Well, Snyder believes his daughter committed suicide
tragically. And then Whedon came in and took over. Then they brought in Danny
Elfman to score the film. Elfman confirmed that he brought back his Batman
music from the Burton films. I think they're going to make a play to sort of tie it
back somehow into what we all loved about those original Burton Batman movies. Hey,
I'd be game, but I don't see it happening.
I'll go over.
So I don't know.
I've watched some clips from Justice League like, you know,
when there is a joke, it's related to the character.
Like for instance, there's a clip from Justice League
where the Flash is like, they gotta go in and fight a bunch of people
and the Flash is like, he's scared.
And he's like, I don't know how to fight.
I was never trained for battle.
And he's like, all I do is I push somebody
and then I run away really fast.
And it's a funny line because it's suiting for that character that is the flash the flash is kind of like this
Smartassie guy. He's not a fighter and it makes sense for the fucking character
What they've happened what they do now with these Marvel film. I mean, these are interchangeable lines
Yeah, these are sight -gags
Nothing that Thor says is indicative of Thor anymore and in one minute he's going he's going
You know like if we had to do it, dude
Brow whatever in like making some dumb fucking brosif joke or something and then in the next scene
He's going this was y 'all doing it's like what what do you have a shake spear switch that you just turn on and off
It's fucking stupid. It's not consistent. It's dumb
And how much are they paying Hopkins to get out of bed for this shit?
Hopkins is for the first time ever. I thought looked like genuinely old like he's always looked like an old man
Man, like the man in his 70s, to me,
but he looked like, I was like,
man, Hopkins is fucking old, man.
Hopkins, like, Michael Cain still tries.
You know, Hopkins does not.
He's not, he's not giving you anything,
except years of familiarity with him,
so his lines have a little more gravitas,
but he barely even puts emphasis in the right spots
on his lines.
Hopkins, yeah, he's become the guy that's like,
I can do this with my eyes closed so he does yeah, and he just sits there and he goes he goes
It was never a place it was a people yeah, he's like sitting now looking at that that landscape
And he's like remember this place boys. It's your home
Always remember you home in this beautiful scenery like what Anthony we're filming
It's what I used to think about Grenier on a entourage I'd be like the cameras are on Adrian
That's the best Grenier's got it or my hate to break. No, I know that's the best
but Pockins also does this now too a lot.
He throws that in everywhere to make it kind
of like to give it a quirk or something.
But it's yeah anyway, Thora Ragnarok.
More like Bora Ragnarok.
Better than part two, not as good as part one.
Visually fun soundtrack was cool.
Visually I'd say it was a lesser Doc Strange.
It was trying to do the same kind of neon and mushroom trippy kind of things, but not as effectively I thought they did a good job of capturing that sort of
The adventures of
What's that movie with Peter Weller from the eight years very no, that's actually a crawl
Like those eighties like fantasy movie like they did a good job of capturing the sort of visual
will spirit of that thing.
So I did like that aspect of it.
Didn't give a fuck about the action sequences at all.
And, you know, by the way,
when whether you're Thor or not,
you can't just stand on top of a jet moving
at 300 miles per hour, however,
fucking fast the spaceship goes.
Right.
You get blown off of it.
Like, it's just shit like that where it's just like,
guys, have some rules to this.
like have some logic to adhere to.
So I care about the character.
There's no danger.
There are no, so anyway, movie sucked,
but was better than in my opinion than the last one.
And I did like it better than Dr. Strange.
Oh wow.
I mean, I fucking hated Dr. Strange.
I hated it.
Dr. Strange so much better than Thor.
Any of the Thor's?
I hated that, flume.
Dr. Strange pops up in Thor Rangerock for like a nut.
That's the other thing too is like okay now when any of these other characters enter your shitty
Movie they all have to kind of lose their personalities as well to suit what movie they're in. What do you mean like Dr. Strange and him
Or kind of like also like riffing and that's why I hated Dr. Strange
He does that through the whole Dr. Strange movie. Yeah, there's a there's a few. No, he does it through the entire fucking movie
Everybody in Dr. Strange makes jokes, that's our Wi -Fi password, it's like Jesus Christ.
Yeah, we talked about that.
Yeah, I know.
So, every character now is written like Tony Stark, every single character now is written
like Tony Stark.
Well, the fucking Hulk is actually dressing in Tony Stark's goddamn clothes.
And then, for the last third of the movie, Ruffalo's tugging on his dick because Iron Man
and where it's too tight of pants.
That's his runner is Mark Ruffalo shuffling around mumbling
and pulling on his dick.
I want a piece of shit.
We didn't even stay for the day.
And what, and this stuff's coming out in November now.
This used to be confined to the summer.
Now in November, Thor Rangerox coming out?
Well, because they got to get Black Panther out in December
or whatever the hell that's coming out.
five trailers for more. Yeah, the next one break. It's too much. They need one to just
tank, but they won't, it won't happen. No, it's too much. So, uh, yeah, uh, that's
through a rag to rock for you, folks. And this is, uh, we'll see you in hell. I'll be, uh,
this week, Austin, Texas at the, uh, front door, something door, son of a bitch. I can't
Remember anything anymore.
All my everything is gone.
I'll be in Austin, Texas this week.
Look on my Instagram for the venue name.
It's the something door, 15th.
That's Wednesday, Friday night.
I'll be at Hyena's in Fort Worth.
That's the 17th.
And then the 18th and 19th, I'll be in Houston
at the come and take it, Festival,
which is being held at the Secret Group.
That's the name of the facility. Follow me on Instagram, Joderos Accomedy, and thank you for
supporting our Patreon. Yes. Pat, do your plugs, and then we get into some shout outs. Folks, I will be
at my house, or at work. I am on Twitter and Instagram at the Patrick Walsh,
And I play bass for Apollo 440, the band that did can't stop the rock.
All right.
Shout out time.
You should stop that now.
There you go.
So we can do the shout out.
So I was going to make it background music.
I don't know if it's going to sound that great.
But let's not do that.
I don't think they're going to hear that.
Let's just give the respect to that.
Such a good song.
It's not a good song.
That sounds dog shitty to me.
All right. Well, it seems like somebody wants to stop the rock.
His name's Joe. Shout out. Thank you all, Mr. Derek Clark.
Thank you. Anthony V. Minneto, AK Party McFly, Philip Rashad, Joshua
Christianson, Barbara Allen, Jonathan Face, Rebecca Cohen, smelly
bubbles. Oh, we have a new contender for best name ever. Probably not a real man. Chris Bowen,
Mike Gibbons, Donnie Joyce, Michael Dawson, Jennifer Smith, Luke Henderson, Hader, Ismail, Nick,
Nick, Nick Walther, Lee Vaughan, don't be ridiculous. So many other neighbors don't be ridiculous.
Yeah. That's good stuff. Good for you. Whoever did that. Conor Denney. Michael, just a
Michael. Okay. Stephen Cooper, Kevin. Whoa. Holy shit. How do you see that name? Swiss
to Wicks. Sorry, buddy. If that said that wrong, that's a tough one. Thomas Koza, Anthony
Annie J. Guiljardo, Annie Joe Hanson.
No, that's not right.
Annie Joe Hanson, Timmy K. Sean Floren, Dolores Martinez, Will Foley, Megan Lybrand, Scott
Blickensdurfer, Alec Walker, Brett Wemmer, Tristan Carlson, Laura Sexton, Anthony Guiljardo
again.
didn't we just do him yeah those two is it the same guy it must be maybe not
the other guy has a Jane his name Maxwell Ashcroft Brett Klinkner Alex Low
Ethan Whittit sorry guys I'm doing my best here Weston Thomas I jump I'm
I'm looking at it right now because he tweeted at me.
Is it Vid Hill, HVID, H -Y -I -D?
Yeah.
He says against all odds, it's pronounced Vid Hill.
Okay.
And thank you for your kind words.
Thank you.
Weston.
Jared Blair, Josh Smallridge, Richie Verdugo, Chris Hopper, Emily
Rosenbaum, Emily Florence, Sean L. Jordan Parker, Dave Kamorik, Abby Manuel. Hello, Abby.
Kim D 'Angelo, Michael Whitsett. That's another repeat. That's weird, right? Didn't I say that one?
That's the donating twice. I'm not looking at what you're looking for. If you're donating twice,
thank you twice. That's amazing. If you're donating once, thank you again.
Jonathan Gallett, old Ben No Bottoms, very nice reference to the Pete Holmes show when
I talked about, oh, it's a Pete Holmes show reference.
We can't get into it right now, but it's, it involved me and thank you.
Carla, oh, Mike Willes, Stephanie Power, Hunter McDonald, Sterling, Abrigo, Giran Sanderson,
in Diego Campos, Jake Ferote, or Ferote, I'm not sure which it is, Stefan Mascha, Zoe Blaskivic,
Edmund Dillon, Asli, oh my lord, Kithin, Kithin is land, are you looking at these?
I don't even know where you're at, where you're looking.
I'm on the Patreon page.
We're not again, we're not making fun of your name, but some of these are just hard to say.
I think that's Ashley Kavinezland, Dan McLeod, Brandon Gash, Lorenz Bunganiers, Alejandro
Salgado, Papa Spouche, Tegan McLeod, Matthew Little, Tracy Reddington, Sean Thomas, Amanda
Linda Alzemora, Jason Weibel, Michael Curry, Drew Spindler, Andrew Kovale, Sam Mitchell,
Aaron Melanowski, Scott Nolan, Jack Gertz, Greg Sorensen, Benjamin Tahia, Misty Zavar,
Brandon Knock, Brandon Webb, Don Dajne Wilford, Johnny Furg, Matthias Paguay, Paguay?
One of those, right? Superfan Giovanni, Michael Gold, Danielle Doer, Eric Lemora, Michael
Madrigal. Go visit Mr. Suit Records if you're in Lancaster, Pennsylvania. It's a great
store. My buddy, Mike, owns it and runs it. Stephen Reese, Walter Keegan, Kevin Masser
Eric Abraning, Lawrence Anderson, Jared Smallridge, Zach Schoendorf, Will Potorff,
Natalie Craig, Nathan Baskett, Edmund Agabbeo, Anthony, just Anthony, Kyle Kinsland,
Brooke Adams, the man whose name we cannot speak, I'm going to skip that one, Ani Babaduk,
Scott Patton, Barbama, B -A -R -B -E -M -A, Barbama, E -M -A -L -E -Marvel, Robert Pearson,
MySpaceMike, Michael I -L, I -L -O, excuse me, Max Unwraff, Dominique, Bander,
Hayton Davidson, Brian England, and John Weissengruber, whoo, I'm overwhelmed, that is
a lot of people tons thank you everybody that's really amazing thank you
everybody we can't thank you enough it's so nice folks I believe we'll see
you next week and patty and I believe we'll see you in hell that was a hit
Thank you.