I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell And when the sound of your screams becomes
a thing of my dreams, you know I'll say I'll see you in hell, you know I will
I'll see you in hell, you know I will
Folks, happy, happy, happy, happy Halloween from your boys here at We'll See You in Hell.
It's the Halloween episode and we are here to give you some of that sweet candy, baby.
It's nothing but treats today, baby. It's nothing but treats. There's no tricks here, all right.
We spoke with the great Emily Florence and asked, hey, it's getting to be Halloween time.
We'd like to treat the fans. What's kind of the most requested title that we have not covered?
She came back pretty quickly with that blob. Yeah. Blob remake. That's what we're doing today,
directed by Mr. Chuck Russell, starring Kevin Dillon, also known as Johnny Bananas from Entourage.
What was his role? Johnny Drama, but he played, he voiced Johnny Bananas.
What was Johnny Bananas? I never watched Entourage. What was Johnny Bananas?
Jesus, you're missing out, baby. Johnny Bananas was a late in the series animated show that
Kevin Dillon was voicing, and I think Andrew Dice Clay was involved. Yeah, he played himself.
Yeah, maybe they were both in Johnny Bananas. I type in Johnny Bananas, it brings up Johnny
DiVinanzio, a TV personality. There can't be two Johnny Bananas.
It's a law of physics, folks. It's a simple law of physics. We all learned it in school.
Johnny Bananas was with Andrew Dice Clay and Kev Dillon, yes. Anyway, not a very good show. I
watched every episode of it. It's very entertaining, but yeah, when I moved out to Hollywood, I was
like, oh, I'll learn how to maneuver through this business by watching this show, and it wound up
being completely unrealistic. Yeah. I remember I went to my first meeting out here in like a
shorts, like, what the fuck are you doing? All right, I'll stop using this as my North Star.
Yeah, that would be like, I want to learn how to be a live performer. I'm going to watch Carnival.
Yeah, I want to be a standup. I'm going to watch Punchline with Tom Hanks and Sally Field.
Um, Alan King, I believe it was, once said, and I didn't disagree with him, he said he felt the
only actor he ever saw play a standup comic that actually got it, like, did it right was Tom Hanks
and Punchline. I was like, I do think I agree with that. He even talked about, like, Lenny,
he's like, Dustin Hoffman is brilliant in Lenny Bruce, or in the Lenny movie. He goes, but the
standup parts, you can tell he's not a standup. He's just a guy being like, I guess this is how
you do this. But Tom Hanks really does, like, in Punchline, like, I buy it. Like, I'm like, no,
he seems like a comic from the 80s. He would have been a good standup. I wonder if they went
to Michael Keaton for that, who was a standup himself. He would have been a great option.
That would have been great. That would have been great. Do you have any plans, Pat, for All Hallows
Eve? Joe, I don't, and I always kind of ask my friends, like, hey, are you doing anything? I'm
always like, am I not getting invited to things? Are things happening? Is it just that other 43
year olds are not having Halloween parties, which I hope is the case? But no, I'm not invited to shit.
Yeah, I don't have much going on. I was supposed to go up to New York
for the old, you know, crash the parade. You know, all the comedy clubs are having parties,
big night in New York. And then on the first, fly down to Austin for a friend's wedding,
which is happening on the second. And I kind of ditched all of it today and said,
I'm just going to fly to Austin a few days early. It was a little too much. I'm getting old. It was
a little too much of like a night of frivolity in New York, like traveling up that day, partying,
and then like getting on a plane the next. I was like, it's just too much. I got to just get down
to Austin, get settled. And I'm sure something will be going on somewhere down there. But,
who knows? Yeah. Do you know people where your house is? Or do you just live in solitude there?
In Austin? I thought Philly.
Well, are you talking about my, well, I live outside of Philly most of the time.
Yeah, tons of friends. Well, all my friends I grew up with still live around here.
But then also it's been really great with tires happening. Shane's up here and Chris O 'Connor,
a bunch of my friends are in town. And then you go up to New York or the New York guys come down,
whatever. And then I'm making my own friends. As you would imagine, all the new friends I've made
own either record stores or bars. Made myself quite familiar in both types of establishment.
So I'm lucky enough to have a town that I can walk into and sit down by myself somewhere and
have a drink and I'll know somebody from the staff or something. And that's probably how it's going
to end up the rest of my life. Nothing wrong with it. I think there's a mass realization happening
and it's happening way too fast. And it's very scary, but I think everyone is realizing they
don't want to be married or they don't want, you know, everyone is in this mode. And I had
brunch this weekend with some friends and this woman was talking about, you know, Lizzie Cooperman,
very funny standup. She's talking about how she had mutual friends or several friends who
got divorced after reading this book called All Fours by Miranda July,
lady who did me and you and everyone we know. I mean, like, I kind of like her stuff. It's
so artsy and pretentious that it's kind of annoying. I have not read All Fours,
but women keep reading this book and ending their marriages. And I look up what it is. It's a fiction
novel about a woman who like has an affair and decides she just wants to leave her husband and
everybody. And it's alarming, you know, there's just people walking out left and right and
I guess not thinking about the end game of that. I certainly see marriage and family and children
not being as appealing as it once did, but I don't know. I think there's like a feeling of like
pulling the rip cord and just being like, we're all going to die here soon. I'm just going to ride
it out and go nuts. I don't know what it is. And it's, and it used to kind of thing used to
happen with people on the fringes of society. And now it's happening with normal, you know,
wives, mothers, families. It's, it's strange. There's a, yeah, I think there, there seems to be
an urgency amongst people that sort of an error of our days are numbered. Yeah. Let's see what
let's just go for it.
That's gotta be it. I mean, I had two more dates this weekend and then
repulled the plug. I was like, yep, that's it. But yeah, full date with a woman who again
had not, well, she had not mentioned the EMM lifestyle anywhere on her profile, but
I started to, she's like, well, what kind of bad dates have you had? You know, we start comparing
bad date stories. I'm like, I got a bunch. And I told him, you know, the one good date I had had
recently was this girl who wound up being in a relationship with a married man who lives across
the country and et cetera. And she goes, well, before you get too critical on, on that lifestyle,
I'm like, oh, what happened? We'd already been taught. We were both divorced. And she goes,
well, me and my husband were open. I told him I wanted to open it up right before we got married.
I'm like, how long were you together before you sprung that on him? Six years.
Okay. But in our discussion of who was at fault during the divorce, all blame was placed on the
husband. And then an hour and three drinks later, it's like, oh yeah, you know, I told him right
before we got married, I wanted to open things up and he was, he was not cool with it and actually
wound up, um, breaking or she goes, I never did anything, but he did. That was the crazy part.
I never actually did anything, but he did. And I said, oh, okay. Well, um, like did he just get
used to the lifestyle or was he trying to get revenge or what? And she goes, I don't know. I
don't know. But then five minutes later, she's telling me a story about fucking his best friend
on a trip. Jesus Christ. She goes, then my best friend beats me on the ride home from the vacation
walks into my house and goes, guess what your wife did this weekend to the husband. And she's like,
so of course he's devastated. And then I said, well, excuse me. And I must, I say no judgment
when I'm talking to these women, like 5 ,000 times, even though my voice is dripping with judgment,
but I'm like, you just said you didn't do anything. You said you wanted an open marriage,
but you didn't act on it, but now you're fucking his best friend. What are you talking about?
And she goes, no, no, no, I just mean, I never broke the rules. Okay. I go, you didn't have a
rule against fucking a best mutual friend. That's interesting. He goes, no, just, we had to like
tell each other before. And I, you know, so I go, well, you didn't tell them before either,
like I just kept catching her and she's created this false narrative about how,
how and why her marriage ended and is just spreading the lie until a person who's
listening to her finally for the first time on a date, probably starts going, well, no, wait,
there's huge discrepancies in your story. These, and I'm going to start a relationship with this
nut. These rules and these scenarios are so much like the rules of engagement and war
it's real gray. You're like, I don't really understand. Wait, what? How's that? That's
better. I guess that makes it okay. Like, okay. I go, um, I go, have you, uh, done any more in the
E and M lifestyle? Cause we were kind of vibing and I was like, if, if that was just her one thing,
and then she was like, I'm not doing that anymore. She goes, no, I never did it again. Well, actually
I was in like a six month throuple. Okay. Okay. What was that? That was me dating a married man
and his wife and we would have sex together. The three of us. Okay. Then they divorced,
I kept dating him. I'm like, quick pause on that one. Why did they divorce? I don't know.
Didn't have anything to do with you. Okay. So they divorced. I'm not sure the details on that
didn't come up when you start fucking him outside of that marriage. So she's fucking him. Then she
goes, then come to find out he was cheating on me with, um, a, and she, I think she said a, they,
them. Okay. And then she said, so me and the wife who were main friends start talking and suddenly
all three of us gals get together and we're like, Oh, so he's cheating on all three of us. And I'm
the point in the day I would, I'd signal the bartender and I'd say, ma 'am, I'm just going to
get you a bottle here and I'm going to leave you to it. I'm going to go. You've got some things to
work out. This is Jim beam. Enjoy yourself. Yeah. Well, then I asked, I said, so you keep saying us
girls was this a, and I'm just curious this, this person he was cheating with, was this a trans
person? She goes, no, it's just a woman. I go, so he was fucking three women, his wife, his girlfriend
and his mistress. And she goes, right. So I go, can I just ask why you said they, them? And she
goes, well, she considered herself, they, them non -binary. I'm like, okay, why the fuck is that
entering into this story? He just fucked another woman. There's no, I don't know. Everything she
said. I was like, now wait a minute. I felt like Barbara Walters or something. Now, now hold on
earlier. You said kind of notepad and a paper out wearing a little press hat, like Fozzie and the
great Muppet caper ridiculous. And then the next day I get a text. She's like, I don't think we're
a match. I have to have to hold myself back from going like, Oh, don't you worry sweetheart. But
to be honest, the rejection still hurts. Even when I hate the person, I go on like a, well,
what did I do wrong? What did I do wrong? Nothing. Yeah. I don't like you. You weren't fucking enough
with my friends. Yeah, exactly. The evening we went to a dive bar and a, I would say mid -level
nice restaurant, but not, not like a fancy steak house or anything. And I dropped about $250 on the
evening. That's why I pulled the app. I was like, that's, that's enough. Yeah. That's a joy. Isn't
it? It's just, can I tell you something real gross? And then I've been talking too much and I'll turn
it over to you. Uh, the date I had for Sunday night, cause this was Saturday night, the date I
had for Sunday night, I called her cause I was scheduled for a nice dinner and I said, Hey, uh,
they're overbooked. They're booked for a private event. So I switched where we're going to go to
get drinks and went to a much cheaper second location. Oh yeah. Just lied to her. Just like,
they canceled my reservation. You know, so now we're going to Chuck E cheese. Basically I was
just like, no, I'd never again. Will I spend more than 50 bucks on a first date? It's just fucking
stupid. Well, yeah, I mean, it's, it's, you know, that's a, that's a, that's a moving target. What
you'll want to spend versus what you need to spend or whatever you want to, however you want to put
it. I don't mean to make it sound so transactional. I don't, I don't mean it that way. I just mean,
you know, it's, it's sensible to make that first date a coffee or, and honestly,
a dive bar makes sense in, in, in every capacity to me. Most importantly, because it's casual,
it takes the pressure off of everything. And it's just like, we're going to sit, we have a shot,
we have a beer, we'll get loose, we'll talk. And then who knows? Maybe we have fun. But yeah,
that don't fly on hinge. It's a lot of, uh, if you're, if your second message to me does
not involve the word reservations, this isn't going to work. You know, so there's a lot of that
going on or they'll accuse you of love bombing. I've had, you know, I've been like, let's go to
the Hollywood bowl for our first date, which I was, which was also stupid. And then I get accused
of love bombing. It's like, what? Yeah. Concert is a bad first date. It was awful. It was a
game. Much like, uh, Michael Richards getting back into the acting game after Seinfeld trial
and error. Remember that movie? I thought you meant he's in something new. I was like, what?
No, it just, that was the first movie he did after Seinfeld. I like trial and error. I never saw it.
Cisco and Ebert raved about it. It's the, my cousin Vinnie guy. And it's like, uh,
it's the same kind of thing. It's like a really good legal story, but with a lot of funny comedy
in it. Jeff Daniels also. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. It's solid. It's good. It's some, some real funny,
you know, Kramer -esque shit in there. I have a good, a good scary stuff. Please. This is actually
a very appropriate one for us. Uh, this company called retro realms has released two video games
in the eight to 16 bit style of the, uh, Nintendo and super Nintendo and Sega Genesis side scrollers.
One is Halloween and one is Ash versus Evil Dead. The games are pretty similar aside from who you're
playing as and, and the abilities of the character you're playing as in the Ash one you play as Ash
and the Halloween one you play as Michael Myers. So Ash is running around with a chainsaw. Michael
Myers just has his knife. Um, and you're killing innocent people as Michael Myers in the Michael
mine. Yeah. You just kill regular people. I thought they were going to kind of twist it up
and be like, you know, you have to kill these monsters are so evil. We have to get a monster
to kill. It's not, you just start going through killing people. It's pretty nuts. Uh, the Ash
one, you're fighting all deadites and whatever. Um, they're, I think they're a little overpriced
for what they are, especially given their similarities. They're running for 24 .99 a piece.
Not terrible, but I just wish the games were a bit different. That said, they're fun enough
and worth checking out if you feel like dropping the money, if you're able to drop the money.
I think I only got the Halloween one and I've watched footage of the Ash one and I'm like,
this is too similar. I'm not going to buy it. If I could do it over again, I would have got the Ash
one. It looks a little, a little more fun to me, but Hey, I'm happy people are doing stuff like
this. I'm happy it's out there. They've got a very cool collector's edition for the switch that
where the box is a retro style box. It looks like the old VHS cover of Halloween, the movie.
Yeah. Uh, you know, that's a cool collectible. If I was going to do this again, I would have
just bought that. I instead impatiently bought this digitally, but, um, it's interesting. Check
it out. I mean, I don't know if you're into that sort of thing, but if you are, you might enjoy it.
Uh, my scary stuff is I have to shout out, Joe, you are always citing movieweb .com
as your movie news site. Yes. Have you seen what they have done to this site?
I'll look at it now. I mean, I logged in today. Immediately. My computer was dealing with viruses.
Uh, it looks so shitty and cluttered. There's ads, there's like recipes on it. There's lists.
You scroll down. It's like, there's a Tylenol pop -up will come at your face. Um, and the stories,
the quote news stories. Here's the top headline right now on movie web, the Mark Wahlberg and Kurt
Russell incredible 2016 action disaster movie, deep water horizon is now free to stream.
Really? It is. What is this site? It is the worst site I have ever seen when it comes to ads.
It does a thing on your phone where if you go on, it does the ads that come in from both sides of
screen and the two, the top and bottom. Yeah. And it's ridiculous. They have sold out every
pimpable inch of this website for ad space. As far as I know, I get, I mean,
there is a sign in and a membership that's free. I guess if you sign up, maybe you don't get the ads.
I don't know. Yeah. Okay. Yeah. Premium. There's a premium you can get. Uh, and it is
50 bucks a year and then you can get rid of the ads. I bet they have 10 people paying that.
Well, here's the thing. As somebody that did a podcast that was released on YouTube for free
and it was monetized mainly through ad reads. Yeah. You know, it always annoyed me when people
would get, give a shit and be like, you know, guys, the episode is 40 minutes and there's
15 minutes of ads. It's like, guys, it's free. I don't know what to tell you. Like we,
we got to make our money, but we had a cap, never more than four. And then often episodes would have
zero or one or two. Yeah. So, so I'm not against, you got to do ad stuff because you got to make
money. That said, I think there's a line you can cross that movie web has crossed where it's like,
you don't have to make the experience so unbearable that it's forcing me now to,
to, to do the premium because I can't stand reading this anymore. That, that to me is kind
of shitty, especially on a site where nine times out of 10, when you try to like watch a trailer
that they write an article about, there's problems with the video player. You end up having to leave
the site and just look up the trailer on YouTube or something. Right. You know, I've actually
written to movie web back in the day on Twitter, very pissily. And like, well, well, just it was
tweets like, Hey guys, maybe don't put spoilers in your headlines. Do you ever think about that?
And they never respond the ever, you know, whatever. So whatever it is, what it is, but
only to the, to the movie web premium members, do they respond?
Yeah. So anyway, um, I, uh, I, uh, well, I got some good stuff for the movie
corner, but I don't, I'm not trying to rush us over there, but
No, it's time. It's time. Let's go. I saw, uh, talking about,
it's almost Halloween, which means that somehow there is two months left in the year.
I hate whatever my mom's like that. Can you believe how fast time's flying? And it is an age
thing. The older you get, the less and less time seems to stick. You know, uh, I saw a Nora. I'm
bringing up the end of the year because we're getting all the four year consideration stuff in
and, uh, a Nora is a movie that, you know, received a 25 minute standing ovation that
it was one of those there's talk of it for Oscar buzz. And I gotta say like an Oscar movie just
does not look like what it used to, you know, everyone was so pissed about green book, but
that's what an Oscar movie looked like for decades. Um, a Nora, if it gets nominations for stuff,
it just shows that we have become a much more open -minded society. It's a movie about a young
sex worker. Um, she is a stripper who is sort of available for a price. Um,
they, they do suggest in a way that's a little odd for this time that, that a lot of these, uh,
strippers will put out, which in a pro sex worker movie is kind of an odd move. Um, but
the movie is hot as hell. It is chock full of nudity and sex from the jump. Um, not one to
watch with your parents. And the story is basically this. She's a young Brooklyn stripper. Her name
it's Mikey Madison from, uh, the hell raiser remake, right? Okay. No, she was in the new
scream. Okay. Okay. Yeah. The new scream. Uh, she's great. She is awesome. She's a star.
She will be nominated. Um, and it's kind of this Cinderella story where she meets this
Russian kid who's like 19. He's a, you know, a bit of a, he's a, he's immature, you know,
he's 19, but he's rich and his parents are incredibly wealthy with ties to the mob.
So the first act is him meeting and falling in love with this stripper. And that's the most fun
of the movie. It's like this great romance. The second act is the mob comes to punish him
and get him out of this marriage because it's making his family look bad that he married a
surprises. The movie is insanely long for what it is. It's two hours and 20 minutes
and it should have been a fun romp. Uh, the middle section plays almost like a corky Romano
or something. It's like slapstick. The mob guys are kind of dim witted. They're slipping and
falling and you know, it's a little broad and the rest of the movie is this very dark, gritty
sex worker thing. So interesting movie to say the least it was done by Sean Baker who did the
Florida project, which I loved. He did tangerine, which I loved. He did red rocket, which I loved
and he does these awesome, incredibly low budget movies with a mix of non -actors and up and comers
and I just love what he does. I am excited to see everything he makes. I think this is a good movie
that hits a lot harder in the end than you would expect. I would not give it a 24 minute standing
ovation, but maybe that's just me. It's a good movie. Joe?
Um, I watched, I got all horror today for the holiday. I watched a horror movie made for TV
back in 1985. It's called the Midnight Hour. I like these 1980s made for TV horror movies.
You know, are they astounding? Are they fantastic? Are they masterpieces? No, but they're usually a
lot of fun. And there's something about the texture and aesthetic of a made for TV horror
movie from the first half of the eighties that just warms my heart. This movie stars Sherry
Belafonte, Dick Van Patten, LeVar Burton, Kevin McCarthy.
Dick Van Patten and like what is his role in a horror movie?
He plays a, he plays a, it's comedic at times. He plays like a sort of funny dad.
Okay. And then Lee Montgomery is the lead who was also the lead in Ben, which I've never seen,
Willard sequel. But anyway, it's about a group of teens on Halloween. They live in,
you know, some New England town where there was a bunch of witch trials and stuff back in the day.
Pitchford Cove is the name of the town in Massachusetts. I don't know if it's a fictional
town or not, but anyway, they're out, they steal a bunch of costumes from the museum in town of
like, you know, old witch finders and whatever. And they find a scroll, they read the scroll as
a goof. And of course the scroll resurrects a dead sorceress who was executed during the witch
trials. And she raises a bunch of demons and monsters and stuff to attack the town and turn
all the townsfolk into demons and monsters. It's a pretty simple plot. It's not, oh,
Peter Deloise is also in this. I always liked Peter Deloise. Anyway, it's not a great flick,
but it's fun. It's for, you can watch it for free on YouTube.
And, you know, it was enjoyable. Some of the monsters look pretty cool.
Some of the zombies look pretty cool. And it's more or less a paint by numbers horror romp,
but it's about Halloween. It gets you in the Halloween spirit. I enjoyed it. I enjoyed it,
certainly. The Midnight Hour directed by Jack Bender, who, oh, look at this.
He's done a bunch of stuff. Directed The Sopranos.
Yeah. Game of Thrones.
Yeah, he became a big deal. Episodes of Lost. Mr. Mercedes.
Wow, this guy's done a lot of stuff. Anyway, I mean, check it out. I wouldn't,
I don't think you'll be mad at it. Let's put it that way.
Uh, I rewatched Birth, which I had not seen in 20 years. I saw it in the theater when I
first moved to New York City. And Birth is directed by Jonathan Glazer.
Jonathan Glazer is a highly acclaimed music video director. He did like Karma Police.
He did that famous Jamiroquai video, videos from Blur and a lot of British artists and stuff.
And then his first movie was Birth. He's made, unless I'm missing something, these are all
shorts. I think he's made four feature films and they're all really good, which is rare.
His first was Sexy Beast, which is one of my favorite movies. I love Sexy Beast.
Uh, highly recommended. I feel like not enough people have seen it with Ben Kingsley
in his best performance by far. Uh, then you got Birth. You got Under the Skin with Scarlett
Johansson, which I fucking love. If you, if you want to see something that's kind of horror
adjacent, very disturbing, very unsettling. It almost feels like a long form music video.
Uh, very, very good movie. And then recently he got a lot of Oscar attention with The Zone of
Interest, the also unsettling Holocaust movie, kind of about the casualness of people living
around the Holocaust. Uh, Birth, like with all of his stuff, it deals with uncomfortable subject
matter. It's Nicole Kidman. Um, we've talked about on the show and it's always a little bit of a gray
area talking about what people do to their faces, men and women. I just love seeing the real Nicole
Kidman again. I think she's, she was excellent in this movie. The movie's almost all her facial
expressions. She doesn't even seem to say much, but the movie is - She's able to still make facial
expressions? She's able to still make them. Yes. All right. Uh, like there's a scene with her at
the opera. I feel like they stole it for the ending of, uh, Portrait of a Lady on Fire,
which is one of the most overrated movies ever made, but they just stay in her face for like 90
seconds and she's great in it. Like you can't look away. I forgot about that side of her,
being good. Um, I want to see her new one, which is all her banging baby girl. Uh, but
this movie is, she's married to Danny Houston, who as always is playing a bit of a jerk, a bit of a
cat, a bit of a, you know, selfish, self -absorbed kind of guy. And her husband dies at the beginning
of the film while running through central park. And this kid, this 10 year old boy comes up to her
and is like, I'm your husband. Uh, I'm your ex -husband who died. So great kickoff point
for a movie. Um, and this just never really goes where you're expecting it to. It's really
interesting. I looked it up and I remember that there was a lot of controversy about it
because they go there. Like there's a scene where they take a bath together
and it's not sexual, but it's uncomfortable. Very. So there's a lot of this, you know,
like she's basically falling in love with a 10 year old boy and then he's kind of this
smooth talker. And you're like, why would this boy be doing this if he's not really her husband?
Um, it's really good. It's, I see why people love it just because it's so unlike anything else.
I also get why people would dislike it. It was not really well received.
It's very cold. It doesn't really answer all of your questions. Um, and it's bizarre,
but I really liked this movie. Have you ever seen that movie? No, it's pretty cool.
No, I have not. Uh, all right. Um, I, uh, like to, uh, revisit during this time of year,
some of the, uh, universal original horror pictures, I rewatched the Wolfman,
the, you know, the original. Yeah. Um, these movies are just great, man. They're, you know,
you're in and out in like an hour 20. They get right to it. Um, the mood, the aesthetic,
everything is fantastic. I only have this one on Blu -ray. Uh, I just bought Bride of Frankenstein
on 4k. And then of course Amazon now has the full set of the original
four or five, whatever it is, universal movies, uh, the 4k set on sale for like
50 bucks. I should just buy it. I haven't opened up. Nope. It's back up to $128. Son of a bitch.
Yeah. Well, anyway, it's just for Halloween. They'll bring it back down. Um, I rewatched
Wolfman. Look, the Blu -ray is no slouch. That, that set that, that, you know, has been out for
a while now where it's, where it's all the, all the Blu -rays of all of the universal monster
classics. It's like 20 odd films. Um, they look great. Uh, they're, they're very, very well done.
Um, uh, the transfers are really good. So, um, but anyway, the Wolfman is, it's just a great movie.
You know the story. Larry Talbot goes to a spooky town and gets bit by a werewolf and he turns into
a werewolf and, and there's your story. Um, he dies at the end though. For some reason, I always
forget that. I always forget that at the end of the Wolfman, Lon Chaney Jr. dies. He played that
Wolfman in at least four other movies. They just would ignore, like they would just -
Oh, they don't even have like a seance or anything?
I don't think so. They just don't care. They're just like, no, he's, he's back in this one now.
So, um, you know, I'm not going to tell anybody anything they don't already know. It's a classic
movie for a reason. I would rank it personally. I like it better than, I got to tell you, man,
I find Dracula to be the most, arguably the most boring of those original universals.
I mean, the, the earlier you get on them, there, there is as much as I like film history and,
stuff. So the ones that are like up against the silent era are always going to be tough,
even though they're only like 60 minutes long. Sometimes you're just like, all right guys,
you know, it's where cinema was born, but like, we're talking now, gang. We're talking.
I also don't, I think Bela Lugosi is great. I don't find him scary. No, I find,
you know, Frankenstein's monster scary. I find the Wolfman scary. I don't find Bela Lugosi scary.
I find him suave and elegant, you know, but he's got like a Jack Palance vibe who also played
Dracula at one point. But I think also what hurts Dracula is, I don't think, I mean,
Frankenstein is a, is, is theoretically a loose adaptation of the book. If you know the story of
the book, I get that they take their liberties and they cut a lot out to tell a succinct popcorn
movie story. But for whatever reason, I feel like we all kind of know more about the actual Bram
Stoker story. And when you know it, it takes away from that original adaptation. Like there's just
not as much meat on the bone or whatever. So yeah, I truly do consider Coppola's Dracula,
the best version. I think it's awesome. I mean, in every way, I'll take it over Nosferatu as well.
Hey, I hope the new Eggers one is a heir to the throne. You know, I'm excited to see it. I love,
I love that it's coming out Christmas day too. That's kind of fun for me. It looks amazing.
I'm like, this looks really good. Um, anyway, the wolf man, if you haven't seen it by now,
you should. Uh, speaking of wolf, that's what I said every three minutes while watching the
new Amazon prime comedy brothers. Uh, I think I mentioned it on the show saying the trailer
looked funny and I would like to take back those statements at this time. Uh, I almost watched it
remembering you saying you liked it, but now I'm remembering you just said you thought the
trailer was funny. Okay. Um, super bizarre. Uh, this movie was directed by Max Barbecao,
who did Palm Springs, which is one of the most critically acclaimed comedies of the last 10 years.
And to pivot into this movie is, is genuinely insane. Whatever his, his team is doing,
they all need to be fired. Um, and it's not really well directed. It's,
it's just a strange comedy, completely devoid of laughs. Weirdly, I totally bought
Dinklage and Brolin as brothers. Like you wouldn't necessarily think of them as looking alike,
but they do. And their vibes are sort of similar. Um, something I was not expecting this to be
is like a dumb and dumber. They're both playing dumb criminals and neither of them is good at it.
Dinklage's whole vibe is being condescending and I'm smarter than you. So him playing dumb doesn't
really work. I feel like Brolin is just not a comedian at all. It's, it's very clearly not
his strong suit. I don't know if he put on weight for it or what he just looks very uncomfortable.
Um, and it's a standard, you know, the one brother once they've decided to go straight,
but then Dinklage is like, no, let's go on an adventure and make this money.
And it's, it's like D level Cohen brothers, uh, mixed with D level Farrelly brothers. There is,
as you saw in the trailer, they stop off at Marissa Tomei's house, who was an ex -girlfriend
of Peter Dinklage. Tomei is reaching for the comedy here in a way I have never seen before.
I, I, I wonder if she tried to get her scenes cut out of this movie. She's that bad. And I love
Marissa Tomei while she's in fucking Dinklage in like a long, weird comedy sex scene where neither
of them take a single article of clothing off. Uh, what's his face? Brolin is being molested by
an orangutan that Marissa Tomei lives with. Yeah. That's in the trailer that he fucks the gorilla
or whatever, something. And it's just like one of those nineties comedies where they,
like the hangover did this with the tiger or whatever. It's like,
if you're going to do that, give us a reason. Why does Marissa Tomei have the orangutan?
Like she lives in a trailer park. Why does the orangutan want sexual gratification from
Josh Brolin? I don't know. Uh, it's just a desperate movie. It was written by Macon Blair,
who is an actor and a great writer. He did, uh, blue ruin and, um, green, you know, you can
look up his stuff, green room. Yeah. He's done lots of great stuff. This was a movie for hire
or something, or it got messed up somewhere along the line or it got noted to death or something
went very, very wrong. Um, Glenn Close is doing her new schtick, which is going so far over the
top. You can't believe it. She's playing, I, you saw father figures, Joe, I didn't see that one,
but it seems like she's playing the same role, like distant mom who comes back and she's kooky
and everything. Um, the worst performance by far goes to mr. Brendan Fraser. Oh, really? He's
playing a cop. You know, he's, he's the Orson Welles fad. He's like, uh, you know, he's, he's
not the whale. He's not wearing the prosthetics, but he's huge. He's bald and he's playing this like,
uh, permanently frustrated sheriff who's trying to get them like the Jackie Gleason part almost.
But he's going, I mean, the direction for this movie must've just been like, no, think the three
stooges, like they're acting, they're acting styles are from a different century. They're going so big
with it. And that is not a style of comedy that has worked in ages. So while I, we, all we talk
about in the show is how we miss comedy. We miss R rated comedy. We miss the big swings, the big
laughs. You see something like this and it's like, well, this is never, we're never going to get it
back if this is what we're doing. Um, it's a shame. I always hate to shit on comedy when there's so
few, but this is a one star bottom of the barrel movie for sure. Uh, well I have for my final film,
a glowing review. I can't believe I'm about to say this
because when I first saw it, I hated it and I hadn't seen it since.
But since I watched the original, I said, you know what?
I'm going to throw on that Benicio del Toro Wolfman.
Folks, I got to tell you, this movie is awesome.
Oh, I'll watch it tonight. I'm watching it tonight, baby.
Now del Toro, which was my criticism when it came out, he's kind of mailing it in. Like he does
seem sort of like he doesn't want to be there. I don't think he's not interested. I think he's
just doing a thing that is reading that way. But I stoned all the time.
He seems high out of his mind in this fucking movie.
Yeah. Like that there's something. So what you're saying about him not trying it's,
it's beyond that. It's like that Willis thing where you're like, is he in there?
Yeah. Like it's weird. And he, he was the best, you know, when he came on the scene, I was like,
Oh wow, this guy's amazing, but he's a little good, even, even half assed. It's just kind of,
he's like, he's got presence. There's just the lights aren't on for some reason.
It's a period piece. It actually takes place
in an earlier time than the original movie. Um,
and they add a lot of elements to the characters to flesh things out. In this movie,
Benicio del Toro is an actor, stage actor. You see a little bit of that life before he
travels home because his brother has been killed and his brother was killed by a wolf.
And the story, you know, kind of picks up right, you know, as soon as he gets home, it kind of
follows the major points of the original movie, but they add a lot. But what saves this thing and
makes it worth the watch is, atmospherically, it's great. Anthony Hopkins is fucking great.
Um, and God damn man, the werewolf scenes are awesome. It's R rated. So you get werewolf
scenes where this thing is decapitating people. The version online right now streaming, I think
it's on prime. Uh, it's the unrated. So it's awesome. It's bloody. It's gory. The werewolf
looks awesome. The transformation scene is great. Um, they use the CGI as a tool. They don't rely on
it. Um, there's some practical effects mixed in with the CGI. They do a nice balance. It's
just a fun movie, man. I just loved it. I thought it was, I thought it was awesome. I was watching
it. I was like, am I going to buy this? I think I'm going to buy the Benicio del Toro wolf man.
Um, it was panned by critics. It's got like an 11 % on Rotten Tomatoes, but look, some of this could
just be people comparatively to modern movies. Yeah. I was like, yeah, this is a lot of fun,
man. And they went for it and it's a good time. They didn't sit there thinking about the sequel
throughout the movie, you know, like they just made a movie for the sake of making this movie.
And I think they did a nice job. And as far as a modern remake of a classic goes,
you could do a lot worse than the wolf man. Um, I, I highly recommend it. Emily Blunt,
uh, captivating as always. I'm trying to, I'm looking it up real quick cause I forget who
directed it. Uh, I always wanted to see it. Now I, I will definitely watch that this evening.
Oh, you've never seen it. Never seen it. Oh, Joe Johnston directed it.
Of Jumanji fame. Yeah. Honey. I shrunk the kids into the wolf. Did the page master.
Yeah. Joe Johnson, uh, is kind of, of a piece with Chuck Russell who directed the blob,
which we're discussing in a moment. Yeah. But I did, I watched this interview with him on the 4k
of the blob and he's had a career that's really interesting. I were there and we'll move over to
blob shortly, but I'm excited to watch the wolf man. Yeah, he did. Um, well, this is interesting
too. I didn't know this. He did, he was an art director on Raiders of the Lost Ark and the
original Star Wars trilogy. And you know what? You see that skillset come out here because the
movie looks pretty stunning. Yeah. Very atmospheric. It's very well detailed. You can tell it's a guy
who understands like, you know, if we're going to go into this world, we have to do it like this.
And it's great. It's, it's just a fun, fun movie to watch and I enjoyed it thoroughly.
Did he direct post Wolfman? Oh, it looks like he did Captain America. All right. He stayed relevant.
Yeah. And Captain America, the first Avenger, that's a great example of what I'm talking about.
Like that movie is a very well done period piece. Like it's, that's back when the Marvel stuff was
not run fucking dry, you know? Yeah. So, um, his last movie was The Nutcracker and the Four Realms,
but how about this, dude? Jesus Christ. Chronic, his next movie in development,
The Chronicles of Narnia, The Silver Chair. They're doing a, that fucking franchise isn't dead.
They're doing a sequel. It's a reboot. It's not a sequel, but they're starting with one of the later
books. Wait, is this, this is upcoming? Yeah. It says it's in development right now, unless maybe
it's one of those, you know, 10 years ago, they were supposed to make it. He's also directing.
That's probably what it is. Greta Gerwig is doing a new Lion, the Witch, and the Wardrobe.
He directed Honey, I Shrunk the Kids. Yes. And now he's also directing Shrunk,
which it says Rick Moranis is coming back for. I'll watch Shrunk. It's gad. It'll be fine.
Nutcracker. Yeah. Yeah. I was reading about Chuck Russell, who did the Blob remake,
and he was Frank Darabont's writing partner. Yeah. Darabont co -wrote the Blob,
but this career is so bizarre. He did, and he doesn't address the weirdness about his career
in this long interview on the 4K, but he started, he wrote Dreamscape with Dennis Quay, which I have
not seen. I own it. I've not seen it. He wrote and directed, wrote with Darabont, Nightmare on Elm
Blob, wrote it with Darabont. And he directed the Mask with Jim Carrey, but it was six years
after the Blob. Now the Blob wasn't a big hit, but six years is a long time. And then the Mask comes
along. It's massive, huge hit on a low budget. He gets Eraser with Schwarzenegger two years later.
Four years later, Bless the Child, the Kim Basinger movie that lost a bunch of money.
Then he gets Scorpion King, which makes a ton. It's a huge hit and does well. And after that,
he doesn't work for 14 years. Yeah. And it's not really mentioned. And then everything since he
did a movie in Hindu. So that's, that's when your career is, you know, when you have to leave the
country, things are generally pretty bad. He's writing, producing, directing a remake of Witch
Board that's supposed to be coming. Well, I guess it already came out. Supposedly pretty good. It's
well, that Witch Board, I think that's like the Toxic Avenger remake where like it's been premiered.
Yeah. Nobody has seen it anywhere. Yeah. Well, with him -
Make and Blair also, Toxic Avenger remake was Make and Blair.
That's right. He produced Back to School with Dangerfield, like, and then he also produced
Collateral, the Michael Mann movie. So I looked into that and where it seems to start to go
wrong is that coming off the Scorpion King in 02, it makes a bunch of money. And then he's going to
do Collateral and he has Darabont do an uncredited rewrite of Collateral. And at some point,
the journey of that movie to the screen, he fucked up so badly that he was replaced on his own
project by Michael Mann and never worked again. So it's like, what did he do? And I can't really
get an answer online, but something because he's a very, as far as I can tell, a very competent
director. I think the blob is really cool. Yeah. Which brings us to it. I mean, I'll say right off
the bat, I've loved this movie for many years. Yeah. I said on the last, I think I said on the
last episode that during the Shocktober sale, I finally upgraded from my DVD to the 4K of the blob.
So when I rewatched it for the review, I watched the 4K. The 4K looks pretty spectacular.
Um, I thought the, right off the bat, just based on practical effects alone,
this is a really stunning piece of work. The practical effects in this movie are
awesome. My God, they are good. They are. He talks about them at length, you know,
the, and I haven't even gotten to all the interviews with the special effects techs
that are on the Shout Factory or Scream Factory package. But, um, yeah, he goes into all kinds
of stuff when Candy Clark in that phone booth, when the blob comes in and like explodes her,
he's like, that is a doll of Candy Clark. And he's like, I urge you right now to go through that
sequence frame by frame and tell me that you don't think that Candy Clark is being blown up
and then they do it in the little documentary. They show it and, and there's no inkling.
Obviously, you know, they didn't blow up a woman to shoot it, but it's like,
it looks so much better and more believable than CGI would have. And he keeps talking about how
they keep teasing a blob remake. I think Edgar Wright was going to do one at some point. Now
he's doing Running Man, but Chuck Russell's like, I really don't think this works with,
the big CGI. I think that's the problem they're having is this needed to be kind of handmade.
And it is the beauty of it. The only time in 4K that the effects look a little dodgy to me is
when it's like somebody standing in front of the effect and it's got that in 4K. It's so clear that
you can tell they're just in front of a screen, but the blob itself always looks believable and
awesome. And the kills are so good. All of them. And there's tons of them. And it's a very
kind of harsh, mean movie. Kids die. The people that die aren't, it's not like what they do now
where they make, if somebody's going to die, they make them an asshole in the scene before.
Like innocent, friendly people are killed left and right in this movie, which is fun.
They do an excellent job in this. In the first 15 minutes of this movie, setting up each character
with one scene where you give enough of a shit about them that when they die, it's tragic.
They got that beautiful scene with the guy that's in all the Stephen King adaptations who plays the
sheriff in this. You see him at the diner. You see the rapport with him and Candy Clark. You know
he's a regular. You know she's kind of fond of him. He gets up the guts to ask her out.
She initially seems like she's going to say no. You see how like kind of rejected and sad he is.
Then you see him elated when she slips him the note. I get off at 11 and you're rooting for him.
And then when she's in danger and you know he's on his way to potentially save her and you don't see
him die, you just see the blobs around the phone booth and you see his corpse inside of it. It's
tragic. And then she dies. I mean, people that you're sticking with for a long time through this
movie drop dead. The most shocking of which is, what's her name? For Christ's sake, not Tawny
Kenton. Who's the main?
Shawnee Smith.
Shawnee Smith, excuse me. Yeah. Her little brother, when they're down in the sewer and that kid
eats it, you're like, holy shit. And that's one of the best effects of the movie when the kids like
burnt off corpse like jumps out of the water. It's awesome, man.
It's awesome.
There's the can man, the homeless guy with the cans. He's like this sweet homeless guy. And the whole
time I was like, well, he's obviously going to factor into the killing of the blob because
they're setting this guy up as this lovable home. Then the next time you see him, the lower half of
his body has been destroyed by the blob and steam's coming off of his organs and everything. So it
does a really good job of that. He talks in the documentary and I sort of missed this just because
Donovan Leach did not go on to become a movie star, but he was the star at the time. And the
attempt Chuck Russell says when they wrote the script was to do the psycho thing of have Donovan
Leach be your main character and everybody's rooting for him. Then his death is so shocking
and we're following all of a sudden this new hero, Kevin Dillon. That doesn't really register
because Donovan Leach is such a zero and you can't even fathom him being a movie star. He's
just kind of nothing. But Kevin Dillon is fine. He's an actor who never has done anything for me
unless he's playing an idiot. He was good on entourage. I'll give him that. He plays a good
punk. He plays a pretty good punk. I wish that our core team was as well fleshed out as the
supporting people. And maybe it was just good casting. They got really good people for all
these bit parts. But I did like that. I liked how it played with me a little bit. Like that sheriff,
you see this guy and he's not a super physical macho guy, but they give him that asking out
Candy Clark thing. You're on his side. You're rooting for him. He's the underdog. So you're
just expecting in Act 3 him to come blasting in with a flamethrower or something. And one by one,
these people are knocked off. It's very effective. It's like that's what these movies don't get. If
you don't kill somebody that we care about, we don't care. Even Thanksgiving, which I liked a
lot, it would introduce say Gina Gershon as a total bitch and then she'd get her head stomped.
But you don't care. It actually winds up having the reverse effect. You don't need to make us
hate people to kill them. You should make us love them to kill them so that we give a shit
about the movie. And it's weird how that's all changed around, especially from somebody
as seemingly vicious as Eli Roth. But maybe these are studio notes. I don't know.
The blob is dope. I had only seen it on DVD myself. So these effects were really,
really like stunning for me. I had watched it over the pandemic. So not even that long ago,
but I felt like this was a totally different movie because even when the effects aren't
seamless, there's something beautiful about how the 4K lets you look at almost like see how they
were done. The handmade quality of them is what makes them so fun and so cool.
One of the best parts of this remake is they do nods. They don't skip or change
classic moments from the original for the sake of it. They just do them again.
And they do them just in a great way. That scene where the homeless guy turns the stick upside
down and the blob goes up the stick over his hand. That's in the original. It's a classic
moment in the original. They just redo it. They're like, yeah, that's a great moment.
We're going to keep it in. In the original, he dies in the hospital like he does in this one.
Now in this one, they made it 20 ,000 times grosser, but they still do it. Then of course,
the most iconic scene, and this movie holds a special place in my heart because I live near
the theater where the original one was shot. I did my new special in one of the rooms at that
theater. You're sitting there going, how are they going to do the movie theater scene? That's like a
horror movie. Everybody running out of the theater in the blob. Everybody remembers that.
They do it in this and they kick it up a notch. That whole sequence where Shawnee Smith is trying
to find her brother in that theater and it goes into strobe lights because the projector goes
haywire. It's awesome. It's fucking mayhem, man. It's such a wild, fun scene. Then they escape into
the sewer and that whole thing. By the way, what you're saying about give us people we love and
then have those characters suffer the terrible fates and that's how you get invested. It also
does something else. Even though I've seen this movie a bunch of times, you're sitting there when
they're in that sewer and you're like, is Shawnee Smith going to die? She might die. They're killing
people in this. Whatever. You're very, very invested. Who's going to make it? Who's not?
That one cop who's the guy from RoboCop that gets hit with the sludge, the nuclear waste or whatever
and it melts off or whatever. That guy plays the asshole deputy or whatever and he hangs in the
movie long enough to have the hero moment where he finally does the right thing and then he gets
killed. Nobody is spared. It's just a very well done movie.
Well, they wind up sparing people like Del Close. Del Close is the legendary second city improv
teacher. If you've seen him, he's in Ferris Bueller. Ben Stein gets all the credit as
being the funny boring teacher, but when you watch it now, Del Close is funnier because he goes,
in what way do like, it's really, really funny. We've all been in a class like that,
but I love him in this movie too. He's so weird looking. He's just, he's like a pervert priest.
He doesn't do anything perverted, but he's giving pervert and then to give him that final moment,
setting up a sequel, which never happened, but he's alive. It's also interesting how much Frank
Darabont hates religious people. That's something I noticed when he writes, you know, you look at
the mist or you look at almost anything he's got his hands in. There's always a religious villain.
Of course, it's Marcia Gay Harden in the mist, but in here it's a priest who thinks that the blob is
bringing back the apocalypse and then he winds up keeping a little shaving of the blob. I really
wish we had gotten that sequel and I honestly hope we get a new blob. I think what's what I like
about the blob in general is that we have seen too many zombie movies. We have seen too many vampire
movies, too many werewolf movies. Am I excited about the new Wolfman with Chris Abbott? Yeah,
I want to see it, but at the same time, I know that movie is not going to have any real surprises
for me at this point. I've seen every version of these stories too much. The blob is its own
entirely new thing, you know, and nobody ever made another blob movie. That's what I dig about it.
It's like it's it's it feels completely fresh and to make something scary that is just a floating
puddle of slime is pretty impressive. I want to say about that new Wolfman,
and I talk about this YouTube channel a lot on here. I got to shout out these Red Letter Media
guys again. I watch them all the time, but they also now, this is why I feel a kinship with these
guys. I was watching it recently. They're taking hard shots at Blumhouse now. I shouldn't say now.
If they did it before, I didn't see it, but I've seen it recently. They summed up Blumhouse in a
recent episode and they said, every Blumhouse movie, it's a dumb premise that leads to a
series of non -events. Here's what I'll say about this new Wolfman. It looks like it was shot
on like one farm. I don't know if they're still doing that every movie costs five million dollar
thing, but it's like you can branch it out a little more. I don't want to see a Wolfman
that's set entirely on one farm with four characters. Of course the premise is
the dad gets bitten and now the mom must fight the awful man. It's like, guys,
all right already with this. Please, everything doesn't have to be a commentary on gender.
Just make a movie. I don't know if it will be good or not. They're saying, and of course
the director is going to say this, but they're claiming that somebody vomited in one of the
we shall see. But in the meantime, on a positive, my hog is way up
like the blob is inside of it. Full. Blobbing. Blobbing hog for the blob.
I would think if my hog was blobbing that it was not hard.
Well, I'm saying it because in the movie it goes inside people and fills them up.
I got to tell you, there was a few moments where I kind of wanted to fuck the blob.
It does look a lot. It looks like a lot of horror creatures. It looks very vaginal to me.
It does at times. It does at times. And speaking of one last thing I'll say about the effects,
you can see that there was, I would think clearly an influence from the thing.
They do stuff that's very much like Carpenter's the thing where like it makes tentacles and it's
really visceral and gross. Yeah. They do all sorts of fun stuff. I like when it's like grabbing
Shawnee Smith's hair at one point, like it just, it's almost just seems like it's a bitch, just an
obnoxious blobby bitch. I dug the blob. I had seen it once before and this new 4k gave me a much
bigger appreciation for it. Yeah. Darabont's work in the horror genre is always just spot on.
The guy does great stuff. Big fan. We will be back next month. No idea what we'll be covering.
Probably Oscar pictures. Yeah. And maybe if we can, if there's one we haven't done yet,
maybe some sort of Thanksgiving. Sure. I'm still waiting on Joe to see the substance. We are going
to do it. I've seen it. Yeah. I'm sorry. I've been running around like an idiot. Yeah, but it'll
inside probably with it hitting streaming, which it's about to do anyway. So we'll see next month
folks. Come out on December 7th, if you can. Summersville, Massachusetts, crystal ball room.
I'm doing new standup material and then salsa windfalls, doing a full set, big holiday show,
big fun time. Some surprises are going to be in there. Come on out if you can. And if you can't,
I'll see you next year on tour. Go to joderosa .com for info on all the cities and shows. And if you're
in New York, stop by Joey Rose's for a sandwich. Happy Halloween everybody. We will see you next
time and we will see you in hell.