I'll see you in the recruiting squad.
Hey folks,
it's your bonus it's your bonus it's the app that you get for giving money
over you sexy motherfuckers we're recording on Thanksgiving day and we are
thankful for all of you boy we sure are and Joe when you told me you'd worked
for weeks writing that new intro song I was supportive but now after hearing it I
feel like you might have wasted your time happy Thanksgiving everybody you're
gonna be getting this when December 1 right it'll be out the end of the
month you know what if we have time today we'll post it today I mean if we
don't we'll post it well thanks given treat I tell you what if I was around my
family I'd need something to listen to for an hour who boy yeah besides you're
people are rough folks dad rough uncles rough mom drunk I'm not home I was the
first holiday season and yeah I always I always stay here but thanks
giving my knock on home for Christmas either I yeah I've never felt so dead
within my heart and soul just it is it's pushing a hundred degrees in Los
Angeles the sun is blinding it's just fucking miserable how are you supposed to
have holiday spirit folks I wake up this morning I turn on the macy's day parade I
wind up like throwing the remote across the room and walk down to the gym get
there all dressed up try to do the right thing of course the gyms closed on
Thanksgiving walked around the neighborhood said hello to three different people
who did not respond on Thanksgiving turned on the macy's day parade today people
turns out it's being sued for people thinking Woody Woodpecker was sexually
inappropriate folks folks that's my dentist Miller style joke on Thanksgiving yeah
the parade was going fine until Snoopy felt up rainbow bright next next to a
fucking hot dog vendor meanwhile yasser arafat still in the hoochie -goochie over all
yeah now that's a dentist Miller is dead or what he's doing he's doing right when
comedy he he's gone quite political he he doesn't lean pretty right I would
say at this point I mean tours with Bill O 'Reilly were used to until Bill O 'Reilly
right did some felt up terrible I don't mind him did he fill up women or did he
just harass them in the office you've heard that voice mail where he talks about
loofing his dick no I shower I have it and then he just gets on TV and it's like
morally outraged by America it kills me this way I logged into Twitter five
times this week like once a day and each time it would be like Republican
Senator caught but fucking a male intern on his desk while signing into law it's
a bill that that takes away all rights of homosexual I mean it's it's just
comical at this point it's stoop they they are cute and I don't I don't even
talk about politics but you hand me a microphone and I got to do it they today
Donald Trump I don't know if you saw this this to me is it was one of the the true
low points of this presidency somebody calls him out and says I don't know if
you guys are picking up in this pattern but Trump loves publicly destroying the
credibility of minorities so he can embolden his his base to think that
minorities are people to be slapped around taunted whatever else okay this was
a just a random tweeter Trump replies to this tweeter and says in all caps make
America great again the exclamation point so he's just saying I am doing that I
don't think that's I'm not supporting Trump but I don't think that's I think he's
being like this will piss this guy off if I just write my slogan I can't do
we can't do that listen he shouldn't be on god damn Twitter to begin with I
mean this is ridiculous the world we're living in I don't care who the president
is when Obama was in office I hate it that he was on Twitter the president shouldn't
be on fucking Twitter with Miley Cyrus folks folks you start to feel like you can
walk into like a grocery store and just point a gun at somebody's head I'm
taking these fucking groceries and walk out it's starting to feel like thunder
dome out there it's a mess bottom time it's it's it's it's coming on it's coming
down on all sides more and more the left are now calling for the reckoning day
with Bill Clinton very rightfully so sure son of a bitch I was just listening to
Gilbert Godfrey's podcast which I always know but he's there's nobody knows what
side we're anybody's right now Godfried had on David Zucker discussing some of
my favorite movies of all time naked gun top secret airplane hot shots the
classics and he's talking through them and just a random off -handed story about
naked gun 33 and a third the Clintons asked him to come screen the film because
Bill was a big naked gun fan right I love no surprise makes sense they go and
Clinton was like hey what's up with that girl in the movie I pulled them aside
and he goes what you in Priscilla Presley it was Elvis's wife and he goes no no
talk about the young girl and he goes oh yeah and Nicole Smith and he goes what's
her what's her story who was I barely know her she had like for the movie she's a
guest jeans girl right he's like yeah and he was proposing to Zucker that the
two of them like get some girls Zucker brings her for him Clinton will
set him up and they're all kind of laughing about the story but I was like this
he's going down and went what a matter of weeks it's it's it's clearly what
happened to Frank and Trump paid off this girl I would say it's come in it's
come in law hard and fast franken franken got a nice one across the face yeah look
I I'll say this whoever you are in whatever set of the political coin you're on
when you're that fucking self -righteous and it bites you in the ass I kind of like
it look I love it myself you know but but but I mean franken just when they
released that picture of him grabbing her boobs with her eyes because I was like
clearly this is being spun it's gonna be that he's like no we all posed for
this together it's a joke and then he just came out I was like I'm sorry I should
that was meant to be funny I guess it wasn't I was like he actually grabbed her
tits while she was asleep well they've gotten in close on it and there's you can
see the shadow between the hand and the tit and apparently he clearly is not
touching her it just it doesn't look great well somebody went after him about his
huff his shoot with area out of huffington and they released all these pictures
they didn't release yeah where he's like grabbing her ass and stuff and he's like you
know that's his whole deal he actually gets funny but it's it's not a joke it's his
way in the I'll tell you the one that broke my heart I heard a story about someone
you and I know quite well really doing one of those alleged jokes who was
somebody who's a very very vocal feminist
well I'm gonna pause this for a second folks be right back and we're back
to get that name off the air it was exactly who I thought it was yeah happy to hear
it because I don't like that guy I'm gonna tell you though folks you know
yeah here's what I would say don't trust a guy who's like never talks about
this stuff or refuses to talk about it but by that same token don't trust the guy
who won't stop talking about how these men need to be shamed for their crime
because largely the people that I'm seeing doing that are people with some
real rattly old skeletons in their closet as well and I know about those
skeletons friend of mine once said to me never trust a family man oh well that's
weird like like not not a guy with a family I would say you should trust most
family not a guy with a family not a decent guy with a that's not what he met
okay the guy where his whole persona is I'm just the old family man I don't do
anything bad sure the guy where he was like never trust that guy that guy is
barion shit it's the Robin Williams thing yeah it's the clown exterior and not
not that Robin Williams assaulted people I'm just saying like it's the idea of the
exterior does not match the interior where you got a very depressed man that
puts out the crown image all the time right family man's the same thing usually
with but in perversity right you know so I'll tell you the one that broke my
heart I'll tell you where the broke my god damn heart Neil DeGrasse Tyson that was
a tough one to do he's getting accusations now apparently somebody told me I
mean I think I think I saw a rape allegation I had yes fucking Neil DeGrasse Tyson
yeah Jesus Christ Jesus Christ should call him feel harass Tyson right well
the last thing I saw this guy thunder was a fucking telescope yeah it just I
mean to me what makes me laugh the hardest is the guys obsessed with morality you
know it caused me of course but everybody in government that guy I did you see
this guy's dick pic that went around this like 70 year old morbidly obese guy
no I mean his dick from an under the dick pose meaning it's it's shooting up
beneath his gut and tits so hey teach the man how to take a fucking dick
pick right but it's on Twitter for all the world to see he's like a Republican
congressman is it a tiny little dick he's like yeah that's my dick I'm probably gonna
just go ahead and drop out of office now if your life's work is stopping gay
people from doing gay things when you've never met a gay person the odds are
you're jacking off to gay porn day and night yeah so it's there's a fight going on
within you there's a there's a we see through you there's a central battle
happening on the inside of you yeah yeah everyone loses we can all be happy if you
let people do what they want to do without it turning into the fucking purge we
could all be happy we can't all be what's not gonna happen in my life we can't
all be happy here's why because people are happy when they're stressed out I have
this theory I'm not happy I'm stressed out this is my theory had this theory for
years called the everyday is a bad day theory I got to write this stuff down maybe
put out a self -help book wow every the everyday is a bad day theory this is my
theory that everybody has to act like their problems are monumental because if
your problems are average then your average so people choose to not be happy
people choose to create problems for themselves that don't need to exist whether
it's being inappropriate with other people or being way too upset about what
other people are doing or saying or whatever and not having any sort of not
that we shouldn't be upset about this stuff but not having any sort of rational
or nuanced way to look at anything going on see they end up with these
senators who instead of saying let's discuss homosexuality it's no it must be
stopped out and I'm furious and then whatever that output is is you know as
we already established usually directly related to some internal fantasy or
something so it's it's everybody's got to act like every day such a bad day
because oh god if nobody does problems then God forbid yeah it's what you go
to a fucking AA meeting and it's it's you know oh you think you were bad sure
well you know everybody's got to outdo everybody all the time with their with
their their plight and their struggle and there you know and it's it you see it
now within in the victimization of everything where people are comparing like
cycling in New York City to the struggle of like black people in America it's
absurd it's fucking absurd so so nobody's happy but hey it's Thanksgiving and I'll
tell you what wash you know who I'm thankful for the fans I already said that
but I am for me yes thanks Joe and I you thank you thankful for you I got you and
con here Pat and I are going to go get a steak dinner today I thought we were
doing a traditional tea gives well I think they have a traditional thing there
but it's a steakhouse you're not doing traditional well I do I do want to do
it but my fear is is you know the plan is to eat dinner at 4 p .m.
uh -huh well do you eat today I didn't eat today I ate a sandwich because I
didn't want to get there and pig out sure so my point is to the seas here's my
thing a turkey for energy reasons I want to be able to go out after dinner have
fun like I don't want to fall asleep at dinner I think we'll all go out but it's
going to be a shut the bars down if you're starting it for it having a giant
dinner it doesn't have to be Joe do you know who we're going out with today yeah we'll
probably be out on my point is is I get real tired after Thanksgiving dinner I
just want to get tired at dinner all right and then I'm gonna want to just go home
immediately so you do a bump in the men's rail this nice restaurant today Pat
not today I bet you it's floating around this place though the oh the the restaurant
stay counseling LA on Thanksgiving yeah you're right full of real fucking it's
like at first when you think about it that would seem a place where you could not
find cocaine but then when I really think back because I was never in the
coke culture I don't like it I don't like doing it but when I would look back and
be really baffled by people's behavior in LA like man this fucking asshole what
is going right it all connects back to cocaine I just didn't know it at the time
yeah and they're usually happen at places like that stay causes there was a bar
used to go to I never made this connection either but the bar was called the
white horse a pure at Hollywood western white maybe it was called white lady
no the white horse was home in the bar okay white lady was a heroin bar too I
don't know I know her horse's heroin sorry okay white lady is cocaine yeah yeah
no I see people all the time and I'm like the guy they just parked in the
turning lane yeah doesn't have his blinkers on doesn't have a signal just stop
talking on the phone I'm honking behind yeah he's not moving I pull around him I
go what the fuck are you doing and you just go yeah get fuck you like like it's my
fault well I would say that's a cocaine addict that's sure it's something here in
LA and I would say maybe it's spread across the country in terms of like
pills you got a lot of people on opioids annex etc and that's seeping into
driving yeah but for LA I would say way more than a drunk driver I am behind a
very clearly stone driver and there are there are differences of course but just
that that kind of like almost adrift into like oncoming traffic and snapping back
and you go up and the people are like young healthy people you're expecting to
see some decrepit old woman or something right just like these young people like
with glazed over eyes like lounge back like like in a snoop dog video yeah and it's
like you were you're blazed high like where if somebody was if somebody's at a
party like look how stone that guy is and they'll just drive everywhere because
it's not drunk driving but it's certainly as dangerous did you uh speaking of
snoop dog we're getting to be like old man on a porch stoop here nothing would
make me happier I would love to just sit in a porch stoop all day sure
that's the last time I sat on your porch stoop I got mulled by a dog that's
not my the building's front steps yeah porch stoop uh speaking of snoop dog if
you seen the ads for this Joker's wild game show he's what the hell is going on
get your money snoop that's all I can say man I love snoop but what the guy who's
whole thing is like appealing to like young potheds and guys career started he was
nineteen the fact that that guy's like 50 and host and stupid shit doing a
Martha Stewart show make your money anyway you can't snoop and he still gets
respected same with ice cube he'll do these shit movies stack him deep but we all
still will always respect ice cube it's very I love ice cube I love snoop yeah doesn't
mean I won't call something a little bit when I when I I can deal with the Martha
Stewart show that makes sense the Joker's have you seen the actual and well I
guess not I don't know what the Joker's wild is it's a game show he's hosting yeah
and it's like a zany game show and one of the things on it is you you spend a
fucking casino machine thing slot machine and if you get three four 20s you win
it's like absurd where's this airing it's like spike or something look I better
better entertainer when I'm telling you when you saw when you see the trailer
commercial you it looks like it's a sketch and then you realize it's real I'm
telling you I know what you're picturing you're picturing a very like
blunt it out sort of gangster funny take it's not like that okay it's Snoop Dogg
in a very like polished sort of game show network environment and it's it doesn't
make sense in a suit yes yeah see I never liked what was the one they well the
when Mike Myers came back I was actually very intrigued by that when Mike Myers
gonna be playing that character and they had really funny guests yeah and I
like game show they've always like games that's the gong show that's the
gong show yeah but you know I got about 20 minutes in and I tried a second and a
third week because I I do love Mike Myers it's easy to forget how at at a time
not that long ago he's one of the funniest people in the world I love Mike Myers
too but it was another guy that suffered from in my opinion unfair bashing it's
like he did the love guru which was not a good movie but no he got hit with all
that racism stuff where they said he's being racist sure and I was like guys
again let's have a nuanced discussion can we talk about whether or not it's
appropriate and not assume that Mike Myers is rubbing his hands together going I'm
gonna go be hateful right now well I forgot I actually had forgotten about that
now that you mentioned of course I remember it the racist backlash I just
thought everyone thought it sucked but Mike Myers would had essentially devoted
his life at that time to that lifestyle and that religion like so to say he was
making fun of the culture is actually pretty fucking stupid like people just
don't even do their research yeah well but I'm not saying Mike Myers hasn't had
some weird questionable you know accents voices in his career don't get me wrong
but you know that one seemed pretty misguided because it changed his life you
think he's a great worst I don't use any questionable ones which one I mean
not one of my very favorite SNL sketches is one of the darkest things they
ever did which was Mike Myers hosting a Japanese game show oh yeah with Chris
Farley that's what's an amazing sketch it's one of the best sketches I've ever
read that's an amazing shit yeah that's what he's surpey Nico yeah where they were
far like he's guess that's Farley's best it might be the biggest laugh outside of
the Matt Foley the first course or chip in the chip in the house but I mean
audible laugh like that I could hear right you could hear laughs there's but the
biggest audible laughs I think I've ever heard of SNL ever are the first Matt Foley
sketch yes and Farley's first line in that game shows sketch when he goes oh
there's been a mistake I don't speak Japanese yeah the place goes to fucking
I don't speak Japanese yeah yeah I mean the best the best I know that's
not what we're talking about but we might as well because it doesn't really fit
our our format what are your favorite SNL sketches of all time my number one is
probably the Matt Foley the original yeah the first Matt Foley none of them could
ever even come close that was like it I mean you're talking like I loved any
time a cold open was clean and that's that's a pretty clean one because I would
have to see each week how long into the show I could watch for my dad would make me
go to bed well Matt that was not a cold open though then it maybe was the first one
back or something it was early I remember because I was like yeah why I'm
wanting to watch something this fun Christina Applegate the one with the word David
Spade and Phil Harman but I would always hear my once my dad sent me to bed because
something would get too raunchy I would hear him laughing and like I would have
tears in my eyes because I was a nerd obsessed with comedy right it's helped me
that's my job now I'm living the dream folks where do I get to wake up yeah careful
what you dream about baby but Foley it was on very early and really you know people
always say this shit changed their life and it probably didn't but I was that
was like I knew who wrote that sketch when I was a kid like Bob Oden Kirk wrote
that yeah I was like I need to know everything about this what's going on in my
maybe decide do I do I should I go into performing or writing well I'm never
gonna be as funny as Chris Farley why would I do that but I can write funny shit
for funnier people in my opinion Bob Oden Kirk is the greatest sketch writer
that has ever lived like I've never hard thing to argue with me and Ferrell had
their classics ever key and peel of that image had their class if I had to pick
a number one I don't think you're wrong that guy is cranked out when I'm just like
Jesus Christ yeah so funny but yeah the Matt Foley thing and then that's your
number one I'm gonna put that as my number one it's just the one I remember best
and can encroach the motion whatever my number one I think is a Ferrell and it's
called red ships of Spain I never saw that word the next time you're at my house
we we need to watch this red ships of Spain Alec Baldwin hosting it was like
the five till one in the morning sketch the last sketch and Ferrell is playing
Goulet Robert Goulet he bald wind is playing Goulet's brother and then Parnell is
playing a third like much less talented Goulet and it's an ad for a Broadway show
called red ships of Spain starring these like brothers Goulet but they're all like
alcohols and they keep getting in these horrible fights and then throughout it they
show you scenes and they're all singing these songs from red ships of Spain but
throughout they post reviews right that they're like obviously like this is the
worst thing I've ever seen or whatever but they are the funniest fake reviews I've
ever seen it's clearly on the K Ferrell sketch right I wouldn't even need to
look it up it's very obvious but so like you're getting the meat of the sketch then
performing these songs is the funniest should I've ever seen and the reviews are
arguably funnier and they just keep cutting back and forth and the first time I
saw it I was well I was very very depressed right very depressed I had moved to New
York I was living like Travis Bickel I didn't eat I was doing like 300 push -ups
a day I should do it now frankly but I was in a dark place I didn't talk to
people for like a week at a time I wouldn't talk to anyone right then they showed
this best of Will Ferrell volume two the original had all your classics but
volume two was like that they let McKay and Ferrell pick their favorite weird
sketches right and that was on even at the end of of that best of Ferrell two
thing and I was rolling around the floor and I like hadn't smiled in a long
time but I laughed for like an hour and kind of like blacked out and went in and
out of consciousness so that's my that has to be my number one all right that was
a right time it's a very funny sketch I'm gonna put my number two by the way
this isn't the topic of this week the topic of this week you're getting two a plus
topics the topic of this week is scariest scenes in non -harm movies correct
and Pat and I are gonna go down and do a couple of those but we're just warming up
you still haven't even really started the show yet but hold on let's finish this
first oh yeah you're right I'm gonna put in my number two it's gonna be like that
departed credits yes my number two is gonna be the Sinatra group oh sure which
which is a contender for number one with Stephen 80 with my Myrism it's just
every fucking line and the fact that they sting Billy Idol on that one sting is
Billy Idol so that's I had I got chunks of guys like you in my stool and the fact
that on national television they got out the joke Millie Vanillie what's with this
faggot crap I mean that's that is insane to me that they got that out do you know
speaking of Gulae that there is a feral sketch I think from when I was
working there where he is playing Gulae and is it's Gulae rap Gulae wraps the
hit so whatever yeah and he aggressively with a hard
art I have says the N words while staring the camera down I've seen it and the gag
is that he's drunk but it's insane I mean that that is so crazy to me yeah I'm
not saying I laughed I just kind of was like wow that's something
I I laughed at it and it's not because I'm a filthy racist person I laugh
because of I get that it's a joke I get that it yeah you know I'm a big believe I
get push back swing I'm a big believer in the credit for the bravery of those two I
get it I'm a big believer if you're if you're joking it's okay even if the joke falls
flat is as long as we know you're not saying I'm really truly a hateful or
whatever this is not my real opinion but I I'm a big believe in that philosophy but
anyway I'm the I don't mean it's brave to say the end word I'm saying those
guys are doing this is see this is kind of the it's quite the opposite this is
sort of every time Pat hosts one of our town meetings it sort of digresses into
this direction at some point here here's what I am saying when I said I hate
when they call anything brave other than like going to war but when it was a
all I'm saying is that for decades now those guys have been doing like the
weirdest possible comedy at a very high level and making a lot of money do it's
an edgy joke it's an edgy joke to make I'm I'm going off their whole career we're
off the end word that was insane but these are guys who just clearly were not
fearful of any of this but that's what which is cool that's what comedy should be
and almost can't be anymore we're we're admiring not just the end we're about
the whole career I know we're admiring chance taking comedy and sometimes that
chance is saying a very offensive term sure it in in in what is meant to be a
humorous context sure and sometimes it's many other things I get it no we're
gonna sue you Pat relax no I know but also a part of that joke is that they
sugarcoat these people like their portrayal of Trump even once ball one started
doing it is too nice and you start to kind of have affection that's what happened
with Ferrell and George W Bush they humanize these people through them but the
truth of somebody like Gulae is like an almost guarantee Gulae uses the
N word on a regular why do you think Gulae's a racist where's that coming from
is he alive still Gulae I believe he is I don't believe he's racist you know that old guard
like you know you know Sinatra had it in him you wasn't a racist man Sinatra he
dropped that N word Sinatra was Sammy Davis Jr.'s best man at his
interracial wedding I know where they ostracized Sammy Davis Jr. I've
read massive Sinatra biop biographies I just feel like that old guard you get a
couple cocktails and they don't see anything wrong with it that was part of the
joke I think of the Gulae sketch but I don't know maybe I'm wrong I always
just as isn't it funny to hear the whitest man on earth rap like street rap
lyric sure sure I just the delight almost with how hard he hits it it like
takes your breath away it's insane one of my other favorite feral sketches and
I'll put this in my top five and it's even better now that I am a dog owner
dishing your dog is your tremendous oh boy sketch I introduced that to Heather
pretty recently and she was blown away cuz I was doing it to our cat yeah and she
kept laughing laughing I was like I got to give credit where to do I'm basically
doing an impression of the old wolf feral ska she hadn't seen it that's the
great thing about having these collections and they're five dollars on Amazon best
a feral best a hard one I have all of them that to introduce somebody like
oh you've never seen like I'm excited to show you red ships from fucking Spain I
want to say it I got to say it's gonna blow you down mine but the one the one
part in that one where he's like you know the palm wasn't taking reservations so
what do you say we go with the cable tonight okay great and then he backs up off
camera then slides back in and goes also you're a fucking dog fucking dog yeah the
the bit the bit is a it's a commercial basically where well feral is talking
down to his dog about what a snob it is kind of because it won't because dogs do
that my dog will do it won't eat yeah like asshole it's been two days I don't
understand dogs can go a real long time without eating yeah so they'll do they'll
do a fucking standoff with you yeah and try to get you to give them something
else right and it's just it's just a really funny sketch my number two well
my I'm gonna say Matt Foley and then toss it back to you that is my number two
I know when Matt Foley got three and then we'll start the show when Matt Foley got
too dark is when he came back right before he died yeah it's too much and he's
peddling on that bike and drenched in sweat I mean I I yeah I it's very sad my
number three and you know I got to tell you folks I've gone back and watch those
first five years the classic years the years we've all been trying to get
back to it's hard to find a laugh on those first five years ass and it's hard
to find a fucking player yeah entire episodes of bombing their their entire
episode and it's not just dated shit it's not just like on weekend update when
he's talking about some you know something with Nixon and I'm like what the hell
is he talking about I'm talking badly written unfunny lame sketches and I know
they're pioneers and they're testing out the format and yes thank you you got
us where we are today but to go back and watch them now it's like oh boy I've
said it I've said it a million times there are gems in there I mean it's cool to
see a young Murray Acroix whatever but I said it a million times it's it's it's it's
it is a it is a sign that show is a sign of the times yeah people were
coked out of their heads yeah they thought the funniest thing they ever saw was
John Belushi in a samurai outfit yeah putting fruit in it yeah like literally
just like that was the old joke yeah exactly or like him waddling around like
just doing gibberish yeah it's like why are this giant like five disc set of all
the best of their musical performances and that's a good reason to watch all the
old ones I mean to like yeah you it's like the Ramones are on one week the
clash the talking head it's incredible those are the days but to me the show
didn't become a powerhouse till those amazing late 80s years I'm part of
that's just because I was growing up and getting in the car leave out don't leave
out the Casarinsky Eddie Murphy years when Lauren Michaels wasn't even there say
I couldn't even watch it at that point but though those sketch I mean that's when
like Martin shorts in there no I've seen them now just for gas they had some
great stuff I'm saying if you go back and watch that now it's 20 times funnier it's
funnier than the then the 75 yeah some of the some of the sketches are like
gut busting yeah funny and the feral the earlier feral years I think can rank
with the Myers Hartwell I mean Hartman Jesus Christ Hartman was in every sketch
and killed it as did Ferrell there's a real nice it's very brief but there's
that real sweet spot where it's like they had everybody Hartman Carvey Farley
then they're eight and Sandler it's like yeah it's like there's a real brief
sweet spot in there where it's like they're all Tim Meadows like they're all there
together yeah no it was incredible my number three I guess would have to be and
that's tough do you have yours go ahead I said mine already what I did Matt Foley
Sinatra Group dissing your dog oh dissing your dog yeah it almost have to be
a feral or a farly I mean you got the glue sketch needs more horse well you know
what you know what I got to do and I'm ashamed of it is if I'm being honest to
myself more cowbell there's nothing to be ashamed of I saw that the night it
premiered as did I and I told it in length in great detail to my roommate at
time Jim Cargill when we were in college yeah and he was laughing uncontrollably
by the description of it yeah and what's it it works so well that like oh like I
would say most of the people who love that sketch know nothing about blue oyster
cold or that that song even had a cowbell it's just so funny that doesn't
matter but if you know the music of blue oyster cold it makes it something very
special because you know somebody was listening to it and started doing it as a bit
walking it's walking's funniest performance including in film yeah it's
is the best he's ever been and who who ruins it in the end if anybody's gonna
bring it down fucking Jimmy Fallon I know as he ruins everything but it's one
of the few times I gave Fallon a pass or I would have made it through that
sketch without laughing either I think I've mentioned this in the podcast I
haven't I have a little acting exercise I do with myself sure by myself where I
watch the best of Will Farrell outtakes which begins with the eastbound and
down run of him talking about his plums the funniest outtakes in the history of
film and television and I mean that yeah if you haven't seen it I advise you to
watch on the eastbound and down DVD to make sure you're you're getting the full
version but if you got to go YouTube make sure you're getting it all but it's Craig
Robinson and Will Farrell and each other's faces and Danny McBride and McBride
like a three -way and they are talking in each other's faces for like 10
minutes and it's the funniest outtakes in the history of movies and or television
the exercise I do is to try to get through it with a straight face yeah I've seen
it now a hundred times I still can't do it yeah but the basic gist is Will Farrell
was playing a like a like a this asshole that runs a car dealership with one of
the biggest swings at a wig I've ever seen and it works and he's right in their
faces talking about how excited he is about like making a sale and he keeps he's
talking about it in a sexual way and he's going I can feel it down in my plums yeah
and he keeps calling his balls his plums he describes with the light a time when
his son walked in on him and his wife having sex and he turned and said no let
the boy watch let the boy watch he goes yeah he goes my son came in my wife said
get out of here I said no let the boy watch he needs to learn as his father learned
before him and his father before him it's the best the best set of outtakes I've
ever seen him all right holy god almighty that is so funny let's get on with the
topic at hand which is well they should have to get on with well yeah I guess if
we're gonna get on with the topic at hand we might also want to get on with the
show and at the same time get on oh yeah yeah yeah yeah that was a very late one folks
we're talking today about what are your favorite what are your what are the scariest
scenes that you have ever seen in non horror movies yes and I woke up this morning and
realized I hadn't quite given it the thought I wanted to but then I decided what I wanted
to pick but I did a quick google to see if this topic's ever been discussed before and all
the choices were from what I would call clear horror movies like I have see did a list
and on it was a scene from seven seven's a fucking horror movie yeah we're talking about
scenes that aren't in are scenes that are in movies that are not supposed to be scary that
are scary yes either because they affected you personally in some weird way or because
they actually put a scary scene in a comedy or something I'll start with my number one sure
because I don't I don't have an exact number of these I just have a handful and I don't want
to do the I don't want to not get to the number one should I go backwards let's go backwards
I wouldn't yeah I want to try to do my favorite one last okay so I'm probably not gonna go
in any sort of order these other ones are in no particular order but I'll start you know what I think
happens with alcohol now hey I I didn't need to I'm just I'm baffled at how drunk I am after as you
can see half a drink they didn't even know you were drinking well now I've told them but it's Thanksgiving
um like that made a difference but what I think happens is like generally you and I go out we have
a couple whiskies we go home staring to each other's eyes staring to those eyes or you know a couple
mocha sodas and go home that's just what I tend to do one or the other I never fucking drink gin and
I think when you introduce a foreign alcohol I think it gets you drunker like it like it felt at that
first time like a virgin like what Madonna sang about in the song like a virgin now before we see
it makes you feel like a virgin to this new alcohol yeah fucked by it for the very first time for
the first time uh now when you did you know the original lyric to that was not being touched by the
very first time was it getting fucked no she had to she did have to change those two dirty it was
getting fingered for the very first time no dot dot dot long pause in the brown that was the
actual lyric before the label made a change was in the brown and parentheses she delivered it as it
were or maybe an ellipses had come before it or something but she didn't rush right into the second
half of that sense yeah now you so I always say we're gonna do this and then we don't you should
you need to come over and watch that sketch and watch slingblade with me one of my five top five
favorite movies and you've never seen it I've never seen it so you come over and watch it but is
there one of your scenes no no no well it could be but in the director's cut
there is a deleted scene that they put in that is so fucking funny where yokem who plays the villain
of the movie right one of the best villains ever yokem and his crew are getting together he's
they're all raging alcoholics and they get together to like play music in their band all night
but they're like this terrible bunch of alcoholic red next and they're trying to write the songs and
they're arguing about where the ellipses can the dot that that should come in the song lyrics and the
parentheses and everything remind me of this discussion that's very funny folks if you haven't seen
slingblade please do I'd like to see it I'd like to see a mashup of slingblade in bad santa okay
a third bad santa movie sure he plays bad santa and then his sidekick is this guy from slingblade
this time around did you ever see bad santa too I saw that half of it I look we we had a big that
was a big thing on our show I didn't think it was that bad but I also caught it on Netflix streaming
like when I didn't give a shit at 2am you know what I mean so it had some funny parts but I mean I
also didn't feel compelled to finish it see bad santa 2 for me was kind of like how you how you
feel with these new star wars you know like I you're real excited and I and I had a fear in the back of
my heart but like the hardest I've ever laughed really was bad santa thanks giving day 10 years ago
I believe to the day maybe 11 years ago bad santa's a masterpiece New York City my buddies came in from
Missouri we saw it wasted I've never laughed so hard on my life bad santa 2 is not funny it's okay you just
can't go back to that well yeah it's it's there's no right way to go back to the well because it's
either now he's a redeemed guy and it's not as funny or the way they did it oh he's still the same
piece of shit so then that discredits the original film right it's it's like there's no real good way
to do it it to me it felt like a lot of if you had a lot of bonus scenes from the first bad yeah
they did rightfully deleted scenes and then they you know it's easy to underestimate how much Bernie
Mac and John Ritter had to do with how funny bad santa was yes and now they're both fucking dead yes
and plus the guy who created entourage wrote bad santa 2 and the Cohen brothers wrote bad santa 1 so
I'm just not a big fan either when I don't know why they do this but why every sequel has to be now
they have a son yeah now their mom is there you know sometimes it works it worked great the last
crusade it worked very well for me in the force awakens it worked at bad moms christmas part 2
I'm a deacresmas by the way no disrespect by the way I'm driving around town saying post for bad
moms too right and most of them make sense it's uh it's uh uh uh uh christian battle a bell
bransky you know it's christian bowel it's Susan Sarandon it's real akunas then it's
Cheryl Heinz right what does anybody know who Cheryl Heinz is by name that didn't religiously watch
curb your enthusiasm so I thought you were going to say she was too young to play no
I'm saying like they're they've got her on these posters like she's like look it Cheryl Heinz is
in this wow that took a turn I mean I I love Cheryl Heinz uh I find her character on curb
your enthusiasm to be one of the most annoying characters in television history well back that up
I think without her the show falls apart I mean I especially she needs to be a mouthpiece for a
normal normal society it is very clear to me I think you and I probably relate too much to Larry and
hate her when it starts when I when they divorced I was miserable I felt that when they got divorced
when it's because I think they're perfect for each other when it starts okay when it starts I'm like
that's how I felt yeah first couple seasons I was like I get it she's got to be the person
that's like your lunatic then it becomes clear to me that Larry David saw that divorce writing on
the wall yeah had hit some kind of point with his own wife and she becomes literally the wife that
just sits in the billion dollar house all day being like that's true Larry you idiot and it's like do
you see where you're living right now can you get off this guy's back do you know his situation
yeah she cheated with the guy she she starts to come across that way yeah Larry David's actual wife he
was building her her own like home and the wife was fucking the contractor in the home and Larry
didn't find out about it and because it had been more than 10 years in the state of California even
though his wife who he was building a home was cheating on him he had to give her half of his money
and half of Larry David's money is an absurd amount of money it's yeah it's at least 250 million
dollars so yeah I mean I would say the portrayal changed but she's certainly never reached the heights
of like Jeff's wife no but Jeff's wife the Suzy Esman is it's cartoonish she's so fun she's
great she's great she's great they make Suzy Esman a little more cartoonish yeah but there's a turn
in the for me now the show is is really about funcows talk about a guy coming into his own talk about
the guy coming into his own house and and part of it is how bad his face looks honestly helps it
but my god he is so funny when he and even stuff that you can tell is not supposed to be jokes like
when he keeps talking about in this past week's episode which wasn't even that good but they open
the champagne and he goes oh I love that sound I love that sound don't you love that sound and it was
so it's so perfectly captured like how boring everyone is like that he had to know how funny that
was to keep saying how much he loves the sound of champagne and he's like we're gonna live it up aren't
we let's live it up tonight we're gonna live it it's a parody of like it's great people who never go
out like going out but holy shit he makes well it's like the deleted scene in about Schmidt where
they go to the prime rib place yeah and they he's the voiceover saying how they go every Sunday
and it's such a routine he's so miserable right and then he's there with the guy that you find out
his wife was fucking yeah and they put this the prime rib down and the guy goes whoa they do it
nice here and all they and you just feel so sorry for him yeah this is the highlight of this guy's
week yeah it's why I'm not going home this year it's awesome but fun cows are I haven't seen the
season yet but I did see the one scene I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry have you seen it about Schmidt
oh sorry the deleted scene where he goes and orders the Blizzard yeah I don't remember it though I've
seen all the deleted scenes it is about a four -minute scene in real time of Jack Nicholson ordering a
Blizzard and I think that it's supposed to be a parody of when they wouldn't make what he wanted in
five easy pieces right and they go you want me to hold it because I want you to hold it between
your knees like choose the girl out slams the tail so now this is him like 50 years later that's I
think that's the point of the scene is parodying that's it where like they wouldn't get him what he
wanted he blew up at them so they keep telling him like what substitutions they will him want to
allow and he's trying to get like he all he wants is like Reese's pieces and M &M's in the same Blizzard
and they won't do it and then finally he's like all right well I'll just go with the Reese's pieces
and of course the scene had to be cut right but man it's it's like like all of about Schmidt
and something he's never been able to do since it's like super funny but also very sad to imagine
that at some point your life will become arguing about a Blizzard which it will and honestly I'd
argue about a Blizzard right now if they weren't making it right but the scene the one one of the
only scenes I saw of the new season because I don't have HBO and it was the fun count of the fun
cows are seen big shout out to Elizabeth Perkins in the new season Perkins oddly never better my left
we follow each other on Twitter don't know how it started don't know where it came from we just
started following each other yeah she's favoured some of my tweets I have a great admiration for the
lady I remember first seen her in about last night where she sadly had to simulate interest in James
Belushi big exactly yeah and I'm not shitting on Jim Belushi I'm just saying you can I've heard a
lot about Jim Belushi you can go ahead anyway she but the scene where she's like do you like my water
and he's like I hate your water yeah I feel like I stuck my head up a dog's ass or skunks ass
whatever yeah he just goes on that it was incredible that scene really made me laugh and I also saw
the scene it could be the greatest line ever on curb your enthusiasm huh the namaste thing for the
ladies like it says that my light inside of me is recognizing the light inside of you and he just
goes uh you see there's the problem there is no light in here I was like that could be the greatest
Larry David line ever I love the show I mean this this seems been light on classics but I mean
any criticism of it I'm like you're getting new episodes of curb your enthusiasm shut up we're
roughly 10 minutes away from the end of this thing we haven't gotten to the subject let's do it
holy shit now for me that we give the people what they deserve folks
uh for me the scariest and you're gonna make fun of mine but I had to go back to like childhood
um the one we've always discussed in the show number one I was gonna say mohalon drive but
having lived in a movie having lived in LA for 10 years mohalon drive is a horror movie yes no
question yes the guy behind the dumpster at winkeys in mohalon drive um so my pick is and go ahead
and make fun of me but it really did traumatize me when I was a kid a picture called return to Oz
I am a huge fan of return to Oz I own it on a DVD I could kind of say any scene from return to Oz
because rough one uh I would say no movie has ever scared me more if I'm being honest and took
because of the age I saw it and etc I had never seen anything scary and was not allowed to see
anything scary and return to Oz you're not expecting to be scary and it's like uh you know it
it would be like a hard PG -13 now I would say it's a very very dark film it's great for me when all
the uh all the heads yeah the queen the queen changes her heads every day which is like an amazing
set piece yeah where she has this like chamber of heads and she can change her head to everything
the whole head and they're trying to sneak through the heads without waking them and I remember
being like honestly like shitting my pants yeah and then of course the head start coming to life and
they all start screaming at the same time yeah I and even now I haven't seen it in years I bet that
would really fuck me up it's a scary scary scene and they're escaping from a tower where the queen
mom be your name is yes has locked d 'Arthia way because she said I'm gonna keep you in here until
you're old enough for me to cut your head off right and then I'll add you to my collection right
so it's a very disturbing the whole prince of premise the whole thing is very disturbing that movie
is very disturbing uh the good guys are scary tick -tock is scary yeah the scarecrow king is scaring for
some reason I always found this the most disturbing part to be when the the wheelie the wheelers are
wheelers there's a gang rape element to the wheelers there is must have been intended and when the one
hits that sand that you can't touch and he turns into sand immediately it's a great special
effect yeah he just collapses and shatters yeah that always disturbed me it's still kind of
I find it still a bit haunting return to Oz uh I would say even like by cult movie standards it's
culty like like no one really knows the movie sometimes people from our age group do but it wasn't
available for long time I bought it on amazon for five bucks if you haven't seen it check it out it
plays like an amazing horror movie it's better to me than both the dark crystal and labyrinth which
get a lot more discussion uh I would put it above labyrinth I will not put it above the dark crystal
that's fair that's fair but you want to talk about non -harm movies that scared the shit out of me I mean
that movie the dark crystal sure when I was when I saw the commercial for that movie as a child
I started crying yeah at the sight of the skexies and the missed the mystic in particular because
all you remember was trying to describe to my ran upstairs to my mom crying and I said why
because they said Jim Henson's name in the commercial I said why would Jim Henson make something like
this uh and I said there was a man in it that looked like he was a thousand years old and it really
really disturbed me uh and to this day that movie if I'm in a dark room alone and I start thinking
about the skexies they still freaks me out a little bit sure very excited for that new Netflix
dark crystal series coming out really who's doing that the Henson companies doing it oh I can't wait
to prequel series to the movie what a dream yeah that's going to be very cool to be honest folks I love
puppets who doesn't who doesn't the great muppet paper is one of my favorite movies of all time
the great muppet paper is is so fucking funny I it's on HBO now so if you have HBO go whatever you can
watch it I mean holy shit not so not only do you have the muppets and like their best jokes of all
time and like cool action sequences frankly right you also have Charles Grodon playing the villain and
a love and trust for Miss Piggy Kermit is battling Charles Grodon for the huff of Miss Piggy is
groten funny in it groten is incredibly funny in it yes he doesn't just play an asshole I mean
he's like a funny asshole he's really really funny yes I'm gonna walk oh Piggy Piggy Piggy Piggy
you know I love you Piggy groten nobody better bethaw not my shoes bethaw and bethaw and not
I'm alone oh bethaw and no we're we're we're we're recently talking about midnight run just going
why would you eat like that why eat that stuff you kids you know stuff will kill you to rezone eggs yeah
yeah yeah cuz I ordered sheree zone eggs but joe I was telling you on my sitcom we had on
shoot him again Chris from McDonald one of the great characters of our time nicest man loved him
and he was telling me
that he had played the Robert De Niro role in three midnight run sequels
and I was like what the fuck are you talking about because they were they were talking a few years
back yeah about making midnight were they really stepper they're they're out there are three like
direct to DVD midnight run sequels start Chris from McDonald that's like when I found out there were
two or three more smoking in the banded films yeah which the two sequels that was the police that was
too much yeah there were two or three more that were like direct to like USA right flicks were
somebody else played the band didn't run on in my career I was approached to write a
direct to DVD money train sequel well and I watched money train out and they didn't have
either Harrelson or Snipes yeah yeah did they just assume the money train brand would be enough
yeah that's like when they did carolitos way rise to power yeah exactly all right listen what are
we doing here okay we're running out of time we picked up we picked our top our top no we didn't we
have a bottom three's I haven't said any yet dark crystal you said dark crystal and I was agreeing with
you I said return to Oz and you said dark crystal I don't know you said for five minutes you said I'll
put it above dark crystal and I said I wouldn't but I'll put I'm gonna give you a quick runner -up
but number one go with your choice my runner -up high school hallway seen in juice when all our apps
shuts the locker at two pocket statement you realize it's already after he's attempting to you
know he's gonna start killing all of his friends after he's already killed the one friend and you
guys how sinister he is and he just does I mean talk about a guy that it's a shame I really think
he could have done some really wonderful film work yeah is that monologue where he's like you know what
last time you call me how's crazy I was kind of tripping right but I thought about it I am crazy
yeah what else I don't give a fuck yeah he tells him he's gonna murder him he goes as soon as I
realize he goes I ain't shit I never gonna be shit as soon as I realize you ain't shit
pow yeah it's it's a very upsetting scene and I get nervous every time I watch it it is as threatening as
I've ever seen a human being I loved juice that that was that was a great age of let's let's say it
of black crime films yeah there was some of I don't know what else I would call it folks
but uh menace's society dead presidents set it off it's fucking amazing yeah uh and then the
comedies Friday uh next Friday yeah don't be a menace like I miss those it was like hood movies it
was like when the hood they don't have boys in the hood well boys in the hood is a master uh higher
learning higher learning uh which more of a race movie but you know it's it's it's that I fucking love
higher learning and they're just not made I don't know why they're not but they're not made anymore
well the I the great beautiful irony and what made it such like an awesome Michael Rappaport moment
yeah because that guy's awesome of course but uh that that that Twitter video he did which was so
amazing yeah of trashing the white the the alt right net white nationalist whatever in uh
down south and being like you fuck a teaky touches why don't you try to get the second base with a girl
get nerds yeah that that was pretty great it was it made it even better that he plays the nazi in
yeah higher learning yeah like and he's and he's shitting it's great uh
okay my number one is in higher learning hi J .R. Ferguson is in higher learning he is
pretty size of a roll my number one no no I didn't do my number one yet pet
you just went so I go no I said I'm gonna give you a quick one runner up
that my number one my number one I've already texted it to you uh army navy backroom store
scene and falling down yeah sure when the guy is basically gonna rape Michael uh Dougal I was
in Michael Cain I'm falling down yeah and finally stop ripe and they thank you Michael Dougalist does
not bend first the prestige then the triple prestige then you raped me in the back of the
army navy store the army navy store that's not a bad Michael Cain that's good the army navy still
governor all right go ahead uh it's just such a scary scene because the guy is clearly pissed off
yeah Michael Douglas doesn't want to go all the way into like white supremacy territory with him
and then Michael Douglas as crazy as he is in the movie stands his ground and goes the guy goes we're
the fucking same don't you get it and Michael Douglas goes no we're not the same I'm an American
and you're a sick asshole yeah and uh you're like here he goes Michael Douglas is about to get raped
by this fucking lunatic right in the back of the store and then uh things take a turn but uh that's
this hands down the scariest non -horn movie scene I've ever seen him I've fallen down it's incredible
yeah um this was not gonna be on my list but I would be remiss not to mention being 13 years old
and seeing pulp fiction and seeing that scene in the bottom of that wreck room yeah with that
rape I mean that uh you I mean I had never seen anything like that in my entire life or even
thought about it and to see vingrams getting butt fucked in the basement of a gun shop I was like
what in the name of guy I was I was and uh Heather so when I if I saw when I was 14 whenever it hit
VHS I was about 14 and Heather said her dad had rented it and she was about 12 13 it was watching it
Heather has never seen past that point in pulp fiction because she said she like passed out
like just rough scene you know it's when you're a rough scene when you're a kid yeah you know like
I obviously now I'll watch fucking anything I might have a very open mind to anything but it's just
kind of like what's like you don't even really really know how to process and you buried the lead
a little bit on it because it starts with him saying bring out the game bring out and I remember seeing
it in the theater being like what does that mean I know and they drag that guy out from literally
the crawl space that is that's a real real rough scene it's the best scene and then right into him walking
across that crosswalk with the donuts and him slamming on the gas like folks have you heard about
pulp fiction it's very good movie you probably don't even tell you that my number one this is the one
you're gonna make fun of me for you watch it now and of course it's not scary if you're watching
that as an adult but something about it still does get to me because of how badly it affects me when
I was a kid and that is the large margin scene in PV's big adventure because much like how when I saw
pulp fiction when I was 14 I had never thought about somebody getting asked right before and there
it was in front of me I had just never seen anything scary in my life and I was so excited to see
PV's big adventure and I was obsessed with it but for the 10 minutes leading up to the large
margin scene where her head turns into like claimation and makes a scary face scared the shit out of me as
a kid when I would rewatch it even the 10 minutes leading up to it I would be sweating as a little kid
sitting there sweating dreading this moment when large margin face was gonna pop out of the screen
um and I mean that's one of my favorite movies as well it's it's incredibly funny
but just to throw that into the movie is like insane and I love it it's great and that's why Tim
Burton used to be the best and now he's a massive disappointment at every step that he takes
folks folks you wanted a bonus app there's your bonus app we'll see you soon no plugs on the bonus
apps we're thankful for use thank you