We have our second ever guest here on the, we'll see you in hell -pog,
podcast. It's, it's our first ever guest for a studio recording studio, kitchen,
recording. We did have a guest as we said earlier on the live show, but we're
thrilled to have this guy. We already talked them up earlier, but you know him
from all kinds of comedy, you're writing for the Simpsons, all kinds of awesome
stuff, and he's on a horror -efficient auto. I know it's wrong in my opinion, one of
the greatest comedy hours of all time. Check it out if you haven't heard it or
seen it. Dana Gold, everybody. Here he is. Hi, everybody. How's my volume? It's
hardy good. I'm glad you pronounced it horror, because sometimes people go,
he's a horror -efficient auto. I'm like, hey, hey, hey. This man knows
how to slow down or slow down. Some things are best left unsaid.
Now, Dana, yes, you have done horror series. Yeah, you did stand against evil.
Walk us through this, IFC. Yeah, I had, I'll tell you, you know, I was always, you
know, genre fan. I'm sitting in my garage, which is kind of, I wish you could kind
of wear on my stuff is. See, a little bit of it. Looks awesome. And you know,
got a lot of, got a lot of famous monsters magazines and bags and boards. Got
all my stuff. And that was a comedian. And I didn't realize until well into my
career, I can combine these. Yes. And I had an idea right when I left The Simpsons
in the late, in around 2008, I guess, to do a show that was basically, what if,
what if I took the cast of Seinfeld and put them in the world of what then was
not at a living debt because it was before the walking debt. And I thought that
was a really fun idea for, you know, just a bunch of self -centered jerks in the
middle of a zombie apocalypse. And then, and this is before shot of the dead and
everything. And, and comedy central and their infinite wisdom said, comedy hard doesn't work.
Okay, great. That's why they're on top, baby. Yeah. You're clearly right. You have game shows
in roasts. Yeah. So that didn't go. And then shot of the dead came out and, and
zombie landed and much of the things that, you know, and I was watching, like, oh, I wish
that was me. Right. And, you know, people have the same idea at the same time. We're just
common. And, and so it took me a while. And then, you know, I could just never come up with
another idea that I thought was, was worth doing. And then I had an idea, basically, what if
you took the ex files? And what if, Jillian add to some of the ex files, instead of being
paired with David to cover me, what if she was paired with my dad who, who just, it wasn't
that he didn't believe in stuff. He just didn't give a shit. Right. And which is a joke, we used to say,
but the idea of it came from when we were kids, you know, my brothers and I, we all watched
horror movies. And we always joke that if my father was in one of the planes fighting King Kong,
that he would keep flying away to check the score and then come back and fight King Kong,
fly or check the game again. And that was basically the idea. And, and from that came
stand against evil, which was, you know, one of the ways to do horror comedy. And there are,
there are several ways to do it. And there are several ways to do it. And then often,
they do it the way that you're not supposed to do it. It doesn't work.
What do you think tilts the balance? Do you think that they get too funny?
Are they're not scary enough? Or what is the problem with a lot of horror comedy?
Well, one, here's the one way I know works. And then I'll give you several examples where they
completely ignore what I say. And it works fantastic. That the horror elements don't know they're
in a horror movie. They don't know they're in a comedy. And stand against evil. All the horror
stuff was played straight as a heart attack. The monsters weren't wacky, they weren't silly,
they didn't fart, they didn't trip, they didn't, you know, they were, and then the people,
because it's a heightened reality, they don't even have to behave comedically. They just behave
normally, right? And not in a stylized horror movie way. And it's going to be funny. That's an American
werewolf in London. American werewolf in London is hilarious. Not because they're funny. They're
playing it the way you and I would play it. Yeah. Just like, this is fucking insane.
It's 100 % true. 100 % true. But then what we do in the shadows comes out, ignores everything I
said much better, much bigger success. Right. You tell me. And Beetlejuice, Beetlejuice shouldn't work.
And it does. So there you go. But I think there's a difference. I think the difference in what you're
saying, I think what you're saying is very accurate. I think the difference though between
the things you're saying, but that ignores it and does work is there's a difference in the genre
approach to those. I think there's, you have a horror movie that has comedic elements to it.
And then you have a comedy that has whatever elements that comedy needs to work. So what we do in
the shadows, first and foremost, 100%, it's a comedy. Yes. It's almost like when they talk about the
Godfather versus goodfellas and they go, well, the Godfather could have been about oil tycoons.
It didn't matter. It was about the family and the drama, the family. Goodfellas has to be
about gangsters. That's true. You know, Coppola said that what because he didn't want to make the
Godfather originally because he doesn't, you know, that's not what he thinks of as Italian culture.
He did want to glorify it. And then he realized that it was about capitalism. Right. That was his.
And then it's true. You know, I think you're right. And, you know, standing as evil was a horror show
that was kind of funny. What we do in the shadows is comedy. Exactly. And by the way,
it's brilliant. You know, it's brilliant. And what would, you know, then again, like,
we talk about like beloved horror comedies, like the monsters and the Adam's families and their
original and their original version. Neither one of them has ever made me laugh.
We talked about that earlier on this episode. We were talking about the new monster's trailer.
I haven't seen, I haven't seen the new monster show yet. So I have to withhold my, I'm not going
to say anything about it. I haven't seen. Sure. But we were just both saying, you know, I think I've seen
every episode of Adam's family some monsters. I don't think I ever cracked a smile as a kid. I watch
them. If they're on, like, I like the world. Yeah. I like the set design. I like, you know, I like
Fred Gwynn isn't Fred Gwynn and John Aston and Carolyn Jones and, and, um, uh, Vandacarole are all
incredibly appealing. Right. Um, but like, I know what the jokes are going to be before they do them.
You know, it's like, it's raining. Let's have a picnic. Oh, I get it. It's opposite. Um, you know,
I think if you look at it, if you look at what I think is the greatest horror comedy of all time,
I think his avid and his fellow meat Frankenstein. Pretty good. Pretty high up there. Yeah.
It's exactly what you're, that's a horror movie. Like I, I have a horror script out now that we're
trying to get fully made and that whatever. We're in the process. And my whole approach with it was,
no, it's a horror movie. It's just in the downtime. I'm going to have the two characters talk like John
Fevere and Vince Vaughn to each other. And that'll make it interesting and funny. Yeah. They're,
they'll just be real people. Yeah. And it'll be funny. And that makes that part not boring.
But at the first performance, it's a horror movie. And if you watch the avid and Castella,
particularly the Frankenstein one, it's a, it's a horror movie. It's just in the, in the butt
avid and Castella parts, they act like butt avid and Castella. Yeah. And it, it gives you a little
telling me you saw Dracula.
I've telling you how I saw it. Yeah. No, that's a great question. Let's say, let's say pre 1970 and post.
Pre 1970 and probably, well, I will say it's not real. It's, it's a comedy. It's not a horror movie.
Ghost, Mr. Chicken. Don, not. Which is great. Very funny still. And post, I mean, I would put
you know, taking the fact that American War of the London is not a horror comedy. Although
people say it's a horror comedy, I would say that or um, Beetlejuice, which I really admire,
just for the fact that that, the fact that Beetlejuice works. Yeah. Is a, is alarming because it shouldn't
work on, on paper. That shouldn't work. Where you really need, and it's, and it's why Mars attacks
doesn't work. Yeah. And you have Martians that are hilarious and human beings that are also trying
to be funny. Right. And you're supposed to have a statement. If you took the Martians from Mars attacks
and use them to replace the aliens in Independence Day, but kept everything else about Independence Day,
you'd have a really funny movie. Right. Because you'd have the humans taking it seriously in the
Martians I carry. But in Beetlejuice, they do the same thing. Jeffrey Jones is kind of funny.
You know, when our writers kind of funny, and, and everything else funny too. And it works. I can't
explain it. That's interesting. That's interesting. What, what, um, would you, I was going to put you on
the spot and ask you to do that. You're done. Not suppression. I'll do that. You don't put me on
the spot. I rarely, rarely I don't do it. Do it. Give us some knots really quick. And then we'll keep
trying to think of what a good ex, uh, well, I did it when I did him on the Simpsons. He was talking
to Chief Wiggum through the television. Chief Wiggum live is amazing for the man in blue.
And when I met him, I, I met him at a autograph show. I met him at the Simpsons. I met him at
an autograph show. And I, uh, I had him sign a, uh, a window card for the ghost of Mr. Chicken. Do
calm and murder go together, which is calm, calm, the calm and murder go together, murder and calm,
calm and murder murder murder. I mean, it's funny. And, and I say, would you sign them? And he was like,
is that a line from the movie? Yeah, this is police. Yeah. Please don't be this person. Um, he's very,
he was, you know, he was very sweet. I was in a room once with, uh, Norma Donald and he,
his very, he used to tell the story constantly about how, uh, Don Knox was out hitting on a woman
at a bar. Sounds ready. Like three company days. And somebody came over and was like, hey, Don,
I, aren't you a married man? And he goes, yeah, he's not going too good. That was my first ever
attempt at an impression. But I'm going too. Yeah, I'm not going too good. The perfect answer.
Well, I one of my favorite, one of my favorite moments in show business. This is a super name,
Robbie's story. Um, I was in a, a movie, I was in the TV movie remake of The Love Bug,
which, uh, in 19, uh, Peyton Reed's first movie, uh, who directed all the Ant Man movies. Of course,
and Bruce, Bruce Campbell, Bruce Campbell was the lead. Oh, well, and I was the evil henchman.
And Bruce and I obviously get along very, a lot of common shared interests. And we were talking about
the ghost of Mr. Chicken Monday. And he just let loose with come, do come. And it was just great to
watch Bruce Campbell do that. And it was just beautiful. I think a beauty. So that's, that actually brings
me to a something evil that too is very high up. Yeah. Yeah. I was going to bring up people to,
that would be mine. It's funny. Evil did too. In my opinion, top of the top of the, top of the list,
right? Top of the heat. Yeah. I don't, by the way, I don't, I don't argue that. I just, it's, it's
all subjective. I don't like Army of darkness, though. I think it gets, it's what you said. Army of
darkness to me gets two Mars attacks. All the soldiers are bumbling. The skeletons are cracking jokes.
Sam Rainey would agree with you. If you listen, if you listen to his commentary on the movie,
he's like, this is totally out of character. I don't know why I'm doing this. Really out of character.
But there's some really funny, there's some really funny moments in Army of darkness, but you're not
wrong. And what army of, I mean, what evil dead too, Dan, I'm telling you, nothing you don't, I'm
my favorite moment of Army of darkness is when he looks at the old guy. You want some of this? He just
finds the one old guy. Yeah. There's a lot to like in Army of darkness. It is a little ridiculous.
Yeah, but what I, what he did, what he did with evil dead too, that I don't think anyone had
done it before was he took Gore and made it slapstick. He just, I mean, it's a three -stugious movie.
Yeah. Yeah. It's all of that could be done. I mean, Bruce Campbell could be replaced with the three
stugies. Yeah. Well, they're literally doing this stuff. That's what the stunt, the stunt, the stunt
you just had a lot of you, I'm sure you've seen it, a plumbing. We will go where they go.
Where they're going to watch the Niagara Falls on television and then the water comes to the television.
Well, if you replace that water with blood, it's evil dead too. Yeah. Yeah. Right. No, that's
interesting. And then, and then in at least in the first season, maybe first season and a half
of ash versus evil dead, I felt like he kind of got back to what I liked because the scary parts
and that are scary. When they end up in the cabin again in the series and the wife comes out of
the thing played by Ted Raimi, it fucking scary again. Yeah. Yeah. And that's what I like. But I want
to, I want to get to something that links to you meeting Bruce Campbell and whatever because Pat and I
were talking about it a little earlier, you have this strange connection to not just interest in
to the world of horror. And I just said to Sam Morrell, you Sam Morrell. Yeah. He's the best. I love
Sam. And you guys worked on a show together. Yeah. We were talking about he was telling me about
the show. But then I said to him, I go, I was watching the incredible shrinking man criterion collection
Blu -ray. And the bonus feature is Dana talking about that movie with Joe Dante. And I go, you know,
you know, you're shit when the criterion collection is tapping you to do the bonus features. Yeah.
So you're, you're officially an auto. I was, I was with Mick Garrus yesterday.
So how do you, Mick Garrus? Does he have the ponytail or what's he doing here?
He does. He's still rocking it. He's doing it.
Aside from your fandom, what is your, because you were telling us the other night, we were all out
that bar together that used to go to a breakfast and with Greg Nicotare and all these, what was
your way in with all of these things? It comes very, I mean, and it's, it's good because as a comedian,
it's given me sort of like a career, it's, it's helped my career because it's given me an area,
you know, it's given me an area to mine and to work in. And you know, if people have a hard
comedy, they come to me. They're like, great. Yeah. I like, I like money.
You know, it's given that one just being a fan and becoming friends with Greg Nicotareau,
who I met through his cousin Frank Nicotareau, who's a stand -up. And we, I mean, we met in the early
90s when he had just wrapped army of darkness. Okay. You know, so I've known him for a long time.
And we're just friends. And then you just meet people, you know, and people just, you just,
people know you. I mean, you know, Greg refers, you know, Greg refers me to John Landis, who's
looking for a thing. And then I, and now I know John Landis, and then, you know, John Landis does
make an I know make. And it's just by knowing people and not being an asshole. And people like,
you know, 90 % of show businesses, can I stand to be with this person? Yeah, that's true.
Um, and so that's why Zoom, I think, is deceiving you. It is. interviews over Zoom. You can't tell who's
an asshole. It's unfortunate. That's, that's I'm playing that card very hard. Well,
well, I should have liked you better since you went to the other room. It's a better vibe. Yeah,
for sure. But, but then, but then there's like with my podcast, um,
hour, um, uh, just talking about things, that's how the criterion thing came about. Like,
somebody a criterion, new, heard me, somebody a criterion, heard me talking about carnival of
souls. And they were doing the criterion version of carnival of souls. And, and we have all this
information about Centron, which was her carbies company. And about, uh, uh, Tara, we don't
and it's kind of dry. Um, but could, could you talk about it and, and the way it'll be a little
bit, but it'll be, do it and it'll be, and as a sure. Wait, Dana, say what you just said again,
because we're getting some interference here. Um, it's okay. Sure. It's freezing up. Let's all go,
let's, I hate to do this, but let's all go off camera. So we get a stronger audio signal because I don't
click your stop video button. It's in the bottom left.
All right. It's part of that. Yeah, that we're
uh, I just don't think as he go, we'll allow it.
Okay, I think we're better. Can you start this story over again, Dana? Sure. Of course. Of course.
Um, I'll, I'll add to the beginning with Greg. Just the carnival of souls.
Okay. Sure. Yeah. I mean, so, you know, a lot of it is just knowing people,
you know, just about the stuff that I'm interested in and criterion was doing carnival of souls
and someone over there heard me talking about it on the wet on my, and they contacted me
through, I think it DMed me to Instagram or something. Okay. We're doing this thing and we have all
this information about, you know, her car V and stuff and it's kind of dry, you know, would you let
us interview you and you can kind of relate the information that we need to get across but a lot of
face to it and, and you know, I just did it and we became friends and, you know, they're great.
They're the greatest people on Earth as you can well imagine. And then, you know,
some else came and I was like, Hey, we're going to do, we're going to interview Joe Dante, but we don't
do it alone. You know, are you free? Are they sure? And did you meet him doing that or elsewhere?
No, I've actually known, I've known Joe from that kind of that, from that world. I think the first
time I met Joe, I interviewed, again, people just know you as like, I'm interested in this stuff and
I'm, I can talk, you know, and I've done enough shows that I'm not just going to, I have a,
I have a comedic ability without the comedian's desire to only ask people questions about me.
Right. So I think the first time I met Joe was they were doing
mask of the red death at the Beverly cinema and someone said, could you interview them?
And that's a sure. And then I met Joe Dante and Roger Corman. And then, you know,
then I know Joe and we're in the same social world. And like, you know, then I see him and he's
like, Hey, do you want to do trailers from hell? You're allowed to. Yeah. And then, and then you get to
the point where it happened to me last week, somebody said, Hey, I was at a wedding and met a friend
of yours. I said, who's that? And then when Joe Dante, I was like, Oh, yeah. And then I did think,
that's insane. Yeah. Yeah. That's insane. And I'm friends with Joe.
Well, I mean, I would put Joe with the ring on my list of war comedies, the original
grandma's and people is of course comedy, but brilliant in its own way as well.
The matinee is underrated. Oh, I love and own matinee. Yeah. Yeah. I've never seen matinee.
Oh, matinee is matinee is gorgeous. It's, it's, it's, I put it right in there with that
it's just gorgeous. And you'd love that over jump. And inner space, of course, is fantastic as
well, you had quite a run there. It was the parody of fantastic voyage that America was demanding.
Exactly. That's funny, Pat, that you mentioned inner space because you Dana, you mentioned specifically
inner space in the incredible shrinking man conversation that that you asked if it influenced
inner space because it was about a guy shrinking down. You know, it's funny. Roger Korman,
I watched Philadelphia for the first time since the 90s the other day. Yeah, he's in it.
Yeah, I'm watching the testimony like we he brought AIDS into our cup. And I'm like, is that
Roger Korman? Yeah. Well, he gave Jonathan Demi his start as a actor, doing women in prison movies
that are pretty good actually. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. He's good. He's good actor. He should have
acted more. So he said around you said, I want to watch an AIDS movie tonight or what
brought you to Philadelphia on a random evening. I was the holiday weekend. And I like to throw on
precious. Sure. Sure. You had just seen Elvis and you wanted to see Tom Hanks skinny.
Right. Yeah. Your home at Christmas, we put on last tango in Paris as a viewer. I was in
put some butter on bread. I was at the airport. I was getting ready to go on a flight. And I was
doing something where they were flying me first class, which is you always remember those flights.
Yeah. And I'm in the, I'm in the, you know, the little waiting area where the gate
and Roger Korman's there with his wife. And I walked up to him and I said, I hadn't met him. This
was before the interview. And I just said, Mr. Korman, I don't mean to bother you. And I wouldn't say
this if it wasn't true. I watched the tomb of LaGia two nights ago. Yeah. And he went, oh, that's a
good one. That's a good one. And we couldn't, you know, it was very sweet, very lovely guy.
That's very, and then we get on the plane and I'm in first class and he's not.
Yeah. I heard he's notoriously cheap, right? Yeah. He said, like, no, I don't like it. That was
the backyard. Yeah. I wouldn't pay for the first one. Yeah. Those, those stories from the bonus
features of the Korman movies where they're like, and then Roger said, we have the castle for another
11 hours. That shoot a second Vincent Price movie. I was just, I just wrote a thing about spider
baby, the, the Jack Hill film. And his first, his first film, his first directorial work was just,
can you shoot 20 minutes of stuff and we'll cut it into the terror so we can release it as a movie.
Right. Right with Nicholson, right? Yeah. And Boris Kroov. Yeah.
That's really, really funny. I just, we just got the 10 minute warning here.
From zoom. Yeah. I also can, we can do another one if you want to do it back or yeah. Yeah.
Let's keep talking. Yeah. I got a question for you real quick, Dan, before we get off criterion.
And I'm holding the, the blue ray of incredible shrinking man here. I got two questions for you. One
thoughts on the Lily Tomlin remake. Hey, it's a Rick Baker girl, a suit. God bless him. I think Richard
Matheson was involved in that, which is bizarre. Yes. Yeah. Well, I think something tells me that
when it left his typewriter and became a script, there were some changes made.
But it's like, what does he know about writing? Yeah. I love Lily Tomlin and I love Richard
Matheson. So, and I love Rick Baker. So, it's great. Did you read the, when I was watching the
criterion, blue ray, they, they, there's a, there's a, you know what, no, that's not true.
I went on Wikipedia and started to read up on the movie. And on Wikipedia, they had a synopsis
of Matheson's original sequel called the incredible something girl. Yeah. Yeah.
Daughter, I think, or something? No, it's, it's, it's the wife. The wife. Yeah. The wife goes back to
the house and something happens that makes her shrink. But then that movie ends with them
together tiny. Yeah. Like, yeah. It was a very hopeful, nice ending, but it never got made. It didn't
have one agreement. You could never cheat on each other, either. The thing about, the thing about,
the thing about the, the Matheson story is an incredible shrinking man is, is also what I love about
his, probably one of my favorite Matheson stories is I am legend. And he also put a lot of it into
the night stocker is that the problems are very real. Like, yeah, if you're shrinking, your problem is
the cat. Right. You know, your problem is standing water. You know, it's like all of those things,
finding food that you can fit in your mouth. And, and I am legend. He just, you, that movie,
that story so effective, because he spends so much time talking about like, I have to take care of my
teeth, because there's no dentists anymore. You know, just like things like that that really
said your teeth on edge. And, you know, we're talking about, like, it's not a horror comedy, but
what's brilliant about the night stocker is every character in the movie is saying, there's no such,
yeah, but there's no such thing as vampires. You know that, right? And the fact that he just hammer it
into reality makes it so much better. It makes it work so much better. He, he, he, he pull, he does.
He pulls the, he pulls terror out of the common experiences of the character. Like, there's a great
amazing stories called one for the books that Richard Matheson wrote. And it's about a janitor
who suddenly is able to absorb information by just being near it. Oh, wow. So like, like, it starts
with like, I forget, it starts with like physics or something like, because he cleans the physics
classroom and there's stuff on the chalkboard and all of a sudden, it's just in his head because he
stood near it. And his duty is cleaning the main, you know, classroom hall on campus, whatever it's called.
And then one night after he has this weird power that he doesn't want and that's haunting him,
but he's just trying to live his life. A janitor says, I need to switch duties with you. Can you
clean the library? And you're like, Oh, no. And he unwittingly goes into the library and screams
because all of the information goes into his head. Oh, wow. It's such a cool, little weird, terrifying
thing. Cause you're like, no, have the janitor have to do a thing in janitor. It's go sweep up the
library. And now it's, it's, oh, that's like the ending of the man with the X -ray eyes. I can't
still see it. What you're saying about the cat being the real threat, you know, that that's
probably the best writing advice I ever got. And I got it very early. My first big job was on
it's always sunny Philadelphia. And Charlie Day said to me one day, because the show was so crazy
and heightened. I was always trying to think of these crazy. What, what, what insane thing could they
do? And that kind of thinking always leads you to make the characters do something they wouldn't.
You're already thinking crazy. And Charlie brought me a side one day and said, you need to be
thinking about what you would do in these crazy situations. And that changed my whole perspective
on writing and, you know, set me on a much better path. Cause I think so few people in comedy,
in horror, in action movies, stuff like that, it's all what spectacle can we give and know how
would a person react? And that's why you hear people in horror movies go, what the fuck are you doing
in the theater? Because if nobody would do it, you immediately don't care about that person.
And in some cases want them to die because they're being so foolish.
Yeah, there's a terrible story. I mean, just a terrible story because I feel bad for both people
in this story. They're filming the end of the first Batman. And Jack Nicholson is going to Timberton.
Why am I going up there? Why am I going up these stairs? And Timber just goes, I don't know.
And that's not good. We already, because we already shot the second half.
Yeah, John McGinley, John McGinley, who was the lead in standing against evil with Janet Barney,
he was very good at that. He would not let us get away with anything.
Yeah. Yeah. It's annoying. When an actor does that, especially, you know, I've done multi -cam
shows and they'll come up. They save your life in the end of the day. You realize, oh,
you just saved my life. Exactly right. You're pissed at the moment. The audience is all staring at
you. And then you think about it and you're like, no, it's going to make the scene a million times
better. Thank you. Yeah. I think, I think in applying to horror, like with what you're both saying is,
I think that's why the best horror, in my opinion, it's always been, I say it all the time,
make it a thing that's inescapable. And then your problems are solved. The exercise to my
opinion greatest horror movie ever made. She can't escape it. It's her daughter, her daughter's
upstairs, her daughter's possessed by the devil. You're fucked. Nightmare on Elm Street. You have to
go to sleep. And then the guy is there. Texas chainsaw massacre. You're stuck in this town. It's a
one -horse town. There's no way out. I think that's such a simple cause. Yeah. Exactly. It's the reason
they hadn't beat up the radio and jobs. I'm assuming. You know, if it's unavoidable, well, then hey,
then you don't have to make the person walk down the hallway for no apparent reason. Right.
Whatever it is. That was actually a really good movie with a girl trapped in the basement with the
alligator. Yes. Yeah. Crawl. Crawl's great. Yeah. That guy's good. That's a guy's a good horror
director. Spanish guy, I believe. Yeah. But the guy that did the evil dead remake, isn't it?
Same guy. Same guy. Then I have to ask, I own, it was my one big dream as a kid was to someday
own the entire criterion collection, which explains why I had very few friends. But I do currently have
the criterion collection. Wow. That's impressive. I saw your tolo thing behind you. Yeah. Well,
if you, you know, they come out with three, four a month, and if you buy them at half price,
which they have sales all the time, it wasn't even that hard, but I've been doing it forever.
My big question is, did you get a peak at that criterion closet?
No, because no, they're in New York. And I shot everything out. I shot everything out here.
Okay. But but if you went to New York, you could get in there. You think I could. I could. Yeah.
They're very there. And if you were in New York, they let you in there. They're really not.
Yeah. I mean, I'm in New York. How do I get in there? I'll connect you with my friend. They're great.
That would be amazing. My favorite YouTube criterion video is because they interview celebrities in
the closet and, you know, and they take things like Hugh Jackman or, and my favorite one is Colin
Quidd because he pulls the, he'll pull the movie off the shelf and I'll go, my kid Nikki is a great
film. You know, he like mutters and talks about how great it is. And then he just puts it back.
He keeps taking things off and talking about them back. It really made me laugh. But there are some
people who couldn't fathom owning a movie. Like my ex -wife was that way. Like what, which explains
a lot because I have a massive collection. You know, so yeah, the criterion closet, it's,
is that a, is that like a, is that on the criterion channel? Or they do. They have celebrities go in it
there and they do like these 20 minute videos where like Bill Hader will go in and talk about his
favorites and hold up the disc or whatever. And then, you know, there's social media and all that,
they, they, I don't know, it seems like a very glamorous place. It is. Well, it's one of those
places that it's so great. I'm surprised it's still operating. Yes. Yeah. Yeah. Has it this been,
you know, completely agree. And when I make all my purchases through them, you know,
Barnes and Noble will have these 50 % off sales, but I always wait for criterion because they do
the same thing just different times of the year. And yeah, if you spend, I think I believe that if
you spend $500, you get a gift certificate for $50, which is an amazing deal. And twice a year,
they had 50 % off sales. So you get these amazing packages for 20 bucks. And you know, I think it's
what Terrence, you know, you used to say all the time, but film school can be watching this shit.
Oh, yeah. I said these commentaries. You know, yeah, you're getting a, I went to film school. You're
getting a better film school by watching the criteria in collection. Definitely. Yeah.
True. And just making a movie. Well, that, that too.
Terrible. You know, make it with your phone and see how it works. Right. You'll learn. You'll learn
and apply. It's like, you know, I'm assuming it's like stand up comedy. It's like, how do I learn?
You have to do it. It's like skydiving. Scooby, do you just have to? Well, speaking of stand up
and harmer, you have, and I told you this the first time I ever met you at the old,
in the back of the old meltdown. Yeah. Doing a show. Now a beautiful empty lot.
Now a beautiful field of dirt. I told you in that back room, there, I mean, there was a show room
back there. We weren't like hanging out. Yeah, lurking around the back room. Yeah. But we were
in the back in the green room. And I told you how much I loved. I know it's wrong. And
but that joke in that that I think is the top tier joke. They're all great. But the black dolly
a joke. I mean, my God, not sure you can do it today. So Pat, if you don't mind, can I tell Pat
sort of, can I take him through the joke? I've seen the special. It was a while ago, which is no
no insult to you, Mr. Gold. But I recall a bit, but not specifics. And I'd love to hear it again.
He describes the black dolly murder, the victim's body being found to with such grim detail.
And he's hitting every part of it. And it's just, it just keeps going and going. It's so dark.
That's ringing a bell. Yes. Yeah. The audience is so quiet. And then the last, I think,
I might be paraphrasing, but he says, he says on her face, her mouth cut into a hideous smile,
as if to mock the very horror she had been fallen. And to this day, police are still don't know
what she said to have the guy do that to her. What she said to deserve that. Yeah, yeah. And then
you go, it must have been a doozy. Yeah. Pretty terrible. In retrospect, you know, you're hard, Dana.
We know. But I, I, I was talking to you about that bit. And I, and then you comment on the
audience, you're like, when they finally break and laugh and you go, that, I love that because
everybody's going, what is happening? Is he having a stroke? Like what is going on right now? And
I was just the director of the special. Like I had to go in and I was like, they had shot it
just with me. And it didn't work. I was like, no, no, no, you have to show the audience not
knowing what I'm doing. That's the joke. Right. The joke is that they have no fucking idea what's
happening. And they're just relieved. I have an ending. I remember, I mean, if, while we're on
inappropriate humor, I remember a dice had a joke where he's like, they're always like, why did he
do that? They never like what did she do that made her and pick her up over his fucking head and
throw her down the stairs. But I remember talking to you about the technique because you're talking
about stand up and just do it with your phone and learn it. You know, you learn as you go to try
by fire. And that's, that joke is the technique of that is something you have to learn over time.
And you called it something. I said it's so crazy data because I'm so loud on, I'm like loud.
Well, I still, but I think what I said was probably something I learned from Stephen Wright, which is
reverse yelling. Yes, that's what you said. That's what Stephen says. Yeah, it's just like he's very
quiet. And it's like yelling because they have to be quiet to hear you. Right, right. You know,
so you just kind of go, you go quiet on them. And you know, so much of coming up in Boston, which
was such a tough place to start out in terms of the audiences. Kenny Rogers and used to say, you know,
you go on stage in Boston, there's two couples in the front row welding.
Another guy fucking a dog threatening you with a knife if you make the dog laugh.
But it was really true. It was really tough. So you really learn crowd control right out of the gate.
Like you had to learn how to us for, I mean, for lack of a better term, assert your dominance over
this crowd. And I still, you know, there's, there's things that I do totally subconsciously,
but just from doing it so long, like I always go to the very lip of the stage. I cover the entire stage.
It's like a dog marking its territory. And, you know, audiences are relieved.
They are, you know, the worst thing that can happen is if an audience feels that the comedian is afraid
of them. Yeah. They get uncomfortable. And, and then they want to destroy you to get you
to get you off. Yeah, there's very few comics that can pull off that like shoulder hunched
slouch to the stage or how it's going on, you know, and they're don't get me wrong. There are very
many people who make it work for them by the kind of the sly approach. But, uh, you know, in a rowdy
crowd, that is never going to work really unless you've got amazing jobs. Right. Philly was Philly was
similar. And I was very, Philly's very simple. Yeah. And I was one of the few white guys in an
all black club when I started. So you really had to like prove yourself. Yeah. And it was like if you
weren't funny, I remember one time. Uh, so two Ray Gordon, who was like my mentor, he's a great guy,
a hilarious guy. He used to host a show called Thursday night hype. But this is how like,
not only was the crowd hard on you, but then if you sucked, the host would then stick it,
which I'm sure they did involve. Oh, yes. And I remember a guy did this bit, man. He was like DJ
hit it and they played some song and he fucking stripped down and did some bit. He was in his god damn
underpants. And it was silent. It bombed. I can't imagine anything worse. It was brutal. And he
goes, thanks y 'all. Good night. And he walks off stage and two Ray comes back on stage and just
goes, God damn. If you want stage butt ass naked and they still ain't laughing, you just ain't
the fuck funny. That's a valid point. Yeah. And you were just, but that was like the the stakes where
you were just like Jesus Christ, man. Like it was like you felt like people were going to throw
rocks at you or something. Oh, yeah. Yeah. It was it's brutal. I mean, it's it's it can be
really. Where did you learn? Because it's funny. I know you're from Boston. I always associated you
with San Francisco. Yeah, I moved there. I moved. I moved there in 87, but I started in Boston in
82. I had, you know, and then you go to and there was so different. San Francisco was like, you
know, it's like, you know, it's back then in the 80s at the height of the quote, comedy boom,
unquote, like, you know, you'd be on stage in Boston. People's like, fuck you San Francisco. People
are like, how many fan clubs do you have officially? You know, it's like, you know, it's just like
such a it was like John Ross said it was like being an otter, having your belly rubed.
The audiences are so so air you died. But it was, but it was, I was glad that I had started in
Boston because I needed the stage craft that I learned in Boston. You can't, it was the same,
there was the same thing with like the alternative scene. It's like, you can't do this every night. You
can't go on stage to an audience of your friends and talk about your audition every night because
you're going to go on the road and you're going to die. And that happened to a lot of people.
What's interesting though to come circle back a bit to horror, but
I always think it's very interesting when I meet somebody from that core East Coast. Jim Gaffigan
always called it the, the, the, what the fuck did he call it the sector of hatred or something?
It was like Philly, Jersey, Boston. Yeah, he's he's it's just furious. You know,
but um, but it's interesting because New York is a very, very different story than Jersey and
mass and Pennsylvania. And but they're all sort of connected through, you know, their own way.
But I think it's interesting when you meet somebody with your set of interests who's from like
tried and true, like sort of blue collar mass because yeah, these are sort of niche. You know,
look, horror is a huge genre. It makes millions of millions of dollars and all that stuff.
But it's a niche kind of thing. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. What what was your gateway thing? What was the
first thing you saw where you were like, oh, this is like going to become a lifestyle thing for me.
Well, and well, I was all, I was a horror fan much earlier than I was in the comedy.
You know, as a kid, I mean, out of the gate, I was reading famous monsters magazine,
watching creature feature and Boston was creature double feature on Saturday afternoons.
Star Trek every night at six like that was always built in the Aurora monster models like that was
always my thing. And I was going to be, I wanted to be a special effects technician when I was a
really little kid. I wanted to do stop motion because I built models and I think, oh, just build models
for living and animate them. And then um, then the night stocker came on and then wanted to be a reporter
for a year. And then, what area do you want to work in, Mr. Gold, monster, monster, monster reporting?
I want to wear seersucker year round. And then, uh, you know, I get older and I got into comedy and
like Monty Python. George Carlin was the biggest influence I had as a standup, but it was also the
heyday of Steve Martin and Saturday night live in Monty Python. I really got into it. And, um,
and I never thought that I could combine the two, you know, I just like, you know, I was good at
being funny and I'll be funny. And then when I go home, I watch horror movies. Um, and then you come
out to LA and you realize, no, you people, you're not the only one. People are really into this.
You know, that was before the internet. So you just, you just have to, do you know who forest
sacrament is? Yes. Oh, okay. Then we can talk for 10 hours. That's for him. I met Goldthweight and
Tom Kenny and Dan Spencer and Paul Kuzlowski. They were all in Boston when I was in Boston. And
they were all like into the same stuff and plan nine and all that stuff. And, and so I knew other
comedians that like the same stuff as I did. And it tied in with music too. We all like punk rock,
horror movie, you know, bad horror movies punk rock. It's, it's, you know, it's, it's that thing.
Yeah. You know, wearing, wearing pink converse because it bothers people. Right. Is the cramps the
intersection of punk rock and rock? That's a pretty good one. That's a pretty good one. I think that's
got to be bones. The remones are in there too. Sure. That's cemetery gets them on that gets them on
the chart for sure. Yeah. Check out both of you. Check out. Um, I just found a garage band from overseas
called The Monsters and they formed in the 90s and they're amazing. Okay. There's, yeah, I know it's
so they dress up. No, it's funny. If you look at their picture on Apple music, they look like the
presidency of the United States of America. They're like these skinny Broadway. And then you listen
to the songs and it's like, I want to die. Let me smell me. Let me smell me. I'm pretty good.
Honestly, it's disturbing that that just popped out of your mouth with no thought.
Yeah. It's my opener for later. You're sure that's not rock team music.
But I love that you talked about the, and I'll just mention it briefly because we talked about it
a little bit the other night. But when you said that when you got out here and you found that this was a
thing, you know, my last two years when I was living in LA, I was so fucking depressed. And the thing
that helped me get through was like I said, I met the guys from Monster Party and I discovered
Burbank. I had one into Burbank. And I started going down to all the collectible stores. Yeah, Magnolia.
Yeah. And buying all the action figures and Monster Memory. And it just, it was a day to day,
you know, makes you happy. It's your, it's your mac, it's like, it's just pop culture mac and
cheese. Just makes you happy. Yeah. It's fun. I said to Kurt Bronholer one day, I realized how
depressed I've been. And he goes, why? And I go, because I have a shopping bag full of GI Joes.
That's beautiful. Dana, what is your most treasured piece of horror memorabilia?
I was given as a gift from, well, there's a couple of them. Myla Nurmi, who was vampire.
Yeah. Was a, was a friend of mine. A very good friend of mine. And she gave me one of her last
vampire fingernails that she had painted a self portrait on. She was very gifted artist.
And on the back, it says for Dana, which was a, that's pretty cherished. And then Bob Burns
gave me one of the flying saucers from Plan 9 from outer space that he had this collection.
Yeah, that's pretty jaw -dropping. Yeah. Did you, so I went to one of those many, many years ago.
Did you, you ran those, correct? The, the kind of celebrity, all comedy readings of Plan 9?
Yeah, that was my thing. Okay, yeah, yeah.
It still is. We're still. Myla's 100th birthday is in December. And we're maybe going to do another one
for her birthday. Oh, that's great. Yeah, when I, when I first moved to New York from Missouri,
I was 22. And I came out at Times Square. And I was just like, you know, it was like Axel Rose
and the, welcome to the jungle video of a piece of wheat hanging out of my mouth, looking around
all the signs and everything. And yeah, I want a date.
This was like, it was about 11 .30 p .m. on a Saturday night. And I was like, oh my god,
this is so amazing. And playing at that big shitty AMC 25 multiplex was this wet -hot American summer.
Yeah, 10th anniversary. And they had the entire cast, a raflo away. And everybody was there. And
it was the most amazing. I was like, this is what New York's going to be like. And it kind of was,
you know, coming from Missouri. Then the plan nine thing, if I'm not mistaken, I went to that
three days into my move. Wow. And it was a very similar experience. It felt so exciting and
and very, very cool to me. So it's so, that's so awesome that that was your thing.
Yeah, it's like the school play. Yeah, you know, it's a big, it's a big night. It's a big fun night.
Yeah, I have, I really, you know, when I first moved to LA, there was a place called theater theater.
It's now gone. It was at Hollywood and fun or Hollywood and Coinga. It's a Greyhound bus station now.
That's been demolished too. I tried to go to Greenblast today. That's permanently closed.
The world is the world's coming to an end. Yeah, sorry. No, no, just in theaters and the opening shot
of Ed Wood. Okay. Yes. The Johnny Depp. That's where he's in front of theater theater. And there's
to be a show there on Saturday nights called the Girlie magazine party, which is Jim Turner,
Mark Fight, Steve Higgins, Nick Bakai, a bunch of people that I knew doing it was a parody of Playboy
After Dark as a stage show. And eventually I weaseled my way into the cast.
And that to me was like, oh, I've made it like that meant more than other stuff because like, no,
I mean, this cool thing that I went to at night, there was just like, everybody was so funny. And so
and it was such an inside thing like if you didn't get the joke tough, yeah, you know, I loved it.
And and that's what playing nine feels like to me. It's like, yeah, no, this is
this is for people that, you know, if you don't get it, I'm sorry. But everybody here gets it.
Right. That's one of the things I miss, very dearly miss about Los Angeles life. And particularly
with Pat, like going to those types of events because this is, you know, where it's all sort of created,
right? So those events are just part of the culture here. And that sort of thing is part of
the culture here. And it's, you know, Pat, how many times did we go to the Egyptian theater
to see? Oh, remember that horrible one we went to data. You'll appreciate this. We paid,
that could be anything. I think we paid $75 a piece to go to the album of Draft House.
What the fuck was it? It was there. It was there. If it wasn't Halloween, it was close to it,
but it was there kind of all day horror marathon. And I love, I love going to that stuff. And I know
the older I get, I'm not going to be able to sit in that tight chair for 12 hours. I want to keep going.
And we went to this thing. They were showing the worst movies. I mean, we paid so much for it.
And did they close down the Alamo at some point? It was the worst theater downtown. I hate to shit
on it. But at original one in Austin was so amazing, was so amazing. And it still is. And you know,
I don't think it franchises very well. But and now every movie theater has a bar and food wherever.
But yeah, but the you know, the Egyptian, the arrow, the new Beverly, there's so many of these places
where you can go and meet your people in LA. I would say more so than New York even. Yeah.
I remember one of the things from that Alamo showing the one of the hosts goes, I know this next one
is a weird choice, but it just meant so much to me when I was 12. We're going to watch the remake of House
on Haunted Hill. No, the Jeffrey rush house on Haunted Hill. And what they really mean is this is
cheap to rent. Yeah. Yeah. The first two movies were streaming on Netflix. Yeah. We were like,
we just paid $75 for this. Yeah, they play. And then they played a, if I'm not mistaken, Joe, the last
one was a film that someone who organized the festival had made sort of an envy. No, no, no, it was
the guy that made green rooms first movie. Okay. Yes. That and green room is fantastic. But this is
a really good movie. We were excited. We thought it was going to be green room. And then he goes,
we're actually going to show my first movie. And then he takes a cheap shot at his own movie and goes,
I'll see you guys later. I'm not staying. Yeah. Yeah. Couldn't couldn't sit there and watch his own
movie with people, but we had to who had paid $75. It sucked. But New Bev is great. You know,
yeah. And there's nothing like seeing like, you know, I, you know, it's just like, if you love a
movie, you can see it again. Like, I've seen planned on a billion times. But if it's on a big theater,
my favorite, one of my favorite memories is before the Center Amidome became the arc light. And
now it's becoming something else. When it was just the Center Amidome, they were showing planned
on one Halloween night at midnight. And I took my Lanermy to see it. And she's a lady. And we're sitting
there. And then vampire comes on screen and the place goes nuts. And they don't realize that she's
sitting with them. And Mila said, Oh, there she is. And it was just that was very sweet. That was one
of my favorite favorite memories. That's awesome. And to get her running commentary during this film
is funny. Right. To see him sober. You didn't see that a lot. You know, things like that.
But the one, the one that stands out to me, we got to see Pat and I got to see a triple, a
Bert Reynolds triple feature. It was smoking the bandit Hooper and Sharky's machine. And Bert Reynolds
was there. Wow. He did a full Q &A with the audience after smoking the bandit. And the one
question I remember in answering, somebody said, in the end, how did you direct Dom Dom Delewese?
And he goes, when you're making a movie with Dom Delewese, you simply don't.
That's really funny. I remember, I don't think you were there.
Simply don't. I went with Avril, I believe. But we saw this Paul Schrader movie that barely got
a release a few years ago with Nicholas Cage. Are you there for that? It was called Doggy Dog
with Nicholas Cage and Willem Defoe. I wasn't there, but I remember. Yeah. The movie was interesting,
you know, but better than its reputation. But they brought Nicholas Cage out and Paul Schrader.
And they're interviewing Nicholas Cage and somebody asked a question right off the bat. And he goes,
let me just stop here because I need to say my son's here tonight, my son Gage.
Gage Cage. Gage, would you stand up? This kid stands up. He's seven foot two.
Just like a golf seven foot two. And he goes, all the movie, all the music you're enjoying tonight
in the film was composed by this young man right here. We all applaud Nicholas Cage's son, very
weird vibe right off the bat. And then somebody asked like, you know, what was it like working with? I
answers in a way that had nothing to do with the question was basically like, what was it like on
how was face off to work on or something? And Nicholas Cage buries his head in his hands and he goes,
you know, I was just making a movie in Bucharest. And it was a 12 minute story that didn't
address the question in any way. But it was a perfect night, you know, it's exactly kind of what
you wanted to see. And then that's happened all, well, they happened all the time. They're
happening less and less lately. Unfortunately, but that movie by the way was the one where he's on the
submarine and like a beast gets loose or something. I mean, yes, it was like Dana, what's next?
What's next on your agenda, man? Like, obviously, I, you know, we know you're writing on something now.
I don't know if you can talk about it or not. But I'm making a movie in Bucharest now.
Right now, I just, I just wrapped the first season of, I guess we can talk about it. It's been in the
Ted, which is based on the Mark Wahlberg series of films, series of talking teddy bear films.
I told Joe, I think you got my job on that show. I didn't tell you the other night because we had
just met. But I believe you got the job that I can graduate. Well, yeah, well, Seth is great. I
really love working with him. He's super great guy. Did they stick to what what it was originally
supposed to be where it's a multi -cam where Seth is voicing it on stage, but the bears not there or
how did they actually shoot it? I don't know. Oh, it's a secret. Okay, I'm sorry, I shouldn't have said
that. We can edit that out if that's a secret. No, that's okay. I honestly don't know.
Oh, okay. You just, you didn't go to the tape. We wrote all the scripts and then I don't think it's a
multi -cam. I think it's a single -cam. Well, then it's, then I met there ages ago. It was a multi -cam,
but that's not for sure, because I didn't know how they were going to do it unless it was alpha style
with a puppet. Yeah, and that ain't happening. Yeah, okay. I can tell you that. And then, you know, I'm
working on a, I wrote a film that we're waiting to see. I wrote a film about Watergate that is
actually nothing to do with anything that people associate me with that we're waiting to see about
attaching some talent to. Nice. Like a Watergate drama, like all the president's men kind of
livers. Yeah, there's a story about story about one of the peripheral characters that's pretty
interesting. And, you know, we'll we'll see what goes on with it. It's a very interesting story.
Has been told. And then I'm going to start another film that's, that's definitely a genre film,
but it's based on a true story. Okay. And then I have hanging with Dr. Z, which is my little
side band. And we're, we're either going to do a third season of that for YouTube, but we're trying
working on that now where it's all the folks what that is, especially on a, on a horror sci -fi
podcast. Yeah, you know, it's hanging with Dr. Z is a show I did on YouTube is you've seen this
before. It's the talk show Dr. Z is had in the 70s. It's based. I've did, I've done the Dr. Z is
as a character a bunch of times. As, you know, because I'm friends with Greg Nicotaro, the makeup is
exactly what they had in the movies, but we play him like, he's like Sammy Davis Jr.
Planet of the Apes was a movie he made. He's done a lot of, he knows everybody. And there's like
when celebrities would go on Mike Douglas or Merv Griffin and just name drop the whole, you know,
I was an Allen all this house. And you know, who came over Susie Flushette, that woman can make an
Ambrosia salad. Now, here's the thing, you know, just that kind of, and I just love that. I love that
era of show business. Sure. And so that's, that's what he is. And he has a, he has a talk show. We've
done two seasons where it's, you know, it's like an old talk show. Dr. Z is the host. And then he,
it's very much like for him with tonight or space ghost, ghost to coast. How many with Dr. Z, you
can see it on YouTube. And we're hoping to expand its profile. How brutal, because I remember
watching that on YouTube and going, I admire this guy's commitment. I remember I pitched, I pitched
admire or question. No, no, no, because I, I, I tried to sell, I tried to sell a thing,
the Comedy Central, a comedy web series about the emperor from Star Wars. And we had Palpatine.
Yeah. Yeah. And I was going to be the emperor. And I was like, like, as soon as they were kind of
asking questions, I was like, I'm not doing this. So I really do it. Like, how bad is that make? Like,
what is the, how long does it take? Is it to stay in? And, you know, the whole idea was a sketch I
wrote for the Ben Stiller show. Okay. Call in 1992. And the sketch, by the way, another key. Yes.
Shaping, comedic influence on a young Patrick Walls. Oh, very good. Very good.
Kim, I mean, I was not allowed to watch and live in color presumably because there were too many black
people. But when Ben Stiller came along, I finally got my taste. He's white watch that. Yeah,
exactly. Honestly, that's probably what it was. Yeah. Um, well, yeah, I wrote a, I wrote
Planet of the Apes of Musical as a sketch. And it was just like a commercial for the musical. This
was before the Simpsons did it. Um, had nothing to do with the Simpsons version that came later. And it
was better than mine. Um, had nothing to do with it. But, um, you know, it was basically like when,
whenever Hamilton comes to town and they do like a commercial and with clips from the movie clips
from the play was that. And then the second commercial, you know, you have to do, you know,
you can't build all those sets and just do one bit. And then it was like, from the producers of
Planet of the Apes of Musical, uh, Dr. Zeyes is Mark Twain tonight. And, and then 20 year,
and we got canceled before we could do it. And the only reason I wrote it was because I wanted to
do the makeup. I wanted to get in the makeup just because I love it. That was that trophy. Yeah.
Getting in the makeup was that would you have gone with the Twain white hair and beard? No,
we did. It's, it's on. You can see it on on YouTube because what happened was 20 years later,
I was talking to John Hodgman. And he was, he had found a photo of one of the orangutan actors
reading Mark Twain's biography. And he said, I want somebody to send me a video of Dr. Zeyes doing
Mark Twain. We were talking about something completely different. I said, I wrote that as a sketch
20 years ago. And he goes, really, and I told him what I just told you. And he goes, would you want to
do it at sketch fast? Oh, wow. Like 2010. And I like, my first, I was, no, that sounds like a lot of work.
And then I, and then I thought, well, I actually do know people that can do this. And then I realized
it'll get a big laugh. Right. When they realize it's not a shitty mask. When they, when they,
like, I realize, there'll be three laps. I'll come out and I'll get a laugh. Yeah. Then they'll
realize that it's exactly what the makeup was in the movie. Right. Not just a crappy mask. And then
I'll get a much bigger laugh. Yeah. And then halfway through the bit, when they realized that I'm
committed to doing Mark Twain, I'll get a bigger laugh. And I get very greedy for those laps. And so
I did it. And I had Greg Nicotaro gave, you know, I hired one of the guys in the shop. And, uh,
and then it just, it just grew. And I did it at TCM introducing the Fathom events for Planet
of the Apes. I did a lot of benefits for, you know, my, my favorite two things outside of the show
were him doing Mark Twain tonight. And if you Google sweet Caroline, I come out and, uh, as doctors
say, isn't an Elvis suit. And we sing sweet Caroline from that's the way it is in front of a live
audience. That was pretty great. I will look this up for sure. That's incredible. Um, um, so the
answer your question. It's two and a half hours in and about an hour, hour and a half out. Jesus,
that's, that's admirable. I mean that I want you to, well, it, it never isn't funny. Yeah. That's why I
do it. It's never not funny. You have anything that you want to plug this side for what you've
already said. We've got a six, about six minutes left on this thing. I just want to make sure you don't
get caught. Well, there's my, uh, there's my podcast, the Dana Gould hour and Dana Gould. Bulletin .com
twice a week. I write little mini essays about nerdy movies that I like. Okay. Great. You monetize
that, Dana? Uh, the people who own the, uh, the, I was paid to write for the first two years.
Oh, okay. Okay. I'm just always curious how people make money. Yeah. I like everybody else. I scrounge.
Sure. We all know. We all are now. I mean, it's, uh, you can send us a few bank statements. We'd
appreciate it. Oh, okay. Yeah. Uh, what, what, uh, and I got to ask you this because I didn't know
that you wrote for the Ben Stiller show did because there are two sketches on it that have blown my mind
forever. Oh, okay. Huge tales of the dark side fan. And I'm a huge twilight zone to me is the,
the, the, the, the, the settling run is the greatest TV show. I agree. I agree. Um, I agree. Yeah, he
spoofed twilight zone in one. We're the animals, man, where, where they, the humans are in the zoo.
And he spoofed his father's episode of Tells in the Dark Side, where the stern type of DJ turns
into the actual demon in hell. Yes. I'm the voice of the devil in that. Okay. So did you write those
because I didn't write either, I didn't write either one of those, but I am the voice of the devil in
the DJ one. That's incredible. And, uh, and I wrote, no, I wrote, um, I wrote all the grady's
commercials, though, that's me. Okay. I remember that. Yes. Uh, I wrote, uh, auto the anti -cupid, uh,
with me. Yeah. Okay. Um, I helped Rob Cohen with Menetti. Okay. Yeah. We did.
Did you write the Woody Allen monsters? No, I think that was Bob Odin Kirk did that. It's,
it's funny because the twilight zone spoof is called bad twist ending science fiction theater.
Yes. And it's a literal ending from one of my favorite twilight zones. And I remember the
first time I saw it laughing and they're going, Hey, fuck you. That's not a bad twist. That got me
what I was. I'll tell you a very quick story with the time we have left. I, you know, because again,
you're like, people know you do stuff, right? You know, like, and people know that I like
plenty of these. But if you follow my career at all or any of the things that I do, I talk about it
a lot. I have an ape talk show. So I got a call one day from somebody had boom comics.
And they say, Hey, we own Rod Sirlings first draft of Planet of the Apes, which is very different
from the movie that got made, which I knew because I read it. And I thought they were going to say,
we're going to publish it. You know, we're going to publish it. Was you like to write the forward
or something like that? And then instead, they said, would you like to adapt it as a graphic novel?
Wow. And I said, like, yes. And they were like, well, the money, I'll pay you whatever you want.
So I wrote it. It's called Planet of the Age Visionaries. And but what I didn't realize is like
the first draft of a screen is 147 pages, like it's like giant. And graphic novel, you can't,
you have eight panels of page, five to eight panels of page, one action per panel.
You know, and so every day, I would get up and sit down and have to edit Rod Sirling,
which is no job for somebody who idolizes him. This image of this chain -smoking ghost
over my shoulder. Why are you cutting that? That's the best thing in the script. It fucks wrong.
Right. And Rod Sirling seems like one of those guys that would have been like,
why can't a screen play be 360 through pages? He's in black and white as he watches over you,
but you're in color, I feel like. I said, yeah, yeah. I met his daughter, Ann, who's very sweet.
And I told her that story. And she laughed and said, I can't say he wouldn't have done that.
But you'd want him to. I mean, that sort of perfectionism leads to that show. Dana,
this has been fantastic. Oh, thank you guys. I'm sorry. I was late.
Sorry. No, please. This was delightful. Thank you so much. This was this was awesome. Thank you
for giving us so much time. You're really, really appreciate it. Check Dana. What are your social
handles? Dana Gould. Dana Gould. Check out everything. Good choice. Good choice.
Or hanging with Dr. Z at Instagram. His Instagram feed is pretty great.
All right, great. Follow, listen, watch all these things that we have discussed here with Dana
today and watch the stuff that we all talked about. That we're all fans of if you haven't seen it.
It's all great stuff. Thanks for being here. We'll see you next time, everybody. And we'll see you in hell.