Welcome to we'll see you in hell it's the podcast you turn to when you want to hear the hot talk about the hot
movies my name is Jota Rosa my name is Patrick Walsh and this is we'll see you in hell this week we're talking about Scott Cooper's antlers starring Jesse Plemmons and Kerry Russell and then in our second episode that drops this week we'll be talking Ghostbusters colon after life there you go welcome Joe how are you we both were just talking before we hit record about what horrible moods were in
hopefully that won't be dragged into the podcast tonight my favorite thing in life is to have to tell somebody the same thing three times in a row sure sure sure it's don't get me started anyway hope you had a happy holiday I'm a little I'm a little stressed you know we open the bar finally it went very well okay but you know it's it's wide
I'm on a wild runaway train as they used to sing runaway train never going back so was it packed I mean you had great beer specials I noticed it was it was healthily full yeah I was steady business was good um some friends popped in but it was a lot of strangers which was great
because that's what you need in a business a stranger's coming in sure but our dear friend Will Pottoff came in with his dad and they hung out for many hours and we had a great time and I was bartending for a lot of the weekend it was a great time
come see if you're if you're in New York 174 Rivington Street Joey Roses Wednesday through Sunday we open at 12 p .m. each day
uh that's great how much you make dollars since 48 ,000 dollars it's very good for quarter beers that's people drink a lot
yeah yeah so we I kid I kid but anyway it went really well and I'm excited but you know it's a whole new thing it's like having a it's like getting a new dog or
something you know it's like all of a sudden there's this new entity in your life that depends on you right are you the guy who walks around
each table like this can't combine make sure you guys are all enjoying your meals I do a little that not not not like peshy casino style but I don't
do it in an apron walking around talking to people like a kiss the cook apron with a little sauce on it but still with a big
gold pinky ring yeah yeah so they don't forget where you came from yeah uh I I do a little that I check up on
people and make sure everybody's feeling good you have to put anybody's head in the pastrami slicer at any point
the pastrami slicer yeah you have to put somebody's like hand in the in the meat slicer and get them to pay up
I was contracts got to get signed I was gonna say you know that each meat doesn't have its own slicer right I mean
in a well -run sandwich shop they would because I don't want pastrami tasting like salami so I know I know I'll
just take my business to Quizna oh boy well you got you got worse than you got worse than they
toast the bread over there yeah I love how they were just like they just held held firm to that like as their
business crumbled they were like you guys know we toast the bread right that that's all they ever had going
for them jeez I didn't know that and then subway you go in you're like can you toast the bread or jersey
mics they're like short who is knows never develop beyond that one thing oh that wasn't their only
thing they also had like quiz no sauce oh yeah which was kind of good it was French dressing basically
and they squirted it on a sandwich and you were it was kind of like when McDonald's put the big
Mac sauce on and they called it special sauce but you're like it's thousand island dressing you just
don't realize it at first it's true it's such a weird taste yeah it's because you've never had it
in that way it's tangy yeah and then you know I'm not expecting it so yeah so you I was over at at
Thanksgiving at at my wife's families we're standing out in her dad was using a smoker to do the turkey
smoked turkey tasted is the best turkey I've ever had in my life I don't know why anybody would ever
cook it without the smoke problem is everybody's raving about how much better the smoke turkey taste
and then the the moms like you know looks miserable because nobody liked her fucking turkey everybody's
that makes everything about the fucking self but we're out there and there's all these like family
friends and relatives and people I don't know and I'm trying to make a conversation doing my best
and then I go so what else have you made in there Phil or dad and he goes the only thing I've
smoked so far as I did some smoke salmon so the turkey might have kind of a fishy taste this dude
who's like 12 drinks in at 3 p .m. slumped over in a in her lawn chair picks his head up and goes
you know I always like heating stuff with a fishy taste
always been a favorite taste of mine a tangy fish taste I'm like Jesus Christ guys daughters there
it was just it haunted me you know I never like I know my dad's friends were never the type that
like talked about pussy around me you know I'm grandson I'm 40 years old but it still made me blush
and I thought gross for Thanksgiving you know I find it yeah no it's in a in a family setting when
in the river somebody starts talking dirty you know when my uncles when they were I've lost quite a few
but the one the one that one of them that died he used to tell some real nasty jokes uh -huh and I
thought I was really funny but like I also was like very uncomfortable yeah it's weird it's just
the the family combined with the perverse it's also because no one of my family was ever allowed
to acknowledge they had heard of human sexuality so it all it always shocks me a bit my friend
love always teases me though every time we go to dinner he says every time that I say the word
sex or anything to do with sex my voice lowers like to a complete whisper he's like that you can
say sex in public like it's allowed but it's it's it's just something that stayed with me my whole life
shame shame yeah I carry a lot of shame still I mean you you're I can't believe a boldly you're drinking
none of that snoopy mug it's huge it's literally as big as my head and basically I I really needed the
coffee today and we only have one mug big enough to house an entire pot and it's old snoop so because
it's put a pull up his whole pot yeah you can fill up his entire nose it's four cups god I feel like
good would come out all wrong because of the shape of that thing you know what I mean like
not it tastes great no no no I don't mean the taste I mean like I feel like it would pour out into
your mouth all like we're all like it'd be coming it out six different ways you'd be surprised
you'd be surprised I just said some coffee at a diner at a turkey club why do I get a turkey club
what what especially this week after all the turkey I just ate why don't I ever just get the
BLT with extra bacon that's what you want you want the mayo hitting that toast with the tomato
and lettuce and the bacon flavor the turkey is just added shit it gets in the way you don't need
the extra piece of bread on the club you definitely don't need that and you got the trip to pan so you're
sleeping yeah every time I get it I'm I I'm all excited and then I take one bite and I'm like god
damn it you should have got a BLT I hate mayonnaise but whenever somebody's like whenever I'm like
what is this on the sandwich it's good it's always a oily or some mayonnaise -based condiment but I hate
mayonnaise I like mayonnaise I hate a oily I don't like flavored mayo they really piss me off wow
we're very different I need the flavor so that I can ignore the fact that I'm eating
gross egg glob what is it eggs and what milk mayonnaise mayonnaise eggs and what
no no milk it's like oil oils I don't know what the fuck's in it I don't know maybe there's
no no it's like egg white now I don't want oil and eggs I'm gonna look it up I'm sitting at a
computer I'm a mustard man through and through I love mustard all right I love mustard but
mustard limits you more in the joke department you make more jokes about mayonnaise see I feel like
if if anyone even made a joke about mayonnaise and come or something while I was eating a sandwich that
would be done with the sandwich that's how much it grosses me out like usually I let myself like
that doesn't bother me but something about mayonnaise really sits with me and grosses me out let's see here
mayonnaise 10 minutes yet and one egg yolk some salt some dry mustard so that's powder two
pinchers of sugar some lemon juice oh this doesn't sound right at all it's kind of corn oil yes it's
basically my favorite jokes ever on on between two ferns was I believe Ben Stiller and he was talking
to Zach Alphanakis and he's like you look great man what have you been eating egg yellows it's stuck
with me forever it's so simple and yet so funny to me uh my favorite joke is when he told Hillary
Clinton that her husband would try to fuck people her daughter's age and then told Barack Obama
how does it feel to be the last black president which I thought was hilarious um yeah you know
edgy shit he gets away with it I guess he's just done acting or is America done with him I don't know
now he's in that new um he's in like a new Disney animated thing or something
like one of those new stuff that he can just roll in and it's pajamas and do it yeah one of those
voice -only things I mean if this isn't everybody done acting I gotta you know I get I'm getting
screeners in the mail this year I'm like why do you even bother nobody gives a shit anymore
about your new move I just got something in the the called the power of the dog
starring Benedict Cumberbatch like what is this why what a waste of money people lost their
wives in these years and you're this is you're what you're doing and Netflix goes one further they send
you a code where you can watch all their stuff online for free and then they send you an expensive
physical copy of it as well so it's like oh you're doing the environmental thing but still you
need to send this I got I just got a big box and you open it and it says tick tick boom yeah like
what what are the jokers send me something is my house gonna blow up if it but is a hand holding roses
gonna pop out like a jack a lantern and then my home explodes well I'll tell you uh I read the
description of that movie and almost through my face through my sliding glass door oh you'd hate it
I watched it I talked about it on the on the solo movie corner because I didn't even want to bring
the energy here the description of just it's like it's like on the eve of his 30th birthday a successful
millionaire art dealer needs to decide which road to take I was like oh fuck you yeah he's 29
you the first hour of the movie is him obsessing about the fact he's about to be 30 and the Beatles
recorded they're they had already broken up when they were 30 like he's got to be do something great
by age 30 it's like as a 40 -year -old sitting there watching it you're like eat my cock you piece of
shit but uh it's yeah it's Andrew Garfield being real annoying and then lineman well Miranda directed
and I'm out I'm already out lineman as soon as I hear lin I'm out I know you you and it could be
you could be saying evil lin but that doesn't matter I'm gonna assume it's Miranda I'm out would you
believe uh he makes a brief cameo as a dishwasher and a diner like he's a man of the people
a sage sage dishwasher please tell me a sage dishwasher that gives advice he said
but uh as I said on the thing and I don't know if I could ever I said it a hundred percent
accurately and I don't know if I could ever do it again but it's a movie about the guy who wrote
the musical rent which like won the Pulitzer about all the people with aides in the lower east side
uh but this movie is about an autobiographical musical he wrote before rent
so wait what's about rent I don't know he lost it's a it's a musical written by the guy who did rent
tic tic boom tic tic boom Jonathan Larson but tic tic boom was an autobiographical musical
telling the story about how he wanted to have the next great american musical by age 30 but didn't get
there so that's what you're watching and then at the end in a one minute epilogue they're like
after this he did rent which became the Pulitzer prize winning biggest musical of all time but that's not
the story they're telling they're telling the story before oh good so it's this guy like
you know just dancing around his apartment with writers block
like song after song about I can't think of the word to rhyme with oh god yeah that kind of stuff
oh god but uh it's for my consideration and um the one the cumber batch one I think is a
Jane Campion movie when you look on letter box there's all these film critics who give it five stars
masterpiece I've seen it three times and then a whole lot of reviews like this is the most boring
fucking piece of shit I've ever seen and I think that divide is getting stronger and stronger over time
between what critics like what people like it's a it's a it's a it's a strange time I think people's
tastes are way off you know like there was a long time during the pandemic where anything was getting
great reviews because people were so deprived of entertainment and now I just find I can't talk
with anybody about anything I don't agree with what they're saying I'm like you love that really
all right but I don't need to talk to you now I think everybody's fucking stupid I really do
it's to the point anything I hear I'm combative about it now sure anything yeah anything
when they like when somebody was like jeer about this omni what's it called the omni pop
omni -crown omni -crown I just was like how fuck you give us a shit I'm just saying
I'm not about all the other ones and then this one you know I think could be potentially lethal
but I just was like I'm gonna stop reading about it Africa is saying it's fine and then of course
people here are saying they're just saying that because they want they don't want to travel band
right and keep in mind those are all the same people that said it was racist to have a travel band
against China so you know it's everybody can suck me at this point I think we both have asked for
people to suck us so far in this podcast it's not a good sign I watch the movie I might have
just launched into the movie quarter but I feel I feel that it does relate to this all right
take us to the movie corner so I can talk to you about I just watch the movie secret window
start on John depp yes thought theatrically directed by David Cope written by David Cope
based on a Stephen King based on a Stephen King story called secret window secret garden
Johnny depp plays a writer going through a hard divorce
and he retreats to his cabin with his dog that he once shared as a vacation cabin with his
wife to try to continue to write and he is then visited immediately by John Turro playing an
amazing hillbilly saying that you stole he stole his story Johnny I don't remember that at all
John Turro as a hillbilly yeah John Turro shows up like immediately on the front porch dressed
as anyone ever seemed like more from a city than John Turro he's a believable hillbilly man he
and he's like he's dressed like the preacher in um culture guised like in that like pilgrim outfit
okay and he's like you stole my story you know and he's he's great uh huh all right and uh and then he
begins stalking Johnny depp the movie unfolds from there I had I had avoided the movie for years because
somebody had told me the ending and I thought it sounded dumb but I got to tell you even knowing the
ending when I was watching at this time I liked it I thought it was a fun little Stephen King thriller
and the reason I thought of it and start talking preemptively took us to the corner was because
I'm just a sucker for any one of the like Johnny Depp's in the in that ripped bathrobe the entire movie
he's constantly trying to take a nap on his couch uh huh he's smoking he's drinking he's in the middle
of nowhere and I found it very relatable okay okay I haven't seen it in a very long I like since the
theater I don't remember liking it very much but I always liked David kept but that's a cap too he wrote
crystal skull and and he he directed and wrote ghost town he wrote Jurassic Park that's right if that
does anything for you he wrote um I can do like mission impossible or something mission impossible yeah
lots of big stuff he did stir of echoes which I love which we've done on the show he said he's a good
good writer director he's a novelist I've never read any of his books but his novels too very well
directed this secret window he has a lot of fun with the camera and he does a great job and uh
I enjoyed it it felt like a Stephen King movie it felt like a lesser misery you know okay
like reading like it takes place in mostly one location there's a handful of characters
the the small town sheriff comes into the mix at some point you know it's he put the main characters
are writer you know it just felt like a lesser misery you know a misery is a masterpiece so how do you
know lesser is a you know I'm using the word very lightly but right but uh but I did enjoy it I did
enjoy it okay uh I saw a house of Gucci oh well Joe if you have issue with the Italian accents
on television's greatest drama the sopranos you you will not make it to the end of House of
I mean not the Italian accents the this slang things that they have to do okay the
jurezified version of Italians that they do is by if I find cartoonish but how bad are the
accents in House of Gucci completely insane I mean people I had I had already read about it but
you're just not prepared immediately you go in and it's they're a family the Gucci's everyone has a
drastically different accent like drastically different and it's Pacino doing like a real thick
kind of old country Italian it's uh it's a real nothing Pacino performance he's he doesn't really
make much of an impression you got Lady Gaga as Patrita Regiani and she's doing like sort of a
tome my cousin Vinnie Italian you got Adam Driver as Maurizio Gucci who's just basically playing it
like Adam Driver but once in a while he'll say like and he got Jeremy Irons as Rodolfo Gucci but he
doesn't these names are so insane that if you handed me if they weren't real people I'd say what are
you doing with these names you got to change these these are ridiculous names Jeremy Irons is
like the head of the family and he does not do anything to minimize his heavy British accent Jeremy
Irons playing Jeremy Irons a hardcore Italian playing like the most Italian guy in the family so
what you get then the movie is two hours and 45 minutes and there's not really a story to it
uh it felt kind of like a very long pilot to like one of those Ryan Murphy shows about like the
new house of Gucci on FX or whatever so it's entertaining I mean it's it's entertaining in the way
like American hustle or one of those movies entertaining it's a period piece the costumes it's big stars
there's some sex here and there you know it holds your interest to a point but it's also just like
really boring I heard rumors that it was rushed which you definitely feel I mean they could have
taken another 45 minutes out of this with no problem and folks I've yet to even mention
the most egregious performance by far Mr. Jared Lido oh yeah he plays he plays Papa Gucci or
something right he's playing like the like the Sean Penn and Carlitos way role except he is doing it
in a way that if he were on SNL they would say hey you're not Italian this is really offensive
to Italian people like you can't do this performer he's doing uh Mario the host of Mario on the cartoon
when they had like the real plumbers that like introduced the cartoons yeah yeah when it was uh
back when Mario was New York Mario before he was yeah uh Rome Rome Mario well now he's doing
is playing like Paolo Gucci so he's the Frado clearly or whatever and he's bald and stringy hair
whatever but I mean I'm not exaggerating when I say he's like why are you gonna throw me out at the house
of Gucci like I'm not kidding so what I don't understand how why is there no backlash now with this movie
being a white wash of sorts when almost nobody in the movie is actually Italian
the only complaints I've seen about it are that are from the Gucci's themselves who are like
our family was not thugs and criminals and it's like okay Gucci you know but uh the movie was a hit
or it is doing well it's doing a lot better than the last duel which Ridley Scott also directed
this year and is a much better film um that said look I had a good time watching it it's fun trash
but I mean you're really watching it just as a I can't believe what I'm seeing kind of kind of
experiment I can't believe it's not Gucci I can't believe what I'm watching it all right fair enough
I watched um great soundtrack is it like one of those like you know like a boogie nights like a nasty
sexy yeah it's like a sports sazy coke soundtrack what I watched uh I never thought I'd say this
I never thought I'd say this I think we have too much star wars I just think we have too much
star wars I watched star wars visions which is I guess it's like an anime cartoon anthology
thing of star wars um like so it's like every you know anthology does so every episode is a different
story with different characters and it's um they're short they're they're they're pretty short they're
like you know I don't know I think the shortest one is like 13 minutes and the longest one is like 21
or something they're not they're not really full episodes um but it just begs the question when
you watch this thing as a star wars fan as a lifelong star wars fan what is the point
do we need this do we need this star wars cartoon that because here's what I'm getting at the animation
is cool it looks really nice but the story lines are like like the first one I watched I saw boba
and job of the hut in the description so I was like all right I'm gonna watch that one that sounds
cool and it's about a band a band first of all a band in the star wars universe outside of that goofy
fucking job a band or or the guys in the cantina you're asking for trouble but it's a band and it's a
band that plays like blink 182 style music which again like what what is this that's stop it this is
terrible but anyway the story is is that one of the um members of the band is a hut and he's being
hunted by boba fat to be brought back into custody by java to be put to death for betraying the
hut clan or whatever and they go the the his bandmates all go to try to rescue him from his execution
and you're like well how are they gonna do this and his bandmates go to him and say
java granted our request to play one song for everybody before your execution so then you're
like oh this is gonna be cool like they they're they're planning an escape and they're gonna pretend
like they're playing a song and they've got guns hidden their guitars or you know like some star
style shit and no that's not what it is they play the song and then the audience likes them so much
that java lets them live so they can go on to pursue their dreams as musicians what the fuck is
this what the fuck is this i don't need every possible interpretation of star wars i don't need it
i need certain things for star wars the force the Jedi the Sith good guys bad guys smugglers
laser blasters shootouts that's what i need that's what i need i don't need to see that also
in the star wars universe sometimes people like to knit or you know you know there's a cooking show
in the star wars you know i don't need all of this my world doesn't need to exist there in any way
shape or form so you know and this thing is critically acclaimed like through the fucking roof
people are raven about this galaxy show or visions show excuse me and i don't understand i don't
understand where she airing of course disney plus de plus i'm like rat bastards
well i discussed uh get back on the other thing that's something you definitely should not watch
jail on disney plus the eight to nine hour Beatles documentary oh jesus christ yeah i hate the
Beatles living here i know you do it's just like spending time in the studio with them i like to
quite a bit um why is that on disney plus no and the Beatles costs and smoke and smoke where
are wana and all kinds of stuff it's odd that it's on disney plus but i don't know clearly they gave
him the most money probably uh joe the ever seen april fool's day the horror film i can't remember
i feel like i must have seen this at some point um i think at the very least i've started it
on a sunday afternoon on like shutter and then like maybe nodded off and not realized i didn't finish it
or something that's the kind of movie it is uh it's on amazon prime and i logged into amazon prime one day
after a long absence and it was like continue watching april fool's day and i was like did i start
who clearly one night drunk i watched half of that april fool's day didn't even recommend our remember it
so i restarted it uh the movie just sucks it's a it's a vhs box i remember very well i seem to remember
critics thinking it was a little more clever than your average slasher movie but it sucks it's about
a group of eight college friends one of whom is portrayed by tomas f wilson who you might know as
biff from back to the future oh okay uh it's always cool to see him and something else i really like
him to the future right it's 86 so it would have been the year after uh okay right oh right in that
okay yeah but uh the only thing i've really seen him in other than that i think is uh freaks and geeks
where he was great plan the gym teacher and that perfect gym teacher but um group of eight college
friends gathered together at an island mansion belonging to an ares named muffy saint john
there that was like an 80s thing remember like muffy and like chip and the sweaters around your neck
and all that yeah those are the good old days i'm gonna celebrate their last year of school they soon
discover that each has a hidden secret from their past blah blah blah so this is a movie that when
the twist comes it makes the rest of the movie makes zero sense and i looked it up and sure enough
that's the party line on the movie they're like yeah the twist is kind of clever unless you spend five
seconds thinking about anything you've just watched over the previous 90 minutes it doesn't work um
so it's really kind of a dull slasher movie with kind of lame kills and then the twist that it's
famous for doesn't make sense so i i did not like the film to say the least i can't recommend
all right uh my final entry is i watched a documentary called Mean Man
what i think it was on amazon prime it's about Chris Holmes the lead guitar player of the famed
heavy metal band wasp okay Chris Holmes became somewhat infamous whether you were into metal or not
because in the decline of western civilization part two he's there's his whole entire interview he's
on a pool float it is pool yeah drinking vodka from the straight from the bottle and shit face this is
mom sits there silently on the edge of the pool i'll say that and everybody that's ever seen that as
always said do you hear that oh everybody that's always seen that it was ever seen that is always
said including myself like it's just so sad and like god would it disgrace that way in front of your mom
and all this stuff and blah blah blah blah this movie catches up with this guy in present day he now
lives in Holland uh he is not the study once was but he's still a tremendous guitar player and he still
plays music and he's sober for the first time in his life and he's doing well he's married he seems
to have a good life and he's like kind of famous you know like he's he's renowned um but the funniest
part to me was and they talked they get into his whole uh i think the guy's name is blacky something
from the the head guy in wasp yeah black it all us yeah they get into his whole relationship with him how
they don't speak why they don't speak um and Chris homes his legacy uh in in in the heavy metal scene uh
you know and a lot of people compare him to lemmy from motorhead and you know it's it's an interesting
fun watch but my favorite part is they interview his mom uh and you realize she wasn't offended at all
by the way he acted in that movie because she's like i don't fucking know you know these god damn
kids i would smoke pot and bounce like you see you're like man we really just read into that we just
put our own mom in that situation and felt bad for this lady but she seems to not not really care
she seemed to think it was i mean she's a comment on that specifically but she comments on a lot
on his heavy metal career and she doesn't seem to have a problem with any of it so mazel mazel mean man
give it a watch uh my last one shall be new order which is on hulu uh i love the band new order
and i i'm pretty sure that's all that made me watch this movie and i and there's no new order
it's got nothing to do with new order it's just called new order but um it's about an uprising in
Mexico city so there's a wedding taking place at this family's house it's very posh you know very well
to do and this guy comes in and he's like on the wedding day of this this rich family he's like can
you please help me out my wife needs an operation and he's a guy who's been doing work there at the
house for years and he knows the family and they turn him down that's sort of the metaphor
the bigger stories that there's an uprising about the poor of Mexico uh taking back what's theirs
from the rich a scenario that could play out here in america sometime in 2022 but um so you're
watching that and i get the the political deal or whatever it's like yeah it's not fair there's a big
wealth divide there's a gap but i got it yes fine but for the last hour of this movie it's these rebel
forces torturing beating killing sexually assaulting um the the people richer than them to kind of make
their point and and take it back so it leads to this feeling where you're just watching people
be tortured or you're watching a girl like be forced to blow a soldier at one point at gunpoint
and it's like i'm not sure you're making the point you think you're making now you know like at this
point it's an exploitation movie and those that the point though is the point to be like they go too far
and then they make you start to hate the victims i guess that's the point but what a what a
gross point like i mean i could last house on the left and all that shit you know yeah and it's not
quite that it felt like a movie done by people who are very good at filmmaking and not very smart
is what it felt like they're tackling really big uncomfortable topics and playing with like i said
rape torture violence but the the message is not there it's like what they think they're trying to
say is not there and they're not smart enough to pull something like that off so you just feel kind
of gross like you're just watching somebody be violated really um i wasn't a fan to say the least it's a
real it just makes you feel bad you know if you want to watch people get tortured and kind of feel murky
and uncomfortable about what the point of it all is this is the movie for you all right all right all right
fairness fairness fairness i uh scary stuff i hit this criterion sale hard
criterion Barnes and Noble did their 50 % off sale then they extended it to black friday then they
extended it through cyber monday um so i really loaded up i think i mentioned this already but uh
i went back we talk about pathetic the fucking cyber monday and black friday deals are you can't you
can't get 10 % off something in amazon anymore well i think because amazon's prices have become so
competitive at this point they're like guys we can't make it any cheaper maybe i think that's
kind of what it is but but i went on and i i saw some interesting i got a great at you know what i
got on amazon cyber monday i got the four k transfer shout factory of glingary glen Ross for eleven
dollars marked out from 30 okay i dove back into the criterion sale i picked up lost in america
Albert Brooks for 20 bucks i picked up beauty in the beast the terrifying french one
yeah i never saw it yeah i've never seen it either i'm excited to see it and then i almost bought uh
the and i got i got also they got i got the incredible shrinking man did i tell you this already on the show
no i got i got uh i got uh oh god i can't see what did i get with that oh nightmare alley
and uh the original nightmare alley because i want to see this new one
yeah and uh the uninvited i think was the other one i can't remember uninvited fun a little too much
kind of like old black and white comedy there's a lot of like a dog chasing around the house that gets
a little old but it's good and i've never seen um or say the others you mentioned
scorsese said it's one of the five scariest films he's ever seen
that's probably due to the age he saw it as my guess yeah along with the original dead of night which is
just an insane statement man yeah yeah it's all the age you see things i mean like uh the clown and
polter guy still terrifies me but i i'm sure it's because i saw when i was five um but yeah it was
a good sale it was a good sale that that criterion 50 % off uh i did i did get i would love to do video
drum on the show let's do it and what do you think about doing repo man yes well i think we're going to
have to do the matrix for next uh um next one and then yeah we're either i think video drum makes
more sense than repo at this moment in time but we can do them both all right we can do video drum
what about deep cover love it own it haven't seen it i don't know if i've ever seen it because i get
it confused with uh what's the lift gal one boiling point with uh Wesley snipes i always mix them up
with gal is in boiling point which one's let go deep impact now that's no let's go in is the bad guy
in ricochet that's what i'm thinking ricochet with that so yeah ricochet is fun and like a way
over the top way i saw it in the theater i don't remember i went to see because iced tea was in it
and it was this movie after new jack city i was all excited and then i was mad that he's only in it for
like four minutes unquestionably the best person on twitter mr iced tea oh yeah i like uh
just it'll just respond to a comment with like shut up you old bitch it's just always i know just
makes me laugh coasted a long order they're not got he clearly has something in his contract that's like
you will never can do have anything to do with my twitter ever i'm allowed to tweet whatever i want
and he is i mean he's been on that show for 38 years um yeah he said that to Michael uh
uh france ace michael france ace in him on his youtube channel and he said uh iced tea goes isn't that
something you mean mike francesa whatever is it either the mob guy with the youtube channel now
but not the guy from uncut gems and sports bro no mike michael france ace okay
this was a mobster and now he has a youtube channel okay and he does really fun interviews um yeah
but he interviewed iced tea and i see he said isn't that something i i was supposed to do four
episodes and now i've been on the show for 23 years yeah and michael france ace was like that's
a really long time man like aren't you know and you don't get tired of it and i see he said i'm
i'm black i don't jump off a boat if it's still floating i mean i gotta say i'm not black but i
am the same way yes yes uh like if somebody's giving me money i'll stay until the bitter end yeah
anyway uh our our our picture today suitable for two animals like that myself
i would say suitable for a dear friend there you go there you go um antlers uh strange
title for a film let's just start there we eat i'd say an unquestionable mistake nobody in the
horror community is gonna want to go see a horror movie called antlers it sounds corny it sounds
like is it a reindeer like a christmas thing you know really bad title it's it sounds like it should
yeah it's it this should be a Pixar thing about yeah uh like uh uh about like a reindeer after
root off it's like yeah it's about like vixen and and his uh jealousy of Rudolph or something like that
yeah um but it's called antlers yeah it stars one um uh felicity uh carry rustle carry rustle
and yeah um you know another guy who fluctuates by about 50 pounds with these role jesse plements
jesse plements who to see i called pat and said he is our new philips emor Hoffman yeah he's he's now
just doing roles where he plays a dejected heavy set man very monot like the whole time i was i
i was imagining philips emor Hoffman in this movie and i was like yeah it would be exactly this
performance it would be the same performance i think he would have been a little more alive than this
i'm a big fan of obviously philips emor Hoffman but also jesse plements and i thought this was a
strangely kind of dead doll performance from him personally i was shocked that he did it and look i
guess you know the all you know everything all bets are off with covid right well yeah this was
actually scheduled to be released april 2020 so it's been in the in the vault a long time yeah so i
felt like i was like watching both of them in this and i was like i'm surprised they did this movie
this is a pretty point a to point b script um it's not very deep um no my well sky Cooper you know
is a is a director uh he used to be an actor he did black mass which had a great jesse plements
performance and they probably became friends on that this this guy did black mass he did wow
lazy heart with Jeff bridges you know uh Oscar nominated he did out of the furnace with christian bail
black mass hostels with christian bail and then out of nowhere antlers yes all right so maybe yeah
maybe covid had had an effect on this yeah but i think he he lured them and i think the fact that
Guillermo del Toro was producing the thing probably lured them because i mean he is a genius a visionary
but producing can mean many things and i think a lot of people don't understand that it can mean
you never once set foot on set or have any input on the film at all or it can mean you're
more involved in the director in some cases uh this does not feel like a Guillermo del Toro movie
i mean the the attacks when they come are basically a man holding antlers like you'd see in an old
1950s movie it's like a guy fighting with a pair of antlers that are the creatures mainly off screen
for most of the film well yeah it's a windingo movie yeah the myth of the windingo which is like the
horned beast yes you know the evil spirit from hell represented by a horned uh biped but um and then
they have the Native American shaman who tells them the history of them tells them exactly what's
happening yeah because because he because he would just know at what point do do the Indian characters
just not know this anymore at what point you know hilarious bit in the horror movies they go to like
this this Native American chief and it lives in a cave or something to ask about what's going on
and he's like i don't fucking know i live in a cave like it'd be a great bit and like a scary movie
yeah i mean it'll be like two thousand eighty and they'll still have an old man you'll be like he
was born in two thousand he wouldn't know this yeah and would he really be smoking a peace biped
2021 really yeah sorry i'm having some sort of a gardening issues somebody's can you hear this or not
no i can't hear okay good if i told you this is a movie about a meth dealer who turns into a
reindeer i wouldn't be lying yeah that's true and honestly that's not how i would have thought of
it but yes now that you mentioned it that is the plot of the movie it's a it's an insane story
you know and and i don't know why this many people felt compelled to tell it frankly i got to tell
you i because i think horror is one of those genres that if you are not a diehard fan
it's real it's like action it's very easy to be swayed in the wrong direction it's it's very easy
you know like like i think you're a fan of this movie but i think you'll also understand my point
it's like there's a huge difference between like con air and terminator two you know what i mean
yeah and i'm giving a compliment to terminator two you know i'm not a big fan of the movie but
my point is is like i feel like the average person would see those as exactly the same thing
but no you're like no terminator two is like it's got a commentary and then this happened
in the twist and blah blah that's so much more than just like an action movie and it's super in -depth
mapped out story and blay yes for sure yeah so i think this happens with horror too where like this
movie starts incredibly intriguing i was like wow this is cool i i also give it give us the quick
plot we haven't done that yet you're usually better at that a meth dealer yeah gets a bit by
something they don't show it he gets attacked in his meth lab that's all you know yeah and then his
son is at school and he and then his and carry rustles the teacher she's teaching in her hometown
again she has come home for the first time since she was a child she had fled because her father
was abusive to her in the in her absence her brother became sheriff of the town she moves back
to live with her brother there is some there there's an estrangement there that they are trying to fix
carry rustle has PTSD from her father's treatment she realizes that this kid in her class
is probably suffering from it as well or some sort of abuse she starts to pry deeper into his life
to see if she can help him and we learn that he has his father locked in this room and his and he's
feeding his father dead things like road kill and stuff and you don't really know why and then as
it unfolds you realize the father is slowly morphing into something and so is his little brother for some
reason who's living in there this is where it starts to get convoluted I really didn't understand why
the father was turning and the brother was to but the brother was turning more slowly yeah yeah and
eventually the father turns into a when dingo and the plot is these spirits find a host and they walk
the earth again until somebody kills it and then it jumps into another host as soon as it's killed
so I guess the idea is at the beginning of the movie when you don't when you hear the father get
attacked but you don't see it he defeats this when dingo by the way Joe it's when to go you're adding
another in I'm gonna I'm gonna stick with when they go it's more fun yes good it
the the assumption is this is that he defeated it and it jumped into him yeah and now he's the host
and he's gonna birth this thing from his own body or whatever um that's the basic plot
and then eventually turns into the thing and he tries to attack everybody and they have to fight
it I mean you know it's it's your paint by numbers horror yeah but what I was gonna say is is one of
the things I liked about the movie was first of all the the it's a very intriguing from the start the
the monster is intriguing the idea of it at least the mythology is interesting I love that there's
not a smile in this movie I mean it just I didn't it's like what why does this thing have to be so
relentlessly grim it's called antlers you know like I really expected kind of a tongue and cheek thing
I don't mean I need quips or something but like yeah it's really heavy and it's all like like every
other movie now it's about loss and drama and grief uh it just seems like that's whatever
you put in comedy that seems like that's what everything is about now well that was the big criticism
of this movie was that it's commentary on grief and abuse yeah gets in the way of the movie itself
and again that's why I think as we're talking about like why do people do these movies that aren't that
good I don't think they really get horror and I think like they see like that it's got an intriguing
set of characters and then it's trying to say something and oh those few scenes were scary
and then by the time they're at the end of the script they're not even thinking about they didn't stick
the landing or whatever like they're just like no I want to do this yeah theme theme becomes the whole
thing now it's like they're they're landing not story beats but theme beats and then you wind up with
a very unsatisfying movie the I read you the guys resume it's not to say that you have to have
directed horror to direct a good horror movie by any means but this guy does not know horror that
there's no good scares in it at all there's no there's nothing unsettling that stays with you so it's
not like a lyncher Kronenberg kind of vibe there's no jump scares startles anything that would make it
a commercial horror movie it's really just kind of a somber character drama and once in a while
giant antlers show up and attack somebody you know well antlers on a beast it's not just right but what
you see until the end is like a guy wrestling with antlers I mean this thing must add a pretty low
budget when you do see the thing at the end I thought it was kind of cool and like it doesn't wear
out its welcome per se I couldn't say I hated antlers but it reminded me a little of the nighthouse
which we discussed on this show except I preferred the nighthouse I thought that they that was another
super somber you know grief death obsessed horror movie and I'll say it for me it worked a little
better it was a little scarier I cared more about the people involved and this was just kind of a
slog it's it's about as average as they come you know there's nothing really to recommend and there's
nothing to say I hated but I like this better than nighthouse okay but that's not saying much yeah
right it's weird I don't think this is a bad movie I just don't think it works yeah don't it's hard
to I don't know but I'm feeling that way about every movie I see in the theater right now I'm like
this almost almost good what happened and I'm like I think what happened is they shot three -quarters
of the god damn thing and then a fucking pandemic happened yeah and they couldn't finish this properly
you know so it feels that way I mean for sure they they a lot of movies like you're saying I go to
the theater and I'm like this just feels like they finally were like look guys we got to release something
at this point and you know maybe people are blaming stuff on covid I don't know but if this
was going to be released in April 2020 then it was done by the time covid started so well in theory
right but I mean sometimes they're doing reshoots up into march and whatever you know like so who knows
but I mean I'd imagine if they had to do reshoots with plements he'd have to wear a fat suit I mean he's
the difference between him like now and then is massive wait he's heavier now than back then
no he's in really good shape he's playing a cop and the score says he moved me with caprio and okay
but he he's a guy who one minute will be Phillips who more often and the next will be just like a
thin a thin normal dude wow and the and the part never really calls for it either it's just kind of
I think he's a fluctuator yeah I can relate I can relate I can too I can too yeah somebody said
that to me the other day they go dude I relate to you so much you gain weight the same way I do I was
like yeah I didn't need to hear that thank you thanks bud what did he mean like it just goes on fast
like I like one week you're fat and one week you're not basically it's really really nice yeah
thoughtful anyway folks my hog is pretty much down but no little up there's a little spark in the
hug it's not drooping but you you took the blue chew two minutes ago so it's in there but it's not
really reached your bloodstream yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah on and free advertisement for blue chew
yeah I my my hog is down although you know we've we've definitely talked about much more
egregious horror movies on this podcast I think if you watched it you'd probably have the same
effect kind of like a okay you know you can do worse but you can do better we'll be back
with ghost buster's colon after life Patrick what the Patrick Wallace Twitter and Instagram
and that's it for my plugs go to Joe's sandwich sandwich shop please come to Joey Rose's sandwich shop
to social club located at 174 Rivington Street in New York City open Wednesday through Sunday starting
at 12 p .m. each day uh Joe to Rose's comedy on Instagram and Twitter uh and we'll see you for ghost
busters all right we'll see you in hell