Summer is here, and Bed MDM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer, or check out
our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz, only available at Bed
MDM Casino.
Spin on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 fortunes, Mystery of the Lamp,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand.
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action.
Bet MGM game sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bet MGM dot com for T's and C's, 21 plus to Waiter, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and
West Virginia only.
Games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as non withdrawalable site credit slash bonus bets unless otherwise
provided in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
The football season is full of guarantees, and here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October, if
your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning, or winning money back in fan
cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
Winning hits different here.
Must be 21 -plus, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gampler, offer not available in all states
terms apply, see Fanatic Sportsbook app.
This is a head gum podcast.
That's okay, folks. It's, we'll see you in hell. I'm going to toss to the patty walls for the intro. Hello, everybody. It's Patrick Walsh. It's a Saturday night about 9 .40 pm to give you an idea of how stacked the social calendars of myself and Joderosa are.
Mm -hmm, sitting in his apartment recording a podcast Saturday night Los Angeles. Yeah.
Um, you know, Elton John sang it best Saturday nights all right for potten.
Do you remember that song? Yeah, I also remember a tune called Saturday Night is the
Loneliness Night of the Week by one Mr. Frank Sinatra. Yeah, and I'd say this Saturday ain't so lonely
because I got you, babe, which was said by Sonny and Cher.
I got you, babe. That's right.
Folks, this little walk -down musical memory lane.
This is, we'll see you in hell.
It's a horror movie podcast. We discuss one horror sci -fi movie picture
a week, and it goes off on tangents and screaming matches and things
of that nature.
Without any further fanfare on with the show and on
And who with the Joe that's that was a good one.
Thank you.
If you could see the glass looking his eyes as he says it.
Yeah.
I got nothing on the tech.
And I always look like a madam to sewed.
Thing had come to life and yelled that.
Yeah.
I was up at 6 a .m. today.
Fall asleep last night about three.
The hell we up at six four.
I went to an old -day seminar at the writer's guild of America.
Oh, God.
Why do you do it to yourself?
You work hard of it.
Anybody I know.
And then in your free time, you're like,
I'm doing a paprika juice cleanse.
And I got to go, I got to go to this class
where they teach you how to use periods in a new way.
I'm like, what are you doing?
Just take a day off.
Well, I was told that if you go to this seminar,
It keeps them from like trying to put additional people on your back for the for the production of the show
So I'm working on this pilot. I'm taking notes from you know 25 different people
I don't need another person in the mix. So I went I send them my receipt of having gone
I did fucking learn a lot. It was a great course, but I'll tell you Joe and
You wouldn't last at five minutes with this woman
The guy who gave the guy who spoke was amazing. You know 40 years of credits
that he had amazing stories, he was just perfect.
I learned so much.
And after every single point that he made,
every time he stopped speaking,
every period of a sentence,
the woman in front of me would go,
Oh God, you can't have that.
Mm -hmm, mm -hmm, mm -hmm.
So it was someone still,
she was always something like a black church response.
Yeah, except she was, you know, nowhere near that cool.
Yeah.
And, you know, like, at first...
Well, I can call him out.
I was here, you know, Andrew Orvidal.
No, but I did know Gorvidal very well.
And he's a very funny comedy guy.
He's on those who can't on true TV.
I'm going to shout out that show.
Oh, I like those who can't.
Is he the guy with the beard?
Is he the main guy?
No, he's not the main guy.
Yeah, they're all main guys I think I know all of them and I think any one of them would be offended right now
That I said I didn't know you were talking about they're all main guys. Yeah, they're good good. They're good man
I like all of them. He's in comedy. It's a funny show
I want to give him a shout out cuz we had a great time together days
We just kind of sat together like kids in church and kept looking at each other
Whenever this woman would go, hmm, okay, and people are kind of looking over but nobody really called her out or laughed and then she was also in a riding
partnership. And when she would say, mmm, then her friend, her writing partner, would
turn to her a nod. Like, mm -hmm. We've been there. By the way, for those of you at
home that don't know what W .G .A. means, I just realized, writer's guild of America. Or did
you say that already? I'm pretty sure I said it. I'm sorry. Pat and I also ate a weed
gummy before we started here. Well, it hasn't kicked in. That was maybe five minutes ago.
Mine started to tingle a little bit. They hit me fast and hard. All right. Like my ex -husband.
Oh, uh, so, but wait, hold on, yeah, but why did you get up at six?
It would have started seven.
It started at eight, but I, I just, uh, I'm not getting a lot of sleep, folks.
I, I got a lot riding on me.
I got, I got the budget of my pilot.
And then you start to think like that much money is riding on me.
And it's a lot, it's a lot of pressure.
I will say people every time I see Walsh here, my friend in years,
the, the, the, the, the, the, the zipper of the track check is a little lower, the buttons
are a little lower on the shirt, he's showing more and more chest.
I mean, he is, he is transforming into one of these, it, it's only a matter of time
before he's got a, a gold medallion nestled in that hair and he's sitting in a, in a sauna
with a couple of agents.
Yeah.
And just has one of those phones with the big antenna for no reason, the wireless like it's,
it's a tough life, dude.
Last night I stood on a hotel balcony and I went, oh, am I?
As you looked at the glimmering lights of Hollywood, the glimmering lights of Hollywood that were starting to fade a little for maybe
Because of all the things that I've seen
And then I did a line off some you know, naked 14 -year -old girl
But that was my Friday and I don't need to bring you into that
Well, I'll say it a very different day than you had today.
What did you do?
Well, I went.
I got a haircut this morning.
I'm going tomorrow morning.
I got up.
I walked my dog for about an hour, which was nice.
He was being a real shit, but whatever.
We had a nice walk.
And then I went and got a haircut.
And then I went.
I got a pair of Doc Martens that I've been looking for.
I finally found them.
Very exciting and folks since the last podcast Joe has come out as a proud lesbian woman
And frankly he doesn't need your judgments
He doesn't need it's 2017, you know, yeah, it is get with it
So yeah, I got some Doc Lawrence, which I was excited about then I went to you ready for this sure
Three record stores. Oh to find the new spoon vinyl
No, but not only didn't none of them have it sold out or didn't have it they were all like
Well, what is it? I was like spoon the new spoon. When did it come out? What yesterday? Did you go to amoeba now because I was
I wasn't on that side of town so that still I mean spoon isn't even alternative anymore
They're almost a pop band. Yeah
I got I was getting the feeling that they were saying take you in your main stream
bullshit and get out here
But listen to it and it's entirety us today and I really liked it. It's not as
Instantly catchy as every other album they've ever had, but I liked it. It's a great album
It's impressive and I just was at South by Southwest and on my plane ride down there on Saturday
Who did I see five rows up for me in an aisle seat, but one Brit Daniel? Hello guys still in coach in the aisle seats
Didn't even have a window look. I don't usually have names to drop but
But about five years ago, me and my dear friend Ian Friedman went to the Matador Records
20th anniversary show at the Palms Casino in Las Vegas, Nevada.
Pavement.
This was before they were like fully re - and it was like their first show.
Tom Sharpling of the best show hosted one of my favorite comedy people of all time.
It was amazing.
It was Yolatango.
It was Pavement.
It was Spoon.
It was like all your favorites.
It was an amazing show.
Guyed it by Voices.
A very drunk guy to buy, boys.
Cat power.
Cat power perform.
Yes, that's correct.
And I was gambling playing a little blackjack and I saw Brit Daniels walk by with a girlfriend
folks and I'm going to give them the benefit of the doubt and say she was of age.
But holy cow, did she look young?
And you know what, Brit, more power to you, if that's what you like and as long as she, you
know, passes muster at the old, uh, law office.
Paid on mustard.
I never heard that term.
What's that mean?
It's an old, uh, hillbilly term passes muster means like good enough.
Okay.
All right.
But yeah, I mean, she looked like four, you know, and they were pretty hot and heavy.
It was very uncomfortable.
That I'm sure she was of age.
She's a, he's a public figure.
He wouldn't go out with a four year old, but still that would explain the, that track, uh,
track seven on the new album that's just called if there's grass on the field which
I have to seize play ball Joe what is your favorite spoon song well song I go back
and forth my favorite spoon album is gimme fiction oh it's a fantastic I think that's
the that's really their their their peak that beast and dragon adore when that song kicks in
I'm just like which one of y 'all bitches wants to fuck yeah that's it you know that one gets
It's me in the heart.
I may be lying to you.
The answer is none of us.
But thanks.
Lines in the suit maybe is my probably my favorite
or my first time volume three is when I like quite a bit,
which is a single that wasn't on any album.
Sure.
I really love Jonathan Fisk.
Jonathan Fisk is probably mine.
It's a great song.
And my other and one of the most mode,
I used to wake up to it every morning
and it powered me through like a rough year of my life
is got nothing.
That's a great one.
Got nothing to lose. Yeah, but darkness and shadows. Yeah, that's a great one too. Well he was on my plane
And I was down at the South by Southwest festival did a bunch of shows. Okay. How'd they go? They all went very well
I had a really nice time. Did my friend J. Oakerson's show what your fucking deal, which is his seesaw show
We did a live version. We we had an absolute blast Eddie Pepitone
Can I quit and do a quick pause?
Yeah, I would say has made me laugh harder than anyone else in the world.
Well, I really do believe that.
This is the one South by story I will tell you then.
All right, and I'm not going to take up too much time, but so what's your fucking deal
is that all crowd work show you have to come out and do crowd work.
So it's, it's Jay's the host, I'm doing the crowd mic, which means I'm in the audience
the whole time with a microphone. Sean Patton comes out, kills. Mike Lawrence comes
out, kills. Bonnie McFarrowin comes out, kills. Eddie Peppaton comes out, kills. And
he goes, he opens with these other comics, this shit they do. Where do you work? Where do
you live? It's bullshit. I want to know your dreams, right? So he starts screaming at the
audience to tell you their dreams yeah so then he goes miss what's your dream I
bring the mic over to the lady she goes you know I want to be a veterinary and
he goes no god damn it I don't mean you're fucking goals what did you dream last night
right hmm so we start doing this thing with audience members where they're gonna
tell him what they dreamt or a reoccurring dream they have and he's gonna
interpret it as quote as he put it the worst therapist of all time all right and
quote. So he'd call on somebody. I'd go over to them, give them the mic. They would go. I have this
reoccurring dream where I'm trapped in my basement. I see my dad through the seller window. I can't get
to him. I need to get to him. I don't know why and all of a sudden they're putting him in a bodybag.
What does that mean? And then Eddie would go, that's a great dream. Okay. Okay. You know what I think
it means. And first of all, let me say this, you're an ugly piece of shit. But the dream
it means your father never loved you. And he would do that over and over. That's a great
dream. Let me get before I interpret it. Let me say this. I hope a cinder block kills your entire
fucking family. I'm sorry about that. Yeah. It's a beautiful dream. It was we were. Everybody
was crying laughing. It was one of the funniest things I ever saw.
So I am a very difficult hard laugh. It almost never happens.
Our true tears in my eyes laughing, but I have a couple times a year where I'm on another
plain laughing. And all of those times have involved Eddie Pepchum. When I was in London, I went
to London by myself for a full week. And I was having fun. I went into casino and I had had
like nothing to drink.
And they threw me out for being drunk.
Like they wouldn't let me in.
They're like, you're too drunk, love.
You're too drunk, mate.
Love.
I was like, it was real condescending.
And I was like, no, no, no, I haven't had anything to drink.
I just saw a play.
I'm completely sober.
They're like, love, brother, brother, mate.
You're drunk.
You're big and knuckered.
You're slagged, mate.
They were, that was their wish and get out of here,
American because some snatch shits about to go down yeah and I was so infuriated because I love
gambling and I went out and then to prove him wrong I got real drunk sure and I'm walking along
and this was only like eight o 'clock and I see this giant marquee and in London of all places
Eddie Pepitone has treated like a god I love it because every time I see him here he's like the fourth
guy on a bill and like the basement of a you know seafood shop or something but he's got this giant
Martin Markey is, you know, not necessarily commercial face.
Right.
And I'm like, holy shit.
I go, how much are tickets for Eddie Peppetown?
She's like, well, I got one near the back for 20 bucks.
She's like, but otherwise it sold out.
I was like, give me that ticket.
I went in.
I had one of the best nights of my life.
I mean, he came out and he was just talking shit on America.
So, of course, it killed doubly hard in Britain.
Right.
But my lord, I mean, I couldn't breathe for part of it.
He's a great guy.
I saw him we're in the same hotel and I saw him I was with Bonnie McFarlane
Who's a dear friend in hilarious?
I saw and we both saw him right before he was leaving he was leaving a day before we had to leave and
He just kept saying over and over we saw him in the lobby and he just kept going. I'm gonna take a dip before I leave
That's a nice pool. I'm gonna you guys getting coffee. I'm not gonna go. I'm gonna stay here and take a quick dip
What did he know he was being funnier was he's just being himself. Yeah, he wasn't he was okay
He had this shit eating grand as he kept saying it. Yeah, it was the oddest joke, but it was very funny
I got a great man. I just wrapped up
Six years on two bro girls. That's why I have a house. You know, it's it was it was a wild fun ride
Think what you will about the show any pepeton played two roles on that show one was a hoarder
and his mom was like buried somewhere in his house.
And his commitment to this performance,
you couldn't see him, you could just hear him.
But like, even though the audience didn't necessarily
love it, it wasn't necessarily a network sensibility.
But man, you could throw him any line
and he delivered it with such like gusto and passion.
And you know, I mean, this whole act
is shitting on things like two broke girls.
Yeah.
But my God was he funny and sold it
And we brought him back as a underground in the subway suit salesman.
He was selling like, he was like, this is a, you know, this is a mustard color.
Like, you know, all different, kind of like Steve Harvey style suits that he was
selling under the subway.
And my God was he funny all over again.
Like he just, he's a man who gives it is all every time.
If he comes to your town, go see him do stand up.
He's the best.
And I, I've never met him.
We're not getting paid for this.
If you like comedy, check him out.
I give you I'm gonna give you four plugs right now for people you need to see if you haven't seen them
Do any peppetone. Yeah, Todd glass show sure Robinson and Andy Kinler do not waste your time
Kinler. Donnie McFarland. That's five. Go see those people if you've never seen them
You're really missing out. These are wonderful wonderful comedians and
There's some of the best out there. I will say you can catch Todd glass on a night where he smokes too much weed
I've done that a couple times
But I still find that when he's on I love him and Andy Kinnler has one of my favorite jokes of all time
It's a little inside baseball
But it's a hey no any of you subscribe to a variety magazine y 'all get this magazine variety or as I call it
Everyone you came up with doing better than you details inside
He sent me one of the best insults I've ever received on Twitter. Yeah
I like when you guys interact on Twitter.
Yeah, he wrote, uh, he wrote, hey, Jotaro,
so listening to your WTF episode,
does anything have to be funny with you?
All right, let's get to Pat's movie rundown folks, you know, I, I wish I had, uh,
parceled it out a little bit more because I used to rattle off 10 movies and I haven't
seen in a full week. I have not seen one movie, one television show, listen to one podcast,
done anything that would contribute to this column in any sort of meaningful way.
When you walked in, didn't you tell me you just saw some, wait, didn't you, are the wrong?
Well, Kong for tonight. Oh, you didn't watch the room. You just said you just got the DVD
or something. Yeah, I ran in the room because I've never seen it. And I always thought I was
was waiting for the opportune like midnight movie screening and it never came.
When I first moved L .A., you couldn't get into them, it would be like Paul Rudd waiting
in line and you couldn't get in and I just never saw it.
But now it's at my house and I can't wait to watch.
A friend of mine, a dear friend of mine, a man Harris went to college with Justin Long and
I do not know Justin Long but I went to see the room with Anne and a midnight thing in New
Big fan, I dragged the hell on all these other things and Tusk, Joe.
And Tusk wasn't out yet.
All right, Tusk was not out yet.
I just like to occasionally, so you know who decide with remind you that Joe's favorite
movie of its year was Tusk.
I did try to get through blimpy ho, what the fuck was that called?
Oh, yoga hosers.
I couldn't get through it.
I didn't see that.
See, I thought you were going to love yoga.
It was rough stuff.
Was it strictly a comedy?
It's Johnny Depp's daughter and Kevin Smith's daughter in a buddy movie.
It's a comedy and it's rough stuff, but I did love to ask.
But anyway, I saw, so he came and we snuck 40s into the movie theater
and he was in need of alcohol.
I didn't have any with him.
So I shared a 40 ounce with Justin Wong.
And then I remember he said he was like,
he was very excited because he had seen it many times.
Brian and he was like you've never seen it. Okay, dude, my favorite part, there's gonna be this part
Where the guy is to move a dresser and everybody's gonna go one, two, three, cock sucker. I think that's what it was
Okay, or one, two, three, fuck it or something like that and I mean this is in the 11th hour of the film that this part happened
So we're waiting the whole time and the part came up and he's like here comes here comes here comes here comes and he yells it one, two, three
Fuck it.
Nobody else yelled it.
And he turned to me and he went, nobody did it.
And he looked, he looked like very disappointed and sad.
But he did it.
He did it because he was like,
and it was clearly a thing where he was like,
this is usually a thing everybody does.
But this time everybody didn't do it.
And I felt bad for him, but he was a real nice guy.
I played poker with him once he was a delightful gentleman.
Yeah.
My dad, when I was about 10 years old,
was like, hey, up at the dollar show
where I had to see all my movies,
like six months after they came out,
went to the dollar show.
My dad was like midnight,
they're showing Rocky Horror Picture Show.
When me and your mom were dating,
this was the big thing, but we never went to see it.
You and I should go.
That's an odd movie to see with your dad.
So he takes me up midnight,
and I'm like, I mean, I could not have been more excited,
just to even be out of the house at midnight.
We went to White Castle.
Right, my dad's favorite.
And we went up there and I, which reminds me, when my dad and I saw Wayne's world also at the
dollar show, keep in mind there was nothing I wanted to see more and I still had to wait
six months to see it at the dollar show.
And it starts and when they're panning down the Chicago landmarks when they pan to white
castle, my dad who looking back now was like my age that I am now, which is very disturbing.
Sure.
When white castle hit, my dad who also looking back was probably wasted even though he claimed
to not be drinking at this time. He jumped to his feet, pumped his fists, and went,
woo! Because that's how much he loved white stories, getting dark. And the entire theater
cheered for my father. Well, that's cool. There you go. But anyway, sort of the opposite
of the Justin Long area. We go to this Rocky Horror picture show, and the thing starts
an out on the stage comes a man who tucked into a pair of see -through women's panties is a pretty
substantial cock folded up and visible in see -through panties. Now we're talking. And my dad grips my
arm so hard and lifted me up and out of my seat and we left the theater. And that was that. And can I tell
you folks, he tried to get a refund at the dollar show, but you were going to say he
tried to hook up with you. He was all worked up. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. It's a bad joke.
Casually mentioned my dad molested me at a screening. No, but I've never seen the room.
I always wanted that perfect midnight movie experience. And it never presented itself. So
I'm going to just watch it at home by myself. I was hoping you and I could do it tonight,
but you've already seen it. I've already seen it and we didn't live up to its name.
Yeah, it's well not by yourself. It won't yeah, probably you're gonna watch it. You're gonna go this is absurd
This is sorry. I can't call Justin long up Joe. I don't know why you got to take a shot at me
At least Justin long let me stay and watch the movie didn't yank me out because they some guy showed his wing
My dad was in the right for me to never happen to a grown man's cock at age tell you were you were old enough
You needed to learn maybe
No, look, here's the problem with something like the room these days.
There are so many bad, you know, exploitation movies of all genres and bad YouTube videos
and bad fail videos and all these things that are completely accessible online.
You're going to watch it and you're going to go, yeah, this is like a terrible movie that
a crazy guy made.
And when I saw it, it was before you could access all that stuff so easily.
So when you saw it, it was like, how the fuck did this get done?
Right.
Now, the schmuck that lives next door to you, or whatever, could make that on his iPhone.
And you'd be like, oh yeah, it sucks.
Of course it does.
Yeah, I mean, the older I get, when I was a kid, or even in my teens or college, we would
rent like a bad movie and watch it and like laugh hysterically and ship but
in this day and age so much of what is out there is so bad it's hard to really
feel anything and that's really the problem with the world in general you don't
feel anything about anything and everything kind of blurs in at sort of a hazy
gray neither black nor white and the world keeps pushing in on you until you you
want to scream. Well, she's coming in heavy tonight, man. Jesus, God, am I wrong, folks?
I know you're at a seminar all day, you know, for how to cut 10 % of your budget down
or whatever the hell the fucking thing was. But look, I got to tell you, and I'm not going
to get into it. I, uh, I think a big part of it is waking up in the morning and just reading
the news. And a way I never did before. It's horrible. It's the saddest time certainly of my
life and perhaps you know I mean obviously you know it's not comparing with the Holocaust or
something but if you're looking at the history of the world history of America I can imagine it's
been that much worse than this and everyone is feeling very uninspired and very miserable and it
bleeds into your life whether you want it to or not it sucks right now this is just our city it's
been much worse than this the slaughtering of the Indian of course of course slavery Holocaust
these are all yeah look folks go back to medieval times you got people you know
dying because they got a limp they didn't play you know this is this you know
this is this time sucks but you know yeah I mean really I think that this
this presidency is harder on those who are bullied like myself because it's just
it's showing you that when I moved out to LA I was like wow these like nerds and
like beautiful, wonderful wives and girlfriends
and like they're successful and they're happy
and they're making the things they want to make.
And this is kind of like just a big swing
in the other direction.
We're like just being a douchebag asshole
can make you the most powerful man in the world.
Right.
And it's hard.
I gotta admit, it's hard every day
that this man is in power,
but we're not a political podcast.
You know, Pat, I've said it too many times.
It's hard out here for a pim.
It is.
And you know, that was a high point in America when that song won best song at the academy wars
I remember seeing Anthony Anderson who has been very nice to me over the years as I've met him
And we've done some stand -ups shows together
But I remember seeing him in a talk show I was on Jimmy Kimmel and he said in the end when that was nominated and he was in that movie
He said he said Jimmy watch this man watch this man watch watch. I'm gonna sing the song from hustle and flow
Everybody's gonna sing with me. Don't nobody know the music from
and he named like two other movies that year,
and then the third one he goes,
don't know him and you know music from Star Wars.
It's like, no Anthony, everybody knows the music
from Star Wars.
But anyway, let's get to our movie of the week.
I thought you were gonna side with Anthony,
and somebody just kind of threw him under the bus.
No, I didn't, I, I, I, I, very nice guy.
A movie of the week folks is Kong, Colin,
Skull Island, which at the very least
This was better than a movie I saw a couple of years ago called Kong Skull, colon island,
where Kong Skull went to an island populated by gaping colon's folks.
Yeah, that was a tough one.
Now I saw something also a few years ago, Skong or Ash, excuse me, Kong Skull community and
it was just a gated community that Kong is living in.
It was not very good.
look, I didn't hate that one.
Now, before, now, this is a first, let me say this,
this is a first for our podcast.
I have no idea what Pat Walsh's opinion on this film is
and I don't want you to tell me yet.
All right.
We did not discuss this at all.
I texted in my thoughts while I was sitting in the movie.
But I do not know Pat Walsh's thoughts yet.
I'm excited to hear them.
Let's give the synopsis and then we'll get into the discussion.
You give the synopsis, Joe. Go ahead.
Look, it's a Kong movie in the sense that King Kong is in it.
It is not a traditional Kong movie in the sense
that it does not feature him falling in love
with a tiny blonde woman for no apparent reason,
and then scaling a building to protect her
as military planes are shooting him incessantly.
This movie is a straight -up monster movie.
John Goodman plays the sort of, and I can't remember the guy's name in the original,
but that's the guy Jack Black played in the Peter Jackson remake.
He plays sort of that role, but he doesn't want to go out there for the sake of his own
movie or glory.
He wants to go out there to prove that monsters exist, and this is a threat.
in the same way that George W. Bush possibly was, you know, saying we need to go
into the Middle East to find them weapons of mass destruction. It's that same
kind of motivation. And they go to the island and it's a rag -tag bunch of people.
It's John Goodman and his associate who the actor's name is escaping me but he's
played by the guy that plays Dr. Dre in straight out of Compton. There's some
military people there, one of them being the guy that played easy, E and straight out of Compton.
Samuel Al Jackson is the military leader. Tom Hiddelsen is a tracker who's going to kind of show
them the ropes of surviving the wilderness, who is ready for anything they might face, except
of course the surprise of a giant monkey and pre -large and pre -large is there as a war photographer.
for. Yes. Yes. And Corey Hawkins is the guy who played Dr. Dre. Yeah. So I got to say
that's basically the whole movie. I mean, they don't leave the island. They get there
and it's monster shit. And that's it. I don't know that I've ever seen a more stacked cast
in service of something this stupid. And there's my opinion. But I mean, when John Goodman and
his partner go to like get the grant to go and explore for Kong or whatever and like
maybe they'll find the cure for cancer or their boss who comes out and says two lines
is Richard Jenkins.
Yes.
One of my favorite actors of all time.
Oscar nominee.
An Oscar nominee not long ago and he comes out and he's like, you guys really want to
wind me up.
Like he has nothing to do.
Yeah, and
Goodman is
Kind of in it. He disappears for a full hour
Live storylines going on in this movie
Samuel Jackson comes in and like is delivering these one liners that like
We're trying to get cheers, but they were so fucking stupid like at one point
He's like I'm about to show Kong that man is the true ruler
no king king come on yeah obviously the next more stuff but I'm like am I
supposed to cheer for man is that is that what I was supposed to do now it's a
it's a it's a real and I endless and I have a certain hesitation about saying
this because two weeks ago I did Doug Doug loves movies with friend Doug Benson
and I ate a great time and one of the guests on it was Jordan what's his name
who directed the movie. Now, clearly, he must have some ties to comedy because everyone
I know in comedy posted that they were at the Kong premiere and loved it.
I never knew Jordan until that night. He was a nice guy. He was excited about the movie.
Uh, I don't want to be one of those people that is nice to somebody and then says bad things.
So I'm not saying anything bad about Jordan. You couldn't say anything bad about the movie
visually. No, visually he did a great job. I mean, I don't think he wrote the fucking script.
That was the issue. But God damn it, the movie stung. It really, it was a lot of, now guys,
This is going to be loaded with spoilers
So not real what what are you really spoiling with Kong school Island? Well, probably not but animals fighting each other
I'm gonna speak freely about everything I hated about this movie all right. Let's start with the opening line
Let's start with the opening line go on the opening line a
cab pulls up
After the credit sequence a cab pulls up in front of the you know, one of those
domed buildings in Washington.
I know what you're gonna say.
And it kind of pushes in on John Goodman
who's the passenger in the cab and he just goes,
there will never be a crazier time in Washington.
Right there, you're like, okay, that's terrible.
That's terrible.
It's so on the God damn knows, look,
and you know I'm a defender of the prequels,
but it's like the partner avenger, the Sith,
where he gets elected, where Palpatine gets elected emperor
and everybody cheers and Natalie Porton goes,
so this is how freedom dies with thunderous applause.
Like, you know, at the tail end of the Bush administration
they don't be, come on, man, it's, that's right.
It's too on the goddamn nose, stop it.
So that line right there, I was like,
we might be in trouble, but Jordan did a lot of really
nice visual stuff so I was hanging in there.
I was a fingers crossed. I was hoping it was a look almost every scene kind of
Reinvents itself in a very cool new visual way that you definitely don't see in
Your average blockbuster he did this any movie called the Kings of Summer that was
Pretty fun and to give them the reins of this thing is kind of crazy but he did do
It a really good job with just a terrible fucking script now here's another
other problem I have with the movie. Go on. Every scene, every scene. Folks, I'm
talking every scene starts with not just the 60s, 60s classic rock song, but the most
cliché. So every I will say, you know, who did, who did that first and did it
worst is your favorite film, Suicide Squad. That movie, every time they introduced a character,
oh, this character looks like the devil. Let's play sympathy for the devil.
In its bad. I know. It was embarrassing. I know. It's bad. But this did pretty much the exact
sample. Hook it even further in this. They didn't take it further, but they did the same thing.
Well, they do take it further. Here's why. Because in Suicide Squad they just do it for the first half
hour to introduce characters. In this, they did do the whole goddamn movie. And by the time you're at
like hour 40 and whatever through the jungle by credence comes on.
It runs through the jungle.
Can I just tell you something right now, movie makers of the world, never put a
credence song in a movie ever again.
It's done.
Credence is great.
They're a wonderful band.
I love listening to them.
Never put a credence song in a movie ever less.
Now, let me throw this at you.
When I heard run through the jungle, I'm like, you don't get to do that because
because that's the Big Lebowski song.
And it's also the Dustle Dawn song.
I mean, they, whenever I see that in a movie
when they're like, oh, now we're gonna use,
okay, so like, I know you haven't seen
the end of the sopranos,
but they close with don't stop believing.
It has been used a thousand times since,
but the power of it that first time almost blew me away.
So then when you see it used in like Glee
and et cetera and et cetera,
it's like everyone associates it with this one thing.
Why are you trying to,
Why not have your own new moment?
Well, that's what I've never understood.
I do have a theory, it's not even really a theory,
it's probably valid.
I would think that there's probably a licensing thing
and a studio says, here are the songs that you can use
that aren't gonna cost us an arm in a fucking leg.
And I'm assuming Credence, run through the jungle
is one of them.
I don't think it's cheaper, I don't think it's cheaper
than most.
I think they are trying to recapture.
Well, it's also in a jungle the movie,
Yeah, they're trying to recapture the feeling that previous not so not only is the song being used for an nostalgia
But it's using nostalgia for another movie that it was used in by the way
Run through the jungle is not in
Fear and loathing. I didn't think so. It's in it's industrial dawn. It's in the big about white
Oh, no, I'm sorry white rabbit is in fear and loathing, which is also in this movie. No white rabbit is in the game
No, white rabbit is also in fear and loathing when he's in the bathtub
I want you to say it was in from dust till dawn. No, no, no, I said
I said run through the jungles in dust all done that maybe true credence
It's the opening thing like when they're driving in the car
In fear and loathing its white rabbit, which is also in this movie and used I would say the best in the game with Michael Douglas
I don't I don't remember where it is in the game. I just remember in that bathtub scene
It's someone who's got like his room is black lit with all these like people fuck them of them, but here's the thing now
Now here's would bother me a bit more than just the cliche usage of music to set a tone or
Or send a certain message because the lyrics sort of correlate with the movie
What bothered me more than that was it's not that kind of movie no one of the great uses of music
ever in a film and and the name the songs escaping me at the moment I
apologize because the gummy is setting in at this point is in predator yeah
they're playing that 50 song on the plane I can't remember what it is right
I don't even but they're playing with that's the only time in that movie you
hear that song right and it adds such a weird interesting energy to that
sequence. And they're all on the plane in that great red lighting. And Jesse Ventura is
insulting everybody. And he spits. You mean Jesse the body venture. I've got a lot of
favorite. Sorry to confuse you. Okay. But you know, when he spits the back on the guy
shoe, Shane Black is in that scene who's directing the new predator. But it's such a good use
So it's like an evil dead one how the closing credits to the movie are this old 50s song. Yeah, but there's none of that in the rest of the movie
When you use it sparingly in a film like that. It's so great in this film. It's like this is not a sick
This isn't far as gump. This isn't a movie about the times
It's a movie about monsters in a fucking jungle stop playing
These like psychedelic hits every three minutes. It doesn't make sense to me
Well usually if you use them if you're using them that desperately i .e. suicide squad
It's because you're like the script doesn't work. We're getting real desperate
We got to like try to make you think that you're having fun here
but
To me the most egregious use of music in this was when
Kong first arrives and we hear
Let me see that Kong
That Kong Kong Kong Kong, right?
you're an asshole I mean and to bring Will Smith out of retirement to to
perform it Will Smith number one isn't in retirement number two didn't
sing the thong song Cisco I know Cisco sang the thong song what is that the
Kong song I was trying to subtly dig at Will Smith who might as well be in
retirement because ever movie he makes these days sucks I like Will Smith and I
I think he'll come back but it's gonna be a ways away and there's a good
Dead shot folks. They didn't do that Kong Kong Kong Kong Kong and King Kong. But I would have
respected it more if they had the comedy attempts in this film when John C. Riley shows up. And I
love John C. Riley and there's another man I played poker with. He's a delightful fucking man.
He was enjoyable, but it went a little too far in places. He's doing, it's like step brothers
deleted scenes in the middle of Kong. Yeah, I know. I know. I never seen King Kong. I don't know what
you thought of the the Peter Jackson King Kong. I liked it. I thought it was okay, but
the monsters were way cooler and that was 15 years ago. This CGI wise looked no better.
I'd say even it looked a bit worse. Nothing had advanced. And I, you know, somebody said
to me, we were talking about the movie and they said, well, John C. Riley was really the centerpiece
of the film, whereas, oh yeah, it's a given the post -credits sequence. Whereas Kong should
a bit and that's what I should I go. Oh, you didn't think the King Kong movie would
end with John C. Riley eating a hot dog. This is the last shot of the movie. It is. And
he was enjoyable. Well, Kong, I mean, Kong looked like he was maybe ten feet taller than
me in this movie. He wasn't scary. He wasn't funny. He wasn't interesting. I've never seen
a King Kong presented in a more boring fashion. Every other monster and they weren't great.
One was just like an ugly bird was like another monster. I want to talk about the monsters, but go ahead
They were all sort of more interesting than King Kong, and they weren't even great
They all were just kind of boring generic. I mean, I fell asleep at one point during during Kong
I will tell you this cold and school island. I almost walked out
I didn't but I stayed for the sake of the podcast because I really got a talking to
By Pat when I walked out of Medea's a boo Halloween whatever the fuck it was called
uh... but
who colon
medea
a school island halloween christmas but i will tell you this uh... the
monsters this was a great and i saw this movie with our dear friend karen
co -gareff of my favorite murder fame
here in los angeles yes
to well tell you this if you two ever do some of that don't invite me again we're
working we went we went we went to a to an early afternoon film on a weekday
i'm having lunch with karen on a nice time we had a lot of fun
but i said to her she enjoyed
She actually gave it a little more, a little more slack than I gave it.
I, she was like, I enjoyed the visual.
She's like, it was fun watching like the crazy sequences.
But she did say something really funny
and then I'll tell you the monster thing.
That sequence where they're in like that smoky field
and like the ground keeps lighting on fire.
I turned her and I go, did I miss something?
why does the ground keep catching on fire and very dead page just goes it's just a bad place
it's just not a good place to be she's right so uh but you know it's uh but what bother
I said her after the film I go they did the Jim Henson trick too many times she goes what do you mean
I go too many times it was like somebody was like sitting on like a log and then all of a sudden would
turn into a monster yeah it was like it was like look look at the wonderment of this place
It's just kind of dumb.
Like I don't care, it's too much.
Like I just, I don't know.
I just wasn't that interested.
And I will say this also when it comes to monsters.
In a day and age, and by day and age,
I mean the last 30, 40 years where we have Freddie Kruger,
a burned face man with razor blade fingers
who haunts you and murders you in your dreams.
Jason Voorhees, a zombie who has crawled out of the grave
to avenge his death.
Michael Myers, an unstoppable psychopathic serial killer,
the centabytes demons from hell
that you summoned with a box that ripped you apart
with chains, monkeys just not that scary anymore.
No, I couldn't agree more.
It's just not that scary anymore.
And if you're gonna do this again
and you're gonna reboot it like twice in my lifetime,
you gotta give them a little more personality
than we saw here.
And, you know, who did it better twice is planning of the apes and beyond or whatever, you know, the remakes.
Both of those found really cool new interesting ways to bring monkeys to us as a threat.
This was just kind of not there.
And the cast folks, when I saw the credits rolling, Tom Hiddleston was in that lead.
Tom Hiddleston was the lead of this fucking movie.
Has anyone ever, have you ever seen a lead of a movie make less of an impression
than Tom Hiddleston in this movie.
No, no, he was, and I even said, I said,
I was saying the other night, the way they bring him in,
they introduced Tom Hiddleston into the story
as like this mercenary type guy.
They find him, I mean, how cliche is this?
They find him, you know, in a pool room and Bangkok.
You know, when he gets into a scuffle with some,
with some surly barb members and like throws darts at them and you know like, you know
It's like such a typical like ripoff of Raiders of the Lost Ark, right?
and
But he comes in and he's like let me tell you what will kill you
The Nats the ain't that he's like, you know, he goes and that's just the shit you can see you're like
This guy's like, this guy's like,
this guy's like, this guy's like, this guy's like,
this guy's like, this guy's like, this guy's like, this guy's like,
it. Hey, I'll tell you this. I love Braylon. She's a strong actress. And she's bringing
a lot to the table, boner -wise. I will tell you this, folks. She looked great. Every time
she came on screen, there were some monsters on Skull Island in my pants. If you know what
I mean, yeah, yeah, she's she's hot. But there were too many sequences where I was saying
to do hard work to, like, get them out of this situation.
And it would cut to pre -locks and like cranking something and she would just go, and it just,
it looked fake, it looked ridiculous, it was, yeah, I mean, the whole cast, and again,
I talked about this when we talked about Dr. Strange.
So when I drive home from Burbank at the end of the day, they always do a new giant billboard
And you know that's a big movie whatever buys this giant spot for the billboard in Los Angeles
There's another spot like that on sunset. We're like that's the movie that's gonna be huge if they buy this spot and
When I saw the doctor strange billboard and it said
Benedict Cumberbatch
Till the Swinton
Victor Hong
All above the line. I was like wait a minute. What's going on here? Right this time out
when I'm seeing John Goodman, Samuel L. Jackson,
Brie Larson,
what's the gentleman's name?
John Ortiz.
John Ortiz, look, I'm all,
all for a diversity in movies and television.
John Ortiz is a fantastic actor.
I love John Ortiz.
John Ortiz has perhaps three lines in this movie,
and he has given an above -line credit,
it. And when you're able to be on the other side of that gross Hollywood line and see that
they are simply putting John Ortiz above the line so that they can attract the Hispanic
community. John Ortiz doesn't say anything in the movie. He has maybe three lines. It's
disgusting.
I turned to, I know who you're talking about. I turned to Karen. He's above the line. 20 minutes
in the movie, I turned to Karen and dead serious. I said, is that Fred Armisson? I thought it
who's also that is he's a he's a great actress in this is that is that a
Spanish name for armistice armistice I'm sure is at least someone Hispanic so
they could have Fred armistice in there I I love John Ortiz I really do I'm
just like when you're going to start throwing him up there with all your your
giant names and giving him absolutely nothing to do it just smacks of the
disgusting Hollywood quality of like we got diversity huh but you're doing it
For the absolute wrong reasons you're simply inserting a Hispanic person into the movie giving him nothing of interest to do
And then exploiting his name to try to bring in the large Hispanic population of Los Angeles by putting him above the line
So if there are Hispanic Gen Ortiz fans, and I'm guarantee there are who go to see this movie and see
Someone of their people
Represented as a hero they instead get to see a guy who's like
like doing absolutely nothing.
Yeah, I agree.
It's disgusting.
I agree.
You're just trying to use the person.
It's gross.
Fox. I mean, the one part that was cool, I will see this. Go ahead. I just did a, I just did a
interview thing where they said, what's the last movie you saw on the theater? I said,
Kong Skull Island. I said, but I won't tell you my favorite part because it's a spoiler,
but I'll tell it now. My favorite part in the movie, the part that did actually get me excited,
was at the end, the credit scene when they come in, they say, Kong is just the beginning,
and they show the slides of Godzilla and Moth around all that.
Wait, is that after the credits?
Yeah, it was at the very end.
Oh, I left during John C. Riley eating a hot dog.
No, the post -credit scene is Tom Hiddleston
and so they're gonna keep doing this.
Well, they're building towards Congress as Godzilla.
So as Tom Hiddleston and Brie Larson in a interrogation room
with one of those two -way glass things,
and he's yelling at the glass like,
You got to let us out of here. We won't talk. Skull Island didn't exist. And then all of a sudden
The the shred of the Compton guy comes in and
And he says
Hey, haha, it's us that have you here. And he's like oh, thank God
We thought it was the government and the and then that guy goes welcome to our such and such facility that they kept referring to throughout the movie and he goes
I know you remember Skull Island good because that's just the beginning look at this and they show this footage
of, he rolls his black and white reel of film, and it shows these hieroglyphics and caves
that were from the Godzilla remake of Godzilla, Mothra, something else, and he showed clips
from, oh, from the, Cranston Godzilla.
Yeah.
Not the Broadway Godzilla.
So they're building up too.
So the next movie is Godzilla.
Is that Godzilla part of this movie's universe?
Yes.
Because that Godzilla sucked dick too.
No, that was bad.
And that guy directed Rogue One, which I thought he did a fantastic job.
So again, not the director or the script, I think, but I know Godzilla, I fell asleep
during both of these movies and that never happened.
The next movie is I think Godzilla, King of all monsters, where it's going to be Godzilla
versus Mothra and I'm forgetting the name of that monster.
But do you really care?
And then it'll be Kong and Godzilla.
Like if you don't care about humans fighting these monsters, do you really care about the
Monsters fighting each other.
I do like Godzilla.
There did a kid I can't speak.
I thought that guy, I thought that Godzilla Remake sucked.
It didn't suck as bad as the Broderick one, but it sucked.
But I do like Godzilla because to me Godzilla is a true monster.
He is like a sort of a mutated lizard
where it's kind, it's literally just a giant ape.
Yeah.
Okay, it walks on two legs.
I don't believe it doesn't look that different
Neither of them can talk or do anything. Why would you want to watch them fight? What is the appeal?
Who are you rooting for? That's why I don't understand unless you're five who gives a shit. I know
Yeah, you're right. Speaking of enclosing real quick recap. Do you think war for the planet of the if she's gonna be good?
That's the third of the series. Yeah, it's a new one with Woody Harrelson. Look, I'm not gonna say I'm excited about it
However, those last two movies that kind of went against my will and thought they were both excellent
So I see no reason to think there won't be good didn't like rise loved dawn loved dawn of the plan of the apes
This new one I'm excited rise and dawn were one and two dawn's the second one. Okay, all right
Excited for this one, although I think it's terrible in the trailer
where Woody Harrelson goes.
And if we don't succeed, it will be a planet of apes.
That's ridiculous.
But we'll see.
We'll see.
Paddy, what do you got?
Any personal plugs?
You know what I want to have them say?
Yeah.
What do you want this to be?
The United apes of America?
Yeah.
It sounds to me like you've gone bananas.
No, Fox, I have nothing to plug. I'm barely awake.
You know, again, I'm at the Patrick Walsh Twitter Instagram.
I love you guys. I love the comments. We love them.
We're on head gum now, which I forgot to mention at the beginning.
And you know, thanks guys. I mean, again, this week I got stopped.
I got stopped right outside your door which I forgot to mention to you Joe by a fan of the podcast. It's cool
I'm glad that we're catching on and it means a lot. Thank you very much
Thank you all for your support
I'll be in Melbourne for the festival of the comedy festival in April for a few weeks if you live in Australia come out to that
Otherwise here's all I'm plugging can you guys please go give and give my album I five albums up on iTunes
Can you give them an Amazon can you give them some five star reviews if you like them because the trolls have brought the ratings down so much
Over the years, and I'm trying to rectify that if you could do that I'd appreciate it. I love you at Joderos Accomedy on Twitter and
Instagram we'll be back next Monday with a new episode
I don't know what it'll be up, but probably a classic. We've done three. Yeah, I think I think the next one is gonna be the neon demon because bizarrely
Joe and I very much agreed on both get out and Kong. Logan, we differed, but not to
an extreme degree. Neon Demon, I fucking loved and Joe fucking hated. So that will be
our next choice. I also don't think there's another big movie on the horizon. So if you
haven't seen it, it's free on Amazon Prime. And you know, that's gonna be our next one.
I think that one's gonna get a little more heated in this one. Thank you folks, we're on headgum. Keep those tweets
A common we have a Facebook page. We'll see you when hell that I check that on today. It's fucking awesome
Thanks guys. Thank you. All right, bye