Welcome to we'll see you in how it's the podcast you listen to when you want to hear that sweet
and sour movies. I'm Joe. Yeah. I should have let you start over. That was terrible. I'm Pat Walsh and I'm also appalled at Joe's intro. I'm Peter appalled and married folks.
No one ever made that. Is it even a joke? Like, what if my what if you were a stand up named Peter? Could you call your special Peter comma appalled and married? That's a cool title and married.
It should be. Peter would have to be married. But yeah, yeah. Is that what you're saying? Are you saying Mary Peter comma appalled and married? Like I'm sick. I got I got a lot of jokes about my fucking wife. How about this? Yeah.
Petered. Oh, that's good that you don't have to be named Peter. Yeah, Petered appalled and married.
You redeemed yourself. That's that's really good, Joe.
I was thinking of a bit today where you say to a guy, Hey, your wife told me she was going to get a tattoo on her boob. And I said, Why are you going to get a tattoo on your husband?
Good. Yeah, that's real good. Thank you. And then laughing joke. Yeah, yeah. And then then she'd hit him with a purse. Yeah. And then lastly, yesterday on taste buds. Sal said, you know, my exercise is routine. And I said, Sal, I've seen your routine. And it's exercise.
Hmm. And it's exercise. I don't. Oh, it's exercise to sit through your routine. Yeah, yeah, I see. Okay. I thought that was really good. I just saw red when you mentioned Sal on our podcast. So maybe I didn't hear the punch.
mention you on our on his podcast. That's fine. We've been
the established, established podcast. Can you hear that? I
hear that. And also you're freezing every 10 seconds. The
audio is fine. But I keep seeing horrific freezes of your face
contorting into demonic shapes. But the audio is good. The
audio is fine. Yeah. I think it's because the fan is on. Let
me shut the fan off. Hold on. Talk to the people while I shut
the fan off. Pretty tight ship over there. We're only going to
have one fan left when this podcast is over, folks. Don't
shut off the only fan. Speaking of only fans, I'm masturbating.
I'm pretty close to coming. But I think I'll edge. Instead, you
ever edge yourself, Joe? I've never done the edging. Now, you
never once have like teased yourself treated yourself like a
lady taking yourself to the market. No, if I'm not going to
do it for her, why should I do it for me? No, I don't know. I
when I masturbate, it's, it's purely to exercise the demon. I
got to get this out of me so I can think straight. I'm not
sitting there having a sensual time with myself.
Yeah, you don't have to be sensual. But give yourself give
yourself an edge. I'm picturing you laying back in a tub.
Yeah, with rose petals, much like American beauty. Also with
with a 45 year old man looking gazing down at me. No, there's
nothing wrong with edging. I actually when I was when I first
learned about masturbation, which was, I mean, this is bad,
but like three years before anything even came out, as I've
said on the show, I started quick. I had a lot of mojo, as
Austin Powers says. And I looked up masturbation. And the first
thing I saw was, I didn't even have a computer, I had to look
at like a boy's guide to growing up or something at the library.
And it said, make sure you don't or there's no need to rush it.
People can often feel shame. That was helpful for me to hear
as a as a Catholic boy. I always pictured Jesus watching me
masturbate sitting at the foot of the bed. That's the only way
you could finish burying his head in his hands in in shame it
that the person I was becoming and coming folks, but the book
said, it doesn't have to be a rush. Take your time. And then
it went through things you could do. It was like caress your
inner thighs. stroke your nipples. Now I don't do any of
that shit. I'm just saying, you can you can you can keep
yourself from coming for like hours and make it feel amazing
book for young boys to read. Yeah, at the library. That is
was like men and women sometimes kiss. It was like very tame. So
I had to look up some actual information. But yeah, little
pictures and stuff too. Because I think honestly, the first I
ever heard of it was in needful things when that teacher jacks
off a 10 year old boy. What was Stephen King doing in the 80s and
90s? cocaine, obviously, but he had so many books where like a
10 year old kid was getting jacked off. It's why I find it
so funny that he's like, the captain of like the woke ship.
Now it's like, dude, you didn't have one book for two decades
that didn't have a couple of n bombs in it. Some kid jizzing on
some fucking, you know, like it was ridiculous. It's like,
buddy, relax, calm down. We've read the books. Yeah, I picked
up Joe once in my car, and I had it set up to the worst sex
scene in literature history, which is in Pet Sematary. When
his wife reaches into the bathtub and jacks him off with
an oven mitt, and he likes the rough feel of the oven mitt. And
it's read by Dexter, the guy who plays Dexter. The so like a
scene that was already like a ultimate boner killer read by
the creepiest sounding man alive. Just I mean, you get the
feeling he's never had sex.
That Dexter's never had sex. Oh, Dexter. Oh, I'm talking about
Steve King. Yeah.
Uh, I would like to hear that scene read by Will, what's his
face? The saddest? Yeah, we've talked about Will Patton as the
saddest voice that's ever existed.
Yeah, no. I mean, Michael C. Hall is, he was like, she oiled
up the oven mitt and gripped his throbbing member.
It's just awful to hear. Awful to hear. And then you picture
Stephen King hunched over a typewriter, clacking it out while
drinking like an old Milwaukee. Just gross. Tabitha waiting
upstairs for him. I'm listening now to Cujo read by Lorna Raver,
the old lady from Drag Me to Hell, and I'm enjoying it quite
a bit. I've never read Cujo, believe it.
The witch from Drag Me to Hell? Yeah. I don't know who reads it
and does lots of cool voices and she's great.
She's great in that movie. She plays like that gypsy like
witch, right?
Yeah, she's excellent in the movie. And then you look her up
and it's like she's hasn't done much of anything else. I mean,
it's kind of sad, but I love her in that movie. That's a great
movie to me. I like, I like it to me.
I like it. It's, it's, it's got its problems, but I enjoy it. I
don't think it's a benchmark. But we said that last week when
we talked about.
We also talked about benchmarks when you get up from your chair
and leave it. Yeah.
We talked about a malignant and you said that it was a worse
Drag Me to Hell. And I was saying, I don't think it's good
if you're the starting point is Drag Me to Hell, you know.
Drag Me to Hell is a much lesser Evil Dead, you know.
It is, but I love it. I love it. The CGI is a great hindrance in
that movie and it's not needed. And I don't understand why he
did so much of it in that film.
Especially the guy who on a budget of $10 can make things
look fucking awesome. Yeah. It's CGI is often a hindrance for
these people. Speaking of budgets of $10. Yeah. I'm not
going to waste movie corner time talking about this, but I'm now
well into season three of creep show. Oh, I'm not doing it. I
don't blame you. I'm now at a point where I'm angry. I'm angry
at my favorite movie franchise of all time. This show sucks.
Like if you like I've said before, you could cobble
together about four of the stories and it would be a
passable third entry into the into the series. Good enough
for me, I guess. But like, now the amount of volume that they
have. Yeah. And the fact that that number has not gone up.
It's just terrible. It's terrible. Every episode, as soon
as I see Nick Cotero's name underwriting or directing for
the episode, I'm like, this is going to be terrible. Yeah, he
did one good episode, which was gray matter, which was the very
first story. And I'm absolutely convinced that he because it
was his first outing as a director on the series, that it
was really directed by the DP, because it looks much better and
has much more style than anything else he's doing on the
show. Or maybe he got lucky with the first one and put more
effort into it and just doesn't apply the same. I don't know
what it is, man, but
I get a little more money for the first one a little more
time. I mean, I, you don't want to sympathize too much because
people do amazing work on a low budget. But I feel like shutter
has too low a budgets on their projects. They look bad, almost
across the board. Their original stuff looks bad.
I don't think see, I don't think they have too low a budgets. I
think they're not monitoring how the budgets are being spent.
That's what I think. Because in the so I had a meeting once
with the guy from shutter. Frank shutter is his name. Anyway,
but he and I said, I sent him a bunch of my material. And I said,
you know, I'd love to was when creep show was about to come out
or maybe the first season had dropped. I said, Look, man, you
know, I don't really do the writers rooms too frequently
anymore. But I've always wanted to write for horror. So like,
would love if you'd take a look at these scripts. And maybe I
could if you're ever looking for somebody for creep show,
whatever. And he was like, Well, we don't have writers rooms on
any of our shows. That's not how we we do it here. He was like,
we just have we have the show runner and then they parcel out
the work to the people they and it's that's what I mean about
like, I don't think any of this is being monitored. And here's
why I really feel strongly about that. The there was an episode
this season, that the first story was about it was episode
two. The first story was about a collector of horror
memorabilia. And the second story was about a guy being
haunted by a demon. The second story was actually pretty good.
But it was ruined by the fact that the demon looked like a man
in a rubber suit. And it looked fucking terrible. Yeah. And what
pissed me off about that was the first story, which absolutely
sucked. Featured a full stop motion skeleton sword fight like
like Army of Darkness style. Yeah. And I'm like, you guys
spent fucking money on that. And not on making this fucking demon
thing look good. It is it's astounding to me that Greg
Nicotero, a guy that has worked his entire life in special
effects doesn't understand that if you don't wet the suit and
make it look slimy, it looks fucking fake. Yeah, that's like
monster 101 shit, dude, like have shit dripping off of it.
That's what makes it kind of look a little more real. Yeah,
it's a quick circle jerk before you call it. Yeah. But two
episodes now they've had a guy in a rubber suit, playing a
monster and it looks painfully fake. Like it's doing couldn't
you just put an x ray filter over the camera and had two
people fight and then you just show their skeletons fighting?
Well, that'd be great. Because because the Well, I guess you
could I don't Are you are you joking? Is that a real thing?
Although I wonder, it might work. But I may have joking. Yes.
Yeah, I mean, it's like this this whole first episode was our
story in this episode I'm talking about was like was like
this like big tribute to horror history. Yeah, it's like, guys,
who gives a fuck about any of this? I'm not here for fucking
fan service. Yeah, I'm here for you to make cool horror stories
that feel like they'd be in the vein of a trilogy of movies I
really love. And yeah, out of 20 whatever the fuck 30 whatever
the fuck stories, you've managed to do that four times. And like
eke by with four story. I'm not even talking about like you had
four grand slams. Yeah, I'd say less. The I don't know, I
couldn't get into it because of the cheapness. I couldn't help
but think with a title as big as creep show. Why not bump this up
to AMC AMC and shutter are the same family. You got walking
dead a massive horror hit, like, just put a little more money
into it and put it on AMC in my opinion.
I think they've got enough money. They don't have the right
people fucking calling the shots. They're getting legitimate
talent in this thing. It's like, this is not a budget issue. This
is a you don't know what the fuck you're doing issue. And
unfortunately, it's a big enough title that I guess it's carrying
well enough in the ratings that they that it's going to keep
going. But here's my question. Why the fuck isn't Tom Savini
involved in this? That's a red flag to me. Tom Savini was
involved with Tales from the Dark Side, the movie, then both
creep shows. So was Romero. Romero obviously is not with us
anymore. So he can't be involved. And Stephen King has
sort of been involved because they adapted one of his stories,
but he hasn't written anything.
Joe Hill does a bunch of them, right?
They adapt Joe Hill stories. And they've done such a poor job
that I'm starting to be like, is Joe Hill a bad writer? Like,
like, or do they just not know how to adapt his stories? Yeah.
It's just terrible, man. I'm so angry about it. This is how now
I get how people felt about the Star Wars prequels, because I
liked them. And people would yell at me. Now I get it. I
understand now how you felt.
Yeah. Yeah, I watched the latest Joe Bob. I mean, it's they're
getting better guests or bigger guests, I should say they had
David Gordon Green, and you're your boy, Jason Bloom, I think
had some really fascinating stuff to say about the movie
industry and how they work.
I think that's interesting. But I think you couldn't find a
greater antithesis of Joe Bob Briggs than Jason Blum. Like I
just don't. I think he Jason Blum to me is everything.
Everything Joe Bob has ranted about like, you can't make a
movie and not show boobs in the shower, you know, like
everything he screams about. That's wrong with current horror.
Is to me everything Jason Blum promotes.
I hear you but compared to Hollywood at large, I feel like
he you know, he's he's a bit of a renegade. I mean, Joe Bob was
calling him the next Roger Corman, which I don't think is
accurate. What? Yeah. What what he was explaining is that, you
know, Joe Bob was like, since you guys do your movies, for the
most part for 5 million bucks, why do all these big stars come
to you? You know, what what what makes you a destination for
actors? And he said that he pays people off the gross that you
find like on variety or on the internet. He says if a movie
grosses $100 billion, there's a bonus structure in place. And
when the company started, he used to take a picture of
himself dropping a check in a FedEx envelope 50k. But
basically every, every once it makes $50 million, there's a new
structure where every 10 million, you make like a $50 ,000
bonus, and they pay it. And they don't go off weird, shady
accounting, like how Lord of the Rings pretended they didn't make
any money off the franchise. They go off the box office
gross, which is a cool system. And that's why people come to
them. And then he said, it's just, it's just very
appreciated by everyone. It's all on the up and up, it's above
board. And then they return because the sequels make even
more money. So I think the actors wind up getting rich off
it. He keeps the budgets low. I guess in that way, he's
Corman esque, but the budgets are way, way bigger, for sure.
It was an interesting guy. And he said, you know, if you if you
do a movie on Netflix, now you do it, this is what everybody's
suing over. Now you make a movie, you get paid once you
might make more than you'd make it Blumhouse, but you never get
another dollar. So if a movie is like that Sandy Bullock picture,
whatever that was rat race, what was that called? The one where
a bird box or bird box.
Bird Box gets seen by you know, 100 million people, the guy who
wrote that makes the same money, essentially, as the guy who or
gal who wrote the movie that they bury that nobody watches on
Netflix, they get an upfront fee. And that's it. That's
fucked up. It really is. So
that is fucked up. Netflix is fucked up. But you know, yeah,
the it's not. I just think I appreciate blums.
intuitiveness and approach. Yeah. And you know that that he
made it to where he is through a sort of rogue method. Yeah. But I
appreciate it the way I appreciate Tyler Perry. I mean,
at the end of the day, it's an absolute terrible product. I'm
sorry, it just is. And with Blum, yeah, I like some of what
Blum does. All right. Well, aside from get out. And lash,
whiplash. They've made some good movies, for God's sake. What is
the B and then the bonnet? It's like Jason Blum, fuck your
girlfriend or something. It's come on, man. Some of the worst
movies we've ever discussed on this podcast were always your
make a bad movie. All right. They make a bad movie. It's it's
that's they don't make a good movie. You think this Halloween
kills is going to be any good. The early reviews are abysmal.
Yeah, I mean, that first one wasn't great. The new one, what
it has me intrigued is that it's supposed to be just a kill fest
like hundreds of people killed, which I'm intrigued by. Did you
hear that firemen are something firemen are suing because
firemen are killed in this movie? It's just what's going on
again. You ever see backdraft again? It's well, that's just
absurd that the firemen suing thing is stupid. I don't know if
that's true or not. But if it is, it's stupid. But again, it's
it's it's we've talked about it ad nauseam. This Halloween kills
sequel is everything that everybody condemned the
franchise for for all these years. And here comes these guys
to the rescue, we're going to reboot and restore and reframe
the franchise. And it's worse than anything they've done
preceding this. It just is it's just sucks. It's got no point.
It's got no plot. It's got no believability. It's just a kill
fest. That's what the last one was. That's what this one will
be. How about we give it a chance? We will. We'll review
it. But I get it every I think I'm actually going to see it
tonight. Matter of fact, every early review, by the way, is
saying exactly what our assumption is that it's just
like, it's pointless. It's gratuitous. So I'll give it a
chance. We're gonna review it. But but anyway, I'll say this
about a positive another positive about Blum, I think
what he does is he allows artists to do what they want to
do, which is cool. Sometimes it works, get out. Yeah, sometimes
it doesn't work us. You know, so it's like, okay, sometimes
it's great. Sometimes it's not he kind of stays out of their
way, which I think is cool.
Yeah, he actually said he never gives notes, which is odd. It's
he does some cool stuff. I just wish I liked what he did more.
And I wish there wasn't such an agenda with every movie he does
now. We're you know, you know, after get out, it was we have to
make a commentary at all times. And it's like, to the point of
bad writing, right? You know, but but what are you going to do?
Yeah, Ghostbusters is also not getting great reviews. It's got
87 % we talked about it's gotten he's getting fantastic reviews.
I've read nothing but bad. I mean, I'm on Twitter. So that's
where Oh, yeah. Oh, really? The Twitter mom is gonna hate on
this new Ghostbusters. It didn't last retribution for the last
Ghostbusters. But I follow a lot of film critics. I mean, I'm not
talking about just your average Joe, as people just didn't like
the movie. I don't know what the time I've seen. I told you the
bad reviews I saw were like, it's too much of a sequel. Yeah,
okay. But I've seen some glowing reviews that it said that like,
Jason Reitman managed to bring in a new cast that you care
about. Yeah, also giving you the nostalgia kick that you want.
This is going to that they're raving about this young girl
that's in it. Everybody's saying she steals the show. And she's
fantastic. I'm excited. Ivan Reitman said something that made
me so excited recently. He said to see Bill Murray back on set
as Peter Venkman. Uh huh. And doing Peter Venkman. Yeah, he
was like, it was so exciting. Because he was like, we just
haven't seen that Bill Murray in a long time. And I got like,
chills. I was like, he's right. When was the last time we saw
just like, funny fucking like stripes. Prick, smart ass Bill
Murray. It's been forever. Like, I'm very excited about that.
You see what is I mean, Rotten Tomatoes says 81 % what or 87 or
something?
What? Yeah, you're right. It's an 81%. The first two reviews of
it are not both refer to it as a lifeless corpse. So that's not
right. But yeah, you're right. 81%. So people are liking it
more than I thought. All right, slimy stinking corpse of a sequel
says the Guardian. Well, you know, leave it to the Brits.
Yeah. They spilled tea on the review before they turned it in.
Yeah, I, I also want to watch this scream trailer, I think
between episodes, you and I should watch it. So we have an
opinion on it. But that comes out in January.
I haven't watched it. I already have an opinion on it.
Well, that's your problem, Joe. I don't problem. What else can
they wring out of this goddamn franchise? I mean,
I don't know. And having the cast back seems kind of absurd to
me. It's like my friends work on head of the class, or they
worked on head of the class. So I'm not saying anything
negative, but the
on on while being recorded. Yeah, I watched the trailer for
the head of the class reboot, or they showed a scene. It was a
two minute, laughless scene. And they were showcasing the return
of Robin Givens as one of the kids moms. And I was like, I
don't even remember Robin Givens being in head of the class. And
I've seen every episode.
She's on the first few seasons. And then she married Mike Tyson.
They have her come out and you hear the fake audience applause
for Robin Givens. And it's like, Oh, boy, like, it's, it just
shows you that TV executives don't know what people want. I
mean, to think that anyone is clamoring to know what Robin
Givens is, she looked fantastic. I'll say that.
We're running out of nostalgia when you're dusting off David
Yeah, as a big, you know, I mean, guys, it's one thing to
bring back. I'm happy about like Mark Hamill's resurgence. And I
know that, you know, he certainly didn't have the
Harrison Ford type career, not that he had a bad career or has
a bad career. But no, I get it. Like Mark Hamill did some some
real doozy movies. And I think a lot of us were thinking we might
never see him on this big screen again. But he came back
and reprised an iconic character in cinema for all of the of the
ages. So it's awesome. And you're happy. Whatever. Nothing
against David Arquette. But I mean, for Christ sakes, you
know, let's bring back Jamie Kennedy while we're at it. You
know what I mean? Like, does anybody make an appearance? I
think he's dead. Not in real life. I mean, in the movie, he's
dead. Yeah. Oh, you're right. You're right. He's the one that
was like the expert on horror movies. Right? Yeah. liver
alone. Still good job.
Lillard liver alone. That's in the first one. Matthew Lillard
goes liver alone. Like liver. It's some it's a bad pun. I
wrote a song and recorded a song with a band I was in years ago
called Bernie Bernie head flap. And I wrote a song that we
recorded called liver let die about an alcoholic. I thought
that was a very good play on words. Was it a full on weird
out style parody? It was Yeah. You can dare to have a drink.
And Fred from the B 52s come in liver let die. Oh, I didn't even
realize I forgot there's a song. I was thinking of James Bond. I
was I forgot there's the Paul McCartney song liver let down
then the is is that cover by faith no more? No, the guns and
roses. Oh, you're right. Sorry, geez, single. They use that to
great effect in gross point blank. For like this, the 711
that replaces his childhood home, he walks in there and
there's like a big shootout to live and let die. G and R. I
mean, guns and roses. There's a band I mean, appetite for
destruction. I own an original copy on vinyl front to back. I
mean, it's, it's a fucking masterpiece. Yeah, that's great.
And then G and R is like, I know what we should do. Let's do
meatloaf style songs on the next rep. Wow. I like them all. I
mean, look, November rain to me is probably their their best
song. I know that's gonna make us slap you in the face you
November rain is a is a masterwork. And I love it. I love
the the ending. But then again, I wasn't you know, I didn't have
to watch the fucking music video 800 times as a kid, you know, a
lot of people have probably different opinions about it than
I actually sat down at a piano. I was like, Oh, fuck off, guys.
Like, I like some of the user illusion songs. But I did not I
was not a fan of that stuff. But hey, they obviously made the
right move. Those are considered iconic albums. But just
terrible. Or it's so easy, baby. I mean, I gotta find a G
day bear. Yeah, it's those that leave the exact lyrics.
They were great live. Surprisingly great live, I gotta
say. I never want to see him again once was enough. I mean,
Axl's not in his prime, but they sounded good. I never went.
What can you do?
Nothing.
All right. Should we get to the movie corner, Joseph?
Yeah, let's do it.
All right. I also wanted to say I, I saw your criticisms,
listeners of my solo movie corner. What were the
generally? Well, generally, I listened to it 100 times before
putting it out, making sure it's all okay, and etc. And this time
I recorded it like an hour before midnight at the end of
the month, because I forgot that it was the end of the month. And
I didn't have time to listen to it. And there's a section, you
all described it in an amusing and accurate way. It sounds like
I'm being kidnapped. I don't know what happened to the audio,
but it sounds like I'm recording while rolling around inside a
trunk of a car. And I apologize. But by and large, I thought it
sounded fine. I'm recording you an extra special long one this
month, which will feature all the Daniel Craig bonds, it will
feature a discussion of venom, let there be carnage. It will
feature lots of big talk. So get ready for that. I got to make it
up to you. The movie corn. I've seen quite a bit. I'm going to
leave off the ones I'm doing on the other one. But I watched
let's let's go with the guilty starring Jake Gyllenhaal. It's
new to Netflix. It's one of these basically one character
thing and the rest is like a radio play. Jake Gyllenhaal
plays a cop who is sort of demoted to working the call in
line, the 911 call in line. And he receives an emergency phone
call from a kidnapped woman. Then the rest of the movie,
which thankfully is a tight 90 minutes, is basically Jake
Gyllenhaal talking on the phone. So in that way, it kind of feels
like no problem.
So yeah, it's not to cut you off. But it's funny, you
movie, I was at a bar last night, and there was a girl
there screaming at me about how much she hated this movie, like
screaming at me was hurt. Well, was her issue that it was a
portrayed women poorly? Or did she just think that it sucked?
She thought that it was a homogenized version of the
original film. Yeah. And that it was it's everything wrong with
American cinema and why we can't do anything right here. Yeah,
which she's right. In many ways. But I mean, it was shot, I read
up, it was shot in 11 days with the director had a COVID
exposure and was in like a different building directing
the film. And it feels like that. It just feels like Jake
Gyllenhaal doing almost like an improvised play. There's some
fun voices that call in and almost reminded me of listening
to the calls on Frasier, like your boy, Bill Burr. You know,
they get a lot of people with like good, distinguishable
voices. But um, it's basically Gyllenhaal spends the entire
movie with his arms behind his head to show off his massive
biceps. And just talking on the phone, and it's dull. I didn't
see the original movie that it's based on. But it's just there's
no suspense to it. And the twist is stupid. And it's just not a
good movie. You know, I your friend who screamed that she was
right. I don't know why she needed to scream. But I agree
with her. It's not he was. She was a lot. She was a nice girl,
but she was a lot. And to a point where everybody was like,
what is with this lady just screaming, she slammed down her
glass at one point. It started because we talked about my first
entry in today's movie corner. A terrible film called The Many
Saints of Newark that I thought was decent when I was watching
it. And the more I thought about it, the more I was like, this
movie sucks.
Well, everybody hates it. I told Joe, please don't watch this
movie. If you haven't watched The Sopranos. And then sure
enough, Joe's reading up. He's like, oh, you know, he's found
out about things that happen like in the second to last
episode of the show. It's I gotta let it go. He's never gonna
watch the day. But it's a it's a prequel. So you don't need to
see The Sopranos. It's a prequel prequel say you would say
somebody watching the Star Wars prequels doesn't necessarily
need. Absolutely. Absolutely. That's one of the major
criticisms about them is that they don't stand enough on their
own, which I agree with. You wouldn't say your enjoyment would
be multiplied by 1000. Having seen the other movies in the
franchise, as obviously, if you're a fan, sure, but like my
nephew, for instance, saw the prequels first and love Star
Wars as much as anybody. So it's, you know, and he's now 22 or
whatever. So it's like, you know, I don't think there's a
must to that. But yeah, obviously, there's value in that
concept. That's good. You hear the siren outside? Yeah, I do,
Joe. Yeah, Jesus Christ. Can anything just be fine today?
We've paused and restarted eight fucking times. The cop has to do
that obnoxious whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop. Like
they probably have somebody pulled over and are still just
making the noise because they like his Christ. Anyway, he's
still doing it. Anyway, LA is lawless now. I haven't seen a
cop in six months. I think they're all just like, let them
let them die and playing board games at the station.
The so this movie.
Spoilers, you're gonna hear spoilers. I just have to well
acted, beautifully directed. Not well written. Why is it not
well written? Because it was written by David Chase. That's
David Chase, as I said last night, is a guy who thinks he's
Fellini making Scorsese movies or Scorsese type content. This
thing's got an imaginary twin uncle in it, which is absurd,
which is fucking absurd. Ray Liotta, the dual role twins
exist. Yeah, and made up. Yeah, no, but Ray Liotta, the most
indistinguishable man of all time, the most incapable actor of
playing anything but Ray Liotta. He can't do anything but Ray
Liotta. And I love when he does Ray Liotta. Don't get me wrong.
But it's literally like Woody Allen. It's like and then so so
so Ray Liotta's character is murdered. And then Dickie starts
to go visit his dad's brother in jail that you have no backstory
about. You have no idea of what's going on. And who walks in
but Ray Liotta as a twin brother, it is never explained.
There's never a line where Dickie says, my god, you look
just like him or nothing. You're just supposed to accept it.
These guys were identical twins. So you go, okay, fine.
They're identical twins. That's a little confusing. And then,
much later in the movie, Dickie goes into a deep fantasy and
looks up and he's sitting alone in the prison, which insinuates
this uncle didn't exist. This was all in his head. This was a
version of his father he wanted to have that he didn't have or
whatever. There's that stupid moment at the end where they
pinkies from the coffin, which makes no fucking sense
whatsoever. I know it's metaphoric, but it wasn't real,
Joe. I know it wasn't real, but it makes no sense. There is
nothing in this to make you think that this is the birth of
Tony Soprano. If anything, you'd walk away from it going, this
kid doesn't go into the life after this. Like, it ends with
him furious at his uncle and saying I want no part of any of
this. And then you think that's going to kind of be the end. And
but then in the last in the last moments, they play the theme
from the Sopranos. So you're supposed to be like, here we go.
Tony is Tony. And it's like, it's not at all. It's a bad
movie. And there's an entire B plot about civil rights and
racial tensions in Newark at that time, which was happening,
which I do think is interesting that they incorporated that they
nothing with. They do nothing with it. The guy says we're
going to start, we're going to compete against the Italians,
we're going to start the black mob. And they show none of it.
You just see him at the end with money moving into a white
neighborhood, and you're supposed to be like, Oh, he did
it, I guess. Okay, cool. Terrible film. Just a terrible,
terrible. When they're on the phone, he goes to like it the
first time I talked to you. So this is interesting. Like I
said, I had to think about it for a little while.
So David, it's very hard to hear any discussion of Sopranos from
somebody who dismisses it and doesn't watch it and and hasn't
seen the greatest television show ever made. It's I can't
really engage it. Although I had issues with the movie myself, I
have attempted to watch the show repeatedly. I have repeatedly
said, I think it's a bad show. And I will refer back to what
most people say, that we're fans of the show. The first few
seasons were amazing. And they lost their way in the middle
there. The end of the series was terrible. And this movie
is that who were you talking to? Meatheads? Everybody I know
that ever like the Sopranos says it loses its way in the middle
when it gets into the whole thing about like, they're gonna
make a mob movie and all this shit and the Hollywood like the
comedic Hollywood plotline comes into it. Tony hallucinating,
which I've made fun of endlessly on this fucking podcast.
Everybody says the finale is terrible. Nobody likes the
finale. And you might like it. But you also like the Seinfeld
finale, which is the worst episode of Seinfeld. I think
people have come around on the finale of Sopranos. And anyone
with half a brain loves where the Sopranos goes. It's setting
the groundwork for where TV would go for the next 2025
years. It takes a bunch of chances. There were idiots who
like nobody got whacked this week. But
I don't mean that. But it's it's it's again, David, watch it.
You gotta David Chase. It's a bad show. The line right at the
top that would Chris
glam show of all time. Oh, well, what is that most? It's what
is it? I'm telling you, it's the best show I've ever seen. And
I've watched a ton of I know a lot of shows you've seen. And I
think you're wrong. But listen, you have a soft spot for it.
That's fine. But I'll say what I said last night off spot like
married with favorite married with children married with
children was considered groundbreaking and innovative.
You watch it now. You're like, there's some funny episodes.
It's not a good show. It's just was a thing that happened at the
time that was very different. I think that's what the Sopranos
is. And you're wrong. You're just wrong. It's not it's not
even a pilot is directed like a film school short. It's the
pilot is the worst episode of the show, as I told you, you
are still good. It's a great pilot anyway. Well, okay, so
explain to me, then then justify the terrible writing in this
movie, please talk about the movie. I mean, to diminish David
Chase, again, perhaps the best television writer of all time,
and of all time, of all time. Yes, you enjoy luck. He didn't
do luck. He didn't do luck. That was his father anything since
the Sopranos. No, he didn't. That's that is not him. Hold on.
I'm gonna look it up. That's the guy who did Deadwood David
milch. Joe David milch.
Oh, yeah, I didn't name him. That's his name. I know. It's
funny. It's a funny name. I can't have fun with his name.
It's just
that I mean, the sweeping everybody hated the Sopranos
after the first couple seasons is just so dumb. But anyway, the
movie, I'm listening. Leota. Look, I don't like I never like
an identical twin subplot either. I thought Leota gave
completely different and great performances. I thought he was
excellent as the kind of softer. He lost like 30 pounds. He so
he looked a little bit different. He had gray hair,
whatever. To me, the one the first guy was Leota and
Goodfellas grown up and kind of, you know, turned nasty. And the
other one was like a sweet older guy who was very intelligent. I
thought they did a great job of separating them. And I thought
Leota did a great job of playing them and will probably be
talked about for Academy Award consideration. Oh, you are
insane this year. Who's better, Joe? Who you are insane Academy
Award because they put him up for supporting actor I think he
could get talked about for playing your role. I thought he
was not a dual role. It's Ray Leota in both roles in one it's
screaming Ray Leota and it's one talking Ray Leota. That's the
only difference. That's the only difference. I thought there was a
lot of differences. And I'd love to hear who your five choices for
the twin brother. I like jazz. I'm different than the other guy
that like spaghetti. Give me a break with this. I thought there
were very different and excellent performances by Leota.
I would say Dickie's got a chance of the nom. He's really
good. But it's just it's just a well, what do you make of the
fat, the imaginary uncle? It was come on. I look there's big
problems with this movie. I think I think a lot of people
went in. I mean, David Chase likes to subvert expectations.
The the birth of Tony Soprano, I think was used in the marketing.
But I don't know that that was his intent. I mean, I found it
baffling that Tony and his mom I thought Vera Formaga was
excellent as Tony's mom. She was good, better than the lady who
played her in the show actually in flashbacks. But that is such
a small part of this movie. And it's mostly Tony trying to get
his depressed mom on antidepressants. I thought that
story was great. But again, what is this movie about? What is
this movie about?
I agree. I agree. The Newark riot stuff. You know, that's
not Chase's forte. I get that. I mean, they're kind of pretending
that The Sopranos wasn't just as wide a show as Seinfeld. There
were almost no black characters of note on The Sopranos. And
these characters all prove themselves time and time again,
to be racist. If when Tony's daughter dated a black guy, he
was furious about it. But yeah, that is what absurd by the way,
what absurd racial slur that nobody says did they did they
write in to that thing? I love at the beginning of the many
states when Christopher goes, nobody made more shuttle. Oh,
nobody talks like this. The Christopher narration was awful.
I almost was like, I'm not going to watch this and let it ruin my
opinion of the show when the narration in the graveyard
started. I'll grant you.
Actually, the narration was kind of cool. I just thought it was
not well executed.
They use a ton of n words on Sopranos. They don't make stuff
up. But it's like that I think they were trying to sort of make
peace with the fact that it was never a diverse show by doing
this Newark riot stuff. They do mention the Newark riots on the
show a couple of times, but it doesn't make sense here. You're
always just kind of being thrown from story to story without real
cause. It lasts exactly two hours, which makes me think
there was probably a four hour version that they tried to
whittle down. But what what the one main criticism I see and
agree with is that this should have been a mini series. I don't
think you would have watched it if that's the case. But no, I
think it should have been chase coming back to do a prequel
series, you know, like his version of Boardwalk Empire or
whatever. It's it's an overstuffed movie. I liked parts
of it. But as a whole, I didn't I didn't love the movie. I
thought the leota stuff was great. And I would have liked to
see it as its own thing. I thought the nevola stuff was
great. Would have watched it as its own thing. I like the stuff
with him and his mistress and his wife and all that. But yeah,
it was a little on the nose a little clunky. The Tony and his
mom stuff I love but it was like not enough of the movie. I
thought the ending was corny with a song coming in. Yeah,
dumb.
Well, it was I thought the portrayal of Tony was odd. It
didn't have any footing in one scene. He was the sweetest kid
in the world. And another scene he was an absolute fucking
maniac. It never got into why he might be like that. They didn't
even tie a parallel between his mother's mental illness, and his
apparent, you know, mental instability or anything like
that. This is why I say I take issue with David Chase is the
greatest TV writer of all time. The greatest TV writer, then you
could say movie, would you say? All right. But would you say
that about Larry David? It's like, you know, like Larry
David wrote many episodes of one of the greatest shows of all
time. Do I think that makes Larry David the greatest TV
writer of all time? I think that's, I think I think Norman
Lear is the greatest TV writer of all time. Because he's
great. But I'm saying you have to consistently prove yourself
over and over and over.
I think if you make a show that goes 10 years, that changes the
face of television forever, that changes every show that followed
it owes a debt to it. And that is funnier than most comedies,
better drama than most are all dramas, I would say. I think it's
the best series in the history of television.
But that's a very TV writer. But but those those are two
different things. I think this is an interesting nuance
discussion, or discussion about nuance, excuse me. You could say,
I think Star Wars is the greatest movie of all time,
because it broke all boundaries and reset the way we look at
cinema and all these things. But I think that's a very different
statement from George Lucas is the greatest moviemaker of all
time. Those are two different things. So I just think if you
haven't seen all of David Chase's work, which there is a
lot proceeding to the Sopranos, he's written many screenplays,
and he did Rockford files and all these shows, you know, I
haven't seen them. I'm saying you do the Sopranos, in my
opinion, you're the best TV writer of all time. I don't think
you have to do a bunch of different kinds of shows or
anything else. I think if you wrote the best show of all time,
you're the best TV writer of all time.
So if he wrote another show that you thought completely sucked,
you would still say he's still the greatest TV writer of all
time. That's my question.
Hard to say it would have to really suck, you know, to bring
it down. I mean, he had an achievement that to me, you know,
the show I'd put beneath it, Breaking Bad, The Wire,
Seinfeld, whatever, it's hard to compare comedy and drama. But I
think Sopranos towers above the mall. I do. And, you know, you
got some bug in your ass about it. I'm not going to change
that. You've, you've effectively spoiled major plot
points for yourself by watching this movie and reading about it.
What major plot points? It's a prequel.
But, but there, there's, there's, you know, Joe, don't, I don't
know. I'm in a, I am in a prequel series.
You talk to me about Christopher crying when he was handed to
Tony or whatever, like, you know, what, what becomes of
Chris, Christopher tells you at the beginning, what happened to
him. It's his narration, and it's terrible writing. That's
like the third to last episode of The Sopranos.
By the way, they put that in the trailer. That's in the trailer,
for Christ sakes.
Well, I think they assume that everyone in the world has seen
the show that you talk all the time about how much you hate it
when you haven't watched it.
Most people have seen the entirety of The Sopranos.
I've watched a lot of it. I'm sorry that I won't watch an
entirety of a series that I don't think is very good. I
don't think it's well written. I think it's a cliched take on
mobster life. I think it's cartoonish. And I also think,
and I will say this, part of the reason you're so fascinated
by it is because you grew up nowhere near any of this stuff.
And I grew up around guys like this. And that's not the way
they act and not the way they talk. I'm sorry. It's just not.
All right. I didn't realize you were scarface, Joe.
I didn't say that. I said I grew up around people that were that
were in this. They were in this world. I'll leave it at that.
And I I had some firsthand experience with seeing the way
guys like this walked and talked. Let me let me just say that much.
And this to me was cartoonish and it was only made more
cartoonish by every stupid commercial they did.
And I just thought it was corny.
I think like I said, I think it's a guy that wants to make art
house film, art house films, doing commercials what they do.
You don't remember the Polly Walnuts, like Tide commercials and shit like that.
Oh, no, I don't remember the slew of shit.
What does that have to do with the show?
I think because in every one of those commercials, it was big pussy
or whoever being like, I ain't no wise guy when it comes to my laundry.
And it just made it even more for those tied commercial.
But it made it even more cartoonish.
OK, show me deserve the sopranos.
You don't deserve to watch Perfect Strangers for the fourth time.
That's more your level.
You don't deserve the sopranos.
Anyway, Chase, I see what you're saying.
I got you. You love the sopranos.
I don't. We're never going to see eye to eye.
We talked about that way too much.
That was basically a full review of many saints of Newark.
We've actually had full reviews that have gone shorter than that.
So let's move to our movie at hand.
The Halloween classic question mark trick or treat spelled like toys are us.
Uh, this is a horror anthology.
It is kind of a cult favorite now.
I hear a lot of people talk about this as being their their big Halloween viewing.
They watch it every year at Halloween.
And I get why it's really fun.
I think it's while it's not surpassing creep show,
I do think it is in the same spirit.
It did not get a theatrical release.
Warner Brothers didn't like it.
There's lots of rumors as to why, you know, Brian Singer was a producer
and they hated his Superman Returns, which lost them a bunch of money.
They're talking about maybe that's why it got buried. Who knows?
But it really found its audience.
And it's great because it's it's an anthology,
but it's also done in an interesting way where all the stories
intersect with each other, kind of like Pulp Fiction.
It's also like you don't know what order the stories are in
until the very end, which is a very cool thing.
You see stuff happening in the background of one story
that's happening in another story, and that's all really cool.
The acting is great.
You got Brian Cox from Succession as an old coot. It's a great part.
It's just really well written.
They took more time to make this something special
as opposed to just three stories and like, you know, some guy in a chair
telling you, here's the next story.
The framing device is actually a big part of the fun.
I'm a fan of Trick or Treat.
They yeah, they took it a step further than, for instance, Shudder did
with getting a Halloween adventure doll
to usher in the stories each week on Creepshow.
The yeah, it's Pulp Fiction.
I I'm a big fan of this movie.
I tend to like it a little bit more every time I watch it.
When I first saw it, I.
Years ago, I bought this on day one DVD release on blind
because this is back when there was no it came out when there was no streaming.
And I was so curious.
I don't even think you could rent stuff back then digitally.
I think it was all like it was either on DVD or it played in the theater.
And that was kind of it.
So I bought this day one.
For like DVDs back then were what, $25 or whatever,
because I had heard so much about it
and I was so excited about it
and I watched it and I really liked it.
But I was I was I think I had built it up a little too much in my mind.
And in subsequent watches, I've had the chance to
appreciate its smaller points and smaller details rather even more.
And this last viewing that I did for for our Halloween and our review,
that was the most I've ever liked the movie ever,
because it really is just very, very, very well put together.
And they don't give away.
Every story starts in one place and then ends up someplace else.
They're very good at misleading you to which way the story is going to go.
And. I think especially with the one about the four women.
Where the setup is, you think that it's they're going to party
and the sister played by Anna Paquin is going to like lose her virginity.
Right. And then you realize it's not that it's that they're werewolves
and she's going to kill a man for the first time, basically.
Yeah. As a where as a she wolf.
And they just do a really great job of of playing that out
and and using virginity as a metaphor for being a werewolf and everything.
They do that also very well in the what's the guy's name?
The the guy from was Dylan Baker, who's the the guy from Happiness
in arguably the most disturbing subplot of movie history,
where he is molesting his son and the son is like jealous
or he's not molesting his son and the son gets jealous.
He's playing kind of a similar thing here.
He has the kid from Bad Santa
who he feeds this chocolate, which he laces with arsenic.
The kid pukes, which is this great kind of gross way to kick things off.
And eventually you learn this guy's a serial killer.
He goes through this town killing people.
He's the principal at the school.
And that that's kind of the most comedic of the stories.
It's his his son keeps kind of peeking out the window
while he's trying to bury the bad Santa kid and distracting him.
So that's sort of a more comedic episode.
But then the Dylan Baker character goes in and out of each
of the other episodes as well.
He's the guy who puts on fangs and tries to kill Pac -Man,
and then they all attack him and get their revenge, which is.
And they do that.
They do that reveal.
They do that reveal very well.
You don't know it's Dylan Baker until Pac -Man at the very end unmasks him.
And it's a great come up in this moment because he's been so shitty
to so many other people through it.
And they misdirect you very well in his story,
because as his son keeps interrupting him, the the gag is,
is you think he's trying to prevent his son
from seeing that he's hiding a dead body and he's cursing about his son
being a little prick and whatever.
And you're like, he's got this secret life from his kid.
Then you realize at the end of that story, no, his kid is in on this with him
and they're going to carve up the bad Santa kid's head like a jack -o' -lantern.
And he's just he's just not a great dad because he's well,
because he's getting his kid in the series, at least he's a bad father.
Yeah, but they hide it all very well.
The third story is about.
The classic sort of
tales from the cryptic kind of vibe of kids going to the site
where a bunch of kids died years prior
in a bus.
That's what you probably want to do today.
Yeah, it's these parents that unite to pay the bus driver
to kill their mentally handicapped children
because they don't want to deal with them anymore.
So that's a pretty dark story.
And then it's kind of like kids in the present day
going to sort of see the site with a girl who is also
although she doesn't seem like it, she's supposed to be sort of mentally
disturbed in some way as well.
But they go to play a prank on her.
And it backfires.
It summons the actual kids from the from the water, from the bus accident.
That's sort of the longest segment.
But I think that one works great, too.
Yeah, and that's that that's the most straightforward one,
because it's a prank, you know, and you kind of know from the beginning
it's going to be this prank where they're setting up this girl
who's clearly like autistic. Right.
And. And then you're like,
of course, the pranks going to backfire on the prankers
and the ghosts are going to be real and whatever.
And then the third story is about the.
What is it? Oh, the Brian Cox one
or the fourth story, excuse me, is the Brian Cox one where
he plays a curmudgeonly old man who doesn't who hates Halloween.
And the character Sam Hain,
the little weird thing in the pumpkin hat.
Yeah, he goes into his house and terrorizes Brian Cox
for not celebrating or believing in Halloween, which is a cool story.
And there's a twist, a major twist at the end of that one
where you find out that Brian Cox is the bus driver
that drove the kids off the cliff and he survives the crash, whatever.
But he did this heinous thing.
And then all the zombie kids that he killed
come to his doorstep at the end and you realize they're going to kill him.
What I didn't like about that is.
There's a weird edit.
Where they show the picture in the story of the kids,
they show the picture of the kids with the bus driver.
In the Brian Cox story,
they show that same picture in his fireplace burning.
The assumption was that Sam Hain left it there.
And you realize, oh, he's the bus driver.
I think it's such a mistake of an edit that they put that picture.
They show you the shot of that picture burning before the kids show up.
I feel like the kids should show up.
They're going to kill him.
You have a what the fuck moment, and then it cuts to the fireplace
and you see the picture and you're like, oh, he's the bus driver.
Yeah, I actually I think Wikipedia actually kind of helped me out on that.
It isn't it isn't done great.
I had seen the movie once before and liked it fine.
I think this viewing for me really cemented it as I get why it's this cult classic.
It's it's I agree with you that that edit could have been handled better.
I read a lot of the troubled production history online and on the Wikipedia.
And apparently this thing was it went through 25 script drafts.
It went through a million different edits where like they they tried to tell
the story in a bunch of different ways.
And it's crazy to me that this was such a problematic movie for them
because it's great.
You know, it it's confusing as to why this was such a troubled production.
There's been a sequel that's supposed to happen for years and years.
And you'd think it'd be a low budget affair that they could do relatively easily,
but it just hasn't come together.
I think it's I think it's I think it was done as a comic book at this point.
Oh, it was. I think so.
Yeah, I think it was hopeless and they just kind of.
But here's it's weird. This movie.
Even though it was direct to video.
It it it's so much it's it's of theatrical quality.
Yeah, I was a Warner Brothers movie.
I mean, you can imagine what the shutter version of this would look like,
and it's it's a lesser movie, to be sure.
But but but well, this is what I was going to say.
I feel like this is the original.
We're one of the original like HBO Max releases.
Yeah. Do you know what I mean?
Because like, you know, for all we for all I bitched about many
since you newer, it's a theatrical movie.
It feels like a real movie.
It doesn't feel like some made for TV movie. Right.
And this is of theatrical quality.
It's they spared no expense.
I mean, I don't know how big the budget was.
I'm sure it wasn't huge, but they they used it very, very well.
And it's got legit talent in it and all that stuff.
And it's it's just very well done.
And it's kind of like this is why I remember watching it on DVD
and being like, this is not a direct to DVD movie.
Like this should have been in theaters.
I don't understand why it wasn't bad luck, I guess.
Yeah, there's stuff about it online.
Like they said, there's a few theories, one being that Bryan Singer
really shat the bed with Superman and Warner Brothers hated him
and did not want to give him any support at that point.
And then the other is that they wanted to get it away from the Saw sequel
and just wound up kind of bobbling it.
And it never came out.
But it is a 12 million dollar movie,
but it was and it shows it's a good it's a really good looking,
well directed movie.
Doherty went on to do Krampus, which I thought was fine.
And he did Godzilla, King of the Monsters, which was not fine.
But, you know, he wrote X2, Urban Legends, Bloody Mary.
He wrote Superman Returns.
So maybe they had a little ill will towards him at that point.
I don't know.
But this is this is what the guy should be doing.
I mean, this is my favorite of his movies.
And I hope that we get that sequel because I think people are really hoping for it.
And I think Shudders should be stepping forward and picking it up.
If they're real horror fans, they must know how much people love this movie.
But, yeah, I dug the hell out of it.
I think I'm going to put it in my yearly rotation as well because it got me in the spirit.
It looks like it shot almost in the same neighborhood as Hubie Halloween.
It's got the same kind of feel as Hubie Halloween.
But it's a better movie.
I'll say that.
Yeah, it does.
My hog is up.
There's more laughs in Trick or Treat.
But the it's interesting.
My hog is up too.
And Mike Doherty, he said when this came out, he said he wanted to make a movie,
a horror movie that was about Halloween.
And he said even the movie Halloween is not really about the holiday.
It's about a serial killer, you know, like, and it just happens to take place on Halloween.
But he was like, I wanted to make a movie that, you know, that was about
stories about the traditions of Halloween and these things you hear about, you know,
urban legends and whatever.
And he did.
And he pulled it off.
And it's a great flick.
I highly recommend.
My hog is up.
My hog is up too.
You know, I think that we get a lot of these now.
You know, with the Mortuary Academy was a very good one as well.
You know, but it just goes to show you how much fun and cool these can be.
If you just take the extra step to kind of link the stories or find some sort of through line
and don't just make it here's a story, here's a story, here's a story.
I think the big selling point for this is its script, which is excellent, in my opinion.
All right, we will be back with a review of The Empty Man, which is another sort of lost movie that
the theatrical release was bungled and is now sort of finding its audience.
I'm on Twitter and Instagram at the Patrick Walsh.
You can hear me and Joe on the We Love Val Kilmer podcast.
I don't know when our episodes will drop, but soon.
And that's it for me, Joseph.
Joe DeRosa comedy on Instagram and Twitter.
Joey Roses is open and real soon.
In fact, by the time you know, that's not true.
This comes out on the 15th.
It won't be open by the time you hear this.
But by the end of this world, well, our pop up is open still.
But the actual location is we're aiming for Halloween weekend.
So if you're in New York that time or shortly after, keep an eye on our Instagram.
It's joeyroseshard8 and we're going to you know, we're promoting a lot and
we'll be announcing the official opening date very, very soon.
But it's creeping up.
That's it.
We will see you next time and we will see you in hell.