Hello everybody and welcome to an all new We'll see you in hell today
s film will be the boys of county hell which is currently streaming on shutter with
me as always is my trusty friend Jotaro so Joe I have notes I forgot I was
even doing it I'm not happy with it either yeah it ain't so easy is it pal well
I've done it once you've done it five million times so there's a little bit of a
learning curve five million you start to try to break it up a little bit try to find
new things anyway yeah it's good to see you boys a county hell is the film for
today boys a county hell it like with a lot of shutter titles it's a it's a
title I can never place I don't know what it is I used to be well it might be
weed might be getting old but like man I could name the eighth lead of a movie
you've never heard of yeah I could just I could do anything I knew every title and
now I think it's just the tonnage of shit coming out it's knowing that every
Friday there's 80 movies coming out and titles don't stick like they used to
they're becoming very repetitive I used to be able to recite to you in
entirety the set list of any concert I went to I was able to feel like I they
opened with this then they did this then they did it like I could just remember it
yeah oh gone it's all long gone now I find myself at concerts
looking down at my phone not to be on my phone but to write the set list down so I
can try to remember it like yeah and then I realize there's a website for it now
so you don't have to do that anymore but you know setless .fm I I go to it all
the time mm -hmm all right used to when we had concerts FM right test to be the
only good steely dance or how does it go so one that goes no static at all
well well aren't you oh well I'm listening to FM yeah suck
man and they had such contempt they already suck and then you see them and you're
like oh no what do they look like I couldn't tell you what they look like take
the moment and google an image of steely then I could send you hilarious images of
these two for the rest of the day the only concert I've ever left was steely
then I went to see Elvis Costello at the bowl thinking he was the headliner
and he was opening and he finished and I'm like all right I'm going to try to get
into steely then and I made it two songs and I walked out the first picture I don't
you can't can you see my phone I mean it's is the guy blowing it the doing the keyboard flute
thing that's a key photo I would have sent to you but he's blowing into the keyboard
guitar it's just these two guys yeah I think one well no I guess they're both still alive
it's just control for beating his wife the one who looks like uh
with uh they have the glasses look at these two
the fucking nerds man this is steely I was so steely there was like seven people
actually I like do it again I like that song
and pito is used to do this uh there's a bit of um when there's a scene of Gandalfini driving
in sopranos where he's singing along to dirty work um a fool to do your dirty work oh yeah
it's it's very funny um but I don't like the band I and I hate looking at them even more and when
you see them live they they didn't have seven people in the band but they had like one of those
like five black women uh background choruses you know that they never interacted with
or it's just like they they're whole thing I think when I was a kid I thought they were black that's
a lot of um like hauling oats and them you don't really realize how you see them but when you see
hauling oats you're like oh okay it's a couple good -looking dudes I mean steely Dan looks like mutants
uh new uh speaking of which um or speaking of just mistaking the band for you know whatever
uh new new new chapter and my parents just hitting a new
I mean they've just gone from the beautiful people that raised me to the two
craziest bitches I've ever met like they're sideways man yeah they're sideways man like
yeah my mom put on the other day on Spotify
Tony Bennett's 90th anniversary birthday concert or whatever okay and it's people singing his songs
contribute to him it was a special they did on TV yeah we're listening to it Diana Crawl is singing
okay not once but twice my father asks is this Tony Bennett singing
the woman's voice oh so he's he's gone I don't know what the fuck is going on man yeah that's insane
yeah well Tony Bennett I saw at the uh at the bowl and he was he's in his 90s and he
was not all there he would forget words at one point he sang a song he had already sang
I still sounded great I mean it's just clear he's kind of like
and you wonder who's pushing this 90 something your old man out on the road you know who who needs money
I think he's doing it I think he still wants to do it I think he's still out there yeah he brought he had his
daughter come out and she either opened her sang some songs with them and I hope Tony Bennett's
daughter is not a listener of the podcast but man I mean her voice if you're looking at everyone's
voice in the history of time she'd rank somewhere amongst the middle and she's saying like 45 minutes
set at the hall it would bowl or which is people like oh boy I guess we'll go grab another giant beer while
we wait here yeah well that was like Jeff Lynn bringing his daughter out as one of the background singers
for ELO and she was just all over the map man yeah it's a shame yeah what are you gonna do you know
they love their family I don't know if they do I think the kid is fucked up and the dad is just like
I'll give her I'll give her a job the kid says hey can I sing in the band he's like no then she goes
but you were on the road playing Wembley for the entire first 21 years of my life so maybe you throw
me a bone so sorry about the hero win dad also you look like a muppet dad you look like a damn
man goes for both dads yeah I don't know that either of the ELO I love Tony Bennett I don't know
that either girl was on heroin I'm just making a joke no I know but yeah no it's a man I was just
gonna tell a good parent story wait a minute you you were on a crawl shit no no no about this famous
shit Bennett bringing out his daughter Lynn bringing out his daughter now it's gone it's gone forever
well one time I saw a loud and Wayne Wright though perform and he brought out Rufus and Martha which
was pretty cool because they're very talented kid yeah they're talented performers yeah yeah I
preferred them to loud and to be honest yeah joy are there any screaming and then are there any
new stories in the world well Pat it's funny ask I got a scary stuff or two please I urge you
horror fans to go take your take your ass over to the internet and you can find these on Amazon you can
also find them on other websites I'm not exactly remembering the name of the website specifically
geared towards this line of movies because it's not named after the company itself however
restaurant video is back now I don't know if it's the original company back again or somebody
bought the name and is just releasing Blu -rays under the name now but it's the classic logo
and they are doing re -releases and remasters of you know 20 and 30 year old horror franchises and
things of that nature just like screen factory just like arrow just like vinegar syndrome and all
these other companies we talk about on this show quite often I just got the Warlock trilogy it was
eighteen dollars marked down from 40 on Amazon and actually on the actual website it was marked down
two so I guess this one is just on sale everywhere but they have a lot of cool stuff they've got the warlock
what's a four -part thing is that a quadrilogy was that how you would say that yeah that's what they
that's how they release daily in movies originally yeah they have that they have a bunch of really
really fun you know sort of niche hard titles and you know they do a really nice job new artwork on
the front of the box like all these companies do and new restorations of the films and things of
that nature and very fairly very fairly priced I think they have I think the killer clowns
blue ray is like eight dollars or something so go check out Vestron video and what they're doing
these days very very interesting and then also if you're a fan of short children's horror stories as
I am there's a fun series of books that I would tell you to try to go grab now if you're interested
because they are out of print and they are becoming more expensive by the day
to purchase but along the lines of scary stories to tell in the dark there was another line of books
called Tales for the Midnight Hour that was released around the same time they are a bit darker than
scary stories a lot of kids dying in these things but they are geared towards second graders
so really cool books fun little stories you know they're written for a younger audience so you know
you're not going to be blown away by the pros but but they're fun books to read they're fun to own
if you're into that scary stories type of thing which I'm sure a lot of our fans are and again I would
tell you to go get these now on eBay if you can because the the prices keep going up and up and up and
up and up and they are not as far as I know being re -released the way scary stories has been several times
again and again so there you go you got some scary stuff this week
for mine after complaining about the Grindhouse video not sending our packages on the last recording
I did receive mine finally yeah it was Matt McCarthy texted me that his ship the day after they cancelled
my order without me saying cancel my order they just had to be hot shots but I'll tell you what I'm
going to do Pat and I can't wait to do this and I am petty enough to do it I am going to drive
up to the archive wow Connecticut I'm going to buy the exact same order that Grindhouse cancelled
on me I am going to take a picture with that order at the archive and in the post I will
shit all over Grindhouse and build up the archive pointing out that instead of being conveniently
delivered to my front door by a company that sucks ass I drove two hours out of my way to support
a company that doesn't okay I mean I don't know I don't know how great you're going to look going
after a an indie video seller but but you can do that I'm not too worried that the
they can fucking blow me yeah all right I guess you're not worried I'm worried no all these places
you know if you're hanging on by a thread you know you'd think that'd be the time to up customer
service and I told you about getting those getting what do you call the invoices from ticket master
sent to my personal PayPal and I was like what the fuck is this I talk about this on the show
yeah I think I don't know basically just as I bought some strokes tickets the show was supposed to be
like March 12 2020 so obviously it was cancelled I sold my tickets way ahead of time and then ticket
master sent me invoices like hey the person who bought your tickets once a refund so now you owe us
this money so I got on with ticket master and I was like so what happens they said we send you
to collections if you don't pay it I said all right do I get my tickets back then and they're like yes
so I pay it it's a sizable amount of money and I still don't have the tickets and I get on the chat
they cancel my chat after waiting online for 25 minutes your chat has been cancelled
so it says you can email I email them it's been weeks this is ticket master you know just they're just
like fuck you yeah yeah well that's why I was so offended by the grindhouse thing because you guys
are supposed to be some of the good guys yeah you're supposed to be some of the good guys you're not
supposed to be the company that that gets an attitude and goes just be patient you know so fuck off
I'm gonna shit on them now publicly again all right anyway let's do the movie corn yeah why don't
you take us over I'm happy to I saw speaking of horror oh wait I do have a new cycle before
you do this miss and you're already aware of this because you told me but call me cat has been picked
up for season two yeah I saw that here god it is just christ the I look heavily heavily
love mr. Leslie Jordan yeah he I bet deep down this is pure speculation I bet he said fuck when
that show got picked up because he is so far above that show at this point it's really bad they fired
their showrunner but we'll see what happens one I wanted to mention that I also sent you
saw spiral with Chris rock and Sam Jackson I'm very curious about it they saw released a image with
basically jigsaw's face on a almost an American psycho type sexualized nude body and I was like is
this in the movie what's going on here so I my my interest is high I don't know if I can convince
you Joe to do all the saws episode because I still haven't seen about half the saws and I you can
buy the whole franchise ten movies for like no and the psychotic it's don't do it to yourself either
I might have done it earlier in the pandemic but I think I only saw one through five and then I didn't
see any after that I'm curious about that I part three you're on autopilot at this point yeah it's
just like and then you're getting into he dies in like four and now it's just a copycat of jigsaw
from beyond the grave right I'll go see spiral though I'll do spiral I want to see it yeah I mean
what they do with it I like that the mask is now a pig head that's pretty creepy yeah Joe and I have
been a little hesitant about doing theatrical movies just because we don't want to force anyone
I know a lot of you like to see the movie first don't want to force anyone back into theaters ahead of
their time but we are in a place now where movies are are coming to streaming within like 30 days or
or whatever so we'll count on saw for one of the next two episodes for sure movies I have seen
speaking of saw it's it's the same director if memory serves dead silence I watched
terrible film yeah I had missed this one and it's just one of those it felt it came out in 2007
and it felt like something that would have come out when I was in high school in the 90s because
it's got like this generic CW cast which to me is always just a sign of of your head and for shit
um the only conceit I sort of enjoyed is the stupidest part of the movie where you learn that his
father is being propped up as a dummy you know that's kind of a cool twist and probably the whole
reason the movie got picked up but like we talked about it on this show scary doll movies always work
the they're always the best segments of horror anthologies right um there's just it's a thing
that scares kids since the dawn of time and exploiting those fears always works a scary doll and it just
don't work such a cool premise I was so excited to see it when it came out I ran to the theater and
then the second donny wallberg steps on screen you're you just know you're in trouble and that's it
he and and my guess is this was mr wallberg's request he spends every scene including scenes where he's
actively on the case looking for clues shaving he carries in his pocket a personal shaver so he'll be
talking and like nobody does this it's not why is that an interesting character detail you know
not a good actor yeah who is also not a good singer who has lucked into something that nobody
looks into and their lives a 30 year plus career 30 year plus great I mean this is adding multiple genres
and and and and and and art you know like he's doing music he's doing movies he's doing television
donny wallberg I mean it's just bad shit does Mark make a call for for him and people are star struck
and cast him I think I wouldn't be surprised but I mean it's you know it's it's what's her name
said it from faxalife the lady that no the lady that just died what's the the famous actress
god damn it from Mel Brooks from young Frankenstein and bankrupt no no no no the lady from for our
brookah from young Frankenstein florist leachman florist leachman she was on the facts of why
yeah she took over after Mrs. Garrett left okay um she's the Billy Connolly of the facts of life if you
will oh by the way another news psycho did you know they're rebooting head of the class
haha
Joe two of my best friends work on it so I have no comments at all but I didn't know they're rebooting
it yes I did what is fucking happening the there is a huge thing now where
everything needs IP almost every pitch needs IP meaning a book a existing show and it doesn't
even matter what it is as long as you can say this thing was a success or this thing you know they'll
they'll just make it anyway florist leachman said always be busy in a scene always have an activity
yeah I agree so clearly Donnie Walberg his take on that was shaving constantly instead of like
smoking and you know committing to the part like a real actor would do yeah yeah yeah I'm sure
it'll be like co -jack with the lollipops you know I'm just always shaving
nuts the movie was was bad it was just a bad movie if you need a great ventriloquist dummy film I
recommend Anthony Hopkins and and Margaret in a little picture called magic masterpiece great
movie masterpiece of a film Burgess Meredith I would almost argue to say his one of his finest
performances he's awesome in it yeah so the he the way he plays is so good in that movie man the
man always gave a hundred percent old burgey I love do you think they gave him those those outtakes
in grumpy old man where he says different different ways to say dick and pussy and fucking or were they his
own no I think they were his own I think he's an exceptional actor yeah I mean a lot of them were just
like phrases like common phrases but that's just funny to see him say them yeah I know I think I miss
outtakes in movies too by the way can we bring that back you you watch him nowadays man where it's like
we have a blooper reel from you know fucking I tried watching the blooper reels on did I wait did I
do one for the movie corner yet sorry I've lost all track of everything no you have an I'll lead me
into what I was going to do I watched goose bumps the movie I bought the double feature goose bumps
and goose bumps too so I want not to I like goose bumps one I didn't it might be a fun thing to put
on at Halloween again you know it's very a very childlike it's goose bumps of course it's geared
towards kids I was aware of that when I bought it but you know earlier today I was talking about
tales from the midnight hour and how dark those stories are and you know same with scary stories
telling the dark and goose bumps though I do like the brand and I do enjoy the stories and I thought
the movie was well done it was just a skewed a little too kiddish for me that said it's well put
together but I watched the outtakes on both goose bumps one and goose bumps two
and they're just they're just joyless fucking outtakes man like yeah they're just joyless like it's
just like they're not there's just nothing I don't know it's weird like it just seems like nobody's
having any fun anymore man everybody's so goddamn nervous yeah maybe that's what is I don't know but
anyway goose bumps would I recommend I think it's a great thing to watch with like your nephew or
your niece or something like that or kid yeah certainly a very very safe monster movie to watch with
children Jack Black he's a little much in it he's doing this ridiculous affectation for no apparent
reason right throughout the entire thing I don't really get why they shoehorn him and I'm just
gonna I'll just do both the second movie I would say is probably worse than the first and then they
also just kind of shoehorn in the second one makes less sense than the first one does and then they
also just kind of shoehorn in Jack Black at the very end of it and none of the cast besides him
returns so it feels very disjointed it oh the second one almost feels like a directive video sequel or
something it's weird also it's called haunted Halloween which is a terrible title it's not like
an Olsen twins movie yeah yeah and then RL Steins and both playing different characters and different
cameo so it's just kind of weird but anyway I got both on it on a single desk from Hamilton books for
like you know five dollars or something so I don't regret the purchase like I said it might be a
fun thing to throw on it Halloween again but that's a ghost bump I remember I saw like an 11 30
p .m. ghost bumps alone on a Tuesday night at the Grove and I was like this is getting dark this
is getting dark yeah I thought that about my life a billion times this is getting dark but I thought
it about your life yeah I hope you thought about your own life too job because my point one finger
you have four more pointing back at you what do you what do you think I'm doing here three more
pointing back the thumb goes out the thumb never goes back I point all four I point possible to do
well I'm triple join it um can you see this cat on my shoulder like a parrot with a pirate I was very
close to buying a cat and then I realized after the six month mark they have dead eyes no matter
what kind of fucking cat it is my cat doesn't have dead eyes I just I can see him pants that doesn't
look like a friendly thing here's what I would say Joe you and I are yes you and I are cats and
that's the beauty of it you can recognize yourself and them they're standoffish um but then again
when you're watching a movie you need something on your lap to pet they're there they don't make noise
you can leave them home alone for a week I recommend it all right fair enough just left onto my kitchen
table even though it's not allowed to be up there I see um I saw my second feature was a little picture
I've always wanted to see called Betty blue um this is the kind of movie that like a lot of uh college
dudes in the 80s apparently like had the poster on their wall and you know it's uh it was a big
crossover French hit on erotic drama if you will and I thought it was great it was one of the
best looking movies I've ever seen I loved the way it was shot I thought the lead couple had
amazing chemistry there are sex scenes in this that are very erotic including the opening like five
minute sex scene where they it's one of those where everyone involved kind of says without saying that
they actually fucked because the couple actually fell in love um so you're essentially watching porn
in a mainstream movie which is always exciting it's um it's very long I watched the director's cut of
it which was like three hours I also watched the documentary where they were like you know half the
people involved were like he didn't need to do this director's cut the movie's better at two and
etc but I got caught up in the world I loved it it's a long romance it's the kind of thing that like
the English patient was doing but I remember being bored out of my absolute scold by the English
patient this couple's like young hot kind of punk rock funny interesting and I'd dug it if you're
into like an erotic drama check her out it looks great Beatrice Dolly is the woman's name she still
acts somewhat there's lots of dick there's lots of graphic nudity it's on a criterion channel at the
moment check her out I like I saw I it was a rewatch I hadn't seen it in a long time but I watched Tim
Burton's dark shadows I just bored one night wanted to kind of put something brainless on so I
turned it on I got to tell you and I actually texted you this I was about an hour into this thing
and I'm like man this is like a lost Tim Burton classic this is awesome like why didn't this do well
like it's everything you want out of a Burton movie it starts as this gothic horror thing and it's the
there's actually legitimately like horror type sequences in it and it's vampires and witches and
all this shit and I was like this is fucking great and even when he comes into the modern in modern times
meaning into the 70s it's very moody and very well done and it was super cool and I was really really
into it and then it starts to actually get legitimately funny yeah and I was like man this is like
cool this is everything you loved about Tim Burton back in the day like Peewee's big adventure
in Beetlejuice like it had a true mood and atmosphere yet it was very funny whatever
and then it's I remember the scene where it happened it just goes sideways they have this big
party an Alice Cooper plays at the party and you can see that this is where the studio got
something happens because they are cutting back to Alice Cooper doing almost full songs through
this sequence and you're like what happened here that they had to fill this out with Alice Cooper
having Alice Cooper perform in Wayne's World felt dated in 1991 the only there's a funny joke where
he goes the Chloe Grace Moretz says we should get Alice Cooper for the party and Johnny Depp is like
we would get this Alice Cooper and then when Alice Cooper is playing he looks through binoculars to see
what he looks like and he goes ugliest woman I have ever seen which is kind of a funny joke but
I was into it man and I actually kind of thought now the ending was okay but kindly suck kind of
suck whatever anyway I don't know it was half good man it made me think that Tim Burton might
still have something tank but as I say that the movie is at this point at least 10 years old so
you know yeah I mean I don't remember enjoying anything about Dark Shadows so I can't say I'm
eager to watch it again but I don't remember thinking it was much special and I don't even see his
stuff anymore I didn't see Dumbo and I didn't see maybe one or two of the other ones but we've
talked about him before I mean it's quite a graph that man's career has where it's just up up up up
and then the deepest of dips that just goes on and on and on yeah is it is it money my bed is
it's money you get that much money you're like even if I fuck this up I can go home and fuck my
gorgeous wife and have all this money and who cares I feel like that's where he's at he does not
seem engaged anymore yeah I don't what was even his last movie Dumbo I want to say oh yeah well
god I tried to watch that that was brutal yeah I didn't do it all right anyway um I saw a picture
that I had never seen I don't know what made me watch it I think I just saw it go by on HBO Max I believe
it's called final analysis uh dick gear Kim Basinger and it's directed by Phil Joanoo or Phil Hwanoo
who is one of the most interesting stories in all of of directing it's like uh you reminds me of
Jeremiah Cheechic who did commercials then Christmas vacation then Benny and June and then like
didn't work uh it's like even now like wouldn't people be going oh people still watch christmas occasion
every year it's the highest rated movie every year maybe we should talk to the director but
the Hollywood doesn't work that way they want new uh Phil Joanoo or Hwanoo was a protégé of Spielberg
Spielberg saw one of his early shorts and loved it and uh gave him the job directing three o 'clock
hi which is a beloved cult classic shot like a spaghetti western um but it's you know your standard
kids got to beat up the bully movie and and sort of a lost beloved film of the 80s teen
teen movement then he did you two rattle and hum one of the most pretentious rock documentaries ever made
where they like go to Elvis's grave and shit like that um but a movie I loved when I was nine and loved
you too and then his career just kind of went haywire he did state of grace with Sean Penn which is a
decent kind of low low rent gangster movie final analysis was probably where it all ended he's a guy
with he loves the big hitch cocky and camera angles the swoops the dips the style and I love that too
Kenneth Branagh was big in that when he did like dead again and stuff you know just like
big almost operatic moves with the camera and shit I like that in a thriller you know Scorsese toyed
with that too and Cape Fear um I say why not have some fun with it visually thrillers now are always so
boring but um this this movie doesn't work at all but I admired how insane it was it's Kim Basinger
Umatherman plays her younger sister I learned from the Wikipedia page that Umatherman was married to Gary
Oldman which is an interesting fact that I had no idea of um basically Basinger plays a woman who
turns psychotic when she has a sip of alcohol which is a character she also played in blind date
like it's this blind date which is a comedy but um it's apparently a real disorder where if somebody
has a sip of alcohol they go nuts Richard Gears falling in love with her there's a bunch of there's a big
like you know fight out in a lighthouse where people are hanging from white houses um you know it's
kind of fun can't be trash and I can't recommend it but I also was sort of entertained throughout you
know it's one of those legal thrillers where there's like a lot of fucking for no real reason and
you know it's one of those early 90s deals it's moderately entertaining I would say
all right are you a dick gear fan I love the Mothman prophecies and I really like that movie he did
about when he lied and said he was Howard Hughes or whatever um okay I can't remember the name of
but you know I could take him or leave him I'm not you know I'm not hunting down Richard Gears movies
to watch but I got nothing against the guy Stallone fucking hates him did you ever hear that story
why does he hate him uh he said that they were on Richard Gears ended up I think getting fired
from Lord to flat bush but okay I guess they were in that together at some point and he
Stallone said like he was just an arrogant fucking kid and he got into the car one day during lunch
and he was sitting next to Stallone he was eating like a whole chicken and it was like dripping and
Stallone's like be careful don't get any of that on me and Richard Gears was like relax man and then
he spilled it on him I guess it came to blows or something but apparently Stallone hates this guy man
like to this day I think I might have heard at some point in the convoluted story of how it started
that Stallone was the initiator of the gerbil rumor honestly yeah no I'm that I'm laughing because
I believe it I maybe it was a reddit thread or something I maybe I googled how did this story start
you know it's like the rod Stewart calm story where they had to pump his stomach of calm you know
and you're like clearly somebody who hated rod Stewart dropped that to the press um but yeah I
think Stallone is rumored to have been culprit with that one I would love it if a rumor was going
around about me that I had so much come in my stomach that it had to be pumped I truly would enjoy
that rumor yeah yeah it's interesting it's not it's like that's a person who couldn't just say
rod Stewart is gay they had to be like maybe I'll go way over the top of the room where he was just
you know insatiable for come uh I did want to showcase in final analysis of supporting performance by
Eric Roberts where he's playing just a complete abusive monster uh he's the dick husband of
Kim Basinger the gangster husband I fucking love Eric Roberts he's all amazing he was he was one
of our best he just kind of fucked himself up for a long time with drugs and stuff you know yeah I mean
I've got I've obviously recommended star 80 is one of the best and darkest movies of the 80s it's
it's incredible and he's so good in it pop a granite village raster now you just if you see him he's
like the villain on an episode of Hawaii five oh or something it's tragic he was good in that movie
what Mickey Rourke about Crank was it called Crank no that's adjacent state the movie the movie about
Crank that had like Jason uh who was the kid from Rushmore Schwarzenegger yeah he's in it and uh
Mickey Rourke from Roberts and Schwarzenegger yeah Eric Roberts spun spun yeah he was good in that um
you know he pops up and stuff man he's great but oh I just remembered the father daughter thing
I was gonna tell okay was that last episode I believe it was but fine it was the oh we were talking
on the last episode about Jeff Lynn and Tony Bennett employing their daughters yeah and I was that
was this episode that was this episode yeah oh boy oh boy Jesus I've been at it I haven't had a
sip today folks uh our brains are dusty at this point um anyway uh the saddest father daughter
story I ever heard was Christopher Plummer going to see Amanda Plummer his daughter yeah play apparently
Amanda Plummer believe it or not it's a real fucking wild card uh so believe it apparently she's on
stage and she just breaks character and starts berating the audience oh no for sucking or something and
they said Christopher Plummer walked out because he was like I'm not gonna want you do this to yourself
you know like no that's tragic yeah it's brutal was she fucked up on drums or something or I think
she's just I think she's just one of those people she's just living on yeah living on the edge
she um when she is in that pulp fiction opening scene I mean she's one of the few people that plays
plays crazy and you sense that there's a lot of truth to the performance you know what I'm saying
she always had kind of wild eyes and shit Plummer you know maybe the mom was a wild card too
because Plummer always seemed like a totally chill dude but I guess I only really started seeing him
in things when he was a hundred years old so yeah now it's uh he's been around it's weird it's I've
in recent years I've caught him in things that where he was very young and I was like Jesus he's
just been around I there was a while where I thought he was like a Danny I yellow type like
didn't start acting until he was like 60 right or whatever you know but uh or like how my dad
told me when I was 23 and hadn't landed a writing job yet told me about how Dennis Frons wasn't
successful until he was 55 right thanks thanks dad listen I definitely the same situation I would like
to hear stuff like that for my parents yeah my parents will say things like have you thought about
maybe at some point you could get a job yeah you know outside of energy I would love it if they said
not that they're not supportive they believe in me greatly they're a fan of everything I do but
yeah be nice if they said you know some guys will hit a big till they're 55 right well before you
start loving him too much he did send me a letter over pandemic telling me that it's there's no shame
in bag and groceries which I agree with you dad I don't think there is but like to to say that when I'm
15 years into a career is an interesting interesting piece of advice to give your son he's already
feeling uh very insecure the presumption of it is is you know it is by the way I was a grocery cash
year for three years I always hate when people are like what am I gonna do work at McDonald's I'm like
you know a lot of your fans work at McDonald's you son of a bitch I begged groceries at one point and
I do think there's a lot of shame in it but I would do it in a little leather outfit while a woman
spanked me well that's I mean look if it's between a consenting man and a consenting woman so
be it if that's your fantasy but you ever get up on the conveyor belt and do it yeah I would doggy
style it on the conveyor belt nice nice and I would say pretend I'm running away from you yeah is it
moved wet cleanup on aisle me that's the lady all right folks listen our movie today
is the shutter original the boys of county hell which Pat wants to call the boys of summer
I've often wanted to call it I keep wanting to call the boys of musky holler what is that I've
never heard of musky holler not something it's another one of these that's our pet name for your
asshole oh yeah that's the musky holler because I would often yodel into it and hear the echo come back
when we were romantically involved um holler I gotta look at hollow sorry musky hollow it's actually
a good name I mean when you're in Ireland they say oh you know he's he's the guy from county cork or
whatever it's kind of a clever name but if you don't know it's Irish it's a confusing title as well
the film is Irish which times as tough and musky holler was a creep show episode that's what I'm thinking
oh okay anyway with started David Arquette yeah Joe tell us a little bit about the picture interesting
little film uh clearly uh you know it's part of this wave of movies that's coming out right now that I
think is that I think it's a great little wave that's happening and certainly the film I'm trying to
get made as part of this or would be part of this uh but you know there's a lot of movies being made
on modern budgets using modern techniques that are clearly nods to 80s films and 80s style of horror
without being um self -aware 80s takeoffs you know that's not like they're adopting 80s music and
shooting things in 80s lights and you know having people act in 80s fashion or whatever they're just
throwbacks to the kinds of stories they told back then and they're done through a modern lens and I
think it's a great wave I think it's a lot of fun and this certainly falls right into that wheelhouse
it immediately begins with two people walking an Irish countryside and you think immediately of
um American Weir Wolf and London sure they go into a small pub uh and are
are you know and they even make that American Weir Wolf and London joke they're warned about staying
you know are you gonna warn us to stay off the the morrow is what I forget what they say yeah um
and you find out the boors the moors that's right sorry yeah and you do find out that in that
scene that this town is a dark secret but they kind of do it in a comedic way and it's funny
and to and the way it's translated to you the viewer is you also don't believe in this local secret
just as the or local myth excuse me just as the town's people don't believe in the local myth and
it's the complete opposite of American Weir Wolf and London it's a town that thinks all of the tourists
that come there are robes instead of being the people that warn them to flee uh and the story
or the myth and the legend surrounding this town is that it's where Bram Stoker wrote Dracula
it's where he based his novel where he met the the first ever vampire that the novel was based on
so you know where it's going obviously this vampire will be returning and bad shit will be happening
and it's only a matter of time and and it goes from there uh a very I'd say light horror film
it's bloody it's gory but it's quite funny uh at times genuinely funny not gag funny like really
like character funny at times which I enjoyed a lot um that aspect of it I thought was good um
and then uh you know so that that's the basic you know before we discuss and I want to say too much
no I I feel like you definitely liked it a bit more than I but I enjoyed it it had a definite charm
to it my I guess my grievances with it would be you know sometimes it's just simply the trappings of
low budget you know it's like and a lot of shutter stuff is very low budget um you know it just looks
a little too much like something some guys shot it with a with a dv camera out in the countryside
but you know if you don't have the money you don't have the money my other real issue was that the
characters were not really they were developed well I mean they went into some of their relationships
the father -son thing and the dead mother and so on and so forth but they all felt a little one note
to me I was sort of rooting for them as a collective but it was hard for me to really attach to anyone
in the cast because they all felt sort of the same I don't know how else to explain it um but I didn't
love it I am Irish I recently went to Ireland so I like that aspect of it it definitely has a charm
it definitely has uh potential in terms of of these filmmakers going forward
but for me the the attacks the you know they they all were jump scares you know there was
the movie was very very quiet a lot of times I hate this just I'm trying to watch it at midnight
you know upstairs but it's like the movie is very quiet and you keep turning it up turning it up
and then somebody jumps out and then the music blasts to like an insane level they do that
about 10 times and that's kind of the limit of the movie's scares so to me it got a little repetitive
it felt a little like a sci -fi channel horror movie and I should know I wrote one
um a lot of these shutter movies are feeling like that kind of sci -fi thing where it's just kind of like
okay this is way better than the creep shows this is way better than a lot of stuff I've seen
premiering on shutter um but it's still not quite what I would consider a great horror movie
and I'm fine with the made for sci -fi feel some of these things I'm glad that there's a horror version of
that now and you know and like we've said about shutter it's nice that now the directed dev would it
would have been directed DVD 20 or 30 years ago is now just directly to the subscriber and right into
the hands of the audience member that would want to see this right which I think is great um the movie
it's an interesting story it's interesting this is the town where the original vampires from bram
stoker was here and wrote the story based on this the bar is called stokers or the stoker because of
that that they all hang out in um that that's the best aspect of the movie I mean if this was just
done in New Jersey or something I'd be like oh god like another one of these generic horror movies
the Irish feel the bram stoker backstory you know the pile of rocks that supposedly houses this
vampire that stuff's all the art is the best aspect of the film in my opinion I agree uh but what's
funny is is we have different uh criticisms here because for a film that you thought played very
traditionally I was actually disappointed that they went into so many new directions with the vampire
lore I thought it got to a point where they changed so many rules it just to me felt like you're just
changing things for the sake of changing them and it's not making it any more interesting to me it's
quite frankly making it more convoluted so for instance you don't turn into a vampire if you get bit
by a vampire they just kill you and drink your blood you can only be turned into a vampire if one of the
stones that that covers the vampire's grave cuts you a vampire can only be kept in the ground if a
pile of stones is over his grave when the original vampire finally rises he's able to draw blood
miraculously from your body without touching you there were all these things where I was just like
I just kind of don't care like like there's no need for the vampire to get close to you
because it can sustain itself on the blood it's pulling from your bodies to such an extent
that people at one point and throughout the entire town are comatose because they've lost so much blood
um so why would he ever need to get near you so why would there ever be a scary encounter at that point
and also why is he able to do that that doesn't make any sense to me um
why does all the blood when he pulls it from your body then go to a lair that he has the
fuck does that what wasn't just go to him where you know uh why is it that you have to be in a certain
proximity like and so if you're two inches to the left he can't do it if you're two inches to the right
he can uh it was there was a lot of stuff like that in this movie where I was like this is just
making it confusing to me and then on top of it all there's a full one act setup of this vampire
ancient vampire rising from the grave that then diverts into this mystery about how one of the kids
dies uh one of the main character kids in this group of like drunk kids in the town dies
but he dies because he touches the rock and gets cut by the rock and then because of that you find out
later he's not dead he's now a vampire his parents are hiding him uh and trying to keep him alive and
then the other vampire that's been killing people is also a vampire but not the original guy
and also not a vampire because he was bitten but because the dad of the kid who got turned
went and scratched this guy with a rock so he could blame his sons
killings on this it was it i mean i'm talking myself in circles here you're like guys this is too
like what the fuck yeah you're off to a great start here and for a 90 minute movie that's a lot of
convolution to to follow i don't i don't disagree with you but i i i didn't think necessarily that the
story uh was too straightforward but the scares the that sort of every 10 minutes of
and they somebody slams their hands down on a piano um that got repetitive to me i agree with you
the story with the story was so convoluted there were several points i didn't know it was going on
and as i pointed out to you as well joe i sometimes like to follow along with a wikipedia page
um or at least glance at it especially if i'm confused about a plot detail this movie doesn't have
one everything has a wikipedia page like shutter do a little more than the bare minimum shutter please
because you're yeah i you know i know you're you're not netflix but like you got to start spending
a little money over there yeah no i agree um the the but this was the most disheartening thing about
this convoluted plot to me was when you finally see the ancient vampire when they get all this other
bullshit out of the way yeah he looks awesome he's like a really cool scary looking vampire like one of
the coolest vampires i've seen since since old men's drag in Dracula since uh since salam's lot from
the 70s he looks awesome and you're like this is all i wanted like a movie where it's just this crazed
beast on the loose and these drunk irish kids who have been kind of fucking off their whole lives
finally have to come into their own and protect their town that they kind of dismiss and and have a
shitty attitude about like that's it like that that's an awesome movie man like i would have had a blast
watching this thing and i don't know why it was it felt it felt such a need to be more than that um
i appreciate trying to do things different but i remember when they reminded me a little bit of
the descent creatures yeah that you know but um you know it's possible that that required a lot of
special effects and money and they didn't they couldn't do a big movie like that but you know there's
some effects here they had a budget you know it just it takes a really long time to get going and when
it does you're kind of like oh yeah why wasn't it just this the the the movie the movie very easily
could have and i'm not saying they should have copied it but the movie could have been friday you could
have been there's one threat that threat is able to create some minions the minions are threat get
through the minions get to the head of the snake that's the end and this was like it's not even the
main threat creating the minions the minions are created if one of them just happens to cut
themselves on a rock from the main threats grave it's like cut Jesus Christ guys like just yeah this is
really just overly complicated man yeah so uh you know look i overall i thought it was
for the most aside from my complaints of the writing being murky i thought overall it was
fairly well executed there were some really cool moments that was very well acted and i thought it
was very funny and i think it's and there's enough there to keep you're into attention i'm not quite
sure why it has an 84 percent on rotten tomatoes i think that's high for this film i would put it
at about a 65 but yeah i've enjoyed way worse than 65 for sure it it you know we've talked about a lot
of horror movies we talked about a lot of low budget shutter horror movies we talked about creep show
etc and this is a nice considerable step above those movies you know it's like it's it's good but it never
to me crossed over into great i just felt like these are pretty confident filmmakers who seem to know
what they're doing they while they didn't give me amazing characters i felt like they presented people
that they had at least thought about who had interesting lives who had interesting dilemmas between
them so i do think it's a step above the usual fair for direct to shutter stuff but um yeah i think even
64 is a bit high it's it's a very average horror movie but at this time in in the world of entertainment
that's a good thing a slightly above average horror movie or an average horror movie yeah yeah so um
you know i'd say i put my hog sideways on this one yeah i mean the way you were talking at first
Joe i thought you were a definite hog up i hope i didn't bring down your opinion uh hug no you didn't
my hog now no in fact pinkstone was the one that recommended this to me and once he told me to check
it out i went and looked up the rot and tomatoes rating and read some reviews and i was like this is
really well reviewed and that's when i text you it said i guess we should do this movie it seems like
people are really responding strongly to it yeah um but um you know i went in with high hopes
and um by the middle of act two i was kind of like all right um this isn't going to take off
anymore than i think it is but it's still pretty well done you know that's my exact sentiment
it doesn't quite take off but there maybe their second one will um i would say my hog is at about
the spot it would be at like one minute after finishing sex so like there's a plumpness to it a
sponginess to it but it's it's down all right i get it though yeah you get it i get it my hog is now
up after that description uh folks joderosa comedy on twitter and calm um i almost said a comedy
central jesus christ and instagram joderosa comedian on facebook check out the taste buds jesus
yes check out check check out the taste buds tech goes to his own iosha taste buds podcast yeah uh if
you want to hear more of me having opinions on things uh me and salvo kano every monday a new episode drops
11 a .m. on youtube video audio everywhere you can get it every week and interesting to see little food
network taking a bite out of us okay food network on twitter taking a bite oh they retweeted
network on now food now we're going to twitter their own tweet what's better pb and jay or or
grilled cheese literally our exact episode from two three weeks ago anyway uh they didn't even shout
you out oh no no they just oh that sucks uh folks i have the Patrick Walsh at twitter and instagram
rarely on either but i am there i recently did an episode of the great vince avril and jessie pops
and our old friend narlie's podcast monday night beers mic burns is also generally a host but he was
not there that week um it's a very funny conversation we just sat and drank beers and talk
and we'll be back next time with sauce spiral and another feature we'll try to like you know
viral already it's out already it's coming out one week maybe two weeks oh i got to take my ass
to the theater yeah it's not out yet but maybe if not if not friday maybe next week all right so
probably spiral and something else maybe something else we were talking about doing another q &a
sometime soon yes thank you to uh mla for all your hard work thank you for uh you know
keeping the instagram popping and and uh keeping the fans in the loop i assume the facebook page is still
going and uh we're almost done with the pandemic everybody i we weren't you know we uh we've been through a
lot of shit this year i hope we helped i appreciate the messages from those of you who i know we have
helped oh you certainly helped us with we certainly yes absolutely we are very grateful to be
keeping this afloat and alive because we love doing it uh that's it joe would you like to say goodbye
to us we'll see you next time we'll see you in hell