I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, and when the sound of your screams becomes
a thing of my dreams, you know I'll say, I'll see you in hell, you know I will, I'll see
you in hell, you know I will.
Merry Christmas, Merry Christmas, Merry -
This Christmas, fireside -
Jingle bells, jingle bells.
Rudolph the Red -Nosed Reindeer.
Why are there no -
Nefar -
Is there a -
Hair tree.
Most recent - wow, it's like an Altman film in here today.
Is this a, um, because of all the overlapping dialogue folks, that's what I meant.
Not because of the quality of the podcast.
We're more of a Dr. T and the women level quality podcast.
Not Nashville, we're not shooting the, the site's too high.
My question is, has there been a hit Christmas song since
Mariah Carey's All I Want for Christmas is You?
Obviously a deserving addition to the canon,
but I don't even know if we've had any attempts at adding something to the canon.
Um, no, I don't think there has been, um, you know, there have been Christmas songs,
you know, you'll hear about like, you know, Toby Keith just put out a beer for my Christmas
reindeers, or whatever, you know, some shit like that, but they don't catch on.
Most humously, after his death they released a -
He's dead?
Beer for - oh, he's got cancer.
Did he die?
He might've died. I think he did.
Yeah, February 5th, 2024. Oh boy, young man.
Jesus.
I don't know any of his - no, I do know some of his songs, I know.
How do you like me now?
Well, and he had a song called Beer for My Horses, right?
He did.
Yeah, that was his, that was a big one, I think.
And he had a seemingly the original Red Solo Cup country song since, since there have been
5 million songs surrounding the magic of the Red Solo Cup.
Um, speaking of Red, uh, today we are reviewing -
A great transition show.
Yeah, for Christmas, Red won.
Okay.
Yeah, Red won, which, uh, hold on, I've been sitting on this joke for a week.
Red won, uh, and folks, I'm not talking about the reason I had to go to the free clinic.
Hi -o!
There we go.
Red won, uh, and I'm not talking about the end of the sentence I say when people ask if I've
ever read a Jane Austen novel. When I say no, I've never read one.
Oh, I thought you were going to say, yeah, I read one.
Oh no, I didn't even read one.
Really? Geez.
Um, yeah, we'll get to Red won, which, uh, Dwayne the Rock Johnson.
I don't know if you, I think I've talked about before this man's Instagram,
which is one of the most disturbing places you can find yourself on the internet.
Oh yeah.
And my friend sent this to me last night.
I'm just going to read it real quick.
This is on Instagram.
Our little Christmas movie, Red won, shattered a viewing record for at Amazon,
at prime, at prime video with 50 million viewers this past weekend.
Red won has a very long shelf life.
Quick pause.
How the fuck do you know?
It's been out for a week.
Do you not know what that term means?
You don't, you can't say something has a long shelf life until at least a year has passed.
Uh, Red won has a very long shelf life with multiple verticals.
What's that mean?
My guess is like in a graph, like how it, the, the things are going hot up, you know,
but he's talking to us like we're in a, a quarter Q four shares meeting.
These people lose touch, man.
They lose.
He's talking to his fans like children and he's, he's using business terms that
you and I don't understand and we're in the business.
They lose touch, man.
They're, they're out the door.
They're out, they're out the door, baby.
Red won has a very long shelf life with multiple verticals.
Kudos to our partners at Amazon for their strategic win.
That's just getting started.
Well, what do you mean getting started?
You think there's going to be an awards push?
Well, what he's referring to is, is I read an article today.
I never thought we'd be reading this much about Red won,
but there was an article that went out today.
I can't remember who put it out, but they said like,
apparently everybody was just waiting for it to hit streaming because
apparently the streaming numbers are like through the roof on this thing.
Everyone's broke.
You can go see a movie that you feel pretty confident is going to suck at
the theater for $25 a ticket, or you can watch it for free on Amazon.
Most importantly, massive thanks to you and your families around the world who,
who tuned in.
We made a little history.
A minus cinema score, 90 % audience rating.
No mention of that critical score.
Not too shabby and make sure you leave cookies and tequila for the big guy.
A little shout out promotion for his tequila brand.
Sick.
Speaking of bombs.
Yeah.
And apparently this, um, uh, Craven the Hunter movie, the latest one of this
in the Sony Marvel verse, the Sony Marvel verse, by the way,
which is entirely constructed around Spider -Man, right?
It's all Spider -Man villains.
They're doing these one -offs of, and they're not allowed to put Spider -Man
in any of the movies because he is on loan to Marvel right now.
So they keep making Spider -verse movies that they're not allowed to put Spider -Man
in or even kind of mention him.
Like he has to be scrubbed from this.
And they say like, well, you know, that might upset our little red friend.
I believe that's what they are, have been reduced to like, like on the
Gotham TV show, which was a good TV show, they weren't allowed to say Joker.
So they had to just kind of like really dance around it.
And, um, anyway, this thing, apparently.
Do you think this might've been the Riddler?
No, but think somebody very similar.
He's got a, he's got a laugh thing too, but he's less about.
Just change the story at that point.
Um, this thing apparently is like, I'm reading, watching reviews of this thing.
People are like, this is astoundingly the worst Marvel movie that's ever been made so far.
They're like, this is Madame Web bad, and people are more mad at this because they're like,
nobody cared about Madame Web.
Yeah.
I was watching Screencrusher's review and the guy was like, it's not as bad as Madame Web,
but I'm more offended because this is a character I actually liked and cared about,
and it's terrible.
Like apparently this thing is terrible.
I haven't seen a mention of it, a trailer of it.
I go to the movies all the time.
I have not seen a theatrical trailer for it, so I guess they were trying to bury it.
But that guy's not a big enough star to open a movie either.
Aaron Tyler Jones or whatever, the guy with the 70 year old wife.
We'll, we'll talk about him on the next episode because he's in the next movie we're reviewing,
but he.
Oh yeah.
I don't think he's a great actor.
Like I think he's okay.
Like, and I don't think he's.
I think weirdly he's captured the public imagination because I mean, A, he's hot,
but B, he's got that wife twice his age and they got daughters that are like three years younger
and America's obsessed with this age gap because she met him.
She, she was a director and met him when he was like 19 or something, something weird.
I don't know.
I don't know anything about that.
Oh, that's all I know about the man.
His wife is, is 57 and he is 34.
That's like, yeah.
All right.
Yeah.
I mean, for her getting some young tush.
Well, talk about people are mad because of the ages they were when they met
and called it grooming and whatever else.
But like that age gap is very standard if you reverse the sexes, ladies and gentlemen.
It is.
And guys, it's not grooming when the person is 19.
Can we stop with this enough?
Uh, she got a, he is a piece of arse.
Good for her.
She did very well.
Yeah, I actually see, I kind of liked him in fall guy, but he was completely out acted
and out charmed by Gosling.
He never should have been in a movie with Gosling because it makes him look less than.
And I liked him, I guess in, in bullet train, which I don't remember much about,
but he's got a certain charisma.
I guess it's just not happening.
And they're, they said his, uh, candidacy for bond was revoked after they saw the
numbers for this new movie.
Craven.
He's, he's, he wouldn't be a good bond.
He wouldn't.
I honestly think, and they're two races to do it, but, uh, Elba is probably the best
choice.
Elba be awesome.
Yeah.
He is James Bond.
I feel like if I met him, I would feel like I met James Bond in real.
Life.
I think Elba's is an excellent choice.
And he would be, he would be fantastic.
And if they're not going to go with Elba.
Yeah.
Let's get it back to the Connery clones.
Get me the, get me the older man with the, with the librarian part in his hair.
You know what I mean?
Like get back to that enough with this blonde flowing hair bullshit.
You know, I, Craig, I know Craig had the part, but it's like,
in his hair, I mean, but Craig always bothered me.
The blue eyed blonde bond had never sat right with me.
Yeah.
I liked the change up and I did like Craig, but I agree.
We could use a little bit more charm.
And I got, I mean, it'd be nuts, but Hugh Grant's probably the same age as Roger
Moore was doing some of those later pictures.
Yes.
He's too old for it.
Don't get me wrong, but yes.
So Hugh Grant in an interview, like I'm sure he's impossible to work with.
He's one of the few people on earth that consistently makes me laugh out loud.
Everything he says is funny.
He's such a grumpy asshole.
Yeah.
I love it.
We are when they're like, how come you're not bumbling and charming anymore?
He's like, I did that for the camera.
I've never liked that.
I thought that's what people wanted me to do.
So I just did it.
Yeah.
He hasn't quite the, he was great in the undoing with Kidman, the HBO show,
but I would love to see him play a true, great classic villain.
And unfortunately, Heredit should have been it and wasn't it.
I think he's got a great villain part in him.
I liked him in Paddington as the bad guy.
Paddington too.
My friend, Pat Contri, who's a YouTuber and game aficionado.
I talked to him on the phone yesterday and he was like, you know, he always wants to
know what I've seen because he knows we do this show.
And he was like, did you see Heretic?
And I was like, yeah.
And he's like, what the hell, man?
And he started going off about it and it brought up almost a rage in me about the movie.
He was pointing out shit that we didn't think of that was wrong with it.
I was like, yeah, you're right, man.
I think because about halfway through, I stopped looking at the movie with an analytical mind
and switched to, all right, this just isn't going to make sense.
Let me just get whatever I can out of it.
I never really did not like that movie.
No, no, no.
And to have it, you know, for my consideration now as a real, other than Grant, I don't know
what they think they're going to get nominated for.
It's like read the screenplay for Heretic.
I'm like, no, it's bad.
Yeah, it, yeah.
These FYC things, I was telling Joe how to do it because I have a lot of friends being
like, where are the, where the fuck are the screeners?
And I'm going to go home for Christmas tomorrow morning and my family is going to be in chaos
because they're all waiting for the screeners and I don't have any.
They send you a link.
You got to download an app now.
And it's not just like the screener app.
You got to download the Paramount app, the Warner Brothers app, the Sony app.
And each one will have like one or two for my consideration.
It's ridiculous.
Absolute scam.
Absolute way to get, I've been saying this for years about these apps.
Yeah.
As soon as they started to be like, you got to do it through the app.
I'm like, this is all just information collecting.
It's all just spying on me.
Do you accept our cookies?
All that bullshit.
And now they're doing it with the screeners to track, you know, it's just.
I'm sure there are people listening who are like, oh, you get sent all the new movies
for free to your house.
Like what a terrible thing.
No, I know.
I know it's a good problem to have.
It's just annoying.
You know, it used to be like a second Christmas and now we got to type in, you know,
A 8 Y J K ampersand exclamation point every time we want to watch a fucking movie.
I disagree with you.
It's not a good problem to have.
I earn these screeners by paying my dues.
Okay, that's fair.
Yeah.
And I pay those dues whether I don't work for the entire year or not.
And I get nothing in return unless I make a certain amount of money.
I get healthcare that is limited to a very finite period of time.
The least they could do is give these damn screeners.
You've changed my mind.
You've made a great point.
I pay 2 % of my income to these people.
They can send me a fucking DVD of a Nora.
Okay.
Well, I'll tell you the one that pissed me off the most,
and I've bitched about this in the past with the screeners.
Excuse me.
Amazon, I've always said you could end world hunger
with the money fucking Amazon wastes on their screeners,
especially when everybody already has Amazon Prime
and you can watch this shit already with your membership.
They're the most pointless screeners.
Now Amazon is...
But then Amazon would do all this ridiculous packaging with it,
which was so gross because it was like passive bribery
to get you to go, oh, look what Amazon did.
I'll vote for them.
What Joe's talking about is they would send you like a $40 jewelry box.
And you'd open it up and it would have like a ballerina
as like an advertisement for Black Swan or whatever the fuck.
And it's like, okay, so times however many people are in the writers guild,
plus whatever other promotion and everything you're doing,
like give me a fucking break.
So yeah, so Amazon now, they, you probably got this,
they sent out the packaging with no screeners.
Now it's just this like gift box you open and it's just,
it's like a box of secrets where you're supposed to keep digging through it
to get cards that just say, by the way,
they don't even name the things they want you to consider.
They're saying, so come visit us over here and see what we have.
It's like, get out of my face and don't take up room in my mailbox with this bullshit.
This is a waste.
This serves no purpose.
Yeah, to tell you, it's a true testament to how fucked up this award season shit is
that like, I don't know if you remember last year,
but there was this great, great movie and the lady got nominated for it.
It was called, I want to say Two Leslie.
Yes, an excellent movie about an alcoholic named Andrea Riseborough.
Mark Maron was in the film.
Movie probably cost, you know, a nickel.
Allison Janney was in the movie, but it was a really good indie.
And she had a couple people in Hollywood, you know, actor friends, whatever,
were like, please vote for my friend.
You know, they don't have the money to give her an Oscar campaign.
So please vote for my friend.
She's so great in this movie.
If you see it, you'd know.
And it wound up being highly controversial.
Why?
Because it was like, well, wait a minute.
You can't, here we go.
I'm going to get this specifics.
The Andrea Riseborough controversy explained.
Nope.
No.
Okay.
Here we go.
Surprise best actress nomination.
She's a 41 year old British actor.
She was in Mandy.
Is she Mandy in Mandy?
Yes.
Okay.
She's a chameleon, so she's had a lot of parts, but Hollywood doesn't really know her.
And she's amazing in the movie.
So what was unusual about her campaign?
A typical Oscar race plays out like squid game.
A large number of hopefuls are winnowed down to a surviving few.
To stay in the conversation until the very end, it helps to win critics awards and nominations.
She lagged on both counts.
She wasn't getting nominated.
During the second week of January, days before voting for the Oscars began,
a bunch of movie stars took to social media on her behalf.
Edward Norton told his 2 million followers.
She gave the most fully committed, emotionally deep, physically harrowing performance I've seen in a while.
The next day, Gwyneth Paltrow announced she should win every award and the ones that haven't been invented.
Other celebrities, Amy Adams, Kate Winslow, Jennifer Aniston, blah, blah, blah,
started to say, yeah, she deserves this.
This movie can't afford any FYC ads for your consideration.
So for some reason, this is a problem.
So and Melissa Leo had a similar thing when she took out her own ad campaign years ago for the fighter.
She bypassed the for your consideration ad complex, opting to wage a week -long war
powered by word of mouth instead of an expensive multi -month campaign
involving round tables, parties, red carpets, etc.
And people were pissed and remain pissed.
Now there's talk about banning this in the future.
They're basically saying you have to play our fucked up game if you want to get an award.
And I think that that's insane.
The director of The Woman King, which was a movie that came and went with Viola Davis,
she said she's a black woman.
The social capital helped propel her to a nomination.
Black women in this industry don't have that power.
There is no groundswell from privileged people with enormous social capital to get behind black women
and there never has been.
Now look, is that a valid issue?
Yeah, but what are we talking about?
Actors are allowed to say, hey, I really admired this performance.
What are we doing?
Yeah, I don't know.
Meanwhile, I've got five million for your consideration things from the movie Saturday Night,
a movie I liked okay, but that critics have despised.
They're flooding me with this.
I've got screeners.
I've got screenplays.
I've got come to this, you know, open table event with Jason Reitman and all that.
I would much rather Edward Norton look me in the eye and tell me he saw one of his favorite
performances in years than buy into this hype on a movie that nobody likes.
That's why it's awesome when.
So two things.
Number one, that's why it's awesome when Kevin Bacon does this a lot.
Where he'll just go on his Instagram and it'll be him like walking out of a theater
and he'll be like, I got to tell you guys about the movies I saw this week.
You know, he blinked twice.
I remember he was like, Zoe Kravitz, girl, you are a director.
Like I was like, this is awesome because it's a very passive way of him doing the same thing.
And I think it's very cool that he does it and I don't know if he even does it with that
motivation, but I'm sure he's aware like this will help if I do this,
which I think it's very cool that he does that.
The other thing is, this is why I didn't get all swept up and teary eyed when Brendan
Frazier and Short Round were being like, dreams can come true and you can come back and be
recognized.
I was like, guys, so you couldn't have been that down and out if you had the means to
access the funding it took to get you the recognition for the comeback.
You don't just get it.
You pay for it.
And if somebody is willing to pay for it for you, you're not that down and out.
Come on, man.
You know?
Yeah, totally.
I mean, reading further into this is the New York Times report on it.
They almost, there was a full investigation and they almost rescinded,
took back her Academy Award nomination.
So they're basically saying, telling your fans, your friends, recommending a performance
to somebody is wrong and sending a million emails to everyone in the guild advertising
your average movie is all right.
And that is basically confirming this thing of like, you need money to play our game.
I think the Blythewood woman has kind of missed the point.
It's like, well, she's doing the same thing you are.
She's like, nobody's going to help me out.
I'll help myself.
Anyone can do the same.
Although now it'll lead to an investigation.
I will say, I do think and it's look, it's a situation that was not created by any of us.
It's a situation the industry has assisted in creating.
But we live in a world now where you can manipulate the numbers
and you can affect the algorithm and whatever.
So I will say that, years ago when I was first exposed to friends of mine
doing these email campaigns saying, I'm being considered for an Emmy or whatever.
Will you all please vote for me?
That kind of bothered me because I was like, what are you doing?
You're trying to, it always felt to me a little bit like you were trying to con
the system a little bit.
It's like when somebody puts out a new podcast and they go,
if all of my friends just listen once, it'll put us on the charts.
But that's not how your podcast should be rated.
Your podcast should get there because it's good and it has a following.
It shouldn't be a trick.
So I guess some of this is to combat that.
But at the same time, we didn't create that.
It's not our fault that that's the situation.
So, I mean, I don't know.
It all was very, you know, Pat, it's Christmas.
Let's be positive.
Yeah, that's always been a recurring theme of this podcast for sure, is staying positive.
Should we hit the corner?
Real quick, before we do, I have a glowing scary stuff.
All right.
Glowing.
Finally, after a year of great anticipation and a lot of advertising and whatever in the
video game community, Bethesda has released Indiana Jones and the Great Circle, exclusively
available on Xbox at the moment.
This game was announced and met with a lot of speculation initially because
Indiana Jones games in the past have been very hit or miss, very hit or miss.
LucasArts or Lucasfilm Games, whatever it's called now, hadn't released a really good
game in some time.
Obviously, there was a lot of fan disappointment with the last two Indiana Jones movies.
I didn't agree with, particularly with the last one.
And then on top of it all, it was a first person Indiana Jones game and people thought
that that was going to be weird.
Anyway, the game finally released, I got early, I paid for early access to get the game a
few days early on December 5th.
What do you pay?
It was like 30 bucks or something.
Oh my God.
To get like a week early.
But you also, if you're a Game Pass member, which I am, you got the game for free.
So you paid 30 bucks, you basically paid 30 bucks to get the game a week early and
then you just got the game.
You didn't have to pay for the game on top of it.
Anyway, I am very pleased to report that not only is the game being met with rave reviews,
it is everything I ever could have wanted in an Indiana Jones game.
You are the character, you feel like the character.
It puts you in the shoes of the character.
The story is awesome.
It takes place a year after Raiders.
Spoiler alert, if you're going to play the game, don't listen to what I'm about to say
because this is a nice surprise.
But the first level in the game, which is sort of the training level where you kind
of figure out how to play, is the opening of Raiders of the Lost Ark where you go into
the temple to get the idol and everything.
The story is fantastic.
There's two plus hours of cutscenes in the game where you feel like you're watching
an Indiana Jones movie and then when it goes from the cutscene into gameplay,
suddenly you forget, like you're sitting there thinking like, almost like,
I'm watching an Indiana Jones movie and then it'll say, you know, he'll be like,
I gotta go check out that temple or whatever it is and then it switches to first person
seamlessly and you're like, oh my God, that's right, I'm Indiana Jones.
I get to go do this.
It is such a wonderful experience.
The characters are awesome.
For the most part, all new characters.
Troy Baker plays Indiana Jones in this and he knocks it out of the park.
You forget that it's not Indiana, you forget that it's not Harrison Ford.
Tony Todd plays one of the villains in it.
He's awesome.
I think this was his potentially last role before his passing.
The entire cast is great.
The characters are great.
It's emotional.
It's fun.
It's awesome.
It's funny.
It feels like Indiana Jones.
It is an awesome, awesome, awesome experience and it's the first game I've played in a long
time with modern gaming where every night or whatever it is when I have time to go back
and play, I can't wait to jump back in and see what's going to happen next.
It's great, man.
It's great.
I can't recommend it enough.
It's an awesome game.
All right.
I bet I would enjoy an indie game.
Is it for PlayStation?
It comes to PlayStation next, I think in the spring.
They're going to release it for PlayStation.
And it's easy.
It's not an easy game, but I mean, it's easy to understand how to play it.
Which was such a smart move on their part because it keeps the momentum of the game going.
When you can remember what every button does, because the configuration is easy to remember,
your momentum goes.
You're not sitting in a standoff going, wait, how do I do this?
I have to hit X plus Y plus what?
It just moves.
It's user friendly.
It's challenging, but in all the right ways.
It's an awesome game.
And the soundtrack and sound design, all the sound effects that are so instrumental to an Indiana
Jones movie are in there and they're like thundering.
Like when you punch a guy, you feel it.
When you hit the whip, you feel it.
And the music is so on, I'm like, is this like John Williams shit they never used?
Like it's just, every part of it is perfect.
It's amazing.
It's an amazing experience and an amazing story.
All right.
Have you seen the new Superman trailer?
I saw a draft.
I didn't watch it yet.
All right, let's watch it between episodes and discuss.
Okay.
I'm just excited they're making a Superman movie.
I've always dreamed of having that kind of beloved character be immortalized in either a
or a TV project, just to sort of see that Superman taken from the comic book to the stage.
We've never seen it before.
It's very exciting.
Christ, couldn't care less.
All the reactions today have been about the dog crypto.
Yeah, that's a big thing because it's never been in, I guess, in any of the live action stuff.
But, and then James Gunn was like, it's like the secret is the dog's not really a good boy.
I'm like, so you're just ruining a movie that comes out a year from now.
Well, and we're going to have a dog plot twist.
Is that what we're going to have, James?
Anyway, let's get to the movie corn.
I have seen a lot.
I have certainly seen a lot of for your consideration type movies.
Um, some good, some bad.
I mean, speaking of Daniel Craig, I would love to start off with the movie queer.
Um, I don't know if you have seen Daniel Craig on the award circuit, but he is basically dressing,
sitting, acting, and talking as if he is, um, has just decided that he's a 60 year old gay man
and not playing a character.
It's very interesting.
I don't know if he is coming out or if he's about to come out, but
it's like he made the, um, the knives out guy gay, which was great.
Love that character.
And then now he's saying, I almost didn't play James Bond because of how masculine the character
was.
And it's like, that's a fucking lie.
Daniel Craig, stop it.
You needed that role.
You were not a household name and you probably heavily campaigned for it.
So stop it.
Yeah.
Um, but anyway, I think, I think it is great.
When any guy known for his masculinity shows you another side, especially a public figure,
Kurt Cobain was doing that for forever, you know, alluding to different.
I love that.
I'm just saying what he's doing seems a little odd and disingenuous, but, uh, queer is done by
Luca Guadagnino Guadagnino.
Is that correct?
Um, no, no, no, no.
This guy is making roughly two movies a year.
They're all critically acclaimed.
And I like a lot of what he does.
He did this asperio remake, which we liked a lot on this show.
He did call me by your name, which I thought was really good.
Bones and all with Chalamet, which I liked less.
And then challengers, which came out earlier this year, which is also in the Oscar race.
He's got two movies up for Oscars this year.
Challengers is incredibly fun and exciting and hot.
And I loved it.
I love that movie.
Queer was not for me.
I don't think it's because I'm not queer.
I think it's because it was a long and boring slog.
And it's, you know, uh, two hours, 20 minutes.
And the plot is literally Daniel Craig kind of wandering around, you know, he's like a
guy who's adrift.
It's based on a William S.
Burroughs book who did naked lunch.
I think I haven't read any of William Burroughs material, but I think it's safe to say from
all the movie adaptations that I would not be a fan of this guy.
It's just not for me.
I don't care.
William Burroughs was the guy who did all those like spoken word tracks in the 90s.
Wasn't it?
Yeah.
He did one with Nirvana.
And R .E .M.
Guadagnino is a great filmmaker.
I like what he does.
I like that he kind of puts sexuality front and center at a time when sexuality is usually
pushed to the back.
Um, but the movie just sits there.
It's in 1950s Mexico City.
An American expat played by Daniel Craig lives alone, wanders around, drinks too much,
hooks up with guys.
And then finally he meets this younger man and they have sort of a torrid affair, but
there's really very little story for a two hour, 20 minute movie.
It goes into very naked lunch type territory near the end where it becomes kind of more
surreal, but this is not a fun sit.
Um, if it's going to be notable at all, it's for its extreme sexuality, which is also not
as extreme as they've let on.
There's a couple of snowballing scenes, which is kind of new to mainstream movies.
Meaning, uh, yeah, you know, Daniel Craig will come in the gentleman's mouth and then
they make out and kind of pass the come back and forth.
Okay.
That's breaking some ground.
If you want to see that, uh, then this is the movie for you.
There's, there's some, you know, fairly, fairly, I don't know, juicy sex, gay sex
scenes in it, if that's what you want to watch.
Um, but the story, the acting, all of that just left me ice cold.
Joe, I'm doing all Christmas movies.
Uh, these are all rewatches except for one.
Um, but I'll start with, uh, Fred Claus.
Oof, I love Fred Claus.
Should I try it again?
I think you should.
I watched it for the first time last year and I was like, this is passable.
It's fine.
Second watch, uh, I loved it.
I was laughing a lot.
You know.
Well, things that were bad then seem good now.
For sure.
It's Vince Vaughn and Paul Giamatti and Kathy Bates.
Yeah.
You know, Kathy Bates plays the mom, uh, and Fred Claus is Santa Claus's older brother.
And, uh, Giamatti plays Santa and, uh, it's, it's, you know, it's, it's a little too
schmaltzy in places, which I would have liked the, like them to have done without, but whatever.
Um, you know, at the end of the day, you're there for Vaughn.
Elizabeth Banks is charming.
Uh, um, um, I can't believe I'm - what is wrong with me?
What's -her -name is in it.
She's great.
The lady from About a Girl and, and, uh, Dead Ringers.
Mini Driver.
No.
Dead Ringers, About a Girl...
About a Girl?
The - oh, uh, Rachel Weisz.
Rachel Weisz.
Yeah, she places -
She plays Vaughn's girlfriend in it.
She's very wonderful and charming.
Um, the guy from, uh, Best in Show that plays the gay guy.
Uh, I always love him.
John Michael Higgins.
Higgins, yeah.
He's sort of the main elf that becomes friends with Vince Vaughn.
Um, ludicrous, isn't it?
As one of the elves.
Of course he is.
But it's just, it's a - it's funny.
It's really funny.
It's Vince Vaughn doing Vince Vaughn, except he's the loser older brother of Santa Claus.
He hates Santa Claus because everybody loves him.
And he has to go to the North Pole to try to scam Santa out of money.
And, uh, and he learns to be a human or whatever.
You know, it's one of these jobs.
So, um, I enjoyed it.
I don't think you're going to be mad that you put it on.
It's a perfect thing to watch with your folks or something like that.
I recommend Fred Claus.
Love it.
Um, I saw a review on the Onion Navy Club,
which is a website that has really fallen apart lately.
But, um, they were talking about some new television show that I hadn't even heard of.
And they basically the headline, because everything has to be clickbait now was
the show would be good if it wasn't for a terrible lackluster performance from one of its stars.
And it worked on me.
I was like, I wonder who that is.
Sure enough, it was Common, who I have been speaking out against for 15 years.
This man makes ludicrous look like Lawrence Olivia.
I'm glad somebody finally called him out.
He is the least interesting actor alive.
Yeah, I'm not a big Common fan.
I'm not a big, I wasn't, I was, I'm not a fan of his rep.
I liked now Common when he first came out as a rapper, his name was Common Sense.
And he was a little more of like an offbeat sort of dos effects kind of rapper on his first album.
And then on his second album, he got a little more grounded.
And I think that's when he just became Common.
And then by the third album, every song was like, you know, let your inner light shine.
You're beautiful.
And I was like, I'm not into this anymore, man.
It's just too emotional for me.
Yeah, that world of like upbeat, positive rap that came around, you know,
maybe the best practitioner would be Jurassic Five, who I was dragged live
to a live show once and they were really good.
But like that genre I just can't get into where it's like, you gotta stay positive, baby.
Jurassic Five was a little more like party rap.
They had an old school throwback thing.
I liked Jurassic Five.
Yeah, they were really good live.
Common is way more like, let's talk about beauty and how it's defined.
You're like, I don't want to.
Yeah, and then you hear about his, you know, how he's actually treating the women he dates.
I don't know if you've ever done a deep dive into that.
He's not really practicing what he preaches.
I have not.
I saw a movie that since the moment I heard the title, I said, I'm going to see this movie.
Wild Horses couldn't drag me away from a film we've discussed on this show.
Night Bitch.
Oh yeah.
When Night Bitch showed up at my house for my consideration,
I was ecstatic because Night Bitch almost completely missed theaters.
It definitely lost money.
Nobody saw Night Bitch.
I really enjoyed it more than I even expected to.
And it's not just because I like the title.
The tagline is motherhood is a bitch.
And that's what it's about.
That's the whole thing.
That's the theme.
That's everything.
A woman played by Amy Adams in one of my favorite Amy Adams performances.
I don't know where she's been.
I think she was doing like Disney plus shows or something,
but like it was great to see her sink her teeth into a great role again.
A woman thrown into the stay at home routine of raising a toddler in the suburbs
slowly embraces the feral power deeply rooted in motherhood
as she becomes increasingly aware of the bizarre and undeniable signs
that she may be turning into a dog.
Folks, that's what the movie is.
It's a lady.
It's kind of like a Nicole Hall of Center movie
where it's like a very laser sharp portrait of a woman who wants to be an artist
who feels like she is aging out of her femininity,
aging out of her life, aging out of her career.
She feels lost and at times hates her child.
It's not to the extent of like we need to talk about Kevin,
but she feels like a lot of mothers in my life,
a lot of parents that we all know who are just like, why did I do this?
There's a lot of funny satire in there,
a lot of great stuff with her and her husband.
Her husband, luckily there's moments where they made him a boob for sure,
where it's like he's not helping out around the house as much as he should and stuff,
but it's not that one -sided shitty thing of like,
look at this idiot man here who doesn't know how to talk to a woman.
He's a decent husband who's trying his best,
but can't quite understand his wife.
He's played by Scoot McNary, who's an actor I like a lot,
and I just really enjoyed it.
It was funny.
Amy Adams is awesome.
The dog stuff does not really work.
There's moments where it's like she finds a tail in her underwear
she's like running through the neighborhood on all fours at one point.
Wait a minute, a tail in her underwear, meaning like it fell off of her?
No, like she has a tail growing out of her ass.
Oh, oh, oh, okay.
All right.
And it's like, it's kind of Cronenbergian, you know,
like there's pus dripping out of it and stuff and a few kind of gross out shots.
It was done by Mariel Heller, who did the Melissa McCarthy movie,
the drama, what was that one called?
Can you ever forgive me?
She also did Mr. Rogers movie with Tom Hanks.
She's a good director.
This is a kind of a step in a different direction.
And she's honestly, she's not Cronenberg.
Like this is, she's not a body horror director.
Those elements of this story are not handled particularly well.
I feel like it just would have been a standard
motherhood is hard movie without that.
So they went that route, but it worked for me.
You know, even at times where it felt a little awkward
or like the tone wasn't quite hitting.
I just love the swing that Night Bitch takes.
And I had a good time with the movie.
Another rewatch, Bad Santa.
Now, we've talked plenty about Bad Santa throughout the years.
The only reason I think it's worth talking about again in the movie corner is
when you watch Bad Santa, it's still great.
It still holds up.
But when you watch Bad Santa the first couple of times, especially the first viewing,
you know, you're hyper focused on Billy Bob Thornton being this revolting human being
that's also a Santa Claus.
That's your main focus.
When you've seen it four or five times,
this is probably my fourth or fifth watch.
You already know that's coming.
You're aware of all the insane things he's going to say.
And it lets you sort of take in the movie as a whole a little bit better.
So on this watch, I focused way more than I ever have on Bernie Mac and John Ritter.
And it was awesome.
Comedy teams of all time.
They're tremendous in it.
Yeah.
The choice of Bernie Mac eating an orange in every scene he's in is so odd and funny.
I don't even know why it's funny.
It's just funny.
And then Ritter just being so aware of how pathetic he is
and unable to have any semblance of a spine or anything.
It's really, really funny.
It's bad Santa, man.
It's a great movie.
What's unsaid in those scenes that is sort of what makes them so uncomfortable and dark and funny
is that it's clear to me anyway that John Ritter is that boss who wants to go off
but is worried about it specifically because Bernie Mac is black.
It's never said, it's never mentioned, but that is such a real dynamic.
Whenever the editing of those scenes, how they cut to John Ritter where he's nodding
but he's in pain to have to be agreeing with, oh my God, that's some funny fucking stuff, man.
It's great.
When he is getting his pedicure, he goes, don't romance it now,
get in there to that woman giving him the pedicure.
Oh my God.
The flip flop in that scene, I'm always a fan of a flip flop in a comedy scene.
The flip flop in that scene where he's yelling at her to be aggressive
and then the second she is, he's like, what the hell is wrong with you, woman?
Immediately chastises her for being too rough.
It's such a great flip flop.
I wonder to what extent he improved, him and Ritter, but the scenes are so well written
that that movie was heavily rewritten by the Coen brothers, which they rewrote it
because they were going to do it with Bill Murray and then that all fell apart.
Like Bad Santa is like, that's the beauty of it.
It's got the hard, hard laughs of like a step brothers or something like that,
but it's also really well written and constructed by presumably the Coen brothers.
The dialogue scenes between those two are incredible.
And my biggest laugh every time, it never fails.
My biggest laugh every time is when he's driving the kid home the first time
and the kid keeps asking him the questions and he's answering them as best as he can,
and then he goes - because it's a joke you've seen done a million times,
a kid keeps asking too many questions.
They did it first in Uncle Buck.
But just in the middle of that, man, when he's like,
God damn it, kid, are you fucking with me?
The pop off is so funny, man.
He is so amazing in that.
And also he's so amazing that you don't even really want to picture Bill Murray in the role.
It sounds on paper like a great Bill Murray role,
but Thornton made that his own to a crazy degree.
I love that moment.
And then of course the choice of the one time you see him eating, he's eating salad.
And I'm like, this is so -
I'm on my fucking lunch break.
Yeah, it's just so ridiculous that this drunk's choice of a meal would be a large salad.
And I love that they don't let Zweigoff direct anymore.
The man did Ghost World, which is an A plus masterpiece.
He followed it with a very underrated movie, Art School Confidential,
which is like an insanely dark satire of art people.
Great flick.
Then Bad Santa.
And it's like that should have kicked him off on this big career,
but he hated Hollywood so much.
He had the movie taken away from him by the Weinsteins,
and he just stopped directing.
And he was one of our best comedy directors.
The choice in that movie to have him dry humping a girl who appears to be 14.
She's supposed to be young in the movie,
but they cast a young fucking girl that Billy Bob is butt fucking,
essentially, in an arcade, if I remember correctly.
Crazy.
Does he butt fuck?
Is it Octavia Spencer that he butt fucks in that movie?
No, they make - there's a thing where he has sex with a fat woman in the dressing room.
They're not going to shit right for a week.
Yeah, and then he says that to her and John Ritter hears it,
and that leads to one of the great John Ritter Bernie Maxines.
And then later he pulls up to Octavia Spencer and he's like,
I need a favor.
And she's like, oh no, last time I didn't shit right for a week.
Which, hats off to Octavia Spencer.
This is an award nominated and winning actress,
so sophisticated, and she's like, yeah, I'll do it.
Well, this was pretty early in her career.
Well, she went back for the sequel.
Oh, really?
Yeah, and I didn't know.
Yeah, and did the same nasty jokes.
I was like, God bless her, man.
That's awesome that she did that.
Yeah, I mean, I fucking love that movie.
Uh, my third, I'm going to talk about, let's get, let me get into, oh, uh, Deedee, D -I -D -I.
Um, really, really good little coming of age movie written and directed by Sean Wang.
Um, it is it, we've had a million of these over time, but we've never had one from,
from an Asian point of view that I can recall.
I'm sure there are Asian coming of age movies.
I just can't think of any, uh, certainly not on this commercial level.
So you get the, um, you know, it hits all the standard coming of age beats,
but it's kind of made more interesting.
This is ideally what, um, you know, giving diverse filmmakers will do is,
is learning about other people's lives, experiences, and childhoods.
I thought Deedee was great, funny, um, very sad at times.
It's a 13 year old kid, uh, Taiwanese and his mom is played by Joan Chen.
She is a failed artist.
She still wants to be an artist, but she's a mother kind of two of the three movies
I did this week are about, uh, moms who wanted to do other things with their lives.
Um, Isaac Wang plays Deedee.
The kid's a star.
He's awesome.
He was in good boys as well.
Um, he's been in a few things, but like the kid was really, really good in this
movie and these movies kind of survived by how good their protagonist is.
It's, it's a movie sort of as deep and touching as Lady Bird in its own way.
And I think it's very special.
It will probably be completely neglected.
Maybe Joan Chen gets a nomination or something, but, um, this is a tiny movie
that you probably have to seek out.
It's available on Peacock and if you like that kind of thing, like a kid
dealing with bullies and trying to fit in and trying to date and the awkwardness
of all that combined with, uh, being an Asian American growing up in, you know,
California with racism and things like that, but not too heavy handed.
You know, it's not, it's not that teaching you a lesson thing.
It's just a very real lived in portrait of adolescence.
I dug it very much.
It's on Peacock.
Joe.
Um, last but not least, or maybe, yeah, maybe least, uh, Bad Santa 2.
I had never seen this.
I actually watched this before I re -watched Bad Santa because I was like,
I realized something this Christmas as I was putting on Christmas thing after
Christmas thing and then immediately turning it off.
I don't like Christmas movies.
I thought I did, but I, I like a certain kind of Christmas movie,
like a lot of them, I was just like, oh God, I just don't want to watch this at all.
So I put on Bad Santa 2 and, uh, look, it's, it's not the original.
None of the original team, as far as writers, directors are back.
Um, cast is back.
And then we also, Kathy Bates in this as well as Billy Bob Thornton's mom.
Um, she's great.
He's great.
Uh, um, you know, everybody in it is great.
They're all, they're basically all back.
I think the lady from Gilmore Girls, um, Lauren Graham, Lauren Graham,
I can only assume she said no, she didn't want to come back because it didn't make sense to
me that her character, they, they, they write off her character in the first voiceover
where they just say, he says like,
I had the closest thing I could ever have to a girlfriend.
I mean, everything's set up at the end of the first one that makes it seem he's going
to go on the straight and narrow is ditched in this one so they can do a sequel.
Right.
And I think a lot of that, I'm just assuming,
was probably affected by Lauren Graham's maybe not wanting to do it again.
And then they said, well, how do we reset then everything instead of
starting with him having a sort of normal life and getting pulled back out of it?
This, it starts exactly like the original, um, you know, uh, there's a misdirection of
who he is and where he's at in his life that eventually ends in him puking in an alleyway.
Uh, what's, uh, I don't know anybody's name, his sidekick for Christ sakes.
Uh, the, the little person.
Yeah. Um, I, I gotta look at it. I'm so, I can't remember anybody's goddamn name anymore.
Bad Santa cast, uh, Tony Cox, Tony Cox, you know, Bernie Mac's not back obviously,
cause he's passed, uh, John Ritter the same. Uh, but also too, it wouldn't make sense
cause they're not going back to rob the same mall. Uh, but Tony Cox comes back,
he pulls, uh, Billy Bob Thornton back into another gig.
Um, this time the mom is involved, played by Kathy Bates. It's the same beats. It's
basically all the same beats at this time. They're going to rob a charity. It's not a mall. Um,
you've got the lady from, uh, um, uh, mad men in there. Christina Hendrix is now the female lead.
Um, Jenny Zagrino's in it. Um, she's funny in it. Um, it's not unfunny.
It's just not good. Like it's just, it's, I kept thinking when I was watching it, I was like,
if I were a movie reviewer, my Little Rotten Tomatoes line would be, uh, whereas the first film
um, was a little gross, the second makes you feel a little gross. Like there is something about it
where it's like, they're kind of going for the, it just, the shock is more apparent. I can't explain
it. Like you could watch the first movie and say, well, that shock value and it is, but it's organic.
Yeah. There's something about the second movie. It doesn't feel organic. It feels like
he's just using that racial slur right now to make the audience cringe. Um,
you know, there was also an odd choice in this one to have every woman in the movie want to have
sex with him and throw themselves at him, which I didn't understand, particularly the Christina
Hendrix character, which they made her a recovering sex addict and alcoholic. Yeah. Um, so then
the, the reason she likes to sleep with him is like her own relapsing, like sort of depravity
coming to the surface. Yeah. Um, which made it sadder. Whereas in the first movie it was just
like, no, this, this catch of a woman just says a weird Santa fetish and then she discovers the
human in this person somehow. Yeah. Um, this didn't really have much of that. Everybody is
kind of out for themselves. Everybody kind of stabs everybody in the back. Uh, it's a much more,
uh, depressing venture for that reason. There, there isn't really a lot of hope. And,
uh, and then finally in the end, it, you know, whereas the first one ends with him sort of
getting a life of some kind, this one ends with him after Tony Cox betrays him again and is now
in the hospital because he's been run over by a van, Billy Bob Thornton going into the hospital
teabagging him. And the end credits are pictures of Tony Cox with ball sacks
on his face. So you're just like, all right guys, I guess, I guess, I mean, you know,
it had some laughs though. I mean, it's, you know, I, I hated it so much. That was the,
the movie where I yelled at those children, um, afterwards, but to me,
the Billy Bob Thornton character from bad Santa is never teabagging anyone.
Like that was, that was such a non, not his character thing, you know? Like he doesn't care
about you enough to do that, you know, like to, to do that, like we're friends kind of vibe. That's
not his vibe. I don't know. Well, he's not doing it as friends. He's doing it as revenge.
But it's not, it's still that character. Like reaching in and taking his balls. I do,
I do not buy it personally. I also didn't buy that like Sturgeon. That's the kid's name, right?
I think Thurman Merman or Thurman, sorry. I just was like,
so he's grown now. Yeah. And just to have him grown where like, he's literally the same exact
character. Like there's no difference. Yeah. Um, you, you just kind of like, I don't know,
like there, you couldn't have done something more with this. Like it's just, it's just so -
How does he get reunited with the kid? They don't really explain. The kid just lives near him
where he lives. I don't, I, it should have been the kid gets in trouble and he's got to help,
you know, something to give him some sort of humanity. Yeah. It should be, it, the sequel
should always, if the guy goes clean at the end of the first movie. Yeah. The sequel should always be,
he now has to go back to his old ways, but for a more virtuous reason.
Yeah. Thurman's in trouble. He can't let this happen to the kid. He's got to do another gig
now with Tony Cox. He's got to convince Tony Cox. You know, Tony Cox is going to screw him over,
but it's for the kid. He gets, the kid finds out he's back to his old ways. The kid is disappointed.
He has to tell the kid, I only did this for you, but it was wrong. That's what you, that's where
you go with it. And they just didn't, they just were like, let's just make the same movie again.
Yeah. That said, few laughs. It is funny. The kid works at Hoagie Hatch or something. He works
on a hoagie job and they do the gag again at the beginning where Billy Bob Thornton is like,
God damn it. What are you retarded? Because he yells at him in the first movie when he first
meets him and he goes, no, they tested me at the Hoagie Hatch. I am on the spectrum though,
which is a very funny joke. And you know, a joke that you don't really, it's funny. This came out,
cause I remember with that joke in particular, I looked up, I was like, when did this come out?
You couldn't make that joke now. And it felt on the line at the time too. 2016. There it is.
That was the line. Trump stepping into office. That was like, get your jokes in now people.
Get them in now. This is going to change real soon. Yeah. And it did. Anyway.
Let's get to that.
Onto a much more family friendly Christmas title. Red One. Red One stars Dwayne the Rock Johnson
as Santa's bodyguard.
Head of security.
Santa is portrayed by a weirdly jacked JK Simmons. Jacked for reasons that don't
factor into the plot.
No, that's not true.
They work against the plot, don't they?
No, that's not true. He's jacked. They show it at the end why he's jacked. He's jacked because
the whole idea is that the North Pole is operating under a branch of the government
that's basically like black ops or something. And that's why at the end, when they show him
delivering all the presents, he's doing like mission impossible flips and all that. And
it's there to be like, this is how this gets done. This guy is like a superhuman specimen
that is able to do this. That's the idea.
All right. Very well.
Yeah. Dwayne must team up with the world's best tracker.
You know how we all know who the world's best tracker is and how to contact him or her.
And that is played by Chris Evans in a extremely misguided performance.
Joe pointed out that it was clearly written for Gosling and that seems to be the case.
He's doing like a New York, New Jersey thing every fifth line and he's trying to be tough
and he does not come off as tough or scary or intimidating at all, especially going up against
the rock. But you know what it is, Ernest paved the way. They're trying to save Christmas.
And you know, it's for some reason the movie is $250 million. The North Pole looks like,
you know, the whole movie reminded me of like a best buy commercial. It's way too expensive
looking for what it is in my opinion. And that's kind of how I feel about a lot of comedy,
a lot of action comedy. It's like this movie works way better
with a hundred million dollars taken off the budget in my opinion. But this movie is hated.
My friends on Letterboxd all gave this movie a half a star which you never see.
I gave it two. I thought at least it, you know, got you from A to B but it's pretty uninspired.
What did you think, Joe? I thought this was a solid C movie. I thought it was a three out of five stars
okay or two and a half, whatever a C would be. But I went in thinking I was going to loathe it
and as I watched it, I was like, look, all the pieces are here. The plot makes sense.
One thing leads logically to the next. The twists make sense. There's no plot hole
that I'm seeing here. The performances are what you think the performances are going to be.
It's The Rock being The Rock. It's J .K. Simmons, you know, being Santa Claus, whatever, like,
and it's fine. And it's Chris Evans playing like a, you know, like a bit of a scoundrel type. You
could tell they kind of want it. They were trying to go for like the Ryan Gosling and the nice guys
thing. Yeah. Chris Evans is not as funny as Ryan Gosling. But he delivers. It's kind of hard to
see Chris Evans play, believably play a creep because he's Captain America now. It's kind of
like if you tried to watch Christopher Reeve right after the Superman movies play like a loser,
you just associate him too much with a character that's pure and upstanding and all this stuff. So
you know, I thought the sequences that were fantastic were fun enough. I thought when they
fought the abominable, not abominable, but you know, the snowmen on the beach, it was kind of
fun. I thought it was when they went to Krampus's thing, it looked cool and it was kind of fun.
I thought the plot detail of Krampus and Santa being brothers that were estranged was kind of
I got to remember that joke, but I, you know, I chuckled a few times and I just was sitting there
going, this is just a big popcorn Christmas movie. They used to make big popcorn Christmas
movies like this when I was a kid. The one I really remember the most was Dudley Moore's Santa Claus,
the movie, but they've made Christmas movies left and right for decades. But the idea of,
you know, a blockbuster Christmas movie has not been a thing that I can remember for a while.
Every Christmas movie in recent years that I remember is like Bad Santa where it's a Christmas
movie, but it's not a big popcorn movie. And this was, you know, and I just, I don't know,
I just thought it ticked all the boxes and I was like, yeah, this is something if I had kids,
I'd watch this with them and we'd all love it and that'd be great. And I didn't find any of
it appallingly bad. I didn't find any of it mesmerizing to the point where I said I've got
to watch this again. But I will tell you this, it maintained a quality that you do not see.
You know, I just tried to rewatch like Beetlejuice again, the sequel one.
I couldn't even get through it. And there are scenes in that movie, not the practical effects,
where the CGI is so bad, I don't even understand. I'm like, what is going on here? And this movie
didn't have any of that. All of it, now for 250 million dollars, it better not. But my point is,
I was just like, it's all pretty seamless. It's all very well put together. I can understand
somebody saying I didn't like it. I don't understand the vehement hatred of it. I'm like,
this is just a popular thing to beat up on. Nobody hates this movie that much.
I got to say, I don't really get it either. I didn't love it. I didn't even really like it.
But everything you're saying is true. It is competently directed in a way that most of
these are not. It doesn't feel like a piece of junk that just nobody was awake for.
And in 2024, that's a rave. Jake Kasdan is a great comedy director. He did the TV set,
which very few have seen, which is one of the best depictions ever of trying to get a
network TV pilot made. Apatow produced that. He also did Zero Effect, Orange County,
The Great Walk Hard. He's a really good comedy director. So when he made the jump to doing the
Jumanji movies, he made those Jumanji movies genuinely funny comedies first, and all the
action and everything came second. Those are really funny movies, especially the first one.
If we got to have these movies, I'd rather have a Jake Kasdan, somebody with some taste,
who knows how to land a joke, et cetera. And you can tell, even though I found nothing in this
movie funny, you can tell it was directed by a guy who at least knows what's funny.
I like the Nick Kroll cameo in it. I always think Kroll's good.
Yeah, Nick was funny. I like too that they actually cursed a little bit within bounds of
a family movie. I tried watching Dear Santa, and this is a fucking unwatchable movie that is so
paint -by -numbers, Hollywood, dropping in cameos and just poorly written. But the thing that
bothered me most was it's a movie where this kid writes to Satan by accident instead of Santa,
because he has dyslexia, so he misspells it. And Jack Black comes up from hell, and then he's like,
did you even look at the, you know, the kid goes, I didn't write to you, and he goes,
think again, fudge nuts. And you're like, you know guys, fucking say it or don't say it,
you know what I mean? In the commercial for Dear Santa, they won't say the word hell,
and it's just like, guys, what is this? You can't even say the place.
Make an R -rated devil Christmas movie or don't. We were allowed to say hell as a place in
a religious school, like religious classes. That's crazy.
So I can't stand the we're being edgy without being edgy crap. It's like either do it or don't
do it. And I found Dear Santa to be, I didn't finish it, so I'm not going to try to review it,
but I will say the half of it that I saw, I found to be eye rollingly bad, which did include a
five minute fart and shit scene that they preview in the trailer.
Five minutes. That scene, Pat,
that they preview where the guy's trying to get into the porta potty and he can't get in,
it goes on and on. And it's like, I'm talking like, I'm talking like Leslie Nielsen level,
like fart, like fart noises and like him being like, oh my God, I just a little came out,
never trust a fart. It leaked. You're like, this is so bad. This is terrible. It's terrible.
And it's really disappointing to see Jack Black in something that's without a laugh. You're like,
I don't even know how you do this. I don't know how you get zero laughs out of Jack Black,
but you did it somehow. Whereas there were parts in Red One where I genuinely laugh,
it's funny when they're in the car and Chris Evans, I'm going to butcher the joke, but when
Chris Evans is like, aren't you supposed to say, you know, Merry Christmas or whatever? And the
Rock's just like, yeah, Merry Christmas, asshole. Okay. You know, I was like, that's funny. It's a
funny interaction. When they come together and start to like each other and work together,
I was like, this feels like a buddy cop movie. It has the moment where I care that they want to
work together and try to save the day. And yeah, all of it made sense to me.
But I think, you know, we both sort of feel the same way about it,
except that was enough for you and that was not enough for me.
Yeah, it lands its beats. It makes sense. And these are things to be commended in the
movie. I liked that it was, you know, just two hours and not 230. There are a few small things
to recommend. I think the women in the movie have, I mean, Lucy Liu is bad in an unplayable role.
Kiernan Shipka, the little girl from Mad Men is for some reason, the main villain of the piece.
I thought she was good. She's like the winter queen. She was okay. Bonnie Hunt is Miss Claus.
I love Bonnie Hunt. She had very little to do. Mary Elizabeth Ellis literally phoning in a
performance where she's Chris Evans ex -wife being like, well, you suck. You're stupid.
It's a very annoying performance and character. I think I realized that was her.
Yeah. Oh, wow. Okay. I texted you. Yeah, we talked about it.
Oh, I'm sorry. That didn't resonate with me for some reason.
Yeah. You know, but what do I care really? I thought nothing about it was good enough
to recommend and yet as a movie I sat and watched, you know, you could do worse. That's all I'll say.
My Hog is not an erect tree, but it's a tree with no lights. It's the tree
at the lot that's leaning over and you say it's good enough. We'll take that one.
My Hog is limp. It is down. However, it's not like it has a disease. You know what I mean?
Folks, we'll be back talking about Robert Eggers' take on the new film Nosferatu,
which is hitting theaters shortly if it hasn't come out where you are. I don't think it's quite
come out yet, but there's - Comes out on Christmas Day.
Christmas Day, yeah. And it is a Christmas movie. It is Christmas
time in the movie. There's a scene where there's a Christmas tree. So it is, so yes, it counts.
Folks, jodorosic .com, all tour dates are up as of now for the Joystick Tour. Please come out and
see me starting in January. We kick things off in Toronto. Lots of dates. Lots of dates. Please come
out and come to Joey Rose's if you're in New York City. I think we're having a little New Year's
Eve shindig if you're around. Come on through. We're going to have specials and music and fun
and parties and all that sort of stuff. So hope to see you. All right. We will see you next time,
folks. We are at See You in Hellpod on Instagram. Tell your friends. Thank you for supporting us
on Patreon, as always. We love you. We'll see you next time and we'll see you in hell.