Welcome to we'll see you in hell it's the podcast that talks movies
folks I'm Joe DeRosa I'm Patrick Walsh good morning Joe afternoon your time yeah
I'm you know I messed up again I'm coming to you we had gone back and fourth all
week changing days changing times I go to bed last night at 11 p .m. usually go
better around two I'm like I don't even need to set an alarm do I but I do set the
alarm wake up 7 a .m. hours before the scheduled start time of the pod wife
to sleep start looking through my phone chilling petting the cat wake up a happy
family she gets up join the phone I wake up hours later with the phone still
clench between my hands for a grand total of like 12 full hours of sleep all
right it's not a good excuse I I I I just slept all day you know I'll be
honest I'm disappointed that a great tragedy had struck well I was like I know
I'm sure Joe's expecting me to say I'd hit by a boss or something but the truth is
sad it's not there's nothing glamorous about it I just I just simply slept like a
bear we are yeah so pets pets what pets referring to is we're in an hour behind
hour behind the start time for the re -records we had to do because he was on
vacation we couldn't do him last week now that I don't really accept plan for
that's like I recorded and I did therapy that day over zoom yeah but you got
understand your therapist being able to communicate with you on zoom versus a
quality podcast recording or two very different things but we've recorded one of
these while I was in Vegas too yeah but but you're also saying it like you were in
that exact room in that exact hotel on that exact floor it's true you're
relying on hotel Wi -Fi any number of variables could come into play since we
had never had a problem I didn't think that would be a problem this this one
today is obviously entirely my fault especially since I said hey to buy us some
wiggle room we should get on an hour earlier yeah yeah yeah it's the kind of
thing we rant about on the show all the time about where you know someone will
say hey we should get together Thursday in the cancel five minutes before and
you're like you started this you son of a bitch you wanted to do it that's what I
was getting at I wasn't necessarily blaming you for the Vegas Wi -Fi issue I was
yeah it was more shot at this was your day it's not that you would pick but what are
you gonna do it's not great I mean you just I I have sleep issues I never dreamed
that I could sleep 12 hours and I then the thing is you wake up after sleeping for
12 hours and you're like why don't I feel amazing isn't that the point because you
you overslept yeah you overslept that's a real thing you know if you sleep too much
you just have no energy and I was racked with guilt you know you wake up and you
see the text where are you buddy what's happening and I had the extra embarrassment
of wearing my three -stu just style nightcap you know which I almost I hit
record and then I realized I still had it on with the big ball on the end of it
yeah yeah yeah yeah whipped it off cuz I was like I was gonna tell Joe I did get hit
by a bus and then I was like boy if he had seen that nightcap oh boy that would
have been awkward for me yeah you're wearing the gown yeah and not pajamas just
the the shin length night dress did men wear that to sleep other than like the
stooges and Ebenezer screwed yeah I think it was a style for wild the cap I never
understood like what was the point of that the campus the dumbest thing I've ever
seen yeah like what are you protecting sometimes women I know here we go here we go no no no no
no women will do wraps I know particularly like black women a lot of time we'll have to do
wraps on their hair at night when they sleep depending on what they have going with their
hair at the time stylized but like I've also seen other women do it like because they get
a perm or whatever it is or whatever so like I guessed it but that's that's not what
the three stooges we're doing they weren't getting hair styles done you know early as famously
bold yeah screw screws depending on the on the portrayal did not have an amazing head of
hair no no no it's a weird it's a weird it's weird I don't I don't know what that style was I mean
but it's all it's as confusing as Jesus this thing's going to keep making noise hold on it's
as confusing as how men used to wear wigs but at least with the wigs I was like okay that was some
weird social you know pre presentation thing right and it didn't seem like men cared about being
bold at the time I don't think that was part of it even I don't know I don't know it's odd it's
odd but it's funny you know speaking of sleep and the circumstances today it's it's strange that
this happened on this day because last night I went to sleep to YouTube videos which I do sometimes
and this this is absolute hard evidence as to why they tell you like do not sleep with your TV on
it's not going to be a good sleep I never listen to that I every night I sleep with something playing
you know I just I'm so haunted by the silence I need something to you know like so
so last night I go to sleep to this YouTube video and I've got my YouTube on autoplay and somewhere
during the night in the queue comes a cinematic or who's a channel I follow they they do the angry
video game nerd videos and bunch of other stuff but James Rolf who's like the main dude over there
he does movie reviews sometimes so this video comes on where he does like a comprehensive review
of every single installment in the Friday the 13th franchise now this comes on as I'm sleeping
right and it incorporates itself into my dream and I guess because of the subject matter I start
having a dream that you and I are doing a live show okay and you in the dream are doing the comprehensive
review of all the Friday the 13th movies that is actually playing on the YouTube I imagine you're
blown away by the amount of time I'm talking on a two -man stage you're you're you're exactly right in
the dream I start trying to interject but I can't get a word in because it's your dialogue is a YouTube
video that's just playing and I lose it I lost it in the dream and I screamed at you in front of the
audience and then and then stomped off and that was like how the podcast ended and then I woke up and
I was like wait a minute that didn't happen that's crazy and I really that'd be a good podcast yeah
what if that winds up happening today what if I wind up getting you that matter that actually happens
it won't happen come on but yeah it was it was crazy because in the dream I'm like Pat did you want
to tell me you were going to do this comprehensive review we're supposed to be talking about this
movie at the live show yeah and just and then people people are getting up and walking out like because
they're like what's Pat doing like he's he won't let Joe talk he just keeps going on and on about
these movies so this but this was a true narcissist dream it was it was it was but it was all confusing
because we also reviewed the move those movies so I was like why is he doing this again we already
did this right it was very strange that all said if you just watch James's video under normal
circumstances it's a wonderful video he does a really nice review I thought Jason was going to be like
stalking you in a nightmare but I turned out to be the villain yes okay all right yeah so
that says a lot about our dynamic I think well at one point in the dream I screamed because he doesn't
because you don't want to do your fucking job I screamed at you and and then today when we went
to record you it you had slept so funny coincidence that's all I'm saying well it seems like I had
overplant for my job if if I'm talking a fully prepared you know there was a second part in the dream
where once you finished the reviews you went off and talked on your phone oh wow as I was trying to
start the actual show okay and but when you were talking on your phone it was the your your
dialogue in the dream was yet another James raw video that was playing so in the dream I was going
up to you going pat you got to get off your phone man like we're trying to do a show and like
whatever he was talking about was just what you were talking about it was a wild dream but anyway
that's why you're not supposed to sleep with things on right we're discussing this dream in our
some kind of monster style therapy that you and I go to the therapist would have a juicy time
digging into the dynamics of this of this nightmare for sure I think so I think so and by monster
therapy do you mean no I'm talking some kind of monster like Metallica therapy oh well I thought
you were saying like a monster who's giving us therapy like a big thing with his legs crossed
woman style right right holding a clipboard yeah full flat head Frankenstein glasses down like this
right right right the only thing that the cost that's the only costume change as like a thinking gesture
he he abs and mindedly twists one of the bolt in his neck as he thinks about how to respond
like like like you were I would chew on a pen yeah yeah yeah yeah I like that quite a bit so that was
wild and his name would be doctor Frankenstein Joe I recommend to you a white noise machine I've
been using one for 10 years it's it changed my life really you you that the only drawback is once
you get used to it you can't sleep without it so I have to pack it when I'm traveling but I would
recommend one highly I have a I have a white no I have a white noise machine that I do play
but I still do the iPad and whatever on top of it okay I just there's something about I need to go
to bed like watching something or listening to something or and I probably don't I probably just need
to sit there and be patient and fall asleep but it certainly accelerates the process to have
something playing but I got it I got to start putting a timer on it or something right you know yeah
I remember I know yeah so anyway that's that all right we're talking this week about the dentist
starring Corbin Bernson and in my case the dentist too did you wind up watching the dentist too
I'm gonna be honest with you I watched most of it it's really not the focus of the discussion I know
the sort of secondary sure and we'll get into why I didn't finish it but it's not it's lesser dentist
don't get me wrong I mean you're treading on thin ice with the first one it's enjoyable but you know
it's like it's barely enough story for a Pono movie and they made it into a franchise
they're pushing in that second one for like it's just like Jesus Christ like yeah just no
well we'll get to it we'll get to it but yeah we're talking the dentist today and then the
episode after this is going to be the conjuring three which I'm happy we're doing second
because I got a lot to say I always like to do the one the the one that I have way more fire about I
like to do second you know you know so so that'll that'll be coming up next but in the meantime
why don't you take us on a stroll Pat we're going I mean do we don't have any news to discuss after all
this time oh oh actually I know I sent you some yeah I uh I actually do well uh Dick Donner
dead at the age of 91 that's what I was gonna start with I mean we talked about the great Jeffrey
Balm on here I think I did that on my solo pod but uh yeah Richard Donner was commercial filmmaking you
know that maybe maybe slightly less than as a mechus less than a spielberg but otherwise he's on
the list of like your top five eighties big tent pole directors and he did them all in such a classy
way if you compare his big like classic action movies to the action movies of today Jesus Christ
uh let's go through him you got lethal weapon which is the you know the template for the buddy
cob movie not the first but uh a masterpiece of the form lethal weapon two excellent as well
maybe three and four are slipping a bit but but oh well the goonies you know Joe are you a goonies man
a lot of people have a great love for it never hit me in that way I'm a huge goonies man it was
a game changing movie I saw it exactly the right age yeah I saw that movie when I was like eight
sure I mean it's just everything you could ever want your life to be at that age uh right
and then chunk eventually was my lawyer for a few years there amazing entertainment lawyer yeah but um
but I was uh you had to let him go yeah to let him go uh I I wouldn't say I let him go but we
we moved in different directions but he's a nice guy uh you let you go no no not at all it's uh
isn't a very amicable parting of ways amongst you know sometimes you change lawyers
the uh but he uh he was a nice guy here he is a nice guy I assume still I've been talked
for a while but I was a big goonies guy um I mean look my favorite work of Donner is the Superman
stuff sure I'm looking here I mean this man did a ton of TV and his first feature film folks
was the god damn omen oh yeah shit I always forget about the omen first film the omen and then
you know nowadays that would just put you on a on a 50 year career of making horror movies or
actually you know probably a five year career until your career blows up but um the omen right into
Superman well it's funny okay well there's Superman 2 then which has the dick Donner cut
yes uh and which have you seen the director's cut I've only seen the original and a lot of people
drastically prefer the Donner cut I own both um the problem is is that because Donner so they shot
those simultaneously yeah and the problem is when they booted Donner in the middle of
they shot them back to back I mean and the middle of Donner shooting too he got the boot
and then they decided to take his ending for two that he had already shot right and make it the
ending for one and then have a new guy come in and do a bunch of reshoots and and and do a new ending
for the end of two so how do you how are you gonna direct Superman 1 a massive hit and then get fired
on halfway through Superman 2 I don't think 2 was out yet I think they did like a back to the
future two and three thing okay something but anyway the problem with that is is the Donner cut is
I think for the most part a superior cut of the film but it ends in the same way Superman 2 ends
I mean Superman 1 yeah so it's it's it's kind of hard to separate it and just kind of judge it on
its own surprisingly the Donner cut has one or two unforgivable jokes in it there's a there's a toilet
flush gag at the fortress of solitude yeah I mean it's just it's just a brutal joke but aside from
that for the most part it's it's better on on all fronts but but the the theatrical release of
Superman 2 is not a bad movie that in my opinion that was the greatest superhero movie of all time
before I even saw the Donner cut so there was only room you know thankfully for improvement
it could have been it could have gone the other way and it didn't so well it's such an I think
that Richard Lester the the director of a hard days night which of course wasn't as old at the
at the time of filming Superman 2 but Richard Lester does not seem the guy to do a Superman movie to me
yeah I mean but what's interesting about Donner going into the Superman cut is I mean I'm sorry
going into the Superman from the Omen is that he that is almost the same trajectory of what would
happen now you you'd be a new director you'd you'd make this hit hard movie yeah that's true and then
they put you on a superhero movie yeah but but back then there was clearly room for artistic
control which is why he got booted I guess or maybe there wasn't and he was just a guy that said
fuck you but now it's his it would be a very different well I don't know maybe it wouldn't be that
different of a trajectory because then he went on and did like action movies and stuff like that
I mean he did all popcorn films yeah well there's a very famous story and I don't remember the object
but apparently Marlon Brando was you know deep in his apocalypse now in sane days he made a million
dollars for like two days of work on Superman and Brando was like I think I'm gonna play the pot
like a sandwich I want to play the role like a sandwich and Donner goes how about you play it like
fucking Marlon Brando whereas every other director was like anyway you want to do it Marlon
so uh I think Brando appreciated that and was like oh all right yeah this guy's uh you know he
tested people um he did the toy which I've never seen but which is considered one of the worst
movies ever made I remember so the toy I've never seen the toy I know it's incredibly racist
is what I've heard about it it's it's problematic certainly yeah especially by today's standards
and by it was it was problematic then too uh but but you know um if you can kind of get past some of
that stuff and watch it just for the prior and gleece and performances they're both very very
funny in it and and uh you know the the the story ultimately the kid does kind of learn a lesson
and and and he does form a bond with prior but but obviously they're the racial element of it is
is quite problematic but I mean Jack it's the movie I cite when I say if you don't know the why Jackie
Gleason is a comedic genius that's the movie all right because of all his smoking okay no his overall
performance and smokey is better that's amazing but Jackie Gleason has one line at the end of
smoking in the bandit where he looked richer prior crashes a party he's doing and Jackie Gleason
goes what are you doing here you asshole and the fact that he chooses to inflect hole instead of
ass I'm like that's literally what makes a comedic genius like the that that line is so nothing
and it's the funniest line in the movie it's so you know it's worth a watch I mean I don't think it's like
I'm not gonna put it next to like stir crazy or or smokey for either their respective great films but
sure but you know I didn't know down or did that though uh yeah I guess I didn't either um he did
lady hawk which is fun you know not great but fun kind of a fantasy joint lady hawk with broadrick
how are five for it's an entertaining movie I saw it at that theater recently uh I remember I saw
it I remember as a kid wanting more out of it it was like every time I dipped in it didn't go enough in
the like hardcore yeah hone in direction so I I always bailed out of it it was one like I'd always
rented six movies and it was always the one of the six that didn't get watched I that happened
to be like six times I was like I just can't do lady hawk but when I watch it I like that uh radio
flyer which is a very underrated drama with Elijah Wood very serious movie about child abuse that
I really dug yeah uh and then again it's easy to forget that the man did scrooge you know one of
the great Christmas comedy scrooge I mean what a what a career you direct one of the all -time great
horror movies yeah you direct what is considered by most or many to be the all -time greatest superhero
movie or at least the Beatles of the like in the in that it broke ground first and it did it the right
way for the first time yeah the ultimate kids adventure movie for sure uh and then the ultimate buddy
cop movie and the ultimate buddy cop movie right and they'll I mean I mean they still say I'm too old
for this shit yeah every one of these movies yeah and then the classic Christmas staple like one
of the scrooge isn't like the five rotation at Christmas time yeah and it's one of the few laugh out
loud funny Christmas movies you know a lot of them have the sweetness but not the laughs uh yeah and a
sentimental favorite for me because I saw a 13 when I rode my back up to the theater and absolutely
loved it Maverick with Gibson Garner and Fireford that's a really fun movie if you have never seen it
it's a great Western comedy and everybody's I thought it was foster you're right foster okay yeah
no I I never I had no interest in Maverick I just didn't care Maverick's great I mean it's written
by William Goldman who you know wrote misery and Butch Cassidy and all that it's it's a good it opens
with uh Gibson's on a horse with a noose tied tied around his neck which is tied to a tree uh
and the first line is his narration he goes it had just been a shitty week from the jump
and that's that's a great way to kick off the move the uh I never saw it because I didn't
have high interest and then my uncle saw it when it came out and I remember seeing my uncle and
him key hated it for some reason oh yeah and he just goes it was so stupid and then they got
daddy Glover in there doing his line from lethal weapon it was just stupid well that
he probably loved the original Maverick or something you don't have any great feelings about
yeah I think that's what it was he was mad he wasn't like a real Maverick movie right
that whereas that didn't really bother me at all uh dig Donner did three episodes of Tales from
the Crypt oh that's a Donner also one of the main players of Tales from the Crypt that's right
Jesus Christ this guy bad bad a thousand man he did dig that cat he's real gone which is the third
episode of the show in my top arguably my second of all time favorite Tales from the Crypt
it was a really good one I mean he's he's the shit and then you know the later career was a sassins
which I never saw with Banderas and Stallone conspiracy theory which I really liked with
Gibson Julia Roberts and Pat Stewart I was a fun movie I did not see timeline with Paul Walker
and then 16 blocks I found with Bruce Willis I found the most death performance
so annoying I couldn't deal with the film I always confused 16 blocks with Inside Man
Inside Man is five million times better yeah I loved Inside Man I was it can whenever I hear 16
blocks I think of Inside Man then I realized it's not Inside Man yeah it's interesting I guess you
know like Terrence he knows talking a lot lately about how he he wants to do one movie and quit but he's
also torn because what better film to go out on than once a point of time in Hollywood and everybody's
like you're still making great movies you're a young man what's the deal and he's like I'm a student of
film I dirt these directors that you know keep making movies till they're 90 years old I know how that
goes their their last 10 movies all suck and I'm not going to do that the honors clearly no exception
here but I do hope we get a couple more Terrentino pictures out of the deal I'm excited to have you
if you were to his new novel his novelization of his own film no no I I'm gonna read it I'm not
against I think it's cool that he did it but but I'm not gonna read it but um you know Terrentino
toyed with the idea and I thought I would have been so cool if he actually did this of remaking
reservoir dogs this is 10th movie yeah I was gonna remake it yeah of remaking it and I was like wow
that's a really interesting cool thing but I mean dude this guy has his kid a grand slam on every
all nine yeah there's no question about it his worst movie is a great movie yeah the pressure of
his only like shit moot not shit but the only one that you don't care about his death proof but
I kind of don't really count that one but I love death proof I think Kurt Russell's hilarious in that
movie and it's too chatty but the ending of it is fucking awesome when the cars rollin over their
faces and everything yeah it's a wild flick um but I mean you want to talk about the pressure being on
Jesus Christ yeah you know he's got to go out he's got to go out with a banger here I really hope that
at the very least he returns to the crime genre and does something that tips the hat and ties into
the universe of pulp fiction yeah reservoir dogs and true romance and all those characters that
crossed over with one I think that'd be a really cool you know Scorsese he says I'm doing one more
and I'm done it better not be fucking like coon dune too yeah yeah yeah you go out with what with
the lady he came with you know I agree and I think you know Scorsese is a perfect example of maybe
your films aren't quite as vital when you're 85 years old but he's making great fucking movies I
know you didn't care for Wolf Wall Street which would be in my movie corner today but um that is a
movie that feels like it was made by a 30 year old man and I feel like Tarantino could do the same thing
we'll see I mean I think in his mind once upon a time in Hollywood is a movie about the end of a Hollywood
career and wouldn't that be perfect but yeah it I mean look I understand the fear too like what you
what if he comes out with his tenth movie and it fucking sucks then you know he's got to do an 11th
and then that's I think how people wind up down a bad track they're trying to like get out of shit town now
well why don't you take us into the movie corner because I have something that relates in my corner
to Wolf of Wall Street I'm gonna take us I'll start with Wolf of Wall Street Joe I'm I'm still
baffled by your lack of enjoyment for Wolf of Wall Street um you know it's definitely the anti -airishment
every every scene is directed at a fever pitch of cocaine yeah lightning fast talking it's
it's classic Scorsese as opposed to like an elegy for the gangster series
right written by Terrence winner of the sopranos I think it's got a lot of that mix of horrible behavior
and dark dark comedy that sopranos drives in um de caprio is hilarious and an excellent in it um his
performance of you know being on the 15 ludes that all kick in at once that half hour of the film
especially coming that late in the film to just turn it over to a big slapstick romp
uh with him and Jonah Hill fighting each other in the kitchen and then him like getting the
thing lodged out of Jonah Hill's throat that's like a in my opinion one of the great comedy sequences of
this last 10 15 years it's really funny it's directed and edited incredibly well I love Jonah
Hill in it they let the improv rants go on too much it does feel like you're washing sort of one of
those aptowed directors cuts where the riffs go on a minute too long every time you know and you're
losing track of the story a little bit yeah however in my mind and I imagine Scorsese in the writers
would tell you the same the movie is about excess the movie is about taking it too far the movie is
about guys who can't shut the fuck up and stop talking or can't stop doing drugs and it's trying to
give you that feeling and I think it it works perfectly my plan was to watch it in two shifts three
hour movie and I watched the whole fucking thing I I really love it want to score Scorsese's funniest
margo roby mama mia that's one that's one of the great female actress entrances I mean granted
she's naked in the movie half the time but it's like that was one of those were in the theater you're
heard a gasp and those come along about every 10 years where there's an actress where you're like she's
gonna be huge I love the movie I'm interested I'm willing to give it a rewatch my take on it is I
disagree I don't think it's class as Scorsese I think that it's directed like Scorsese doing below
who was doing Scorsese yeah a movie below I mean I think it is a film riddled with nothing but wholly
unlikable characters I feel like there's no honor code or anything that brings something like a casino
or a goodfellas back down to earth where you're like this is the these are the everybody breaks the
rules everybody fucks everybody else over everybody is selfish and I just don't care enough about the
subject matter to sit in it for three hours I hated I hated the 30 minute quay loot thing yes I
thought it was kind of funny and I thought it was well acted but it's like for God's sakes man I'm
like sitting there in the theater like what the fuck does this have to do with anything it's not
moving the plot forward in any way it's not in my opinion and then again maybe on rewatch I'll change my
mind but it's not you know people complain about the last act of the Irishman and it's like no that's
the whole movie the whole movie is the realization of what my life has become that quay loot sequence is
just there for laughs like I'm like I don't really get what the point of it is so as a short film sure
yeah it's funny but like yeah I don't feel and I found it I found it as painful to sit through that
sequence as painful to sit through as I find Eugene Levy in a mighty wind where it's like I just
and you're like oh my god man like I get what you're doing dude but like this is painful like please
just get to Eugene Levy in a mighty wind is one of my favorite supported performances in that
decade so we're we have some we usually line up these days but we do have some pretty
godblastic differences well I'll meet you with a good well no I just I wanted and I'm worried now
about you walking off with me talking too much about wolf lost I I read that a lot of the criticism of it
was that they thought Scorsese was making these people heroes and not really showing you consequences
of the life he's like you know people were like what same same deal you had but at the end the final
shot when it's all these dumbasses lined up to learn from Jordan Belford and say hey you're a guy who
was a complete drug addict who blew up your family who destroyed people's lives who had no moral code
who didn't think twice about destroying families and innocent people and there's a conference room
full of losers lining up to learn from him how did you do it how can we do it too I think at this
time in America's history where people are you know it seems like everybody is very much aware of
capitalism and how it has destroyed and we'll continue to destroy us Scorsese is too smart a guy
I think to not let that theme go across he won't hit you over the head with it he's not that kind of
director but I think by the end it's that little subtle moment of like even if I did paint this
to be a fun lifestyle to your average douchebag guy who's like dude we gotta we gotta have a wolf
wall street type weekend bro which I'm sure still goes on it's that last shot which I think it is the
movie which is like we idolize these people and it will be the end of society and I think that's
what we're watching now so it felt very timely to me I think that message is surely time surely
timely and interesting but it's you know it just kind of becomes a thing like look a movie about a
Trump type would be timely and interesting do I want to watch it as a question but I'll meet you with
another film on the same subject matter that's it that I'd seen once when it came out and I just
rewatched it wall street money never sleeps so I missed all of her stone I remember seeing it initially
and enjoying it and I just rewatched it because I was curious to see if it held up in any way this is a
terrible terrible movie it is now here's the thing it's one of these flicks where
is it is it poorly written not really the script is strong enough it's solid enough it
strangely is not co -written by Oliver Stone and I'm blanking on his name but the writer that he wrote
the first wall street with and the reason that's curious to me is because the guy he wrote wall street
the original with wrote or or and worked on whatever movies on either side of this with Oliver Stone
so they still work together maybe that guy just didn't have an interest in writing this I don't know
it's two different writers who were not on the first film that wrote this movie they I don't
know who they are I didn't really look into it I might know who they are if you brought up some other
movies that they worked on but as far as I know I don't know as far you know off the top of head I don't
know who they are what they worked on anyway so is it a decently written film yet solid enough
is it well acted yes carry Mulligan shy LaBuff Susan Sarandon Josh Brolin and of course
Michael Douglas whose dare I say excellent in the movie um you know he certainly has the
medias part everybody else in it is I'd say Brolin probably has the second juiciest part
but really the point of all these characters is to be oh god Franklin Jellis in it you know these
characters are all sort of characters that are spider webbed out from Michael Douglas's character
in one way or another so Michael Douglas really is the weight of this film he is excellent
in it and everybody else does a very strong job so where does the problem lie because I've heard
this reaction before from fans where they say oh it was well acted it was well written but you hated
it why I'll tell you why this thing is directed like film school 101 I mean it's embarrassing to me
that a man of Oliver Stone's caliber would resort to the stupid tricks he does in this movie I mean
there's a thing the theme of the movie is time is the greatest commodity and he's like cutting away
to insert shots of calendars and dominoes falling and clock spinning it's just fucking embarrassing
there's a part where they're talking about how this green energy works and it cuts to a graphic
that shows you what they're talking about this is real amateur hour directing stuff it's Oliver Stone
thinking he's throwing a lot of fast -paced stuff that you like you didn't like a JFK for instance
which is excellent and it's just bad it's just bad the original Wall Street is a solid film it's not
great it's very heavy handed in parts but this one is even more heavy handed with its themes
and it's underscored the entire movie is underscored by this horrific David Bern
late error soundtrack like if you ever wanted to see the soundtrack to white
listen to late error David Bern like every song that plays in this thing you picture baby boomers
in their 60s dancing at a David Bern concert like thinking they're still hip like he doesn't play
one good day except at the very end he plays one the talking head song time whatever you know which
is an obvious choice what is time not time I forget there's a talking I can't remember but there's a
talking heads of song at the end of the movie finally and you're like oh that's like finally a good
David Bern song he's been playing like David Bern solo version of this song throughout the movie
was it you may ask yourself now it was something about I don't know some stupid heartfelt
I can't remember but but anyway the movie sucks it's too long fun cameo from Charlie Sheen when
he pops back up that was kind of cool seeing him and Douglas on screen to get together
is it worth a watch just for Douglas's performance yeah sure I'd say so you know and it'll
tug at your heartstrings here and there but overall it's just not a good film all I remember is
LaBouffe sitting in the dark and then like Douglas enters and he leans over and pulls the string
on the light to turn it on like revealing himself like you're getting like a 40s movie I laughed out
loud at that yeah there's that there's the like I actually want to I was like I get you to write like
a comedy scene with not for anything just just to write it down so I know I have it on hand if I
want to use it one day yeah for something but like Brolin's character it's so cliche like like LaBouffe
in his office for the first time before they meet and he's like staring at a painting and like
Brolin enters and he's like he's like the such and such such and such only three of those in
existence or you know what I mean like that whole it's like it's like oh for gods it's literally like
written like Montabon in naked gun right yeah it's absurd so anyway not a good film
uh the naked gun has a very good film but yeah I I did on one of the solo movie corners an in -depth look
at every film of Oliver Stone's and if I mentioned Wolf Wall Street 2 it was very brief because it's
just not it's it's probably the least quality film in his career it's another guy who's you know for
the last 10 years has maybe there's there's nothing that that makes you say yes Stone needed to keep
directing till we got this I think his last great movie is probably any given Sunday which is
oddly underrated for a movie that made millions and millions of dollars but I think it's really good
I watched the entire series which didn't take long it's it's uh two seasons of party down
a show I watched when it originally aired it was on stars nobody had stars it was their attempt at
comedy and it's become a real cult favorite and I get why it's it's a it's a funny show and it's
one of those where the entire cast all went on to bigger and better things or at least bigger things
it's Adam Scott who at this time is kind of an insufferable presence but he was very likable around
this time and of course step brothers where he played a hilarious douche I mean his family is singing
sweet child of mine is amazing one of the most unexpected scenes I've ever seen and I just
remember dying laughing at that in the theater but he annoys me now and it was him it's Lizzie Kaplan
who is fantastic it is Ken Marino who oddly is the heart and soul of party down his character
is probably the most broad the most insane and yet he you know he almost maybe emotional a few times
with how real he play it's he's a loser but they learn the lesson from the office of like this stuff
is all it hits harder if you really care about him and he makes it into a very well -rounded sad
deeply sad character it's a sad show under it which is I think what makes it last beyond its jokes is
that everybody wants to be something different they want they're in LA some of them want to be writers some
of them want to be actors and they just get failure after failure after failure this is the realism
of aspiring actors who work at a catering company they don't do the thing of like I got the part
and I'm the new James Bond or something you know they keep it real these guys don't get big wins
they're losers and that's the beauty of the show the crazy thing about the show is how problematic it
seems now and how problematic it did not seem at all at the time when I'm looking online you can't
find mention one of this show being like really really rough and there are so many scenes of like the
white characters saying like screaming the word jigger let's say which is a which is a like a small
amount of alcohol yeah screaming that as like the two black people in the room walk in and him going
jiggers and then they're standing behind him and that's like the end of the episode they do that joke
so many times and it's like in addition to that not flying today you've you've paid these two black
actors to be props for your joke there are no black characters on the show and it's a very large cast
with a lot of guest performances there's Kevin Hart in a very funny early scene but he's playing the
the you know pot smoking rapper it is it's wild it's like so many times there there are two black
people in the episode who are there just to accidentally hear them say something racist so right in
addition to it being a good show it also worked as sort of a weird time capsule of what was funny
in 2007 which was almost all times problematic and not not incorrectly problematic sometimes stuff
today everyone gets oversensitive we talk about that as well but this show had some issues and I'm
sure they'll be corrected in the new season which is coming out and they're supposed to be working on
now they're at least doing a party down movie right now and yeah we'll see I don't they have to
sort of address what they did the first time around but we'll see what happens it's a very it's
entertaining show more in my opinion for the the characters and the love you have for them
Jennifer Coolidge comes in she's awesome and at Megamallale he's really funny in it
yeah more more for the characters than the laughs because some of the laughs kind of stick
on your throat on this rewatch but it's a funny show uh back to the Scorsese tree I watched
after hours we had talked about it recently on the show yeah I was really in the mood to rewatch it
I'd only seen it once uh you know yes good film I wouldn't you know it's one I always thought I
should own and then when I rewatch I was like I don't need to own this uh pretty funny pretty crazy
definitely of the time for Scorsese I think he followed it with the color of money because he was in
need of a hit at that point yeah he did um because despite critical claim king of comedy and after
hours did not do well at the box office I don't think now sucks for Griffin done because he was
probably like I have made it yeah I'm starring in a Scorsese film any Griffin done set a tremendous
career don't get me wrong but um and I think he actually got some kind of nomination for that movie but
well he's a big producer now he produces a lot of documentaries and stuff like that yeah but
you know look it's it's a solid little film it's enjoyable it's a lot in the sense like taxi driver
to me where I think it's quality uh I enjoy it I guess but it's not something I'm ever going to
want to put on again uh or or rewatch and then surprisingly every character is so goddamn again
unlikable even Griffin done who you're supposed to be like kind of rooting for yeah to get home like
immediately like he sets up the date with Rosanna Arquette and then like immediately tries to
fuck her roommate right as she's out getting like you know medicine at the drugstore whatever she's
doing and he's just like it's just an odd yeah it's odd and I think that's kind of the point there's
the thing at the beginning with Bronson Pinchow where he's annoyingly talking about what he wants to do
yeah yeah working in that office first thing yeah once to start the magazine and Griffin done is
ignoring him and I think that's kind of the setup of the whole movie of like here you know we're all
in our own little world and we all think the other person's annoying until but what if you're the
guy that needs to be listened to and I think that's a cool theme um but uh it's something I don't
necessarily need to watch ever again uh you know but but but but a decent film yeah it's oh there's
a lot of people who cite it as their favorite score says you especially nowadays and I'm like
I think you're just being contrarian I think you're just picking the one of the least loved movies in his
uvra because I it's one I return to every couple years I like it a lot I love that kind of meet the
parents is oddly an after hours type story where it's just like things keep happening to the hero that
are worse and worse and worse but um I love that kind of story this one there is sort of a
soullessness to it that that just kind of keeps me at a distance I don't I don't really get into
after hours as much as I like a lot of it um I watched in the heights which is on HBO max maybe for a
couple more days it's also in theaters uh so of course if it's if it's a new movie it's got to be
two hours and 25 minutes long for no reason these Broadway shows people like
they're they're all too long even the best Broadway show uh two and a half hours they do that
because they're charging two hundred dollars to go see a Broadway show and they want people to feel
they got their money's worth that's not the case in a film people spend thirteen dollars and they're
they don't want to just sit there forever and ever and ever as a story goes well past its
sell -by date I mean there there are five songs in this thing where you're like
you know like the grandma has three lines and all of a sudden she's singing about the old country
for five minutes and you're like guys you cut this uh Lin -Manuel Miranda shows up himself as a
shaved ice vendor and you're like what what and then all of a sudden he's going
I said my pineapple and my cherry and my grape and you're like this don't let this be a full song
but it sure is it's Lin -Manuel singing about all the flavors of shaved ice he has
shaved ice vendor I thought she made a hairless ice vendor
shaved ass vendor um it's it's for I don't look for half of it I thought it was pretty delightful
I don't hate a musical but it is the genre that is probably the hardest to get right and as this
thing starts to go off the rails I mean there's a point at about the two -hour mark where you're like
what stories are we even telling here what do you like somebody needed to just come in and say look
I know this is a Broadway show that made a ton of money but there needs to be cuts here here here
and here that's a producer's job the studios job like every one of these songs is not gold you run
the risk now of cutting it and then some 12 year old girl watches it and goes where's the shaved ice
song that's the song I used to sing with my abuela you know sure so you can't please everybody the
controversy surrounding this movie is madness although it's not my place to comment on it but it's
a movie where every actor in the cast is Latina and we talked about it we already talked about it
on the show yeah so the backlash is that they weren't dark skinned enough
Rita Moreno has already apologized for this look I didn't notice it it seems to really be a celebration
of Latino culture I was speaking before having not seen the film and having seen it it's like
it feels to me like you really needed something to complain about
um I'm not saying these these complaints are
unimportant that they are that you know but in a way I agree with
with Rita Moreno and just that take the win it's it's a it's a huge victory for for Latino representation
in film again I'm a white guy what do I know but I agree I agree with her it's a wrong target that's
why I was just supported when she apologized but yeah but anyway as a celebration of Latino cold
culture you know I thought it was a pretty cool movie I think it's got a very strong first hour
and then just a mess there's also like some CGI you know it's like the beauty of these old musicals
of like Fred Astaire and Ginger Rogers dancing around is that they're doing it you know that you're
seeing them do it and it costs five dollars so like to see a shot of like 500 fake people dancing
in a pool CGI style where like it looks completely fake it's probably cost five million dollars it's
like guys you're missing the whole point you could do this cheaply you just you you get professional
dancers and have them dance amazingly but there's something about
it might have been a COVID issue yeah yeah um what's why cats were so awful is all CGI
oh god but for my last film real quick rewatched heat masterpiece yeah if you haven't seen this film
and I've been bringing it up to people for the last two weeks yeah I wouldn't watch rewatch heat
I'm alarmed at how many people are going never saw it I'm like what are you doing what see the movie
it's a masterpiece agree that's it that's all I'll say about heat if you don't know now you know
all right everybody will say oh the opening of dark night the bank robbery scene was like that's
like the best action scene ever and it's like it's heat there are people who don't even know heat
which is troubling to me uh um what's his name uh Christopher Nolan said that he he says it on the
DVD he said that heat was one of the primary cinematic influences for dark night and in the middle of
dark night Batman and Joker sit across from a table of one another that's right Joker's going you
complete me and all that's the like that's the diner scene and he's awesome there's also the scene
where Batman goes do you like cat woman because she had a great ass right uh our movie today the dentist
from one cinematic classic to another the dentist starring Corbin Bernson
always a signifier of quality I'm a fan I've always liked the guy I like that also directed by the
guy that directed society I'm blanking on his name his name is Brian Yuzna and that was a huge
reason I was excited to watch this because I think society's amazing I have had this movie sitting on
my shelf ever since I saw in search of darkness part one and they talked about it and I said why do I
not own actually quite a bit in search of darkness yeah that was the 90s I watched something maybe it
was torture maybe it was a Eli Roth's history of horror I don't know it was one of these dock you
horror things right and there's a sick segment on the the dentist they said uh it's pretty simple
premise dentist catches his wife cheat takes it out on the wrong people at work right all right that
sounds pretty cool it bought it on Amazon for like five dollars yeah and there it's set and then
you know the other week I was sitting here and I'm like why the fuck have I never watched this yet
and I texted Pat and I was like I'm gonna watch the dentist and he was like well we could do it
on the show because I can watch it too and here we are um it's a wild ride this movie it's a wild ride
it's in possession of 0 % rotten tomato rating as it is it's it's sequel and uh look you would
you would never be angry with someone for saying the dentist sucks you would never you know scream at
somebody who thought it was a masterpiece but it it it's just kind of hits the hits the bullets of
horror especially this was a straight to VHS at the time horror it's when I always saw at the
video store um it's just something it's hard to work up much passion about it goes through the
motion steward Gordon helped write it who is great I love steward Gordon but it's very much a paint
by numbers kind of story with most of the kills the action scenes that if you will uh circulating
around the mouth you know it's the same thing as like little shop of horrors where they use like a
big model of a mouth with teeth and they're drilling into them and you're like look I know they're
gonna be drilling into a fake mouth how troubling is this gonna be it's pretty troubling I mean these are
these are graphic scenes and a lot the dentist makes a lot of people uneasy yeah real life so it it
it they're effective they start out they establish right off the bat the Corbin Bernson has severe
OCD right and he severely anal anal aint attentive and he
uh it's it's his anniversary with his wife and uh he she thinks he's gone for work
and then she he catches her sucking the pull man's dick I mean it's real this is real like just
we're just gonna hit you exactly where you think we're gonna hit you who she fucking the pull man
of course like it's it's cliche's done in the best way it's also like weirdly what bothers him
seemingly more than his wife cheating is that she had this dirty penis in her mouth because he's
very cleanliness and mouth focused and obsessed yeah and the pull man's got like pull muck all over his
body right and she's got it on her body and he's and he's got some on him because she got it on him
and that's how he figured out she was fucking the guy or whatever and and then and then he follows
the pull man to find out that not only is his wife fucking the pull man her best friend that he hates
is also fucking the pull man so this guy's having a bad day he ends up murdering there
oh man's having a great day pull man's killing it yeah Corbin Bernson ends up murdering their dog
and things unfold from there when he gets to work and he has an array of the zaniest patients
a dentist could ever have there's a teenage girl who's it's her big day to get her braces off
is one of them right another one is a blonde like Bucks a model who is who was managed and potentially
being uh fucked by a character played by Mark Rufalo which when he came on the screen I was like
that's not Mark Rufalo that was like it's Mark Rufalo jaw on the floor when I saw Rufalo
it amazing he doesn't reference this movie more in his interviews and he's doing classic Rufalo
in this he's doing like he's great uh and then the first time I remember seeing him was you can't
uh you can count on me where he was I was like this guy is the best why have I never seen this guy
before turns out he had been in the dentist at that point I thought that was his first movie so did I
yeah I didn't realize he had a couple before that and then the third patient is the guy from
what's this guy from he's from like every sitcom and uh the tall bald guy uh I know who you're
referring to but I don't know who it is he plays like his accountant who's like extorting him for
free dental work yeah it's so nuts yeah so it's it's wild and he's you know he punishes all
these people it's basically you know it's basically Friday the 13th except instead of
campers dying in in creative ways it's mouth drama being done by the dentist and what's sort of the
most troubling aspect about it and it's they go into it even more in dentist too is that he's also
having hallucinations the dentist so like yeah while he's in your mouth he'll see like uh
cockroaches crawling around on your tongue and then he'll try to kill the cockroaches and wind up
you know knocking the shit out of your mouth so yeah that stuff gets pretty disturbing too you know it's
okay you almost start to feel a little sympathy for the man because he's tormented by these visions
that he's in his mind has to stop he has to stop these things that he's saying and it's like all right the
guy belongs in an asylum which is where he winds up and where he breaks out of in part two in part
two he's in paradise misery wait wait before we move to part two I want to go back
or old bowin is the actor I'm talking about okay he was in naked gun 33 and third he was in
terminator he was in all three terminators yeah um but you god damn it I'm trying to find there's
something he was on a sitcom or something where you're like oh it's that guy and I'm trying to find it
here and I'm saying what's happening I'm saying eight is enough yeah he just
I'm seeing the Jefferson's he popped up on everything uh also in this film is one Ken
Forri who who was uh the main character basically in the original dawn of the dead so it was cool seeing him
pop up in this uh but I mean what's the culmination here the culmination here is
he his staff hates him he freaks out he gets he hallucinates when he's got the model lady who
Mark Rufalo manages under anesthesia he molests her while she's under anesthesia then Mark Rufalo threatens
to kill him then one of his nurses figures out that he molested her because she finds the woman's
pantyhose he then chokes that nurse to death with the pantyhose uh he then goes to his house
where he cuts out his wife's tongue but she's still alive yeah and then finally this accountant comes in
that's trying to blackmail him for free dental work and that guy kind of takes the bullet for the
girl who's gonna get her braces off because he's gonna basically go in and and really fuck up the
girl with the with the braces and then this other guy comes in and that sort of becomes his focus
the cops bust in at the very end or no they don't bust in he gets out of the office and they catch him
because he goes to a nearby school where he sees a woman singing opera and has another weird sort of
hallucination and then that's where the cops catch him right and he goes away to an insane asylum
which is where the movie opens with him and a padded cell miming dentistry and then at the end of the
movie he's carted off to where well where else but the insane asylum's dentist who is being played by
his wife who's gonna now do horrible things to his teeth and it's assumedly uh another crazy
hallucination he's having but it's just come up and so whatever and that's where the first movie ends
all in all I give it a hog's up personally yeah uh maybe not fully erect but you know
75 degrees you know uh but I I liked it overall it's a crazy and Corbin Burnson's great he's
really good at it he's he plays good he plays crazy well I just noticed in looking through
Corbin Burnson's credits that he played the coach of the bud light team in the 1994 bud bull
the man said a wild career but um I do like him I like the film my hog would be like starting to get
chubbed like it probably is not going to lead to masturbation or anything but it's just like oh
got a little something happening down there I didn't love the film all right take him into the dentist
tuner well you're Earl Bowen by the way I always think of him as uh Reverend love joy on the
Simpsons because I feel like he looks exactly like him but he played Reverend Meacham on Mama's family
is how I know him and he also played a Reverend on on uh what is the show here
what is the show well he played a lot of reverence you know that's what I'm going to say to you
and you would recognize him if he saw him he was a Reverend in my stepmother as an alien he was a
Reverend in two episodes of the Golden Girls so he's just he's a man who looks like a Reverend clearly
uh part two opens in the insane asylum and Corbin is getting out and he heads to where's the where's
the place where uh a sadistic dentist can act out his crimes in peace Missouri my hometown
he goes to paradise Missouri but oh is that tidal ironic folks because what he's going to do here
there's nothing paradigy see about it uh the dentist too is very much like a retread he's doing
what he did in the first movie he's just doing it in a different location the town is all kind of
nice kind people and he's because he is in the throes of these hallucinations he starts killing them off
the most effective of these is probably Clint Howard who I had just seen an amazing interview with
on Jobab's show uh if you watch the evil speak episode which stars Clint Howard Jobab does
one of the best character actor interviews I've ever seen with Clint Howard they have a great time talking
and they don't mention the dentist too but he is so good that like immediately Clint Howard walks in
and you're scared for him and like he acts the scene so well that you're like God I hope he gets
out of here um I've just I don't know the past couple weeks I've become a huge Clint Howard fan
he's great he's really good in the film um but again it's the same thing it's even more of a paint by
numbers of just killing off people uh sadistic mouth stuff the mouth stuff in this one is way more
graphic than the first one and this one Coleman H Joe and I don't think you made it to the end of
dentist too but he gets a nail gun shoots like 50 nails into his face and the the last scene you see
Corbin Bernson driving off laughing maniacally as he pulls out nail after nail from his face and you're
like wow they're just going for a straight cartoon I mean he looks like pinhead at the end of this
and then for the final moment he's he's fixing a cap in his tooth with one of the nails he
just digs it into his which is one of the ongoing things in the movie I remember he's got this cap
yeah then he murders a dentist because the dentist doesn't fix his cap properly
correct right but oh good sorry no it's you get a real feeling as you watch dentist too of like
yeah this is your standard horror sequel it's like let's have him kill more people in dentist style
there's no real uh creative spark to it if the original is kind of a slightly above average
straight to VHS down the middle horror picture this one would be below that so probably not
worth your time I hated the setting of it I hated the country setting I thought it was good yeah
I love the escape sequence from the asylum I thought that really was cool and creative but then he
gets to the town and it's not like he's assuming some sort of alias it's like they know who he is
yeah and they know that he was a dentist and you see headlines in the paper and hear news
on the radio about the crazy dentist that murdered everybody has escaped and it's like how would
they not know that this was happening that would be national news right so it's it just gets off to
a very very thinly veiled I mean all they had to do was have him set up shop someplace where he
wasn't known yeah have him go back to a place where they knew him was absurd to have this plotline of
a private eye searching after him because his wife had all these postcards of the places her husband
visited was just a real half -assed detective clue way to find this guy yeah there was
I I felt like with 20 to 30 minutes more of thought this could have actually been a pretty cool
little sequel were you know because it kind of starts off in that psycho two way where you're like
maybe he is cured maybe he is better maybe it wasn't his fault maybe not his fault you know what I mean
like maybe he's had a chemical imbalance and he's fixed now man you know and then it's just it's not
that and it just doesn't even try to be that really and I would say a hog down on this one I mean it's
you know I feel a little half -assed here as a as on a movie review show saying a movie I didn't finish
I'm giving a thumbs down to but like I said the the show today was really about the dentist the
dentist too which is kind of bonus fodder right both dentists are available currently on tubi I made
fun of tubi with Joe for years on the show and it just sounded fake to me but then you get on there
and it's like if you can put up with ads they have an amazing selection and they have a lot of stuff
that other streaming services won't touch you know really controversial edgy shit on there and
I recommend I think dentist one is also on Amazon prime tubi I thought I was going to mine the ads
I was watching a little Jackson's the American Dream the other night and you love the ads you're watching
a TV mini series it feels like you're a kid again you go in you pour yourself a glass of water you
come back I kind of like it um so hog way up for tubi hog down for dentists too we will be back with
the review of the conjuring colon the devil made me do it we thank you all for your love on patreon
please continue to give us those five star ratings on iTunes if you haven't even better leave a review
um I've just started reading a lot of the comments and messages on the patreon page which we miss
so we will check those out for sure and get back to you guys on that I understand there was a few
billing issues we're addressing them we're on it thank you all for your patience see you next time see
it hell