Welcome, folks, to We'll See You in Hell.
It's a movie podcast hosted by me, Joe DeRosa, and me, Patrick Walsh, and me, Patrick Walsh,
well, Jiminy Glick. We're talking today about the night house, working on the night house.
And folks, if you saw, if you thought the day house was scary,
wait until you see what we have in store this week.
The yeah, we'll talk about it in this movie. All right.
I think it's a theatrical only release, but is scheduled to be streaming very shortly.
So if you're still not venturing out, just be patient. Everything's got like a one month
window now. So fair enough. Fair enough. What's going on, Joseph? What's happening?
What's happening in New York City? Well, I am sitting here the feast. There's a big feast
happening tonight in Bedford, Bedford, Stiverson, Bed -Stuy. No, no, no, no, not Bed -Stuy. Yeah,
Bed -Stuy. No, wait, not Bed -Stuy. Oh, boy. Bensonhurst. Bensonhurst. Okay.
Um, big Italian feast happening out there. The feast of San Gennaro. That's, that's in
Italy. No, that's here. That's in Manhattan, that one. No, this is another one. Big street
fair thing. You know, food booths. Looks like a hell of a lot of fun. I was going to go meet
Krista Stefano out there tonight because he lives kind of close to it or much closer than I do.
I was going to meet him out there at 6 PM. That was my plan for this evening,
but I just looked at Ubers and they are in the $80 range. Yeah. I think Uber and Lyft are
essentially bankrupt and are just not telling anybody, or they have no drivers or something,
but it's impossible now to get one of those things. So now you're faced with the decision,
you know, is it worth spending a lot of money to go experience this traditional New York thing?
You know, am I, am I being shortsighted if I go, I don't need to do it or do you do it? And you
get out there and you go, son of a bitch, you know, like, this is cool, but God damn it. You
know, so I don't know, there's like carnival rides and stuff and I'm just so you can have fun.
Yeah. But then the other part of me is like, I can walk up to the stand and drink with some buddies
and right. You had just have myself a little Friday, you know, so I don't know. What do you
think? Well, I think you go to the fest and go to the stand anytime, but you think it's worth
$160 round trip to go to this festival. That's what I'm saying. No, I don't know. Yeah. That's
my point. You were not talking a $20 Uber. We're talking. And then also too, I get out there. I
know. No subway. I ain't getting a fucking subway with all this shit going on right now. What are
you nuts? I didn't get on it when there wasn't a fucking pandemic. Well, I mean, you're going to a
festival with carnival rides. I don't see that much difference. You're out. I'm not going to get,
yeah, we're going out there. I'm going to go into the house of mirrors.
Not going to go on the rides. I'm just saying like, love a house of mirrors.
Uh, what do you think? If I can get out there, affordably go if I can't, it's not worth it,
right? For sure. I mean, do you still have your car, have 10, 12 drinks and drive out? Yeah.
That's the other thing I was thinking about driving my Jeep out. But like, do you think
parking near the biggest Italian festival of history is going to be easy? I think it's going
to be like, it won't be easy, but, uh, I bet you could find 10, $15 parking half mile away,
you know? Yeah. Yeah, we'll see. And then maybe you stay out there. I don't know.
Then he can't drink, you know? Yeah. It's seven miles from me, which seven miles in New York is
like, you know, it might as well fucking be, you know, might as well be in another state. Yeah.
Yeah. Anyway, there you go. That's the whole story. That's what's going on in my life and my world.
I mean, I, I sort of meant what's the, what's the city of New York going through currently? Is it,
are things back to normal pretty much or no? Yeah. We're heavily vaxxed at this point. Yeah.
They're imposing the mandatory vaccination thing to go into bars and eateries here.
Everyone? As far as I know, uh, I don't know. I've only had it once out here.
Uh, I mean, our mayor was like, this is it. Like we're imposing this. So, so, you know, look,
I say all the time, I, I, I have no problem with that. I also fully understand why somebody might
have a major problem with that, but we're living in a time where, and I think we talked about this
recently, you know, America is the United States of America. It's becoming a much more European
landscape where state to state is, is the thing. And just like in Europe where they're all on top
of each other, but it's one country is its own country. So I feel like that's sort of happening
here. And it's just a matter of, you gotta live where you can put up with it. And I realize
everybody doesn't have the means to relocate. I know I don't at the moment. I'm very lucky to be
in a, in a, in a world where, or an environment rather, where I am okay with it. So, you know,
said from the beginning, amen. If showing a vax card means I can go drink and laugh and smoke and
hook up, I don't give a shit. I just don't care. Like I'm not worried about it. So, and New York
is doing that now and New York is, I think it was the only way to keep New York, New York.
Yeah. Yeah. I did a little three bar crawl the other night. Nothing, nothing too intense,
just kind of walked from bar to bar and had a drink, but only one of them was doing it.
And I felt great about it. I felt extremely safe. I don't hook up, but I think that would be a big
appeal as you're in a place where you know, everyone is not going to get you sick.
So LA, we're, we're fine. We're kind of, I feel like we were circling another lockdown and now
maybe we're not, but our issue is they're trying to take our mayor or our governor Newsome trying
to recall him and such a fine job out there. He's done a terrible job and everyone on Twitter and
beyond has said, this guy sucks. He's the worst. Everything he does is terrible. Then they switched
on a fucking dime when this recall came up and started saying, we must keep governor Newsome.
I know he sucks, but you have to vote no on the recall. And they just shot themselves in the
fucking foot. You can only talk so much shit until people go, Hey, maybe you're right. Let's,
take them down. Our issue is if they take down governor Newsome, the front runner is this guy,
Larry Eldard, who is super Republican. He's pulled a gun on his wife. He has, he doesn't believe in
anything, climate change. He doesn't believe in the pandemic. He's taking away the mask mandate.
He's taken away the vaccine mandate. And if LA goes and is not a democratic city anymore,
California is not a democratic state anymore. The country falls pretty quickly. And I'm not,
I'm not one of these guys who thinks that California is the center of the universe or
something like that, but it's always been this democratic stronghold in the country. And if we
lose that it's bad news for a variety of reasons, because if they recall him, they're going to learn
they can do that everywhere. They can get little grassroots efforts to recall every democratic
governor in America and replace them with these extreme Republicans. I mean, this guy,
but you could, it's a two, it's a two way street. The Democrats could do that to Republican governors
and they absolutely will not because they're fucking pussies and they don't organize and they,
they don't, they, they, well, we don't play dirty, even though they fucking do, of course,
but it's like, we don't do these things. Well, then you're going to lose every time because
I wouldn't worry about it. These are, everybody here is extremely worried about it. We're at 50
right now. That's all you guys do out there is worry. That's California's pastime. Your, your,
your state mascot should be a wart. I'm not losing sleep. Don't get me wrong. I know you're not. I'm
just, I'm going to say you people. I don't mean that in a derogatory or aggressive way. Yeah,
no, I, I'm just saying the people in that environment. Look, you're in the eye of the storm,
dude. Like you're living and working in Hollywood. It's like, it's going to seem like the, you know,
the, you know, the world's about to collapse, but I, I, you know, it's, it's like the COVID
worries where they're like, well, we don't know what these new variants it's like, okay,
we didn't know what the initial one either. Yeah. So let's not start saying all the children are
dead. Right. When we don't know, let's take a breath. Keep seeing this is the worst time for
cases and it's not like it's not going great. Don't get me wrong, but like, if it's the worst
time for cases, why were we locked down for a year and now we're not? None of it makes any sense.
None of it makes any sense. We just watched Donald Trump tell a room full of Alabamians
to get vaccinated and then he believes in it and they booed him. Yeah. And then he said,
I, your, your personal liberties are very important. We need to protect them,
but I do believe in the vaccine and I'm sitting there going, did Donald Trump just nail it?
Did he just say the thing I've been thinking the whole time? What is happening in the world?
What is happening? I don't know what's going on anymore. Yeah. It's, I mean, you can't make a
hero out of the guy because if he had just fucking said, get the vaccine when he got it a year ago,
this whole situation, I don't know that it would be alleviated, but it would certainly be.
Well, I, I don't, I don't even know that that's the case. I think that I don't know. I don't think
that's the case. I knew his, his supporters at the time that he got it were telling me
that I'm friends that supported him. Yeah. That's that we're saying I'm not getting that fucking
thing. Yeah. It's like everybody's just everybody. This is what happens when you make an equal
playing field for everybody. When you tell everybody that they have a platform, social media,
and that they're allowed to be a critic. Yeah. Amazon rotten tomatoes and everything else.
We've always bitched about on this show. When you give this power to everybody,
everybody suddenly is a epidemiologist and everybody is an expert and everybody's it.
So then you go, here's a president that I love. Not me. I'm just saying a person. Right. Here's
a president I loved and supported tooth and nail to the point of certain people, not everybody,
but certain people that liked him supporting a storming of the Capitol.
And now I'm not going to follow his lead. Yeah. It's nuts. It's wild stuff. It's wild stuff.
And you got Democrats doing that with, with Biden and yeah. I mean, I think the only way out,
the only way out is, is going to be this vaccine mandate. And I think they are going to do it,
but I think they're going to do it nine months from now when it's just too fucking late.
They don't, they're, they're, they're scared of riots in the streets. They're scared of violence
and they should be. These people will not go quietly. They're already comparing it to the
fucking Nazi party every chance they get, but it's like, they're going to have to do it.
So why not just do it? It's this pussy footing around. That's not helping anybody. I think,
but they're not going to do it though, because the group of people not getting vaccinated far
exceeds crazy right -wing people. Well, it is a very, it is an extremely, extremely diverse
group of people. Yeah. The dams will only continue to paint it to their advantage of saying by
demonizing just the Republicans. I know plenty of people on the left that haven't gotten it.
And the whole anti -vax thing started with like far left -wing hippie types. That's where it all came
from initially. So, and then it was adopted and, and, and, and, and amplified by the right. Sure.
And sure. The typical right -wing pundits take on this is, is what is advantageous to them is to
talk it down. Why? Cause the gut, cause the dams are only talking it up. So doesn't matter. It's
not going away. Nobody. And we have now made a, we've made it protocol in this country that
whoever you are, whatever your causes, whatever you represent, if you don't like something,
you can storm it. Yeah. Well, destroy it. So you know, those graphs that are like the two circles
and then it's where they meet in the middle and there's a little diamond or whatever, where they
meet. There is no diamond anymore. It, there always used to be, it would be Republicans have
their beliefs. Democrats have their beliefs. And here are the areas where we see eye to eye.
But now, which unquestionably was fueled by Trump, they, there is no overlap. They,
they will not say, I agree with you on anything because they're so both sides are so disgusted
with each other. It's beyond polite disagreement. It's disgust and hate. And they, we are saying,
I don't agree with a single word you say, and I never will. And in that case, at some point,
I think we're going to have to divide the country. You know, I think, yeah, well, I don't know what
else, what the other option is. Absolutely good. You live in a blue state. If you want to live in
a blue state, I live in a red state. If you want to live in a red state, I respect everybody's
personal freedoms and beliefs. Yeah. I think, I think Trump certainly put the icing on this cake.
I do not blame him for starting it by any stretch. I think you can go way back before him. I think
the, the left calling anybody that could have thought to vote for him, a racist and a moron
was a horrible, horrible fucking misstep on their part. And then, but before that,
I don't think anybody who voted for him was a racist and a moron. I think people who were
supporting him three years in were racist and morons. Yes. Um, I think, and you can disagree
with that. That's fine. I think that's my, but I'm saying the left started saying that during the,
his campaign. Yeah, no, they did for sure. But, but then you could flip it and go, yeah,
but that's just a response to the way the right responded to Obama. And you could go, yeah,
but that was just a response to the way it goes on and on and on and on. The bottom line is
snowball has been a rolling a long, long time and old Trumpy is the cherry on top
to the point now where who knows what the hell is going to happen. My point is this, you gotta,
it's, I said it in my hour special years ago, Walsh, and I hate to pat myself on the back,
but I have been prophetic in my day, the hour special that you didn't come to,
you had to go see Tom Petty. Uh, no, it's actually worse. It was, it was anti -vaxxer Van Morrison,
but it was, it was, uh, if it was me and Heather going to the show, I would have sold my tickets
in five minutes. I was taking her father and mother to a show. I'm breaking your balls.
Plan years in advance. I know years, not years years. Uh, I know I'm busting your balls,
but I had a thing about Arizona in that hour where I was like, stop wasting my time with how we need
to make Arizona evolve. Don't go to Arizona anymore. If you don't like what they're doing,
which a lot of us don't, don't go there. If you can put up with what they're doing, go there.
But this idea that we have to make them think and act in a certain way, it's pointless. It has never
in the history of humanity ever. It doesn't fucking work. So let it go. Just let it go.
Go live your life. That's it. All right. Enough controversy. Let's talk. Is this,
do we talk about this too much? Not at all. Let's move on to Afghanistan.
No, I mean, it's a, it's a time, man. We are living. I don't want to be living through
history anymore. I would be fine living through boredom again. It was fine by me.
And sorry, I do apologize to anybody getting a little irritated with this because I know it's,
you don't tune in for this kind of talk. You tune in for the movie talk, but I will say this.
I do think that anymore. This subject matter is almost synonymous with the entertainment talk
because the, every problem we're discussing right now is reflected in entertainment.
And that's kind of where it all starts. It all starts with, we're going to cut this here. We're
going to make this do that over there. And people go, Oh, stop being ridiculous. And it's not going
to get out of control. And that's crazy. And this and that, and here the fuck we are. It's gotten
that crazy. Yeah. In my opinion, on all sides, I know people, other people think it's worse on one
side versus the other, whatever. That's fine too. My opinion, it is, it has exploded down to a point
where it's, it's just nuts. It's just, everything is nuts. I've been pitching a show
for the last couple of weeks and generally just, it's something you learn from your parents.
Don't talk politics, you know, don't talk religion. Yeah. And now I go into pitch and
the questions that follow this pitch of a show that is not super political,
revolve around politics, diversity, the world, red states, blue states, et cetera. It to say that
it's separate from entertainment is kind of silly, but I do get that if you come here for,
for movie talk, you might get annoyed and we'll, we'll move on to movies now.
And you're going to get that movie talk bitch. Here it comes. I have three, instead of movie
corner for me today, I have three new psychos that I want to discuss. Let's do it. And I want to,
I don't want to just glaze over them. Number one, the venom trailer for the old one. Is
there a new one? Yeah. Venom let there be carnage. The new trailer. Did you know? Okay.
Trailer starts. You're pretty excited. You got Woody Harrelson in there as carnage,
whereas he says carnage.
The effects look cool. The venom character looks really cool. Carnage is a cool character.
This is going to be cool to watch these two face off. I'm like, all right, they're jumping in with
both feet. The, the, the criticism of the first one was it took too long for him to turn into
venom. You didn't get enough of that, blah, blah, blah, blah. This one clearly, you know,
we're in the mix already. So I'm excited. I'm watching the trailer and then comes
the inevitable fucking Marvel humor. They just can't fucking help themselves to a point now
where they've got this alien symbiote or whatever it's called, who's supposed to be the most vicious,
scariest, carnivorous, human eating demon that has ever walked the earth, cracking jokes, cracking
jokes, hitting Eddie Brock, who's the host played by what's his face Capone, Tom Hardy, Tom Hardy,
like jokes were like the venom demon arm comes out of his chest and like hits him in the nose.
And he's like, ow. And he's like, and then the demon's like, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I didn't mean
to do that. And then he does it again. And he's like, I'm sorry, I just like hitting you too much.
And then like being like, you're a loser. I thought it was definitely too much when he did the,
got your nose bit to Tom Hardy. I was taken out of the film by that. I mean, it's just like,
it's like, you're doing like three stooges humor. Yeah. Get a hold of yourselves Marvel.
Get a hold of yourselves. Stop with the goddamn jokes. The for me, and you know, my opinion
is not a good one of these movies. But for me, the sweet spot is somewhere between that stupid
Marvel three stooges shit and the solemn, we're all at a military funeral vibe of DC movies.
And very rarely do they hit that. But you can have humor without like gags.
Yeah, for sure. Like one of the gags, one of the gags in this is like he meets his ex girlfriend's
new fiance. Yeah. And he's like, he's like, nice to meet you. You seem like a nice guy. And then
you hear the demon in his head go. It is not nice to meet him. We do not like him. And then,
and then Eddie Brock slaps the guy in the face. And he's like, sorry about that. And then the,
and then as he walks away, the new boyfriend goes, he needs some serious couples counseling.
That's the, that's the last line of the venom. Let there be carnage trailer.
Yeah, I, you know, really, when I'm describing that sweet spot, I think I'm describing Suicide
Squad, the only one of these movies I've liked, or the Suicide Squad, excuse me. How did these
Supers, the Spider -Man trailer look, because I know everybody was shitting their jeans over that
one. That looked pretty cool. Okay. I love bringing Molina back. Always happy to see Molina. Yeah,
that was very cool when he comes back. But again, this is another classic case of Marvel just
completely fucking ripping off DC. As soon as, I mean, it's just unfucking believable, man.
As soon as they announced Batman versus Superman, all of a sudden it was going to be Captain America
Civil War. Right. And it was going to be the Avengers fighting the Avengers. Oh, really?
Where'd you get that idea, Marvel? Then they announced two years ago that Flash is going to
be Flashpoint, where they, where it's Crisis on Infinite Earths. And they start on the television
show, The Flash, tying together all the different universes of DC and saying like, we're bringing
this in from the Christopher Reeve universe. We're bringing Keaton in from the Burton universe.
We're bringing Affleck in from that universe. And we're going to start crossing everything over
in this weird time, you know, this time warp thing that's happening. And then what happens
with Spider -Man? Oh, you're doing the multiverse for the next Spider -Man. Oh, and you're bringing
all the Spider -Man's back. And now Malene has crossed over from that dimension into the new.
They're just such fucking hacks. I really, really, really do not like Marvel at all.
You suck. You suck. And the Eternals, my God. I mean, it's just like, it just looks so boring.
It just looks so boring. And I love that in that trailer, they go, they go, well, why did you guys
fight all the other fights we've been fighting? It's like, well, we didn't have them in the
franchise plan at that point. That's why they go, we were forbidden to be called. Shut the fuck up.
Well, the picture I'm taking out involves a member of the Eternals. So I won't be speaking on it,
but I think it looks visually cool. I mean, I don't, the trailers I see are kind of wordless.
I don't even know what it is. I got nothing against any of the actors of the Eternals.
Yeah. I just think the movie looks painfully fucking boring. And then they, what's it called?
And Marvel, and I mean, just hitting the peak of gluttony, the peak of gluttony is now them casting
the same actor in different character roles. When is it enough? Well, when is it enough?
When Doc Ock, Malinak is talking to Peter Parker, in that world, is it Tobey Maguire,
or does he know it's a different Spider -Man? He's crossing over from the Tobey Maguire
universe into this Spider -Man's universe. There are multiple realities, which is exactly what
The Flash is doing, which is how Keaton and Affleck are going to be together in this one,
because they're crossing realities. Did Sam Raimi do the new one? Sam Raimi is doing the Dr. Strange
movie, the sequel. Oh, okay. Okay. So I'm excited about that. I mean, I like those Maguire Spider -Mans,
even the third one. I enjoyed it. I do too. I actually, like I said, the Spider -Man trailer
was good. I was excited to see Malinak. There are heavy rumors that Defoe is coming back as Goblin.
Yeah. That they're going to bring Andrew Garfield in. Jamie Foxx has already
confirmed as Electro, so you know they're crossing over with the Andrew Garfield universe.
That was far and away the worst of any of these movies, was the Spider -Man with Jamie Foxx. And
I can't believe they would bring that horrible character back. Well, I think the idea here is,
and it's a smart idea, it's let's right all the wrongs. We can right all the wrongs here.
So, you know, my point is, is I have nothing against any of the actors in any of these.
Well, some of the actors, but not for the most part, not anything against any of the actors in
any of these movies. These movies just, it's so goddamn paint by numbers. And it's, what was I
saying? Oh, who from the Eternals are you going out with? Well, I don't want to say. I mean,
it's not a pitch that I can discuss. I probably shouldn't have even said that.
Oh, oh, well, sorry. Somebody's got meetings with Joe Lee, it sounds like.
You know who I'm going out with, Joe, but I can't say it on the air at the moment. It'll be
announced. No, I don't know who you're going out with. We haven't discussed it. You don't tell me
anything. I'm disgusted by you. You keep, no, we haven't discussed it. I said, I know I flipped it.
I did a little fun word play. Look, save something for the pitch, man.
It's done. I've already pitched it. Do you think it's going to go? It has sold. Oh,
that thing you were telling me about. Yeah, Joe. Oh, okay. That's great. Yeah. That's great. Yeah.
That's pretty cool. Well, I wish you best of luck with that. And I like that actor quite a bit.
Thank you very much. And so do I. I thought maybe you were going out with another member.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, of the Eternals. I'm dating Salma Hayek. That might be the confusion.
I've been seeing Kamel Nanjiani quietly in a CD motels around the country.
I don't know if I've told this Conan story. It's a two second story, but Salma Hayek came
to Conan when I was there and she was wearing like, it might as well have been in a bikini.
She comes up and she had to sign the paper that which get everyone who appears in a talk show
gets $600, which I'm sure is laughable to these people. But I'm handing her the clipboard to sign
it. And she like rested it on her chest. And I was like, I was literally talking to her like,
Hey, yeah. I mean, I could not pull myself together. She is extraordinary looking
and has been for 30 years. She's unbelievable looking. Yeah. You're doing the old
car horn goes off.
Yeah. All right. Second, second news. Psycho trailer. I saw that I was very excited for,
and I didn't think I cared until I saw the trailer and I was like, this movie looks
fantastic. The eyes of Tammy Faye caught that really good, man.
It does. I was always fascinated with those guys. Tammy and, and, and I are just forgot the man's
name. You just said, which is troubling to me. Andrew Garfield. Yeah. But also Garfield,
eyes of Baker, Jim Baker. Okay. Yeah. Yeah. They both look great in it, especially Chastain.
And I guess it's D 'Onofrio is Jim Falwell, right? Is that who that was? Jesus. I didn't even catch
that. If that's who it was. Jerry Falwell. Yeah, Jerry Falwell. It, it looks great. It
really does. It's like to me, any movie that comes out now that isn't one of these giant robots
throwing each other around is exciting to me. I like movies about people. And I love that. It's
like, it looks like it's going to show this wonderful, amazing side to Tammy Faye that a
lot of us didn't know, you know, for years, she was just the punchline to the joke of makeup,
you know? Right. And this is like, they show you in the trailer, like that she has sympathy for
this guy that has AIDS. And like, it's, it's very controversial in their community, because that's,
you know, that was back when they were all saying it was a sin and all that shit. So it looks like
she was fucking around. I mean, there might've been news stories at the time, but I didn't know
that. I don't think any of us knew because all the focus was on Jim Baker getting caught with
fucking Jessica Hahn. Right. Right. In the hotel and then blubbering like a baby. Yeah. Remember
that? I'm so sorry. What a fucking idiot. Yeah. There's been a long, rich history of, of idiots
falling for idiots, you know, just, just going like, yeah, these people are right. And it,
I'll never understand it, but that's, that's the beauty of life, you know? Like they were,
they were huge and seen as religious paragons. Even after that, is paragon a word?
Uh, I think it is. I'm going to look up paragon. Paragon. I think I hope I used it correctly. I
typed in paragon and it brought up Yahoo finance. That's really weird to me. A person or thing
regarded as a perfect example of a particular quality. Yes, I'm right. A person viewed as a
model of excellence. Trust yourself, Pat. Trust your vocabulary. Uh, yeah, the movie looks great.
I agree with you to go back to Spider -Man for one second. They showed the Doc Ock Spider -Man
fight and they were like, isn't it tragic that this fight from 2002 has not been bettered by
superhero cinema? And I completely agree because Sam Raimi knows how to direct the fucking action
sequence and you're watching this thing that should feel dated and old and it seems completely
fresh. You know what each party's point of view is. You know why they're fighting and you know
where they are in relation to each other, which is just the bare minimum. But sometimes you don't
get that in today's action movies. Right. Well, wait, I don't understand the what, who's saying
what about what about the Doc Ock fight? What hasn't been bettered? The, the, the fight in
Spider -Man two, the, the, the Raimi one, they're just like, isn't it sad that with all the
advancements in technology, this fight hasn't been bettered by super superhero cinema and I agree.
Or something. No, it looked great. That's what they're saying. I think I'm being quite clear.
Oh, you're saying like it's never been beat, even though they can do so much. Oh, okay. Okay.
We never made it better. No, no, no. And they showed, you know, Spider -Man flying through
New York and it was like, why does this look better than current Spider -Mans? You know,
and it's, it's true. It's like, it's the same way Jurassic Park looks better than
Jurassic world. You know, it's like they've, they've, they've gone too far and fuck things up.
And let me be house. We're discussing tonight. Somebody pointed this out to me in the theater
by talking, but they, there are no, there's no wild, they did it digitally. So like the
lake behind them is still the entire time. Yeah. It's a CGI lake. Like that's how bad things are
getting. Everything has to be CGI. I mean, guys, it's a one location shoot. You can't just rent a
house and shoot in it. Agree more like serious. And then also when everybody goes home for the
day, Rebecca Hall just gets to live in a beautiful lake house instead of some fucking hotel.
Like rent an Airbnb, you know, on the lake. I just, I do not get why everything's CGI.
I just read some big thread from Edward Zwick, who's a director. He did glory and courage under
fire. And all these, you also did the sequel glory hole. He did do glory hole, which I liked
by the way I liked it was a departure, but it was good. It was certainly a departure. And I
think we were all shocked that Denzel returned for it, but the, the, he did a thread on Twitter that
was all about, uh, directing tips and it was circulated a lot. Cause these are really good
tips. His number one is call ahead and ask about actors and find out if they're monsters. And I
was like, yep, that's number one. But then he also had some great points. Like the one kind of
disturbing thing was he was like, I did a movie once where you see the actor on film day one.
And you're like, this guy doesn't look too good. And he's a big movie star. This is a problem.
And then you're like, okay, maybe he's hung over. And then day two, it's like, Oh God, this guy
doesn't look good on camera. What are we going to do? And then somebody came in because he's an
old kind of old school director and was like, Ed, they do it with CGI. There's stuff we don't even
know about. They'll go through and I'm not just talking about the X -Men where they're de -aging
Patrick Stewart or whatever. If an actor's got wrinkles or an actor's hung over red face or
splotchy, they CGI that that's how these budgets get completely out of control. And it's also how
we watching movies feel terrible about ourselves because we don't look like these actors, but they
don't look like themselves. It's insane. I always wished I could see the genitals of all the biggest
actors in the world, not for perverted reasons, but that would be the great equalizer. You know,
very few people have attractive looking genitals. I just listened to Sam Jackson on Stern, a
wonderful interview of Sam Jackson on Stern and they were talking to him. Stern was like, would
you ever show? He always asks actors, do you get hard in sex scenes? It's like his number one
question. And Samuel Jackson was like, I tell them, you know, I took this from Denzel because I tell
him, I'm sorry if I do, and I'm sorry if I don't, which I thought was very funny. But he also said,
like, you know, Stern was like, wouldn't you show your penis? Have you ever shown your penis? Would
you show your penis on camera? And he goes, no. And he's like, honestly, the reason is it's fine.
It's not super impressive. He goes, my whole thing is I'm the guy who walks into a room and goes,
listen up motherfuckers. And if they see that I got a normal sized dick, those motherfuckers aren't
going to listen to me anymore. And I was like, that's exactly it. The only big stars I've seen
do it are like Willis in color of night. And he had a good size hog. I mean, the only actors who
want to show it are the ones who got big old dicks. That is true, baby. That is true. Unless
it's a comedy dick, like in sideways, where the comedy is that it's a little dick flopping around,
you know. So my last news psycho, and then you can do your, then you can do your little movie
corner. Thanks, Joe. It's about the reviews of the new Candyman. Yeah,
excited to see it. I'm hearing a weird thumping on your end, by the way.
Consistently? I'm touching my computer. It's probably that to stop doing that, I guess. I
got it. Yeah, I need to go to the website. It's like a heart. It's like I'm hearing your heartbeat.
Is it done now? Yeah. Okay. So I'm going to go to top critics reviews as of now Candyman,
just open to I'm half excited. Look, you know, I think it's a duty of ours
on this show to speak honestly about the movies we like whether or not or dislike whether or not
people or colleagues are involved with them. And you know, look, I'm a guy that roots for
Gordon Peele. I am in the class of people thinking that Get Out was one of the greatest
horror movies ever made. You know my thoughts on a lot of what he's done since. I don't mean
for them to be spiteful, but I don't like a lot of what he's done since. And my continued,
my continued criticism has been the message is too heavy handed at the expense of the enjoyment
of the film. And the reviews of Candyman for the most part are pretty good. Like I said,
it's got an 87%. My concern is the few bad ones I've read
is that are exactly this. Sarah Tao Black says the kernels of complex ideas regarding race,
class and gender are too often thrown out or too often thrown out at us without consideration for
full breath and form. Adam Graham says Candyman lacks a center as well as grounding. Chris Hewitt
says, Nia da Costa, the director has lots of ideas and she seems determined to cram every single one
of them into Candyman. That was my problem with us. Yeah. A black critic. And I think that's
relevant to point out with a movie like this and with Jordan Peele's company, because it is very
race based stuff, right? He said, yeah, I was about to say the most negative reviews I've read
have been black critics. Yeah. Robert Daniels of Polygon says Candyman is so message driven that
it flattens into a generic fable. It's like, so look, am I going to see it? Absolutely. Are we
going to review it on the show? Absolutely. But my hopes are a bit dashed because this is a lot of,
this is exactly what happened with us. Everybody said it was this coming and birth of this
brilliant new art artist. And if you remember, the one guy said, we have our Hitchcock about
Jordan Peele, whatever. But those few bad reviews kind of got lost in the shuffle. And the few bad
reviews were the ones I agreed with, not even having read them. So I'm seeing the word slow burn
a lot in the reviews. You know, that scares me a little bit. That said, I look forward to seeing it.
I hope it's good. But the message driven, you know, I saw another review that was like, we're,
we are more than our tragedy. It was like one of those reviews. And I was like, oh boy, like,
right, you know, so we'll see. Well, the hope is it wouldn't be along the lines of like an antebellum.
But yeah, it's, I think it looks really cool. Of course, I enjoy the original. I still got high
hopes, but I have been seeing the reviews get kind of more and more mixed, fingers crossed. I've
never seen the Candyman sequels or any of them good. Farewell to the flesh is passable. I never
saw Day of the Dead. Yeah, I think that one was straight to DVD, if I'm not mistaken. I might have
tried to start it once and I was like, yeah, this is like, yeah, I actually want to purchase all of
them. I think I have the, I think I have the Scream Factory version of the Ridge. I do. Yeah,
I believe that was one of the ones you could get recently for like, it was like a hell of a deal.
It was like $14 or something. But I don't own the other ones, but I'm not against actually
eventually purchasing the other ones. And I hope Tony Todd shows up in this. I mean, there's heavy
speculation that he will. Would be awesome. I don't know. But yeah, I'm going to see it as soon as
possible. So it doesn't get ruined for me. But for me, my movie corn is this. I finished watching
White Lotus on HBO. It's also on HBO Max. I really liked this show. Speaking of reviews,
this is a show that like everyone seemed obsessed with. And now that it has ended, the backlash has
really begun and a lot of people are criticizing it for being a show. It's entirely about white
privilege. It's about these very privileged white people who go to a Hawaiian island, treat the
like shit, don't care about the culture of the island and are so swept up in their own problems
that they don't really notice what's going on around them. But that's the commentary, right?
Like it's to me, that's called satire. And that's what it all that's the whole point of the show.
Is it a comedy? Yeah, a dark comedy. Okay, it's Mike White, who wrote School of Rock, he did
the enlightened with Laura Dern, which was a brilliant show on HBO that ran for a couple
years. He's done a lot of really good work. He worked on Freaks and Geeks, all kinds of things.
But it's very good. I love the show. It's stolen by my friend, Jennifer Coolidge,
who I am extremely proud of. It's a little annoying to see her getting all this praise
for the one role that she is more serious in, because it's just another way that critics are
so biased against comedy. She's one of the most brilliant comedic performers of all time, in my
opinion. And it's like she can't get praise for it until she's in a more serious role. But she's
very funny in it too. Steve Zahn is awesome in it. Natasha Rothwell is awesome in it. The guy who
plays the hotel manager is awesome. I've never seen him before. Is this the one with Kidman?
No, that's Nine Perfect Strangers. Oh, that's why I asked if it was a comedy.
Okay. And basically all the reviews of that were, oh boy, I bet they wish they didn't come along
after The White Lotus because this ain't good. She's doing a Russian accent on that thing, Nicole
Kidman, that is absolutely absurd. But The White Lotus, I've read all these reviews. The most
interesting ones are by black critics, minority critics, who think that it missed the boat and
that it was almost celebrating white privilege. And it was all written by Mike White. So that means
it's all just one middle -aged white guy's opinion. The interviews with Mike White have been fascinating
where he's like, am I supposed to stop writing? Am I supposed to hate what I do just because of
where society is headed? There's a lot of really interesting stuff to dig into for a six episode
comedy series. And that's what I loved about it. I had great conversations with my wife.
I've really enjoyed reading the discourse online about it. And I've agreed with both sides and the
points they make. I do think Mike White is smarter than a lot of these people take him for and that
he's criticizing these people. I hated these people and I think you're supposed to.
But his gift is portraying characters that feel very, very real, slightly heightened. I mean,
you hate them, but it all just felt very real to me. That's why it's exactly why we're losing
Bret Easton Ellis. Yeah. Bret Easton Ellis's content now is a podcast that was fully behind
the paywall and I'm sure it's a great podcast. Yeah. I might even subscribe to it. What I've
heard of it, I've enjoyed, but it's like, it's why we're losing him because he's a guy where it's
like, you couldn't get a guy that's probably more centered and open -minded and was at the forefront
of progressive culture when it was still quite taboo and these things. And you know,
you can hear it, man. He's had it with the shit. It's like, oh, because I write characters. He's
never said this, but I'm assuming he would agree. Like, because I write characters that don't redeem
themselves in the end. Yeah. Like, you know, it's like, fuck you. They take it as though the writer
is supporting it. It's like what I said in the last episode about Scorsese and racism. It's like,
just because you don't have somebody come in and say this is wrong does not mean the writer agrees
with it. But the points are good ones. I mean, in the premiere, there's a Hawaiian woman whose water
breaks and she gives birth. She's a worker at the hotel. And then it's like, what happened to her
character? We never see her again. There's one other Hawaiian character who's kind of central,
but then he gets in trouble for stealing. And one of the other characters puts him up to it. And
it's like, so they just come in and just use him and toss him to the side. And it's like, yeah,
guys, that's the point of the show. It's white. And unfortunately that means you're not going to
have as well -rounded characters for the diverse characters because it's presenting them as not
important to these white people at all. And that's true to life. And that was, to me,
the whole point of the show. This is like when they were like, that dipshit reporter goes
to Tarantino, why would you have, what's your face?
Pamela. Harley Quinn. Margot Robbie. Why would you have Margot Robbie in this movie and give
her so little to do? It's like dipshit, do you think he picks the cast and then writes the movie
for them? He's that fucking established that Margot Robbie was willing to do a two -line part
in a Tarantino movie. It's not the other way around you dumb fuck. God damn it.
At its core, that movie is about late in life male friendship. That's what that movie is about. So
of course the focus is going to be on these two guys. We're both reading the book by the way.
I love the book. It's very specifically geared towards people who like film, I think. There's
30 page chunks where they're talking about actor's careers and it's like, well, I love this with the
average reader. I don't know. I'm earmarking every Sith page. There's five movies on this page.
To me, that's a kick, but it's not going to be for everybody. I really recommend The White Lotus.
It's six hours of your time. It's definitely a conversation piece. There's lots of stuff in it
that's like, whoa, you know, like big water cooler type moments. And the cast kills it, you know,
and I get the criticism. I get the love. I recommend it. It's a good show.
We got, what's her name in it? From D 'Addario. Yeah. The hottest girl that has ever lived.
Yeah. And she plays that in this. She is really good in it in a way that she has never been allowed
to be. She's very good in this. And her boyfriend in the show, Jake Lacey, who's an actor you've
seen in a bunch of stuff plays the greatest entitled fratty asshole I've seen in a long, long time.
So they float in the first episode. It's like a murder. She wrote, you know, that one of the
on the island dies, but you don't know how I, my, my recommendation is don't worry about that too
much because you just sit and enjoy the characters and their interaction. It doesn't really work as
an effective murder mystery. It's just kind of, they needed a hook to get them on the island.
I saw a double feature at the new Beverly. I'm so glad it's open speaking of Mr. Tarantino,
but I saw a double feature of two old Steve Martin's one dead men don't wear plaid,
which when I was a kid, my favorites were Steve Martin and John Candy. No one came close except
maybe short and chase for a while, but, um, dead men don't wear plaid left me cold. Then
it left me lukewarm. Now it's a cool gimmick that he's it's a film noir parody of sorts.
He did it with Carl Reiner after the jerk and it's all in black and white and it's Steve Martin
interacting with film noir movies. So he's like when he makes a call, an old clip of Humphrey
Bogart in a, in a Maltese Falcon type movie answers the phone on the other end. So that's
kind of its hook. It's gimmick is that it's Steve Martin talking to all these old greats from old
Hollywood. That works really well. It's seamless. It's shot beautifully by Michael Chapman who did
raging bull, great black and white photography. As far as like hard laughs, it doesn't quite
do it for me, especially for a Steve Martin classic, but I like the movie. Uh, and then the
follow up to that was Carl Reiner and Steve Martin. Again, they made three movies together,
the jerk, which is of course the best dead men don't wear plaid, which is fine. And then
the man with two brains, which I think is super funny. Kathleen Turner kind of steals the movie.
Steve Martin has some hilarious bits in it. Uh, but by the end, when they're all running around
the mad scientist lab, it's kind of like, wrap this up. It, it, it has the problem. A lot of
comedies have where you start getting bored and you've only been watching it for like an hour,
you know, because I used to say, why do comedies need a story? And the reason they need a story
is because they got to get you to the end. Gags can't always take you there. It works with like
wet hot. It works occasionally. It works with MacGruber, but you do need a plot if the jokes
aren't a plus level throughout. And men with two brains doesn't really have that. I liked it.
It's Sissy Spacek is the voice of a brain and he wants to put her in the amazing body of Kathleen
Turner, uh, who plays just the biggest bitch in the world. He's obsessed with her physically,
but he wants her to be nicer and be better. So he tries to do a brain transplant. It's kind of
the bride of Frankenstein story. Some big laughs, especially early on, if you've never seen them,
but they're not Steve Martin classics in my opinion. Have you seen either one Joe?
Neither. Really? Neither. Never. My mom tried to show me a man with two brains when I was a kid
and I hated it. Okay. Okay. And then, uh, dead men don't wear plaid. I just never had any interest
whatsoever. Well, that title doesn't lure you in. That's for sure. The, uh, I, uh, I'm not a fan of
the jerk either, which I know was sacrilegious to a lot of people, but I don't find it funny.
I love the jerk, but I would put it, you know, pretty far down the list of, of Steve Martin's.
I think he's made better movies, but I think it's got a huge laughs in it for sure.
Steve Martin to me is funniest with like, I thought he was, I thought he, I like his standup,
but to me he's funnier when he ditched the whole, I'm an idiot thing. Yeah. I like that. I like
that version of Steve Martin way better. Sure. Well, he exudes such intelligence that you don't
really buy it in a weird way. Like his whole standup was, I'm an, I'm a wild, crazy idiot
kind of thing. And, uh, that's not my favorite stuff with his either. I think he is truly a
comedic persona like no other. There's never been anyone quite like him and he's, he's been great
in stuff and weird and stuff. You know, sometimes he doesn't work at all, but, uh, just a huge
favorite of mine. I love the guy. All right. Well, let's get, you know, watch that new short,
Martin, uh, it Selena Gomez. I'm fairly interested in it. It's interesting that Selena Gomez is in
it because she was one of the more, she made her, I think her last movie was a Woody Allen movie.
And this movie to me is Manhattan murder mystery. I mean, it looks, it's almost similar, identical.
If podcasts had been around and if Woody Allen had ever heard of a podcast, then yes, it would
have been for sure. Yeah. So I was, uh, I want to check it out. I mean, I don't know. It looks,
it looks similar, but, uh, you know, it's Martin Short and Steve and Steve Martin. Yeah. They
haven't acted in anything together since three amigos. I'm down. It almost makes me sad that
Chevy's not in there with them, you know? Yeah, no, I'm excited about it. When I saw the, I saw
their standup special on Netflix, of course, but then I saw them live here at the Greek and it's
great. You know, they're, they're, they're older, they're in their seventies and you feel that,
but it's, they're still super, super funny and great together. So I'm excited to watch it.
And I still sort of, because it was like a side of New York that I saw before I ever lived here.
Yeah. And a side of New York that will never accept me or I will be a part of, but I still
have a, I romanticize that upper west side pseudo intellectual. Right. My going to my analyst. Yeah.
Yeah. I mean, I just, I couldn't pay my way into one of those cocktail parties, but
it always looks like fun to me. Um, anyway, uh, our movie today
is the night house, not to be confused with any of the other house films, house one, house two,
horror movie titles. I mean, they have a real problem. There are so many of them that are so
generic that like, if you go up and even like, even when I went up to buy my ticket for the
generic title and I texted Joe before I was like, I'm going to see spooky house. I knew it wasn't
called spooky house, but I also had no idea what it was called. I think this was originally called
the lake house. I think when I first saw the trailer, it was called the lake house and it was
retitled. I think there's a, there's a Sandy Bullock Keanu Reeves movie where they communicate
and that's my mailbox. That's what I'm thinking of. Nevermind. Then this was always called the
night house. Um, when I saw the trailer, all I remembered was this. I didn't remember the trailer.
I just remembered seeing it and then I wasn't interested because Rebecca Hall has done some
indie horror flicks that I've found very boring. Uh, you know, and they've flown mostly under the
radar, but she's been in a few where I'm like, Oh cool. Rebecca Hall is a good actor. This is a
horror movie. It must be good. And then I'm just kind of bored senseless. Yeah. Yeah. However, uh,
we've been locked in fewer things are hitting theaters. And when a new horror movie does hit
the theater, I get excited about it. Uh, this resurfaced. I didn't quite remember seeing the
trailer. I just saw that it was getting good reviews. I was excited. I said to Pat,
we should review this. He said, what the fuck are you talking about? I've never even heard of it.
I said, it's some new Rebecca Hall. Heart's supposed to be pretty good.
Uh, and then I went to see it and I ended up texting Pat an apology that I made both of us see
this film. Uh, I think he liked it better than I did. It's a, I mean, you want to talk slow burns.
This is a movie about a woman who's husband, again, spoilers as always, but a woman whose husband has
died. You learned that very early in the film. You then learned that he had shot himself.
Hmm. That becomes a confusing aspect because they seem to have had a very good marriage.
They do the old afterlife Ricky Gervais thing where she's watching old videos of them.
And by the way, you gotta find another way to tell that, you know, the, the,
no, and it goes both ways. I mean, every cop movie, it's a guy up late drinking bourbon,
watching his wife on a beach with like the wind blowing her blonde hair around. And it's like,
guys, you gotta find another way to tell this story. And by the way, by the way,
there, they portray it in movies coming out in 2020 and 2021. Like it's a guy with a Sony
shoulder cam in the eighties. This footage is like, it looks like snuff film footage. It's great.
It's like everybody has a high definition camera in their pocket. Now Rebecca Hall is 40, her
husband, you know, these videos would have been taken five years ago. Give me a fuck a break.
So anyway, yeah. Um, and slowly the mystery unravels of why he killed himself.
Was he having an affair? It seems that he was, it seems that he was having affairs with numerous
women. It seems that she never really knew her husband. And then the big reveal is they, she
finds plans for a house. He had built their house that they live in and she finds plans for the
for an exact opposite replica of the house. So it's a complete reverse version.
And lo and behold, at nighttime, this house illuminates
somehow across the lake, even though nobody has ever seen it. Nobody knows it's there.
She goes looking for the house. She does find it. There is a structure in the woods.
It's completely dilapidated and unfinished yet somehow it's lighting up at night.
They don't really quite explain that. There's a, there's the old mysterious black neighbor
trope, uh, played by Vondie Curtis Hall, who I always fucking love. He's a great actor and he's
great in this, but it's like, you know, is he involved? She goes out looking for the house and,
and she runs into him in the woods and he's acting very strange and mysterious and you
don't know why. And, uh, yeah, go on Joe, sorry. No, it's fine. Um, she, you know, and then I guess
the reveal is, is that eventually you realize he's been, he's probably murdered some women in this
house, but you don't know why. And it's more, you get the feeling that it's more so than he's just
a bad guy. Yeah. And, and Andy's like, he told me he had urges, strange urges. And I'm like,
I got to tell you, if I'm murdering multiple women in an abandoned night house, I'm probably
not telling my neighbor that I have dark urges. You know, it, there's so many things like that
in this movie where I'm like, it feels like a screenwriting exercise as opposed to a living,
breathing thing. And that's the thing. There's too many cryptic clues throughout this thing
that when it's finally revealed what the husband was up to, yeah, none of them make sense. For
instance, his suicide note. That's what I was about to say. I got it right here. There is nothing,
nothing is after you. You're safe now. Right. That's a, that's a completely bizarre suicide note
that is clearly just a clue for the person watching the movie. It's not a suicide note.
Anyone would write. And if he's going to write something to his wife before killing himself,
why wouldn't he make it clearer to her? So she knows what's going on. Well, that's the point.
And so she interprets it as she told her husband that she had, she had, she had, she was in a car
crash where she died for five minutes and was rejuvenated. And she tells her husband, she said,
my husband is the only person I ever told when I died, I saw him absolutely nothing. There was
nothing. And so she goes, this is what his note means. There is nothing. Nothing is after you,
whatever. He's telling me there's nothing after we die. Then you find out that what it is, is,
is there is a ghost who's a shadow called the nothing, which I read online, like in the fucking
story. Like you, you would not say, especially to your fucking wife, nothing is after you.
And what you actually mean is that there's a being called the nothing that is trying to get you.
That's absurd. It's absurd. Yeah. So you, so, and this thing's after her for, for what reason?
Because she didn't die all the way. And it's like, what? Who cares? And then also how many
almost die and don't, but he's just fixated on this one woman. Like he wants her soul.
And, and does he do this with everyone who almost dies or he's just fixated on her?
And why would he be? She seems like a perfectly nice, normal woman.
It makes, you know what? She does seem like a nice, normal woman until about halfway through
the movie. And you're like, you know, you know, Bex, whatever, I forget her character's name,
but it's like, you get about a two week pass on that pissy mood grief thing. Like you're,
she really is just being an asshole to everybody. Well, it's my favorite aspect of it is they don't
make her the sad morning victim. She's kind of a bitch. And I talked about with Joe,
my favorite scene of the movie is right after her husband kills herself. She's back at school.
She's a school teacher and this mom comes in wanting a different grade for her child.
And she's like, what do you want to be? What do you want to fucking a, my husband just blew
his head off. She's great in the scene. She's great throughout, but she, they do definitely
make her like a tough cook. Yeah. So to the point where you're starting to go,
I get why the guy blew his brains out. Yeah. I certainly get why he cheated. Definitely. Yeah.
So, so, so that, but I think that's a red herring. That's that's that they did that for the reason.
So I'm being funny, but that's actually one of the elements, one of good storytelling elements
in it. But, but my biggest gripe with this thing is, you know, it's like you had to,
why is the ghost? So you find out the husband went out, got all these occult books.
He learned in the occult books that if you build the reverse of your home, a ghost can't find you
because it gets confused already. You're like, for Christ sakes, what are we talking about here?
This thing can travel through dimensions in time. It's about it. It's able to find you on planet
earth, but you're going to confuse it with a copycat house. I mean, it's so crazy. So why don't
you do the Looney Tunes thing of, of, of put up a house. And then when he runs towards it,
it's actually a screen picture of a house. So then he knocks himself out and you can kill him. It's
that stupid, which by the way, I've seen that new Jack Estrell at eight times that thing of the guy
bike into the fake. It's like, it's like, I can't wait. It's just unbelievable anyway.
So then you find out he's not having an affair. He's like seducing these women and luring them
to this house and murdering them because women who kind of look like his wife so that he can fool,
fool the ghost, the nothing. Of course. Here's what I was imagining is pitching this movie.
Yeah. How does the person hearing this pitch not go, all right, wait a fucking minute.
You know, it, there's too much like that in this movie. And, uh, of course he doesn't fool the
ghost. Yeah. And then by the way, after he kills himself, the ghost just starts haunting her. And
you're like, why didn't you just do that to begin with? Yeah. Yeah. This is nuts. This,
this makes sense. No. Uh, I not only hated this film from a logical standpoint,
it was one of the most boring movies I have seen in years. There is not a happy moment.
There is not a speck of joy. I'm not asking for jokes or anything. I'm just saying for Christ's
sake. It's, it's, it's Ricky Gervais's TV show without any of the comedy parts.
It's a woman walking around in her house, depressed with no dialogue, watching videos
of her dead husband and then turning the same dirge like song keeps coming on the radio. Like
the good, the husband turns it on or the ghost turns it on. And you keep hearing the same song
over and over and then, and then just, I guess the husband, I guess the ghost is after the husband
to lure the husband into killing himself because that'll lure her in more easily. Cause at the end,
she almost kills herself when the ghost is trying to convince her to, but it's just a long way around
the bend. It's pointless. It's just fucking pointless, especially when she says halfway
through the film that she had mental problems or she's had mental issues through her life.
And it's like, again, then why wouldn't the ghost just prey on you and exploit those issues to try
to lure you in? I just don't, I don't know. Maybe he needed the husband out of the way first.
I, you know, I guess that makes sense because he was her rock or whatever, but
well, I'm going to, I'm going to surprise you here, but I liked the movie for an hour and 15
minutes. I was enjoying it because I trusted the filmmakers. I was just like, they're building to
a great reveal and these moments that might not be clicking for me right now will make sense later.
And there's really nothing more frustrating than when you put that kind of trust in a filmmaker
and then they get to the end and you're like, what the fuck? But I'm not a guy who, when the
sucks, I write off the whole movie. I think it was pretty damn effective as a thriller.
I loved how they did the jump scares, which is generally it's like, Oh, it was just a cat. Oh,
and then everybody calms down. And then the thing jumps out behind them. That's the jump scare. I
hate that's how they train audiences to like, and when Heather jumps and stuff like that in movies,
I'm like, you didn't know that was coming, but she doesn't, she doesn't like horror movies.
Uh, for me, this one had a much more effective way of the jump scares are just like,
bam, the, the sound design was great. You know, they hit you out of nowhere. That moment were all
the women in the bathing suits, which I still don't really know what that was when they were
all jumping and running past her. Do you remember that? That was, yeah, that was like, she was seeing
the ghosts of all the women he killed, I guess. And it was supposed to be like, this is how they
ran when he tried to kill them. Cause he did, I mean, I guess down to their panties were going to
and then he would kill them. But it's like, how is this ghost making you see all this?
You know what I mean? I don't know, but that 32nd, it was a 32nd nonstop jump scare essentially.
And to me that was extremely effective. I was like, this is fucked up. I don't know where this is
going, but you can only sit in that feeling of, Ooh, where is this going for so long until you
got to start paying it off. And that is where the movie falls completely to shit. I walked out,
that women running thing was way earlier on than you're remembering, man. Cause a long
while after that, I looked at my watch and I was like, Holy shit, there's another 45 minutes of
this. Oh no, I'm not saying it's at the end. I'm saying it was a super effective moment. And I
thought that there were several of them that scared me. Like when you first hear his voice
in the house as the ghost, I mean, look, that's not exactly fresh to hear a ghost like you don't.
They do it in the funniest scene of Talladega nights with a John C. Reilly, but it's to me
was super effective as a horror movie. These guys have talent, but as the thriller and the plot
elements of it, it doesn't work at all. And when you really look back at it, I immediately walked
out, everybody that was in this movie walked out and got on their phones and was looking at
Wikipedia. There were people in the lobby discussing what happened to with strangers like, well then why
did she do this? And that's just not good. It got a really bad, sorry. Wow. Really wobbling. It got
a really bad cinema score review, which is when they pull audiences after. And it's, it's because
the ending is the most important part to your average audience. Like in the 89 % on rotten tomatoes
and then like a, like a C minus on cinema score. And it's just because it doesn't play by the rules.
When it ends, you're left with more questions than answers, but not really in a good way.
What I will say is great about it is Rebecca Hall, who is excellent. I think in the movie,
Sarah Goldberg from Barry plays her friend. She's great in the movie. Bondi Curtis Hall, as I said,
the mistress I thought was really good in it. Well acted. It's the guys who did Superdark Times,
which we reviewed on this show and which I love that. Did they, did they just, I loved Superdark
Times. Did they just write? Cause they only wrote this. They did not direct this. Did they direct
Superdark Times? No, they wrote it in this guy, David Bruckner. Let me make sure cause I'm often
wrong. Oh, he didn't direct Superdark Times. So let me check. Oftentimes we just go, yeah, yeah,
yeah. This happened. We don't really know, but that David Bruckner is directing the new hellraiser
and it's being written by these guys who did the night house, which is a little troubling, but
Superdark Times was directed by this guy, Kevin Phillips. I don't know who that is, but
they wrote Superdark. They are writing the new hellraiser and the director is also directing
the new hellraiser. Well, what's funny is this played tonally and pace wise and twist wise exactly
like Hellraiser, Hellseeker and Hellraiser Inferno, which were the two direct to video
follow ups to the first four that were direct theatrical group released. And it's just a slow
burn who gives a shit of a mystery. Like you just don't fucking care. I'm over the, my husband,
I never knew my husband thriller. I've trashed what lies beneath on the show before. I'll trash
it again. I just don't find it to be interesting. I know. I don't find it to be interesting. This is
there with the cop with a dirty secret thriller. Like I just don't fucking care, man. It's right.
So anyway, my hog is way down on the night house. The more I think about it, the limper it gets.
And you know, my hog, I would, I would honestly put it in exactly the same position as with don't
breathe to it. It's out in front of me. I would recommend it to somebody who liked horror, but I
would also say, you know, just don't be expecting it all to fall together and do a nice bow at the
end. And I understand people who, if the ending doesn't work, the movie doesn't work. I get that.
But for me, I try to look at the big picture and for at least an hour of this thing, I was pretty
riveted to it. I thought it was well done and certainly well acted. Um, it's got, it was well
acted. Yeah. I'm pumped about the new hell raiser because I feel like these guys are circling
something great and not quite hitting it, but I don't know, man. I felt like every scare in this
was, aside from that one with the women, every scare in this was a jump scare that was based
entirely on volume. It was just blaring volume at you after a long stretch of silence. And it's
like, of course that's going to startle me, man. Like, it's not scary. I'm not at all scared by
the music turning on, but it wasn't going by the jump scare formula of, Oh, it was a fake out,
whatever. And that's what, that's why they were more effective to me. I agree with that, but here's
the thing have jump scares. Fine. Yeah. But you gotta have some real scares too. You gotta have
some movie. You gotta have some spooky, whatever. And they, this had none of that in my opinion.
Um, and I, and I thought it did, although at the end, especially when they're in, when, when the,
the nothing is dragging her around the house and then she's watching her husband kill these women
in a parallel universe or something. I mean, I, I truly had no idea what was happening at the end.
Why was the house her, when she went to the house that was like half built in the woods, why,
why did she, why was she able to see, why did it look finished? Yeah. And why, my point is,
is if the, if this demon can do all these things, why is this such an elaborate scheme? You could do
whatever you want. You could make her walk out into traffic. It's stupid. Yeah. No, it's,
it's for sure. It's like, it's when these guys were mapping this movie out, they were strictly
focused on the screenwriting element of it, the twists and turns and not being concerned about
how it would play to an audience. That's, that's just what it is. And that's why I think audiences
aren't responding to it at all. They're that suicide note is anytime something like that,
like a clue in a movie is written or designed in such a way that it only makes sense to make
your story make sense. You haven't done your job. Like, you know, it's very much like when the,
guys got one final piece, honestly, the best example of it is, is Rollo Tomasi and LA
confidential. You buy it because it plays out so beautifully. But if you think about it for a minute,
you're like, would Kevin Spacey have known to say Rollo Tomasi there? And, and so he, I don't know
if you remember that specific, but sometimes that works. If everything else around it is great,
you can get away with one thing. Everything around this is not great for sure. Yeah.
All right. We'll be back next month with Candyman for sure.
And wait, no, no, no, no, mid month. These are for the 1st of September, right? Oh yeah. We'll be
back mid month with Candyman, the new one. And we'll, there'll also of course be some discussion
about the old Candyman. If you want to refresh yourself and Jacob's wife, right? Yes. We will be
doing Jacob's wife, which is new to shutter starring Barbara Crampton and the great Larry
Fezenden. How the hell you say? Power couple. I just saw today, although Emily had told me about
it a few weeks back, that there is a zoom horror movie group offshoot of our Facebook page where
CU and health fans are getting together to talk, to sort of feel better about the world, to have
friends, to, you know, to bounce things off each other and have a good time. And I, I love that.
I think we have, you know, everyone says we've got the best fans, but I love that you guys are all
connecting and getting along with each other and finding some outlet for these kind of very
isolating times. Love that. Love you guys. That is awesome. Thank you for supporting us via Patreon.
Thank you, Emily, for keeping the online world alive for us as we increasingly want to be detached
from it. Um, and, uh, I'm Instagram, Twitter, the Patrick Walsh.
Jotaro's a comedy on Instagram, Twitter, Joey Rose is coming very soon. Brick and mortar,
September, hopefully on Rivington street, New York city. I will keep you posted.
We'll see you next time. And we'll see you in hell.