Summer is here and Bed MDM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer or check out
our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz.
Only available at Bed MDM Casino.
Spin on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 fortunes, Mystery of the Lamp,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bed MDM Casino right from the palm of your hand.
Download the Bed MDM Casino app today and get a piece of the action.
Bed MDM game sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices. Bedmgm .com for teases and seeds, 21 plus to wager.
Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania, and West Virginia only.
Games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as normal throwable site credit slash bonus best unless otherwise
provided in applicable terms. Rewards subject to expiry.
Gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamber.
The football season is full of guarantees.
And here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee every single game day from now until October.
If your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning or winning money back in fan cash.
Guaranteed. Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
Winning hits different here.
Must be 21 plus. Gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamber.
Offer not available in all states.
Terms apply. See Fanatic Sportsbook app.
Welcome to will see you in hell.
It's a podcast where you come and listen.
If you want to hear more of you.
It's about horror movies and sci -fi movies and fantasy movies and other movies too.
My name is Joe DeRosa. This man singing is my name's Pat Walsh.
It's Thursday afternoon. I was just complaining the Joe.
Nowhere to park. Thursday 2 p .m. in a neighborhood.
That's Los Angeles in a nutshell.
Everyone is home with a giant bong making others life more difficult.
You want to hear truly how stupid this fucking city is.
Yeah. This, oh boy.
Put me right in the fucking mood today.
Right in a fucking mood.
All right.
So I get up this morning like 7 a .m.
Can't sleep.
I haven't a real what am I doing with my life.
I got a text from Joe at like 7 .45.
A text from my mom at 7 .30.
A text from another friend who goes to bed with his baby at like 9.
So he's responding to my 9 p .m. text at like 7 .15.
I was like could you all knock at the fuck off.
But anyway, yeah, sorry.
You were the third to text me.
So don't worry.
But it was pre eight seems early to me woke up in a panic.
What am I doing?
Sure.
With your life.
Yeah, just every aspect of it.
I was like, I know it'll make me feel better.
I'll I'll purge some more DVDs.
I got too much junk around here.
So I start pulling DVDs off the shelf that I don't want.
Right.
And then I'm like throwing them out the window.
Yeah.
I'm like, you know what?
I got some video games that I don't want either.
And I got a couple extra systems.
And I start piling everything up.
But I got the shitload of stuff.
And I'm like, you know what?
All right.
There's a video game place that also takes DVDs for trade.
Right.
I'll drive over there.
That'll put me in a good mood.
I'll walk the dog early three miles.
I'll eat some drinks of coffee.
Make some vegetable juice.
Yes.
Drive over early early do a trade.
It'll put this little spring on my step today.
I drive to this place.
It opens at 11 a .m.
I get there at 11 .05.
Okay.
Yeah.
Walk through the door.
Got a trade to do.
The guy goes, it's going to be about an hour.
I'm like, okay.
So then I'm like, so what does that mean?
Till the trade master comes in.
Till they can finish.
No, no, no, he's actively working on it.
It's going to be about an hour.
To know if he can give you money.
Yeah.
So I go, okay.
And I'm pretty confident in the trade.
So I'm like, I'll just walk around the store for an hour.
It's not the big of a deal.
It's hard to keep interrupting,
but aren't these usually like an $8 transaction?
Well, I had a lot of shit.
It doesn't matter.
Even when it's been, even when I've had a $500 transaction,
it hasn't taken it out.
You're dropping off a ton of shit.
He's going to look through it and give you an overall price.
Still, yeah, still shouldn't take an hour.
Absolutely not.
But I get it.
I thought you were handing him a DVD or something.
No.
So then I walk away.
I walk around the guy goes,
oh, he's ready for you.
I go, oh, that was fast.
It's like five minutes later.
I walk over.
He goes, okay, so it's going to be an hour
till I get to your stuff.
Then it's going to be whatever amount of time it takes me to figure out.
And I go, and I go, I go, I got here at open.
Like when he goes, yeah, there's one guy in front of you.
One guy in front of me because this is how fucking LA functions.
I'm so angry because this is how LA functions.
It's the, you know, being while this store,
I don't want to blow up their spot.
But this, you should, this, well, I've actually given them a shout out
before online because I like the store.
I don't think I'm ever going to go there again.
Store looks like a fucking bomb hit it.
I mean, there's just shit everywhere.
There's nothing is organized.
It's like, guys, you're not doing anything meticulously.
Clearly, right?
Anyway, so even then I go.
Also, the 11 o 'clock opening.
I've never even heard of a business opening at 11 a .m.
outrageous.
Should have been 10 a .m.
If you're retail, yeah, even fun retail, 10 a .m.
Yeah.
So anyway, I go, all right, whatever.
Still being cool about it.
Because I drove all the way out there.
Then the guy goes, so
let me see your ID.
So I give him my ID.
He goes, I got half the shit unpacked already from the box.
He goes, I need to see your ID.
Okay, okay.
Give my ID.
It's my New York license.
He goes, this is expired.
I go, yeah, I know.
And he goes, well, I can't take an expired light.
And I'm like, well, it's my license.
You can see that it's me.
And quick pause.
What does he need your license for?
It's, I'm getting to it.
So I go, I go to me, but I give him some albums for trade.
No one's ever asked me for an identification.
Yeah, I know.
So I go, okay, here's my temporary license from the DMV
that I just got.
They haven't mailed me the new one yet.
Yeah.
I, you know, and he goes, I can't take a paper temporary license.
And I go, dude, I don't want to tell you.
My license expired.
I got a new license.
Yes.
It's not in my possession yet.
This is the paper they gave me.
Right.
He's like, yeah, I can't take that.
I go, I buy alcohol with this.
If I get pulled over by the cops,
this is what I show them.
Yeah.
He goes, can't do it.
You got your passport?
I go, no, I don't have my passport.
Who's bringing their passport to the DVD shop?
Can I get a quick description of the man place?
Sometimes it helps me to visualize.
I'm picturing a big fat guy with a long beard.
Oh, no.
Rick Rubin's stuff.
Guy about it is mid to late 40s.
Okay.
Physically, like everybody behind the counter in LA.
Physically fit in better shape than me.
Right.
You know, it's like, it's like, I should,
you should be the one on the other side of this counter.
Yeah.
But for some reason,
I look worse than you and have figured out
how to live life properly.
Yeah.
Anyway, so far, you know, not to say that if you work
and retail, you know what I mean.
So anyway, so he goes, he goes, I need your passport.
I go, listen, man, I go, I got a picture of my passport.
I'll show you that.
He goes, no, I need the real thing.
I go, sir, I have literally secured work
in other countries by sending a picture of my passport
so they can verify my identity.
I'm showing you an expired license,
a temporary paper license issued by the DMV.
Right.
A picture of my passport.
And I've got credit cards here with my name on it too.
Yeah.
I don't know what else you need.
My pictures on all this stuff.
Can't do it, man.
Can't do it.
And what is it here?
What is he not doing with all this?
Can't do the trade.
Can't, can't purchase used goods for me.
Because why?
You're not a citizen in his mind?
I go, I go why?
Who says?
And he goes, LAPD.
Oh, you're telling me this is a law?
He's like, yeah.
I go, he goes, you want to drive home and get your passport?
I go, no, I go to drove a ways to get out here, man.
Like, I'm like, dude, I've been a customer here for years.
I'm in your system.
I'm in here all the time.
Why is this an issue right now?
Guys like, sorry, man, nothing we can do.
LAPD, hands are tight.
I go, forget it, man, forget it.
I'll just come back another time, meaning I'm never coming back.
Because before that, it was going to take an hour and 20 minutes
to look through six copies of like, you know,
it's always sunny season one and fucking the odd couple two.
You know what I mean?
And so I leave.
I'm so aggravated.
I'm like, this is a stupid policy.
This store has, there is no way this is a law.
I call another game shop.
Yeah.
The guy got a guy on the phone and who I knew was the owner.
It was actually this place, game realms that I really like a lot in Burbank.
And I can recognize the owner's voice.
And I was like, hey, man, I got a question for you.
If I want to do a trade and I break the whole thing down for him, he goes, yeah, dude,
we need like a valid picture ID that's not expired.
He's like, that's the law.
So I didn't get mad at him because now the guy is reaffirming like, no,
this really is a law here.
So we live in a city where the DMV can issue you a piece of paper that is literally good enough
to buy alcohol, to vote, and to present to a police officer during an incident of some kind.
And your identity can be verified from it.
But if you want to go sell fucking Super Mario Brothers 2, it's not good enough.
But why does the Meebe not do that?
A, or any place I've ever been to, maybe it's video game related.
I have no fucking idea.
Then question two, seemingly the only reason the LAPD would be involved in this
is to cut down on theft.
If I break into a car tonight, steal a giant sack of video games and DVDs and walk into this place,
then I show them my ID.
I've still stolen the, what are they proving?
Like generally if somebody steals something, there's still a person who has a license.
Yes, and also, hey, they're not off the grid.
Here's the thing, hey, dipshit, if I doctor to license to sell stolen goods,
I'm not going to doctor one with an expired fucking date on it.
Like, I don't, you know what I mean?
Like, what is, it's clearly me on the license.
So if you don't think that it's me on there,
and you think that somehow I'm scamming you, do they run the license to,
we need to look into this law?
Do they run the license to see if you've stolen things in the past?
I just can't even wrap my head around.
I was so fucking mad, dude.
I was so mad.
That's outrageous.
Here's the kicker.
It's nut ridges.
That's outrageous, Philbin.
I get home.
I'm taking the box, I got a box full of shit.
Two of which, two of the things in it are a Sega Saturn system which is not cheap
in a fucking Sony PlayStation.
I take the box out of my backseat to put it into my trunk because I'm like,
I'll just drop this later in another store.
Spill the block box.
Both systems hit the concrete.
Thankfully, they didn't break.
I don't think.
I'm just going to, you know, I won't know that until they plug them in at this place where I tried
to crack or anything.
I'm just like, you got to be fucking kidding me today, man.
You got to be fucking kidding me.
This fucking city, so fucking much.
If I see one more fucking open micro online with 12 times the fucking Instagram followers I have
because they figured out how to post the right YouTube clip.
I'm just, I'm done.
I can't.
No, I don't know where.
Now you're losing me, but what do you mean?
If this was a debate, you were making some great points and then you took a hard ride into
Instagram.
Oh, I'm just talking about the people in this city.
All right, fine.
You go on Instagram.
You go, oh, you know, here's it from my phone.
Don't look at it.
Here's a guy who's been doing comedy three months.
Oh, he's got 155 ,000 followers already.
Is he hot?
No.
None of them are.
Got a big D.
I don't know.
Just something.
I did just a sick of it.
There's no escape and I guess what I'm trying to say is there's almost
fucking escape here.
Yeah, where do you go?
Why do you get away from the shit?
That's true.
I haven't had a drink in four days, by the way.
I'm going.
I haven't had a drink in about the same.
And I've been doing 10 ,000 plus steps a day because your phone tracks it.
Yeah.
And I feel calmer.
I'll be honest with you.
I don't know if the drinking has anything to do with it, but the long,
extensive walks each day helps me a lot.
They help.
I've been walking about 6 ,000 a day.
Yes.
And I do feel much clearer, much sharper.
I'm eating one meal a day, which I find fine.
It's like I don't get hungry.
Where do you eat?
If somebody has dinner plans, then it's that.
If otherwise, I'll have a big breakfast or something.
I think if you're doing the one meal a day plan,
which I'm sure no doctor recommends,
you're supposed to do it at the same time every day.
But I sort of play it by here.
But you'll eat it breakfast some days and literally not eat another thing
for the rest of the day.
Yeah, and it doesn't bug me.
And especially if you have a cup of coffee at some point,
the, you know, it just is an appetite suppressant.
I got to drop a couple LBs.
You know, I got in a bad place with work.
That's all.
It's already working.
Good.
I feel the mood improving, the mood lightning.
Guys, I'm in a real pendulum swing.
I go from great to furious.
Yeah.
But that'll work itself out.
Well, hey, let's get on with the show.
Yeah.
And at the same time on.
Oh, boy.
We're clearly out of these.
You know, we're just out.
On.
With the Joe?
A little Italian.
There you go.
How about that?
I'm going to let you take full movie corner today for all three.
I'm going to do six then.
I'm going to do a rapid fire.
I'm going to well, all right.
What you're going to say don't do six because I actually have three
screaming ends.
Oh, so it's going to say I meet your three.
I need to do some rapid fire and get some fucking things off my phone.
With all this time off now, I've been watching a lot of shit.
I'm going to be quick.
All right.
I'll leave the horror in case we want to watch the horror.
The horror?
I'll leave I won't mention the horror ones.
You see what I'm saying?
Oh, I thought you were saying a movie named The Horror.
No, then I couldn't tell with your accent if you're saying the horror.
All right.
I watched.
Let's just get into this.
Fletch.
Hand seen it in decades.
Masterpiece.
Well, I'm doing a lot of re -evaluation of things.
Always love Fletch.
When I was a kid, not one of my favorites, but liked it quite a bit.
Great laughs.
And it is still solid, funny.
I don't consider it a classic by any stretch of the imagination.
I think outside of the vacation, the first three vacation movies,
that's as good as it gets with Chevy Chase.
And that is truly the only great Chevy Chase movie.
Meaning this.
It's his movie.
Yeah, vacation's Beverly Hills Cop.
Yeah, it's vacation's an ensemble thing.
That is the truly one great Chevy Chase movie.
I can't, I'd be hard pressed to think of another.
I agree.
I mean, vacation, you could argue.
Michael Hall steals that thing.
But the engine, the way, I mean, you got to hold,
it's just a cavalcade.
But this is, it is a great vehicle for Chase.
It is his Beverly Hills Cop.
The music is even the same.
The Gogano, Gano, Gano, Gano, Gano, Gano, Gano, Gano, Gano, Gano, Gano.
I think it's the same guy did both scores.
Then it'll get like deadly serious at the time.
Yeah, like what just happened?
He was just wearing a wig and buck teeth.
And then a guy dies of like a heroine overdose.
Yeah, I mean, they got him in basically black face at one point
and an afro.
I mean, it's pretty wild.
Fletcher lives, has its moments too.
But whatever, Fletcher, there it is.
I mean, I'm going to go quick.
I watched Stepfather 2.
It's streaming on Amazon Prime.
They still have Terrio Quinn in the mix.
I think the Stepfather 1 is a fantastic horror movie.
Really great thriller in the, along the lines of Hannah Rocks the Cradle.
One of my favorite genres.
Never saw Stepfather?
Yeah, never saw it.
Oh, well, it's fucking great.
I have the screen factory of that.
Why don't you go to skip the horror one you just said?
I did, but you and I are never going to do Stepfather 2 on here.
I don't know, I guess.
Maybe it's a prequel.
Maybe we do this series.
Yeah, I should have skipped it.
You're right, I'm stupid.
But Stepfather 2 was, there's so little to say about it
that that's why I'm just checking it off the list.
All right, for any reason.
This was such a paint by numbers horror movie.
It like barely got a theatrical release.
And the first one was a big hit.
The family he moves in with in this one is not as interesting.
The script is not as good.
The direction is not as good.
The twists are not as good.
The kills are not as good.
And then after it was done,
they made Terry Aquin go in and add some violence
because they thought there wasn't enough.
He didn't want to do it.
I think he thought he was making something serious and important.
Right.
Stepfather 2 is a pretty embarrassing and lazy movie.
All right.
I saw
a stir crazy.
I've got some thoughts.
Gene Wilder,
Dickie Pryor, Richard Pryor.
These guys are considered like a hope and cross.
Be like a legendary comic duo.
I've seen silver streak.
I've seen here no evil,
seen no evil, which I think a lot of people love
just because it was on cable so much when we were kids.
But stir crazy is considered the classic
directed by Sydney Poitier.
And man,
you know, a big thing I've learned from listening
to this 80s all over podcast,
which I recommend once again,
is like sometimes I like,
I so wish I had not watched this again.
You know, because it ruined my memory of it.
Right.
I had no great memory of stir crazy.
I had seen it.
I like the two of them and they make it work.
But man, it is two hours.
It should have been 80s.
They're funny together.
Don't get me wrong.
Another movie involving Blackface,
silver streak also involves Gene Wilder and Blackface.
Yes.
But yeah, it's just kind of,
it's that they dress up as chickens.
Two other guys dressed as chickens.
Commit the crime robbery robbery.
So Pryor and Wilder wind up in prison.
And then they're out of prison relatively early.
I remember to being a prison movie.
It's not really, it's just kind of,
no, they're in prison till the very end.
Think it out of the very very,
they escape at the very very end.
It's just very episodic.
It's very, you know,
there's no real through line.
And I don't know.
It's the,
it's my favorite of the wilder,
Pryor movies.
It's got the funniest wilder and
Pryor performances and scenes I've ever seen in any movie.
Yeah, in it.
But it dies about halfway through.
It does that thing that many comedies do where they're like,
okay, you've had your fun.
Now let's get to the story.
Right.
And then it starts revolving around this rodeo premise.
Like it almost like this longest yard.
I guess that's what I mean.
I wasn't for some reason associated in the rodeo with prison.
But yeah, the rodeo shit is boring as hell.
They like, yeah, I mean, so, but I mean,
up until then, that's one of those movies.
The last truly funny scene in the movie is when Pryor is in
the hospital with Franklin and Jay.
Yes, that's like the cutoff for when like the antics stop.
And it becomes about a rodeo.
And this movie was a massive hit.
Just massive.
And then the end is like,
the end is literally like, you know,
them out in the desert like, hey,
can you believe we dug that hole and it worked?
Like there's like no, yeah, there's no no showcasing
of it all kind of working out.
They just kind of get out at the end.
Right.
Anyway, I watched Lorraine produced by Jordan Peele,
which is timely because we're also going to be discussing
Jordan Peele's Twilight Zone reboot today on the show.
But Lorraine is a four part four hour Amazon Prime documentary
about Lorraine of Bobbitt.
Obviously with that subject matter, it holds your interest.
It's very juicy, but I was kind of like, all right,
we know what happened.
I mean, what's what's what how long they're going to go
into the the semantics of how the dick cutting worked.
And they do.
You see pictures of the dick off the body.
You see pictures of the stub on the body.
I like to see that.
But really, it does a nice job.
It's no, it's no excellent documentary,
but it's certainly held my interest all four hours.
And that's no, that's not nothing.
What the best part about it and the reason for its existence
is they really spend a lot of time going into how much
late -night hosts and, you know, comedians, etc.
Loved this story and made cutting off the dick jokes.
It seems like every comedian when I was a kid had a Lorraine of Bobbitt chunk.
And man, they just laughed and laughed and laughed.
And this woman's crazy.
And like, Jay Leno calls her a crazy bitch in a joke
and it like makes you gasp.
Like, there's just all this Leno comes off really awful.
But so do they all.
And sure enough, Lorraine of Bobbitt,
not granted anyone who's going to do that has some issues.
But she was being analy raped every night by her husband.
And on the stand, which was a heavily televised publicized trial,
they brought up his friends and you forget that John Bobbitt was like, you know,
25 at this time.
So you get these kind of like dumb looking mullet head guys from
and they're up on the stand and they're like, yeah, you know, John Bobbitt was my best friend.
Like, did he ever discuss rape?
Yeah, all the time.
Oh jeez, I didn't know that.
Like, it was like a big, like would you say it was a turn on for him?
It was, it sounded like it was the only thing that turned him on.
Oh boy.
And what about anal rape in particular?
Yes, he would talk at length about how he loved to analy rape women and especially his wife and so.
So then you're like, well, now wait a minute.
And once this hits, and they have interviews with modern day Lorraine of Bobbitt
and also modern day John Bobbitt, who conducts his interview while drinking from a 64 ounce big gulp
of soda on a couch.
And he's got a couple during the couch for it, of course.
But he's out and talking and being interviewed and everything.
And the whole time, you're just kind of like, this is awful.
Yeah, it sounds awful.
And they kept it from the news because it makes the story not funny anymore.
Cutting off somebody's dick is a story the news can run with and have a field day with for years.
And they did.
I remembered hearing about it constantly when I was a little kid.
And they knew, especially late night comedians,
if they really dug into this story and saw the true horror and darkness of it,
that the jokes would go away.
And that I thought made the documentary particularly worthwhile and interesting.
And necessary that this poor woman has for really when I put this movie and I was like,
I'm watching a movie about a nut job, Lorraine thinking about Lorraine of Bobbitt.
And then really I'm like, you know, if somebody's analy rape in me every night for years,
I'd cut their dick off.
Yeah, probably.
I would think so.
You got all these old, you know, Republican dudes who are like,
you know, like, there's such a thing as cruel and unusual.
Now, she won't leave.
There's the door.
But she didn't need to do something like this.
And it's like, okay, buddy, then let's see how you react.
Yeah, that's fucking outrageous.
The, you know, she weighed a hundred pounds.
And it's just like, yeah.
And then it's, and then it's what's it called.
There's, you know, the, it's, it's a lot of those stories.
It's the McDonald's coffee burn story.
You know, there's a bunch of those where they don't release the true story
because the perceived story is much more sensational.
Yeah.
And it gets way more traction.
I mean, it's, it's, you know, people acting like
this sort of concept of fake news and bullshit journalism.
And it's like some sort of new thing that, that, that, that, you know,
Trump or the other side lit a fire.
And it's been going on forever.
Yeah.
It's all bullshit.
Uh, yeah.
But Bob had apparently performed to the venue that I just performed at in Vegas.
And a guy was, one of the comics there was telling me that he was like,
oh, it was fucking awful.
He's up there just fucking talking about it.
We got his dick cut off for an hour.
Nobody knows what the fuck he is.
Bob, it does stand up.
Yeah.
But he was like, saying he's like, he's like,
these people are remembering this guy is, you know what I mean?
Like it's like,
well, they don't go into that.
They go into his porn career.
I don't know if you remember that.
Oh, I do.
But he made a porno with the dick.
The man is called uncut.
Everybody gets it to see the dick.
It was a big seller.
He makes a lot of money off it.
Then because of the jokes like, boy, not, not too big a penis for a porno,
haha, he decides, and they, they talked to the surgeon who did it.
He was like, I told him like, we have given you your manhood back.
We've like done like a Frankenstein style thing here and given it back.
You should be really grateful and et cetera.
He does this porno and then's like, I want it bigger.
I want it bigger than it was when it got cut off.
So he goes back in with some quack doctor,
pumps it full of juice and it becomes this amorphous blob
like where it's just like a big, like things oozing out the side of it.
The operation was horribly botched.
And now that's what he's got.
Because he wasn't happy with just simply having his dick reached that.
He was like, it's got to be bigger.
So it never worked after the botched job.
It's been ruined now.
He won't, you won't discuss that.
So clearly no.
But they, you know, it got really badly mangled.
Good, good.
The more I talk about it, the more I realize I really enjoyed this movie.
It's got a lot to say.
It's very good.
I did a rewatch of a picture called Greedy
that I've talked about.
I think on this show stars two guest stars
for my own show, Cool Kids.
And I talked with them both at length about how much I loved this movie when I was little.
Jerry Burns, who plays Leslie Jordan's boyfriend on the show
and Ed Begley Jr., who plays the zodiac killer on the show.
They are both in it.
It's a Michael J. Fox vehicle.
And Kirk Douglas plays the patriarch of this big family.
Yeah, yeah.
He's in a wheelchair.
He's on the verge of death.
And they're all trying to get his money.
The first act of this thing.
And, you know, I assume people know this.
Movies have, generally have a three act structure.
The first act I was howling.
Phil Hartman destroys.
I've never seen Phil Hartman more unhinged and more nasty.
I remembered he's got the hair slick back, you know, and boost back.
But I always remembered this line that is one of my favorite lines in a comedy.
And Phil Hartman goes, you know, I didn't like the Beatles and I don't like you.
And I just remembered always loving that.
It's funny to hear it when you see it in the movie.
It's a little less funny.
And I would say that about everything else in this movie.
The first act they are fighting Phil.
It's actually it was before Rushmore.
So the funniest scenes of Rushmore to me are when Bill Murray is like beating up his kids.
Okay.
Phil Hartman has seen like his, he's got like an annoying teenage son and the son's like,
shut up, dad or whatever.
He goes in and like, matches his son's face into the table.
Like, bashes his head down.
There are scenes where like, they're brothers and cousins and they'll still grab each other's face
and throw them into like a wall or a vase or something.
Breaking shit over each other's head.
There's some insane comedy violence like three stooge's shit.
Very unexpected and very well directed by Jonathan Linne who did my cousin Vinnie.
A great comedy director.
Austin Pendleton who played the stutterer in my cousin Vinnie has a hilarious scene
late in the movie where he's just an obnoxious desk clerk.
And Michael J. Fox is trying to get upstairs.
It's a perfectly written two and a half minutes scene.
Movies written by Laul Gans and Babelou Mandel who did splash,
multiplicity, all kinds of big hits.
And basically for this first third,
I'm enjoying it, but going, this is a J. Fox vehicle.
Where is J. Fox?
They cut to him finally and he's like a boulder with Nancy Travis of a last man standing fame.
And then like another movie starts where it's like Michael J. Fox's story.
Then it becomes a complete drama for the last hour.
It does?
Where J. Fox and Kirk Douglas are like talking about life and money.
And there's twist after twist after twist, but there's no laughs.
And the cousins are out of the movie for a while when they brought all the comedy energy
at the beginning.
I've never seen a movie structured this bizarrely.
And I could honestly say that I thought it was a very bad movie.
And this is a movie I had very high thoughts of when I was a boy.
So a lot of these revisits that I'm doing are not paying off to say the least.
All right.
I think is that five, that's five of six.
I'm doing one more quick.
And that movie is going to be Greta newly released.
That's a theatrical release.
Greta is a Chloe Grace Meretz who I like.
Doesn't look great.
And Isabelle Hupear who is a phenomenal actress, French actress.
Directed by Neil Jordan of the crying game and also many bad movies.
Okay, it's all over the map.
Again, it's a psychological thriller.
I was very excited to see it because they make so few of them.
And I love the genre.
This thing's bad.
It's going to be I assume very quickly coming to streaming and on demand and all that.
I started the theater.
It is a thriller with zero thrills.
There's one kind of there's one moment of violence that sort of makes your heart give one extra
beat and then just kind of goes back to being boring.
The plot is Chloe Grace Meretz.
Be friends a kindly old woman.
Turns out the old woman like really wants a daughter figure basically.
Okay.
And becomes too obsessive and too close.
But it's all these scenes of like she's a waitress at a restaurant and then she looks at the window
and Hupear is looking in the window at her.
And then the whole shift she's like she's still out there looking at me through the window.
And I'm like okay and then her boss is like uh -huh and she comes into eat and she's like well
I'm sorry I can't order why won't she take my order.
And she's like she's crazy get her out of here.
But like these aren't exciting things to watch.
The actresses are good.
It's just a very very average movie and I can't recommend it.
Well all right.
Let's do a little screaming in.
I got no thoughts on Greta.
I wish I could hand it to Andy a few.
No it's fine.
I will say Chloe Grace Meretz uh strange choices you know she'll be in like these award -winning
you know critically acclaimed things and then she does these ridiculous
you know he does five pictures a year.
He's like why are you in dark shadows.
Yeah well to work with Tim Burton I assume.
Which although Tim Burton now is not Tim Burton then.
You guys see Dumbo?
Then Tim Burton Tim Burton then either.
That was well -passed.
That was yeah that was.
Fuck no I'm not seeing Dumbo.
I'm not seeing Dumbo.
He writes asks about Dumbo.
I and I probably said this before when I was a kid
if you would have told me there would be a new Tim Burton movie that I would say
not only am I not gonna see in the theater but I know I'll never see it
and it's just gonna keep happening.
I would have slapped you in the face and I haven't seen his last couple of movies.
I didn't see the Peregrine's home of Falcons or whatever the hell it was.
I am getting a feeling about Tim Burton that he's been missing longer than we think he has
and that the people because even the people like us that love Tim Burton movies
you love a couple of them and even those don't line up with fans.
You know what I mean like for instance for instance like
one of my favorite Tim Burton movies is Beatles juice the best.
I love Beatles juice.
Classic.
But then my buddy wasn't that into Beatles juice but he loved Nightmare Before Christmas.
I don't really care about Nightmare Before Christmas.
I agree.
You mean other people some love sissor hands some could give a shit about it.
Some love Batman some hate it.
I think it's all a matter of the ones you do like I'm not even sure if they're good or not.
I mean maybe you're just kind of caught up in the right moment when you saw it at that time period
or something.
All of his I revisit again again and have no issues and I'll go with him.
Peewee all the way through Sleepy Hollow.
Beyond that I can't go.
I can't do it and I don't think he cares.
I think he's big fish I guess but I never want to watch.
Big fish is fantastic.
One of the favorite movies of my wife but I I feel like he doesn't care anymore and he's
got to be making five million a picture or something but it's the same thing with Spielberg
or something but Spielberg still tries and it's like what how much money do you need you know.
Well you can tell when Spielberg's heart is in it and you can tell when he's just like
yeah I know how to do this for my sleep.
He's got I mean ready player one and even some elements of Jurassic Park because he was busy working
on Schindler's list and I'm sure more things we don't know about he sort of forms out the direction
to like second unit and I think that happens more than people know.
Wait Tim Burton's probably doing something like that as well because he did it on Jurassic Park 2
I don't think he did it on one.
He was directing Schindler's list and giving notes and stuff.
Apparently directing Jurassic Park 2 via monitor one is right.
Anyway all right screaming in is one about Nicholas Cage?
No okay news stories for the screaming in
24 hour news psycho.
I'm still not remembering the name of that correctly.
Anyway Helen Mirren yells fuck Netflix.
I saw that yeah.
At a panel thank you Helen Mirren very nice of you I like it and I like what she did.
She's like look Netflix is great but let's not act like there anything that there's anything
that beats going to a theater and sitting down and experiencing a movie.
I agree like but more and more people say that people say they're just the other day our friends
Vince and Georgia.
I said Georgia of my favorite murder fam Georgian Karen.
Yes but I said you know I'm all excited because tonight I'm going to go see stop making sense
easily my favorite rock documentary the talking heads it's a masterpiece I've seen it 50 times
never seen it in a theater the sound design of that movie is so incredible they got a dance floor
at the will turn I can't wait and Georgia's reaction and no criticism of her but she said
but you could just wash it at home why would you do that and for me it's a real thrill to get to see
it at a theater and I think that more and more people would side with Georgia nowadays and I get it
completely there's many nights I don't want to leave the house but you kind of got to you got to keep
that experience alive pet cemetery which Joe was saying the night and we're going to do next week
you got to see that at the fucking theater you have to yeah it's not that's not going to be the same
well I thought what she was saying with that was because this is how I felt too I was like I don't
know that I would go out of my way to see a concert movie at a theater even at the will turn like
with a great amazing sound and everything now I mean it would just I would just feel like I wasn't
seeing a concert still I guess that's all like but you know it feels weird to go to a concert venue
and then look at a screen and there's no band there that that that's how I took that sure because I
agreed with that but anyway people regardless of what her opinion was or was in or mine is or isn't
it's uh it is true more people are just you know people want everything fed right into their house
without thinking about it uh you know and uh first question you get whenever you recommend a
move to anyone is it on Netflix and when I was running the show I would talk about
movies I loved occasionally it's like this movie oh what's that and I would say I'll bring in
the DVD and it was people you could see people's like what what what yeah it's and these are writers
people interested in the arts you know yeah no it's it's fucking crazy it's uh it's you know it's
it's uh god don't get all right I was gonna get real negative for a second there I just went to watch
pet cemetery too um we're gonna do a big all -encompassing book both versions of the movie uh new
version of the movie pet cemetery podcast next week but um I went to go watch pet cemetery too and
I'm like it's on none of the streaming services so this oh you know everything's great we've got
everything we want except anytime I want to watch anything it is not on any of you rent it
I well I went to rent it for $4 .99 and then I saw you could buy it on Amazon for $3 .99
so I bought it I'm like yeah then I'll have something it's bad purchase then I can take it over to
your guy and kill three hours I'm curious here what you think of that sequel but we'll talk about it then
second story and folks here's why Marvel sucks oh boy oh this is such poetic justice the trailer for
Joker came out I didn't watch finally this thing looks so fucking good doesn't it looks like a god
damn Scorsese movie okay Joker okay it looks fucking incredible you've got I heard mixed things it looks
amazing you've got Joaquin Phoenix yeah dancing around in clown makeup the voiceover of him being like
my mom always told me to put on a happy face and try to make people laugh then you see him getting beaten
half to death by like thugs in the street right and then him slowly getting crazier and crazier
throughout the trailer and then the last line it reveals him in the full Joker wardrobe and he goes
I always thought my life was a tragedy but I realize now it's a comedy Joker a title screen comes up it
looks fucking it looks like art it looks like a piece of art I can't even believe this is this is
what's his name for mold school Todd Phillips Scorsese produced it right I believe so and it shows
Todd Phillips always put a lot of style into his movies that hang over and all that always but I mean
the the the I talked to Pinkstone about the trailer he goes I think that movie looks awesome but I think
it looks absolutely heartbreaking it made me feel very sorry for him in the trailer and I was
like yeah it is and Todd Phillips keeps saying the genre of this film is tragedy it is absolutely a
going to be a tragedy about a man who an awful society beats over the edge and he snaps and becomes
the most the Patrick Wall story it looks fucking incredible and then De Niro's in it De Niro's playing a
late -night talk show host so now everybody's like saying like you got De Niro in front of like a
multi -colored curtain so people are making king a comedy parallels can comedy a true masterpiece yeah
this thing looks so fucking amazing and I'm like what why is there a late -night talk show host in the
Joker movie I don't know yet okay I think I think he's his dad I think I think that's weird all right
I thought it said De Niro I don't know it I don't know my point is you see you just see him in front of
that curtain and it's clearly a nod to king a comedy right but anyway and it takes place in like
81 and it looks like 81 truly 81 it doesn't look like people in 1981 costumes right and I'm just
watching this fucking thing thinking about everybody this is DC sucks and it's like you know what have
fun at your Paul Rudd Fest for the 19th time at a theater where everybody's doing still -lone style
quips from the from the early 90s well I mean the Joker may be great but DC does suck they've made no good
movies no good movies we've been over this no good movies yeah suicide squad Batman and Superman you know
you know we've discussed them all you don't like the new new movies you didn't see Wonder Woman which
was good I didn't see Wonder Woman and I didn't like it all right but you can't see is that okay everybody
he's never made good movies just you don't like the new ones I didn't I wasn't aware they had I
wasn't even aware Wonder Woman was a DC really but what are the ones like the Burton ones you like
Batman you like Batman Return oh well I don't count you like the know well those are DC movies all right
fine anyway I'm talking about the new Marvel DC my point is I hear the criticisms of criticism
criticism criticism criticism of new DC I hear them I understand them I get them I don't agree with
all of them I agree with some of them but I will say this is a company took a minute for them to
find their footing they have found what looks to be an incredible tone in this new film it looks
incredibly dark in the best ways possible and I just think it's going to fucking I think this is
going to be like Oscar -level shit it looks like a film which it looks right awesome I don't know
yes yes Mark Hamill is voicing Chuckie it's exciting it is exciting and got a voice actor yeah now I
want to see the fucking movie I didn't want to see it when you remember how both how pissed we both
were when they said an a -list actor was going to do Chuckie we thought that was a huge mistake but
now it's Mark Hamill and now I want to see it because I have like not an a -list actor by the way well
yeah I mean that doesn't get your movie made that's what an a -list actor is yeah I was like they were
saying it like it was going to be like George Clooney's voice right inside Chuckie and it's like
you know Hamill that makes sense yes and he's right there in that sort of I mean he's more he's
got a higher profile than Brad Dorif but he's in that Brad Dorif zone of like amazing character actor
yeah you know sort of chameleon that can morph into all different styles and personalities and voices
and I think he's going to be a really great Chuckie and the idea that he's probably going to be a
crazy guy that hacks into the doll I believe and not the doll just goes crazy because of a bad program
or whatever right makes it a bit more interesting to me uh that he's going to be a lunatic controlling
the doll so that's sort of still within the world of the original films concept um you know they're
just taking out the supernatural element um so uh now I want to see child's play uh I do too
Aubrey Plaza plays the mom which is uh interesting the mom was sort of a non -character I think in the
other child's play no she's pretty big it's the lady from um I just don't remember her bringing
anything to the party and I think plaza will I I I disagree I'm not trying to be difficult I
disagree the uh the first movie the mom's was a pretty central character and I like her a lot
it's that lady from Star Trek 4 uh a whale lady you never saw Star Trek 4 it's the best Star Trek
I've only seen Wrath of Con and the Wrath of Con's the best Star Trek Star Trek 4 I own the thing I've
only seen Wrath of Con it's a comedy and they pull it off somehow and I've seen the terrible generations
and all those yeah those suck it's uh it's like a comedy and they but they have to go back to the
eighties to get away I'm gonna watch them all one day I'm gonna do a marathon it's amazing it's uh
Spock tries to learn how to curse and you can't do it right you know there's very very funny scenes
all right there's like bone you know there's a lot of bones like he has to go to a modern day hospital
all right you know and then he's like looking at like the technology disease and it's a lot of bones
being like it's like the goddamn dark ages in here you know yeah it's very funny okay it's very
very funny uh the Joker is written by Phillips and Scott Silver who wrote I mean the finest hours
which no one saw the fighter which I thought was decent an eight mile which I liked the mod squad
movie which was terrible so that's a weird and very spaced out career um but I'm excited to see it
well he might have just been uh you know a sort of collaboration punch up guy yes one more quick
screaming and Nicholas Cage got married in Las Vegas this weekend divorced divorced four days later
and he was super drunk when he was doing it apparently like beligerent drunk
and he kept saying to people I don't like this woman she's just trying to steal my money
and she was like you don't have to marry me if you don't want to and onlookers were like
what's going on here he's like this woman's trying to take my money I don't want to marry her
her boyfriend's a drug addict he's a drug dealer all this crazy shit they get married and look
the man you know these stories the more they break we're never gonna get him back in a uh
in you know a Hollywood movie again unless it's a voice like spider verse or man look
Hollywood ain't making the good movies I don't want him in a Hollywood movie again I want him in
Mandy movies I want a Mandy series of movies you know so speaking of Nicholas Cage here's a hangout
that I would literally snap your neck right now to be a part of okay I go online I've told
you recently sort of befriended Ron White from doing a show with him yeah so I followed him on Instagram
his Instagram there's a throwback Thursday actually it was actually an Instagram post from his
tequila company number one one I've drank a bottle with him yeah it's delicious yeah uh
trying then they don't sponsor or say anything try number one tequila it's really fucking good right
anyway um uh it was like throwback Thursday to Ron's such and such birthday celebrating here or so
and so and so Ron White and Nicholas Cage and they're in some green room and it appears that
Ron White is like dancing around I'm assuming they've been drinking the tequila sure and Cage is like
bopping his head and I was like love it what did that night turn into love it what did that night
turn into yeah son of a bitch um to be a fly on that wall
uh let's talk about twilight zero starting with twilight
going yeah yeah I never say any of the twilight's uh you you couldn't
wild horses couldn't drag me to it I think just just to say like you know sometimes I like to see a
big cultural event for the jokes you're right in these shows and you want to know the references and stuff
um I watched part of the first one maybe finished it so terrible so terrible um but that's
not we're talking about we're talking about the new twilight zone of which Joe and I have seen
the first two uh it's all it's been released so far it is on CBS all access you can watch the first
one for free there on amazon prime on youtube um if you want the second one you can do a seven day free
sign up I mean for this show a show with this pedigree Jordan Peel coming off get out to go to CBS
all access they must have put a considerable cash offer on the table I bet they had offers all
over fucking town and to go with them not the cool choice believe me well let me cut you off yes
I think CBS still has the rights to it I think oh so they you're right they probably had a first
well but wait a minute that's probably right first look yes CBS has the rights because they've put out
the latest blu -ray it was away from CBS well I shouldn't say away uh you know the twilight zone
from 2001 with forest Whitaker was put out by new line cinema okay the last deep the last blu -ray
set that you and I both own that came out as CBS so CBS has the rights so the fact that it's on
all access and I said this to you uh was a bad sign to me yeah because why and in fact CBS had
the rights in the 80s too and I think they did the original show so I don't know maybe they lost
it for a minute they got it or I don't know doesn't matter the fact that they're the right whole rights
holders and something of this caliber with this much star power in it and this this higher profile a
guy behind it or at the helm why is this only going to streaming and I said this that's not a good sign
I mean why isn't it just not on regular television why would yeah why would you not put this on regular
television and then drop your early episodes on streaming and get people from both fucking sides of
it this is a huge fucking show that they're about to drop huge and it's it seems like CBS so you know
people like that good fight show but I've never seen that the they haven't had their breakout and I
signed up for CBS off the trial and really they're just showing big bang theory repeats if you need to
find big bang theory repeats try turning on any television in America and waiting for one second
so I don't really get it clearly they were like this is going to be the big launch of CBS all access
and you know I feel like it was a very strange move to put this first one online for free because
that usually is such a sign of confidence I do want to say upfront the gentleman who wrote it is a
again a friend would be too strong in this business you have a lot of acquaintances people you meet
Alex Rubens he's a great guy and a brilliant writer folks you don't hear these disclaimers before
a good review and in the Jordan and the Jordan Peel camp you know Jordan Peel of course is you know
friendly with Joe I've never met the man but you know I think in hindsight and I'm going to see
us again I think we might have come down a little rough on us I do want to see it again but
there is sort of a weird thing abruin they the the reviews have not been good oh the third
party we should mention is that Joe and I were friends certainly with Kumail who is the star of
this first episode yes and I haven't seen him in a while as he becomes a massive star but
you know it's a little awkward to talk about but this podcast of course we got to talk about the
twilight zone and it's weird because any show the pilot is usually the worst episode of any show
without question you know the worst episode of the pranos is the pilot it's a little clunky
people are figuring shit out but something like the twilight zone each one is its own self -contained
thing so it's not really that and I read you know the Hollywood Reporter had a particularly I would say
way too nasty scathing review of the first four episodes that might as well have like called it a
piece of shit but they're like all four of these are terrible and are they do 13 to do 22 I don't
know the reporter review I read was of the first two and he said the he goes one of these is a classic
one of these is not and he really when that was on an AV club I think I would report a guy I read
I would report a review the first four and said they were all terrible and he was rough um I mean
look this first one right off the bat it was clearly moved to the front of the line because Kumail was
in it I think he was a smart choice for casting but I think the network pushed this to be the drop
episode Kumail is very good in it and he is very more dramatic than I've seen him everybody is good
in it and they're doing the best with what they're given but I mean it's just look guys it's called
the comedian it's about a comic who finds out there are certain repercussions when he does certain
types of material on stage I won't ruin it for you the final twist is pretty cool and interesting not
nearly enough to save the episode what's wrong with it in my opinion we've seen this premise
many times from Rod Serling himself there are two episodes of the original Twilight Zone that
revolve around ventriloquists and before you say well this is a remake then it's not this is not
an adaptation of a Rod Serling story this is an original story Rod Serling also did an episode called
I believe make me laugh on the first season a night gallery uh that Steven Spielberg I think
type of concept better um you know Tales from the Crypt has done the thing about you know the twisted
ventriloquist or comic this this premise has been done before the danger on the other side of the
laughter or whatever you know so to do this again you got to do it really special and to do it
really special is not the way they did it by making a solid hour version of one of these stories
way too fucking long it way too fucking long it's so felt like a half hour you know like you just
there's so much that can come away it's very repetitive um and not in a way where the where the new
layers are are adding any reveals um it just kind of keeps happening and it's unpleasant I mean you
you spend time in a really unpleasant man's uh head really for a full hour and everybody
and it is unpleasant and I you know for me I was kind of like comedy is rough the kind you know
whether you're a stand -up or a writer whatever else you got it and you know some of the themes I
liked you got to use people in your life um to make great art great comedy I get that but um
it just sort of I just kind of kept wanting to get away from it you know in a way that wasn't fun
the problem with this episode was the same problem that I had with us they were trying to do too much
they were trying to say too much it didn't need to be that complicated yes uh you know at the
beginning of this episode this guy is supposed to be you know one of these sort of social commentary
self -righteous comics that does care you get the sense in the beginning of the show that he does
care and he's bombing with material that he cares about because he's being too preachy but you don't
think he's being phony you think that he does care by the end of this thing the idea is you're full
of shit you use people and and you don't really have respect for anybody it's like well then you have
to set that up at the beginning there's no part there's no point in this where you're where you have
this transitional moment where you go uh oh he's now becoming the thing he be hold or be held
yeah it just never happens it's just all of a sudden he's a bad guy and there's no seed planted for
that it's Tracy Morgan I'm sorry is is possible in this role that he plays this mystic you know
barely in it I found that so strange unless they knew this is going they must have known it's
gonna be the premiere or they wouldn't have you know gotten the guy that big for that little part
yeah he's he's he's he's it's a bad casting it's distracting it's distracting to see Tracy Morgan
in a role of like the sort of mystic overseer kind of guy yeah which again this has been done before and
it's been done better uh in no offense to your friend but to me the writer of this thing has never
set foot in a fucking comedy club and has only got his idea of a comedy club from the movie punchline
I mean I've never seen anything like this it's like he's got comics like basically like in the
green room getting like they're having a conversation then a page comes on five minutes till stage
Jesse Jesse report to this I'm like what is happening right now there's crystal chandeliers hanging
to me I put a lot on the director and the set design unless they were going for some weird like
old like it is supposed to be the twilight zone so things are a little different but like
I have never seen anything look less like a comedy club it was outrageous and they were and they were
painting it by the way it was called Eddie's comedy club yeah first of all terrible name
Eddie's comedy club and then eventually when you meet Eddie like halfway through the episode he's
this guy he's like he's like an extra from black mass he like comes in he's got this silk shirt
unbuttoned down to like his you know his ribcage yes and he's got like dark sunglasses on he's like
hey use it's your big night I heard you was killed it's like crazy yeah and you're like guys this is
so stupidly cliche and by the way if this is the club you want to portray if you want to show that
the fat guy that belches and is misogynistic that goes on stage and says horrible things
is the star breakout guy in this club that does really well every week well then you can't make
the club look like a fucking artsy ballroom where the most alternative show in town would take place
it doesn't make any sense it's like people are in suits in the audience you know it's uh
it's a strange vibe it felt like it was like the cotton club or something yeah it looks like it's
like a weird like thematic it just doesn't work I don't know if they were trying to make it look weird
like he shakes it's twilight so it just doesn't work the director did san june perro which uh
is you know a very beloved black mirror episode and that the look of that was just fantastic it was the
one set in the eighties and it was very eighties like a thousand eighties of songs on the soundtrack
etc um which episode is it about what's it about it's the two women it's like a lesbian love
story that goes back to the eighties i don't remember um it's great uh but
he yeah the i don't know if it's the cbs stink on it or what but there's just like this nothing feels
cool about it i it's hard to put a finger on it feels like a cbs show i mean and i can't fault
anybody working on the show for that cbs is gonna get their fingerprints all over the thing but yeah
but i mean just no part of this connects it just makes no fucking sense and again the end the end
twist is very cool but it's not enough to save the episode and then the final punch of this episode
again no offense to the writer it's just complete completely fucking ripped off of one of the most
famous horror movies of all time i mean just just a complete literally somebody just being like we're
to do the thing from that movie at the very very end and you're like what guys you what what
why did you just do that because it doesn't even in the movie that i'm referring to and i can't say
it's gonna spoil the ending in the movie that i'm referring to this thing at the end makes sense
because it goes along with the concept of the movie at the end of this thing it doesn't make any
fucking sense right there's no foreshadowing it's just it's just crazy it's crazy and you've got
you know he's like he becomes famous over three days or something and like that's the other
thing i couldn't tell him like is this supposed to be a time lapse because it seems like three sets
after he realizes what does work on stage he still keeps opening what the same joke that always bombs
and you're like this doesn't make any fucking sense i gotta say that really stuck in micro two and
every time he started with that terrible joke i was like god damn it like it it's an annoying
launch it's a really irritating watch because you just have to keep hearing this joke and i don't
know man so that was episode one i that being said i did not go into episode two with any sort of
excitement i was rolling my eyes before i even hit play and i will say this at the top episode two
reinstilled my faith in the show i enjoyed it it kept me on the edge of my seat i it made much more
cohesive sense to me it's still tried to do a little too much but it with but at least landed the
plane episode two is called 20 ,000 terror 20 ,000 feet nightmare at 30 ,000 feet and wasn't that the
shadner one and the lift gal one so classic Richard Matheson story yes and it was the shadner one
and then it was remade as the lift gal one a little inside info Matheson here's what i find
confusing Matheson hated the lift gal version uh -huh he hated it because he was like they do they have
nice little nods like they you know don't just somebody named donner and both Richard donner directed
that that segment of the twilight zone movie and Joe donner Joe Dante Richard don't you know
little nod little fun nods you can catch in both episodes i think donner directed the original
episode and donte directed the thing in the movie i think no donner directed the the movie he wouldn't
it had been alive i don't oh he would have been alive but i don't think he was a director
you sure yeah there was four segments spielberg donte donner and john landess who killed uh -family
donner was the fourth guy all right anyway anyway um
um the uh make sure god damn it i know donner did something i think with the original twilight i
think he directed one or two of the original twilight anyway while you look that up here's with
who i found George Miller god damn it directed what that's the that's right George Miller i was wrong
yeah we'll see if donner directed the donner um here's a thing Matheson hated the the George
Miller version with lift gal because he said it started at 10 he goes the the thing opens with
the guy in the middle of a nervous breakdown he was like he it's not supposed to do that it's
supposed to you're supposed to see a guy going slowly crazy right over the course of the flight
so then there's some there's a place for him to get to uh to go to an extreme so they actually did
that in this version which i thought was cool and i thought honored Richard Matheson's original
vision however the story of this one is so incredibly different i'm like why is it saying that this
is based on Richard Matheson because Richard Matheson isn't even alive to go cool you know like yeah
this is really just an airplane episode of the twilight zone that being said you were annoyingly
right Richard Donner directed the original thank you um yeah he's like 85 dude he is very i just
think of him as being an 80s director so i didn't but there's only 15 years earlier so i've looked it up
he didn't do Superman until he was like 51 or something yeah like so uh you're you're much more
of a zone head i've only seen the first season and scattered highlights i have seen this episode i
have seen the shadow version the lithco version and i thought okay shadow and lithco two of the greatest
hands of our time and then to be given Adam Scott i was troubled because he is not that actor i
did think you did a solid job in it but um i boy i like this a lot less than you did
and i'm not sure i followed it uh i mean i a whole time like scroll ahead in the podcast
find out what's going on stop listening to it in real time find out what to do save yourself it was
kind of well that's that again harkens back to what i was saying about like they tried to do too much
like he gets on the plane okay so the setup is he's had a traumatic experience in uh
was it fallujah or something he's a reporter he's covering war territories whatever war zones
he had a traumatic experience he's getting on a plane to go back to work he had a nervous breakdown
so it's all the same setup as the last as the original version basically this guy's been through
something right and now he's got to fly and he's not thrilled about flying uh this one again
things that just didn't need to be there like at the beginning he does this body scan thing in the
airport and everything in the airport looks like it's 20 years in the future from now and you're like
that's not what a body scanner looks like in an airport like this guy would be flying out of
fucking Chicago or Ella you know one of the major hubs and it's like i've been to the major that's not
what it looks like why are you making this look weirdly futuristic right now when it's clearly not
supposed to be the future so that's one thing that's odd he gets on the plane he finds a weird looking
MP3 player in his seat that has this podcast on it about a flight that's gone missing and the
and then he listens to it it's the flight that he can i tell you and i was following this very
carefully and not high or drinking or anything else i thought he was just listening to his own
iPod no which he finds that in his seat yeah and again it just over complicates it just make it be that
he's listening to me it's more interesting if he's listening to his own thing that he likes right
because then he goes then that gives himself doubt this can't be how i listen to this show all the time
this is impossible yeah you know they they just put a little too much on to everything
you know and it's like all right but anyway that all being said this thing didn't really do
anything too crazily new you know you you've all kind of well there's no gremlin on the plane which
i was waiting for the entire time the in both other versions there's a gremlin on the plane like
freaking them out well that's why i say it's weird to say it's based on mathis and story
right really it's just a guy at the end you know when he lands there's a little fun easter egg where
there's a little gremlin doll uh when he falls into the ocean as a little wink but i mean trying to
do too much i absolutely it was a half hour and i found myself sort of confused i like uh Chris
Diamontopoulos who plays the uh i mean i don't know why we're trying to not spoil things almost
uh well because if you don't have amazon prime you can't even see you know i don't or youtube or
well you can't see this one on youtube i don't know i feel like this is a little harder to get to
than some of the other well i mean it doesn't matter it's say go ahead spoil it i just
the the reveal that this guy was the pilot you know i didn't know what the i didn't follow the theme
i just felt lost and i guess it's because when i get when i get lost in something and i'm not i
keep her winding it it generally means i just don't care and i didn't care about this at all
this could have been much more streamlined it didn't have to have
it didn't need it didn't need the it didn't need the mysterious man that he like lets into the
cock it just didn't need any of that there was a way they could because what happens ultimately
here and here's the spoiler is by trying to save the plane he actually allows the man who crashes the
plane access to the cockpit yeah um that could have been done many different ways without having
to have that character be some mysterious guy that's in his ear the whole time on top of the
mysterious podcast that he's listening to yeah on top of him now acting weirdly in a plane where
everybody is on high alert because of racial tensions and religious tensions and all these other things
you know there was a lot to be said about a white guy suspiciously talking to Russian people on a plane
Russian immigrants on a plane or to uh Islamic people in the but i thought like those moments i was like
this is really great like he has to kind of shake down these people a little bit and he's going to
look like a racist and he's also this writer about how we're supposed to be more tolerant that's a nice
little fucking detail in there that's a very awkward thing and i was cringing for him but at the same
time you're like just let that be what it is let it just be that he is freaking out he you know
it it manifests itself in the worst possible scenarios form on the plane and then because he
causes a stink the plane gets hijacked and it crashes right it doesn't have to be that there's this
weirdo guy there like hey i'm with you buddy yeah you know almost giving it away
and you know especially when it look i mean the the story is nothing new either of
away and then he runs into him at the magazine desk ahead of time the Hudson news or whatever yeah
he's what is he he's a figment of his imagination he's a real person that's what it's two episodes in a
row they did that i don't like it yeah it was the same thing with the Tracy Morgan character right you
didn't know if he was dead right or if he was a ghost or if he was really there or the ending when
it's like lost and they're all coming on the island and walking over them i'm like what yeah i didn't
follow that either are they in heaven is that no no the end of the thing is is the podcast plays again
and it says the second part of this is everybody that crashed on that flight was miraculously alive
and saved the only missing person was the Adam Scott character right and the reason he was missing
is because they all kill him because they're like you cost us to crash into the ocean so his own idea
of civility turns on him and they murder him i was confused about the fucking timeline of the thing
so the podcast is happening in the it's it's a future event that he's listening to now supposedly
i mean that that's a lot to grasp that's why i'm saying stop layering stop putting other layers of
icing on top of it just let it let it be that he's listening to his favorite podcast to try to calm down
and on his favorite podcast they're like yeah man we're going to talk about flight whatever and he's
like wait what that's so much fucking cooler it's i don't need everything dumbed down and simplified but
like i didn't understand what was going on that the podcast is in the future so Adam Scott is dead
from the beginning or dead then what is the podcast he's it's just the it's the it's the strange
anomaly that he is on a plane he finds a mysterious podcast player mp3 player he starts listening to
this podcast and this podcast is somehow saying in real time what is happening and that the plane's
going to crash so then he starts freaking out trying to save prevent the plane crash and in preventing it
he manifests what is inevitably going to happen which is the plane gets hijacked and it crashes
i forget what that term is there's a term for that it's called i can't remember i'm not gonna try
to remember but this is my point you've all we've all heard that story or seen that story before
where the guy reading the book and then he looks up and he's like wait a minute this book is talking
about what's happening right now right we've all seen that before uh it's it's it's a bit of a
confusing thing so then don't on top of it put all this other shit that you got a sift through
right and keep track of that just muddies it and again back to us and i'm not trying to be a
pure appeal bully here i'm a fan of Jordan peel it's the same problem us had it's got too much
fucking shit on top of too much fucking shit and then after a while you start losing focus of what
the story is and it can streamline it man streamline god damn thing every original twilight zone the good
ones and that's most of them which is rare in a tv series of five seasons right that show is super
economical it's always crystal clear it's fucking start to finish dude it's like four characters
right the first episode is i was talking a pinkstone about this the first episode is where is everybody
and it's the guy alone right completely alone he doesn't know where anybody's gone and then
at the end of it you find out he's in some containment experiment with the army yeah like
that's what the twilight zone is and a reporter commented on that too but with a review of this
saying like it's not really capturing the concept of the outsider looking in right you know the
the twilight zone was kind of this thing about like well what if you were straight not i'm saying it
wrong what if you were put into a into a bizarre situation but you were the only one in that you were
so alone yeah and having to figure it out they're kind of bringing in these ancillary characters
that are also part of the situation but you don't understand why yeah it would make way more
fucking sense you know if a guy came in and said like you know like when they would do that on the
original show a guy would come in and he would go i'm a dealer of rare antiquities and he would sell
the guy something and then the thing he sold the guy would be like fucked up right and make weird
shit happen and then the guy would have to go find the dealer and be like get take this back it's
ruining my life yeah but this it's like why does it ghostly Tracy Morgan come into the club
and give a guy bad advice on to how to be a good comedian that when i was like is this a commentary
on comedy that you have to be a piece of shit and then also so does that mean everybody else doing
well at the club except for him is a fucking asshole you know what i mean is that mean the black
girl character is an asshole and then they portray her to be a fucking asshole in real life and i'm
like well what is it's just a fuck you to all comedians yeah well i mean that they were they were
telling a camell's character like you know you got to make it more about you which is like crashing
and all these other shows but i i don't i don't i don't i i got so little out of both of these
episodes and i am much less of a fan than you i'm sure you were very frustrated as a twilight zone
fan i know you like the second one i'm a fan it offends me as a comedian but um
i just they really both rubbed me the wrong way and i was pumped about having you know i just bought
the tales from the crib box because i've never seen any of them you know i like it so you're
gonna there's there's some doosies but you're gonna have a lot of fun with a lot of those
i love a short you know anthology horror and i think the time has come i realized there's like one
on shutter there's another one on amazon prime i think there's one on netflix and they're all like
they have no traction nobody watches them i thought this was gonna be it but in a world where we have
black mirror man i mean this really really pales in comparison off off the the starting line i'm gonna
keep watching i'm gonna give it a chance but like the coming soon on episode three oh boy no and
that i think if it's not it looks very much like an adaptation of the hitchhiker episode yeah or no
i'm sorry i it's not the hitchhike the i forget what it's called but there's a lady going from town
to town and there's a cop she keeps seeing behind her yeah or a hitchhiker she keeps seeing it behind
or something like that it looks a lot like that one i've never found that episode to be any very
riveting um i also thought again like i enjoyed to nightmare of thirty thousand feet i thought
that was a strange choice to remake started been remade once you know go for some deeper cuts like
there's so much it's a wealth of material there that's never been adapted or or or or revitalized
or anything are they gonna be doing any just originals and well the shouldn't the comedian is an
original well that's true it's just but you're saying it's very different other ones derivative yeah
but like look here there's a there's an awesome episode in the eighties twilight zone about a comic
played by uh um um who's the guy plays like doll man and uh he was in rhinestone the guy in who's
Harry Crumb that like dates Annie Barry Corbin no no Tim Thomerson never heard of him he's the guy
who's Harry Crumb that dates Annie uh pots okay he's having the affair with her okay anyway Tim
Thomerson sure there's an episode of him from the eighties twilight zone where he's a comic and he's
like it opens on him on this show and he's killing he's fucking killing and he comes off stage and he
finds out that you you find out that he stole a bit from somebody yeah and you know and he's like
that guy wasn't doing anything with that bit i made it the fucking it made me famous because i know
what to do with it like and you find out he's like kind of a piece of shit yeah and he gets into a car
accident and then he ends up in this club and they're like you're you're twice a night you're headlining
you're the biggest thing it's packed rooms every night and he thinks he's in heaven and he goes on stage
and he does all his a list material and it all bombs and then the more bombs the more frustrated he
gets so he starts lashing out at the crowd right and then he's like you just sit there like my second
wife yeah you give me this fucking attitude that's why I hit her because she deserved to be hit
and he starts letting out all these horrible secrets and then they start howling right at all the dark
secrets and they realize as he's in hell and the only way for him to perform every night is to come face
to face with his darkest secrets it's 12 minutes long yeah it's perfect yeah you're like the yeah that's
that's set up at the top that he's a piece of shit and then show the payoff so go back to this comedian
and it this is a problem with a lot of movies and TV shows about comp stand -up comedy the audience
will be howling and and Camille is not saying anything close to a joke or funny I think that's the
point though I think the point is is that it's it doesn't even have to be funny at that point he's
just saying awful things about people but what what is that saying you know like well that's why I
asked you I was like there there were many points in this look I'll say this flat out and you
disagree with me I think that that black girl character was it absolutely a fucking shot at Tiffany
Hattish a hundred percent I haven't seen anyone saying that I I believe you but I didn't she didn't
remind me of Tiffany Hattish she ends her set with going and that's any impulse a joke and then she's
dancing backwards and she's very very animated uh -huh I and this this was clearly supposed to be some
sort of commentary modern comedy they got in the me too shit yeah they got in the fat misogynistic
pig guy every white comic in that episode was a fucking asshole right like like it was clearly a
commentary of some kind of some kind of modern day comedy yeah and I was like that's a little strange
to me like that seems like it's supposed to maybe be a shot at Tiffany and then this all seems sort of
like a shot at comedy in general like I never knew why anyone was laughing or what why they weren't
laughing and I don't know and then even the clientele like like oh these are the douchebags that would
go to the comedy store hedge fund investors right even that part was absurd where the guys like
I make about 85 thousand a week it's like this is not how heckling works yeah you go see a show
like this is crazy right so I don't know that's that's the twilight sofa we're an hour 20 we're
way fucking over here all right I don't know how many they're doing um I think about 12 I think it
is about 12 or something I cannot uh give my money to CBS so I'm going to cancel my uh subscription
and and wait till at some point it gets put out and watch it another way but um yeah I might do
the same because I mean I'll tell you this I'm like what else is on this app I don't want to watch
the good fight there's nothing on the app but I mean I the truth is and it's not even like people
whispering behind their hands people have seemed pretty let down by these episodes and I would imagine
knowing CBS there was a tremendous amount of interference I don't know that for sure but I would
imagine and it can't really shake that feel of it feels like a CBS drama and if CBS does anything
right it ain't drama um so I don't know they miss the mark I don't think CBS gets it for a second
I think they got it at one point I think whoever's there now they don't get it yeah and I've I said
this to you too this is the only iteration of the twilight zone including the forest witter
version right if I'm remembering correctly where they put the hosts name in the opening credits
like like when they when they show who's starring in each episode it says and Jordan Peele as the narrator
they never did that they always let there be a mystery even though you know who that was kind of
in the 80s when you don't even see him it's just a voiceover but even in the fucking movie when
Burgess Meredith narrated it and that was a nod to the original twilight zone and Burgess Meredith
was a legend of Hollywood they didn't write at the top of the fucking movie and Burgess Meredith as
the narrator like I just that couldn't it couldn't have bugged me any less but um I think it speaks to
modern television no you got to have their name there right they you got to have their like no
that could have been it could have been in Jordan Peele's contract could have been an agent thing you
never know but whoever made the call it was a bad call it's it's just it to me that's it and he's
doing a little like arch eyebrow move when he says the twilight zone like almost like a wink
like those the twilight zone raises eyebrow kind of like I couldn't I couldn't figure out the tone of
this thing I will tell you this he is as much of a twilight zone fan as I am yeah and if I got put
at the helm of the new twilight zone yeah somebody said and we're gonna put your name in the credits
I would have said no you're fucking not you could put it at the end if you want you do not put my name
with the cast at the beginning right that's not how this show works I'm telling you all those little
details are what makes something they add up they add up the demos in the details are you
continuing I mean are you keeping the app and going down the road with it I mean you hate CBS I didn't
even get to make money from them I mean they fired me before I make any money so I mean I feel dumb
keeping the app too yeah yeah you know I mean so I don't know it's and it's six bucks a month for the
one with commercials and they go with minimal ads it's like four solid minutes of ads well
I was just doing the trial I just went ahead and got the
yeah shit I forget I knew it's great so one I was too afraid I'd forget to shut it off and then I
would just keep paying right $12 a month anyway folks that's our show this comes out when Monday
so Joe DeRosa comedy on Instagram sorry folks I'm not gonna be in Valley Forge at the casino
after all I apologize I had to cancel due to a scheduling conflict but I'll try to reschedule that
as soon as possible I don't think many hellians are out that way anyway and if you worry I probably
saw it the filly shows a little while back but I will however be this weekend at the in Milwaukee
Wisconsin at the such and such casino bonkers presents so Google bonkers Milwaukee Joe DeRosa you'll find
the shows there's two Saturday at a casino please come out and make those shows tolerable
because it is a long ass fucking trip out there and back and the second I land is like the second I
leave so anyway that's about it for now new story in penthouse in this current issue and
billburn I have well that billburn well I'm not gonna plug that because we got to switch it up but
but billburn I have a podcast called uninformed again and more to come on that I'm at the Patrick
Walsh Twitter and Instagram our next episode will be all things pet cemetery that's probably gonna be
a juicy one we're gonna be talking pet cemetery the Stephen King novel we're gonna be talking pet
cemetery the 99 movie and the new movie we're gonna be talking pet cemetery two we're gonna be talking
the documentary about pet cemetery which is now on shutter a lot to chew on so we'll see you next time
and we will see you in health