...
2023 back at it again for the new year, but the same old bull is just how you like them.
Have you noticed, Pat, that now for consecutive seven years? Yeah. Everybody tweets.
See, see you later, awful 2022. Here's to a better year next year. It's like it's been seven years
consecutively of that notion. Yeah. New year's day. It's just such a terrible time to be alive.
Yeah. It's just gotten worse. You know, I talked about that on the solo pod. It's like
this year has to head in a more positive direction. The graph of the last decade is just a straight downhill.
It's like that price is right thing with the yodel or that goes up the mountain and then falls straight
down. What game is that? You don't know that one. It's like a Swiss mountain climber with like
the ice pick on his back kind of guy. Yeah. They might they might have discontinued it. It was not that fun
again, except for the yodeling. The only game I remember on prices rate is Plinco Classic and
and then them spinning the wheel. That's all I remember of the show. I probably used to be like they
they wait those Plinco chips or something because they never hit the big bucks. They put a wait in
those Plinco chips. She's right. She's probably right. She's probably right. I've actually never seen
an episode of the Drew Carey. Price is right. I've only seen the Barker era. I have seen some
and I remember thinking dear God, this man looks to be at the end of his tether. Like it just
I've never and I'm not knocking Drew Carey. I'm a fan of the guy but I mean I just it just I was like
he's he I just never saw a game show host looks so much like he was mailing it in.
Like just like well, then you then you missed that run that was on like NBC for a while there.
Those those prime time game shows. That's that's when they had the with Alec Baldwin hosted one.
I mean the Joel McCale. Well, I've actually never seen anyone like lower in their career than
Joel McCale. He was he was not hiding his hatred for the format. My favorite has become Pat Sajek
who is just at a go fuck yourselves. This is how I make my money and like with it, he's he's
smart ass. He shits on the guests but it's not angry. It's just a guy being like who gives a fuck.
It's will afford you know, like this is a deal.
Sure back. Sure back was the same by the end and I always loved it. One of my favorite not
just jeopardy clips but all time favorite internet clips. I don't remember the specifics but it's this
guy talking about how he like he gets together like his favorite pastime is to get together with
his friends and do like political wraps. And he's so he's talking and he's like, you know, we wrap
on the political issues of the day and you know, like kind of build off each other and freestyle.
It's the then cuts over to a trip back and he goes loser.
I'm going to find it and send it to you. It's it's the best comedic timing I've ever seen.
By the way, a big happy birthday to Pat Walsh. Yes.
Thanks. I saw the post that the CU and Health pod Insta put up and I appreciate it. We
always forget to mention that we have a CU and Health Insta. You can find some best of clips and
if you're not on Facebook, that's a good place to meet some people in the CU and Health community.
Folks, we're talking today about Violent Night.
This is a film that did pretty well in theaters. It's done pretty well on streaming and I've seen
a lot of positivity about it. Will Joe and I agree. You'll find out. It's about, yeah, this is
Santa who fights back. The tail end of Christmas on this episode just covering the last of the
Christmas movies and I've got a couple in my old movie corner that we didn't get to.
And how was your, I guess we haven't spoken since Christmas. How was your, well, we mean we've spoken,
but not on the air. How was your Christmas? My look, I'm not going to sugarcoat it. My holiday season
was not good. I stayed local and I'm glad I did. So look, I'm going to look glass half full and say,
I could have wound up stuck in an airport, you know, for days or stuck in Missouri or anything else,
but basically I was going to go home for Christmas. The flights were all well over a thousand,
which I've never even seen before. And I could just tell it was like going to be chaos and it was.
So I didn't go anywhere. I didn't do anything. I had a lovely Chinese dinner with our friend Lizzie
Cooperman on Christmas Eve. We went up to a Chinese place in town and that was nice.
Beyond that, I just kind of laid low. New Year's Eve didn't do anything, you know, is what it is.
Birthday didn't really do much. But you don't got it. Yeah, when you get older, it's just a sad
fact of life. If you don't have kids, birthdays, holidays, they just mean shit the more the older you get.
Yeah, I, I, I came, I tested negative on, I, I had COVID. Yeah, that I tested and I felt fine for days,
but I was testing positive. So I was like, all right, I guess this is Christmas. Christmas morning,
I tested negative on three different tests. I called my family. I was like, look, guys,
it's up to you all because you're not the ones that had anything.
I can come down and spend the day with you if you want. They say you're supposed to test negative
for a few days first before doing that, but it's up to you. They were like, yeah, we're come down.
We've all had it recently. We're all clear, like, come down. So we, we, we locked out at the very last
minute. Yeah, that, that we were able to get together. And I got to be honest with you, you know, I showed
up at my cousins. It was so last minute, I showed up at my cousins. They were already eating dinner
on Christmas day. And I, I, we were there for a couple of hours. Then we went back to my parents' house
and my folks and I exchanged our gifts. And I laid low there for a couple more days before seeing
any other people to make sure I was definitely in the clear. And I was, so it was fine. But um,
it really put a new, I got to say it put a new spin on Christmas for me. Like it, because Christmas
is my favorite holiday. I love it. I make a very big deal out of it. I have a lot of events I plan
and do around it annually. Yeah. And this year when all that was gone and it was just kind of
like, Hey, we actually are getting to hang out together. Took a lot of the tension out of the room.
My parents and I didn't fight about anything. Good. My mom fucked up my present. I didn't care.
What was your present? She got me a couple little things. But, but the two, the two, one of the two,
like, I guess, main and heavy quotes things that I asked for was the Godfather 4K collection.
She got you the BHS. Yeah. Yeah. I got the blue rays by accident. And she was like, I'm really sorry.
I think I got you the wrong thing. And I'm like, it's okay. And she's like, well, I'm going to
return it and send you the 4Ks. And I was like, yeah, okay. If you feel like it would ever, you know,
I think, uh, I think under different circumstances, I wouldn't have gotten mad. But I certainly would have
been like, tomorrow morning, I will meet you at the dining room table, where we will place the order
together for the 4K, you know, like I would, I would have been very concerned about getting it right.
But five years ago, Joe would have smashed her face into the DVD box. So what does that say?
Read it out loud to me. What does that say? Now read my list. What does that say?
One of that 4K, K, a, a, a, a, peace, mommies. I wouldn't have smashed her face, you know,
but that is very funny. Uh, it's a very funny, uh, what do you call that a jib at me? A jipe?
Jive? Uh, I think jive and jipe both apply there. Um, you know, so it was, it was, it was a nice holiday
in that puke true meaning of the holiday kind of way. Uh, and that was it. Then I came back to
New York and then New Year's Eve, we had a huge, I had four shows and then we had a huge thing at the
bar. Uh, I was in my bar until, I want to say 6 .30 a .m. Yes. I was so hung over on New Year's day,
I didn't wake up until 5 p .m. Oh, what's that? You doing coke? No, I'm, what's that? Who's that?
6 .30 a .m. I just wondered if maybe there was some sort of substance. I don't know. I don't know
anything about substances. I'm like, I had a, I had a few sodas and I went home.
Oh, a couple like a cream and a, and a diet seven up. Um, but anyway, as I've said on the show,
the one time I did coke, I had the worst hangover ever. So I'm sure you felt like dog shit.
So I didn't say I didn't need drugs. I, when you, I will say this, when you own the bar staying
up all night with it is not a hard thing to do. Sure. It's not like, it's not like trying to hang
out the roost till 6 .00 a .m. where you're like, baby, we need some assistance here. Right. Uh, but
what remind me, I got, I got a little story about the room. It's remind me. Um, but it was very fun.
Um, I feel like I've told you all of this already. No, but I haven't, because we haven't talked on
the phone. Do you leave the bar open? Or do you just have like a few people and clocked dorm?
Had our hours are till 2 a .m. Uh, on, on a Saturday evening and we follow those rules strictly.
Oh, okay. I feel like there's a lot of line going on in this podcast. I'd have fun. That's fine.
Oh, he's lying. We're just, uh, we're just the other night. Um, so I, I tried to not eat until
like two Joe and I were doing this intermittent fasting different times in noon or two, depending.
And sometimes I forget to eat because if you, if you don't eat till two, sometimes you just go
by your day and it doesn't occur to you. So the other night I'm driving around. It's like 9 .30. I
hadn't eaten anything. And I was just like, I didn't feel good. I wanted a dive bar atmosphere,
even though I'm not drinking. And I was like, I wonder what the old roost is up to because I love how
they decorated around Christmas time at the roost. Our old stomping ground. I go in just like every other
time I go in, there's no hello. There's an immediate what happened to you and your friends. Where are you?
Where is Joe? That's nice. That's nice. That's a hello. Yeah. I guess it's a hello. But it's
just like, you know, I, the implication is we were keeping them in business. Essentially, we, we
were. Have you seen a couple for a couple of months there? We were. Yeah. But, um, I, you know, I started
talking to her and, you know, she seemed like her usual kind of strange self ordered the Thai food
there, which was delicious. And I had always heard it was. It was great. Yeah. They, they have nice food.
But, um, Joe used to tell the owner of this place like, look, your, your quote,
specials are embarrassing. They would have these like a shot and a beer specials that were outrageously
priced. And she had gone so far in the other direction. I look up and I asked her, I go, is this
for real a white claw and a shot of vodka for $19? That's so crazy. She goes, yeah, and I just started
laughing. And she's like, well, I go, this, I know, I almost said her name there, but I'm like, this
is, I love your bar. Obviously, but this isn't like some high -end cocktail lounge or something. You know
that, right? And she was like, yes, yeah. I go, 19 is not a special, a, a, a white claw pretty much
anywhere on earth is going to be about five bucks. The most you'd ever see it for would be like a
concert where it might be eight. Maybe about, you saw them for about six, seven bucks somewhere
in there. I'd say in New York. Yeah. But, but, but now is that a shot with a shot of well whiskey at the
most should be $12. A shot of well vodka. So I'm like, well vodka. I go, you're going to have people
getting sick. Like, that's like the worst shot you could do in their, and she goes, well, they
chase or they can mix it. They can mix it with the white claw. I'm like, yeah, that'd be a well
vodka soda, which should cost about $7. You know, like, and you try to help her, but she just won't
take the hint. I don't get it. Nick Rutherford, who's, who's a funny guy. He's, he's in, he's in that
debt show on adult swim dream, something or other. I forget what it's called dream team or whatever
the fuck. Anyway, I know him. He's a good guy and check out his stuff that he acts in if he can. He's
funny. Actually, he's one of many people that I, without ever speaking to him, decided years ago,
I don't like have nothing to back it up and just continue feeling like I don't like it. I think
you'd like him if you talk to him. I mean, he was events in Georgia's wedding, right? Yeah. He became
a late error friend for me in, in LA. Like toward the end, we just got tight and, and he, he's actually
been out in New York a bunch lately. It's, it's, he's a good guy. Anyway, it doesn't matter. We were
in there. We, this is, well, actually, this is when we became friends. We started just meeting at
the roost for whatever reason, right? And, and he and I were in there one night drinking and we were
telling the owner, we were like, you, it's a dive bar. You have to have a shot and beer special.
Like you have to have it. You have to have a $10 shot and beer special, right? It's crazy that you
don't have this. Yeah. And, and only because everything was so overpriced, we're like, you got to
give the people one thing. I think every bar gives the, gives the people one thing. You know, my
bar, their one thing is that giant seven dollar PBR that Vince will have 12 of an on a one day night.
But yeah, our, our bar is, we have a menu of eight sandwiches that cost eight dollars each. That's
an unbeatable deal. Like, give a, give your audience one thing. And we were telling them to go there.
Yeah. Yeah. We were telling her like, please, just, so, and she's like, she's like, what should
it? And we were really like discussing it. And she was listening. She's like, so what should it be?
We're like, you know, like a Miller high life in a shot of whiskey. That's your special
boom. Yeah. And she's like, okay, all right. That's interesting. I'm going to take it into consideration.
So we leave, I go back a week later. She's like, look, and there's posters all over the bar
for this new shot and beer special. And I'm like, oh, my God, you did it. And then I look and it's a
pony of Miller high life with a shot of well whiskey for $10, which is not a great deal. It's
possible, I guess. And I was flexible. Yeah. She was so elated like, this is your special. And
then I said to the bartender, can I have my special, but with the well tequila instead of whiskey?
And she said, only if the owner doesn't see me give it to you, because I will get in trouble.
Wow. I mean, what is the point? What is the point? I hear, now, here's the
one thing they do that that's the reason you go to the roofs. A heavy poor. Yes. That is
true. You never see the little mini shot glass come out. You never, you know, generally,
if you get a vodka soda there, you're getting three shots of vodka at a normal bar. Yes.
I'll give them that. But yeah, it's just there's some places that just don't get it. I live in
you know, a really cool part of town. And at some point, I'll probably be a little too old for
the part of town, you know, like it's, I, you know, silver like Echo Park. Let's feel as it's a
young town. And these cool bars come and go just for these reasons. The bars that spill out into
the street are the ones like trophy wife where they do buy one, get one.
The trophy wife, I don't understand. I don't understand how it stays open.
Well, they pulled they pulled the two for one. And they're still crowded. That, that was their
kind of genius thing is they create this fun outdoor neighborhood bar vibe with an unbeatable
drink special. And then at some point, they dropped it. And at that point, they had already kind of
become the top spot. Yeah, hooked. Um, I, I, it's the, it is a heavy port. Oh, that's what I was
going to say. It is a heavy port. The roost. The roost is the only place. Well, that I saw our friend
Jesse pop many a nights, a sleep on the bar in there. Uh, sharing that with everyone. I don't think he
cares. Uh, or almost fall off the stool backwards. Sure. You would just get ripped. I'm not knocking him
for it. I'm saying, this is how drunk you would get in there. Yeah. And you know, you know,
what I was going to say is the only place though that where Jesse was asleep on the bar top. And then
when we woke, we were like, dude, dude, he's like, I'm fine. And ordered another drink. And they gave
it to him. Oh, they never cut you off. He weren't like, no, that's enough. And it's the only bar
that you see that woman refusing service at any point. No, no, it's the only bar also. I've watched
you, I've watched you take a turn or two. And I'm sure where you'll go around the corner. And I'm like,
what, uh, well, that's what I was, that's what I was getting to. I haven't had a corner turn like
that. Honestly, since you left L .A., I've kept myself in way better check. But during that, uh,
that really stressful period of my life, when we were going there all the time, I was, I was running
wild. And that night, uh, it reminded me when I was up there because they had this special,
the eggnog special. Yeah. And it says, uh, like in quotes, a roost style poor of whiskey mixed with our
eggnog or whatever, whatever they pretend, whatever they used to pretend that it sounded better than
it was. Um, but I ordered it. I feel like it was post Christmas. And I was already pretty drunk.
We were, it was, it was right before Christmas, you were, we were, it was right before the break.
You were terribly stressed because that's when work is usually the worst is right before that break.
Yes. Because you're getting everything for sure. Yes. That was the same night.
Uh, on your third drink there, I don't know what you drank before that, but I get from work. I think
there you said. And I quote, what is the highest level alcohol beer you have?
You got that. And then you said, I want to try this eggnog. And I remember Vince and I were like, Pat,
slow it down a little bit. This is probably not a great idea. And then that eggnog, whatever the
fuck it was, put you out. I was, that put, I never saw a man get put down by one drink like that.
I've had two, two of those in my life. One is this beer that they no longer serve at the red lion,
which is another just amazing bar that thankfully has hung in there throughout all the shit.
But it's, it's the vibe indoors is like the englorious bastards bar and the vibe outside is
like a dream beer garden. It's a perfect bar. So, um, they used to have this beer called the
Spartan optimator. And I asked the guy, I was like, does anyone order that? And I'm like, that looks,
that beer is like black as like, you know, the devil's soul. You know, he was kind of laughing
and stuff. And he's like, no, it's a crazy high alcohol. Like, it's, it's very intense. That's
why it has a name that sounds like a Schwarzenegger movie or something. They go, well, you know,
I got to try one of these Spartan optimators. Beautiful summer night. I remember I had been flirting
with this girl. I had maybe had two drinks. Having a great time. This Spartan optimator, I remember
about halfway down just the lights went out in my brain. I just went like, what woke up the next day
at home? Drove. Yeah. Something was wrong. Like that beer was like it had some sort of weird,
you know, drug and fentanyl laced or something like that. And then the other time was that egg
nog. And I remember, I hate eggnog. I hate alcohol being mixed with anything cream based because it
curdles in its disgusting. And it was like, I was remembering that I hated it as it hit my lips.
And then the lights went out there as well. I was like, whoa, sometimes it's one, it's one drink.
Sometimes you can have 40 drinks and feel completely fine. It's strange. Yeah, it is strange, isn't it?
So strange web it weaves. I didn't watch the evil dead trailer and I should have. But it is crazy
because I saw I was about to click on it yesterday and I got distracted by something. But as I'm about
to click on it, there's this like beautiful demon woman who's like the poster for the evil dead.
Yeah. And I go, holy shit. Is that blank? Sure enough, it is my good friend's girlfriend.
And the ex girlfriend of another good friend of mine, who I know really well. I was just like,
well, you can see she's on the poster. Yeah. Who is it? I don't know. I don't know. I
think all right. All right. For some reason, I feel weird to talk. It's because they're friends
who dated the same girl. And I don't want, you know, I don't know. You're not saying their names.
What's her name? All right, you don't have to. I don't care. All right. She's a New Zealand actor.
She was on that outlander. She's just pretty red hair. I did watch the evil dead trailer.
I was looking forward to seeing it. I wasn't particularly excited about the concept of this new evil
dead. Yes. But it's a new evil dad, Ramy and Campbell are producing. And I'm a fan of those
guys. I want them to always kick ass. And I have friends that have been involved in the franchise.
And you want to see the franchise continue to do well. So I was excited to see the trailer.
And they've never really churned out a bad product. Yes.
And this might be good. It looks solid enough. But I have to say, it's just it's another iteration
of the concept. And for what I can tell, it's a new necronomicon. It's not the one from the new remake
or the last movie they did. It's definitely not the Bruce Campbell universe.
Evil dead. Right. But I also don't think it's the universe of the remake of Evil
Dead that came out a few years back. I think it's yet another just, hey, it's evil dead again.
And this time it's over here. Is it modern day? And like haters and a cabin in the woods?
No, no, it's called evil dead rise because it's in an apartment building.
Oh, right. I guess I rise. But it takes place. It seems to take place amongst a family, mainly.
Yeah. Well, I was looking up her name because I wanted to make sure I had her last name correct.
It's a list of Sutherland. I've never seen her in anything. She was on the Viking show for a long time.
But yeah, I, you know, that's her name. So, but it's just weird to see it to see a friend dressed
as a zombie, you know, when I'm a movie poster. But you know, man, I got to say,
I don't know. I just was kind of like, I just was like, all right. I guess it's, you know, they,
and like, there's a shot in the end of the trailer of one of the main characters wielding a chainsaw.
Yeah, I'm like, how many variations are we going to do on like the chainsaw and evil dead and the
elements of evil dead? But it's not the same universe. So like, I just wish it was just the same
universe. Like, right. Yeah. Like, or, and maybe it is, it's just a different book. And there are
many of these books, or I don't know, I just, it's, it sort of gets, sort of, it starts to get like the
DC thing after a while where you're like, you're like, wait, what? This is Joker, but it's not the Joker
or in the Ben Affleck Batman, but down there, right, Eaton's back. And, you know, but God bless,
it's a, it's a property that works. It's a good concept. Well, what's interesting is he did,
the director, this guy Lee Cronin did the hole in the ground, which was a Sundance movie that I watched
that, you know, I would say was average at S. It was a very kind of a 24 style,
semi horror movie, not scary at all. And sometimes it's just crazy how these people get bumped up
to these things. I don't know how it happens. Maybe they just pitch a great take or they have
a great vision. I don't know. But he, that guy did not seem like the type based off that movie
to take over the evil dead franchise. But what do I know? Whereas Fetty Alvarez, who did the other
remake, I think was a really good fit. You know, with my, I have issues with that one. But what you
remember about it is the insane over the top gourd. And that's what Alvarez I think does really well.
This is in the same, this is in the same vein as that last one. It's very dark. Is it an R -rated,
I mean, a red band trailer? I think so, yeah. It's, you know, it's very dark. It's very sinister.
You know, it look, you know, I'll see it. It looks okay. I'm just not excited about it. You know,
the other trailer that you saw that you told me to watch and I did in Christ almighty. This
Renfield looks, yeah, Renfield looks to be not a horror movie at all, which is what I was hoping for.
I like the lead kid, Anthony Holt. I always liked him and stuff. I just saw the menu and I thought he
was, I'm sorry, what did I say? Anthony, Anthony Holt. Yeah, Nicholas Holt. I liked him in the menu,
which I just saw and really enjoyed and Nicholas Cage, of course, as Dracula, like the dream.
And the trailer has very little Nicholas Cage. Don't know what that means. Don't know if maybe the
performance is one of his ones that are so insane that they're trying to hide it or what? I could
prove he's just not in it very much. No, it's, I took that 100 % as you're supposed to be like,
whoa, it's Nicholas Cage is Dracula. Like if you watch the trailer certainly is presented as
you're not supposed to know what it is already. Yeah, but you're watching it Sherlock Holmes style
fighting from Nicholas Holt. So it's like, oh, it's an action movie, but then they're making really bad
jokes. But it's supposed to, it's clearly the trailer is supposed to unfold in a narrative of,
here's a guy that's in a support group because it's in a toxic relationship. What is that? And it's,
it's, it's delving out the information slowly, but surely throughout. And then the big climax is
the reveal like, oh, he's Renfield in Dracula is who he's talking about and then enter Dracula and
it's Nicholas Cage. Yeah. And I got to tell you, I like Nicholas Cage. I have an acquaintance who's
in a new Nicholas Cage movie. I'm very excited for her. I'm, I'm over the, he's in on the joke. I'm
over it. It hit, it hit a wall for me with that fucking thing where he was with Pedro Pescal,
you know, playing himself and, you know, it's just, it's like, you got to, I'm just, I'm just,
I'm just, it's the gold bloom thing now. It's like, oh, you know, you're weird. So now you're going to
be weird. And here we go. You know, I hear you, I mean, walking, I, I walk in, only did kind of joke
performances for 15 years. I think I remember like, catch me if you can. I was like, always trying
again. He's acting again. And I really hope that they remember at some point that Nicholas Cage is
an amazing actor. You get, you get taste of it. Mandy, for sure, pig, for sure. But then there's also
this other side of him. And maybe that's the money. And I know he's always in need of money. So
maybe he goes for that too often. But yeah, him with the tongue and cheek thing, it's, it's not for me
either. But in his case, it's just remembering what a brilliant actor he was. And hoping that returns,
you know, or when he can modulate it as in the rock or something where he's a person that you
believe as a human. And then he says crazy and hilarious things once in a while, or he overreacts
like honeymoon in Vegas. But yeah, when he's pitched at a 10, the whole movie, it's very boring to
me. I agree with. Well, but also too. It's like, it's like this, this sort of ironic excitement that he's
playing Dracula, which, oh, it's like vampire vampire's kiss and you know, and all that stuff.
It's like, that's not enough to make a movie interesting. Yeah, that's a nice little element if
you want to add that in there. But like, meanwhile, you got to also too, I'm like, look, nobody is ever
going to do the mundane aspects of life, meeting the supernatural better than what we do in the shadows.
They did it the best. The movie is the best version. The show is as good as it could get
outside of the movie. That's it. It's done. Like this whole thing of like, you know, we're being
attacked in a support route by a vampire. Yet we're all still using safe space terminology. And that's
the joke. Right. Like it's stupid, man. It's just not funny anymore. It's been done and I'm over it.
So yeah, and I think we're just going to get a lot more of that because that's what people have
been making over the last several years. I think we're at a point where it feels like we're running
out of stuff to me. Like HBO Max seems to have no shows coming for months. I'm about done with a lot
of the streamers. They're just kind of, they have nothing to offer. It's really weird.
I think where I don't know if we're out of stuff or it's just everything has become so homogenized
and sterile in the fear of offending anybody anywhere at any point that there's just this is what
this is as good as it's going to get now. Like there's just there's so many ideas you can pursue.
And I know I lean too far in the direction at times of the everything is woke. It's ridiculous.
You know, I get it. I know that I'm I exaggerate the effect of that. But it is something that is
happening. And there are other factors here also too. You know, when you can glamorize every single
movie studio and everything and movie production and television production now functions the way
banks do where you have four choices. Yeah. I mean, what the, this is it. We're done. It's conveyor
belt entertainment. You know, like you got to go to the indie labels to get you to get the good stuff.
Yeah. My buddy, John Gabers, who does that the great show on church TV, I recommended with Adam Pally.
Yeah. You know, 50 places to see, you know, before you die or while you're drunk or whatever,
sorry, you can look it up. But I just hiked with Gabers. And he was telling me like the big
kind of axe hanging over them is like this Zazlov character, this new guy has to decide
what to cut. And he's cutting everything like he's not going to air that girl and all this other stuff.
So they're like, well, we think ours would be okay because it's cheap. This show about literally
two guys drinking across the country in cheap bars. And he's wanting them to cut the budget in half.
And it's like, that's going to be a problem too because everything starts to look like shit. And
you have to say, well, if I want a season two, I guess I'll have to accept these cuts.
Dude, I just caught a tough. We got to go to the movie corner, I think. But I just got to say,
I caught a few minutes of this Jay Leno game show that's on now. And this poor bastard,
like this fucking thing looks so cheap. Yeah. And like it's not because of like,
you know, people say like, well, that's high definition. And you're going to say, no, no,
it's not that. It's the fucking thing looks cheap. Right. Period. Like if you like you can
look at the furniture, look at the way it's built. Like look at the colors of it. Look at the
paint job on everything. Look at the background. These things are being put together. It's like a
crazy person went into the studio and cobbled together, whatever they could find. And you're like,
what the fuck is going on in here? There's no concept to any of it because they don't want to pay for
a good art designer or set dresser or whatever. You know, they don't want to pay for quality
products. They want to be able to tear something down within moments. Yeah. And it's probably
that's probably there. They have a $1 .1 million per episode budget. One million goes to Jay.
They're like, that's probably what's going on there. Or at least that equation.
Because they'll just that's what they do. Like on peacock. I finally the other day was like,
why the hell do I have peacock? It's 20 shows with Kevin Hart. I like Kevin Hart. I think he's
very funny. But it's like Kevin Hart cooking. Kevin Hart interviewing celebrities. Kevin Hart
interviewing sports figures. Keenan and Kevin Hart hosting a best week ever style show. Recapping 2022.
It's like guys and good for you making that money. Kevin, but holy cow.
Give it work on something else. If you're throwing all your money at one man, where's everything else
going? But I will say this and take us into the movie corner. Please watch this show on the peacock now
shitting on them called Paul T. Goldman. It's got a bad title. Bad title folks. And I'm sorry.
But it is amazing. I don't want to tell you much about it. It is well worth getting peacock. Maybe
you let them build up. So you got all the episodes. But so far, it's amazing. What it is is a standard
kind of true crime story of this guy, a single father who's a wild character. He's just a weird guy.
And he gets swindled by this woman. And then her story winds up being very, very dark and twisty.
This guy called contacted the director Jason Walner, who's a TV director. He's done a bunch of great
comedy. We did a bunch of modern family and stuff. And contacted him. He's a young guy and said,
hey, my story's amazing. I think it'd be a great movie. And I've written the script. The script that he's
written of it is kind of nuts and very funny, but it's all true. And he keeps saying it's all true.
Then you start wondering if his story is all true. So there's only three episodes posted. I hope I've
hooked you. It's very Nathan Fieldery. It's very funny. It's got a tiger king kind of vibe to it.
But I've never seen anything like it. It's the best thing the peacock's done so far. Check out Paul T.
Goldman. All right. I'm just going to do two quickies. My last two Christmas watches of 2022.
The first of the two is the the black Christmas remake, which was highly recommended to me by
our friend and initiator, if you will, Ken Hanley. So you mean not the most recent one? Not that one.
There was a remake in like 2006 or something that was done. I don't think I've ever seen it.
Stars. Well, not Lorraine Newman for Christ sakes from SCTV, the lady from my big fat Greek wedding.
Andrea Martin. Andrea Martin's in it. I did.
Andrea Martin is in it. Oh, for God's sakes. My brain. Jesus Christ. The girl from Cloverfield
basement with John Goodman, whatever the fuck that would be with the basement.
10 Cloverfield Lane. Easily the best of the franchise, I would say. But you're talking about
Melanie. No. Sarah Michelle. No, it's a three -namor.
Mary Elizabeth Winstead. Mary Elizabeth, Nastra Antonio. Yeah. So she stars in it. Lacey
and then a nice turn from Oliver Hudson, who I've become a fan of because of rules of engagement
where on rules of engagement, he plays a real airhead. And in this, he's kind of a dirty prick.
And I enjoyed watching him in that role. Anyway, Ken Hanley recommended this to me years ago,
before the the Blumhouse remake came out. He's like, Joe, I don't know if you've seen it. Believe it
or not, though, the remake of Black Christmas is really solid. Give it a watch. I thought there's
no way in hell. This is good. But Ken is saying it's good. And the DVD is like six bucks on Amazon.
So I'll take a chance. So I bought it. And then finally this year, I watched it. And I texted you
early on when I was watching it. And I said, oh, this isn't very good. And why did I say that
because, oh, I'm sorry. No, that wasn't black. I'm getting mixed up with deadly night, which we already
did. I talked about that. Sorry. This, this, I did think was very good from the jump. It's well shot.
It's well written. It sticks closely enough to the source material that it's worthy to be called
a remake unlike the Blumhouse version that was just confusing. It's a it's a it's a no holds bar
unrelenting crazy slasher movie like it's, you know, it's Billy the the the craze killer
returns to the house that he grew up in, which is now a sorority house to murder a bunch of people.
The one change they did make was black Christmas. I believe was the first ever movie to do the
call is coming from inside the house thing, right, before when a stranger calls. And they, they
take that out of this one for obvious reasons, because it's like, it's really not the plot isn't
too reliant on it. Number one, and number two, it doesn't, you know, you would have seen it.
If you know that that was going to happen, it kind of would ruin the movie for you.
But it was it was a it was a really fun watch. It was great. The kills are crazy. It is suspenseful.
It is sinister. I would recommend this one. The the ending is wild and over the top.
And you know what? It's back when they made a goddamn movie and they let the movie be the movie
without any worry of can we franchise this? Can we whatever? You know, and I'm not saying
that 2006, you know, was a, you know, like they didn't do that prior to two. Of course they did.
They've been doing that for years and years and years. But my point is is I appreciate when you see a
movie in this vein that is allowed to just be its own thing. It's directed by Glenn Morgan,
who final destination. I think so. And a lot of ex files work.
And there you go. There you have it. The original, of course, directed by the great Bob Clarke,
who directed the Christmas story, starring Olivia Hussey, who is currently
suing over the Romeo and Juliet news. Oh, yeah. So like I get the criteria on stuff, you know,
like newsletters and stuff. And I read up on it. I'm a collector of their shit. And
one, I was not particularly excited about it all because it's a super boring movie was this
Franco Zeffarelli 1969 -ish version of Romeo and Juliet that I saw when I was in high school
was bored by and moved on with my life. So criteria and has a version of it coming out. And in the same
week, Olivia Hussey is saying that it was like child porn. And she was forced to get naked for
the cameras. And she was lied to and suing the studio for millions and millions of dollars. It's
gets a wide story. What's sus that just got that just made it more suspect now it is fucked up that
they showed a naked 15 year old. Yeah, but he's arguing that. Here's the suspect part. Olivia Hussey
said in 2018, multiple times in multiple interviews, we know exactly what we were doing. I was not
taken advantage of this was we were in safe hand. She said the complete I read all those quotes. And
I'm like, how do you do a lawsuit when you know you've made those quotes? It's really interesting to
me. I hate to say it. And I will say it and own the statement. It sounds to me like this criterion
thing's coming out. And she's not getting any money for it. She was like, well, fuck you then.
I'll burn this whole goddamn thing to the ground. Yeah. Because the guys are the guys doing two. By
the way, I googled, I was just on gut felt on Fox. I'm sure you tuned in, right? Pat, you're a big Fox
news. Good watching gut fell. No, I was on gut felt on the show. No, I didn't. I don't have no.
He's an old friend of mine and I did the show and I like doing the show and I know I know some of you
are going, well, why? Because I believe in talking to people that have different opinions than
me. That's why. And anyway, I did the show and I said on the show, you know, I look forward to whatever
government list I have it. I've gotten myself on because the first thing I did was Google the scene
when I was reading the story about I was like, I wanted to not because I was like, oh,
Nathan, I was like, I want to see what they're talking about, you know, and it seems readily
available on Google images and videos and well, here's the movie is rated PG. I watched it in high
school with my class, you know, like it's not it's not a super provocative film. But if the filming
conditions were fucked up, they were fucked up. It's just like, don't talk for years about how much
you loved it and owned it. That's not going to help your case is all I'm a little strange. Yeah.
Anyway, um, go ahead. What do you got? Well, what do you got? Well, I'll, I'll, we, I'll do two,
two, two. But I'll do two TV shows. I want to talk about another really good show that I don't feel
is getting enough love. And it just ended. It is called Fleischmann is in trouble. Mm -hmm.
It is on FX and Hulu, which I guess are the same now, which is so disturbing to me that FX,
the, the edgy like groundbreaking network that brought us to shield and all these shows that
like created a whole new world of television is now owned by Disney and then still trying to pretend
that there is rough and edgy as they always were. It's like, but wait, so then five, but it's
funny enough mentioning Fox news isn't Fox the owner of FX, Fox, you have a Disney's the owner
of Fox. So Disney owns Fox. So that's why that's why Disney ESPN and Hulu come as a bundle. They're all
just they are a bundle. It's I mean, this is, you can't, there you go. There you go. You got to,
if you want to boycott one, you got to boycott all of it now. Yeah, no, you know, I hate Elon Musk,
but it's like you want to get mad about him. It's like, well, look up the ladder of everything you
do and you're not going to like what you see, frankly, but it's, that's getting worse and worse and
worse. Anyway, yes. Anyway, Flashman himself is an actor that I generally like, but can annoy me,
Jesse Eisenberg. I think outside of social network, he's never been better than in this. So
wild performance from him. He's like naked a lot, not dick, but like very naked otherwise a lot.
He's very vulnerable. He cries a lot. He's amazing in it. He really is a great actor.
It gave me a new respect for him. The story is this. Jesse Eisenberg is semi happily married to
Claire Danes, who was an actor I've always loved as well, home one in my so -called life, home for
the holidays, etc. One day she walks out on him and his children or him and their children. No
explanation. She's just gone. So they wind up getting a divorce that he finds out that like she's
in town. She's like just like sitting in a park. She's just not coming home anymore. So he's kind of
grown. This obviously the show hit me on kind of a personal level, but I think it would hit pretty much
anybody. It's very funny, very heartfelt, very emotional at times. There's a lot of him getting on
the apps for the first time, which is something I'm doing now. So there was a lot of humor in that. I
really related to that stuff. And the vibe of it just felt very funny and real. It's also Lizzie
Kaplan and Adam Brody, who are two actors. I always love and everything, but they play like
the best friend characters and they're both really funny in this. And it was directed by Jonathan
Dayton and Valerie Ferris, who did Little Miss Sunshine. And it was also directed by Polchini and
Burman, who did the great American splendor that we talk about on this show all the time. And when I
saw that, I was like, well, no wonder it feels like one of those great early 2000s Indies
It's an eight -part limited series. So it's you don't have to wait for season two or anything. It
tells a self -contained story. But I absolutely loved it. I thought it was great. Check it out.
Flashman isn't trouble. Excuse me. And I'm sorry. By the way, Lizzie Kaplan does these monologues
throughout that are really funny. And at one point, she's taking her family to Disney World and she talks,
she immediately starts changing the narration and talking about how we can't show you any of this
footage from our trip to Disney World because halfway through production, this show was bought by a massive
company that we also can't name. Like she talks about it on the show. I don't know how they got
away with it, but it seemed like Disney wouldn't let them air stuff. So they're already censoring their
shows. And they must have struck some deal where they were like, at least let us comment on the
censorship if you're going to miss Disney is our absolute rotten dog shit. And you know, keep going
to see the fucking Thor movies, everybody. Like it's all just a gas. And then wonder why
that's not directed at the audience. We have good people in this audience. Yeah, good people. Yeah,
good people. Anyway, I went off on somebody on the Patreon. That's the other day. And I'm not
here to apologize. Sometimes I get on there and I'm like, God damn it. And I blow off some steam.
And that's just how I feel. I saw the eat me was my favorite part of it.
A well -placed eat me always makes me laugh. My other Christmas watch with last of the season was
Christmas evil. It was formerly titled Better Watch Out. It's a movie from 1970 something about a kid
who witnesses Santa Claus eating his mother's box basically under the Christmas tree.
And then grows up to be obsessed with Santa Claus, wants to be Santa Claus,
turns himself into Santa Claus with the intention. But all the while watching all the boys and girls
in the neighborhood, not in a perverted way, but in a way of marking off who's naughty and nice,
keeps records, all the stuff physically turns himself into Santa Claus on Christmas,
delivers toys to children. And then of course, things go awry when people don't take him or insulting
to him or act naughty as he puts it. And he ends up killing as well. I enjoyed this movie very much.
I thought it was a very, very art house kind of approach to this type of movie. It's been referred
to as the taxi driver of Santa Claus movies. I agree. It's a man melting down. And the main character
whose name, the actor's name is escaping me at the moment. I looked him up because I was like,
this guy's fucking great. Who is he? Ready for this? He's ready for this, folks? Hold on a second.
I want to say his name. Hold on. Give me a second.
1980 Hart, so the Brandon Magart is his name. He's Fiona Apple's dad. Yep. I must have
watched it with Joe Bob because I knew that anyway. Oh, Frank Stoller is also in this. So I'm a big fan
of Frank Stoller's the character's name. Joe, I think Joe Jamrock. Is that him? The guy that's from,
you know, he's in a lot of the Stephen King. No, I'm sorry. Jeffrey Dimon is in it. He's in a lot
of the Stephen King adaptations like the mist and storm of the century. I like this movie quite a bit.
All right, all right, folks. Let's get to the film at hand. Another Christmas Santa type deal
called Violent Night. Stars David Harbor from Stranger Things. The guy who plays the big old sheriff.
We open with a very bad Santa feeling scene where it's Santa complaining about having to do the rounds
and this and you know, and there's another Santa at the end of the bar from the mall and he's like,
oh, I hear you. But little by little you reveal this is actually the real Santa Claus and he's kind
of depressed and he's a big drinker and etc. So this year, he winds up going to a house. The house
is clearly inspired by like knives out. There are, it's so clear what went into this pitch was just like
six movies in a blender. Home alone, die hard, knives out, bad Santa. And that's what it feels like.
Just sort of a regurgitated version of those movies die hard. But that's what happens. He gets locked in
with this snooty capitalist family and these terrorists come in and they're going to steal money from
the house. The family matriarch is Beverly D 'Angelo from Christmas vacation. And then Santa basically
fights the terrorists. So it's basically die hard with Santa Claus as John McClain. And for an hour
than the back half of the movie is Santa beating the ship out of henchmen until he gets to the big boss
John like Wasamo at the end. And there's a lot of wisecracks, a lot of Santa style 80s wisecracks that
don't really hit comedy doesn't really work. The action is sort of fun at times, but never never
cool in a John Wickway where you're really like pumped or anything. It's just kind of there.
And to me, the story didn't really work either. I didn't care about this family because you're
really not given much reason to care about them. They're awful people. Yeah, it's
yeah, I don't really understand where you're supposed to go with this thing. Like, you know, there
are three redeeming characters in the family, which is the core, you know, the estranged husband and
wife and their daughter, those are the three redeeming family characters. Everybody else in the
year like who gives a shit, they're terrible people. Otherwise, I said, so I get that to an extent.
It's just not very well done. But also when you do that, and that's the only direction you do it in,
you don't care when anybody dies. Like, and it's nice to care about a character getting killed in a
movie like this. It's it gives it some emotional depth. But I agree. It felt really like a graphic
novel. I don't think it started that way, but it felt like a graphic novel. I felt that this
started with a guy watching Die Hard and saying, wouldn't it be cool if it was Santa Claus fighting
the terrorists? Yeah. And then from there, they said, well, what if we just did every, you know, as
they flesh it out and add characters, what if we just did a take off or a send up of every Christmas
movie ever? And you named all of them that they that they do send up. But and the big but is
those movies are sort of weird takes on Christmas movies. So now you're doing your own take
on Christmas movies that are doing their own take on Christmas and then it just starts to feel to
me like borrowed material and not like, you know, it's not like it's, if he was spoofing,
if there were elements of its own wonderful life in here, it would be very different than having
elements of home alone. By the way, we've the home alone thing. It's just been again, another thing
that's just been done to death from fucking Rambo to whoever it's thought enough. Apocalypse is
is a brilliant movie. I think it's it's Mel Gibson directed it unfortunately, but it is one of
the coolest action movies of my life, I feel like. And it turns into at the end, Native American Home
Alone. It's like, that's what it is. There's that James Bond movie, I believe Quantum of Solace
that ends as home alone. And who we equalize or two. The equalize or two is home alone. Yeah.
It is, it will always for many years, it was my favorite movie when I was a little kid. It came
out when I was Kevin McAllister's age. It was like a dream movie. So it's still one of my favorites.
But who would have thought it would be so influential on on action movies? It's really weird.
The traps. I mean, just grown men setting traps. The beauty of home alone is that's what a kid would do.
Set traps. Yeah. And look, it is a kid in this one that sets traps, right? Okay, yes.
So at least it's a kid and not so vest just alone. Well, Santa's setting traps too by the end.
Does he said traps by the end? Well, we learn he might not eat. There's a trap or two probably,
but we learned that Santa was a Viking warrior. And they go into this kind of flashback of him as
this guy who used a hammer to crush skulls. Yeah. And through over time he evolved into the Santa
clause that we know and love. So, well, let me, let me just cut you off. The, the insinuation,
and they never fully explained it, but the insinuation is is that he was such a bad,
awful, violent man. Right. And his penance was becoming the most wonderful, loving, benevolent person
of all time. Right. You know what I mean? Yes. So, which is interesting, you know, and it is,
it is a cool way to justify like, well, why the fuck does Santa Claus know how to kill people? Yeah,
and all that stuff. It's interesting. There are elements to this that are interesting. It just
doesn't really hit. Now, I said to you, as we walked out of the theater, they're going to make
a sequel. He mentions the elves at the end. There's going to be a sequel. It's going to be
else. Sure enough, I read online. There is a sequel in the works with the elf that will feature
Mrs. Clause and the elves. And they're trying to get Charlie's there on to play Mrs. Clause. And
they'll get her problem. But you know, man, like it just none of this really, it doesn't not work.
It just doesn't work enough that you care. Like, it's one of these movies you watch it.
The whole time you're just sort of bored. Yeah. You don't feel the new and I saw it together in
Florida with nothing else to do. And still it was kind of like, boy, I'd rather be doing something
else about halfway through it. It was getting very dull and repetitive. It's too long. Like everything.
I wasn't so mad that I felt like I got to walk out of this. You know, it wasn't like a slug.
But we also didn't go back in for the end credits, which tells you something. If you hear
an end credits bit start and you don't care, that means the movie probably wasn't very good.
Yeah, that's a that's a good telltale sign. I just, I just, yeah. And then the second it was over,
I was just like, I barely even remember what I just watched. I just don't give a shit. It's shot
like a TV commercial, like a hallmark commercial sort of. And that's about the emotional impact that
it has. The action every, you know, it just never to me was as cool as so many other movies,
like John Wick and stuff. That this stuff has been done so much better. That when you see it,
it's kind of like, okay, but I get why people would like it. I get why you'd want to make it into
this cult movie because that's what it's trying to be. But to me, any movie trying to be that
will never be that because you can smell that coming a mile away. So I don't know, it didn't involve me
in any way. It wears its influences on its sleeve. And that's kind of charming, I guess, but it just
didn't hold my interest. Yeah. I don't know. I guess I sort of am interested to see what the sequel would
look like. Can't believe there hasn't been a movie called Violin Night up to this point.
There has to have been there. Did you look it up?
There has to have been. I don't think so. Well, I mean, all it's going to show me now is this. But
yeah, I think that's it. It's the first one. Now there's, you know, maybe Silent Night Deadly Night,
maybe they did a Silent Night, Violin Night, the should of. How did they miss it? But sometimes
they just missed these things. Yeah. God. I don't know. I guess it's like painfully down. It's just
not at all. Not at all. There's a charm to it. You know, it's a hard movie to hate. It's kind of like
a fun puppy running up at you. And maybe this sequel will take it in a more interesting direction.
My hog is, you know, hogs in a normal spot. Let's just say that. Yeah. I'm wearing a pair of jeans.
I'm waiting for the bus. People like what they see, but I'm not, you know, bulging it up.
Bulging it. Yeah. Well, that's our show. Joderosa Comedy on Instagram and Twitter. I'll be
at Austin, Texas at the Vulcan 4 shows Friday the 13th, strangely enough. And Saturday the 14th
of this month, that's just next week. I hope to see you there. Please come out and see me.
I will also be at the following weekend in Levittown, New York at Governors. And we have announced
officially the residency of this new hour I'm doing. I never promised you a Rose Garden at the
Crane Theater here in New York City. We're doing those once a month. Next one is January 25th.
You can get tickets and info about all of this and other shows, which there are a ton coming up
between festivals and other cities and what have you throughout the new year at joderosainfo .com.
And Joey Roses, Delhi, or sorry, sandwich shop in bar, open seven days a week now at 11 .30 a .m.
Every day, Joey Roses NYC .com for all that info. Check it out.
The Patrick Walsh, occasionally rarely Instagram and Twitter, our next project we will be discussing
is called, what is it, Joe? The banshees of Inesheran. The banshees of Inesheran, I believe it's for now.
Inesheran, Inesheran. I don't know. Anyway, that's up next.
We'll see you next time, folks. We'll see you in hell.