Hey everybody, welcome to We'll See You in Hell of Life!
I just realized, does The We'll See You and How Thames Sample Push It by Salt and Peppa?
No, that is an original composition by me.
But inspired by Salt and Peppa.
I can't think of much of my life that isn't inspired by Salt and Peppa.
You took at least a sprinkle of Salt and Peppa.
Folks.
Little seasoning on the steak?
Right, yeah, sure.
I feel honestly, I was pretty influenced by Salt and Peppa as well.
The hot 9 at 9 was a nightly countdown in St. Louis.
And Shoop was number one for nine months, probably.
Then replaced briefly by Bex loser.
Then immediately obliterated by what a man Salt and Peppa.
They dominated the charts for about a year.
Yes.
Now, I've caught you many times when I'll come over to your place to meet you before night on the town.
Right.
Dancing in your underwear, too, Shoop.
By yourself.
Well, let me bring you back to the subject.
Peppa's gonna set.
Make you get hot, make you work up a sweat.
When you say, to Maloo, my darling, not fall in.
In love, but I'm falling for you.
Want to get shot?
Bet you might not let you a best under pressure.
I don't know the lyrics.
But...
Thank you.
I don't know the lyrics, but I will say this.
You do when I come over and I say, can we just...
Can we act out Shoop together, Pat?
You will insist that you get to be Peppa every time.
That's true.
I'd like to be Peppa once in a while.
Our buddy, Vince Averl, is usually Spenderella.
Yes.
There's no alcohol in this.
I know.
I need you to rectify that.
I was monitoring you and judging you backstage
and put a fucking diet coke and put lime in it,
like some kind of communist...
Uh -huh.
It was Coke Zero.
But fine.
Folks, how was...
How was everybody?
Who was at the last show?
That's awesome.
She was a bargain.
You got two for...
Well, two for a little more than one, I think.
Who was not at the last show?
Oh, wow.
So you're all just at both shows.
That's awesome.
But literally nobody?
That's great.
All right, well then we really have to make this...
sing just as much as the last one.
And I think the key is in that bottle right there.
I do have one request.
Could we get rickety your chairs?
Louder?
Rickety your chairs?
Feel like the goddamn tin man up here, folks.
You're doing a...
You really slipped into a sign felt just then.
Can we get rickety your chairs?
Sure.
I mean, good to chairs.
Be any rick...
Oh, that's Chandler, I guess.
Chinon, Chanandler, Bong.
I remember that was on his TV guide.
Look, friends is nowhere near a sign felt,
but we can't deny it had some great bits over the years.
What was your favorite bit?
Actually, I really only like Chandler and Phoebe,
and the rest of them can go to hell.
My favorite bit on friends was when,
remember when they did the flashbacks,
Ramanica was fat.
Yeah.
Not really appropriate now.
And they'd all make fun of her.
Yeah.
How many cameras are on you right now?
And my favorite bit is after they'd all make fun of her,
she would go,
jokes on you,
I'm dying from type 2 diabetes.
I didn't see that episode.
That was called the one with the type 2 diabetes.
Yeah.
Which by the way, they took from Frazier.
The one with the, that was Frazier's thing.
The one where Sam comes back.
The one where Diane comes back.
Friends just fucking jacked it, man.
Or did Frazier jack it?
I don't think Frazier jacked friends.
I don't think so either.
No.
Did I?
Well, look.
I'm never going to meet Kelsey Grammar.
Do I ever tell you?
Don't tell this.
I think they want to hear this.
Don't do not tell this story.
Do not.
Do not stop it.
Do not tell this story.
Trust me.
Because we're going to go backstage after you go,
we should probably cut that Kelsey Grammar.
Look, maybe we'll cut it.
These people flew to be here and I'm telling them
this fucking story.
Hold on.
As you all cheer, I have to fucking cut it.
He doesn't fucking cut it.
Right.
He thinks you look at the MP3 and go, cut that.
And it just happens.
I have to sit and cut the fucking thing out.
I don't have time during the day between my viewings
of golden girls and perfect strangers reruns.
I was going to say, folks, the man's got time.
The man's got a time.
You hurt me.
Joe's like, can you hang out tonight?
Well, I mean, I got a show at 11 p .m.
Okay.
I'm already 16 hours today, but all right.
So the story is, and I won't tell you who told me the story.
That'll protect him.
There's a guy who worked a lot on the set of cheers.
And Kelsey is very open about this.
I call him Kelsey.
Kelsey Grammer.
Very open that he would just be black out drunk
and doesn't remember episodes of cheers, including the finale.
He has no recollection of it.
He had a cocaine habit and et cetera.
This is all stuff he says in public.
I'm not telling you anything new.
But they said, oh, Kelsey's not out here yet.
Where is he?
This is something actors start to do once a show is successful.
It's like, they won't want to be the first one on stage
because it makes them look like the lowest class.
So they all sit in their trailers.
And like, oh, is he out there yet?
Is she out there yet?
It's really shitty behavior, but that's the town we live in
and the business we've chosen.
But Kelsey Grammer.
They're like, where is it?
We're all ready to start the scene.
Where is Kelsey?
And there's this young female PA.
And they're like, can you go back and get Kelsey?
And she comes out and she's like, I knocked on the door.
He didn't answer.
And they go, he's in there, though.
He's passed out or something.
You're going to have to go into the room.
She goes back, she opens the door.
This Kelsey Grammer completely passed out drunk.
She's undershirt up over his head like so.
And the after effects of masturbation across his chest and stomach.
I'm not cutting it.
That's all right.
I'm going to say that.
I'm going to work with Kelsey Grammer.
Now when she pulled the shirt from over his head,
did he go, really niles?
Did he wake up and do that?
Yeah.
And I don't know what to do with those tosses.
Now it's it and come on my stomach.
Oh, yeah.
I'm coming again.
Good night.
By all accounts, a true story, folks.
It's not like it's humiliating for him, of course,
but it's not like he lunged at this poor girl.
He was passed out.
And that's a humiliating story.
But he comes off, OK.
Who amongst us?
There used to be a TV show on TV land.
It was called TV Land Confidential.
Do you guys remember that show?
No.
It was like the eat true Hollywood story of old sift coms.
Right.
And they would do two per episode.
The best episode ever saw was cheers and livern and cheerly.
And the cheers one was Kelsey Grammer hated the cast so much
that he would not bathe for days and just stink.
Like just smell like shit around them to annoy them
because they had to be near him.
And he got so drunk and coped up that he doesn't remember shooting
the finale, which is amazing.
And then the livern and cheerly would was basically they were like,
they fucked everybody on set.
Squiggy.
Plenty.
Yeah.
I've never seen livern and cheerly.
I've only seen the Wandsworld one parody.
I'm talking about Wandsworld a lot.
But that was the parody of the opening credits.
And I remember my dad going,
that's livern and cheerly.
I also remember my dad standing up and cheering and applauding
when they passed White Castle in Wandsworld in the theater, folks.
Woo!
A cheering White Castle.
It was humiliating.
I've never said this to you before.
Yeah.
You come from trash.
No question.
Not my lovely mother, but yes.
I like your dad.
I had fun with him at the wedding.
Well, one of us did.
I feel safe talking about him on here because he'd have to pay to hear it.
So that's not going to happen.
He'd also have to support something that I did.
Folks.
That's my problem.
Don't feel bad for me.
I'm dealing with it.
I go to therapy two to three times a year.
I always leave therapy by telling her,
nice try.
You gave it your all.
Very good.
She said, my therapist, if I never said, I probably said this too,
but very memorable exchange I had with her.
I said, you know, in the department, they say,
the Irish are the only people who are impervious to therapy.
It does not work on them.
I said, do you think that that's true?
She thought about it for a very long time.
She goes, no, I don't think that's true.
I do think you are impervious to therapy.
And I think she's right.
I recently fired my therapist because I saw her in the T -Mobile store.
This is a true story.
I ran into my therapist in the T -Mobile store and I said,
you're fired.
You should be doing better than I am if you're going to give me advice every week.
Get the fuck out of here.
Is T -Mobile a lower class?
It's the lowest class.
It's above grasshopper or whatever the fuck that thing is called.
Cricket wirelands.
Cricket, yeah.
Yeah.
T -Mobile, I might as well string two cans together.
Folks.
Yeah.
Speaking of cans.
I got dumped the other day.
Throwing out on my can.
Yeah.
Yeah, I got dumped.
I know.
Walkers threw it.
Let me be honest.
And I have AT &T.
I have Verizon now.
Okay.
They upgraded.
They're all great therapists in there.
Just great companies.
Oh, shit.
I love the fact that once every couple of weeks,
I'll get to use my phone as a telephone.
Right.
You know, it will work somewhere where I need to make a call and I don't have to walk
six miles off into the sun so I can use it.
You about to launch into a text messaging bit.
No.
I have a phone in my hand.
I can just never call anyone when I need to call them.
If I needed a camera, I would have went to the camera shop.
Something like that.
Something different than that, but yes.
Something a lot different than that, but yes.
Hey, by the way, by the buy.
We weren't really moving these gifts at the last show.
And Emily pointed out that we have sharpies here,
so if you got one, we'll sign it.
I thought no one would give a shit.
But if you do, then we'll sign whatever you get from us, if you want.
And we'll sign the new ones for this show.
Right.
We have more to give to you.
Also, before I forget, I'd love to thank the gentleman who did the artwork for this show.
Mr. Will Potor.
I could just stand up.
Absolutely.
Will, where are you?
Stand up, Will.
Yes.
Will, there's all our posters and everything.
And Brandon Gas, where are you?
Brandon, did the poster for the show today?
Thank you, my friends.
Brandon Gas does the awesome...
One more?
The funco type people as well.
Benjamin Tahia also, please stand up, who's sent some of our...
Thank you, Ben.
That's some of our stuff.
Guys, Bert.
Yes.
We can't believe that people put more time into this than we do.
And we thank you for it.
It's really...
No, it's in Cret's touching.
Yeah, Brandon had the funco figures where I was in the Orco costume from...
My first Halloween costume when I was five.
He man's shit sidekick Orco.
And then Joe was Freddy Krueger.
Those were very cool.
We love all your guys' work.
Will, you look like Doc Holiday and I appreciate that.
Pre -consumption, Doc Holiday.
Healthy.
And I couldn't see you, sir, but I will see you later.
That's the meat and drink.
Yes.
Shall I take us to Pat's?
Actually...
Did you realize how you just glazed over me getting dumped?
You just don't give a shit.
Didn't go anywhere with it.
You said what happened.
I started telling you to go before I forget.
Let me thank the artists.
That is how...
That is how it happened.
Yes.
Alright, continue.
It's alright.
I got dumped!
But walk us through.
She said our schedules didn't line up enough.
It seemed like if she liked us, she would have made the schedules work.
That's what I said to her.
I said, you know, if you gave a shit, you'd make it work.
You don't need her.
I said, you know, you've always had a lack of effort, no spirit.
No, I'm kidding.
I didn't say that.
I'm just kidding.
Joe, what do you need a woman for when you got me?
Patty?
Last night we had a lovely Italian dinner.
Listen, we had the loudest fucking bitches next to us.
Just screeching and screaming.
I love you, you're all I need.
I'm tired of sharing you with that succubus that you put a ring on.
Folks, that succubus is right here.
Miss Heather Anna.
I'm kidding, Heather, of course, obviously.
No, everyone loves Heather.
It's annoying.
I burped really loudly and close to Heather's face backstage.
And I went, hey, sorry about that.
That was very rude.
She goes, I'm disgusting.
So I thought I'd get a bit more.
It was funny, she was saying don't worry about burping.
Yeah, I was saying don't care.
Who cares?
Pat?
Why don't you take us to?
You didn't talk about the dumb.
Can we peel back the onion a bit?
What's going on in here?
Pat, she couldn't figure it out.
Yeah, and that's why she's gone.
Do you think it was that you are too closed off emotionally?
I won't open up a problem.
What the fuck is that supposed to mean?
Do you think it's the barely suppressed rage?
No, I really think it was our schedules.
Do you think it's the fact?
I think they agree.
Could it have been that you've been carrying around a 1 .75
leader bottle of Jack Daniels?
I'm just spitballing.
I don't know.
Look, Joe, you're...
I think it might be related to...
I was telling her the day before she dumped me.
I was telling her that a friend of mine was saying
I think I might need to get a gun.
He might need to.
Yeah.
Because they're having some issues and I go,
yeah, get a fucking gun, dude.
Get a gun to protect himself from his...
Like from intruders.
I was like, yeah, get a fucking gun.
Get a fucking gun.
And I...
Listen, I'm just telling you what he was telling me.
It's in the news, right?
My advice to him was, yeah, if you think somebody's going to break in your house,
get a goddamn gun.
That was my advice to him.
And I...
All guns aren't bad.
Some of the guns are okay.
I'm anti -gun, Joe.
You know what I...
Oh, well good for you.
I keep under my pillow a little bottle of silly string.
And if somebody comes in just...
You know, I blind them with it,
and then I hit them with like a sheet and push them out the door.
This has happened three, four times.
No casualties.
I do this.
They come in.
I lock my...
My hand to their eyes like this.
I go and I do the three stooges thing.
Down to their head, repeatedly knocks on the floor.
Then they go unconscious.
No, I go, yeah, get a gun if you think.
You know, I got no people there.
So I was telling her the story.
Yeah, I don't know.
Like I told them to get it.
And she was like, eh, I don't know how I feel about that.
And I was like, well, you know, I don't have a gun.
I'm not going to get a gun.
Yeah.
She's like, would you?
And I was like, well, no.
I was like, listen, somebody has been snooping around my balcony at night,
which is weird.
Maybe I'll just keep a big knife under my bed.
And she went, oh.
I'll see now.
We're getting into some reasons.
And I didn't think that was weird till we went to see last night
the new Halloween.
I was like, oh, yeah, knives are weird.
The idea of a kitchen.
They caught and they kill you.
I've had, look, I've had crazy people like come on to my property.
It's fucking scary, dude.
Sure.
So I don't know what to do.
I can't fight.
You know what I mean?
And then you tell that you call the cops.
They can't help you.
And what about in the new Halloween picture when the kids got the gun
and then the nice psychiatrist comes out and he's like, don't shoot.
And he shoots him in the stomach.
That wouldn't have happened.
It's a nine year old boy.
Right.
On a bus of escaped mental patients in that sea.
A little bit different than an intruder coming into my apartment
where I'm the only one there.
You're the only one in the mental patient there.
Yeah, there is.
There's no psychiatrist in my apartment that I might shoot by accident.
That's true.
Unless he's the one breaking in.
I don't have a gun, people.
That's not the point of this.
Yeah.
But I thought maybe that freaked her out.
I don't know.
It could have been any number of a thousand things.
But maybe because I'm surrounded by video game consoles.
That might be it.
Yeah.
I tell you folks, when I'm over there, I put myself in the shoes of a young lady.
And I'm frightened.
It's all video games and like bloody horror shit on the walls.
And then like the occasional golden girls figurine.
So I have.
I have a lot of mixed signals over there.
I have a painting of a horrifying clown next to my bed
that stares at you while you sleep.
I don't think girls like that.
I find it comforting for some reason.
She's commented on it several times.
Right.
I didn't take it down.
Heather, if I had a horrifying clown painting next to our bed
when we first made tender love.
Would we be married today?
See, a little sweetness tonight for you.
Thank you.
Thank you, Heather.
I have a grim reaper painting behind my couch.
Yes.
Hey, listen sister.
You can't take the heat.
Get out of Joe's kitchen.
That's what I say.
Fair enough.
Let me have my interest.
I have hobbies.
Some of it is collecting morbid paintings, you know.
I am so grateful to not be dating.
Just what a nightmare.
And in LA just quadruply so.
Oh, this town is awful.
Terrible.
Yeah.
It's the worst place to date on planet Earth.
I don't know if any of you have tried it.
But it's like dating your Nana.
Except she wants to be famous too.
It's fucking horrible.
Famous I got, but walk me through Nana.
Because everything is precious and offensive.
Oh dear.
I don't speak that way.
By the way, can you introduce me to Weinstein's brother?
I want to get assaulted.
No, the brother.
You think he's innocent as well?
I don't know, Pat.
I'm not here to tell Bob Weinstein to do what he did.
It was merely...
Marilyn Maxlake, just a thought and passion.
All right, fun.
He ran with it.
Thank you, the only man who left it, Marilyn Maxlake.
You are right.
And everyone else is wrong.
I don't have my paper with my movie corner movie.
So I have to briefly look at my phone.
But I would like to take this, if I may, to Pat's movie corner.
But first, I'm about to take this there.
But I would also like to get on with the show.
And at the same time, on...
...with a jaw, we're halfway there.
Joe, living on a prayer.
I had never done it.
I thought I had done it.
I'd never done it.
I would remember that.
You did it.
No, I never did it.
Not with that passion.
I'll tell you that.
It's not a dry seat in the house.
Oh, God.
Stop it.
Fellas too.
I watched The Wife with The Wife.
It was an Academy Award screener, starring Glenn Close and Jonathan Price.
And the story is about a famous writer whose...
Yeah, it's real boring.
So they send...
If you're in the writer's guild, they send you Academy Award screeners.
Which is the best part of the job.
Especially now that Joe and I have decided to be quarantined in our homes.
And not leave.
So you don't have to go out of the house.
They send you movies.
The wife...
They're getting real stingy.
This one, I was like, I can't even know what this is.
Jonathan Price, who's the guy from Glengarig, Glenn Ross.
The staff.
Yeah.
And he...
Mr. James Link.
Yes.
I thought that yesterday.
He...
That's from the movie, like, World Famous author.
And he wins the Pulitzer Prize for a book that he wrote.
And then, little by little, you learn that Glenn Close, his wife,
really did the bulk of the writing.
So it's a serious version of funny farm.
That's exactly right.
The serious farm.
The people that got that really got it.
I love farm.
Funny farm is one of Chevy Chase's best.
And not enough people have seen it.
Folks.
The wife is...
It's like kind of an interesting story.
You can see where that would be interesting.
It's not based on a true story.
Somebody's made this up.
But Glenn Close, as always, looks like George Washington.
I think I joke I got on always sunny 10 years ago.
And Jonathan Price always looks like Abe Lincoln.
That's right.
Coincidentally.
Yeah.
So this movie is like about their kind of loveless, terrible marriage,
and all the jealousy within it.
There are scenes where, like, they'll cut to Glenn Close,
and she's literally doing acting like this.
Like, whoa.
It's just, like, hammy in spots.
The guy playing their son is really embarrassing, I thought.
But it's sort of an entertaining story.
I just was very bored by it.
And...
I can't imagine watching it.
This description is fucking awful.
Yeah.
This sounds like the worst movie.
I have the screener, and I thought, I don't want me to keep it.
Maybe this is good, but it doesn't sound good.
By the way, it opens with, and I'm not kidding.
I want to stress that I am not kidding.
It opens with a five -minute sequence.
Holy God.
That's a...
That's a hellion right there, folks.
That's how we start most of our podcast.
It opens with a five -minute sequence
of Jonathan Price aggressively fingering Glenn Close.
And I want to stress yet again that I am not joking.
So like...
Now I want to see it.
Like, all these art house people going out,
like, my dad texted me.
I saw the wife, whatever.
Just, why would you start it this way?
There are a couple with no...
They have this loveless, terrible marriage.
Why do we need to see them fingering each other?
It baffled me.
I've never been a fan of gratuitous sex scenes in movies.
I am, but not when they involve Glenn Close.
I don't.
I'm Jonathan Price.
I don't like them.
I love Glenn Close the actress.
It's just like...
You know, I don't want to see her get fingered.
Is that so wrong?
I'm not a fan.
I just feel like movies seldomly need a gratuitous sex scene.
I don't feel like I ever agree with you there.
I don't know, like, before the devil knows you're dead,
it opens with fucking fat -filled seemer -hopping.
I don't want to see this at the top of the movie.
That's what makes me not be able to show it to my parents.
That's a great movie.
But Philip Simmerhoff and Emerson Toe made
cancel each other out so it says,
though, you saw nothing.
She is so hot and he's so not hot that it says,
though, you did not watch any sex.
In my opinion.
I agree.
They cancel each other out.
But that is a big ol' white ass RIP.
RIP PSH.
Great actor.
Don't get me wrong.
I've told the Grants -Rain on story.
I watched Blum House's first entry
into their new anthology television series
on Hulu exclusively, called Into the Dark.
I never know what you watch.
I always want to get on board with you
and I don't know what you're talking about.
You think anybody watched the fucking wife?
This is a deeper cut than the wife.
At least this is on genre, you know what I mean?
Blum House is a new anthology series
called The Into the Dark on Hulu.
Has anybody seen it?
Good.
Don't waste your fucking time.
This thing is a pile of shit.
The first episode is called The Body.
I'm just going to go out and say this on right now.
Blum House is done.
More like a done house.
Oh.
It's done, dude.
This thing is so fucking bad.
They're doing that.
We saw two trailers last night that said
from the studio that brought you,
which is like, you know, she's got a great personality, basically.
Like from the studio that brought you,
it's like, who gives her shit?
But Blum House thinks that they can say that.
This thing, so it's about a serial killer
who kills his latest victim,
or Hitman, excuse me, who kills his latest victim
on Halloween night.
And right off the bat, he's on the phone
being like, the job is done.
And his, you know, guy, whatever the fuck, you know.
And Big E was bullshit guy that paid him to do it.
On the other end, the phone goes,
I know you've got a flair for doing what you want.
But for once, could you treat this job professionally?
Like, oh, here we go.
All right.
And he's going to fuck the job up,
because he's got a flair for the theatrical, whatever.
So of course, he drags the body out into the street,
because it's Halloween, and he's going to get away with it.
And then he goes to a party with the dead body
that is hosted by the kid that plays Pablo
on Ash vs. Evil Dead,
who I was a fan of, and now I hate him.
He is so annoying in this fucking thing.
It's just terrible, and it just goes on and on.
And it's every dumb cliche.
He meets a girl that's obsessed with the serial killer.
He meets a girl that's obsessed with the party.
And he doesn't get why she's obsessed with them.
And then she realizes he's a killer.
And then, oh, she wants to be a killer too.
You know what I mean?
It's just every stupid fucking cliche.
And I'm not this mad at it because I was almost had a part in it,
and I didn't get it.
And the truth slides out.
But it's just not good.
It's just not good.
And then the next episode apparently
is going to be April Fool's Day,
because each one of these is going to be based on a holiday,
which has already been done in the movie holidays,
which is an anthology horror film.
The next episode is supposed to be April Fool's Day.
What do you think that's going to be about?
Could it be about pranks going too far?
And we don't know if this is a prank or not anymore!
Oh, what a pile of shit.
You know, I lost Faith in Blumhouse.
I'm sorry.
And our movie today is From Blumhouse, Halloween 2018.
And we'll get to that.
But I was very, very disappointed in this.
They may get out for Christ's sakes.
They should be doing better.
The studio doesn't have to make every movie a studio makes.
It's going to be good.
Some of them should be good.
They also made in City as the last key.
Right.
They made Truth or Dare,
which is absurd looking.
Right.
But he didn't see it.
Do you think that movie's good?
I have no clue,
but I wouldn't say it.
It's not having seen it.
It's eye -donsane.
Oh, come on, Pat.
Come on.
You know, one April Fool's Day,
I was about 10 years old,
and I loosened the salt shaker on my table.
And my dad dumped it on his thing
and all the salt fell out onto it.
And he was so angry that he was trembling.
And he pulled me into my room and shut the door
and went into this like 30 -minute lecture
about the danger of pranks
and how nobody likes them
and their cruel and mean
because he felt a little embarrassed.
I once on April Fool's Day put a cellophane
over the toilet.
Oh, you told us on the show, yes.
I might have told mine on the show too.
Yeah, and my mom called me at my friend's house,
screaming that I'd better get my fucking ass home,
yeah, immediately.
So I can only imagine she pissed her shit all over the floor
from the cellophane prank.
She was real mad.
I just, I never liked pranks.
Maybe it was this traumatic experience early on,
but like when there always like Clooney loves pranks on the set,
I'm like, well, then I don't want to work with him.
You're not going to.
And he's not worried.
He's knocking my door down.
It's like, pal, we're doing good night and good luck too.
As a, as a Balticam.
Exactly.
I love George Clooney.
I hope he's well.
Wife seems cool.
It's a Europe.
What's your next one?
Europe.
It's a, uh, yes.
I saw the land of steady habits.
You, you, you, you shit on my selection,
which is a blunt house horror release.
Well, this is also a four -year consideration picture.
It's on Netflix.
And it was written and directed by Nicole Holliff's set owner.
Oh, wow.
Who was one of my favorites?
Better rush out and see that immediately.
I did.
Who was that?
It's got bet.
Nicole Holliff's set owner did enough said,
which was my favorite movie the past several years.
Never heard of it.
Gandalfanian.
Oh, I love that movie.
I really like that movie.
Oh, that's such a sad movie.
I love that movie.
That's one of my favorite movies of recent years.
I thought it was a very special movie.
The only really, uh, you know, valid Gandalfanian
other than Truro Manson's sopranos, of course.
I love it.
The sopranos is debatable.
Never, never really watched.
But, uh, it stars Ben Mendelson as like a fuckup
who's like always getting high with kids.
And then one of the kids dies.
Uh, Eddie Falco is in it,
uh, playing his like long suffering ex -wife,
also from the sopranos.
So is he just, is this lady just going to go through
the sopranos cast film by film?
I think so.
Next one I'll have Uncle Junior in it.
Uncle June.
There's like 113 years old.
The ghost of Uncle June will make an appearance.
But, um, it's, uh, I really love her.
And I love that she, like, looks into care.
Like I feel like her characters all feel very real to me.
This one, you just, it's impossible to like the guy
and not in any kind of fun way.
Uh, the stuff I liked about it was
it was talking about like the awkwardness of sex,
post divorce.
Some of that felt very truthful, I guess.
There were scenes I liked.
But a lot of any movies have just kind of been replaced
by television shows.
Because even all comedy and dramas,
all these things have gone to television now.
So it felt a little familiar to me
and for somebody whose work I've always liked very much.
All right.
So don't check it out.
It's fine.
All right.
And the title, like I just had to look it up
and now I've forgotten it again.
It's the worst title, like the land of steady habits.
What the heck?
Like that sounds like the most boring movie of all time.
Last night we were watching Halloween 2018.
The trailers were one of them was called
like the possession of Anna Nebenina.
And one was called like the ghost of Llorna.
The exorcism of loony Llorna.
Like what are these fucking movies?
And who wants to see them?
Picket better title.
I didn't think the ghost of Llorna is that bad of a title.
All right, Joe.
The movie looks like Shimmeriant.
Well the trailer is them sitting in a car
and there's like somebody trying to get in the car.
Then Halloween, they did somebody's in a car
and they're trying to get in the car.
I was like separate the movie.
Yes.
These things are moving by rote, unfortunately.
But I was the star of the ghost of Llorna.
They put her name up like filled the whole screen.
I was like, who the hell are you?
I keep my finger on the pulse.
What is she?
Jane the Virgin or something?
I don't know.
Does anyone know who's in the ghost of Luna Llorne?
Carl Laney.
No, I was not Carl Laney.
He is?
The ghost of Linda Carl Laney is the name of that person.
Why does she look so different?
She looks very different.
Oh, okay.
All right.
Pat has said frequently he doesn't like anything
made by not white.
Those are the words he'll use.
He'll use those words.
Some Asians are fine.
All right, let's talk about a good horror movie.
I, in honor of the pick of today,
the review that we're doing,
I re -watched some classics.
The first being Halloween three.
Season of the witch.
It's just a wonderful movie.
I have nothing wrong.
I have nothing bad to say about it.
I have nothing to spare you to say about it.
I love the film.
I said to spare you things on this podcast.
I said once that it didn't make any sense.
And it doesn't really.
It's bad shit.
But it's a fun movie to watch.
It's got the old man from Robocop
and it's playing once again,
the creepy head of a corporation, you know.
The guy from that 70's show.
Well, that guy is, yeah.
Kurt Woods.
No, no, that's the guy in Robocop
and that 70's show.
He's not in Halloween three.
The old man from Robocop.
Peter Willer.
No.
The guy that's like,
the guy that's like,
how soon could you show me a demo of this robot cop?
That guy.
Yeah.
He's the guy that's like,
the children must wear the masks or whatever, you know.
That's him.
It's just a fun movie, man.
I don't really understand why the kids turn into
millipedes.
That doesn't really make sense to me.
Well, your favorite is Halloween too, right?
We'll get to it.
All right.
I said to Joe last night as we're walking out of Halloween 2018.
I said,
you know, it was fine, which makes it one of the best Halloween movies.
You're barking up the wrong tree in this room.
It was fine.
We'll get to it.
Don't ruin it.
How do we think it was just a lot of fun?
It doesn't really make any sense, but it's a lot of fun.
Right.
And it's got Tom Atkins.
From a,
can anybody else name one movie Tom Atkins was in besides me?
Are the creeps very good?
Fog.
Very good.
Creepshow.
Do you know the best line in Creepshow by Tom Atkins?
Just say yes or no.
I think no.
Huh?
No?
Is it yes or no?
No.
This is the best line in Creepshow.
That's why God made Fathers babe.
That's why God made Fathers.
After he disciplines his kid ridiculously,
he takes the, he smacks his kid for reading Creepshow,
the comic book.
Right.
And his wife goes, go easy on him.
And he goes, do you see this crap?
People turning into plants for Christ's sake.
Nobody's seen Creepshow.
I've seen it.
It's shit.
I thought, I thought people would get excited about the quotes.
I don't have the, I don't have the love for Creepshow.
You do.
I thought it was fine.
The second greatest horror movie of all time.
I just can't go there with you.
Huh?
You think the sopranos is good?
It's so does pretty much everyone in the entire world.
Everybody also thought Britney Spears was good too.
Is that, is that a ballot comparison?
Everybody thinks Taco Bell is good.
You think Taco Bell is good.
I love Taco Bell.
It's a discriminating itself.
Besides the point.
It's, it is the point.
I'm sorry.
Check it out again.
I saw, the only other thing I saw was Ron White's stand -up special.
And I'm telling you folks, I was talking backstage.
I spent a night with the guy in Vegas once.
I really liked him.
And I saw his show there.
This was a lot of the same material.
He's in the blue collar comedy circle.
But he's so weird and filthy.
And always like, make sure you know he's going up against an audience
that is full of hate, which is like Republicans.
And he is going out there and saying like, how much he loves gay people.
And I think there's something kind of beautiful about it.
Well, how do you know his whole audience is Republican?
I sat in it.
I was sitting between like, eight people in American flag shirts,
with like yards of Margarita.
Can a liberal love his country, Pat?
Yes, they can.
You get a real narrow mind.
I don't like movies by Spanish people.
I never said that.
Nobody can burn American shirt.
You could feel the audience like back away from him.
It's like Jeff Foxworthy goes out and it's like, hey, you know,
I got a refrigerator in my yard and they laugh for like 25 minutes.
If you ever use a Sharpie marker to color in your bald spot,
you might be red now.
That's better than a lot of his jokes.
I wrote for him for years.
Ron, why do you think when Jeff Foxworthy writes a joke,
he asks himself if it's Foxworthy worthy?
I believe he actually has a Fox there.
Who decides?
Is it worthy?
Sure.
Yeah, I think he's cool and I think he's really, really funny.
And I like how he is talking to an audience that he knows
will hate some of the things that he says and still says them.
I don't think he's some super progressive comedian,
but I just like that he is who he is and I think he's one of
the more underrated comics there are.
I don't think cool alt people would ever watch a Ron White special,
but he's super funny.
I recommend you check him out if you haven't.
That's all.
All right.
I'll check him out.
I'll check this guy out.
I've never heard of him.
Well, we were talking about the duck pussy lips.
Yeah.
It's a funny special.
I've seen it.
But I chose to watch an actual movie for the movie corner.
I can only watch what I had time to watch.
Well, you could have chosen a movie in place of Ron White special,
but you talked about all kinds of things on this show.
Here's my last one.
I also watched Halloween five.
Not not good.
The revenge of Michael Myers.
Yeah.
It's bad.
It's fucking terrible.
It's so generic and boring and bad.
I watched all of them last October.
And you know, it doesn't exist to me anymore.
Yeah.
From now on, these are the Halloween films that exist.
Halloween one, Halloween two.
And you're talking Rob Zombie on the right?
Yes.
Yeah.
Strickly.
Carpenter bullshit.
No.
Halloween one, Halloween two.
Halloween four.
Fine.
Halloween H2O.
Halloween four is lame as shit.
Halloween four isn't bad.
It is though.
It's not bad.
Halloween H2O, I'll grant you.
Outside of the yellow cool jade.
And Halloween three is great, but it's more like if they made a TV series of Halloween.
Sure.
It's like a fun episode.
Yeah, I agree.
But Halloween five, six.
Fine.
Throw four in there.
I don't give a shit.
Who has love for four in here?
No.
All right.
It's just, it's very lazy.
And I put it with five.
They're not, they're not even trying.
Five is beyond terrible.
Do you know there's just, who's got love for five?
Nobody.
Okay.
Come on.
The director of Halloween five.
All right.
There's, okay, so there's a scene with two cops that come out of the house after, supposedly,
there's a Michael Myers that's sitting or something.
And these two cops come out of the house and it's playing this like duck quack music.
Like they're walking and it's like, what?
It's like playing this ridiculous fucking music.
That's close comedy in the end.
And I was like, what the fuck is going on?
And then I looked it up and it was like Halloween five contained a storyline with two bumbling cops
that even had their own wacky music.
But they cut the whole storyline out.
They cut the whole storyline out.
So now cops come out and just say regular cops shit.
And there's like ducks and fart noises behind them.
It makes no sense.
And isn't it true that they replaced the iconic score with,
quack quack quack quack, quack quack quack quack quack quack quack, quack quack quack quack, quack quack quack, quack quack quack quack quack quack quack quack quack quack quack quack quack.
Yeah.
I knew we were in trouble when the movie, when it opened with Holiday Road by Lindsey Buckingham.
Halloween road.
Oh.
Oh, yeah.
Sure.
I thought this isn't going to be great.
Lindsey Buckingham.
Woof woof woof.
Yeah.
Uh, it's, it's a really bad movie.
Holiday Road is a fantastic song.
Of course.
Lindsey Buckingham, one of the co -kest men of all time.
Pat, nobody's arguing with you, all right.
You're not lashing out at nobody arguing with you.
My sister's going to see Fleetwood Mac tonight
and I was like, you know, Lindsey Buckingham is not there.
He's suing them and she was like, what?
Like I think people buying tickets don't know
they're seeing a Buckingham -less Fleetwood Mac.
Well, you, I have no comment on that.
I think you got a problem if you're going to see Fleetwood Mac
to begin with.
Oh!
I've seen him several times.
I don't give a shit.
Once they play the chain, what's left, folks?
Come on.
Hundreds of hits.
What's left after the chain?
What do you want to hear?
Just like the whirlwind blows.
Give me a fucking break.
That's solo next.
It's a great song.
Can't tell the difference.
Crap is crap in my book.
How dare you?
What other songs?
Tell me lies.
Tell me sweet little lies.
Right?
That song sucks.
You can joe your own way.
Good song.
Yeah, they have thousands.
Thousands.
You ever heard, I gave you a tusk.
Did you ever sit and listen to tusk?
I have listened to tusk.
The cookies now never made it.
I listened to it.
I've listened to it obsessively.
And I like tusk.
And here's what happens every time I have a party.
Pat sneaks off and puts tusk on.
And 10 minutes later, everybody goes, what the fuck
is on the radio right now?
Please turn this off.
That is true.
I'm not a fan of land slide.
Monday morning, you should look fine.
That song I like.
Yeah, that's a good tune.
All right, so the chain and Monday morning,
and then I'm out.
I'm heading for the parking lot at that point.
I don't need to sell you on this.
You don't?
They've sold many.
They're doing fine.
Now, we have a new segment we want to do for you guys.
Is that OK?
Yeah.
They seem sort of into it.
Well, they don't know what it is.
You don't know what it is.
This is the horror story?
Yeah, this was your idea, but I think the good idea.
This is the good idea earlier.
So when I was a kid, I would stay over at my friend's house.
This is my friend who had the gay dad who would sneak out.
He would leave going a drive at about two in the morning
and come back at five.
He'd always leave and like, you know,
ass -less chaps and stuff.
Later came out.
Anyhoo.
We'd stay over there.
And his mother would, I think, turn a blind eye for a long time.
Really?
Yes, clearly.
You think she was just not asking any questions?
I believe so.
Now they're best friends.
It all worked out for the best.
But we would stay over there and we'd stay up.
This is why he'd always think we'd be asleep
and then come down and kind of have this caught expression.
It's very sad, if you really think about what was going on.
The man couldn't be himself.
Hey, are y 'all asleep?
Right.
Whatever you do, I'm not wearing ass -less chaps, right?
But we would just keep sleeping, y 'all.
Yeah.
We would sit and our big, we had this Halloween thing
where we would try to tell each other scary stories.
And my friend had this little brother, Caleb,
and he was like eight at the time.
And he told this story.
And we had you had to, we were in the dark
and you had to hold the flashlight under your face
and then see if you could freak everybody out.
He started this story and he goes, once upon a time,
there was a house just sitting there.
And the room laughed for like an hour and a half
because it was so, it's maybe not as fun
and that's kind of fun.
Was he a eight -year -old, be like,
this is really going to freak him out.
A house just sitting there is very fun.
Was he a sea captain?
Well, we are going to tonight attempt to tell you
a scary story that not only have we not discussed,
but we barely know what the segment is.
But Joe's going to start telling a story
and then at some point he will turn it over to me
and I will continue the story.
And we will add little segments bit by bit
until the story comes to an end.
Yeah.
And let's bring the lights down.
Oh, let's do it right.
It's sort of an improv exercise and I'm sorry about that.
The gentleman who runs the club here was telling me
if you want to go outside and like take a breather
get some fresh air, he goes, you're welcome to.
But you should know there's lots of improv people out there.
I said, I'm going to be staying in here tonight.
I can handle some scares but that one's a little too real for me.
All right.
Does it look scary?
It's not your best look.
It's like when you turn on the camera,
when you just wake up and you're like,
God, do I look like this?
Are you ready?
Yeah.
Once upon a time.
There was a boy.
Okay.
Whose father would sneak out at 2 a .m.
For inexplicable reasons.
Right.
Many in the neighborhood said, he's just gay.
But others suspected he was up to something more monstrous.
Sure.
Okay.
So the man went to a local rest stop.
Put the thing under your fucking face, the flashlight.
I saw how you looked and I don't want to do it.
I don't give a shit.
I'd rather do it like this.
That's a better selfie angle.
And do a voice.
Do a voice.
Commit to it.
All right.
So the man went to a local rest stop.
But folks, it wasn't for anonymous gay sex.
It was for something far more sinister than that.
For you see, in one of the rest stops stalls,
the man had a cauldron.
And in that cauldron,
the summoned,
a witch.
But then the man left the stall
and the cauldron behind.
Because that wasn't that interesting of a direction
for the story to move in.
I couldn't agree more.
And he went into the water.
Woods, where he had an altar.
Caked in blood.
But whose blood was it?
And for what reason?
So much better job.
Thank you.
Well, I tell you folks,
the blood was from a horse.
A horse that the man slaughtered.
And why did he slaughter it?
Because he needed the horse's skin.
And why did he need the horse's skin?
He needed it to make leather.
So he could make several pairs of ashras chips.
And that's what he was doing.
The end.
I brought that shit around.
That was a really great story.
I honestly expected that to be much better.
It wasn't our finest work.
It was funny.
Everybody laughed at it a nice time.
Why do you have to?
You know, I feel bad.
Oh, shit, we forgot to do the giveaway.
Let's do it.
Nobody wants this shit.
We're going to sign it.
Bringing the interest level up.
A fraction of a percentage point.
Folks, I have here a graphic novel called Witches.
Spelled with a wise, was scarier.
It says right on the front.
Stephen King calls it a fabulous triumph.
Stephen King's Peter Travers, apparently.
Worst film critic in America.
It's written by Snyder, Jack Hollingsworth, and Robbins,
who I don't know who they are.
And this is only volume.
Snyder is good.
I don't know the other ones, but Snyder.
Who's Snyder?
No.
It's a book about, you know, I read this once,
and, you know, there's a witch in there.
Now, true or false, you bought it because you thought it was about sandwiches.
Well, yeah, because they spelled it funny.
I thought it was a sort of Guy Fieri kind of fun cookbook.
Right.
Which is the damn things about Black Magic.
Who wants it?
It's also got the definition of witch right in the front.
In case you're reading it and you go,
wait a minute, what's a witch?
You can turn right back there and get the definition of witch.
Right away.
Right away, so you're not lost.
You'll get to walk to that pesky dictionary on your shelf.
So anyway, it's a witch's graphic novel.
Again, I can't stress this enough for my own personal curated collection.
Who would like this?
And I will sign it.
See, I told you, Emily, offering to sign it and then getting it refused makes it much worse.
I'll tell you what I'm going to do.
I'm going to sign it.
I signed it.
And then...
It'll be over there if anything wants it.
I throw a pork chop into a kennel.
I'd like to offer you the very picture we're talking about tonight
and whether you want the movie or not.
Look at that hologram art, folks.
And let me give you a second copy of that.
Give these both away at the same time, please.
Joe still has the 99 sticker on it.
Mine's still wrapped, by the way.
Okay.
All right.
Here's a still wrapped.
Yeah.
A signed copy of John Carpenter's Halloween.
We know that it cost at least $9 .99 at one time.
And it's the night he came home.
I believe the he here is referencing Michael Myers.
Any interest?
Two copies.
Boom.
Take both.
Please.
Boom.
Let's speed it along.
Do it next.
All right.
I've got here to give away.
The best Halloween movie?
Halloween, too.
The best of the series in wide -screen DVD.
So you can see it in all its glory.
This is the best Halloween movie.
If you don't think so, you're fucking wrong.
This is a great flick.
Who fucking wants the shit right now?
Everyone is fucking wrong in the world.
It's a great horror movie.
It's really great.
And it's got, what's his face in it?
Dom Delewies.
Yes.
Yeah.
That's that great scene where Michael Myers appears.
Somebody goes,
BAM!
Yeah.
That's my favorite scene in the movie.
A subtle performer.
I always love it.
Adrian Barbot comes in and shows cleavage.
Yeah.
Michael Myers gets distracted.
Ooh.
Yeah.
Rah!
BAM!
Ooh.
Yeah.
Halloween, too, folks.
Who wants it for that Dom Delewies scene alone?
Great.
All right, let me sign it first.
I'm offering up a three -pack.
The unrated hostel directed by Eli Roth.
I love that movie.
I really do.
From Dust Till Dawn, another fantastic picture.
Hey, I guess I'm watching a crime thriller.
Wait a minute.
It's a vampire movie.
Sorry if I spoiled it for you.
And then Bruce Willis.
You know him from the Comedy Central roast of Bruce Willis.
In a little picture called the sixth sense.
Anyone?
All three movies could be yours.
They could also be yours for $1 .99 at Walmart.
If you're willing to take the time to sift through the bin.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Okay.
Sign it, Pat.
What about these pins?
I think these are for us.
Oh, okay, great.
Yeah.
All right.
Are you going to give these people everything?
I'm sure it's off our backs, Pat.
I feel they deserve it.
Who made these?
Who made them?
This is very cool.
I got the cooler too of the two.
Thank you, Emily.
I'm signing it over my boy George Clooney's face here.
Did you get a takeer for these?
Somebody, yeah.
Okay.
They're good movies.
They are.
They're not bad movies.
They're just a diamond dozen.
That's all.
For the one person who likes Halloween 4, here it is.
Yeah, give it to that person.
Signed.
Okay, right here.
Some man in the back that I think is a vagrant that just wandered in.
He wants to sell it for crack.
Don't give it to him.
Is there any food?
Do they have any food?
That's not funny.
Stop laughing at that.
Folks, this week on Cool Kids we did my favorite episode.
And it's horror themed.
And you'll see it in about six weeks.
It's just in time for the holiday.
It's Vicki Lawrence.
And she's dating Ed Beggley Jr.
And the question is, is he or is he not the zodiac killer?
And it's a, it's really like a horror multi -cam episode.
And he was brilliant in it.
I think he might get nominated for something.
If we put him up.
One of my favorite movies of all time.
Zodiac.
Sorry, Jake Gillan.
Yeah.
Anyone?
David Fincher's Zodiac.
Director's Cut.
Enjoy.
And then let's just get, let's wrap this up.
This is my last one.
All right, great.
Ready?
Folks, sticking with the Halloween theme.
Halloween H2O.
Again, the wide screen edition.
And this is a phenomenal, phenomenal.
I truly mean this.
I know I get a lot of shit for saying Halloween too is better.
I really mean that this is such an exceptional sequel for the franchise.
And we will get into exactly why when we review the new Halloween.
But this is, I mean, come on.
And you got, you know, Los Angeles Times calls it sexy, smart, and stunning.
Josh Hartnett's in it, guys.
One of the most electric performers in film history.
W. Wake is he asleep.
We don't know.
And that's why we keep watching.
An instant classic raves, W -W -O -R -T -V.
Remember when he had the hair, he had like the dumb and dumb or bull cut
from like the faculty through H2O.
He shot the faculty in H2O at the same time.
Do you know that?
I did not know that.
I knew that.
But I think that something might be wrong with Josh Hartnett.
Just a theory I have.
I think he's convinced people that there's not something wrong with him,
but I think there is something wrong with him.
Nobody wants H2O.
I'll take it, he says.
Like, yeah, I guess if you're not going to eat those fries.
Sorry, it's the only thing I paid money for.
I'm offering up another three pack.
Francis Ford Coppola's Bram Stoker's Dracula, a fantastic Halloween movie.
Containing Keanu Reeves delivering the line Dracula.
Dracula walks in.
He's 800 years old, and Keanu Reeves goes Dracula.
He's playing a British man, and he goes Dracula.
That's one of them.
John Carpenter's the thing, baby.
This contains my favorite commentary of all time.
I'm Kurt Russell and John Carpenter discussing the thing.
If you've never heard it, this is actually kind of rare.
It's on the blue ray, but it's hard to find.
Can I do my impression of what I think that commentary sounds like?
This goddamn thing was crazy.
Is that what it sounds like?
That's a lot of that.
Remember that?
Shit, it was cold and shit out there.
God damn it was nuts.
It's very fun to listen to.
Those are two funny guys.
And then when we reviewed on the show that we differed on strongly,
I think it's an extremely great horror picture stir of echoes.
It's a three -pack open to the public, and I'm putting it in a Miba bag.
Trying to sweeten the deal.
Are these gifts for us?
Should we open them on now?
I don't want to open presents in front of people.
Just put it on our schedule and release presents.
Okay.
Which sounds like a horror movie as well.
You go first.
Present.
Card first.
Okay.
P -dub.
Thank you for that.
I didn't get a card.
You got a card.
You can get a card.
I got one that you made out of paper in the lobby.
Can something be about me for once?
Oh, for once.
What's your card, too?
Oh, it's Reba McIntyre and Tremors.
Very onboard there.
You didn't get penetration even with the elephant gun.
The line right here?
She said that on our wedding night.
Folks.
I was about to get mad and I couldn't argue the quality of the joke.
Oh, wait.
I just got to learn on my phone before you read this.
Kate Mulgrew wants to return to the Star Trek universe.
Thank Christ.
The die am I through and that wishing well finally paid off.
I really got that alert on my phone.
All right.
Pat, Joe was absolutely wrong about Tremors.
Don't let any man, Joe, change your opinion.
Baby girl.
Love Emily.
Thank you, Emily.
I appreciate it.
And I'm opening my package.
That's what folks.
That's what got less moon ves in trouble.
Okay, I thought it was weed.
So whatever it is, I'm a little disappointed.
But I'm going to look.
Yes.
We've got...
That's not weed.
What is that?
Mushrooms?
Oh, they're Tremors.
They're gravelids.
Where do they make miniature gravelids?
On Etsy?
These are awesome.
Thank you very much.
All right.
There you go.
Little Tremors figurines.
Thank you very much.
Joe, what'd you get?
Well, I got a fucking bullshit card to begin with.
Look at this fucking thing.
You had to open an envelope.
You flew here from Dallas to put this show on.
Joe, I didn't have time to make a card.
This will suffice.
No, it won't.
Now I'm kidding.
There is crazed...
There's a crazy artist in Denton
who made these prints.
I decided you needed all three.
I'm just kidding.
I'm like, you know I love you.
Let's see what we got here.
It's Prince of Tremors.
Is it?
No.
Oh my god.
These are wonderful Star Wars pictures.
Look at these.
Those are beautiful.
Look at those right there.
Those are so nice.
Here is Vader's ship landing on Endor.
Right after the Emperor says that boy will come to you.
Okay.
Everything is going as he's foreseen.
Here's Hoth.
They're taking down our...
And this girl dumped you?
I just don't get it.
I just don't.
Listen.
I know your wife is going to be rare to go when you get home with those Tremors toys
later tonight.
We'll see.
And here's Luke's speeder on Tatooine.
These are beautiful.
Thank you, Emily.
This is very sweet.
That's very sweet.
Thank you.
Seriously.
I don't have room to hang these up in my apartment.
So, who wants them?
I'm kidding.
You know when you know it's a bad gift and my family is really big on this.
Is when you're opening it.
My aunt always does this.
You start to open it and you're like, oh cool.
It's a sweet gift.
Then you start to pull it open.
And she's like, now I have the receipt.
If you tell her, like, always like launching into some explanation.
And you're like, all right.
Well, if you think it sucks, why don't you give this to me?
We should get to our movie.
I think we should.
Yeah, we're fully shit.
We're deep in at this point.
We're fine.
I'm not saying we're not fine, Pat.
I'm just saying we should get to the damn review.
Can I do one thing without you judging me?
Is that possible?
You sound a little whiny right now.
See, I was judging him.
Folks, we saw at the arc light last night, Halloween 2018,
the kid comes out to do the intro.
That's something, if you don't live here, they come out.
And they go, you know, this movie is directed by so -and -so,
turn your phones off or whatever.
This kid comes out and it wasn't a bit.
It was not a bit.
He goes, all right, everybody.
The movie for tonight is Halloween.
It stars Jamie.
Unbelievable.
The Curtis.
A place almost turned on him.
It almost got very ugly.
Unbelievable.
It was pretty shameful.
But yeah, I mean, we saw the new Halloween picture.
How many people have seen it?
You all go see it while you're in town?
All right.
Shit, there's about half the people didn't see it yet.
I don't know.
We're not going to spoil anything about it.
Probably are, but it's, you know,
Michael Myers kills a lot of people as well as what it is.
I think, let me just say this as a setup.
Sure.
So this is a sequel that takes place after the first film.
So clearly what the motivation here was was,
H2O was a sequel that took place after the second film
and picked up Laurie Strode's story.
This one picks up after the first film
where they're not brother and sister.
They're not related.
But she is still very scarred.
Is someone watching like a black and white television backstage?
You guys all hear that or is it just us?
I can hear it.
All right.
She's still very scarred by her encounter with Michael Myers.
That's basically where the story starts.
40 years later.
Yeah.
For me, having Michael Myers dressed as the love guru
was a mistake.
Because it wasn't that popular, but no.
No.
I mean, for, I stand by what I said,
I kind of played my hand earlier.
I thought it was a decent movie.
That immediately marks it as in the top 4th or so
of Halloween movies.
I just was not particularly gripped by it.
I kind of admired how the first kill was a 10 -year -old boy.
I thought he was going to kill that baby.
I think the whole theater thought he was going to kill that newborn baby.
Luckily, that didn't happen.
But there were some gross when he stomps in the guy's head.
You know, that was pretty gross.
There were some kind of cool kills.
They do a lot of dealing with the teenage kids in a way that's not great.
I wish it had been about the blonde girl and the blackhead
that she was babysitting.
Because I thought they were the best part of the movie.
And I was terrified that she was going to die because in that one two -minute section
they put all the character development into those two
and made them so likable and so awesome.
And I was laughing out loud at the kid.
I thought he was hilarious.
And I was terrified that they were going to die.
I wish they had put the same care into the other people.
I know it's a slasher movie.
But when you have something like that,
it obviously makes the movie that much more tense.
Everyone else, you're like, all right, kill him.
I don't care.
Excuse me.
I went into this skeptical because I thought I'm not buying this.
They're not brother and sister.
Why is she waiting for him to return?
This was a traumatic experience that she had when she was a kid.
I don't believe that this woman would become essentially a militia member,
you know, one woman militia.
Right.
Thinking this guy's going to escape.
I think if you're that traumatized by it,
you leave the fucking town and go set up camp somewhere else.
Yeah.
But so I didn't care for that aspect of it.
What made me buy into it was I did like,
especially in this Me Too error,
that how they played that was,
a woman is saying I was a victim
and I think that this thing is going to strike again.
Yes.
And nobody believed her.
And then she was right.
So I thought that was a very clever commentary on Me Too.
I thought it was very relevant.
And I thought Jamie Lee Curtis was great,
but to speak to some more of the specifics of the movie,
you know, the Halloween sequels from two on,
have been criticized greatly for one of the main criticisms they get
is that they contain excessive amounts of Gore,
whereas the first film didn't need that.
This film was not only not an exception,
but it was to the extreme.
This was the glorious Halloween film I've ever seen.
I think so, yeah.
I didn't buy that they were somehow,
it was a rehashing of the original film.
I didn't buy that they were transporting Michael Myers on Halloween
to a new facility.
It's a little ridiculous.
Take him on November 1st, you know?
Common sense.
He somehow magically finds his way back to Laurie Strode,
a little ridiculous.
There was a lot of suspension and disbelief in this movie.
I like the characters.
I cared when they got killed.
I felt bad for some of them.
I really loved Toby Husson and I'm a big Toby Husson.
Toby Huss was awesome and yes, I'll grant you that.
Did you get a career bothers me for some reason?
I can't explain it.
There's something about it.
I find her cheesy.
I think she delivers things for camera.
I don't like her.
I like to grow the plater daughter
and I like Jamie Lee Curtis quite a bit.
The daughter was really good.
Her boyfriend was good.
The nerd that came on to her.
I found that a little weird.
I like the motion sensor bit.
I like some of the set pieces in it for sure.
It had its moments.
They had a loomis type.
This doctor comes in.
For the first five minutes of the film,
you hear the new doctor just doing his commentary on Michael Myers
and I was like, oh, that's pretty cool.
They're doing like a stand -in for Dr. Loomis.
Then all of a sudden, you see the doctor.
You're like, oh, it's Dr. Loomis.
It's the guy that sounds exactly like Dr. Loomis.
Right.
Who's also another old man who's for some reason
infatuated with Michael Myers.
In a very different way than Loomis was.
There was a lot of leaps here.
To think that I get that the doctor wants to understand
the origin of evil.
I didn't believe that he would do it
after a 45 -year career
would do it at the expense of innocent people.
I just didn't buy that.
Did you like the podcasters?
That was so stupid.
And that was like a thing from Halloween resurrection,
the worst of all Halloween film.
Which is saying a lot, because six is a fucking pile of cow shit.
I just don't know why they brought the podcasters off.
Nothing to do with anything.
And then not go into the very fertile area of these shows
like, honestly, our dear friends making a murderer
who really dig into these murderers,
and is that okay?
And I think that's something they struggle with.
Is this cool to make comedy out of people dying, et cetera?
It didn't touch into any of those very ripe themes.
It had nothing kind of a frustrating one.
It was a useless device.
It was a useless device to get us into this.
I remember this.
You guys remember the evo phone?
From about ten years ago.
Do you remember that?
Okay, so when the iPhone first got big,
there was a phone called the evo.
That was its main competitor.
And it failed.
I remember being on the opening Anthony's show
with Patrice O 'Neal.
And I had the evo phone and he goes, you know,
they just made that different just so it could be different.
It's worthless.
And I felt like that in many moments in this film.
I was like, they can't do the structural sound things
that they did in H2O.
So now they got to do it differently.
Yeah.
So now it's like, okay, we can't just have that he broke out
and raided the nurse from Halloween one's house
and got all this information about Laurie Stroden
and then 100 down.
So we have to do a thing where these fucking
documentarians or whatever the fuck it is,
go in and talk to him and put it in his head.
It was just a lot of like the bathroom scene
was already done in H2O.
They redid it in this one.
You saw more poop, though.
You saw more poop.
Which I didn't appreciate.
It was extremely violent in this,
which doesn't offend me.
But in H2O, it played out much more like a tense scene.
And here's what I like.
I think H2O is better.
Here's why.
H2O to me portrayed a much more true to form Michael Myers.
He picks his spots.
He doesn't kill every single person he comes across.
He is on a mission.
He breaks out.
They don't explain how he broke out,
which is fucking better by the way.
I'm sorry, I don't believe that an inmate
from an insane asylum somehow got loose during the bus trip
and killed the driver.
I don't buy it.
Did it in the fugitive.
They did it in the fugitive.
And they also did it in the original Halloween.
All of a sudden they're just all out on the lawn.
And it was the same fucking scene again.
They were just wandering on the street.
Folks, I'd like to recommend the fugitive
if you haven't seen this.
Fantastic.
They did a much cleaner in in H2O.
It made way more sense.
Michael Myers was calculated like he is in the first film.
He felt they dealt with Jamie Lee Curtis' character
better in H2O.
Absolutely.
The PTSD registered more there.
The fact that she was struggling in relationships
was an interesting wrinkle.
And this one, she's nuts from the jump.
She walks into a family dinner and is chugging wine on the table
and like, sure, I get that.
But I just felt like there was kind of,
it was really lacklustre.
And I'm surprised they got her so on board
because there's nothing interesting about the characters.
She's just a nut from the jump.
And then she gets her revenge.
When they did the mirror of the shot
where you think she's going to be in the yard
and she's not cool.
Very cool.
Of course I like that.
But for me, it never really took off.
Who liked it in here, though?
And you're not wrong.
It wasn't bad.
It was just who loved it, what's that?
Nobody.
But some of you liked it?
No.
Okay.
Let me tell you.
I didn't walk out pissed.
I mean, I just think it was not the dream that you wanted.
They misused the Halloween theme.
They ruined it.
They gave it no fanfare.
H2O starts with it.
I like the pumpkin inflating in the face.
Yeah, that was cool.
But H2O starts with a 12 -minute sequence,
including the nurse from the first film.
She gets killed.
Her office is scattered.
You find out she was caring for Loomis.
All of Lori Strode's information is in there.
What the fuck is going on?
And that sequence, I'm getting chills talking about it.
That sequence ends with the detective.
It ends with the detective looking at Loomis' notes on the wall
and going, Michael Myers, yeah, whatever.
Right.
And he slams the door.
And then the fucking Halloween theme kicks in.
Like Danny Elfman's style.
It builds and builds.
Like in Batman Returns, when the frame finally kicks in.
It's so good.
And there are three scenes.
There are three scenes in H2O that define Jamie Lee's character,
which make it so much cooler.
It's so much more interesting, as you said,
to not see somebody who's a mess from the beginning,
but to see somebody who's barely holding it together
and kind of convincing everybody she's okay.
That's how most survivors react.
That's how a Vietnam vet reacts.
He's not walking around going,
I saw some shit, man.
You know?
He's walking around being like,
I got to keep shifting from Vietnam.
That's but okay.
But there are three scenes in that in that in H2O
that are fucking absolutely defining.
The first one is when she's out to the lunch on her date.
Adam Arway, Fred.
Yeah.
And she has a full wine.
She's a full wine.
And she goes to the waiter.
Can I get another wine, please?
And he's like, what the fuck you have a full?
And she goes, today.
And he goes off.
And as he's going to get it,
she downs the wine.
He brings the other one.
And she's pretending that that's still the first wine.
Right.
That's the first one.
And then the second one.
And then they do a wine bit on this one that's less good.
Like did they watch H2O?
I think they did.
It's probably a remake of H2O to me.
The second one.
And they blew it.
You never get a pour like Judy Greer had in that restaurant.
That was three, four glasses of wine in that cup.
More of a chalice, really.
The second thing, which they blew in this new one
as far as I'm concerned,
was the first time she comes face to face with Michael in H2O.
And this one, she sees him in a mirror and she just goes.
And then shoots.
Right.
It's not dramatic.
These are wide shots.
They're doing in H2O.
She keeps seeing him.
It's in her head.
And then when they come face to face,
it's through like a fucking, you know,
one of those ship -port -hole windows.
Yeah.
In a door.
And when it finally happens,
and she makes the fucking face like,
holy shit, this is real.
Again, chills.
And then the best part of H2O.
Which again, they didn't do in this because she just played
crazy from the jump.
When she fucking sends her kids out in H2O
and she's like, get out of here.
And they're like, you can't stay here.
And she's like, go.
She shuts the gates to the school,
breaks the thing that opens the gates,
goes to a thing, kicks it open,
pulls out the fire axe.
Right.
And starts walking into the night screaming,
and you realize she's now hunting him,
and it starts playing the fucking Halloween music.
Dude, that is like...
I started crying when I was...
I watched it today.
I rewatched it today.
And this girl dumped you.
I just...
I can't wrap my mind around it.
I rewatched it today.
I started crying out of excitement
like the way I cried in like,
at like, I'm Batman.
You know what I mean?
Like shit like that.
Like Han Solo coming back on of the fucking Millennium Falcon.
Right.
It's so exciting.
And 13 going on 30 when she first is 30.
Yes.
Yeah, right.
Yeah.
Exactly.
Uh...
It's like she's been 13 this whole time.
And now...
Yes.
And now she's 30.
This is for all it's 30.
Yeah.
I agree that it was lacking that moment.
I thought this was going to be like me like,
fuck, yes, like go Jamie Lee, et cetera.
It never really took off the ground
in that capacity for me.
And I obviously feel the same way.
There was no, uh...
You know, this is...
We've gone to this well a lot.
This Halloween well.
And to just kind of do another thing
and not have anything special about it,
it's pretty frustrating, I thought.
Uh...
Yeah.
I thought it was a solid movie.
I thought it was a worthy sequel.
In my opinion,
the Halloween's that exist.
The Halloween films that exist are one, two,
H -2 -0 in this.
And the difference is you go,
okay, this one is a sequel
if they're brother and sister.
And this one's a sequel if they're not.
And, you know, and they're all solid flicks.
But, uh...
But I thought H -2 -0 was a much...
Much better movie, man.
Like, it's just...
It's...
Four fucking people get murdered in it.
Right.
It's so much...
It's so much more like the original
than this is, and, um...
Well, it's from the writer of Dawson's Creek.
That's why you get that quality.
Kevin Williams.
Yeah, Michelle Williams in there.
I like H -2 -0 quite a bit.
And I agree that it's...
I think it's...
I think it's a truly a work of art.
I really do.
And also, this is the last thing I'll say
about the comparison of the two.
H -2 -0 ends.
The Halloween resurrection is the worst
piece of garbage that's ever been created.
So, but H -2...
And I saw H -2 -0 in the theater opening night.
Uh...
It ends with her cutting Michael's head off.
Yes.
It's the definitive end.
Right.
It's...
Where she kills him.
Right.
This fucking thing ends...
Uh...
With them lighting the basement on fire.
And then it cuts back.
And Michael's not there.
And you're like...
Okay.
It's gonna be a fucking legal.
Yeah.
And...
Blumhouse again...
To criticize them.
Came out before the goddamn movie even hit theaters.
It was like...
We're already working on sequels.
And it's like...
Oh, so we know that Michael Myers definitely isn't dead already.
We already fucking know that.
And now you're gonna make more sequels
to fuck up the sequel that was supposed to make up for all the fuck up sequels?
Like, what are you doing?
Like, you know, so...
Um...
I don't know.
Uh...
I like the movie.
Like the movie.
You know, now I know Kevin McCallister doesn't die in one.
Because I had to see every movie at the dollar show.
What do you think?
I would see them three years after their release.
What do you think of doing a homelone 3, starring Trump?
Jess, Bill Trump is in the homelone.
He's from Kevin McCallister and he's in the White House setting up traps for the press.
For the press?
Yeah.
You never get me.
You wet crevados.
Whatever they're called.
What do they got?
The liquid banners.
Or the sticky banners.
Um...
I like that.
But there was a homelone 3, starring Alex D. Lin.
There's a homelone 4, did you know that?
With French Stewart?
I believe, yeah.
And I believe he gets into some sort of computer technology in the house.
Uh...
Are you excited about the homelone remake?
About the stoner?
It's just...
Ryan Reynolds is playing a stoner who...
Is that Strasfer?
People are going to just...
48 -years -old.
I know.
There's no big deal of being homelone at that point.
Not.
I'm...
I'm 37.
I'm homelone fairly often.
And I do fine.
Uh...
I give it...
I'll give it...
I'll give Halloween one hog sideways.
Yes.
I'll give it a partially chubbed hog.
Neither...
Neither bone or nor flaccid.
Fair enough.
Uh...
We want to thank again all of you for being here tonight.
Emily, please stand up.
All of our artists...
Stand, God damn it.
Guys, come on.
Stand.
Everybody that had a partners, all the artists, stand up.
Come on!
Stand up!
God damn it for another round of applause.
Guys...
We truly, truly love that all of you are here.
We are blown away that so many of you flew in for this.
We can't wrap our heads around it.
I hope you had other things planned while you're here.
If this is it, that's too sad for me to wrap my head around it.
No.
You saw Disney or...
Or something.
The tar pits.
Um...
You know what?
I've never done them.
We should do for the podcast.
You want to see the tar pits?
Check out the bathrooms in this joint.
Folks!
Um...
You know what we should do for the podcast.
I'm kidding, the bathrooms are fine.
Bathrooms are beautiful.
I don't think this is a general for toilet early.
The...
Horror bus tour of L .A.
Where you go see the Halloween house
in the Friday the 13th house in all day.
Are they in L .A.?
They are.
You take a bus.
Has anyone ever done that?
The Halloween house.
Okay.
Is it part of a larger thing where you see the Nimer on Elm Street house and all that?
I would love to do it.
Oh that's cool.
I drove on my way home from work the other day.
I made a point of driving past the people under the stairs house.
Because I just saw that for the first time.
And we're doing it on an upcoming episode.
It will be done in an upcoming episode.
We will be talking about the people under the stairs.
Probably next week.
Spoiler alert.
I'm fucking loved it.
Well Monday is...
Monday is...
Who is fucking insane?
It's...
It's so insane.
I loved it.
I absolutely loved it.
Monday's episode of this week is Deep Horizon, I believe.
Deep Horizon.
What?
What is Deep Horizon?
Event Horizon?
The thing in Deep Impact.
Sorry Morgan Freeman.
Are you thinking...
I remember seeing Morgan Freeman in Event Horizon.
He was in Deep Impact.
The Armageddon...
Like Anson Bugs Life.
There was Armageddon in Deep Impact.
I watched a Bugs Life.
And I'm ready to review it.
No.
Event Horizon.
I got confused.
Well Anson Bugs Life.
Event Horizon.
It's acceptable for an aunt to potentially hit on his stepdaughter.
Why'd you take it there again?
We're doing Event Horizon on Monday.
The next one will be The People Into The Stairs.
Which in the Pat's movie corner segment of that episode,
I will be talking about the film Shocker,
which is holy Christ on the Cross.
Well it's Graven took the good will from that movie,
which was a big hit.
People Into The Stairs and made Shocker.
No, he made Shocker before people.
It was before.
Okay, well then he redeemed him.
So we'll be talking about Shocker also on that episode.
But you guys are amazing.
How many of you are going to, by round of applause,
who's going to stay and drink can hang out?
I'm sure the staff.
Good.
And for the people that didn't clap, why wouldn't you?
Why would you not say this guy here?
I don't think I have a long drive.
Oh, that's fair.
Okay, fair enough.
Why would you not over here?
You didn't need to make a sad.
That honestly felt a little joke.
Wait, clap again.
Who's staying?
Clap again.
Oh, everybody but you two.
All right.
No, you're smart to not drink.
It's a terrible disease.
But a great one.
Where do you live?
Out of all the diseases, it's a great one.
Irvine.
How far is that?
About an hour.
Okay.
Have six, seven drinks.
It's an hour.
We're just going to have six, seven drinks and go.
Yeah.
Yes, thank you very much, folks.
Thank you for coming.
Stick around.
We got tons of booze.
Make sure that if you want beer or wine,
you buy it out there and tip generously.
This place is awesome.
Oh, my ribs.
Give it up for all my ribs, please.
So the best.
Yeah.
And for letting us stay here and drink.
That's pretty awesome.
They're amazing.
I love these guys.
They're the best.
I hang out here all the time.
Yes.
Beer and wine for sale out there.
And up here will be free shots of liquor.
So enjoy yourselves.
Yes.
And let's have some fun.
All right.
Thank you.
Cheers.