唔睺嗌
i've seen a well
he's a champion
he's great
i've seen a well
for that round of applause
oh thank you, Bull
how are you everybody
good to see you
Welcome, Tampa, Clearwater, Petersburg, which of the three cities I never heard
Clearwater are we in Clearwater as well? Clearwater, St. Petersburg, Tampa, yeah many
places that sound like some sort of time share company and what do you do in
Tampa? Opioids mostly? How was the Salvador Dolly Museum? Should I go? We're gonna
go in the morning, all right, good to know, good to know. And did Salvador Dolly
spend some time in Tampa? We're confused. That makes sense, okay, gotcha. This
many people that have tickets just didn't show up. I don't know what's going on.
You guys just rolling and cash down here. How did anybody fly in for this? You
flew in? Welcome. We're where? Where are you in from? Charleston, South Carolina?
Oh yeah, plenty. It is still about, now Joe you're making it sound like we were
playing to two people. There's a healthy crowd here but we are missing a pretty
good amount. I don't know why. I don't understand why. Was there maybe they were all
coming in a bus like the Muppets and it blew up or something? Yeah fell off a
bridge. I'm just grateful the ceilings are so high. We got real high ceilings. You
let a balloon go in here. What's that? You got a bear tree over there. We could
get a couple ornaments on this tree but they're all over here. Okay. How often
are their raves in this space? This is a real rave space. I think it's
presented on the backdrop. I mean clearly I should have been Donna Reed, right? I
agree. I would have liked you to be my little daughter. Get my head. This is for
those listening at home. We've got a screen behind us with a picture. It's got
the logo and then a picture of it. It's a wonderful life with my face over Jimmy
Stewart's face. And Pat left out completely. Yeah. Which wasn't my fault. I swear I
didn't have any part of that. Pat was stewing backstage. He thought I told them to
do that on purpose and I didn't. It's strong. It's doing souping. But we are
gonna do. It's a wonderful. We're gonna do two episodes for you guys tonight. For
the other people be here. Yes. We're gonna do two episodes. Maybe they thought I was
like a show at like the Hollywood Bowl and they'll be like there'll be openers. Yeah.
Podcasts. Then the white stripes here. Come on about 11. There's still a popular
big. Jack White on his own trash. Anyone love like a solo Jack White? Any big
blunder bus fans in the house? We all pretended for the first couple Jack
Whites. You're like, oh, this is just as good. No, it isn't. No. Because you don't
listen to any of them because they suck. And it's not like Meg was writing anything, but
there was a magic with the two of them. There was a magic that's. I'm telling what
the magic was. I like Meg. Her breasts. Her breasts were great. Yeah. She's a not a good
drummer. And she held him back just enough. Maybe that he made good music. Once he
hit, once the sky was the limit with him, it was a bad scene. You might be like
bringing the horns. You're like, no, no, Jack. Because he'd come in and be like, hey, I got
this like classical piece and like you're gonna have to do some like contra -puntled
drumming and stuff. And she was like, you mean like this? And he was like, oh fuck it.
I'll just put those on my un -listenable solo house. I think you're actually right. There
is, there's, it's, it's why so many early punk band recordings are great because they're
making them, well, at least they used to in the 80s and 90s, like they'd have to make it
with the four track or the eight track, or even the 16 track. And then when they go to the
beach, you're talking like classic punk. Yeah. Yeah. Newfound glorious. Yeah. Yeah. But then
they go to the studio and then it's like, it's unlimited tracks. Right. And it's not
just the polish. It's that, then they start adding the strings and shit. And you're
like, no, man, it's better when you're limited. Like when you're limited. Constraints make
you better. They make you more creative. They do. It's why I feel working with you.
Because I hold you back. Yeah. Well, I mean, Tim Burton is a great example on the movie
end. It's like you give the guy five million to make pee -wee. You're left with an enduring
masterpiece. Yep. You give him a hundred million to make Wednesday. You got fucking
Riverdale. I haven't seen Wednesday, but it looks like just a piece of shit. It's getting
the first thing he's done in a long time. It's gotten good reviews. Yeah. Yeah. He, he
would, they woke him up. He was sleeping upside down. And he was like, well, they're like
good reviews to him. And he was like, hmm, is he still with HPC?
I want a bottom card. Hell in a bottom. Lisa Marie. Yeah. No, he's with bottom carder.
Still? No. Somebody's very strongly saying no. They divorced. They, I think they divorced
too. She had a big day in the press the other day, went hard and the paid defendant,
rolling and deaf in the same day. I mean, just imagine being her agent and just crack
an open of variety. That's why I keep my mouth shut. So, I made me laugh. Sorry. It's
fine. It's a comedy podcast. All right. So, let me, let me just, there's a person in the
back in the room I'd like to get to know. Miss, are you the bartender? Well, that we're
going to be closely acquainted this evening. Could I, could I trouble you for a red wine?
I believe there are two options. You all know the Neil Diamond version or just the U .B. 40.
Check out the Neil version. It's sadder, but I saw Neil one of his last shows before Parkinson's
took him down, not to death, but took him down from live performing. And it's sad. I love, I mean,
he's a great songwriter, but Neil gets up there. He's at the Hollywood Bowl, actually. And he's
singing red, red wine. And you could see people around us being like, is he covering U .B. 40?
What's going on? They didn't know. But then he gets to the middle and to confuse matters even
further. He does a rap, a 75 year old Neil Diamond, to confuse matters even further. He does his own
rap, not U .B. 40's rap. He'll eat before he doesn't do a rap, but they're breaking the lion,
bloke, the monkey got show. That's right. That's right. It's close enough. I forgot. It's
much of a rap is like blondie rapture. Yeah, yeah. No, I forgot about that part. Which is considered
the first rap rock song, even though, you know, it was the first, yeah, it was the first mainstream rap
ever or something like that. Rapture? Yeah. Yeah. I believe so. Something. And that's not a,
if that's a rap, then yeah, that's not a rap. You know what I mean, Joe? I know exactly what you
mean. But he did. That rap is so bad. It made me want to say Debbie, do more acting. Yeah, I know.
Well, he's Debbie Harry. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Anyway, Neil, he's singing red, red wine. And then he gets
this middle point and he's like, I, all I remember is the last line of it was like, with red, red wine,
we're going to party all the time. And it just made me feel so sad. I didn't wish that you got
the Parkinson's. I made me feel sad. I wasn't at that point. You ain't show. He goes out. This
was pre -COVID, of course. He's, he's, he's married, man, but he leans out into the front row like this.
And most people would do the high, how are you? How are you? How are you? He was fully more than 10 seconds
kissing each female in the front row. Oh, nice. They were doing it. And we can do that here.
It's up to you. This guy looks so much like my friend Tim Hedrick. It's throwing me off. You're
not. I know you're not. Which guy right here? Tim? You know my friend Tim Hedrick? I feel, buddy,
the camera man, you, you can sit. You don't need to, yeah, you don't need to. I went, I went with
him to see Fu Manchu the other night, favorite of the pod, Fu Manchu. My favorite band ever.
I got to tell you guys, and this is not a great thing to admit, but if Fu Manchu comes to your
town, the ticket is 15. They're very reasonable. And they're a great live band. The albums that they
are selling for 20 apiece go online in seconds for 100 plus. So each time I go, I buy the whole catalog
and I sell it in a week. And it's like they could do this too. Why are they selling $15 for a ticket?
Keep it really real, man. They really do. I've, I've ordered a lot of stuff from their website. Yeah.
And days, they send you, when they send it to you, it is written in Scott Hill, the main guy. He
writes, it's his writing. Like he does all of it himself like a wild man. They're really DIY.
You think they panicked about getting canceled for cultural appropriation for a Fu Manchu?
I actually, for the first time ever in Googling them. Because for some reason, I have to Google them
to find their website. I can never remember exactly what the website is. But every time I Google them,
Fu Manchu .gov, yeah. People forget that they started as a government agent.
It's .eu. No, for the first time ever, when I googled them the other day, it said,
it is Fu Manchu culturally inappropriate. I don't know if they meant the band or just the
name, the term or whatever. I mean, my favorite bar in all of Los Angeles, five minutes from my home,
two minutes from your old home, Joe, one of your many leases. You're talking about one of your many
three month leases that you took on in Los Angeles. But the good luck bar was my favorite. But it was
decorated kind of like an Asian theme, I guess you would say. Sure. And it caused a big controversy.
Only in LA. Only in LA. Only in LA. Do people have the amount of privilege that they're angry,
that the font of good luck bar is offensive. And what is it now? An abandoned warehouse.
Yeah. It looks like dog shit. It's got that broken windows. Put six waitresses in a bus
boy on the fucking street because you're offended by a picture of a fortune cookie. That was a bar.
That was a bar where a man could have sex. Not at the bar. Probably although it happened, I'm sure.
But that was a bar where if I took a date, 80%. It's dark. It's got like a red filter on it.
It's just there's something real like red shoe diaries. I like that bar a lot. I like that bar a lot.
It never hit the levels of Coke. I wanted it too. You always felt like it was going to be more
of a Coke party in that place. That's where we went the night we did Coke. The one time I did Coke.
We went to that bar. You're going to have to narrow it down for me. Well, people said when I got my
house, they were like, Pat, your house looks like a Coke house. Yes. You got to do Coke over here.
I was like, I've never done Coke. So then we all did it. We all went out to that bar. That was the day
I was home alone going to bed early. Then I came to your house at 2 a .m. and started doing Coke at 2 a .m.
Yeah. Yeah, it was fun. By the way, Joe and I are both not drinking right now.
I was walking over to Joe's hotel. Joe's at the Hampton Inn in Switzerland. I'm at the courtyard
Maryette. Ladies, anybody want to come watch me play with my steam deck? What's a steam deck?
It's not a euphemism. It's a new handheld gaming system. I thought it was a hotel. They said,
give it a name that sounds like a take in a ship. I thought your hotel had a deck where you could
like steam or something. No, no, it's a video game. It's called the steam deck. It's the steam is a
video game website service. They made a handheld called a steam deck. Yes. I have it for a night just
like tonight. I'll go back all wind up and crawl to bed and play Tomb Raider. I was walking
over to Joe's where I haven't drank since December and a whole month of December I haven't had a
drink, believe it or not, folks. Joe is in the same boat, but as I was walking over I was like it's
got to happen tonight. I was in my room before Pat mentioned anything about drinking. He had
in my room full disclosure I was sitting on the toilet. Joe, by the way said I'll be down in a
second I'm having a bathroom issue and he came down 19 minutes later. So I was sitting on to that's a
bathroom issue, ladies and gentlemen. And I was just reflecting on life and everything and I was
saying I can't believe we're not going to drink at this thing. I guess we're doing the right thing.
And then my phone buzz and I looked and it was Tex from Pat and it said I've been in your hotel for
30 seconds. I'm already contemplating a drink. And it was as if Santa had come down the chimney
into the room. I said thank you, dude. I thought I was the only one. And he said I know where this
is headed. And I said yes, here is the list of strip clubs. Let's go. Well I told Joe that he better
not say hey, would it kill us or just have one whiskey? Because Joe is always the devil on the shoulder.
And then who winds up doing it me? I am the devil. I like being the devil. But I'm a fun little devil.
Joe's like, you know, he's Mr. Shots. I finally got him to stop giving me shots. I had an intervention.
I said I don't like them. And I need you to stop screaming in my face. Take the shot. You pussy.
Because I feel like it's peer pressure. Then he left L .A. Am I drinking fell by 99 percent?
I'm not kidding. When I lived in L .A., there were five different people that would say to me on a
regular basis. When you're not in town, I drink way less. Which lets you know how fucking boring L .A.
But that's that's very true. We should wait really quick. We should bring out. I know we're
going to do the segments first, but let's bring out Calta now. Let's get him in for the movie
corner. Let's get him in for the review of the first movie. I love it. Ladies and gentlemen,
how many of you are from here? Just clap. Don't wait. It's a sadder when you raise your hands.
Wait, wait. How many clap? How many people flew in or drove a long time? How many people were made?
I've seen this gentleman before. How many people have made a trip to get here? I don't
mean like you drove an hour. That means flying. You have to stay the night.
All right. Really? Thank you for coming. Well, you're getting a bonus app. They're happy.
You'll get a bonus app plus less chance of COVID. We get 20 more people in here. That's 20 more
chances to get COVID -19. And we'll all be shit -faced by the end of this. Yes.
Anyway, if you're from Tampa, you definitely know this man. If you're not from Tampa,
you still may very well know this man because he's a friend of comedy. He does an amazing podcast
with Robert Kelly called Calton Kelly. He's a champion of all of us and stand up and he's one of
the last. There goes the last DJ. The last. He's one of the last true morning radio man in America.
And I love him and he's great. It's great for him to be here. Mike Calton, everybody. Welcome our guests,
please. Hi, bud. Hello. Hello. Hello. Are you sure there's not Tim Hendrick? Do you know Tim Hendrick?
No. Hi guys. How are you? That's great. This gentleman here. And I saw you follow me on Instagram
as I was coming out. And I said, I'm trying to follow him back, but it was too late. Know that it's coming.
Yes. Why? Know that it's coming. I will only hold that against you next time you come to town.
I'll be like, fuck me. It doesn't follow me on Instagram. Yeah, I've done such a baby like that.
I have done that before. Yeah. They'll be like, this guy wants to come on the show. I'll be like,
no, he doesn't fucking follow us. I believe me. Can I get this couch understands petty probably more
than I can. I'm pretty petty. We were singing Tom Petty as you came out. I'm going to move to that
chair because otherwise, I'm going to be doing the back and forth little hurtful. But all right.
No, no, no, you can stay there. I'm going to move here because it's killing like the right to left.
Yeah. It's a little, it's a little close quarters. Sure. Well, now you got your back to half the crowd.
Just how's that? Good. They call it in the theater. They call that cheating out to the audience.
Yes. Cheating out to the audience. Not eating out the audience. They do that in Amsterdam.
Those sex shows. They'll just eat them out. You ever see a sex show in Amsterdam? No, I went to Berlin
a couple of weeks ago. A couple of weeks ago. Yeah, I went to go see the the Bucks play.
Okay. And I read all about the sex shows. But you wouldn't see the Bucks play in Berlin.
Was it Berlin? Munich. Munich. I know so little about sports. I just went, uh -huh.
Our American football team, the Tampa Bay Buccaneers, were playing the Seattle Seahawks in Germany.
And I used that as an excuse to have my company send me to Germany for free so that I could go cover
the Bucks game. Yes, thank you very much. Very smart. And it was pretty awesome. I never thought I would
like Germany because all you saw are videos of them with sledgehammers breaking down the wall and
everything looked gray. And then before that, it's even worse before that. Yeah. Yeah. And, uh,
and that's the part of Germany. Yeah, I was like, well, surely he's going to mention the Nazis, but
no, you didn't like the wall coming down. Freedom for the Germans. I'm all for the wall. I just, it was
all you saw in music videos. Everybody would come by out with a wall coming down. Surprisingly,
I heard heard, don't make any Nazi jokes or Hitler jokes. Is there a real embarrassed by that shit?
But it's the only thing to do over there. Yeah. I looked at things doing like you can go to Hitler's
vacation house. You can see Hitler's other house. I was like, so you guys are cool with that now.
I mean, that was like the biggest thing to do in Munich was to go see Eagles Nest were Hitler.
The Holocaust, they refer to the Holocaust as Hitler's folly. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Your travel
agent wasn't Kanye West. I married to a Jew and I kept them on the down loo.
Oh, there's over there. Yeah. Uh, there's that great Monty Python, Monty Python story.
This is the only thing Monty Python ever made me laugh ever outside. I'm glad we agree on that.
Yeah. Monty Python is shit to me. Monty, now it's, it leaves you pretty cool. Yeah. Monty Python
and John Belushi. Just two things I couldn't find less fun to dare put John Belushi in them.
Fuck off. What about animal? Whole country was on fucking Coke in the 70s to the point where they
thought it was funny to watch a guy yell cheeseburger for eight minutes. He stinks. Or he's still stinks.
Or play baits over. Put the, put the wig on and just simply play a song dressed as baits over. Yeah.
I love the Blues Brothers movie, but that bit was two guys singing songs with no comedic talent.
I'm taking even farther Jim Belushi is funnier than John Belushi. Now, now that's enough.
Now that's enough. Now you're being, now you're being stolen. I was never a big Belushi fan, but you're being stolen.
No, but the Monty Python story, but maybe my life was they, they went to, uh, they went to Auschwitz for
the tour and they got there at the end of the tour day. Like they were like, sorry guys, we're not,
we're not doing anymore tours. You can't come in. And Eric, I don't say tell them we're Jewish.
That's a good line. Yeah. Yeah.
On Luchy lines, uh, I think Dan Accroyd's useless. Dan Accroyd hasn't done anything without somebody
funnier with him. No, I disagree. I love Accroyd. In what though? Like, what do you know he's great in
Rose Point blank. I think he should have gotten a nomination for that. I just, just doing his speed talking
shit, but he's very, very funny. I'll tell you what I love Accroyd in. And I'm, for once,
going to take us down to the movie going, okay? Because this ties into my first movie. Okay.
I watch Dan Accroyd this morning. Pause. And then you can talk about Dan Accroyd. I wanted to tell
you about the sex show. I saw an absolute. Oh, wait, I forgot. Yeah. Yeah. Go ahead. Way more
entertaining than Dan Accroyd. I saw a sex show in Amsterdam. And Joe's like, I'd rather talk about Dan
Accroyd. Uh, but the, just of the shows in the front row, which I, I was like, it's at it. You don't
be in the front row either at an improv show or a sex show or a sea world for the same reasons.
A Gallagher show, but there's no danger of that anymore. But they had a spinning wheel on the stage,
like a wheel of fortune type spinning wheel, seven segments in the show, solo segments and then
fuck segments. So the solo segment, woman comes out, gets completely naked, spreads her legs, much
like I have done now. And then pulls miles of colored flags out of her vagina. Miles,
you say. Miles. Uh, then out comes a couple. And they have sex on the spinning wheel, which gives
you like all angles, I guess, which means that as it comes spinning, at least one of those times,
you're just looking into two buttholes. Right. They used to have that shot in porno too. They would
cut to the asshole shot. They're like, what are you doing? Now they, they know to leave that out.
Is that where they attractive people? They were on the verge of attractive. I saw a sex show and the
people that fucked on stage were gorgeous. I got pulled on stage. Well, these were not gorgeous people.
This guy and the guy could not could not get hard. So imagine your eighth show. I'm going to struggle
to do two episodes of this thing right now. Maybe he couldn't get hard because you were staring at his
butthole. Imagine he's on his knees. The woman is there waiting. So think of all the times you
couldn't perform. And then imagine there's an audience and you're on a spinning wooden wheel. And
this guy's doing the downward overhand stroke trying to get hard trying to get that blood flow going.
The woman's like kind of waiting, whatever. And then finally, he kind of gives a little sheep a smile
and they leave. Then out comes a woman who does the ping pong tricks, etc. Then there next guy that comes
out, jack hammers the woman on the spin. Like just like, oh, he couldn't perform. I'm going to give
you twice the show. Oh wow. It was really a wild show. I got pulled on stage. Yes. And the stripper
put a, I'm not kidding, put a marker in her, like a sharpie marker in her vagina. And then
wrote on my chest with the marker, took the marker out of her vagina and then squatted down and
pressed her raw vagina into my face and mouth. And then shouldn't they ask? Yeah. I went in the
bathroom to see what she wrote. Welcome to the world of AIDS. The last part's not true but the rest
of it's true. I was fucking terrified for days. I was like that fucking. Yeah. That chick. That's how I
saw my last question. You know, but when I was fine. My best friend in college. That's fine. I'm
sorry. That's it. I see you talk about coming to Tampa and strip clubs. Yeah. And that's what everybody
always asked me. I got a lot of strip clubs anymore just because I grew up here. Well, my wife doesn't
care. Like she, if I say, hey, we're going to go gross. There's wives that don't care. And then
there's the wives who initiate it. Yeah. My wife's not a little, I always find they're trying a little
too hard. You think that that would be great, but I haven't filmed those relationships or really
fucked up. I feel like there's some closeted lesbianism perhaps. I also feel like you end up like
Willie Macy and Boogie Nights where you just walk in on somebody. Yeah. But people ask me like,
what should we go to? Should we go to this one? That one? And I always ask them the same questions.
What do you want to see? What do you want? You want the hottest girls? You want to see
buttles? You want to see real girls? Do you want to drink? Like there's so many, everybody just
thinks it's strip clubs in Tampa, but it's not. There's different categories. Yeah. It's that always
sunny bit where they, they, you want to see the journey to wild. Yeah. You don't want them to start
wild. You want to see the transition? That's funny. That's wild. Yes. I went to, I went, I was in
Cabo, Mexico. San Lucas? I guess so. Well, there's two Cabos. I'm not Cabo Illinois. There's
Sammy Heygars Cabo. Oh, Cabo. Yeah. But I was in Cabo and we went, it was for the worst
comedy festival of all time. And we went, a bunch of us went to, it was actually me,
Janus Popus, Dante Nero, I think. And then the guys, all the guys from the stand, Paul Talia,
Kimowitz was still alive. And we went to the strip club and we walked through the door
and the manager of the strip club greeted us at the door. Not because of, he knew us just because,
yeah, just greeting us. And he goes, boys, boys, boys, welcome. What do you want? What do you want?
What do you want? You want pussy? You want weed? You want cocaine? I go, sir, we'd like to sit down
possible. Maybe we could just get a table first. It was wild, man. It was what we didn't do any
of those things. But it was just like, it was crazy, man. We imagine you closed your eyes and left.
I, yeah, right. We were in Cosmell. We were in Cosmell and the place we were at, they said,
there's a strip club. It's about a mile up the road. So we all were drunk. We piled in the cabs,
take us to that strip club. And it was not a strip club. It was a whorehouse. But it was not a
whorehouse. It was a storage unit place. And they would bring you in the storage unit. And they had
a mattress on the floor. And I was like, no, no, I don't do it. I just felt like as I walked down the
hall, I was like, this is where we all get our heads got off. This is ridiculous. Yeah. And then some
of us were brave enough to leave and some of us were drunk enough to stay. Did you stay? No, my wife
was at the other club. I had to go back to the, we were at like a resort. And I was like, I
had to go back. I can't go to the, I can't leaving a resort heading to a storage unit. I would have a
problem right off the back. You guys know the storage unit. You didn't fuck a prostitute on a
mattress in a storage unit during a family vacation. Why the level it all? I'd like to correct you both
by saying that they mean sex workers. Yes. It went from L .A. So when he said whore and he said
prostitute, I had two small hard times. Well, Christ, yeah. They shut Pat's local bar down because
they had to pair chopsticks out next to the napkins. That's true. So we're going to go to that we do
this thing called the movie corner, Mike, where we review, we do quick reviews of movies that we've
sort of just watched randomly, not for the purpose of the podcast, kind of what we're watching. You can
join in if you like. Before we get to the main movie, the main movie for this first Christmas episode
is National Ampune's Christmas vacation. Listen to that fire. We didn't make it. They don't have to applaud
that movie. And then the next episode, we're going to do it's a wonderful life.
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Some Jimmy Stewart fans in my house.
So my first movie for the movie corner is I got I woke up at 5 .30 this morning and I got on an
airplane that left at 7 .30 a .m. for Tampa, Florida, Delta, which has about 300 movies that you can choose
from to watch. And I chose to watch behind the candle lobby because that's where I'm at right now.
Mentally, is I needed to get into that at 7 .00 a .m. And I've seen it once. I loved it the first
summer salt. Loved it even more the second time I saw it. And for God, Danny Acroid plays Seymour
Liberacci's manager in it. And he is fucking great. It's not a funny part at all. It's not
even an eccentric part. It's a just straight drama role, which he does do. It does those as well.
And so I got to say, I really, really like Danny Acroid. But if you haven't seen the movie,
it's it's great. It's an awesome movie. It's about Scott Thorson's affair or relationship with
Liberacci. Liberacci hiding from the public that he was gay. Boy, what a good job he did. Yeah.
Hide and Met. Well, it's funny. The first scene, have you seen it? Yeah. Yeah, the first scene.
Straight. Yeah, that was like his whole bit. He's at the piano, you know, playing and he's sparkling
and everything. And Matt Damon, it's the first time he's seeing the show. And Matt Damon turns to
Scott Bakula. He's in it. He's great. He's got Bakula and he goes, I can't believe the public
would accept something in this game. And Scott Bakula goes, they have no idea he's gay. And Matt Damon
makes this face of like, what the fuck are you talking about? Like, and then they have a relationship.
They fall in love and Liberacci is very weirdly controlling, but Scott also sort of exploits him,
but they love one another. It's actually kind of a beautiful story, but tragic in its own way.
And haunting, but I will say it was, it was a little awkward because you got some hard anal scenes.
Yeah. And I'm on the plane next to me. Two, seventy three year old.
I would think even a soft anal scene would be uncomfortable. And it didn't help that I kept turning
them going, that'll wake you up. Hey, stupidest. Let me get a Vino over here.
We open up the bar cart. It's 5 .45 a .m. Yeah, sure. Anyway, I recommend it if you haven't seen it.
It's a good move. I loved it. I saw it once. My first will be three thousand years of longing.
Oh, Jesus. Already the title just feels like a kick in the throat. It's just like,
oh, this is going to suck, but it was George Miller. George Miller directed the Mad Max movies.
Those are good fucking movies. The last Mad Max doesn't get much cooler than that.
So I'm like, don't leave babe off the table. Don't love picking the city, but I love babe.
I had a tweet once though, was I want a babe in the sheets? What was it?
I'm looking for a babe in the sheets and a pig in the city in the streets. Something like that.
It was funny at the time. But George Miller, so he's following up Fury Road and I'm like,
this has got to be a good movie. They'll let him make whatever he wants. But what he's doing is one
of those classic, I gave you one for you. Now I'm going to make a real piece of shit that nobody likes,
but me. So the movie is, and it's, uh, Tilda Swinn being weird. She checks into a hotel and
outcomes Idris Elba with ears like Spock ears. And it becomes clear pretty quickly that
Idris Elba is playing a genie. Oh, he gives her three wishes. This is a whole fucking movie about
a genie. What is Elba doing? Dude, he did this right into that fucking giant line movie. Yeah.
He needs a new agent or he's taken whatever pays the most or something. But I get wanting to work with
George Miller until the swim. But this, this movie, it's about the power of storytelling. So,
I mean, it's a, the three strikes right there. It's about a genie. It's called 3 ,000 years of longing.
And it's about the power of storytelling. And they fall in love, I assume, right? They fuck,
yeah. Then they do kind of fall in love. But Idris Elba, like, he goes, uh, let me tell you the stories
of some of the other people that have asked me for wishes. And then you see the stories being acted out,
but the stories suck. It's a movie about the power of storytelling. But the story telling is bad.
What were her wishes? Well, one of her wishes is I want you to fuck me at the end.
And then Idris, Idris Elba said, that's the exact opposite of my wish. Oh, really? Unfortunately,
that one we can't do. Really? Because you did it with that last girl. You told me,
and no, that was a different situation till the, I could see if you were maybe a Kate Blanchette.
But till the swim night, I just don't see it. Uh, it's not a good movie. It's not a good movie. I've
never really liked the George Miller outside of, uh, Mad Max to be honest with you. He's too weird.
I like babe fine, but I never saw babe. Why'd you chew me out about babe earlier?
Cause he's known like it's like considered, that's, that's probably his most popular movie. I mean,
I like babe. I like babe. Now Mike, you can join us, but you were telling us
that you have certain movies you put on when you're going to bed. If you'd like to share one of those
with the crowd right now, I saw a good movie. I don't know if you guys have talked about it. Emily,
the criminal, rented it, have not watched it. I heard it's good. I hear it's good. I like it. I'll
be plaza. I'll be plaza. Play poker with a boyfriend. Really a good actress. Yeah. And, uh, it was a
good original film that I hadn't seen 50 times in different ways. Nobody had elf ears or anything
like that, but it was good. I only watched Genie project. Yeah. Yeah. I watched some movie where the
guy wished that a girl wrote on his chest with a pussy pen. Gotta go, gotta go to Amsterdam.
I do, I do have that set of movies I put on and I fall asleep too. And I feel like you guys will
shit all over them. I watched that. You can't go with the second one. You've already done Emily
the criminal. No, no, I don't, I just watched it on a plane. I didn't watch it when I go to bed.
And that's your one. Oh, I get one. Sorry. I just started following you today. I don't really know
how the rules go. And I'm out. Yeah. Yeah. No, you come back for two. Yeah. I want to see Emily the
criminal though. I mean, why don't you come on your little show tomorrow and do it our way. We'll
make sure you read the rules before you come on the show. Any any white lotus fans? I found out
today that guy's dick was fake. The dick we were all wondering about. It was fake. The HBO's getting
weird with that. They'll put on like everyone's got like a 12 inch dick on there and they're all fake.
It's weird. I feel like that's just to make guys feel better. They say they're fake.
Like I don't want to feel like an asshole when I want to say I can really think I did. All the euphoria
dicks are apparently fake. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. All right. I don't know. Used to be a man. Yeah.
Used to be a man can see a dick when he turned on TV. A real dick. All right.
Yeah. This is probably going to be my last one because I have a lot to say. Don't confuse him.
He's just learning. You're changing the rules now. Well, we went a long time. We can each do two and
then we can talk about the move. That's fair. I finally watched last night. Last night I spent 599
to rent clerks three. Have you been waiting for it to drop from 1999? Yeah. Yeah. And to me, I hit 599 and I say not low enough.
Yeah. Shockingly, I would have spent the 1999 but something was telling me that it would be possible,
possible, that a man who is stoned off his ass 24 hours a day, making a movie, starring a cast of
people that only act when it's an installment in this franchise might not be that good.
So 599 was low enough. I said, all right. Let me. I've. God. Damn it. I am a Kevin fucking Smith fan.
And I've been very disappointed. And the reason I rented this was because I rewatched Zach and
Mary make a porno, which I'm not going to get into, but I like quite a bit and is a very, very funny movie.
And I want to say that to be a positive, to say a positive. I don't want to just sound like I'm
bashing Kevin Smith. I love Zach and Mary make a porno. I think it's really funny and it's the same plot
of clerks three. It's the same fucking movie. Zach and Mary make a porno is about guys that work
in a coffee shop clerks that are broken need money so they make a movie because they want to do
something with their lives that haven't gone anywhere. Clerks three is about clerks and instead of
just the humor of we're broke and what the fuck have we done with ourselves, which is all you need from
the clerks. Instead the catalyst has to be Randall has a heart attack and makes a movie because I don't
know if you guys have heard. Kevin Smith had a heart attack. He doesn't he doesn't talk about it that much.
They make a joke about that in the movie but how much you talk in the movie Dante's like oh Randall
did you have a fucking heart attack? You haven't mentioned it. It's Kevin Smith has and I say this out
of love. Kevin I've never met you but we have a lot of mutual friends. We have a lot of mutual friends.
Some of them are in this movie. Stop smoking weed. You're ruining yourself.
This is so it's so up its own ass to the point where the kid that plays one of the the kid that plays
like the new he's doing a legacy sequel where characters are now going to take the place of the original
characters which guys are right in the Star Wars universe. Sure there's a lot to mine there.
I don't care about a new set of fucking clerks but that's kind of what they're doing in a bit of a
subtler way. And the new kid who's going to be like the new Silent Bob who's the kid from Shrine
are scary stories until in the dark the funniest kid in it. The kid with the dark curly hair.
He's sort of the new Silent Bob and that kid in real life dates Kevin Smith's daughter.
And this is how smart that's how you get to come on after. Yeah but this is how up its own
ass it is. There's a scene in the movie where those two are to like meet for the first not meet.
They're in a function together and she's like giving him big eyes and then reaches over like hey
and he's like oh shucks this girl likes me. You know like dude he's just putting podcasts on film at
this point. He's just taking his life and going I'm just going to put all the inside jokes and
everything up to look. God bless you can do that. I guess you can create cinema and treat it like
the family laundry mat and pass it down to your kids and create a legacy. Sure you can do that.
Is it interesting? Not to me. No. His fans seem to love it and he certainly is making good fucking
bank on it. It's so good for him. I do respect it and admire that that ingenuity but the movie
it's it's just so fucking schmaltzy. Dante Dante in the last movie falls in love with Rosario Dawson.
At the beginning of this movie you find out she's dead. Of what? Meaning she didn't want to do the movie.
Right. Meaning they could get her for two scenes because she is in two scenes. As a ghost?
Yep. As a ghost. Let me work for Arthur too. Let me tell you how they let me tell you how she died.
She was pregnant. I noticed a dark silence but then thank you. I appreciate it. She was pregnant
with their baby just after they got married and she's already your straining credibility that she
would fuck that guy. Yeah. Well the last one it was not believable and this one it's yeah.
Anyway she was pregnant when they got married and she was pregnant and she's hit by a drunk driver
and dies. This is a clerks movie. This is where this is where we're at at the beginning of the
clerks movie. One guy has had a heart attack. Dante's wife is an unborn baby or dead in a fucking grave.
She appears to him two times as a ghost. He
everybody's emoting all over the fucking place. It's gross. It's like they're giving Michael
Kane in dark night rise as a run for his money. Like everybody's weeping the entire fucking
life. I remember I was on I was on OP and Jim right after that movie came out and Norton goes
look look fucking Michael Kane blubbering all over the fucking mouth. He was really bad about it.
Anyway but you know it's like so then Randall said oh oh I almost forgot.
Jay and Silent Bob now run the video store which is no longer a video store. It's a dispensary
because Kevin Smith loves weed now. Did I mention that? He's desperately wanting to make in my opinion
to make the kinds of jokes he used to make in his movies that he can't make anymore because he's
now like a very very much become a captain of the woke movement. So they sort of skate up against
or brush up against jokes that are almost sort of funny or almost sort of like the old
style of Kevin Smith here but they don't ever go in any direction. The only thing he points any
fucking ammunition at is Jesus because it's like such an easy fair target and nobody cares. Yeah.
The Christophe? Yeah. So Randall starts to make his movie his movie is big surprise clerks.
They need a DP and who turns out to be a DP by surprise?
Who suddenly knows how to shoot movies? Silent Bob.
Silent Bob. Did they make a DP joke, double penetration? No, but they make this joke, Pat.
They make this joke. Why would we shoot it in black and white? Are you insane? And then Bob,
Silent Bob's one line is no I'm not insane. I'm a fucking director and I know what looks
like.
Anyway. Yeah, that's tough. They do an audition montage where at one point Kevin Smith's actual
mom is auditioning and goes, who wrote this, Phil? His mother should be ashamed. This is open
mic comedy show fucking garbage. I'm sorry. It's terrible. It's terrible. It's it's it's it's it's it's
better than this. This is why I'm mad. I'm not being hard on the guy or I am, but I'm being
hard on because he's fucking better than this. He's making student film level fucking
Dreck because he's so baked out of his goddamn mind that he can't get his goddamn emotions
in check. Everything in the movie doesn't have to be a direct reflection of your life. It's not
that fucking interesting. I get it. You and your friends have grown up and all have kids now.
Fine. Give Jay and Silent Bob kids, but they don't have to be great parents. That's not
fucking interesting or funny. Put a little conflict in this. Put a little drama into it in in a
in a good way. I mean he tries to put drama in it and that's people weeping the entire time.
Anyway, cut to the end of the movie. Randall is being very selfish but we cut to the end of this
review. Christ on a cross. Randall's getting his movie or getting very selfish about getting his
movie. I could have paid $5 .99 and watched it by themselves. I'm sorry. Dante flips out at Randall
finally. You're being rude. You're you know all you care about is yourself this and that the whole
thing. And what happens? Dante drops dead. What? Spoiler alert. Dante has a hard attack.
Randall goes to him in the hospital and he's like buddy you can't die on me. Dante's
unresponsive because he's dying. Randall runs to his home and recuts the movie to make it not about
Randall but about Dante. And he plays the movie for Dante as Dante dies in his bed. And he says,
you're the star of my story. You're who my movie has always been about. Yes, fucking way.
The same character that in Clark's 2 said at the end of Lord of the Rings he would have been
surprised if Frodo fucking bricked in Sam Gange's mouth. That scene was so gay at the end.
He's now doing the same fucking thing. Dante dies and then
comes to him watching the original clerks in heaven with his dad life. Wow. That's tough.
That's tough. They watch it. Dad together and he goes we can let's go and she goes but the
movie is not over and he goes I trust the director. Let's go. And he dies.
Wow. Wait. Wait. Wait.
Ready for this? So you're like that's the end of the fucking clerks franchise. He kills Dante.
He was supposed to kill him in the first movie decided not to because it was a terrible fucking idea.
So he does it in this one. It's still a terrible idea but now it's schmaltzy. It doesn't even
have like the ironic twist of the first one. And the end of the movie has a sitcom ending where
they get bailed out for the money they owe the big bad investor because the kids it is also the
ending of it's a wonderful life. Yeah. They sold crypto and money comes in and it's it's a very sick
come lazy ending. Randall never shows his movie to anybody. And Randall is standing at the counter
and starts weeping again and says I wish you were here buddy.
And who appears but a ghost of Dante. This is insane with the idea which Kevin Smith I believe
has confirmed that he's going to make more clerks movies. That Dante now is the force ghost of
the clerks franchise. Kevin stop smoking weed. What are you doing to yourself? This is fucking madness.
So that's the end of the movie. Camera pulls out slowly as a ghost of Dante looks on it Randall.
Randall doesn't know he's there because he's a fucking ghost. And as the camera finally pulls out
to the full shot who's revealed but Kevin Smith's daughter in a female version of the clerks
like uniform putting milk away because she's now stepping into the shoes. And the movie impression
she's some sort of gifted actress as he. I don't know. He put his life in the giant town of
all over the world. No one's wife's in this too. She plays the she plays the she's quite a bad actress.
Yeah. That's a tough conversation to have with your wife. Yeah. But you're the boss. You should put
me in it. Yeah. You can't talk to the director. Yeah. I don't think and I don't I don't say this to be
like I'm not trying to be like wholelier than that. I don't think like his family is pressuring him
to put them in this. I think he is just one of these guys. There are a lot of guys that do this.
They put their whole fucking family in the thing because they you know Dante sells tile when he's
not doing those movies. So if he's putting those guys at the leads. Why the fuck am I putting his own
kid in the movie? That's what I mean. Like it's almost like he probably casts his daughter because he
couldn't cast somebody that acted better than the clerks. But here's the thing. They're so
I feel bad for his daughter because it's like dude. I forgot. I forgot because this is how
poorly the movie's written. They don't even call back to it. She's Jay's daughter in that universe.
Yes. She's Jay's daughter. That what she's Jay's daughter and Jay and Silent Bob reboot. Yeah.
Which is even worse than this movie. Which I'm in by the way. Really? As what? My likeness is in there.
So he put us in the movie and my family vacation was that weekend. So I couldn't go. So at the
Comic Con my guys from my show and my cut out and my logo and all that are in there next to Chris
Hemsworth in the movie. Anyone know the most fucked up part. I still haven't watched it.
Now would he get mad at you for being critical of one of his films? I mean that's per I don't mean
that. I don't think so. He's pretty he's pretty quick. He's a he's here's what I feel comfortable
doing this. I've never met the guy. He's very critical of movie. Like when he doesn't like something.
He's yes. He's pretty ruthless. I think this guy could still make great movies. I think Seth
Rogan introduced him to weed and he is I mean my god. I watched his last Silent but Deadly which was the
last like live thing he did. The last stand up. Whatever you want to call it special. He did that was
the one when he had the heart attack. Yeah. This fucking every fucking story he's talking about weed.
Every time he fucking panels on a talk show he's talking about weed. He doesn't shut the
fuck up about weed. He has said I get high so I can write or he goes I write so I can get high.
I made a deal myself that if I if I'm gonna smoke I have to work and I want to smoke so I work.
That's not the way the equation is supposed to go. And this thing is you know so I feel bad for
his daughter. His daughter shows up at the end of this and I'm like why is she even in this? She
is no lot. And I'm like oh wait she's Jay's daughter. Wait a minute. They weren't
a scene together. Why is he not like because that like group of people that are still seeing
clerks three know all that shit. They're not looking to he's not trying to bring a new
audience for those movies. It's the same group of people that like I saw the first one in the
Angelic theater in Manhattan when it first came out and you couldn't see it anywhere. And I now I
wouldn't even have in Kevin Smith on a show it doesn't time to still haven't seen clerks three
I rewatch dogma recently it's so funny it's so well written it's so well done and he still has
access to Hollywood like that's the thing he is not ostracized into this weird little corner of
New Jersey. He's got Ben Affleck shows up in this like he does a cameo as one of the guys auditioning
for the movie like he's fucking can he got he got Rosario Dawson he got it for two scenes but he's
still got her he can get access to real people it's like just like I'm not even saying that even if
you don't use your crew great but make Jason Mew's funny like make him funny like I just don't oh my
god it's so upsetting it's I don't know why do I care so much I die don't know I'll be brief because I
have to now so through a review it was no but so I talked on the show about so they did this
sight and sound pull the hundred greatest movies ever it's it's a good thing to talk about on your show
sure but it's never pans out these it's ludicrous the number one movie is a three and a half hour movie
about a woman washing the dishes honestly I talked about that on the show but I saw another movie on
the list that I had not seen called Wanda and I was like all right I'm gonna give it a go this is
the pilot for the wander sakes yes exactly yeah and Wanda was a much better experience is it one
of the best movies ever made absolutely not not even close but it is about a woman
she at the movie the movie starts is this guy in court and he's got a woman there with some kids
and his wife hasn't shown up and he's trying to divorce her and the judges like why isn't she
here and he's like I don't know but I really just want and she thought who's this woman and he goes
this the woman who takes care of our kids I want to marry her but I can't tell my wife gives me the divorce
finally the wife shows up like an hour late this is Wanda and she's like I don't care given the divorce
the judge is like you don't want the kids she's like no which is a pretty cool way to start a movie
really right so then she's just like completely indifferent to her life she doesn't love her kids
love her husband and do any ghost no ghosts but she goes and just like gets picked up by a dude he
winds up being a bank robber and she's just like this woman who like goes along with whatever anybody
tells her kind of so she's had all these abusive relationships of course because abusive people target
that type of a person and that's pretty much it it's like a 70s bank robbing movie and it was fine
it was a decent movie I have no idea why it's on this list of the best movies ever made this woman made
one movie and died she doesn't do any more movies I don't know how it became so popular but she
comes back in clerks for so be back but I bring this up because I have to read I read Pauline Kale
the one of the most famous film critics of all time I read her review from the time and it made me
laugh so hard that I have to share one sentence Wanda's an attractive girl but such a sad ignorance slut
that there's nowhere for her and the picture to go but straight down wow that's like a sandy canyon
crazy yeah yeah it's by Tinder bio it's a it's a decent movie but this list is really throwing me
for a loop anytime I check something out on this list of the I mean granted if you're told this is
one of the greatest movies of all time you're gonna go in like with this kind of arms folded attitude
but both these movies I've watched have been average I don't really understand it what
what's that one movie with the chick that won the Academy Award when she lived in the van recently
like two years ago oh it's not a good movie no madland no madland shat shat in a bucket there's that
Reese no that's Francis McDormand I didn't mind that movie but I didn't I when if I saw it by accident
I wouldn't go fuck they should give that award exactly but I didn't mind it while it was on I was like
oh okay yeah it works lamb is on for a little while yeah I didn't get it life of the party
Francis McDormand all right so tell us your fall asleep films I told you mine was zodiac which is why
it's just just just one of them yeah I know I learned the rules back off Joe I have an idea I have an
idea we're at an hour let's just let's just each do three and then and then crawl it and then the
next one computed two I've done two and now he's gonna do it yeah I'm saying then we each do a third
and then we and then the next episode can just be lampoon's vacation and it's a wonderful life
all right I'm good with that all right cool all right I watched alpha dog last night alpha dog that was
a hot movie from what I recall I wasn't causing it a lot when I watched it was a really good movie
that made me feel really sad at the end and I'm not typically the kind of guy to get sad especially
at movies I watch a murder and I go yeah I think a reason they probably deserved it but they they kill
this poor kid at the end because they kidnapped them and they're afraid if they get even though they
were planned on setting them free they feel like if he rats them out they're gonna go to jail right
so the only thing they could do is kill them and they convince them they're not gonna kill them and
then they take them up to the mountains in LA and they start duct taping them and the kid starts to
cry and Justin Timberlake does a ridiculously good performance and he's feeling bad with the kid
and now I'm in bed and I'm sad I want to go wake my son up and just make sure he's okay and I'm like
fuck this movie's really getting me and and then they end up fucking shooting the kid with a machine gun
with an oozy and I was like this is awful and they didn't even try to make it look like I was an
accident they just shot him up and left him there and then they all it was a true story and then they
all end the jail for life so at the end when they're showing you the future I was like this is the
most I don't know if I can go to bed now I have to go watch that thing you do for five minutes just
to cleanse my palate so alpha dog I saw alpha dogs it so who's a male Hirsch I saw when it came out
male Hirsch is the like the thug kid and he owes another kid drug dealer money so there's some
heat between the two of them so the kidnap the guy's brother the guy owes the money to and but
there's a bunch of white thugs from rich part of LA right it's hard or wherever they live one of
those California towns not LA long beach I think yeah some like that and it's just uh it's like no
life that I knew I grew up in New York so I don't know any of that but I felt like that was really what
it was like where they lived I never see bully the Larry Clark movie about a similar thing rough no bully
is great it's a similar thing it's like these kids that kind of team up and kill somebody oh yeah
I think I did I did see that I don't want much more sexual but yes yes yes my favorite aspect of
bully I'm just looking to see what I'm gonna say on the podcast that I made out with Biju Phillips the
star of bully I did okay good I wanted to make sure you all knew that good a note is any to end this
episode on uh we are gonna take after this by the way a max five minute break I'm gonna pee for four
of those five and then we'll come back uh let's have a hand from Mike here a huge round of applause
for Mike thank you and Mike thank you for having me as they say on the as they say on the talk shows
you're welcome to hang around if you want no you got it this man does morning radio he has to be up in
17 minutes yeah do the show doesn't in his living room yeah yeah yeah but if you got to go that's
five but if you want to hang out for a little while longer you're no I'm leaving there's complimentary
water in the great room plenty of water thank you all right don't try to make me responsibly
drink and drive thank you so much for being here I will follow you back on Instagram and we will
be back with a discussion of two Christmas classics Christmas vacation and it's a wonderful life
we will see you next time and we'll see you in hell