Hey folks, it's we'll see you in hell, your podcast, but you like so much when
it's time to get the info about the latest genre pictures in your life. If
you'll pardon me, I'm sounding exasperated. It's doing everything I can to even
breathe in the oxygen at this point anymore. The will to live is so gone that it
feels like an effort to actually keep breathing throughout each day. Holy cow. So let's
start there. I'm happy to start there and I'm with you for the first time in
my life. I'm going on inside of presence. Literally dozens of people have
told me I should be on them, including mental health professionals. And it's
time to listen. I feel depressed. I need help. And there's no shame in it folks. It
doesn't have the stigma attached that it used to. I reached out to Joe. I
says, hey, so you're not supposed to drink on these anti -depressants, right? Joe goes,
I don't know. To be honest, I don't know. Joe's on anti -depressant. He doesn't know.
He's on the things. Let me tell you the so let me tell you the folks. I was going to
save this for the live pods in Chicago, but we'll do it now. The string of text, how
the string of text actually went from Pat. He was over in Scotland and Ireland for
two weeks. Yeah. I get a text from one day, you know, drinking at a bar in Ireland.
Bar tenders given weak pours. This is bullshit. Oh, well, I mean, I want to do an
Ireland Scotland chunk at the live show. That's fine. I won't get into that. All right. Next
text. Found a great bar in Ireland. This was what I was looking for. Awesome. That's
the next day. Yeah. Day after that. Drunk again in Ireland. These guys do it right
or whatever. Next day after that. Joe, I love drinking. I got to tell you I love drinking.
Next day after that. What do you know about these anti -depressants? It's weird that I would
drink a lot of a known depressant for days in a row and then feel depressed afterwards.
But no, it's I was telling Joe, you know, it's always a bad sign when the drugs ain't working,
the drink ain't working. The things you used to turn to are like, nah, you just you're depressed
and I'm like, yeah, all right. I'll get some help. But it better work, baby. I know I'm in
trouble. I want to get them boners. Yeah. And what's the other side effect that you can get?
Lethargy. Lethargy is fun. Lethargy is a side effect for some. Tell you this, if there's
a weight gain element, I'm getting off of them at a scary time. Like, I'll be off them so quickly,
they'll definitely be severe side effects. You got to pick my person. Look, you're going to have
to go through the trial. You might not get the right one first. You might, but you might not.
Should people fucking know at this point? Nobody knows anything. So get this on our own. When
you got to figure that out, my therapist, you know, I pay her some ungodly amount. And she's like,
well, yes, I'm so happy you've decided to get on them. I think they'll help a lot. I'll think
they'll help with your OCD, your spiraling thinking that this is going to be like fine. You know,
it'll be a life changer. And I'm like, great. Fantastic. Let me recommend a couple of pharmacologists.
Like, what? There's another doctor visit and another paycheck that comes out of my pocket. Yeah.
Why don't you do it? Because it's a racket, baby. It's a racket. She's told me a hundred times
which one I should be on. And I'm like, but I know, right? So why don't we go to this guy?
Yeah, you just got to go. And guess who gets a kick back from her every
guy. Sometimes she sends a guy over there. Yeah, it's the mob. Pete Pfizer. I'm just cronies.
I'm just so sick of everything. Everything sucks. Let's get into it, Pat. Sure. I really want to talk
about this fucking commercial I heard on the radio to two things that are pissing me off in this
fucking city this week. All right. If I see one more billboard for pretty little lies
with six women judge mentally staring down at me from Sunset Boulevard with these expressions
that just wreak of, you man. Maybe that's how you're taking their breath. There's six of these
things like in a row. Sunset in your head. It's, it's, whoa. Are they now pretty little liars
I believe was canceled, right? So is this a reboot or big little lies? The Reese Witherspoon thing.
Big ugly truth tellers. Oh, the big little laws. Yeah. There's billboards all the way down Sunset
between here and every club I ever have to go to. It's it's Dern Witherspoon. The awful
lady that was in the descendants that plays the daughter who's always plays a mean person.
Woodland. Yeah. No beef with shaleen. I'm not fed. They're all I like I like Dern and I like
Witherspoon. I forget who else is on the. Oh, rabbits. Not Lenny. The daughters. Oh, he
rabbits. Oh, he craves. It's boring actress. They're all standing on a beach in wool hats.
And they've added stern. I mean, a street. Meryl Street. Meryl's in it. Yeah. And they're all
Staring down with this badass look. Yeah. Judging you the man me personally. Yeah. So that's pissing me off.
That's really pissing me off every day. And then also I'm driving today and I hear a commercial
For rocket man on the radio. The Elton John biopic. They go they go the voice goes
A mesmerizing sensational feat. You've never seen anything like it. Was it Traverse?
It was just the voice over. I don't know who he was quoting. I'm like get the fuck out of my house.
Stupid. I've seen a lot of things like it. Every music biopic that's ever been. You've never seen
anything like it. We're going to tell the story of a musician's life
using his songs. And then the clip and then the clip they play for the movie is is Elton going.
Maybe I just shut it. Ben more normal. And then his friend goes, you've never been normal, mate.
Just fuck off. Yeah. I saw some interview with him. He was like, you know, a lot of studios around town
didn't want to do so much of the sex and drugs. I said, all right. Next. I'm like, yeah, I'm
sure it's going to be the super edgy butt fuck version of Elton John's life. Him face down and
cocaine get reamed from behind. No, it'll be the same thing as bohemian wraps. I saw hard
or sex. I mean entertaining as hell. I love bohemian wraps, but they weren't telling me I was
a mesmerizing feat that I've never seen anything like. That's my new, uh,
falafel store, by the way, bohemian wraps. You're what? My new falafel restaurant is called bohemian wraps.
That would have been a tortilla. I thought it was your rap name. No. No. All right, far
fair enough bohemian wraps. No, it's bohemian wraps. Uh, I thought of a great rap name when I was
in Austin. Now I forget. Oh, Leviathan. That's pretty good. It's good. It's pretty good. He says,
I mean, I wouldn't actually use it. Leviathan, like, like the movie Leviathan, like deep,
deep space. Yeah, I don't know what I'm gonna start. What else would Leviathan be? What's the other
one? Deep star six. Deep star six. The Abyss. Somebody told me somebody told me the other day the Abyss
scared her as a kid. I said, what the fuck are you talking about? I love the Abyss. It's a movie
about like floating water that makes the turns into like a face, isn't it? I can see you getting
scared. And that's seeing where she almost drowned like where they put, they lock them in the water
is, is very claustrophobic. If that's a fear of yours. No, I think it's scared her like the move,
the water, the alien water is scared her. All right, let me tell you what I'm pissed about today.
Coming in hot today. So since Apple decided the only way to listen to, uh, their product is with
these earbuds that do not fit in my ears. The little ear, the earbuds they've been using since the
dawn of iPods. I've never been able to use. I take one step and they fall right out of my ear.
And they've just decided that everyone has to use it as if everyone has the same shaped ears.
So now, and I forget this every time you can't even plug in a pair of headphones and listen to your
iPod. There's no plug. You need the dongle. What's the dongle? I have the attachment if you need one.
I mean, how much of this shit do I got to buy? So I found these things called plantronics
and they, they're like basically clip on the ears, their rubber, their waterproof, which is good
because when I work out, I sweat a lot. I fucking love these things. I put them through the ringer
for three years. They were incredible. And even when they died technically, it's just because
you push a little nub to start them and turn them off. And I had pushed the nub so many times
that it had vanished. So it would have still worked, but I was like, fuck, these things, you know,
about 60 bucks, they're on Amazon. I love them. And the sound I, you know, was like beats by
Dre quality. Rap sounded great. And on the bass was thick. It tuned out. The gym noise, the street
noise, they were the best headphones I ever had. What do they go? Mantronics. Plantronics, which
sounds a bit much like plantation for my taste, but I get on, I buy them again. Now they're up to
$80. I'm like, okay, fine. The design is different. I'm like, that's worrisome. But I read the reviews
and they're like, same old plantronics, shows up at my house. I put them in because I walked over
here today. The sound is about half what it was on the previous model. So over time, maybe it was
noise regulations, because they were probably causing me to go deaf. They just say, let's make a half
as effective product and let's charge $20 more per unit. Why don't you just buy one of the older models?
I look into it, but what I, they're not going to take these back.
See, a lost 80 bucks. It's just maddening. Why change the recipe now, you know? Because nobody is
on your side. Get it through your fucking head. I'm walking over here. I'm like, I couldn't even hear
the music. I'm like, I guess I'll just listen to fucking birds. I have a gift for you here.
Got you this in Austin, Texas. Waterloo records. Well, thank you very much. I've never seen this.
It's the Frightenite 2 Blu -ray. Frightenite 2 is out of print ever since it was released in this
country. You can't get it. Waterloo gets it exclusively from the official Mexican release. So the entire
Blu -ray box is in Spanish, but the movies in English. And is it going to work in my player?
It'll work in your player. Thank you very much. You're way to watch. Never seen it.
It's not a great flick. It's goofy and fun in the way Pet Cemetery 2 is, as you said.
You know, it's, but it's nice bragging rights on your shelf. People don't have that fucking movie.
I appreciate that, Joe. Yeah. They were two there. I bought one for me and one for you. Left the
price tag on. It's kind of a dick -slap model. Just so you know what went into it. More than your
average DVD. $567 for that Blu -ray. No, I'll watch it tonight. Maybe you will. We're gonna hang out
for a little bit. We're hanging out. You know, we're hanging out. I'm in a bad way, Pat. Don't you
say? I'm here. I'm drinking a gruel. So that's fucking delicious. I'm drinking a this is taller than
your average beer, right? That's like a pint. Yes. I got used to pints over there. I like a pint. What
have been good if they had a yogi beer? Like a yogi bear? Like it was called the yogi beer.
The yogi bear was on it and then it said taller than your average beer. You've ever,
because his thing was smarter than your average bear. A couple extra ounces. Yeah. Yeah. That'd be great.
I always miss my boat. There's still time. Day late dollar short as usual. They just made a movie
years ago with everybody's favorite sweetheart, TJ Miller. Yes. Yeah. Yeah. Talk about when I would have
liked to I went to see that picture in opening night. Talk about a time I would have liked TJ to call
on a bomb threat. Folks. Yeah. I thought maybe you're gonna say the picture was a bomb was another way
to go. No. I like that. I would have liked the theater to have cleared out from a bomb threat. Yeah.
I wanted to see it. The day it came out, but I are what was the old David's paid joke. I blew it
already. It was, uh, you know what's weird? They used to have I used to be. I liked it the first
side. We got it. It was called candy. Shit. No. It was a Hollywood minute thing. And he's like,
I was about mixed nuts. I said, fellow SNL legacy. And a funny. And a sandwich in that. Yeah.
But he goes, I want, uh, yeah. I think that's what it was. It was like two old SNL greats had a movie come
out mixed nuts. I wanted to go see it, but I was sick that day. Very funny. Spayed to me if I mean,
he's the only it was one of the few worth following on Instagram. The man I see him and I smile. I like
that a man can just be like that old and lonely and seemingly very happy. It just makes me smile.
There's a great TMZ TMZ clip where they talked to him about when Louie did that set and everybody
was mad about the audio that leaked. Don't talk about. Yeah. And he's like, uh, they go,
do you have any thoughts of that? And he's like, Hey, you know, man, um, people deserve a second chance.
And, uh, you know, I try to be forgiving. Um, you know, look, I'd love to stay here and talk longer and
stepping it myself toward my own career, but I got to go. I mean, that's the perfect answer.
It's like, no, I don't want to talk to you about this. There's no positive that can come from it.
Uh, folks, all right. Were you, did you have more to bitch about? I'm sure you did.
Or should I take us to the movie corn? Um, by the way, folks, yeah, no, I have one more thing to
bitch about. All right. I post about this in Instagram the other day. Folks, as you know, Joey D,
pro hell, hell a pro choice. Hell a pro choice. This guy, real quick, because I just thought a one.
Let's get on with the show and on with, uh, Joey D's, help me, Joey D's, help me, help me.
Maybe that's the new twist. Did you say Joey D instead of Joe?
Was that Bruce Orons B? Yeah, but maybe that's the thing is now you rhyme it with Joey D.
All right. What is he actually singing? Follow follow me?
And then a Veechi did that too, I think before he died. Who the fuck is a Veechi?
There's an EDM artist who killed himself. I thought it was a sharp cheese.
He's like just killed himself. Oh, just now. I don't know. Sorry. I thought you met like 20 years
ago. Look, I don't know much about the man, but, uh, I don't think we got to be making sharp cheese
jokes. I didn't know that it was a recent trap. Sorry. The folks, if you are a suicidal reach out to
a, a helpline. Um, I want to look, I'm, I'm pro choice than a motherfucker as they say. Yeah.
But this is driving me nuts. Canada banned this unexpected movie about it's a biopic
about the lady that worked at Planned Parenthood and then got upset overseeing an abortion one day
and became super pro life. Oh god. So they made a movie about her. Was it a faith -based release?
Kind of. It's released by that thing called Pure Flicks. Sure. Yeah. Which weirdly, you know who does
tons of Pure Flicks stuff now? Ted McGinley, they got to play Jefferson on, on married with children.
People say he's killed more pilots than 9 -11. I've heard that. Anyway, so they make a biopic about
this movie or what? Maybe I should have said Pearl Harbor. Yeah. Or World War two. You
would have heard. I don't know. He's just a guy who's, I think he's had like 30 failed pilots.
But he, but anyway, so they make this biopic about this lady. If you cast a me ruined the show.
Uh, you know, I'm not interested in the story, but hey, tell your story. I don't give a shit.
And if people want to see it great, Canada bans it or so that they were the entire country
refused to show because they go, no, these abortions lately here and we don't believe in this. It's like,
yeah, you know what else? I don't believe in Hitler. You still show the Hitler biopic at the
fucking Cineplex. You don't not show a movie because you don't agree with the fucking message behind it.
Just show the fucking movie. If somebody wants to say it, they'll say it and if they don't, then they don't.
But for an entire country, that's crazy. I agree. That's fucking crazy, man. I can understand a couple
comps, you know, certain movie houses. I agree. I want to know what Cineplex is showing this
Hitler biopic. It was, I heard Channing Tatum is excellent as the Führer. Folks, it's called,
it's called the Führer in the Führer. It's a hot, it's a hot somba dance flick. Oh, okay. It's a
retelling through somba music of Hitler's life story. And I have heard that Mila Kunis is excellent
as Eva Brown. Yeah, there's wife. Yeah. And there's there's a gag that keeps going through the
flick where he goes, you know, honey, I'd really love it if you changed the last name from Brown.
And then she goes, it's brawn you idiot. Yeah, they do that through the entire flick.
Well, I mean, it needed a little bit of comic relief, I would say. Yeah. Well, you know, Seth
Rogen produced it. Yeah, you know, I mean, Jonah Hill as the, the Jewish accountant, he'd be friends
who changed his mind about Jews. I thought, I thought he did a nice job. Jonah Hill plays the camp.
I'm losing concentration on this bit, concentration camp.
There you go. All right, let's go on down to your favorite place, but concentration camp.
Movie corner, the movie corner. I mean, again, I've seen so many things. I'd love to shout out
easily, easily, the biggest laughs that I have had in this miserable year, the absolutely hilarious
sketch show on Netflix. I think you should leave with Tim Robinson. Very funny show. Have you watched
the whole thing? I've watched a bunch of the sketches, uh, disjointedly on the internet and stuff,
but I, it's, I find it very funny. Please sit down and watch the episodes. Holy shit. I mean,
there's so, so few duds in the mix. I watched it once. The night it came out, howled laughing. I showed
it again to my wife on vacation. She howled laughing. We watched it as we woke up on our one -year
anniversary. By the way, um, Tim Robinson was so beyond wasted on Saturday Night Live. Surprise,
surprise. I don't remember him doing anything funny on that show. Wait, wait, what? He was on SNL.
Tim Robinson from Shashank. That's Tim Robinson. Who's Tim Robinson?
He's the guy we're talking about, the sketch show. I think you should leave. Oh, waste. I thought you
meant Tim Robinson had hosted SNL and was drunk the whole time. The hell are you talking about?
I thought you were saying this show was better than SNL and that this previous week,
Tim Robbins was the host and was drunk. And I was like, really?
Tim Robinson, the star of the show. I didn't know what his name was. He was wasted, meaning not
used. Completely not utilized properly on SNL. As most people are not used properly. Correct.
He went on and did Detroiters, which I thought was hilarious. And this really lets the man shine.
Every joke is just like, you know, it's got the weird comedy, the broad comedy.
My one complaint on a second viewing is there's a lot of shit jokes. I would say kind of an outrageous
amount of shit jokes, a lot of talk about shitting. And some of it is extremely funny. But
that would be my one note. You know, the amount of times the man talks about mud pies or making mud
or whatever else. I got it. But sketch comedy, I mean, I don't even remember the last truly great one
that came down the pike. This is some real funny shit and I hope they do another season. Watch it.
I watched, well, I picked up a box set and I strongly suggested, usually I would save this for
scary stuff, but I actually want to talk about some of the movies in the movie corner and I'll do
something else for scary stuff. But there's a great box set out. It's by Arrow. And it's called
the American Horror Project Journal or excuse me, the American Horror Project volume one. It comes
with a booklet called the American Horror Project Journal. Anyway, volume one is out, volume two is about
to be released. But each set is three movies and they are essentially unsung, sort of masterpieces
from the horror genre. Be it a grind house thing that sort of slipped through the cracks or
something that deserved a little more critical recognition that it ever got or whatever. So this
first one is putting it together, just the Arrow curators. And I got to say Arrow is given scream
of run for their fucking money, dude. I fucking love Arrow stuff. They do sales pretty regularly and I got
an amazing haul recently. I would advise though that you just make sure you're getting one that
works in your DVD player because about a fourth of their titles are British only. But I mean,
look at this box. I think it's gorgeous. I've gotten some amazing, amazing shit from them.
You can pick up this set right now for about 45 bucks on Amazon. I highly recommend it. The first
movie I'll review today, I'm going to review two of these today from this set because I haven't gotten
to the third yet. But the first one is Malatesta's Carnival of Blood which is an old grind house flick.
It's about a carnival in Willow Grove, Pennsylvania right near where I grew up.
And it was shot in an actual shittium amusement park in Willow Grove that I probably had gone to a
one point as a kid. And it's basically for some reason, this guy has an underground layer of
these zombie -like ghouls that feast on human flesh. And he kills people that come into the carnival
and he feeds them to the ghouls. It doesn't really make a lot of sense. I mean, he said for some reason,
there's no reason given in the movie. They never really explain why he's going out of his way to
feed these ghouls or what they're there to do other than just eat the people.
Is it like, is he helping them so they don't eat him? Does he like it?
No, no, he plays like the devil is in it at one point. It's all sort of devil run.
It's a little, no, no. The devil is actually in it is played by, oh wait, no, that's a different
movie. I'm sorry. The devil is Malatesta, I believe, in this film. The character Malatesta.
Malatesta is not the filmmaker. That's what I thought it first. The evil guy is Malatesta in the film.
Okay. Anyway, it's sort of like a fever dream. It's very, if you ever saw the first copula flick,
what's that first copula movie conversation? No, no, no, no. It's first rain people.
No, the horror movie that he did, oh, dementia, it's very dementia 13, it's very carnival of souls.
You know, it's very, it's a weird dark sort of genre piece. It's got some really creepy cinematography in
it. It's very low budget, but it's very enjoyable. And look, you throw this on a Saturday night and
you have a couple drinks and some popcorn with it, you're not going to have a bad time.
All right. Do you have popcorn with movies? I don't know. I've banned it from my home.
But you're just colloquially saying maybe you were home. Yeah, I don't like popcorn.
Fine with it. It's pretty tasteless. My mom made a huge bowl every night, every night.
And I think she uses like an appetite suppressant or something.
I love that as a kid. My dad had one of those old school popcorn poppers. Yeah.
And he'd make it on like Friday and Saturday night for me and him and my mom. There's something fun
about it. It was very fun when you're little and you know, and your dad putting the salt in the butter
on it. Sure. And you get older and you realize it's not sex or drugs and you don't want it anymore.
That's Taylor's oldest time. Folks, I watched season two of the critically acclaimed,
some would say outrageously acclaimed Amazon Prime series called Fleabag, which was also a BBC show.
I think I mentioned the first season. It is. I mean, that's the frustrating thing is
you watch these reviews and you're like, come on. And generally you watched the thing and you're like,
oh yeah, this fucking suck. Fleabag is that, I mean, this woman is just a tremendously gifted writer
and director. She does the whole thing. Phoebe Waller bridge. Although, let me check, it may be
Bridger or Bridges, but I think I'm right. I only saw her name 15 times in the credits every week.
Phoebe Waller bridge. I was right. The first season was really about this woman fucking her way through
London and was just like very honest and refreshing and dark and funny. This season, I would say just
as funny, just as dark. It's all about a sexual attraction she has to appreased. And it much more
follows just one relationship throughout all six episodes. You'll watch the thing in an afternoon.
It's less than three hours to watch the whole series. Just beautifully written stuff,
beautifully acted stuff, every bit part shines. You see all these great British actors excel,
including Olivia Coleman who just won the Oscar and from Peep show as well. It's a hell of a show.
I recommend it. Check it out. All right, film two from the box that I'll review is
the witch who came from the sea. I gotta tell you, people. They made a movie about my ex -wife.
Oh, I didn't say the witch who wouldn't go to the kitchen. Folks. Talk about a movie
that went from being a movie I had never even heard of to one of my favorite movies I've ever seen.
Good Lord. In one watch. What's it called again? The witch who came from the sea. All right.
But it's about a woman named Molly who this is how the film opens. Beautiful, beautiful, extreme
wide of a beach with the title card up and in the waves crashing in and the music playing. It's very
seventies. You know, very haunting, 1970s, whatever. And then this woman comes walking along with two
children and they're having a lovely time and it's all very sweet and whatever. And they squat down and
sort of set up shop near some workout equipment on the beach and there are these large football player
type men working out on the equipment. Okay. And the woman starts looking at them and you start seeing
all of her extremely morbid death fantasies about all of them. This is how it begins. Okay, so you're
like, okay, she's got some going on here. What's going on? Yeah. And slowly it unfolds from there.
There's see which ain't right. You know, there's tension between her and her sister over their father
who has died. You find out where that is later. There's a very long scene where she is seducing two football
players in a bedroom and they're all on drugs. And it is, I'd be shocked if this was not the
inspiration for the mushroom scene in Mandy. Okay. Very similar. Okay. Very, very similar.
Basically, as this movie unfolds, you learn more about her sailor father who has passed
and what his relationship to her was. And you see her going on a slew of sort of sexual encounters
that turn violent. And it's very American psycho. Like she kills the people. At first, it's very
American psycho where you're not sure if she's imagining it or not. And it goes from there. It's
beautifully shot. I will say I thought the decision to have her sailor father actually be
Popeye the sailor man was wild. Right. It took me out of the film. Right. Right. I mean, she comes home
like that. I've done something terrible. And he's going, uh, it took me out of the picture. Right.
It was directed by Matt climber. It was directed a bunch of genre films, including the candy tangerine man.
That sounds like he might have enjoyed the occasional talk. Yeah. He was also the co -creator of
glow wrestling. Okay. I wonder. Is he the guy Mark Marenblas? In the show. No, no, I look that up. He's
not. Uh, he's, he was married to the woman who, no, no, I'm sorry. The guy that wrote the movie was
married to the female lead in the movie. Uh, Matt climber was, uh, or Simber, excuse me, not climber,
Simber was Jane Mansfield's final husband. Never understand when you're writing a film where your wife
has sex with a bunch of dudes. Well, Robert Thome wrote the film. Yeah. I'm not sure what else he
wrote, but it stars Millie Perkins who played Anne Frank and the diary van Frank. The rich. Yes. Great
film. Uh, she was also old Annie grew up. She was also in at close range. She was in Wall Street.
She was in Necronomicon. Uh, it's just a, you got to see this flick, man. It's, it's, it's, it's
a amazing, amazing movie. And again, it is very clearly an influence on the, you know, the, the,
the hereditaries and the, uh, the, the, the mandies and the, the modern harm in the harm movies of that
ilk. I'm definitely going to check it out. I, uh, will be buying from Arrow. They have a new
16 candles and a new weird science. So when I buy those, I'll throw this in my cart. What's on the
weird science? I'm interested in that. The features were as yet unannounced, but I think it comes out
like next week. So I should check again. Uh, I'd love it if they could track down why it
because every release they do when they do like a retrospective, why it's never there.
An Anthony Michael home. One of them is like, why, wherever you are, man, we love you. Charles
Martin Smith, they couldn't get him. Charles McKenzie Smith. He never, he's like, nobody knows
what Elon, Michael Smith, they know he's alive. That's all they know. Right. But like, he's way out
of show business. Huh, I get that. I mean, anytime somebody leaves show business, A, thank you,
more jobs for the rest of us. And B, I definitely understand. Yeah. Uh, Elon Mitchell Smith,
I think I actually eventually stumbled that actual name out. I love the man didn't act much.
I'll check out your sea witch movie. Yep. The witch who came out of the sea. The witch who came
from the sea came from the sea. Not really about a witch. And the lady didn't come out of the sea,
but it's a metaphorical title. I'd like to make a movie about when my parents would take me on
vacation while I was going through puberty called the boy who came into the sea. Yeah. I used to
swim out and jack off into the ocean. There was a time when, you know, there were people like the great
Norman Lear making television in this country. Now it's pigs like you. I was gonna do that as the third,
my third one will be the Woody Harrelson. Let's do it. Let's talk about it. Uh, I, yes.
I watched both of them. The, hey, I've never seen the Jefferson's, which I know is crazy. I've
only seen little clips. Every clip I see of it is hilarious. Sherman Helmsley is hilarious. Yeah.
That seemed to be a pretty big mess fire to me. I thought Jack A was great. Uh, I become friendly
with Jack A from doing cool kids love. She is the best human being and she has every bit as funny
in real life. I thought she kind of lit up the Jefferson's, but the rest of it was boring. They didn't
pick a great episode. Farrell was, was funny when he came out and their little story was funny.
But, uh, the only family I thought was way more successful. I liked Woody. I like Marissa Tomei who
kind of stole the show. I liked Juan de Sikes. Jamie Foxx comes in immediately messes up his first
line like he's Jimmy Fallon. Yeah, that was the thing with the audience. Come on. Actually, they
cut over to Juan de Sikes and she was looking at him like, I'm not laughing motherfucker. Yeah, it's,
it's terrible. It's like get through the thing. Yeah. It's, you know, but, uh, um, you're there to,
you know, pay tribute to these led. Yeah, it's ridiculous. But, uh, uh, Jamie Foxx bugs me.
Me too. But, uh, I thought Juan de Sikes was great as weasy. Uh, she was. Look, the problem with the
Jefferson's episode is, and this annoyed me, you're going to make this big show out of, look guys,
this is a time when we could use humor to address our problems and the ugliest parts of ourselves.
And you pick a Jefferson's episode that room that hinges on the N word. And then you bleep it.
Yeah. I, it's like, what are you, what are you doing? I didn't get the choice. Like,
obviously there are 500 Jefferson's episodes don't center around the N word.
And it's like, and if you're going to pick that one to prove the point, then prove the point.
Don't half -ass it. Right. Yeah, it was weird. It was weird. It was, um, it was like a celebration of
free speech and then they didn't do it. Not that I have an absolute theory about this ABC thing.
Yes. I, I am 100 % because, because the, the, Roseanne stuff started to bubble up again because she's now
selling out theaters and stuff and starting to go around. Yeah. Is it all Trump ads?
I have no idea. But she's starting to come around again and sell tickets and move tickets. James
Gunn got rehired. Roseanne's son. Look, I'm happy that James Gunn got rehired. But Roseanne's son
rightfully so came out and read his tweets. And I was like, yeah, the kids got a point, you know,
an offensive joke is an offensive joke. So my, my theory is this was a very big gesture on ABC's part
to try to cover their asses for destroying Roseanne. I think that's what they did. What's the
difference between an off -color joke she makes on Twitter and an off -color joke Archie Bunker makes
in a, in a, in a sitcom. It's still a distasteful joke. Any way you slice it, right? Yeah, but he's
a character and she's a human being. So that's the difference. I get that. I get that. But I don't think
their stance when that happened was something's just aren't funny. Sure. There are jokes you don't make.
And then they do a whole special that revolves around. It's, they were apparently at the live show saying
it's okay to laugh at these jokes. They're just jokes. It's like it's a little suspect. That's all
I'm saying. It's a little weird. It certainly is. But I, I enjoyed what I saw of it. I thought it was
fun. It was certainly fun. And apparently it was a big hit and they're going to keep doing them.
The talent they brought in I thought was pretty impressive. And I thought by and large people did a
great job. Harrelson terribly miscast. Said like he was doing a cockney accent at times. Very
strange choice. And yet he worked for me. He worked fun. Should have been Brad Garrett. That part
should have been Brad Garrett. Everybody loves it. You know, it'll also be a good Archie bunker,
except he can't get rid of that accent as Jervace. Jervace would be a great bunker. Sure. Uh, you know,
and Harrelson, he, it's not that it was too cartoonish though. He was like, he'd be like, well,
you go. Yeah, it's silly. Well, it's certainly a testament to how men aged differently,
even 30, 40 years ago, because I didn't look it up, but I can almost guarantee what he Harrelson is
probably older than Carol O 'Connor was when he did Archie bunker. Yeah. And he looked like a child.
Yeah. Uh, even though he's bald and everything else, like old men back then all looked like old
men at age, the day they turned 50, they were handed an old man card. Carol O 'Connor. Carol O 'Connor,
I did look it up. He was 31 when he was cast in the right now. Yeah. Come on. Yeah. What do you
Harrelson was no, uh, O 'Connor? I don't know. Tomay was unbelievable. Tomay was really good. Uh, I
enjoyed, uh, I enjoyed Anderson. Again, though, yeah, let's be honest. Let's, let's, let's, let's
I'm not throwing him under the bus, but has had some stuff act leveled against him that is far
worse than an off -color joke on Twitter. I've been, and the choice of putting him in this was very
strange to me. Not only that, he's been the lead of Blackish for six years, one of their biggest
comedies, and it's just like he's one of the guys who everyone's like, all right, we won't talk about
that one. So look, I'm not, and Joe, if I may, why did you tell him to do what he did? The guy's always
saying you're not, I'm not saying how you should feel about Roseanne. I'm just saying it's a little
suspect when ABC, some of the moves they made with this product. It's a little, it's a little weird.
Agreed. Um, anyway, uh, that's, well, yeah, let me, let me do one here. Well, that was the one.
That was the final one we did it together. Yeah, that was, I just want to check one more off.
All right. Was it killing you? I'm going to make another drink. All right. Uh, folks, I,
watched, you know what I'd like to talk about? You know what I'd like to talk about is a little
picture called, wait for it, skin deep. Joe, you ever see skin deep?
Um, I read it. Yeah, he said he read it as a kid. He got up sexy. It was too dirty. Uh, it is
one of the few adult sex comedies. I mean, like Blake Edwards basically made them
10 and all those movies for decades. He made adult sex comedies. At some point, all anybody wanted
was teenager sex comedies. And you rarely see outside of, you know, the Appetite Camp 40 -old
Virgin, whatever. They're a dying breed. It just made me realize how much I kind of missed them.
Skin deep is a pretty funny fucking movie. And it's one of the few true starring roles and showcases
for the great late John Ritter, who has stolen so many movies. Two of my favorite supporting roles
of his, his amazing and funny dramatic work in slingblade where he manages to earn your affection
with the worst haircut in movie history. And also his so funny performance in bad Santa with Bernie
Mac, those scenes are probably the highlight of one of the best comedies of all time. I've never
agreed with you on the, I grew with you on the slingblade. I've never agreed with you on the uh,
Santa clause one. Uh, you don't like him in that movie. No, I don't think he's bad. I just think he's
out of all the characters. He's the most forgettable to me. I just think him and Bernie Mac together is
Bernie Mac. The funniest part of the movie. Bernie Mac with the orange is masterful. Yeah.
The fact that the man figured out like I can peel and eat an orange here and somehow make it look
insanely sinister. But I think it's Ritter A letting him do all that orange bit. Yes.
And just holding his ground and every reaction you get from him is giving you an extra laugh.
Yeah. He plays it perfectly. I wouldn't say he steals the movie though.
What do you, there's to me, there's scenes of the highlight. All right. But when he says, uh,
you're wrong, but you know, when he says, look, you fuck that woman in the ass. They cut over to Ritter
and he goes, you know, that wins. I mean, hilarious, hilarious stuff. Uh, but any who John Ritter rarely
starred in a film, he starred in Skin Deep. He's so great and charming and funny and a believable
romantic lead and his physical comedy is incredible, which is what he was known for. But Blake Edwards gives
him some like masterful Peter Sellers type. Like true set pieces that you rarely see just
great silent physical comedy. Uh, the most famous scene of the picture is him with a glow in the
dark condom. He comes into the room and you see like a boner walking around the room. That's the only
scene I remember. It was a very famous scene. Uh, the movie was a hit. And it was right before kind
of the problem child decline started. Uh, some would say I fucking love problem child one answer.
But when I went out on a bang, my wife, uh, Barry, my kids or whatever that was that show called.
It was my daughter. Ten simple rules for dating my team. That's what it is. Okay. No, the man works
right until the end. But Skin Deep, I think is a very lost film. It's very hard to find. I randomly
saw it on Amazon Prime. And I was like, how many times did I walk past this video box and wonder what
the dirty, I think they actually taped a like a sticker of a condom on the front of it. And I asked
mom what it was. And she got so visibly shaken that I was like, I knew it must be a filthy movie.
And it's pretty dirty. Uh, a lot of nudity. And, uh, you know, it feels super 80s. But I loved it.
I recommended highly check it out. Uh, scary stuff. You know what? I'm going to skip scary stuff
into a screaming end instead today. Screaming end. Is it about, uh, well for two quick ones. First of
all condolences to John Singleton. That's very sad that he was passed a while ago at this point.
But it's sad. And on the last one, you know, I, I made a very, uh, off -color joke about him
that I regret it because I knew he was going to die. But the whole point of that segment was to pay
tribute to a man that I was really pulling for. And still, it throws me that I had randomly watched
three of his movies the day before this happened. But an absolutely amazing talent gone too soon.
Check out those movies. I mentioned great places to start. Boys in the hood. Higher learning.
Baby boy. For me, the three classics. Uh, yeah. So shout outs to John Singleton and his family.
You're in our thoughts. Absolutely. Uh, that's a bummer, man. That's very sad. Um, I want to talk about.
51. Jesus Christ. Yeah. Um, it's brutal. Another quick one. Hateful eight is coming back to Netflix.
Recut. It's already mini series. It's already back. I've heard there's almost no difference.
No, but I got excited for a minute. I was like, yeah, I'd watch them. That basically,
they were like, hey, if we put this thing up as six half hours, I bet people would watch it and
think it's a new series. But somebody did the math and there's like one additional minute or something.
All right. Uh, last is, uh, Sonic the Hedgehog trailer. Uh, again, we're a little behind on this one
because we haven't done a show in a while. But can you believe this shit? These fucking baby
fans complained to a fucking point that the studio apologizing goes in and changes the goddamn.
This is up there with the unexpected abortion movie thing. What the fuck is going on right now?
This to me is genuinely insane. Uh, all these people bitching. We're probably not going to see the
fucking movie anyway. And bitching that they didn't like the way he looked. And then, so then they
go and change it. They apologize. And then they were going to redo the whole movie. Like what's
since I was a little kid, I was like, what could be cooler sexier than making a movie? And these guys
just somehow fuck it up again and again. There is nothing less cool than filmmakers. And I know it's
the Sonic the Hedgehog movie. I don't care. Filmmakers going, oh, the people think our design is bad. I
should be your vision in the movie you want to make. You should be proud of it. Happy with it.
You shouldn't be able to be swayed by these people. It's absurd. And they're not going to like the
new design either. They're going to sink a hundred million into it and people be like, yeah, this sucks.
It's Sonic. Sonic. Yeah, no, it's just setting a terrible precedent for everything. Everything.
What is happening? That one, you know, especially if it had been a movie I cared about, I'd give more
of a shit, but it did seem like really just the final nail of the coffin. Anyway, let's get on to,
or by the way, shout outs will be posted as a separate file this month. I was just going to tack
them on to the end of this episode, but then the people who only pay five dollars wouldn't get to
hear them. And that's not fair. So shout outs will be an additional bonus download for this month.
But until then, also we would like to apologize. We were thrown by the Justin Long thing. We were
basically asked, hey, would you do a quick ad like we always do ads? Great. Joe records a little thing.
I'm a fan of Justin Long. Check out his new podcast. Suddenly a new episode of our show is released
after we just told everyone we're going on hiatus called introducing the Justin Long podcast.
And we found out that like every show on the network was being asked to chill for a man whose podcast
is immediately going to have a million followers anyway. Well, look, I have no check out. We do like
Justin Long, but the release of it as a new episode felt shitty to me. I didn't like it. I'll say this.
I have no problem with the fact that we plugged it. We were paid to plug it and we're our fans
of Justin Long. So I had no problem with that. And they did say to us guys, even though you're not doing
a new episode, we could still put the ad in the feed. And I don't think I fully grasp what that meant.
What I didn't like, what I didn't like was it wasn't just the ad in our feed. It wasn't the ad
attached to an old episode, which I thought maybe would have been the case or something like that.
It was the ad by itself automatically getting downloaded by our fans
with a five minute snippet from his show on it. And I didn't think that that was right.
And I thought that that should have been properly explained. And maybe help us by putting us on the
Justin Long. Well, we would have to pay. He's clearly paid for ads at my point, which is fine.
And when you say paid, that's actually not true as of yet. I assume we'll be paid, but we will be
paid. But it's my point is, is that was a paid plug. Find nothing wrong with that.
We agreed to do it. And again, we agreed that it would go into the feed. I didn't know that it was
going to be in there though. As again, this, it was like when you got the YouTube album,
right, the YouTube album with the iTunes. And it was like, I didn't, I didn't ask for this.
I don't think people were more furious or anything, but I was a little embarrassed by it. So we apologize.
Our picture today is John Wick three, Colin, Parabellum. It's Parabellum, Mr.
Wick. I had completely forgotten that that was the title. I thought was John to John Wick two,
have a, Colin? No. John Wick three. No, it was just, remember, he says that. He goes, it's complete
pyramid. Is Parabellum like madness? It's like all out war, all out war. Okay. Yeah.
Look, John Wick one took me by surprise in almost as much away as the matrix did. I mean,
obviously it wasn't his groundbreaking, but it was another Kiana Reeves experience where he's a guy
who just, you can't help it lower your expectations a little bit. When you go to see a Kiana Reeves picture,
you're like, ah, whatever, you know, and I love the man for years, but you lower your expectations
a little bit. The matrix tore the roof off, obviously. And John Wick was the same way. I mean, the,
people loved that fucking movie could not tell you how much fun I had watching it in the theater.
John Wick two, I remember being like, this felt a little like they rushed it out. I had fun,
but I wasn't as impressed. And John Wick three, I would say, is one perfect half hour that
really exceeds the original John Wick. And I'm talking like around the time where they're having
the fight in the knife store, which is the best fight in five years that I've seen in a movie.
It was a, it was a fight where every punch, every knife throw made me laugh out loud.
Like I just couldn't believe how cool, how amazing the stunts were. But the problem is it
peaks too early. That half hour is really the first half hour. It is so exciting and so good.
And the rest is just chasing it and not getting there. They go too far into the mythology of this
assassin hotel. I do not care about the specifics of the assassin hotel. I do not really understand
them. And I don't care that I don't understand. Back up for a second. Sure.
Because we're charging right into what we didn't like because I'm not disagreeing with anything you're
saying. But first of all, just a synopsis of the film, it picks up the second, the last movie ends.
John is running for his life in New York. The entire, what seems to be the entire city of New York is
populated with assassins. Everybody that lives there, apparently, is an assassin is trying to kill him.
And he's got to get away. He committed the ultimate sin. He killed somebody on company grounds
at the end of the second movie inside the continental hotel. That is forbidden. He is labeled X
Communicado, which means he's out on all sides and he's a free target for anybody to kill, right?
With a huge price on his head, $15 million or something. And every hour that goes by that they don't
kill him, the price goes up. They have like beautiful models updating the price on his head,
which is like a weird touch. Yeah, that's that's a kind of a fun little sequence, like the little
the price room. Yeah, where it's like all the wordly tattooed pierced people. And then I like that
Robin Blancon is last name from Gotham is in there is like the sort of, sort of curator guy,
whatever you want to call him, the guy that plays the penguin. So that's the plot of the movie.
So you start from this place of he's committed the cardinal sin of this line of work.
What is he going to do? And they say right off the bat, Ian McShane goes, I'd say the odds of 50, 50, right?
Like they they they clearly set up like he's got more than a fighting chance here to get through this.
Ian McShane, by the way, fabulous as always. What a what a delight to have in any movie. I cannot wait
for the Deadwood movie this weekend. There's a huge poster on sunset that says it for Deadwood and it says
welcome the fuck back. Yeah, I saw that. Yeah. Pretty good. You watched Deadwood. No, you'd love it. It's terrific.
Sure. I've heard. And you also haven't seen six feet under you haven't seen the the jewels. I've seen six feet.
HBO crown. Okay. I like six feet under. All right. It's a great ending six feet. Fragile rock. I love
Fragile rock. Anyway, for some reason my internet stopped working anyway. So how is he going to get out
of this? He's got a fighting chance. How's it going to do it? And as Pat said, you know, the first, you know,
30 to 45 minutes of this thing is basically what you'd expect. It's him getting cornered by different
people that are trying to kill him and him very creatively killing his way out of it creatively. But
like, it's worth a step back to talk about the creativity of these choreographers. I mean, like it's amazing.
Just beautiful fight work. The horse fights. The horse stable scene to me was a man. That was the
horses as his weapons basically. I've never seen that before. Anytime in this day and age, you can
show me something I've never seen before in an actual movie. More power to you. That was the best part
to me. More traditional knife fight was just to me the highlight of the movie. It was unbelievable.
So it goes, you know, it all is building towards this place of the first under the first hour. He's
got to get out of the city. They make that abundantly clear. He needs to get the fuck out of New York. Yeah.
He has one chance to do this. It's by using his marker from the second movie. You find out the value
of that marker, which is he goes and trades it to Angelica Houston who's a new character who plays a
sort of Russian mob boss who who's front is a ballet theater. So I thought that was pretty cool.
Always good to see her. Yeah. Yeah. And I liked that they were bringing like the Russian mob into it,
but they were sort of separate from the other. Like I thought that was cool. Anyway,
so he gets this pass to go to to to Casablanca and to to leave and you think like
that's his goal. He's got to get to Casablanca. So I think now, okay, the rest of this movie is
going to be him trying to get to fucking Casablanca alive. Right. And then once he crosses the line
there, you know, the borderline, it's like you can't touch him or whatever it is.
Next scene, he's in Casablanca. And then he's like, well, now I got to go see this guy.
And he meets up with Halle Berry and he's like, I need you to take me to see this guy. And she's
like, okay. And she take, well, not at first. Of course, she hates him too and wants to kill him
like everybody else. And then she takes him to see the guy he needs to see. And then that guy tries
to kill them. So then they kill that guy and all his people. And then they're like, well,
now we're really fucked. And you're like, you were already really fucked. What what happened here?
Right. And then it's like, I thought that that Halle Berry section really dragged because it just didn't
go any way. Wasn't advancing the plot in any way. And it wasn't that cool, really. And I felt,
I felt kind of bad. I didn't feel bad for him. She's playing a part in a movie. But I mean,
you know, she's in there. And I'm like, this character has no purpose in this film. Like this is just
not a lot to work with. So anyway, so then they, you know, they go and they kill the other
the other guy and they go, now when they were really in trouble. And you go, again, you were,
you're already really in trouble. And then they go, well, now we got to get, now we got to get a
blessing from this guy. Now who's the head head guy? They keep kind of going up this ladder.
Right. And you're like, it just never stops. Like every time he fucks up with somebody,
there's another layer above that person that goes, no, if you now get the concession from this
guy, then that means what you did to that guy is okay. At one point near the end, he's actually
walking up a like Donkey Kong style, almost like a stair system. And it looks like a video game.
Like it's super neon. And it just looks very much like a game. And I thought, well, really,
that's what I'm watching at this point is a guy beating boss after boss, like it's Mike Tyson's
punch out. And at some point that just loses its appeal. And the hundreds by the end of, you know,
nameless Asian guys who attack John Wick, it does kind of get a little deadening. And the movie had
no right being 215. And it felt 215. It didn't, you don't care enough about the mythology to keep
the plot wheels spin until the end. You just don't. That's the other thing too is halfway through
this thing. This woman from the high table, who supposedly is the, you know, in the first, in the
second film, they told you that the continental was the be all end all. You can't kill a man on a company
property. Now in this movie, they're going, no, it's not the continental. It's the high table.
The high table controls all the strings of everything everywhere all the time constantly, right? So you
okay, great. So then he, so now he's pissed off the high tables. Now a lady from the high table is
like, you know, kill John Wick. And then she brings in another assassin who doubles, who nightlights
as a sushi, sushi chef, for some reason. That, uh, that stuff did not work. And he's also stupidly
comedic, like stupidly comedic, accurate. Yes. And a lot of like eyebrow raising and thumbs up to
John. And it's, it's, yeah, like literally like in the middle trying to kill him. He'll be like,
it's really cool to meet you, by the way. Like it's, it's pretty stupid. Yeah. But, um, but anyway,
um, she brings that guy in now to kill it. And you're like, what, what is fucking happening right now?
Like, who were all these people? How are they all connected? Anyway, it ends back at the continental.
Ian McShane has refused to step down from his post as he was instructed to
forgiving John Wick an hour to get away before putting out the ex -communicado hit on him. Right.
He's instructed by the high table to step down. He says he's not going to. John Wick returns to
the continental. Ian McShane, luckily, is now on his side. They're going to hole up in the continental
and they're going to take on the world together from the armory of this hotel. And I'm like, okay,
now I get it. It's them against everybody. This is where the movie's going to end. It ends with a
full on back. It doesn't help to be continued basically. Well, that's what I thought. And then it
doesn't end there. Then they do the whole thing of killing everybody that comes in the continental.
And then he still has to kill the sushi chef that the lady brought in. So then he goes upstairs in
the continental to kill that guy. And he's now once again in an all glass room, which is
painfully similar to the all mirror room at the end of John Wick, too.
And then he kills all of them. And then Ian McShane turns on him. But you're not sure if he turns on
him to save his own ass or to save John's ass. And at the end of the movie, John Wick is miraculously
still alive. And all of the same people want to kill him. And he's still in New York. And you have
gone nowhere from the beginning of this film. It has not moved one inch off of the starting and you
really starting to feel that, you know, like you, but for me, by that point, I was like, I'm done
here. We saw one o 'clock show and I caught myself dosing during the Halle Berry section. But you can't
really say enough about the opening half hour. And some amazing action there. Friends of mine
who saw it like opening night with a big cheering crowd. Of course, all have much higher opinions of
the movie. Joe and I saw Matt and I with a very reserved crowd. These movies are, you know, probably
best seen in a big audience. But John Wick three has some faults and some faults that really the
franchises got to figure out, I think before we get four. Unfortunately, they already have a release
state for four. So they'll just keep churning these out like fast and the furious without putting any
real thought into them, which is a shame because I love this late period renaissance of Keanu excited
about villain Ted three. There's some great stuff in this movie though. I liked, as I said, he
and McShane. I liked Asia Kate Dylan, who is one of the first trans action stars. She's on
billions as well, which I have not seen. I liked that Lauren's fish burn is just like a big fat guy now.
He is fat. I liked that. And, you know, a little reunion, Matrix style was fun as well. The movie
is certainly enjoyable enough for a recommend. But it ain't quite what you want it to be is my take. And I think Joe's as
well. I would agree. And it's a little disappointing because, you know, the creators openly said when they
were asked to do sequels, they were like, we wanted to take a couple weeks or a month or whatever was
and figure out can we think of something worth doing? Right. And if we can, we'll do it and if we
can't, we won't. And so the fact that they've already got a part four release date set
on like opening day of this one, I'm like, there it's now become fast and the furious where it's like
it's just going to be movie after movie of you do or me just say this exactly. Did you just say that
including fast and the furious didn't hear a word of it? What supposed to be a conversation?
I'm trying to get into the damn website so we can do the shout out so I can't get what's the
fucking password? Do you remember? Well, I'm not going to tell you on air. Hold on, I'll pause it for a
second. Okay, we're back. Pat just gave me the password off air. Yeah. 69 69 69.
Pork, fork, or lane. Anyway, John Wick three fun popcorn flick. You'll certainly get your
actions popcorn today. Yeah, I'm sorry. You'll actually get your money's your action money's worth
but you know, it's it's certainly not part two and it's certainly not part one. So that's our show
folks. It was a pleasure to be here with you. We'll see you in Chicago next week. The first show I
think is sold out. Second show is selling. Yeah, it's at the North bar in Chicago. Seven o 'clock
show is sold out. The 10 o 'clock show. I think Will sell out and it is Sunday. The ninth I believe is
the date. The ninth of June. North bar shy town. No promises but I feel like Joey and I will probably
out to paint that Chicago town red afterward. My flight is not till 7 p .m. the next night. Beautiful.
I haven't even set mine yet. So maybe I'll get on that same one. So I'm ready to get busy.
Busay or yes. Okay. And movies will be announced soon but I'm assuming we will do two Chicago centric
horror films of some kind. That would be awesome. The only the only Chicago films I can think of
off hand are comedies. But we'll be doing the untouchables and the fugitive. The first of the
Chicago horror films will be the film Chicago starring Richard gear. You know the fugitive might be good.
I can't think we'll find some Chicago horror. We will. We'll find two that makes sense but I'm
excited to watch Ferris Bueller and Adventures in Baby sitting before I go to my favorite Chicago movies.
Yes. Thanks for listening folks. Joderosa comedy at gmail .com and if you're in the DC. Sorry.
If you're in the Boston area, I'll be at Laf Boston in June. One of my there the 19th, 20th and 21st.
And then I'll be at Skankfest on the 23rd or 2nd rather. If you can't get laid at Skankfest.
The 22nd at Brooklyn Bizarre of June. And then I will be at bananas. It has
break heights that following weekend in June. So I'll see you guys out there or in Chicago.
I'm at the Patrick Walsh Twitter and Instagram. Joe and I in the future, you know we've discussed
doing the movie Unsane, which is on Amazon Prime, Steven Sotoberg's Unsane. I think it's a great
one for the podcast that a lot of you have asked about. So watch for that one. We'll do it at some point
and we'll have the announcements. I'll put them on the Facebook page of what the Chicago features
will be so that you guys can watch to your homework if you wish. Thank you very much folks.
Thank you for bearing with us during this hiatus. We'll see you next time. We'll see you in hell.