Huff, puff, and spin the house down at Golden Nugget Online Casino!
Right now, new players can deposit just 5 bucks and get 500 total spins on Huff and
more puff!
The slot that's blowing players away!
Download the Golden Nugget Online Casino app and use promo code Nugget1.
That's code Nugget1 to enjoy 50 spins a day for your first 10 days!
All on our players' favorite game of the summer!
Now's the time to score daily bonuses and spin for all the bacon on the game everyone's
hoffat about.
At Golden Nugget Online Casino, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamberler.
Please play responsibly.
21 and over, physically present in Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania, and West Virginia
only.
Void in Ontario.
New customers only.
Non -withdrawable casino spins issued as 50 spins per day for 10 days valid for featured
game only and expire each day after 24 hours.
C -terms at GoldenNuggetCasino .com slash promos ends at 11 .59 p .m. Eastern on August 31st, 2025.
The football season is full of guarantees. And here's another. No other sportsbook has
been offered this good. With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until
October, if your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash. If you bet on football
with fanatics, you're either winning or winning money back in fan cash, guaranteed. Switch to
Fanatic Sportsbook.
Winning hits different here.
Must be 21 plus, gambling problem called Winning 100 Gambler,
offer not available in all states,
terms apply, see Fanatic Sportsbook app.
Howdy folks, welcome to. We'll see you in hell. This is the podcast where you get the stuff in the juice and the fat on, uh, you know, horror movies and sci -fi movies and fantasy
flicks, all the juice and the fat and the stuff.
Well, I mean, I've never heard fat described as something people want from a podcast.
Yeah, give us the meat, well, the meat, sure, the fat does not want it.
Let's chew the fat.
That's what it was.
We're chewing the fat because it's a talking thing.
Does the expression chew the fat come from like a guy sitting on the porch after a steak
dinner literally chewing the fat while he talks to a friend.
I would imagine, that's probably what it is, it's disgusting.
I don't know why it's got to be on a porch.
It could be in the house. Look, if my husband was chewing fat in the house,
I'd send him out on the porch. I'd also be living in an entirely different lifestyle.
But that's not there. There's going to be a man doing it.
I don't imagine a lot of women are chewing the fat out of the porch.
Maybe that's a sexist attitude. I don't know.
Somebody wrote to me today online. I never thought I'd say this, Joe. I love the podcast.
I never thought I'd say this, but you're the more moderate of the two. And I didn't understand
if he was saying that I was moderate and you were more liberal, or if you were more conservative
than I, and I was more moderate, I didn't understand, but that the person also did think it was
very funny that we argued about Dennis Miller needing to be more balanced in his current
I saw that that gentleman tweets us frequently and it's very funny. I think he is a right -wing guy
Oh, so he surprised that I lean a little closer to him as a moderate
I think so I think I he's probably views me as more liberal, which I am fine being in that position
That's fine. I don't I don't hate the term moderate. I really don't now
Did you see today Kanye West takes to Twitter with a maga hat?
Uh, no, he did.
Maga had signed by Donald Trump, what appeared to be a child signature.
And then he's tweeting, he's tweeting three times a minute.
He's back in a full manic episode mode.
But any, any gets people talking about him.
Maybe he's a provocateur, but I don't think this is like, I'll say I'm pro Trump to get people
looking at me again.
I think he's very pro Trump.
But yeah, right after he's doing it, he's like, hey, just got a call from my wife.
She wants me to be very clear that I don't agree with everything Donald Trump said.
I was like, Kim Kay, you're doing your job here.
I would hope if I did that, that my lady friend would call me on my bullshit.
What were on the real living in when Kim Kay is now the voice of reason?
And I'm gonna as we are and say I'm surprised you're the more moderate of the two
Yeah, are the less moderate of the two. Yeah, it's
I don't know what anything means anymore. I think it just means like you get kind of played up the middle a little bit
Right, which is how I've always played it up the middle and whatever I do. Yes, yeah
Real quick
Let's just get on with the show and also
on with the Joe baby. I love you way every day. I think you've done that one before. I never
have. I was singing it while you were setting up the audio because somebody requested it on Facebook.
Oh, okay. I believe it was Mick Mack, which is certainly not his actual name, but he goes by Mick Mack.
And that is, that is the actual Mick Mack that started McDonald's. And that's right. That's right.
did the big Mac. And another fun fact is last name is patty whack. Folks, give a dog
a bone. Would you? Yeah, I had, well, I, yeah, there was a girl who was like a new
camera, I guess, to the thing. The group, the face to the Facebook group. Okay. And she
She was from like Dubai.
I wish I could find it.
I think it was Dubai.
Wow.
You know, she was like, my favorite part is the On with the Joe.
You can really tell how much the boys love each other during the On with the Joe's.
I was like, that's nice.
Maybe she can get us into the illuminati over there.
Or even hit in the Dubai model circuit.
You think?
Or it was a bot I don't know.
Isn't that...
I doubt a bot goes that deep into the...
That's true.
And what would the butt gain from commenting?
I think everyone's a bot.
We gotta do buy that's cause that's where everybody's gonna go
when the world is on fire.
I think I talked about this on here.
Maybe I didn't, but I tweeted, stop if I did.
I tweeted a year ago when the hurricanes
were hitting New Orleans.
I was like Fox News had just confirmed
that the hurricanes are in fact Muslim.
Right.
right. And some like house of representatives of Louisiana retweeted this and it's like,
here's what a Hollywood liberal finds funny. The death of thousands of New Orleans people
right. Ain't nobody died or I wouldn't have been making jokes about it. No one died in
these this weather incident. But it shook me up. And I got, you know, for the next week,
of course thousands of angry tweets by people with the American flag and their profile
Wow.
I've been there, baby.
It was just exhausting and then like the death threats start
and maybe you'd like it if somebody came to your hut,
you know, that kind of stuff.
And sure enough, a buddy of mine sent it to me
and was like, hey, just found out.
Didn't these guys tweeted you about this
and they were Russian bots.
It was a fake site that was stirring up all kinds of trouble
and going after people.
Oh, boy.
And why they would go after me?
It's without where they the initial tweet. It wasn't really a Louisiana
Senator they were fake. Well, it wasn't a senator. It was it was like the Louisiana
Republican party. That was fake. That was fake. Yeah, it was about Louisiana, Senator.
I wish I was in politics and Louisiana so I could say that on the on the floor of the Senate. Louisiana,
I dressed as thinnest. Why don't you put in the time to become one just to do it and then immediately
really quick. You know, when you suggested that, my first thought was, I bet it's not
that hard to become a senator in Louise. Clearly, it's not. What was the distinguished
gentleman about? That's the only any Murphy movie I haven't seen. I think. I am also
haven't seen the haunted mansion. You did see meat Dave though. Did you? I did see meat
Dave, uh, starship Dave. Is that what it's called? I think it's called meat Dave. Uh, the
The distinguished gentleman is he runs for office,
but I think he actually is a politician.
I don't think it's like,
I don't think it's like one of those things,
we're like a guy that sells hot dogs,
runs for office.
Like head of state.
Yeah, which is funny.
I think I've seen parts of it,
and I remember being relieved that it was a return
to some sort of funny form for Eddie Murphy,
because I know people consider Boomerang a classic.
I didn't care for that turn.
Sure, I didn't like that.
I didn't want to see romantic lead any Murphy.
I wanted like, you know, golden child any Murphy.
I want it like the straight comedies.
I got in an argument with the lovely Tony Rock,
brother of Chris, who sides, you know,
he is obsessed with any Murphy
and his favorite of his pictures, boomerang.
Look, I couldn't, I couldn't let it go.
I just kept, I was like, but you, you must love,
come to America, you must love trading place.
I love it, love it, love it.
I heard Boomerang.
But you know what?
It was probably 13 when it came out.
I think whatever you see when you're 13 is your favorite.
No, no, no, no, no, see, I think that's the other way.
I think if you were with Boomerang, I mean.
I agree with the 13 comment.
But I think if you were 13, like I was and saw Boomerang,
you hated it.
But if you were a little older, you realize
this was like a really smart comedy.
But it was one on me.
I didn't want to see it.
And he wasn't saying, fuck, I wasn't having it.
He wasn't playing four characters.
Now, had he played the romantic lead also in Boomerang and played the couple, then I would
have enjoyed it.
Well, he wasn't doing that shit at that point.
Oh, come to America, he played a bunch.
Yeah.
What am I talking about?
Then I would have enjoyed it.
But he's not putting a wig on.
In fact, I just parted ways with my copy of Norbit and I'm starting to think I made a mistake.
Clearly, you made a mistake.
You'll want to watch Norbit at some point.
That's a movie I would give a second chance because it was fascinatingly bad.
Norbit to me I left start to finish but I got it when blockbuster was going on a business and they had
They had these racks of DVDs. It was like you'd get four movies for $10 or something right so I got Norbit and precious
I remember once in the same visit. I now have your copy of precious. Yeah, I hadn't seen either. Yeah, and both were a single watch for me
Well, precious I get why you'd watch that once I actually really like press
I enjoyed Norbert, I thought it was really funny,
but I'm like,
do we need to play an Asian character in that movie correct?
Plays an old Asian man, he plays the nerd,
he basically just does the role again from Bofinger.
And then he plays the,
oh, I thought he was just great in Bofinger, in both roles.
He's so funny as the nerd brother
and so like weird and specific and good.
And he is also really, really funny as the movie stuff.
Yeah, yeah, he that whole opening sequence when he's going off about how racist Hollywood
is.
Oh, it's incredible.
And then he shoots the symbol on his drum set with a gun.
Yeah, it's pretty great.
Yeah, yeah.
It's pretty great.
You know, how many how many Ks are in the script?
I counted.
There's three hundred or three thousand six hundred and ninety nine Ks.
A number that's divisible by three KKK.
You got to tell me that's not intentional.
And they're going to send this to me very funny. He was, I think he was, it was kind of
like supposed to be that paranoid like Martin Lawrence type vibe. If that was happening
at during the age of both finger and I believe it was, uh, and I always love the line, get
my door as fast as you get Tom Hanks. Yeah. Yeah. That's a great line. Um, it's very
fun. I mean, he's sl, and I love Steve Martin. He slapped Steve Martin around in that movie.
He's so much funnier than Steve Martin. Steve Martin gives himself almost nothing funny
to do when the entire movie.
It's true.
He does like, I mean, he has the best line in the whole movie or the funniest joke when
he tells Heather Graham, we're done because he's furious and he goes, why?
And he goes, you slept with so and so and she goes, who cares?
And he goes, I never thought of it that way.
Right.
That's the funniest joke to me in the whole movie.
But that's like his only, he gives himself nothing funny really in it.
Yeah.
Some days a bit.
I think it's a very good comedy script.
And I think we've talked about both finger probably more than the two people in the world. The scene is funny when he's in the
When he's trying to sell Robert Downey Jr. on the square with the cordless with the cord. Yeah, that's very funny
Robert Downey Jr. I mean talk about a comeback for the ages Jesus Christ
I mean that guy was doing bit parts in both finger. He was it was all iron man
Speaking of movies I'd like us to hit a segment. We haven't hit in a while all right
And why do I want us to hit it because I just saw our dear friend Karen Kilgarif out in the
We were we couldn't think of what you would call it. She called it a causeway that you know that that that that that that
Sidewalk
That you walk up in my building that sort of separates all the buildings. Why is it nobody has a cause on the cause way
But your park
Park on the Parkway.
You don't park on the Parkway.
I've just always heard that George Carlin bit.
I'm like, is this that good a bit that we've been hearing
about this for 25 years?
Why do you drive on the Parkway and Park on the Driveway?
Oh, that was some like, okay.
Yeah, that's fine.
I thought you were really doing a bit.
I was like, I don't know much about Carlin.
My dad liked him, so I never really did.
And I know I'm more as an actor sadly.
I should hear all of this stuff.
But that, for that to be his most known bit, I think that's why I never dove into it.
It's not his most known bit.
It's the only one that I have been hearing for literally my entire life.
It's one that gets quoted in a lot of joke books and shit because it's clean and it's clever
and it's sure.
But it's, that's not his most known bit.
It's, you know, there's better out there.
Trust me.
I'm a huge fan of the man.
You know, you know, what he was in, outrageous fortune, discussed on last week's episode.
What the fuck did he play in that?
Okay, some burnout guide, you know.
All right.
I liked him in Jersey girl.
Kind of playing in the Halloween and train wreck role, right?
Yeah, but he actually hits an emotional thing
I've never seen him do in a movie
and he's the only redeeming quality of that film.
It's a bad, bad, bad, barely remember it, but yeah.
It's terrible.
I saw it not opening night, but like the rush hour
on opening day, like 5 .30, that was the only person in the theater.
It's not good.
Yeah.
And I like Kevin Smith.
I'm not trying to kick him down, but that's a bad flick.
So anyway, I ran into Karen Kilgarif in the DMZ, whatever the hell you would call this
central area.
We called it the DMZ when I was in college.
I don't know why.
It's the quad.
Yeah.
She was coming from recording my favorite murder, right?
give it a listen folks. So they're gonna be in the fucking news this week. They seemingly caught
that guy, the guy, the Sacramento Strangler. Yes. Right. Yeah. That's what we talked about.
Living down the street from the house, Heather, my fiance grew up in down the street in Citrusites.
Wow. Yeah. Now what are Heather's ties to this case? Look, there's gonna be a lot of questions when
I get home. I don't know. Karen, here's when I'm bringing up Karen, other than it was
nice singer. Yeah. She said, you mother fuckers after she was kidding. She wasn't being
serious. Right. But she said, you mother fuckers after all the support I've given to this
podcast, you attack my Bloomberg screen V suggestion. Yes. And she said she seemed particularly
off -puts. It's worse than what we thought it was. It's Bloomberg's scream V. The scream
is replacing the T terrible. Now she did say she was particularly off -putting by us saying
at least call it Doomberg. Yeah. And then she said, look a bad idea is a bad idea.
Which is fair. Yeah. But I still stand by that Doomberg was a little bit of a
Denver is obviously better than then scream V. She texted me after scream V
I said I'm warming up to it a little bit because I am it's for some reason and writing it seemed better
Yeah, but I said I'm not only gonna talk about this now on the show today because I'm going to record
But I also want to discuss
New story yeah
So it was good seeing Karen and she was in great spirits and so was I and it was just nice running into her quite frankly
But yeah, she was very I saw the great Eddie Peppaton with her the other night had a lovely evening
You went with Karen to the Peppaton show. That's correct nice. That's a nice night. Yeah
All right, who's a oh this new somehow no TMZ attention when we left
I saw a TMZ thing the other day I
Has it she'll never hear this it doesn't matter. I won't say names, but
a comedian that I know from New York, yeah, post this thing on Instagram. Throw back Thursday to
that time TMZ snapped a picture of us all at lunch. The picture is her. Somebody I can't remember
who I might have known the other person. I can't remember. Oh, it was my friend. Actually, I do
a rumor is my buddy, Gene. Okay. Cross of Geno is a guy that works for TMZ. Okay. Next
to him is Arty Lang. And she's somehow trying to make it sound like they had, you know,
they had to get a shot of me. It was insane. It was obviously all I need to know who that
is off the air. Off the air. Someone said they don't care for it when we, when we have
off the air secrets. I feel everything should be out there. But it can't be. I love you,
I love your support, tough shit, you know, it's like you got to get Jesus Christ, we got to have a fucking life. I'll tell you this.
I'm going to talk about the show, I'm going to keep it very brief, that's going to be on the bonus app because the odds of anyone at CBS ever listening to this podcast are zero,
but the odds of them paying to listen to it are less than zero. So you want to hear me give my little synopsis of what went on, it's going to be on the bonus app.
All right, talking about Biblically by the way.
And the only, okay.
I said the show.
I mean, as if people know what the fuck I'm talking.
Sounds good.
Here's the, here's the Deadline.
Deadline.
Oh, Scream and End.
Deadline from Scream and End's 24 -hour news psycho.
Now interestingly, the Scream is replacing the C and CNN
just as it replaced the T and TV,
but Scream and End is much better.
What could Scream and End's with an MN sound?
Yeah, you're you're you're it's it bleeds beautifully into that first hand. It does
But Karen, we love you couldn't couldn't love her more
Halloween 2018 test screening goes over poorly
With horror fans
We've been following this where this is on deadline hollywood. No, it was on movieweb .com. Oh, okay
Deadline is a play on headlines, but there's also the big, yeah, well, but that they're
not a part of this and they never will be as far as I'm concerned, it's a filth site.
Here's what a source had to say, according to horror freak news, the New Halloween movie
was given scores of fare to poor at the test screening with many noting that the movie
is too long and that the ending is not very good at all. According to a source, I'm just
reading the movie way. What else boilers here, I assume? No. According to a source who
attended the test screening, considerable time is spent developing characters who don't
last long. But that wasn't the worst news that had been reported about this Halloween screening.
the source had the dynamic problem. Halloween suffers from a lack of continuity, with barely any
exposition connecting this Halloween to its roots. Another person said, or maybe this is the
same source, the movie is aimed at modern heart. This was the thing that hurt when I read this. This
movie is aimed at modern horror fans who enjoy franchises like the purge and sinister. Rather than nuanced
or complex tapestry that Michael Myers of Fish Unitos are craving. I like sinister, but I also don't
want Halloween to be sinister. I want it to be Halloween. I also can't imagine that those guys
made that. I just don't believe it. And these reports could be a rough cut, it could be anything,
but who know, maybe it sucks. Well, look, first cut is I'm assuming what they showed, which
Jason Blum praised and the trailer went up today right that you watch it no it did believe it did a lot of trailers
Went up today and I didn't watch any of them, but I would love to see it the ending
Here's another note the ending is unsatisfying and hardly benefiting of and hardly befitting of something John Carpenter promises
Will be the last Halloween movie ever well, then they'll definitely reshoot the ending
You know and then movie web mentions that look you know reshoots could fix reported problems
And, you know, so who knows if they're going to do them or not, but this is also why as they point out test greetings or help.
So, so who knows.
But, you know, there was another thing I read about it where it said like, yeah, there were some cool nods to like parts three and four,
but it was basically them just recreating shots that you already saw in those movies as like homages to them.
and it was like, yeah, I like the Halloween franchise.
I don't care if it has nothing to do
with the Halloween franchise.
I just want it to be good.
It's a direct sequel to part one.
Right.
Now, here, this isn't really a spoiler.
If you want to know absolutely nothing, plug your ears.
But the premise apparently is,
is that after he gets shot in part one,
he was in fact abducted and brought back
to the institution or apprehended and brought back
to the institution. And apparently there's a line in the movie where they even say a bunch of kids
say didn't Laurie Strode's brother kill all these people and another kid says that's just a thing
people made up. So they are getting rid of which I'm fine with. I don't think it's a direct sequel to
part one, but that doesn't mean that it will have the the the the nuance or the
whatever of of earlier Halloween films. Yeah. My hope is that they they just
brought the same spirit of their comedies, which is like pushing the absolute
envelope over the horror without that becoming what Rob Zombie did, which is just
mashing your face into misery. Because I think they made one masterpiece of a movie, Observing
Report. And I think that they made one masterpiece of a TV show, Eastbound and Down. I have high hopes.
And I, you know, some test screening of people in Orange County or whatever, it doesn't really affect me.
Well, we will see now in a different side of things, the new puppet master movie
called Puppet Master, the littlest Reich, which was written by the guy that wrote Schindler's
list. No, but the guy that wrote Braun, so about 2099. And what? And, uh, and, uh,
Bone Tomahawk. He wrote the latest Puppet Master script and it's a reboot. It starts. Oh,
it's a bigger budget reboot. Well, it is going to see some theaters because apparently it's
that good. Uh, was this an early script this guy wrote? There's no way he wrote those movies
that are getting them all this heat i mean look the first movie was written by
david air or whatever the guy that wrote like the dark night
but unless this was like a a juicy theatrical reboot or he had the script
line around somebody on that trajectory who also wrote this new vence fawn male
gibson police brutality movie right it's not doing the new puppet master
so i look maybe he is because he thought i know how to make this awesome i don't
know maybe he's big fan but anyway he wrote it it starts thomas lennon
It's Lenin.
Yeah, it's screened recently and I think things blow in my mind.
Yeah, I know, it's weird, right?
And it's not a comedy.
It's got humor in it, I think.
But they said that it is fucking brutal.
And the only note I read that gave me an insight
to the script was it said,
Udo Kier, the guy from human set of pd, he's in it.
They said, the opening scene or his opening scene
is him going into a bar and giving a monologue that would, quote, make the PC police shake
in their boots. So apparently, it's a pretty rough lick. Well, that guy, that guy, there's
something going on with all those movies as we discussed. He's, he's a button pusher.
And I think this police brutality movie that seems to be from the side of the police might
be what finally pushes this into some uncomfortable territory. I'm all for it. Anything where I go to a
movie and I'm like, whoa, what the fuck? I love it. Well, and that's what, you know, I was having
friend lunch with my friend Joanne the other day who works at Netflix and I said one of the things I
like about Netflix a lot is that everything presented on there is without explanation. It's between
two points of a piece of art. And it's, hey, this is what it is. It exists between these two pillars.
and I think that's what art should be, you should not agree with all of it. You can make a movie
about a hateable person if the point is to explore what makes a person like that tick
and everybody doesn't have to like it and everybody doesn't have to see it. But at the end of the day,
art is art. So I agree with you. You think everything on Netflix follows that model?
I don't, obviously, I don't think everything that's made for Netflix, people are saying,
art is art, but I do think that they showcase a lot of stuff that is very challenging that you
wouldn't see anywhere else. You know, the Rocco -Safredi documentary comes to mind, which we talked about
on here. Sure. Sure. You know, it's hard to find a documentary these days that doesn't take some
sort of specific narrative or propensity towards one side of the argument. So, you know, I just
I used to appreciate that that's a place where you can still find stuff that is moderate.
Had a meeting over there the other day, it was like a hotel lounge, it was like 300 people
in the lobby waiting to go upstairs. Yeah. I guess to make, they're deeply in debt. I guess
they're going to try to fix that soon. But they, I mean, there's things on there like people have no idea
they exist. I bet there are things that have never been streamed on Netflix. I'd like them to slow down
the output a little bit, but also make more that I like more for me. Right. I log in every time
I'm staring at Paul Rudd and mute and deciding not to watch it. That's every day. And then I log out
and watch something else. Mute is the guy that made Moon. It's supposed to be pro pedophile as
all I've heard about it. But it's a, I love Moon. And it's supposed to have the Sam Rockwell character
or in like a nod to moon in the movie,
but I just can't bring myself to watch it.
Rockwell's got a flick on there I've never even heard of.
Where he's in a wig with some kind of go -t on,
and it looks like sort of like a comedy.
Don Verdine.
Yeah.
That's from the guy who didn't pull in dynamite.
It is?
Who I think has very quietly made a series
of really funny little movies.
Oh, well, I'll watch you.
They get no attention.
Sorry, I didn't mean to step on you.
No, it's fine.
Don Verdine is pretty funny.
and like gentlemen Broncos, very funny.
Yes.
Poignant Dynamite.
Obviously hilarious.
Masterminds with Gallifinakis was bad.
That's the Napoleon Dynamite guy.
But not unwatchable, it had funny bits.
He's a guy who sometimes goes a little too broad
with the wigs, the glasses, the hats,
but he's a funny director.
Well, I want to watch this now.
I already wanted to see it because I love Sam Rockwell so much.
She's my favorite current actor next to a GMOD, yeah, man.
But now I really want to see it because
Don Verdeen's got some laughs.
All right, Jared Hess.
Mormon, Filmmick.
You want to roll us over to the movie corner because we're about 30 minutes in already.
Sure.
And I think we are essentially there.
We've been discussing movies.
We're kind of in it, which is good because I haven't seen much.
But I will say this is for for the Joe fans. You're going to enjoy this. This is a rare moment of weakness for me. I saw quite a place again because Heather had not seen it.
Hold on. Let me bask in this.
Well, a big part of it is probably you shitting on it. And then it's impossible to not hear your voice. As if you were sitting behind me like, really?
But seeing it a second time in Santa Monica, some shitty fucking theater out there at 5 p .m.
when it was daylight with six people in the theater as opposed to that like big thumping
Saturday night crowd, the flaws showed more.
The flaws showed more.
And I saw it on a Sunday afternoon with not a pack theater and people weren't going crazy.
I think that probably, you know, that probably helped.
When I saw that Saturday night,
there is something to be said
for that big theatrical experience,
but when people are like,
you have to see it that way,
that is the marker of a movie
that's not necessarily standing on its own.
But comedies and horror are the two genres
that are always better with a big audience.
There's no way to deny that.
I will say, I still liked it.
I still think it's a well -made movie,
but there are a lot of things that don't quite add up.
And when they...
when they stumble upon that old couple was the new one for me this time. I was like,
did this old man just discover his wife was dead and then just starts screaming
the second Krasinski walks up when we didn't even know there were other people alive in the world.
It was there's too many coincidences. I will grant you.
And also they do know people are alive in the world because they do the beacon fire at the beginning
And then the movie and all the other fires go off.
So it's, I guess that was supposed to be a glimpse
into how people might react to this situation poorly.
Right.
But like, why would he scream in that second?
You know, it's just crazy.
I don't know.
But by the way, right after we recorded it
and I forgot to mention this, a meme did come out
that was like, that was basically my point,
which was like, I'm not saying it was based on my point.
I'm just saying like that agreed with my point,
which was basically like, you know, we can't use the top hat monopoly, but screaming baby,
no problem. You know, we're in danger of the whole family. So that is still the one aspect of it.
I completely disagree with you on. I think that if you want to look at it politically, it's a
commentary on people bringing babies into this sick fucking world that we're in now.
Yeah, but the people bringing the babies in don't have the insight to go, everything is terrible.
the people are going, whoa, dude, dude, that's true.
I mean, I think also, you know, we already discussed this.
They did this fucked, you know, people fucked.
Let's save movie corner then.
Let's skip, let's skip past it.
Okay.
Cause we gotta get into, I want to spend a little time.
Let me do the one I saw.
All right, then I'll do the one I saw and then you can,
cause it'll be out of, I think it already is out of theaters,
but I saw lean on Pete.
Okay.
It is a movie about a boy and his beloved horse, but it's rated R but it does not contain horse fucking and it's
Bishemi, it's who's the girl who sucked off Vincent Gallo. Chloe Savigny. She's a fantastic actress in
her own right. That's the first line in her bio. You know her as the girl who sucked off Vincent Gallo.
I mean that such an incredible actress not I mean she's a good actress. She's been a good actress in a lot of great
Indie movies for years and years and to blow Vincent Gallo on camera
You have to know people are gonna think of you as that. I have never heard one nice thing about Vincent Gallo
No, no person I've ever heard that met him said he's a fucking asshole. He wrote some wild
Yeah, I think you got to read that he posted everywhere that he wrote. He's supposed to be a nightmare
Yes, anyway, it was, it's been, you know, it's got a hundred percent run tomatoes this
thing.
Yeah, Moshe Cashier asked me if I wanted to go see this, I was like, oh, you know, Pete,
a horse movie.
Yeah.
Not really.
Let's go see, like, hereditary or something.
Well, that's not how you'd, I'm dying to see that.
Yeah.
It's Andrew Heiss, who's this, it's H -E -I -G -H, I don't know how you pronounce it, but he's made
very, you know, critically acclaimed small movies. And it was entertaining, I guess. It was very kind
of slow. I saw it because I was sort of looking to cry. I feel like I walk around very tightly wound
and pent up. And I was looking for some form of release. And boy, I gotta tell you, it didn't take me
there. I just, I don't know. I don't know why all the praise for it. It's just a little
movie about a kid who likes his horse and he's trying to bring it across the country.
But, you know, I also don't understand why you wouldn't, why you would make that movie
are. I don't know what to say. There was literally nothing about it that was
our fuck here, a fuck there language. That's, you know, they say fucking PG -13 movies anymore.
They do I was kind of I was kind of thrown by it said fucking our movie today ready player warned. That's right
I also watch motion
Legero special which I enjoyed I got it. I still got to see it. I'm very behind
I thought they were each funny on their own and then they were they were really good with the off -the -cuff material and the it's a and it's a
I can see it. I hadn't seen go she goes a half hour. He goes a half hour half hour together
I liked it go watch them do their thing their their their lovely couple and very funny honey moon special
Uh, and her, her, like mother, Natasha's motherhood posts on Instagram are the funniest things.
Like the funny. I'll follow up to check it out. She'll literally, like, I'm, I'm sort of
powdery, but she'll literally post like a picture of her breastfeeding and it'll say, like, watch
by D or. Right. They're really fucking funny, man. Uh, you know, uh, anyway, um, the, uh,
Anyway, so I saw you know that I watched Gotham fairly religiously. I've been keeping up with it
This is a big spoiler if you don't want to know
But I'm assuming if you're a fan you would have seen this already or know this already, but they finally revealed the Joker
It was awesome. I
Apparently the last three episodes of this season will be like a Joker arc
Who portrays the Joker?
Uh, the kid that was still Nicholson, it's still Nicholson, but everybody else is very young.
It's, uh, in a, you know, in a rare, yeah, it's Nicholson has reprised the road.
Have you seen him now?
Like, and look, whenever they get on some, like, 75 year old man who's been amazing for, like,
60 years, because he put on a gut, like, shut the fuck up.
Yeah. Like, whose dad doesn't have a fucking gut at this point?
Yeah, he looks like everybody's grandfather.
Right, but you know, he still does coke. So you're weird, but lately when he's sitting on the sidelines at those Lakers games
Yeah, he's I mean he doesn't he a comb hasn't touched that hair. He looks on shower. He'll eat a foot long sandwich
Like I mean, I'm loving what he's what he's doing and then he won't act. He's like I'm sick of fucking
All right, now I can't eat for three months because I got to be in a movie. I'm not doing it anymore. Yeah
All right.
It's the kid that's all right.
I interrupt.
That's all right.
The kid that portrays the Joker is the kid
that also portrayed the red herring for the Joker
for the last two or three seasons, whatever it's been.
They had a character on the show named Jeremiah,
something, what the, of course I'm blanking now.
Hold on, talk for a second.
I don't care.
Nobody cares what the guy's name is, Joe.
Well, no, I like to just be accurate, you know?
We're never never been accurate on this podcast about it most things
Well the kids a good actor. Oh, you're gonna. I thought you were giving the characters name I
Should know that too. I mean a little embarrassed so I can't remember his name, but
How is it not? I don't know for Christchurch
Gotham Joker hold on
Actor here we go all right Gotham Joker actor Cameron people often ask if you could have if you could play one minute of your
podcast to like really hook people, what would it be? I think it would be this man. You're
looking for Jeremiah's last name. Cameron monagon, mon again. I don't know how to say that.
But anyway, for the last few years, he's been playing, whoever he thought was going
to be the Joker. He was a kid with red hair, who was crazy that laughed all the time. And
they kept doing Joker storyline stuff with him. Like there was a thing where he had his face
ripped off and he had to have his face reattached. He says in one episode all you need is one bad day to go
crazy, which is the most famous Joker line ever. They were doing it on any of the movies. It's from
the it's from the killing joke, which is the very very famous Alan Moore comic. So anyway, they
this was, you know, and he also was sort of doing a heath ledgery kind of thing.
And so I really thought like well clearly this is the Joker and then in an episode they
revealed that he had a twin brother who was actually the opposite of him who was very
successful and very straight -laced and was the reason this kid got thrown into like a
mental asylum when he was a child.
So he says to his brother, I'm going to kill you but I'm going to make you go, I'm going
to drive you mad first.
And then at the end of the episode, this kid who you think is the Joker reveals they're
gonna spray these gases on Gotham to make people laugh to death and go crazy. Again, Joker plotline.
And he ends up dying. And after he's dead, his brother, who's straight -laced and successful
returns to his home and finds a package that he thinks is from Bruce Wayne, he opens it gas sprays him
in the face. And he goes crazy. And it ends with the crazy smile on there like, oh, his brother is the
Joker. Pretty, pretty fucking cool. Pretty cool way also to to give fans like a rehashing
of Joker shit they're already familiar with. Right. And then say, okay, now the real
Joker's going to come in and it'll be different, but you won't, you won't be disappointed
because we've already given you all the other stuff. So hopefully you like the new take.
But it was, it's been a great show. It's been a lot of fun. I don't doubt it. I've never
spoken to anyone who's seen it. Nobody watches it. Yeah. The ratings continue to sink. Yeah. But
every actor on it is terrific. And once in a while there's a bad or cheesy episode that feels like a bad
crime, you know, show or whatever. But most of the time it's pretty great. And I really like it.
Anyway, let's get to our movie. We're at 40 minutes. All right. And I check. So right now,
as this podcast goes, we are accumulating Q &A questions. This month's Patreon bonus
app will be Joe and I each answering all of the questions that are posed to us on the Facebook
page during the hour we're recording this episode. Yeah. Joe was concerned. It might go crazy. I just
just looked, we're at a nice 30 questions.
I think we'll be fine.
Yes, I agree.
Ready Player One.
I have no idea what you think about this movie.
I don't know what you think, I mean, either.
It's rare that we don't let it slip.
I, to give my little syscolony a bit overview.
I felt that Ready Player One was Spielberg
a legend, a true filmmaking legend that I think can be considered up there with your hitchcocks,
etc. Is getting a little long in the tooth, his movies are feeling like retreads of his other stuff
and this was his attempt to kind of get back in with the youth market. I think it was not entirely
successful. I thought there was some corny shit. Sort of like an AI, which is a movie I hated on
first viewing, liked the second, but it felt like the entire movie was in that center section
where they go and like Chris Rock is there for some reason. Remember that in AI?
I forgot that Chris Rock was in it, but like the weird like battle bots. Yeah, yeah, I do remember
that part. Yeah. It felt like all of that. So for me, the movie, especially in its first half,
there's a great chase up front was visually spectacular at times. I like some of the soundtrack
choices, the nostalgic choices got a little old, a little repetitive. For me, I kept thinking
I wish I had seen this high. I wish I had seen this in 3D. I have talked to friends who loved
that they saw it that way. I found myself as with a lot of these two hour 30 minute things
now maybe even longer. Found myself checking that time real early and often I
thought there was zero personal connection to these characters. The lead kid was
a nothing. The lead girl was nothing to me. The subplot about the Bill Gates
like character who runs the thing with Simon Pegg was nothing. I did not care
about any of these people. And at the end, then when they tried to make it this Spielbergian,
like, Oh, aren't you moved? Aren't your heartstrings pulled? I was like, Oh, they were going for that.
Like it all just felt tacked on and weird. It lacked a human connection, a human element to me.
And that for that reason, I couldn't get into it. Although, I liked some things about it.
Well, first off, if you don't know the movie or the book, it's based on a book.
The book is very popular.
I have several friends that have read the book, it's one of the most amazing books they've
ever read.
The kid is apparently obsessed with the 80s, as is the guy that created this virtual reality
space called the Oasis, which is why whenever the kid does anything in the virtual reality
where he does it based on something from the 80s.
For some reason, they put that line in one of the trailers,
they took it out of the fucking movie.
This is where I scratch my head,
which shit like this, it's two seconds
to put that line in the fucking movie,
and it makes the movie make so much more sense to somebody
who's not understanding of what's going on already.
Two seconds in a movie that's running like 240.
So yeah, so that wasn't clear to me at all.
No, so if you don't know that,
It seems like it's very imbalanced and you're kind of scratching your head like why is everything sort of from the 80s
but it's not everything is and whatever
Right
But anyway, it's about a place a world where you can go into this place called the oasis and live in virtual reality and
The guy that invented it hides is fortune in it after he dies and
It's a race to find it. So there's an evil corporation trying to find it
So they can dominate everything and then there's this kid who's very golden ticket and Willie
Wonka.
Yes.
Same exact thing.
Very, very Willie Wonka.
I was happy to.
Look, the movie starts with the song Jump by Van Halen.
I was smiling.
I was like, okay, this is cool.
Right.
I was into it.
The first race that they have was pretty fucking cool, like the kids driving the DeLorean from
back to the future.
All this was cool.
Ben Mendelssohn shows up as the bad guy. I'm like, all right, man, this is going to be great.
And then in about the 25 minute mark, TJ Miller strolls in as the bad guy, America's
sweetheart.
It ruins, I texted you immediately, like, oh, TJ Miller just ruined this movie for me.
He comes in as this like imposing, frightening, looking, skull monster guy.
And then it's TJ, and then the gag is its TJ Miller, and it's his voice.
And it's him going, I've got a neck thing. I think I need to see a specialist. My neck's been killing and it's like
This is exactly the kind of humor that I fucking hate. This is exactly the kind of humor that ruins movies like this
It is out of place. It is bad. It is obvious that somebody was brought in to write this and punch it up and try to make it funny
It's not funny. It's out of place and it's stupid and from there on out
I was like, well, here we go. And from now on out, it just became more and more evident to me
that and I'm paying to say this because I am a huge Spielberg fan as well.
And I'm afraid because I'm excited for the next Indiana Jones movie. I'm excited for it.
I want to see Harrison Ford send off the character and I want to see him do it well.
But I will say this and it's something I never thought I'd say. Spielberg is not good anymore at making popcorn movies.
He's not good at it anymore.
He's great at making these Russian spy films.
He's fucking phenomenal at that.
He goes into these things.
You could tell his heart's not in it.
It's paint by numbers for him at this point.
And the movie was boring.
I didn't give a shit about the characters.
It was boring.
Even anything, the only character I kind of cared about
was Ben Mendelssohn, because I thought he was a decent villain.
And then even in the end, he just betrays his own character
and doesn't take the golden orb from the kid
when he finds it or whatever, which was stupid.
The Ragtag team that they assemble,
it so makes you appreciate these like the goonies
and all these movies that Spielberg used to do and produce.
Like those two Asian brothers, they have zero personality.
There's nothing interesting at all about them.
Lena Weith, who was a television writer, suddenly playing this role, I wasn't even aware
she was an actor, and she was the lead girl or woman.
No, she's the black girl and she's for most of the movie, The Ogre, and then you realize
that it's her.
She's a television writer, she's a TV, she won an Emmy for Master of None with the Zsanzari,
And I, I'm like, what?
Because she didn't bring anything to the movie either.
And then the lead kid, the main kid is kind of nothing, too.
The main kid is the romantic lead, which I found out after I saw the film in the book when
she says, you don't want to, I don't want to meet you in real life because you'll be disappointed.
Yeah.
I found it in the book.
She actually is sort of unpleasant looking and she has a reason to want to hide herself
because she's self -conscious, I mean.
And then in the movie, they just take a pretty girl
and they just put a birthmark over a eye that's fine.
It's not even a brown birthmark.
It's like a light red.
It almost looks good.
It would have been so much more fucking interesting
if this was like an actual unattractive person.
Yeah, it's fucking Hollywood.
The girl's beautiful.
Um, I don't know, man.
I, I, I, I would say 25 minutes is exactly right.
I was like I am on board with us and then I was just immediately off the movie sucked. It was tedious and endless and
I wasn't into it and there there were really no highlights after that first half hour. Here's another thing
I learned from my friend Brian who told me to think about the female character, too
He said the cool thing about the book is almost the entire book takes place in the oasis. Right. So it's interesting because it's the writer is showing you
how he creates stakes in a virtual reality world.
And that's what makes it so cool.
He goes, all that shit where they're in the van driving him
around town, so he goes, none of that is in the book.
He goes, this movie so much of it took place in the real world
and none of that's in the book.
That driving around in the van with those characters
I just discussed, that last half hour is so boring.
It's so boring.
Also a big part of me.
Why would they invent it?
If the book is a beloved and be apparently very well written and exciting, why would they
fuck with it?
Harry Potter didn't fuck with those books.
They did every word of those books.
And then another thing is too is that this whole film is about how this virtual reality world
has made interconnectivity that's taken it to the next level, has made people live their
dreams, you could be, you know, you could be anybody you want and go anywhere you want.
Plan it to plan it, whatever, no matter where you actually live.
And then when the shit goes down for the main character, all of his best friends just
happen to live down the street from him, and they just come and they can help him and there's
no problem whatsoever.
And they all also happen to be very capable, nimble people in real life as well.
I don't have a movie fucking stunk.
God, I hated it.
It did.
You know, when I'll pop into the Facebook page now and then
and be like, you know, what do you guys think of this?
What do you guys think of that?
And I'll say, I liked it.
I didn't like it.
I just threw up a, didn't like it.
And people seem to angry.
People do like the movie.
I thought you were gonna tell me you liked it.
I was getting ready to,
well, I will say when I was watching it,
I was like, Joe was either going to absolutely love this.
You are an nostalgic man particularly for the eighties or hate it and here and now we know now the what did you think of the lengthy segment?
Where they go into the movie the shining and do you know if that's in the book that I don't know if it's in the book
That was the only part in the movie that captivated me
I thought that was really damn cool. It was cool somebody reminded me a bag of the future two when they go in a bag of future one
Yeah, which I thought was a genius idea. I loved it
But somebody spoiled it for me. So okay. I was it wasn't a surprise. I knew it was coming
I liked that a lot and also at the same time I was like the shining was made in 1980 or made in the 7 is released in 1980
But that that feels to me not like a classic 80s movie. I feel like Spielberg is close with Kubrick's family
It was probably like we can get that one
Yeah
I liked all the back to the future nods
I like that it played like the music,
it would play little musical phrases
from back to the future, right?
That stuff, like we gotta use the Zamekis twist or whatever.
I mean, some of these things feel like Spielberg,
like at his millionaires club weekend,
trying to impress his buddies.
And there comes an age where that kind of stuff
doesn't look good on you.
And Spielberg is at the age where
This is this movie wasn't his you know this movie was not something he should have made he I don't maybe he plays video games
I doubt it. I
It felt like something where he could kind of
Let people handle all the effects and like I don't know none of it none of it had his usual flair for character for heart for
Anything no it was it was wreck it Ralph. Yeah, except not as good
I never saw a wreck it Ralph because I knew once I got past the references. I wouldn't give a shit anymore
You I bet you'd like record. All right. Oh, you don't like cartoons and either do why but I give it a shot pretty good
I'll give it a shot, but this was I mean this is this had to be a licensing nightmare. Oh, sure
That's the other reason you don't make a book like this into a movie because then there's references repeating right and you're too much
And you're like, why don't they keep going back to this goddamn thing that's not that interesting right so the best ways
I've seen this kind of thing done and I was who knows how much that cost to do
But it was who frame Roger rabbit. It's because at the end they had the loony tunes characters and the Disney characters like together
Which you would never see
And it felt seamless. They they tapped on it. This felt like only that
Well also, too
There was there were stakes funny enough. There were stakes in Roger rabbit
There were no stakes the fate of Los Angeles. There were no stakes in this to me
I was just like I know the kids gonna find the fucking orb. Yeah, even at the end
and when he meets the Bill Gates guy in the virtual world
and the Bill Gates guy goes, he goes,
wait a minute, or the kid says to the Bill Gates guy,
wait a minute, you're not dead, are you?
What are you when he goes, well, we'll see,
and you're like, what?
Right.
What?
And what does that guy's name?
I don't know, he's great actor though.
I don't like him.
I thought he was very good in it.
Well, he's become, you know, Scorsese's Deniro,
or now Scorsese is DeCaprio.
Wait, oh, the kid, you mean?
No, I'm talking about the guy who played the Steve Jobs guy.
He's been like four Spielberg, he played the BFG.
He was in Bridge of Spies.
Right.
What's his name?
I don't know.
Can we look it up?
Yes, sure.
He's a really good actor.
Wait, who is he?
I think he's playing Spielberg's DeCaprio.
Yeah.
They said Scorsese.
I was like, wait, what?
Just like Scorsese has his.
I probably did, but that's what I meant.
just like Swarcese has is De Niro and I just always like Spielberg can get any actor in the world.
So when I see this guy again wearing a wig to make him look younger, I'm like,
why couldn't we have got a different actor? He's really good in that role. I believe he was that guy,
but his name is Mark Rylands. Mark Rylands, yeah. Ty Sheridan is the lead who also was in,
And he played Cyclops and X -Men Apocalypse.
And he was also in, oh, well, look what we have here.
The Trial Life.
I like Trial Life.
I can't stand that fucking movie.
He was also in Mud.
Yeah, he was good in Mud.
Mud is what?
He was good in Mud.
No, Mud is what, though.
Oh, it's McConaughey.
Oh, okay.
It's a little like Southern noir kind of thing.
all right well anyway there you go folks ready player one thanks for being here
with us go watch by night origins on Amazon Prime if you're a horror anthology
fan or if you're just a horror fan show us some love if you could also I'll be
opening for oh no that already happened and I'm doing a show with Burr but it
already happened by the time this goes up I'll be at Rooster T feathers last
weekend of May in the old silicone valley. All right. I am on Twitter and Instagram at the Patrick
Walsh. I am sorry for telling you last Monday to watch my favorite episode of the show because it
did not air and maybe a layer in the summer. I don't know. That's the one with the folks jokes in it.
But maybe America wasn't ready to hear folks on a large scale.
We will be back next time with something else.
I don't know what just yet.
Perhaps stir of that goes if you haven't seen that dusted off.
And please do check out our Patreon bonus where we will be answering your questions.
Till next time, we will see you in hell.
That was a hitgun podcast.