Summer is here, and Bed MDM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer.
Or check out our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz.
Only available at Bed MDM Casino.
Spend on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 Fortunes, Mystery of the Lamp,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand!
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action!
Bet MGM game sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 plus to Wager, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and West Virginia
only.
Games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as normal, durable site credit slash bonus best unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
The football season is full of guarantees, and here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October, if
your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning, or winning money back in fan
cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
Winning hits different here.
Monthly 21 -plus, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gampler, offer not available in all states,
term -supply, see Fanatic Sportsbook app.
This is a head -gun podcast.
Hello everybody and welcome to We'll see you in hell on its new home head gum.
We are very excited to be here.
My name is Patrick Walsh.
I'm here with my dear friend Joe Derosa after about a month long hiatus.
We're very excited to get to this.
today's movie is called Get Out, directed by Jordan Peel, and now on with the show and
on with the Joe.
I missed it somehow, I missed hearing you say that, Joe said to me, how are you going
to get it on with the Joe and now that we don't have our old pre -written intro, I was like,
don't you worry about it, baby, I'll find a way.
You got writing in your blood wash.
You were born to do it.
It's true.
It's good to see you, man.
Your dog is shitting on the floor as we speak.
This is how our new podcast starts
with me watching shit squeezed out of your dog's ass
onto your hardwood floor.
He, uh, it's a watery shit as well.
And now is he going to eat it?
No.
Is he going to eat it?
Joe, if I have to watch this dog eat shit.
I'm gonna eat this shit.
All right, are you gonna clean that up
or what are we?
We really did just shit right on the ground there.
We, do we do an intro?
We're happy to be back.
and the dog shits on the floor four feet in front of me.
Con, why'd you do that?
What happened?
That was wild.
That was real wild.
Why did he do that?
I don't know, but it's not a great omen.
I'll say that.
I just took him out a little while going.
He's just shit.
I don't know.
Did you go to an Indian buffet or something?
God damn it.
Oh, Con.
All right, well, you want to take the wheel while I -
I'll take the wheel while I -
joke cleans up an animal's shit folks I just want to say you know we were never
going to not return the show we're kind of shopping it around and seeing
where we'd wind up on our new network basically what happened is
Fangoria essentially went under which is a negative way to say it but it is
what happened it's in flux it'll probably wind up at a new location as well
but Joe and I dearly love the people at Fangoria for giving us the platform for
so long, particularly Ken Hanley, who was always such a great help over there, and they're
apparently going to continue on elsewhere, which I did already say.
Fangoria is going to keep going.
Fangoria is going to keep going, so keep looking for them.
There's no beef here, aside from Ken holding me out of a hotel window by my knees, chug
really no bad blood. And we wanted to say, I wanted to say, thank you for the really constant
tweets that we get and comments elsewhere, Instagram, whatever it may be, Facebook
about how much you guys love and miss. We'll see you in hell because it really made us
want to get back. And we appreciate it. We have a new Facebook group called, we'll see you
check in, I love what I'm seeing.
It's getting some numbers up.
Thank you for the five star reviews.
I want to say thank you to Chris,
who approached me right after I saw get out
on the streets of Los Felas and said, Pat,
I love, we'll see you in hell,
and then gave me a hearty and now on with the Joe,
which I thought was a beautiful thing, Chris.
Thank you.
You made me feel like a big time star.
We're gonna give the blow by blow with a shit cleanup.
Joe's almost done, we got it up, luckily it's a brown floor so if there is
stage we don't know. We're going to talk this week about get out, first we're
going to update you with I guess I'll go into my normal segment and since this is
the first time, basically we have a real loose lacks approach to our segments where
we often forget to do them. Oftentimes we're not even really sure what the other
the person's segment is, but the bulk of the show is me and Joe yelling at each other
and talking about a new horror or sci -fi movie each week that, you know, eventually goes
off into wild other tangents.
What I have seen in the interim, I saw the Lego Batman.
All right, I'm back.
You don't start the segment without me, you know, just give me, give me a second, but usually
Hopefully the segment is me talking about movies I've seen.
It's actually both of us talking about movies we've seen.
And I'd also like to add, it's never the two of us not knowing what the segment is.
It's Pat not knowing what the segment is, because the guy's got a wet brain.
I don't know what to tell you folks.
I mean, he sounds like a nice guy on this podcast.
I have a thousand things going on, is my experience.
He rolled in today like Mr. Hollywood.
He's wearing a sweatshirt that literally says cool on it, and he's wearing sunglasses.
glasses. Uh, well, it's sunny. And this is a sweatshirt that I owned that was clean.
My life is falling apart. Uh, let's, let's do good. And on to Pat's movie, Roundup.
Pat's movie, Roundup. I saw the Lego Batman and I'm glad you're bringing this up because
it's everything wrong with this country right now. Oh, wow. All right. So let's talk about
Hey, have you seen it? No, okay, that's it. I refuse to participate in the
make having not seen the film, but I refuse to participate in a culture
and an activity where where people somehow have a have a lust and offer a Lego Batman
yet they shit over the real if you're going to talk about Batman versus Superman,
I will walk back out the door. I'll shoot on your floor like a dog bit and then I will walk out.
I got to tell you something. The golden raspberry nominees and and awards, whatever happened.
Yeah, worst screen worst movie Batman super worst movie. Did it win? Yes. All right, Joe
That's it that should tell you something that's insane. That's it be dirty
Give me a fucking break. You're gonna tell me there's not a vendetta against this movie. I I thought I had forbid you from ever
Discussing Batman versus Superman again. It takes Joe to a bad place
It's why I don't talk about time Warner Cable. I go off on on dark tears and I can't come back from do you think that
Dirty grandpa is a better film than Batman versus Superman. Can I say this with a hundred percent truth?
Yes, you're you're fucking nuts. I hate your fucking mind. I hated them both
But dirty grandpa was a 90 minute comedy that sort of passed the time. It was offensive
It sucked, but it wasn't like
Boring and it didn't take two and a half two forty five of my life. It took 90 minutes. That's why I prefer dirty
Oh god, yeah, all right, so you liked Lego Batman big surprise a couple decent jokes man
Zookas is funny and dirty grandpa
The Lego Batman I did not love I thought the first Lego movie was
hilarious and I really loved it Lego Batman looked awesome
It had a very very funny first 20 and then it just kind of started losing me
But it's a fine movie all right. I think a big problem with it was I saw Gallif and Agus was playing like a very
insecure Joker. I don't like that. I was like, that sounds funny, but he didn't bring much to it.
I don't like an insecure, I like Galfanakis. I don't like an insecure Joker. I love Galfanakis,
but yeah. Make the Joker crazy, but in a funny way. Yeah, I don't know. It wasn't my bag, but it
wasn't terrible. All right. I saw John Wick chapter two. I know you did as well. What were your thoughts?
I loved every minute of it. I enjoyed it thoroughly. Thought the first John Wick had a better storyline
because it dealt with the loss of his wife and that sort of thing and the dog and the dog.
I thought that like these movies are only as good as they're you know why he's killing everyone in sight and this one
Yeah, it didn't have well, I don't heart. I guess you would say it didn't have quite the heart
But I enjoyed watching it more than the first one because I don't think I didn't I don't like it quite a bit
I don't think these movies are just the heart
I think like a big part of these movies is how crazy will he kill people yes and boy does he kill people he killed a lot of
Spoiler alert, if you haven't seen it, my favorite part in the movie was the montage
when everybody gets the text to kill him.
Yes.
And it's just that montage of him killing several people at once that are trying to kill him.
And then I mean, I saw it opening night in Hollywood when he picks up the pencil.
I mean, people went fucking crazy.
People went fucking crazy.
So that was a lot of fun.
I really enjoyed it, but I like the first one too for for slightly different reasons, fair enough. Yeah. I saw Tony Erdman, which was a nominee for
Best Foreign film this year and it's being remade with Kirsten Wigg and Jack Nicholson, which is in Wigg.
Christian wig. I went with Kirsten, and I'm sticking to it. It's wrong.
Well, she lives in my neighborhood. If I yelled out Kirsten, I bet you're
gonna look. I mean, what is with you? What are you turning into? You come in here
with your cool sweatshirt. I got cool. I don't understand it, either. It says
cool. I think it's the Kurs logo. It's the audacity that you're wearing it. I don't
think the sweatshirt says I'm cool. It's a very uncool boring sweatshirt. No, it's
It's a very uncool and a sort of hipster, ironic Hollywood kind of way.
All right, now you're dropping names about your neighbors.
You want to tell everybody who else lives in your neighborhood?
Andy McDowell.
You know, some names.
That's all I'm saying.
All right, go ahead.
Tony Hinchcliffe, what's this movie called?
Tony Erdman.
All right.
Yeah, Joe's dog is starring in only turdman.
Boy next month Tony Erman is about a it's yeah, it's being remade with Kristen Dunst and Jack Nicholson
Kristen Wigg Pat. Oh my god
People that was the Matt Kirsten Dunst
Kristen Wigg and Kristen Wigg is the one in the movie. What is the matter with you? There are two
Agresses who I love folks and I'm not trying to be Hollywood. I got a lot of shit going on
I wake up every morning trying not to scream and then I go through my hole
I have currently in both of my hands fingernail marks in both of my hands like a stigmata
Which is a terrible horror movie starring Miss Patricia R .Quette and I know that's the correct pronunciation right R .Quiefe it is R .Quiefe, yes
Anyway, it's being remade. That's perfect casting this movie is three hours the remake will be two hours
I'm sure it'll be funny, but they'll probably fuck it up
It was an insane comedy about this girl, woman, who's 40 years old, she's very, very stressed
out at work.
She's one of these people who's obsessed with work and has no time for fun or pleasure.
Her dad hates to see this and basically, he's like, before I pass on, I'm going to make
it my goal to get her to loosen up.
But he never tells her he's going to do that and he does it in this insane way where he
dresses up with fake teeth and a horrible wig as this character named Tony Erdman, who
doesn't exist and shows up at all for she doesn't know that it's him.
She knows.
Nobody else knows.
And she's at first, I appalled and then eventually she finds she learns the life lesson,
right?
It's, it's, it's going to be that in the Hollywood version.
This was a insane, like almost x -rated movie.
They fuck at the end of this.
They don't fuck, but he keeps showing up at her business events and parties like in this
ridiculous wig and teeth.
Kristen wig, ridiculous Kristen wig.
It is really, really funny and really, really crazy.
There's a come scene in the middle of this thing
that the audience like cleared out
as though a bomb had been thrown into the theater.
It was all these old people,
because that's an artsy theater.
I mean, everyone was clearing out.
It was a wild time.
If the movie comes out and it's rated PG -13,
they've already fucked it up.
But Nicholson and Wigg and these parts are gonna destroy it if they keep the movie the same
I don't know that they will all right. I loved it
That's about all I got except a DVD recommendation would be hunt for the wielder people
Which I thought was hilarious and there's a Lord of the Rings joke in it that made me laugh for 10 minutes all right
I saw
I saw her I found a saw green room
How'd you like on the plane loved it? I was playing I hate when people watch a great movie on a plane
I watched it on my Amazon Prime on an airplane.
Why is that?
You're phone, right?
No, on my iPad and I put the earphones in
and I watch it.
What's wrong with that?
I hate thinking of people watching a great movie
on a device.
I enjoy it.
Can I say it?
I enjoyed it thoroughly.
It was very good.
I was a little confused as to what the bad guys plan was.
You know, because I was having a hard time
understanding Patrick Stewart.
Okay.
But, you know, when he would say like,
I thought if I were staging up the road,
yeah, like I was like, what are they staging?
What the hell is going on?
But I knew that at the end of the day,
they were trying to kill the people in the green room
and I really liked it.
I loved it.
Did you feel like the punk stuff was as accurate as a movie can be?
I thought it was as good as you're going to get.
I know you played bass for Blenke 92 for many years.
Yes, you're a true punk.
Yeah, yeah.
And I sang bass for Green Day in the American Idiot Broadway tour.
You portrayed like Jim base. No, no, no, I sang bass bass parts in the course. Okay, like Mike Dirt
No, that's the bass guitar. I sang bass and acquire the chorus. Okay, the chorus. Just be just be clear
Just kill a fucking joke. Just be clear. I don't know if I killed it. I think
The work was done before I arrived on the scene officer
I
Like the movie quite a bit. I you know that whenever there's that self conscious of a decision that it's gonna be about a punk band
There's let me put a pause on here. We should probably do on a green room episode, right?
All right, we could but I mean you talked about it at DC. I care for it, but here's the thing. We are gonna do an episode, so I loved it
We are gonna do an episode
In fact, it'll be next episode probably about a movie we have discussed already and I will just mention it briefly here
Because I also watched this on the plane
little pile of shit called the neon demon that you sang the praises of so
many months ago I can't wait to discuss this fucking movie that was a movie
where I said I don't think anyone would like it but I loved it well so I
understand we're gonna get into that really the if you go back to our archives
which are gonna be available on head gum maybe hopefully a lot of you can
from Fangoria, but if you're new fans, or if you hate it either way, I don't care if you're
hate -listing, we still get the numbers. The episodes where Joe and I disagree are probably the strongest
because we argue and the anger is always very real. I think people respond to that. But when we agree,
as I'm pretty sure we're going to on today's film, we'll definitely find some side things to argue
about, don't you worry. We wanted to kind of bring you in carefully and easily, like when
you're kind of just, you know, you know, you kind of graze your tip along the outside
before you enter of the V. You kind of move it back and make sure you're good to proceed.
You're P against the V. Yeah. Yeah. That was a high score. Sure. Right. Grip. Yeah. It's
called P V. Perkyman Valley. Yes. Yeah. So we'll get into Neon. We're even in because
we're talking about a movie that you'd have to be a damn fool not to love on today's show.
Yes, we will get into Neon Demon next time.
What else have I seen?
I watched Front to Back, the entire series, or first season,
excuse me, of channel zero.
What do you think?
That is the sci -fi anthology horror series.
I enjoyed it.
I thought it was very well done.
It was a little, the territory has been traversed.
Is that the word?
Not really, but I got it.
with well -trauged territory, because it's about a bunch of kids that get involved in
some sort of evil demonething.
So it's very it, it's very stranger things.
But it was very good.
I thought they did a great job.
I look forward to seeing what they do next season.
Oh, it's kids stumbling up, it's the same kids in each episode.
No, next season will be a new story, but I thought this was a really good first outing.
All right, it's not a it's not like a twilight zone where every week's different. No, it's just an anthology
But it's like the way American horror story is where every season is different. I don't know if the hovercurring
I don't know if all the actors come back to play different characters or not, but I am not a fan of American horror story
I think it tries way too hard. I dropped out years ago. Yeah, it comes off way too Marilyn Manson for my taste
But but this show I thought they did it because the show
removed its rib so it could suck its own dick. Yeah, well there's that. There's
only because the show was Paul from the wonder years when it was a kid. Remember
when that rumor I remember it well, what's going around? There's that. There's
the Richard Gear gerbil. There's the Rod Stewart had to have a stomach pumped and a
bunch of cum came out. I don't believe any of these stories but they were all big
even when I was in grade school,
hurt him all the time.
All right, so that's the round of what we've seen.
Let's move on to Joe's scary stuff.
You know, always gets a laugh.
It's not a great title.
Joe's scary stuff.
What do you want for me?
I try, you know.
This week I'm highlighting the release of a DVD
or Blu -ray excuse me.
And again, this is not a review of the movie itself.
It's just something worth buying.
It's a product.
But Shout Factory has released the Texas Chainsaw Massacre 2,
Special Edition Blu -ray.
We have not discussed this, I don't believe, right?
We haven't, but I'm not doing a bit here.
I thought Joe's scary stuff was about things that aren't movies
that are scary.
Yeah, because you're just adding on another movie that you see.
I'm not adding on a movie what I want to know what your own segment what I wanted to talk about was how good of a job
They did with the Blu -ray. I mean, I'll allow it, but it's not part of the special features and the special features
Look, you want it's supposed to be like books video games things in the horrors of scary stuff on god damn day with you
Dude, Resident Evil 7 just came out you'd buy about it on the last one
Resident Evil snow I read mentioned Resident Evil 4 2 ago and the last one was when I talked about
out the DVD service horror pack.
Okay.
So Resident Evil 7 biohazard is out.
It's a great game.
Everybody's loving it.
It's supposed to be phenomenal blah, blah, blah, blah.
Who gives a shit?
You know what I mean?
I will actually do your own segment correctly
and talk about a book I'm in the middle of
called Outrageous Conduct, Art, Ego,
and the twilight zone case by Stephen Farber.
Well, and I also have another thing I can do.
So go ahead.
You can alternate.
This book is about the John Landis segment
of the twilight zone, which of course killed
actor Vic Morrow, Jennifer Jason Lee's father,
and also the two Vietnamese children
that he was holding, decapitated them all.
That he was being overworked.
They were being overworked and Landis basically kept going,
get the helicopter closer to them, closer, closer,
close until they were decapitated and there was a lot of cocaine on the set it
was 83 I love John Landis I think he's directed some of the best
companies of our time obviously his career fell apart after this pretty much
except he still did three amigos and coming to America which are fantastic but him
Spielberg a lot of people in this book do not come off well and it's a
fascinating look into that time and people that especially Spielberg you think
being like a sweet grandpa at this point, but apparently Landis's first call because Spielberg
was a producer, was to Spielberg, like holy shit, like we just killed three people and
Spielberg's immediate response was, you better have a real good fucking publicist.
I was like, okay, that's an interesting way to respond to death of three human beings, but
But that segment was supposed to end differently.
That story was supposed to end with the guy learning his lesson about being a racist,
which would have been a very twilight zone ending.
Yeah.
It's all discussed in that book.
Instead it ends with him being cartoed away by the Nazis with no mercy.
And this is what's, as some of the listeners may know, the twilight zone is my favorite
TV show of all time.
I am obsessed with it. I own every episode from all three iterations of it. And I also own
the movie and my problem with the movie has always been that it is far too sinister for
the Twilight Zone. The Twilight Zone is supposed to be scary and creepy and freaky, but there's
also supposed to be a social commentary to it and it's not about comeuppance. Tails and the
The opening segment is a great opening segment with Dan Ackroyd and Albert Brooks.
But it's basically Dan Ackroyd is a demon man and he kills Albert Brooks and there's
no real reason for any of it and that's not the Twilight Zone, that's that's straight
the finished version. I would like two young boys to still be alive so they would be grown
in now and I'd like to still see Vic Morrow's work so it's all very tragic. I met Dan
Acroid two times. I'm going to do his more name dropping. When I was working as a page at 30 Rock
and the first was he came to an SNL after party offered me cocaine. Could not have been nicer but
I mean he was 55 or 60. He offered me cocaine. I'm like no I'm good. He was there. Well I'm hesitant
to say anything because he's a married man, but he was, uh, he was having a real good
time and like, love blowing up spots offering everyone cocaine. He was, he was being fun,
but he was like the life of the party and there was an element of, of a little bit of tragedy
about it because he was trying to live like it was 75 on the set of SNL and, you know, he's
like, your dad and he didn't do coke with him. You fucking, I hadn't done coke at the time.
I didn't do it till I met Jotarosa. Oh, stop it. And then I hated it. And I'm so thankful
I hated it because I have an addictive personality that's not true. You did it before I ever knew you. I didn't introduce you to a drug
The first time I did it. I did it with you
Really? That's a hundred percent true. I'm flattered and I didn't like it. I'm the Dan Acroider this podcast
No, folks. I mean Joe rarely offers me any cocaine
He's always
Doing it, but he never offers it stop it. That's not true. All right
And then the other time he came to Conan and you want to hear a real dark story
And it sucked as he was nice, but this was perhaps due to the years of cocaine use, decades of cocaine use
He's like afterwards he goes, so how are we gonna handle this?
I'm supposed to walk him down to his car on the street after his segment on Conan. I go handle what?
He's like, well the the fans and the paparazzi and everything
And I was like, oh no, because huge stars were often like they don't know that they're coming to Conan
You have a few autograph seekers, but that's it and he comes down and he's like up against the wall
like a Tom and Jerry cartoon like how are we gonna handle all these people and I
look around and there's like one guy in a wheelchair looking to get something
signed and Acroid sprints out past him he was like can you walk with me like he
he thought that I was gonna like block the the throngs of fans oh good and then he
sprinted out almost like an illwood blues style run with his knees up high ran
man out of 30 rock to his car, it was real rough and it made me realize like you got
a really rule with the ups and downs in this business, baby.
You can't think like it's, it's 75 when it's 2005, you're not on top anymore, baby.
Sure.
Yeah.
That's a rough one.
That's it.
What is he's doing, Coke?
At least he's got Coke sweets.
It's a close out the Joe scary stuff segment. I will plug. I mean, again, these are not people sponsoring me to say this. These are just things I think our fans would enjoy if you like old school video games. I'm on a big Nintendo throwback kick since the NES classic came out. I just picked up a super Nintendo the other day.
But if you like that sort of thing, two games that fall into the sci -fi genre and the sci -fi horror genre.
they did ports of, I believe, the first six or seven Mega Man games on the Apple iPad and iPhone.
They also did a great port of R -Type, which is really fantastic. I would suggest playing them
on the pad because it's bigger, you have more space, you're going to be using virtual buttons,
the phone's a little small for my taste unless you have that jumbo iPhone. But they are excellent,
excellent excellent ports and they're right you're gonna love it so just go get
that shit okay and that's the segment Pat and again because the segment
always be strangely close to an ad these are not paid advertisement I said that
already all right all right now that's why I said and again let's talk about the
movie get out is the movie this week George get out and get out folks is certainly
the best horror movie of this year, and I would say the best in quite a few years.
And it does what, I mean, there's whole documentaries about how horror and the 70s and stuff
would be talking about Vietnam or talking about race, talking about all kinds of issues.
But it's been a while till there was really any sort of, since there was any sort of commentary
in a horror movie, unless I'm forgetting something, or unless it was very stupidly handled.
I would I think that the comment this type of commentary found in a horror movie hasn't been seen in a while
I think a long while too long. I think other movies do have a commentary. It's much more subtle. Yeah
But but you know, this is you know the comparisons to get at the you know how like the fly was an allegory for AIDS
But if the fly came out in 1986 it's much rarer
And I wish there were more because it gives the horror genre which is always in the ghetto a great deal of legitimacy
and it makes people talk about them much more seriously than they would ordinarily.
Well, the movie that this is compared to pretty consistently in the reviews and write -ups that I've read is The Stepford Wives.
Sure. So you have movies like The Stepford Wives, or like Get Out, that have a very overt statement being me,
and then you have other things like Friday the 13th, that is sort of a much subtler statement about teen sex and the dangers of misbehaving and that sort of thing.
Do you think that was the intent of a Friday the 13th because I absolutely I absolutely do. I don't think it was to
Skold them. Yeah, I think it was just a commentary on on the times of teenagers being scolded
We should again
It's a very professional show. We did not do even a brief synopsis of the film which well we're getting to it
We would do I wasn't gonna let it's not do it get out is written indirected by the great Jordan peel of key and peel fame right
Um, so people ask, you know, well, he's funny.
Is it a comedy?
Truthfully, yes, it's an extremely dark comedy.
It's, but it doesn't detract from the horror and it doesn't feel like a comedy
like scream where it's parodying a genre.
Um, basically the gist of it is a, uh, a young African American gentleman is
dating a young white woman.
They've been dating three or four months.
She's going to take them home to meet her parents.
He gets there, parents are Bradley Whitford and Catherine Keener who are both great as our
Allison Williams and what is the young gentleman's name?
I don't know, because I've never seen him in any of these.
I think I'd mispronounce it.
I think he was on a black mirror.
I'm going to look it up now.
I've never seen him before.
I did notice he wasn't a black mirror because I did notice there were a couple times where
I was like, wait a minute.
Does he have an English accent?
Yeah.
He will.
He is British.
Okay.
I thought I heard it slip through a few times.
And my buddy, Little Rowell, is in the film, so funny.
As the best friend and he's just hits a home fucking run man. Yeah, well
I mean we'll tell you when there's gonna be spoilers
But I I have never heard a cheer in a movie since that fat force awakens as I did at the end of this movie
Yeah, I mean he that guy is so he's funny
And there were moments where threatened to go a little too big to keep the horror real
But they never did like he kept it very legitimate the guy is so is so great
He's a he's just if you've never seen a little raldo stand up do yourself a favor go see it. It's
He's he's he's you know gut dare. I say gut bustingly funny
Yeah, but I mean he's the kind of comic that I watch and I retell the jokes to people
And he hits it just a grand slam in this movie everybody's great in the movie. I mean he's a complete star from the second
He's saying but Daniel Caluia is the actor. I didn't want to say
Kaluah, which is what I almost said, not that it's that far off, but I didn't want to be like the guy who says
Shamalama ding dong or something and be offensive. Daniel Kaluah, he was in the, actually one of my lesser favorite black mirrors, the one where the guy
Is in like war times and they're telling them they're killing bugs and all that kind of stuff. All right
But she goes up top and and he reads the strange behavior at home as being judgment on their interracial relationship
But actually something much more sinister is going on. Yeah, and title itself is kind of genius because it's basically like
Get out of our country and like of course this was made pre -Trump
But like there really could not be a more timely way to handle this subject matter than in a horror movie where
Comedy's great the horror is great and the social commentary is great. They're all 10 out of 10's like you can't do much better than this
Yeah, and you know pretty much from the jump. I mean that there's a
I was talking to a friend of mine and he said well, I want to see it
But I feel like the commercial gives too much away. And I said the commercial
Doesn't give too much away the commercial gives you a lot of information because I feel like the movie is bigger
than the plot and the twists and whatever the movie really is
About the satire and the social commentary of it all because you know right off the bat
There's a line very in the first scene or whatever between the couple where
Allison Williams
What was the guy right? What's the guy's naming in Daniel Kaluuya, so we're Daniel's use Daniel's character says
I'm a little nervous, you know I'm paraphrasing but but your parents don't know I'm black
Are they gonna be okay with it? And Allison William says my dad would have voted for Obama third time if he could have
huge grown in the theater. So right off the bat, you know, at the very least, we're dealing
with some guilty white people here that are saying the wrong shit. And then it's obviously
gonna snowball from there. And it does. And those early scenes, which are, you know, almost
like meet the parents and got similar giant laughs are Whitford, who was really fucking good
in this, like just saying all the things that your dad would say, if you're white, my
dad would say, if he was trying to make an African -American person feel more comfortable,
but in doing so makes them significantly more uncomfortable.
Well, the one thing he says that I don't think a lot of dads would say is, and it's in the
commercial and it's very uncomfortable when he goes, how long's this been going on this
thing. Yeah, that's very uncomfortable. Yeah. He kind of shows his cards real early with that one.
Yes. But Whitford is great. And somehow plays a bigger piece of shit than I've ever seen
Whitford play. And Whitford always plays a piece of shit. The first time Whitford was on my radar was
playing a huge old piece of shit, trying to kill Billy Madison's good time. Billy Madison delivered
my favorite line in Billy Madison when he's mad because his friend didn't offer him
Trisket crackers because you know, I'm hungry.
Didn't offer me a trisket crackers and he goes, oh, I'm sorry.
That doesn't put the delicious trisket crackers in my stomach.
Not does it? Yeah.
Whitford's great.
I'm a big fan.
When he first was on my radar, it was Revenge of the Nerds 2.
Oh, sure.
He plays the villain.
Yeah, that's right.
He plays the head like fraternity jet.
Let's go bash some nerds.
Like he's always that guy.
Yeah, but he's great at it.
And I know I kind of don't want to see him play anything else.
It's probably, oh, he said of a woman.
Yeah, that's right.
That scene is my favorite scene in set of a woman.
Wes Wing, he was a good person,
but he still had a bit of a swarm about him.
Yeah, but homerun, Kathleen Keener,
everybody was really good.
We need to really, you gotta praise fucking Jordan Peel,
who's never directed anything and never written a movie.
And when I heard he was doing a horror movie,
I wasn't skeptical at all.
I knew it would be interesting,
but, you know, I, well, I,
Yeah, this is what happens is now that you work in this business.
You start to shit on something and then you realize you shouldn't.
So I don't and I won't.
But folks, I love Jordan Peele and I think that this is one of the best debuts of my lifetime.
I mean, to get something that this theater was like, might as well have been on its feet
by the end of this fucking thing.
The ending of the, I saw with the buddy of mine, I look over at him and he's wiping tears
from his eyes, and there's nothing emotional in it, but he was just like, I realized that
I was so stressed out that like, I started crying. Like, the horror works so well, but really
what you're thinking about it when I'm thinking about a week later, and why I'm going to see
it again as soon as possible, is what it's saying. And I think, it doesn't in such a way that
the white people in the audience can feel like, oh, well, that's not me, and I'm better than
that. But it also does it in a way that makes you be like, I've been that guy before. I've
said that before. I've made somebody feel uncontrolled before. Um, I think that's what's
kind of genius about it. And the get out is the perfect title because that's essentially
what, I mean, Trump's not saying get out black people, but he's saying get out a lot of
people. And that's really what the point of the movie is is that America wants to use black
people for their athletic ability, their entertaining ability, their coolness, their this and that.
But they don't want to treat them as equals, and it's disgusting, and that is essentially
what's going on in the movie's head, which is what makes it, I think, the best.
As you keep talking about this, I'm getting more and more nervous.
Why?
Because we're revealed.
Oh, you think I'm going to say something stupid?
But yeah, it's making me nervous.
I'm just, and that's the beauty of it.
I'm just telling you exactly what the movie is about.
It's about white people essentially using black people
and not realizing they're doing it.
Do you think it's about them not realizing they're doing it
or them not caring that they're doing it?
Both.
Yeah, I think, I mean, these people obviously don't care.
The light of the evil people.
But I think who it's really going after
is the people who are sitting on that audience
at the Los Felas III when I saw it.
And the people that you and I have
of a real hard time stomaching,
the people who think that they are super progressive,
but are actually gross.
It's like, you know, how Jamie Kielstahn,
let's talk about Jamie Kielstahn.
Steen.
Steen, you know, that dude.
But let's just look, you can,
perfect example.
He's like, he's a outspoken feminist,
and you find out he's been harassing women online.
Well, he's been accused of it.
We, we, we, we, we, we, we, we, we, we're not here to condemn.
We don't, we're not the judge or jury,
but he's been accused of, I'll judge him.
He's he's been accused of it and you know, I'm not a fan, but you know, I don't know
anyone who is.
I wouldn't be surprised if he did do the things that people were saying because it's
usually the loudest voice is the most corrupt.
You know, that's what I'm saying.
And I thought that was a big undercurrent of get out as well.
But there's an easier way for you to say this, there's an easier way for you to say who
you're trying to talk about.
Most of our friends.
Yeah.
There you go.
Yeah, most of the people we know, patting themselves on the back, I'm so good. I'm so understanding.
I mean, it really killed me. I mean, you want to get into this. The Oscars. You want to talk
about something here? Yeah, the Oscars aired on Sunday. To watch. This is going to drop on Monday,
so it'll be a week ago, but you know, you know, we're talking about it. To watch so many celebrities
that I've seen publicly condemned Trump for being a self -centered businessman who only cares about
money and doesn't give a shit about poor people unless it, to see these same people
stroll down a red carpet. Oh, this is Giovanni Burdeen that I'm wearing or whatever
fucking designer they're wearing with these six, seven, ten thousand dollar dresses and
tuxedo's on. Fuck you. Yeah. Fuck you. Yeah. It's so fucking gross. It's so fucking gross.
And then as they partake in this event that is perpetuated every type of entertainment
in our popular culture that has allowed a man like this
to become president, the city that is fucking just conveyor
about produced reality TV for the last 20 years,
that has only worshipped the dollar for the last 70 years.
It's so fucking gross.
And they all act like, oh no, it's not me,
it's not, no it is you, it's you, it's you.
You're as much a part of this fucking problem
as anybody else.
So anyway, couldn't agree more, let's see if I keep that tone when I get nominated.
No, I mean, if I ever, I feel the same way, I mean, the people get up there and it's like,
like, I mean, here's another thing, I assume she was a producer of Moonlight, but when they
finally corrected the vote, and Moonlight went up there, I'm going to have to agree that
Moonlight is the best picture.
But everyone feels, I think really truly feels judging by Twitter, and almost everyone
everyone I know, everyone that saw La La Land before the hype started, fucking loved it.
Then I see people like, now shitting on it, because at some point it got misconstrued
that La La Land is a racist movie because Ryan Gosling is a white guy who likes jazz.
So that level of sensitivity is so ludicrous to me, but people won't even admit they like
it anymore.
And then when they saw the LaLand had won
The all all of America at least the people on Twitter were
Vocally talking about how this is a racist country because a movie won a thing like what are you talking about?
Of course it is a racist country, but not because of that then Moonlight
Rightly wins and it's like oh, okay, so what now racism ends cuz Moonlight weren't what the fuck are you talking about that's and again
Let's get back to get out
That's the beauty of get out the beauty of the grown moments when the things come out of the white characters mouths in the movie
Yeah, it's because you know that Jordan Peele has his finger on I know you think you're not racist
But what you just said was racist. Yeah, he's got his finger on that pulse. It's expertly done
It takes shots equally at at at at at at a leadest
Conservatives as much as it does as guilty liberals
I really just think it's it is a brilliant brilliant commentary on the on race relations in America and
Smaller things in it like Keener hypnotizes him very early on in the movie and she's doing it with a silver spoon
Well, I pointed that out to you the other day
But if you want to take it now into you and make it sound like you thought of it. That's fine
But I point that out to you the other day
I said to you literally the exact words the attention to detail the fact that church hypnotic devices is so
over spoon. I mean, you just, you just take it. What does it matter with you?
The, what does it matter with you? The beam of light when they're taking this is what
the movie's talking about. You're at arrogant. No, Joe, Joe, this isn't, this isn't what
the movie's talking about. That thinks he can just throw his balls around on everything.
How do you know the end of that sentence, which I did not get to finish was as Joe pointed
out because it wasn't. You're not going to, you're not going to massage my balls. Um, theft
And to think it's okay that you just stole that, but it's okay. I'm not
Thieving what what was an idea that was in the movie? It wasn't your idea and I'm taking credit for it
You said I didn't notice that. That's really cool. All right fair
Fair, Joe you didn't say that I was a lie. I lied about that part. Yeah, I didn't say it
Jesus this is a wild time
But there's there's an element with a camera in the movie and what the camera does to people in the movie
I'm not gonna spoil that, but just these things that like they work brilliantly as simply horror
But then a week later, you're just like fuck
That's exactly right. That's perfect. That's but and nothing is showy or calling attention to itself
But it's also not so obscure that like somebody tells you, you know
Home alone is an allegory for the Holocaust or whatever and you're like no, you're an idiot. It's all there
Yeah, it's not room. What's that documentary? Oh
Yeah, the shining one.
Makes me want to roam through 36 or no.
Uh.
I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you,
didn't like when the main character said to the guy
from news radio, spoiler alert.
Spoiler alert.
When, you know, he finds, figures out what's going on
and everything and he goes why black people
and Stephen Root goes, I don't know, why not?
Why anybody?
You know?
That was the only line I didn't like.
I actually thought that sold the weight of it a little short
because there was clearly a reason
they were only going after black people.
I thought.
Yes, well, I think that he was painted as a better than the other people kind of guy because
he was blind.
He's obviously a monster, what he does in the movie is monstrous, but he's a blind guy
who truly doesn't see color because he can't.
Oh, that's interesting.
And I think he's saying, you know, why not black people, but everybody else can see and
is just doing it anyway.
All right.
Well, I think that made him a slightly morally better person.
I think not really now he's a monster, but morally superior to
Whitford for Christ say
No, no, he still buys a human being
Pat maybe I just like Steven Roode. I think this was a hell of a kickoff discussion and a hell of an episode one for our
fourth season of we'll see you in hell
I forget we we call them seasons just when we forget to do the podcast for a month or two then it's like
Oh, that was a hiatus and now this is a new season.
It changes up and it, you know, whatever,
but we're really thrilled to be here at HeadGum.
We're very happy to be here.
Let's sign off on some plugs and get it into the port.
Well, a personal plug and a business plug.
I know I talked a lot last time about how I was hoping
I had a pilot picked up by the CBS Network and I did.
So I've been working on that.
It's a living nightmare.
Every aspect of it is worse than I could have ever imagined.
Now we are casting, I gotta tell you folks,
if you're an actor, I need to talk to you.
I need to talk to you about changing how you're doing things.
A lot of bad acting out there.
There's a lot of people who are like, offer only,
you see that next to their name,
which means like Tom Cruise is offer only.
If you're gonna put Tom Cruise in a movie,
He does an audition, right you offer him the role, right also offer only
50 % of actors in Hollywood who have never done a single fucking thing, right sounds like
Sounds like you're in your own Jordan peel movie. Yeah, I'm like, hey
I'd love to see this actor try it. I feel like they might be able to do it, but they won't audition
I don't trust you off of you being in one episode of ugly Betty to be the star of a multi -cam sitcom get the fuck over yourself. Not really a
plug, just weren't a shot at somebody, friends with America, Ferara.
No, that wasn't a real person, I just made that up.
But the ego of these actors, and then people come in,
and I'm like, oh, I love this actor,
and then they're bad in person,
and you're like, oh, I guess you were edited to be good.
There are people that you're like,
oh, that piece of shit actor,
and they come in and they're amazing.
Pat the world is shit, and we live in the butthole
that is spewing all the shit out, so.
It's terrible, it's all just the hype machine,
and people who are absolutely worthless are celebrated
and people who are amazing are swept off to the corner
because they won't be the Eagle maniacal maniacs
that this town makes you be if you want to succeed.
And I'm slowly slipping away sanity -wise
because of this whole process
and I have to just keep telling myself every day,
Pat, you're funny and this will all be over soon.
And hopefully I'll have a show in the air
but then the whole problem just keeps going for it.
I don't even know I don't even know of course I want to show on the air and I'm being very careful not to talk about anybody or anything in particular
I'll just say every aspect of it is beyond frustrating and I'm trying to do it
We'll also working a full -time job and and keeping this podcast going which takes up about 45 minutes a week folks
It's a grind
We do it all for you want to plug something pet on a personal plug. I'd like to plug love
I got engaged to my girlfriend of four years
There's, do you want to plug something?
I told you, I have a personal, and I'm,
it's not, that's not plugged.
You just, this is on a therapy couch.
Is, is gas gonna seep into this room
if we don't finish in the next two fucking minutes?
This should happen the other night.
You know what?
You know, I'm out at the bar the other night.
We sit down, great to see, I've been gone
for a week and a half of it on the road.
Great to see you buddy.
What's going on?
90 minutes later, I say, well, that's,
that's pretty crazy pet.
I mean, for 90 minutes, he's screaming at you.
Booth about this goddamn TV ship I've been that voice for you as well
And I would call that friendship, but I guess it's a one -way street
In derosa time. Well Pat. I have always said friendship is only it any kind of ship allows more than one person on board
I don't know what that means. I really don't know what that means
But um ship so I got engaged and maybe they don't at you on it
But a lot of people have asked about it. I'm not gonna tell you how I propose because it's my personal life
But I'm engaged I don't get personal as you just blow up the spot about your entire
Pilot in her workings in the I know from Ugly Betty or this you can Dan Acquire try to give you coke in the bathroom literally
Nobody I mentioned is a real person. There's nobody who did one episode of Ugly Betty who I'm talking about people in general
I'm not singling out any actors all right, but God it's a nightmare another way to go there Joe would be to say
Congratulations on either the pilot or getting engaged. I've congratulated you many times and not just
but the people haven't heard it.
You see what I'm saying?
Many times.
The people have not heard that I'm in,
you don't care about us.
You want to know if I'm engaged.
They want to know if I got a pilot going.
You scream for four minutes, but you're pilot,
and then you passively you go,
and I got engaged.
Talk for four minutes about the engagement.
I don't want to talk because that's my personal private life.
So is the other thing.
No, it isn't.
Why is it not?
I've talked about both things on here,
and people ask, hey, how's the pilot going?
How's the engagement going?
Listen, congrats.
You got engaged and very proud of you.
I hope your pilot doesn't go
because you will be an insufferable man
if that show gets good.
Can I tell you, people,
and I'm gonna give you 100 % guarantee
everyone is much more interested in those two things
I just briefly talked about
than you saying you're at the chuckle factory
on July 12th.
No, that's really.
In Tempe, Arizona.
Nobody gives a shit unless they're in Tempe, Arizona.
Well, that's very harsh.
I'm talking about my life
because I feel like people want to know who we are.
Notice notice a thing Pat doesn't do when he's talking about his life. Hey Joe has your life. No, I know this is none of that just
Me me me you're gonna do your plugs next me me me me me me me me me me me me
Listen you sold your soul to a dirty bastard business, and now you're reaping what you've sewn
Suck it up daddy. You're in hell, and you made your bed right in the flames
games. So enjoy it. I'm in. Just terrible. I'm sorry. I'm sorry you're feeling down,
all right. Tell us more about video games, Joe. I'm just listening on a on a more movie
podcast. Can I plug a thing? I need a favor from the fans. Sure. Also, folks, you can find
me at the Patrick Walsh at Twitter and Instagram. Very nice. I follow Pat. It's very enjoyable.
yeah look I'll be at South by Southwest if you're in Austin come by yeah Pat
because I get out of this town I go visit to the regular places I go talk to
the common people not like you and your golden throne next to Andy McDowell's house
what are you talking about listen I actually need a favor from the from the fans my
special and album are out now you let me down released by Comedy Central they're
both on iTunes.
Guys, can you give me a favor?
Can you give me a favor?
You've given us such great reviews on this podcast.
A series of trolls have brought all my album ratings down
to shit on iTunes and Amazon.
And I mean that, they're trolls.
They weren't people giving bad reviews, they're trolls.
Can you please go give me some good reviews on these albums
if you've had them, if you've heard them, if you like them?
I'd like to get the ratings up back
to where they were supposed to be,
which was five stars across the board till the trolls came along.
So, and also, if you could rate this podcast, which is now on a new network,
yeah, that big grade, because that's what this is really about.
Oh, is it? You sure?
Yeah, I thought it was, I thought this was about another chapter in the life of Walsh.
Walsh, I'm answering the fans' questions.
I'm answering the fans' questions.
You think I don't get fans' questions?
Joe. How are you in bed? Joe, how big is it? Joe, you're ego. Will you
quite me? Oh, stop it. All right. I love you. Joe DeRosa comedy on Twitter
and I and Instagram and the Patrick Walsh on both as we've discussed.
Patty, keep the tweets coming. If you guys want to find some archives, you know,
one I'd recommend on the top of my head would be the blue and media Halloween
episode. Joe, what's your favorite of our old ones? Dr. Strange is one of my
favorite. Dr. Strangler. That's great. That's set me off in ways that I can't even exploit.
Yeah. We're happy to have you on the new place. We're thankful to HeadGum. We love you guys and
we're excited to be here. Thank you everybody. We'll be back next week with probably the neon
demon unless things change, but we will do the neon demon at some point if you want to watch that and
get caught up. Take care. Take care. That was a HeadGum podcast.