Summer is here and Bed MDM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer, or check out
our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz.
Only available at Bed MDM Casino.
Spend on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 fortunes, Mystery of the Land,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand!
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action!
Bet MGM in Game Sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 Plus to Waiter, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and West Virginia
only.
Games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as normal, durable site credit slash bonus bets unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
The football season is full of guarantees, and here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October, if
your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning or winning money back in fan
cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
Winning hits different here.
Monthly 21 -plus, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamberer, offer not available in all states
terms apply, see Fanatic Sportsbook app.
Hey folks, we'll see you in hell. We're all back again. You'll podcast your love. It's
brought to you by the Fangoria Podcast Network. You want some info on the network? Maybe
this program, other programs. We'll see you in hell. Find an old episode. Go visit
Fangoria .com. Pat, the magic's gone with this intro. I can't read this goddamn thing anymore.
It wasn't great. No. Can you start reading it for a little while?
I think the people want that and I was waiting for you to extend that offer to me as I think we all were.
I, yeah, it's forced. It's desperate a little bit.
Yeah, I feel like I'm in the talent of a six month run.
Yeah, of Oklahoma, like, we're just, you know, it's a mat and a show.
I'm like, I can't do this anymore.
There's a soft golden haze on the meadow.
That's the first song from Oklahoma, which Joe is apparently unfamiliar with.
I am making the reference.
I don't know any of the songs.
I was in Oklahoma in high school, and I was great, frankly, I was in Oklahoma last week.
Okay.
At the ha ha.
See, I was doing a location joke.
I also portrayed Danny Zuko in Greece.
How?
Well, very well.
I mean, you couldn't resemble an Italian less.
You know, it's Missouri high school.
like it's not like we had like a melting pot.
Yeah, that's what I'm thinking.
I also portrayed Miss Rosa Parks in the Rosa Parks story.
Sure.
I refused to move to the back of the bus in a very
tasteful black face.
Sure.
No, that's not true.
But I played the 10 man.
I was quite a performer.
I played the the juror and 12 angry man who was like,
yeah, budget idiots.
The one that's like, my son hates me.
at the end. In high school you played this role. That's right. It's pretty heavy for a high school
play. Look, I was a thespian. And that's what you want folks is for your principle to announce
loudly over the intercom while you're amongst your peers and being bullied every day. That you're
a new addition to the international thespian society. Well, I don't know if you're picking up on it,
but it sounds a good deal like lesbian. I tell you my classmates definitely picked up on.
That's an old golden girls routine
What that that's been sounds like yeah, yeah, yeah, well wait. No Lebanese. That's the one I'm thinking
Yeah, Lebanese rose
Lebanese
The uh, I just love it would you know just when I thought I couldn't be more impressed by my buddy Pat Walsh
Find out he's covering roles
That were portrayed from everybody from Travolta to Victa back on the stage. That's very impressive to me
That's right a wide range. I didn't actually play Rosa Parks. I feel like I need to be I know overly sensitive today because I was called a racist twice today
And both I find equally ludicrous
The first was of course on Twitter where even though I do shit on Trump pretty regularly
No one's I never brought out that real awful element. Yeah, you know the whole other half of Twitter
until today, when I tweeted, which I think is a decent joke, Ben Carson as the head of
housing and urban development, what was Godzilla unavailable? Because Godzilla destroys houses
and cities. Right, right. I thought it was a very clear joke. And this guy, I didn't even pick
up on that part. I just, that's a layered joke. I just thought, because he's a monster. And I thought
I was very funny.
Oh, okay.
That impressed at the layering
with the destroying of houses and cities.
Oh, I guess maybe it wasn't clear
and maybe I should clarify it.
Well, look, how somebody else took it on the right
was that I was racist
because Ben Carson is black
and I guess so is Godzilla
except Godzilla's green.
Or maybe he thinks that
Dinosaur is a race.
I didn't know.
But once he did it, 10 other guys were like,
you racist, et cetera, et cetera.
Well, here's the thing is, and I've noticed this,
people that really are, that are really into the extreme right.
The way they react to the PC police on the extreme left
is they start to call you racist ironically.
You think they were doing it ironically?
Yeah, they do it to be like, how dare you, you racist.
Do you? Okay, I sized a black person. I'd buy that's usually what they're doing and then they try to they you know
They do want to so a lot of the time harm you right with the words
But they're doing it under that guys usually well
I mean at any time you're called a racist which I I have been twice I think in my life both this week
Effected me the other was a big fan of this podcast who tweets at us 10 12 times every time we do a podcast
I guess she's usually very delightful,
a young African -American lady.
And in the midst of like 10 great tweets
about love in the show, and this was funny,
and that was funny, and she said,
we really do need to talk about Patrick's hatred
of all black leads in movies.
Why Pat doesn't like black actors?
I didn't see that.
And I stared at this for an hour,
And I was just like I'm not gonna respond because it I feel like on Twitter if you respond to someone calling you racist
Whether people want to or not. You're scrolling through on the toilet. You associate me with racism kind of if if if I'm suddenly
Engaging and defending myself against being a race
I was like I'm just gonna let it go. The girls clearly not out to get me and I thank her for being a fan
But I kept thinking about it and I was like we've talked about so many movies. I've shot on so many actors so many movies
All I remember doing is I think it's on one that hasn't aired yet, but last week we recorded two
I talked about how charming and delightful Denzel Washington was, but that hasn't aired yet, and I was maybe the only person in the
World to support Tyler Perry's boo Medea Halloween journey. That's what I was going to say. I mean if anything proves that pet
or else it was racist, he had the audacity
to say boo, a Medea Halloween.
Would you just call it a Halloween,
Halloween, Medea journey?
Yeah.
He had the audacity to defend that film.
So I was baffled and I could see if like somebody
was going through all our old archives
and was like, I said something that could be construed as racist.
I would believe that.
I'd be like, oh yeah, I mean, we've done so many of these
and drunk and maybe something came off wrong
whatever. But to say like your problem is you don't like any black male actors. I'm baffled by
that because I can't think of any black male actor I've shat on on the show. Neither can I right
now. Not a single one. I can't either. Maybe she was just joking and it didn't land. You know, I
can, you know, that can happen without getting two into details. I sent you some texts a friend
that was sending to me the other day and I said, pet, this person, is this person crazy or what?
like look at these texts and I said yes she is and you said yeah but she's
trying to be funny right now yeah yeah you what you said you said you're you
said what's happening is she's trying to be funny it's not landing and you're
taking it literally so maybe that's what happened with the tweet maybe she's just
trying to be funny it didn't land right in that case I think it was a a crazy
person trying to be funny which is a very hard thing to follow let's not start
calling the fans crazy no I'm talking about your person oh oh now I'm going to
talk about okay so this tweet and that the young lady's name is Chanel I won't say her last name
because I don't want people to talk to her and harass her. She looks lovely as a child and her
photo or perhaps just a young boy who's a friend I don't know. She says we really need to talk
about how no black male entertainers impress you. Then there's this frowny face and then it does
say LOL frankly. Yeah maybe she's just maybe she's talking about me because I really went hard on Tyler
Perry, maybe, maybe, but like I was, I was very confused. And blackmail entertainers.
And I don't think I've talked about any blackmail entertainer in a negative way.
The, the, the, Medea is really stuck in my head right now. I can't really think of, I
loved it. I mean, I, I just booked tickets to see the weekend on November, our January
3rd December 30th. So what do you see? The weekend. Oh, the musician got a poster up
I swear to God, I thought you meant Tyler Perry was doing a play with Medea and it called the weekend and you were going to go see it now
Paramount or whatever. I mean, I'm not going to be the guy who starts listing off all the black entertainers. I like and my black friends, but I was I was
Shooking up. I love all entertainers, particularly a black entertainer. I don't think you're defending yourself hard enough right now.
the extremely sexual music of the weekend brought my girlfriend and I together.
Honestly, it was the first show we ever saw. We sat in the front row before he was famous.
We all know you're not a racist. Now we're going to see him on New Year's.
This man played a slick hair ginger Danny Zuko. Any racist would have spat at the idea of
playing an Italian man as a redhead. I don't see a race, frankly.
Yeah, well there you go. I look did you see oh no here's what I did and this I know this has an aired yet
Because we did too so sometimes you get confused which ones aired and which hasn't but in the in the one that's coming up
We discussed town. Oh, no, we did this was the killborn one. I discussed how I don't like Trevor Noah
Oh, maybe that's what she's referring and you agreed that you don't like Trevor Noah
But I got I just got singled out for some reason now since then that amazing Trevor Noah interview with that tome
Fox News bitch aired
and he eviscerated her for 30 minutes.
I watched this interview and I was like,
what an incredible interview this is.
And I loved that, but you know, night by night,
I don't think Trevor Noah is hilarious.
Also, I don't know if you could find a whiter back man.
Now that's probably racist.
I don't know people.
Listen man, you're really on pins and needles today man.
Well, I think like it happens, trust me,
I've been at the receiving end of a lot, a lot, a lot of Twitter hate over the years.
It's people say thing and I've had people actively try to destroy me.
No, I know.
Like I was some sort of evil like business landowner or something like, you know, so
I wouldn't worry about it.
I think she was just having a little fun.
She was.
Now that I see the smiley face, I don't know why I overreacted.
You didn't overreact.
You got a little rattled and that's part of life, you know.
I just know that that's not what's in my heart, isn't that what Michael Richard said on when
and they brought on the most awkward interview of all the time.
Yeah, I'd say the more you talk about it,
the deeper a hole will get.
I just like to dig into shit.
That's a little uncomfortable.
Yeah, I had a situation the other night,
because I said on stage at my,
we do this hip -hop comedy show called Can I Kick It?
And at the top of the show, I said how I didn't vote.
And that's not a, I've learned not a great thing
to say in front of an LA audience.
There's not a stop right there.
They're not very uh what's what's wrong with you? There's nothing wrong with me
What's right with me is what you should be asking? What's wrong with all of you? No, I know look at what you've all done
I know that you did look at what you've all done
Please do not include me on that
but I know I
Know you didn't vote. I don't agree with it
My my go -to statement is uh, you know
Not voting is like not applauding at a concert
It makes no difference, but I do it because I'm not an asshole.
That's how I feel about it. That's a terrible reason to vote.
Maybe it is, but I think people would say that you vote to, you know, people fought for your ride, et cetera, et cetera.
If you don't vote fine, and I think I think probably some of these people who are going over the top about voting,
maybe some of them didn't make it to the polls either, but just like to talk about shit, but
When Joe says on Twitter the other day, I didn't vote blah blah. And then is texting me like why are people upset?
That's not what I did. That's not what I did. That's not that's not
Contort history here the gist of it was no that was people are no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no
valid point and that's the valid point that I think and I was absolutely right in the
response it got because the response it got was everybody that loves Hillary being
mad that I didn't vote for Hillary.
And then people on the left who I'm friends with who didn't like Hillary and were mad at
the left because of what they did where they allegedly did to Bernie Sanders then texting
me and saying and then defending me on Twitter and saying you're getting bullied by Hillary
supporters right now, which is exactly what happened.
And I also will take Umbridge with this.
I will also take Umbridge with this.
If we're, I consider myself a progressive, I do, honestly, I think that I'm a pretty
open -minded and liberally -minded person.
I don't vote, I don't subscribe to either party, I have never voted.
But it bothers me when the team that waves the progressive flag the hardest starts coming
down on you because you didn't do it the way they wanted you to do it or the way they
think you need to do it. I think it's kind of bullshit. And I saw it a lot when people
were being chastised because they supported Jill Stein. People were being chastised because
they supported that other third party guy. People were being... Gary Johnson, excuse me. People
were being chastised because they liked Bernie. Bernie himself was chastised. And really
what it came down to was we've now muscled in this candidate, which is fine, well, I don't
give a shit what you'd think about Hillary Clinton or not, but then don't tell me that
I'm a fucking asshole because you shove me into the ring of something and go, you know,
now participate.
No, I don't have to do that.
And I happen to truly believe that not voting and people bucking the system and giving
the middle finger up will potentially, could potentially change things.
I don't believe that playing ball as we always have all the time is doing a goddamn thing because every eight years
Half of this country is telling me that our country is over and it's the worst it's ever been
It happened at the beginning of the W. Bush administration
It happened at the beginning of the Obama administration. It's happening now again with Trump
The things people were saying to me about Trump who I think is a douchebag and I'm not happy about that guy being an office
But the stuff people are saying to me
I'm like, this is literally the same thing everybody was saying to me about Bush and this is literally the same things
I read liberal or conservative people saying about Obama and you know what?
My life hasn't changed that much since either of the presidencies were in the course of action and
have ended. So do I think Trump's an idiot? Of course. Do I think he sucks? Of course. Do I like the guy?
No. But am I going to go into a goddamn white knuckle panic and think that my world is going to end with
a mushroom cloud tomorrow? No, I'm not doing that either. Sorry. No, that is not going
to happen. But I think things are going to get quite bad. I never heard anybody say
that around the time of Obama. All I heard was hope. But then I wasn't living in, you know,
racist bum fuck down. Well, that's why I, that's why I say the things I read because it was
re, because I lived in New York when that happened and it was a very hopeful time or hopeful
spirit in New York. But if you went online and read or if when I went home and talked
to people in the neighborhood, I grew up in the older people, not people my age. But
you know, adults, maybe friends of the family, whatever. Dude, they were talking about Obama,
like you would have thought Goddamn to take a line out of your book. Godzilla was in office.
I was just like, what the fuck? So my point is, is I just refuse to play that game. I have
no stake in any of this.
I try to be a good person in the day to day.
I try to love the people around me.
Yeah.
But you're not changing anything by not voting.
That's absurd.
I think if a lot of people didn't vote,
and there are a lot of people don't vote.
There are.
It doesn't matter.
There are other believers in the movement out there.
There is support of a non -voting movement out there.
And that's not a movement.
Well, why is it not doing absolutely nothing?
Because this is what the rules are.
You you you staying home and sleeping in does not change anything nor will it so that if you were to if you were to go
You know, I don't know protesting doesn't seem to do a great deal except sometimes it does look at this the Native American situation going on
I don't I'm not saying I have gone to protest or anything either writing a letter to your congressman probably doesn't do much
But people do that. I'm just saying you saying I'm going to do nothing is certainly not going to change anything
I don't think it's doing nothing.
I think it's saying it is doing nothing.
I think it's saying your part because you're not actively going out and saying like trying
to rally people to cause a non -voting, uh, then collective, then, then what, and if
I did, would I still be doing nothing?
I still wouldn't be doing something.
I think it would be, it would be probably a waste of time like anything else, but I just,
I just, it just makes me laugh as a guy who, uh, has quite frankly done a lot of news television
over the years, and has very much slugged it out, face to face with people like Anne
Coulter on TV for my values, and been chastised regularly for them for saying that I didn't
believe in God, or I believed in certain female freedoms like abortion or whatever on channels
like Fox News, and then getting a shitload of stuff, sticking up for feminism, speaking
out against racism, these things, I've actually done these things publicly.
I've put my money where my mouth is for the things I believe in and I've paid the fucking price for it
And I still haven't stopped so it just kind of makes me laugh a little bit that in this one situation. I go hey
Actually, I don't vote and I have a reason for not voting and it's just it's an it's an unspeakable offense to so many people
I know I think my my point to you is you seemed
Be Wilder at that the anger that was coming to you. I was a little bewildered at the amount that
But because I think if you're going to claim to be a progressive, you have to be open -minded
to all types of progressive thought, not just your own.
So when you attack instead of trying to understand, not only me wrong, everybody that was on
me apologized, I had other friends stick up for me.
It ended up being a very fruitful experience.
But when the country is mourning in a sense, there's no jokes on Twitter anymore, it's essentially
just people woe is me, the world is ending, some doing something, some just simply tweeting
that the world is ending and they're doing nothing either.
But you can't be surprised when you enter the fray three, four days after the election.
You're like, I didn't vote.
People of course are going to be upset with that because they feel like you're not with them.
But that's not saying that's right or wrong.
That's the point of the tweet.
If you're going to announce, I didn't vote.
You just not vote.
And that's it.
But that's the point, that was the point of the tweet.
You're not mad that when people when all those people reacted and said you're an asshole because you didn't vote
When I started to say so let me get this straight had I voted for Trump
Would you not be mad at me right now? And then the response to that was by
I'm not doing sure and it's like they would be more mad at you if you voted for Trump
That's the only way not trying to make that's for sure. Don't don't mask don't mask your recruitment as
As as as as Patriotism or something like that or you know
Don't try to make it look like you're doing anything more than saying do what I want you to do right now
That's all that that is I think if you had which would have been perhaps more cowardly if you had dropped
I didn't vote from the start of that statement you would have I think had a much more interesting conversation
I did drop that involved personal attacks with you. I know the tweets that I didn't vote but had I not you mean had I not yeah
Oh, I thought you said had I no
Well, if you would drop that then it becomes less personal and it becomes a statement you're making
Well, and if you're saying I didn't vote
You're gonna of course you're gonna piss people off because everyone's like
It turned out to be
Although it you know nobody really seems to know what the actual results of this election were
It seemed to be a situation where it came down to a few votes in some places
California is never gonna be one of those places frankly, but
It's it's hard for people to see not voting as anything other than
Uh, not giving a shit about this, this right that many, many countries wish they had was a right to apply a lesson.
That's just, that's just tough for those people.
And they have to, they have to be able to see pass their own perspective.
That's all there.
Look, I'll tell you this, I'll tell you this.
And I am in no way comparing myself to Rosa Parks.
Okay.
Oh my God.
I am in no way comparing myself to Rosa Parks.
And it would just saying that it seems like an away you're about to go right ahead.
But to use a very extreme example, you look at any person that's ever made a difference
socially ever, it's never been met with open arms.
It's been met with people completely chastising it, people who you think are on the right
side of history.
You're not voting is not that, it's not that.
There are other people.
We're all vote.
The world is voting.
That's our system.
Stupid.
It doesn't work.
It doesn't work. It doesn't work. The electoral college doesn't work. But you not voting will will not and cannot change that
That's a you can start a movement of people not voting and you get enough people not to vote it could
Are you doing that? I?
Supported it online, but no, I don't do anything any more than you guys do at the end of the day
It's so there's no difference between you and the guy who's hung over and doesn't go vote. Oh in you
There's no difference between me and you well the difference is that I've got ourselves in different big deal
didn't do anything. Didn't do anything. No, that's broke you felt and I said
there are this couch and said I knew it wouldn't do anything and then I thought
Trump was gonna win. I almost you almost couldn't say Trump is going to win at my
work without people yelling at me. I was like he is and he did and and that's
terrible and while I may agree that it's sort of futile I really have to take
issue with you acting like you're some sort of social justice warrior by
getting an extra hour never never put that title on me or whatever it is you
You think you're doing or starting a movement or effective change like Ms. Rose Parks?
As I said, I was using an extreme example and my point is if you want to be a group
of open -minded people, don't act like the people throughout history who have oppressed
anything that wasn't perfectly aligned with their way of thinking.
That's a very fair point to make.
I am not saying I am doing anything as important as Rose Parks.
I know that that's absurd. I mean there are the people who affected change and everyone thought they were crazy
Or are throwing you know burning bricks into buildings and and getting out there and like butting heads with people and stuff
Not voting is not that it just is I'll tell you this. I'll tell you this. I will tell you this
That's what you need is more coffee. I'll tell you this when I was on I
was pouring himself a cup of coffee remember of time being on
Fox News and the thing about West
the former General Army General West when he, after he left the chambers, I forget who
the female senator was, but she criticized a bill that she was opposing.
He then wrote her a letter that said, you didn't act lady -like, you know, it was a really
like demeaning sexist thing.
We talked about it on Fox News.
I said on Fox News, I'll tell you who's acting lady -like is West because he's being a little
bitch right now.
I had people telling me that they were going to come to my show and punch me in the face.
For insolent and you know what the response was you know what the response was from my open -minded friends
Why did you say anything why say it why say it you know those people will react that way right funny enough
Now all my open -minded friends are saying the same thing and that but as many of them act just like those people did with venom with with with
Blind attacks and and once again it boils down to why did you say anything?
Why do you have to say anything? Well, let me ask you this if we live in a world where
Half the shit you say is gonna piss off the right so you shouldn't say that the other half a shit
You say is gonna piss off the left so you shouldn't say that you can't even tweet something without getting jumped on
What fucking comparison to Godzilla anymore? What fucking difference is anybody really gonna make?
Doesn't it just kind of seem like this thing works the way it's gonna work and that every eight years or so
The pendulum swings hard in one direction and then it swings hard back in the other direction
We go from panic panic panic and consume to relax everything's good
But still keep consuming. It's a fucking farce to me. It's a farce
I don't think that anybody from Trump to Obama to Clinton to
to fucking Abraham Lincoln was gonna get anything really done when they stepped
into office because the powers it be will not allow it and we've seen that
well Abraham Lincoln freed the slaves Joe and then he was murdered immediately
after yeah buddy freed the slave so don't you think that they're you know
doesn't seem suspicious to you I mean you can't say Abraham Lincoln did nothing and
that's saying he did not you're a very passionate speaker so sometimes it's hard
to not go no that's crazy but sometimes you have to whether you're talking
about doc strange md or comparing yourself you don't think it's you don't think it's strange
that our most progressive voices in America have all been silenced have all been assassinated
you think that's just a coincidence Malcolm X Martin Luther King but those people the Kennedy's
by the way who are scumbags but but progressives politically at least what show are we doing
here what's just talking politics all right can we not talk politics we can talk politics but I mean
I mean, I see this, I see this getting further and further carried away.
Well, I can get carried away.
I know.
I mean, how much do people really want to hear about lights out?
We'll get to it.
Yeah.
Lights out.
It just bothers me when people that defend, so vehemently defend free speech tell me I shouldn't
say certain things.
That bothers me.
No, I'm saying hateful.
I'm saying because I've been on the receiving end of several texts where you're upset that
people are upset.
I'm saying, don't want people to be upset, don't say the thing.
You can't stroll out into the public forum of Twitter with all your followers and say you didn't vote and
Be surprised when people are upset by that. I'm not surprised that people get upset by that what I'm surprised by are the
Types of people that get upset by that sure when if you say to me
Pat if you say to me hey, man
I got a real open mind dude like I'm just like all that hate shit out there all that bullshit all that discrimination
I'm not with that dude. I'm not I'm not that dude and then I go pat that's great. Can I tell you something?
I love Jesus Christ and then you turn around and go oh, you're a fucking idiot really the fucking Catholic
And it's like dude, you just told me sure that you're open -minded and I trusted that and whatever now
I'm not saying everybody on Twitter's open -minded, but I'm just saying the people I got shit from were open -minded and again
It's all settled, but it does kind of it's an interesting thing to talk about just because you know
I'm pretty apathetic to all this shit anyway. We're probably not that far divided from each other except I voted and you didn't
That's not that big of a difference at the end of the day, but
Let me ask you if you said I'm open -minded. You can even say anything to me
I'm open -minded and I say well, I fuck my dog, right
Then can the person be outraged just out of curious
Are you supposed to be like yeah cool? Well, I would say that's illegal so you shouldn't do that. Okay. All right
Now, maybe somewhere down the road,
the pets get those brain helmets, they start talking,
they say, we want you to fuck us.
I don't know.
Yeah, yeah.
But I'd say outside of things that are not hurtful,
and then, and here's why I could theoretically
pass some judgment on that.
Pat, we've no idea if your dog wants you to fuck it or not.
You might be hurting your dog, at least emotionally.
I'd tell you, if you've fucked your dog
in front of a mirror as I have and seen that face, that ecstatic face as I thrust away.
I don't have a dog, folks.
You can get it.
I do have a cat.
And the only reason it hasn't been fucked is it's two, actually, at the word, yeah, two
sprites.
The cat, it's very weird.
The second my girlfriend goes to bed, the cat jumps onto my chest and it sits there until
I go to bed.
Like it waits for her to go to bed and then it's like now you and I can have our time waiting to steal your breath
Obviously, it's a female cat and it stares on the I'm I'm always very uncomfortable with extreme eye contact
It stares at me in the eyes until I look away. I'm like that's enough
Then it'll reach out with a paw and caress my face and I start to feel like
Is this cat putting the moves on me? I get uncomfortable every night with this cat and I don't know what to do about it
It's I'm not gonna fuck the cat folks. That's not where this is going. It's you know to bring it back to politics for a second
I thought I was this is a political cats are Clinton dogs are Trump
Okay, Trump is a big dumb dog. That's fair who sometimes
Is kind of playful. Yeah, but it bites the shit out of people and you're like we can't put this this dog
Can't be near anybody. Yeah, you got to just put it in the other room and just let it be a dog
Clintons like a cat. You're not gonna get too much trouble out of her. Yeah, she's gonna do a shit behind the couch
But she's fucking creepy and weird and cold and it freaks you out and you can break her again and again
She just keeps coming back for more dogs get their feelings hurt and then they tweet all night about Saturday night live
That's a great point fucking country
Yeah, so in conclusion. This is how we're gonna wrap up our political discussion
Hillary Clinton is cats
Donald Trump is dogs and Ben Carson is Godzilla
Now let's talk about lights out
All right, um, I know you hated this. No, we got to do your movie corner first. Oh, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I like this here's how this podcast is gonna be like one of the old podcasts
We're at the end. We're like oh yeah, yeah, we were talking about lights out by the way we didn't like it look lights out
We I don't feel like there's not gonna be a ton to say. Yeah, the movie's 80 minutes. I don't have much to say about but
My movie roundup I saw
Jesus what I see last night for Chris. I saw the edge of 17. I heard it's fantastic folks. It's fantastic
So I sit around personally wondering why those old 80 there was a teen movie every week in the 80s
John Hughes of course being my favorite then the 90s brought us another great run for of course American pie and those
But there's lots of other better shit down the way
You know going down to like ghost world if you want to get real artsy sure
But even more mainstream shit that I think was really great. Joe's in the pussy cats is a genius satire of teenagers
majors, I think.
Edge of 17, it would have fit right in
to one of those late 90s classics.
One of those John Hughes -type movies.
It's fantastic.
The writing is fantastic.
It's very funny.
There's a guy who's really in love with her at school
who's one of the most realistic dorks since like
the Anthony Michael Hall days.
Beautiful.
This Asian kid, I really wish I knew the actor's name
because he was so fucking funny.
like everything he did, lines that weren't laugh lines were cracking the audience up
because it felt real and I knew the movie was produced by James L. Brooks. It felt
a lot like his old classic shit, a lot of like old camera and crow shit where
every moment feels so real that you're just laughing because you're like I've
been that person, I recognize that. It was great. What else did I see? I saw Army of
one, which is a Nicholas Cage movie. Oh, man, I want to see that so bad. That's out. Yeah.
He plays the guy, a guy who basically a crazy middle -aged guy who just who God spoke to
him. And he decides he's going to kill Osama bin Laden. God is played by a Russell brand
in a very strange bit of casting. And folks, I've loved Nicholas Cage and everything, the
good shit and the bad. He was just ridiculous in this movie.
That's why I can't wait to see it. He looks like he's off his rocker.
Well, they show you the real guy and he seems a little cookie. But for Nicholas cage,
they're like, you won't be able to tell the two of them apart. You will. Like he could
have played this guy cookie and it would have been great. But he went so insanely over the
top that I didn't even know what I was watching. And the movie is just stupid. It's Larry
Charles the guy who did Borat and Bruno and Seinfeld and Kermit Thusiasm and I expected it
to be a really great comedy and it just was not. It was a pretty damn bad movie. I'm
sad to say. Alright. I'm still pushing bad Santa too off for our Christmas episode. I have
a story to tell about that. Okay. You can wait. I saw Elle, which is the new Paul Verhoeven
movie. Rehoven did, you know, basic instinct showgirls.
That was any clam in this one.
There is because that guy loves showing clam.
There's nudity in it.
Uh, it's a French movie.
It's Isabel Hooper, one of the most beautiful women in the
world. She's in probably 50, 60 years old.
Movie opens, uh, with a home invasion.
Uh -huh.
She is brutally attacked and raped by her invader.
Yeah.
He leaves
Who pair stands up very calmly goes gets into the bathtub?
She's got bubbles all over and then blood rises up in the bubbles from her vaginal area
Right, which is a very haunting and disturbing image that I have not been able to shake and
Then the projector broke and
That was it. I was seeing an Academy Awards screening of it. They come in there like folks were so sorry the projector broke
We're gonna have to start it again
So for a second time, this audience in this tiny, very like close to each other theater, has to watch this woman be brutally assaulted and raped, and then the blood rise from her vagina into the bubbles.
Oh, God, that is terrible.
And then, folks, the framing was off, the subtitles were out of frame.
So our son comes in and starts talking to her. You can't see the subtitles because they're out of frame. Once they spliced it
They set it up wrong. Oh good. So folks we watched her get raped a third time. So at that point it's hard to necessarily say what
I thought about the movie because I felt like I was in clock orange with my eyes taped open. But it was a very interesting movie like all of her
and movies, sorry folks, Joe's texting.
I'm not texting.
I'm trying to look, I'm trying to find my review
for later while you talk.
It's called fucking double, double duty over here.
I'm listening to you.
I probably could have done it before
or at least turned the sound off.
Sorry, sorry.
Maybe I could have done it in the 30 minute late window
waiting for you.
I tell Joe, I'll be over when I get off of work.
I don't know when I get off of work.
I don't have, I don't work at a coal mine
where I punch out at five.
You said, you said, I'll see you at 620,
Which was fine and it was fine. You were late, but here's what Pat does everybody. He doesn't text you at six to be like
Hey, I'm gonna be late. He waits till six twenty five because I still thought I'd be out at six.
Since the text at six twenty five. Hey, dude. I'm still here. Sorry
Send it at six and say hey, I'm gonna be late because I didn't know we're supposed to be out at six at six
You know, you're not out
Yeah, but I thought it was gonna be a minute and then I thought well I can get there and probably ten fifteen
I told him 20 I can make this work then you start to realize you're not gonna make it
You're not going to be five minutes, which is an understandable level of
lateness. You got a text and say I'm going to be a little later.
Yeah. All right. Well, look, just look. Stay out of my lane.
I'll stay out of yours. All right. I'd happily stay out of your lane.
If you weren't loudly making noise on your phone.
Well, I'm talking about a woman being brutally raped, telling a funny story
about how we had to watch this.
I did. Did I not laugh at the start over? Did I not? Did I not go? Oh, God,
that the subtitles were out of frame. Jesus Christ. How was the movie?
It's not amazing, but it was very thought -provoking and interesting, because she seems sort of indifferent to being raped, and the whole time you're like, what's going on here?
And it's very uncomfortable. I liked that level of discomfort, and it led to a lot of conversation after the film.
Okay, Jesus Christ.
All right, you happy?
No, you know I'm not happy.
Why? What does it matter?
You come over here.
You take all the troubles of the office out on me?
There was no troubles in there. I'm not I'm not we just stayed 20 minutes later than I expected. I'm not your job
Okay, I'm your partner and I I want yes, I want my own Pat time. Yeah, okay. I don't want leftovers
You're getting it
Wait, which
Well, I'd like I'd like a man who looks me in the eye and isn't over there on his goddamn phone
I was just trying to find the review that because I accidentally closed the window and I didn't want to stumble to find it later
And then as I was doing it the phone rang and I didn't realize the ringer was on that was the noise you heard all right
That's all that's all it was
All right god damn it
All right, I've seen nothing oh
Great
That's that's great
Well, I'm sorry. I haven't seen any movie since we last recorded we recorded like three days ago
I know but I you know
I intentionally kind of split mine up because we also had a whole month
a part that you might have seen more than a movie, but I guess not.
Sorry that I was running around the entire world trying to pay my rent, you know.
I didn't have time to go fuck around with a box of jujee fruits, okay?
I've never eaten jujee fruits.
James L. Brooks movie must be nice, Pat.
It is nice.
But some of us got to work for a living, you know?
Yeah, I also work.
Yeah, I was late this evening.
I haven't seen any movies since we last met.
But that's why it's called Pat's movie corner. Well pretend you saw the last movie that I'm going to say a magnificent
Seven tell tell me tell me what I thought of magnificent seven. I know what you thought of it. Go on
The text that you sent me said watching magnificent seven. Oof
Yeah, that's exactly what I thought about it
Oof and I was popping off text left and right. I didn't touch my phone during this edge of 17 last night
I was so caught up in this teenager's life and
Magnificent seven. I'm like I might as well have been playing fucking screwed on my phone or whatever that game
I heard it was a fun movie. I still haven't seen it. I want it to see it
People really like it and then a lot of people really hated it
And I'm in the later camp. It just like it fucking sucked like I look forward to Westerns and
There was no fun in it
Denofrio was great in it Vincent Denofrio. He played a very weird kind of part
Okay, everybody else everything else like it should have been one of those like the blues brothers
Whether they're assembling the team, you know, and everybody's got their craze. That's what it was and yet
It wasn't because nobody was interesting or fun or crazy or had any sort of personality
I'm gonna just say at all. I'm just gonna throw this out there. Yeah
I'm I'm predicting that Chris Pratt is gonna be our next Sam
I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I
Being heard through the windows on the lot screaming. How dare you fuck with my script? I've did these are things I hear
Folks that never had no what I was gonna say is I
I think Sam Worthington is a great actor, but I think
What the face is average? Pratt's not a great actor
Worthington is average at best Pratt has charm to spare
Sam Worthington has his career he does his thing and it's consistent and there's a thing he does
He's serviceable is what I would and Chris Pratt I find the same way as a movie star
I find that if you take Chris Pratt out of being the smart ass zinger man
It's pretty boring after a while. Yeah, so anyway
And even he was the smart ass zinger man on this and it was pretty fucking boring
And so my point is is you got
Now Guardians of the Galaxy was good. Okay. He was perfectly cast. Okay, great
We have yet to see what Guardians of the Galaxy 2 is going to bring that's Jurassic world snooze. Yeah
Apparently magnificent seven snooze. Yeah
He's got that new movie out with Jennifer Lawrence the billboard. I saw it
I almost fucking fell asleep at the wheel the goddamn things just their two faces on a white back. Yeah
I mean it's so I think like he's the guy where it's like you're all supposed to love him and he's going to be in everything
But I don't think he's necessarily putting himself in the right stuff and making the right choices and that's what I would say
Sam Worthington Sam Worthington was in everything for like a year and a half every fucking blockbuster
And then they all weren't that great and then that was kind of the end of it
But he was picking like man on man on a ledge and shit that weren't blockbusters
He was picking like just bad movies. I'm sure crushed the Titans probably seem like a surefire bet maybe
Pratt's been in his terminator people like terminator salvation was I mean Christ almighty
He was probably like I made it this is it sure and you know, I think a big part of why certainly why I like Chris
Pratt is that he used to be a big fat guy
I think that helps a lot. It's a real rags to riches. I'll tell you what I don't and he's and he's he's funny
He's not he's not even Ryan Reynolds funny, but he is funny. He's funny
But I'll tell you what I don't like that he's not a big fat guy anymore
I don't like all these fat guys getting thin and I've said it for years now. Yeah, don't care for skinny Seth Rogan
I want him fat again, and I'm thrilled that Jonah Ray ballooned back up Jonah, Jonah Hill or Hill
Excuse me. Jonah Ray is our comedian and a friend of ours. Yeah. I'm thrilled that Jonah Hill ballooned back up
Gaines and lose is a hundred pounds monthly and
I'm sure he'd like you to think he's doing some sort of deniro method acting. He doesn't. He said
I don't think he is. The fact is I've ever seen the lead in a movie
outside of maybe Orson Wells was Jonah Hill and war dogs and I read some interview
where he was like, yeah, I put on weight for the part. I looked up the actual man.
The man is very normal size. It's just a completely ludicrous thing to say.
Oh, God. All right. And the thing is, Jonah Hill, he'll get a trainer and slim up,
although he's never been slim. He was on his way when he did 21 jump street,
the first one. Yeah. He was, wasn't in shape, but he was, you know,
But him and what's his name, Tanning Chaden, were on the cover of magazines together, and it wasn't like, you know, it wasn't like putting, you know, a fucking Volkswagen buggy on the cover.
It wasn't to a Lamborghini. Yeah, exactly. It was God. My analogies are terrible. I don't know where that was going. I was before I got to a good one. You know what I mean? They both look like handsome guys.
And I was like, man, Jonah Hills really getting himself in shape and that's when I said I don't I don't like this
Yeah, so I started to mail him cakes
Well, they always get him coming out of Frollo with you know if like at this point
I get Frollo once a year or something with my girlfriend
But they have the one size that everyone gets the the normal size of Frollo and then like the bucket
That like you assume is for a family, but Jonah Hills always coming out of there with like a bag and two buckets in it
So he's a guy who just can't control himself and I get it. We all struggle. Yeah, it's like the sign felt episode when Newman's yeah in the frozen yogurt place
Yeah, you know, it's just loaded with candy topping. Yeah, and he's just he's not getting a kiwi
We got to get to this movie, Pat.
All right, fun.
We're 45 minutes in.
We haven't even -
This entire podcast has been a tangent.
Well, look.
Which I like.
It's never not been that way.
I almost said you tonight after how long we talked about just Dr. Strange.
I almost when I came in here was like, you know, we should have laughed.
it to be a little freer and go off on some tangents tonight because people
like the tangents. You got your wish didn't this has been all tangents I'd
have to say it worked. Yeah, lights out. I think it's been a tangerine dream
personally. That's just how I've mad boo nights tangerine dreams. Lights out is a
movie about now it's based on a short film that won a contest. Did you know that? I
did I haven't seen the film but I did know that. The short film is like 45
seconds long or something it's so short maybe it's two minutes but it's
really short and it's scary as shit and I believe the lady that plays the
secretary at the beginning of lights out is the lady that stars in the short
film okay but it's tremendous it's terrifying very simple they're in she's in a
hallway in her house she turns the lights out you see the shadow turns it back
on it's gone it's basically the opening scene with the manic exactly okay and then
at the very end is the reveal the monster and it looks way scarier in the
short than it does in the movie. So then they take this they say we're going to make it into a full
length film. I was part of it. I mean it's it's 79 minutes long. Yeah. I was partially excited when
I heard it was coming out but I had a big part of me that was like this usually doesn't go well when
they take something cool that's short. Yeah. Into the point and try to stretch it out. But if you
haven't seen the film lights out as about a ghostly apparition of a demon type being or something
that only appears in the dark.
It cannot go into the light.
If it goes into the light, it gets burned.
It starts appearing to various members of this one family.
And then we go from there.
What's going on here?
Right.
And of course, I was right, this is the first thing I'll say.
They bring in the whole backstory of how the ghosts came to be.
And it's a real stupid backstory.
It's terrible.
And the major undercurrent of the movie really is depression and the mom is very depressed.
The daughter is acting also a period of her mom but seems very depressed.
The son is depressed.
It seems like the 10 year old kid.
And it's also a very depressing movie.
Everybody seems down.
The mom has played by Maria Bello who's like not great in it.
Also too.
I always have a problem with this.
I have a big problem with this.
two things. Number one, Maria Below. Great actor. I'm a fan. It's clearly at
plastic surgery. Please don't cast. Get on the plastic surgery you want. But you
want me to believe that this woman is like a broken -down suburban housewife.
You can't have her obviously having had four fucking facelifts. It takes away from
the believability. They did that in Insidious with Barbara Hershey. Barbara Hershey
has had a ton of work done. Fine, I don't care. But then don't cast her as like the
fucking salt to the earth mom right you know what I mean her she has for sure I
didn't notice Maria Bella I and I tend to not notice that I think she's she's
she looks like she's been pulled back so that that kind of bugs me this the other
thing that really no one Hollywood you don't do it they're all over you for
looking old you do do it you're Renee Zellweger and everybody's mad at you for
doing it I'm not saying anybody should or shouldn't do it I'm just saying if you're
producing a movie where you want me to believe there's a depressed woman that
lives in darkness.
Yes, don't have her obviously have had plastic surgery.
That's fair.
It's probably just who they could get, you know?
I guess she's not even a name,
but I guess she's something of a name.
She's a name.
She was starting that, she was starting in that team.
She's a name for that kind of movie.
Yeah, for sure, but she's from my hometown.
Do you know that?
I didn't, Joe.
No, serious.
No, I didn't know that.
Listen, I'm going to just throw this out there.
Not a fan of this.
That's the second one you've done.
And I don't care for I didn't care for either of them
How would I know that you and I are out out for lunch and we're talking about Maria bellow together?
Yes, now here's the thing the other thing that really annoyed me right off the bat in this picture
The daughter character. I forget the actor's name. She did a good job. She was convincing
But Piper Johnson or something Tracy, but she plays this is why I hated mama
This was the only, this was not the only reason, but this was like the key reason I hated Mama.
Yeah.
Hollywood, please stop making main characters who are supposed to be like rock and
roly or gothy, because it is so fucking obvious that your costume designer goes to
hot topic, buys three things in some candles that are black, and then goes, this is
what a person like this would be into, and it's like, no, that looks like the
dorm room of the kid nobody wanted to hang out with when I was in college it looks dated it looks
like there's black light posters in there so they put a lava lamp up while you're at it let's
also not forget her rocker boyfriend yeah who's only rocker characteristic was that he had long
hair and it had as long a hair as I did it wasn't even that that's crazy yeah so she's dating this
supposedly like her name is because we we never seem more incompetent than when we're like our names
Tracey Johnson or something.
Let me tell you her name, Teresa Palmer.
All right.
You threw a piper out for her.
I thought, you know, maybe she look
as a piper parable quality of Coyote Ugly fam.
Um, the, the boyfriend is in the movie.
Her boyfriend is supposed to be like this like bad boy rocker type.
Yet the first scene like they have sex
and she's like, all right, get out.
Yeah, and he's like all sensitive.
It's like, who's writing these characters?
Yeah, this guy would be like,
He's like, can I please leave a toothbrush here?
Yeah, it's like, what is this written for?
Yeah.
And she's telling them he's got to get out.
Man, I guess maybe they're trying to play.
I guess play with the stereotypes or something.
I get that they're trying to play up to define her
as being the loner and emotionally shut off,
but then don't have her date in a fucking rock and roll guy.
Have her date a nice guy in it.
Or make her, make her like somebody
who's obsessed with their job,
who does really well at their company or something.
The characters, especially for a 79 -80 minute movie where you have plenty of time to
develop these characters, the characters were beyond paper thin.
My problem with all this stuff, you didn't care about any of them, and really everyone
being depressed in a movie makes the movie miserable to watch.
So it was a horror movie with no fun in it.
The scare scenes, when they came were effective, you know, I was never scared.
But I thought they were done well the rules of the light thing seemed to kind of come and go right like
Okay, so when at one point that this hand reaches out they shine a light on it and the hand starts burning and
Sizzling but then in the other scenes they flash a light and it disappears. So does light burn it and harm it?
Or does it make it disappear? Pick a lane. Yeah, that was another another problem I had with it was the science of the film
It just wasn't accurate.
It was like, here you've got a supernatural being
that clearly has the ability to just go,
I'm never going to be in the light.
Ever, if I don't feel like it.
It can disappear and reappear at will.
Why would it ever walk into light?
Why would it ever have to?
It wouldn't.
It wouldn't go live in, you know,
go up to Alaska for solstice and get to know.
And the back story is, you know,
I guess spoiler alert is if you give a shit
that this was when the mom when Maria Bella was in a mental hospital as a little girl,
she'd be friend of this other little girl who had like translucent skin
and couldn't be exposed to light.
Which is a real condition.
I know.
And they sell it so poorly in the movie.
So poorly.
That I thought they made it up.
They didn't even do like any really cool flashbacks with it.
They easily could have done.
No.
It's literally just they put a like a shroud over a little kid.
Yeah.
And they're like, look, it can't be in the light.
Yeah, it's terrible.
Then they do an experiment on the kid, which isn't it really explained at all why what this
Experian experiment was what it entailed, but they hit it with a lot of light and she died
Then now the girl comes back to haunt Maria bello who didn't do the experiment
Why isn't she haunting the people who performed the experiment on her?
This is this this also bothers me about her when they do this and I'm glad you brought it up
I can't stand these this person was a was a pure soul that that got a bad
run a luck and now they're rotten and shitty because of it and they try to kill people in the afterlife.
Wouldn't the pure soul, if this whole afterlife thing exists, wouldn't the pure soul like go up to heaven where God would be like my sweet child?
I'm really sorry about what happened down there.
Either go to heaven or go after the people who fucked you over, not your only friend when you were a freaky light sensitive skin girl.
Yeah, it's it's a real shit show of a movie and I was particularly angry because I was very excited to see it
It's got like a 73 % or something on your favorite critic somehow Richard Roper dick Roper gave it a four out of four stars
I saw that I mean people love this movie and it was a mat
I learned that worldwide this thing brought in almost two hundred million dollars did very well and on a
Ten million dollar budget and kudos to it. I'll tell you why I was really mad
I was excited to see it because because any horror fan probably knows
A horror movie getting like 70 % any radio on rotten tomatoes
I add 20 % to it for horror movies or comedies. Yeah, so I'm like this thing is is a 90 % I got to see it
I
Was in a fucking hotel on the road. I rented the goddamn thing in the hotel. I paid 2099 to see it 2099 to see it
That's tough and and halfway through it. I was on my phone. I was so fucking bored. Yeah got room service
That was another 20 bucks easily that was this fucking thing plus $15 lights out on Joe's wallet that fateful night folks
Am I right and then really the biggest issue with it
I'm just going to cut to the chase and if you don't want to know the ending of lights out don't don't listen to this
The ending I
Couldn't stand Maria bello I'll cut to it is shooting at the ghost
And then surprise that it doesn't work her daughter is standing behind the ghost and yet Maria bello's shooting
at the ghost, which I'm also kind of like is the daughter didn't even react. Like one key detail
before you describe the ending, that's important. Throughout the movie, the daughter is saying to the mom,
you're crazy because you're not taking your pills. The mother refuses to take the pills. We find out
later the reason she's not taking the pills is because she's scared of the demon and when she takes the
pills, it makes the demon go away because somehow Maria Bella being lucid,
it closes the door for the demon to come in.
So she doesn't take the pills,
and then we cut to the end of the movie
and she's trying to kill the ghost with a gun.
So she does take a bunch of pills at the end of the movie
and it doesn't work this time, also not explained.
But I don't think she takes them.
I think she's about to take them in the ghost like a taxor.
Oh, that's right, the ghost tax.
Yeah.
So then she points the gun immediately.
Like there's no buildup, no suspense,
no not, points the gun at her head,
And her daughter who's watching this goes mom. What are you doing? And she goes
Saving our lives in like this badass action movie voice. Yeah, saving our lives
And then blows her brains out in front of her daughter
While her 10 year old kids outside horrified
Then she falls to the ground dead and the and the ghost goes away until lights out too, but
But let's take a look at what this movie is really saying because now I'm going back
to my film school roots with the Jeepers, Creepers, and now this analyzing the shit out
of these things.
This movie is saying the pills, if you're depressed, pills can make your demons go away,
but it's not a permanent fix.
You're destroying your family's life with your depression, you're bumming everyone out,
you're ruining your children's lives, and the only way to get rid of these demons is
to kill yourself, right? Hey, are you depressed? Well, guess what? Everyone around you hates you because
you're ruining their lives and being annoying by being depressed. So fucking kill yourself is the
message of the movie. It has to be. Death is the only escape. That is what it feels like. Death is
the only escape. And it wasn't like a hard R where you're like, wow, that's a fucking dark ending.
It's PG 13. And then I read an interview with the director about this and he's like, oh, that's not
what I intended he's like I just wanted her to be like a hero you know like where she that's not
what I intended and he's like actually in lights out too I'm gonna go into how um the depression
about their mom killing themselves makes the kids depressed which brings the girl back so he's just
doubling down on it oh god so now they're gonna be depressed which will bring back the demons which
I wouldn't bring the demon which above the people in their life why would they why would they be
be fucking with her kids,
she doesn't even know them.
And I'll tell you,
I've got a problem with any movie
where the solution literally is,
do me a favor, honey.
Take the 10 -year -old for the night.
I'm gonna play nice with the ghost.
Tomorrow morning, I'm gonna go outside in the sun
and just take my pills and we'll be fine.
That's literally what the solution could have been.
It was such a,
oh, fuck it.
All right, Patty, we're out of time.
Let's skip the movie review this week
Because I can't find the goddamn one that I had and I thought it was gonna be good
But two thumbs down. Yeah, two thumbs down for lights out
Plug -wise
You know, I don't have much going on right now
It's the holidays go read my short stories if you will some severe situations is the name of the column
It's on the Fangoria website follow me on Twitter and Instagram. Please
Joe DeRosa comedy on both
Yeah, and I have absolutely nothing, you know, Twitter, Instagram, the Patrick Walsh, that's it.
You see everybody, this has been brought to you by the Fangoria podcast Network.
It's executive produced by Thomas DeFail, and produced by Ken Hanley, if you want
some info about our show, advertising interests, that sort of thing, you email Ken at
fangoria .com.