I'm here for Bet Rivers Online Casino and Sportsbook with poker icon Phil Helmiut.
And now thanks to the excitement of Bet Rivers, I'm also a slots icon.
That's great! And a same game, Parley icon.
Cool, cool. A Blackjack icon, a Moneyline icon,
A roulette. Take it from Phil Helmiut.
If you love games, Bet Rivers is the place to play in Bet.
Bet Rivers.
Games on.
Must be 21 plus in present in West Virginia.
Void were prohibited. Terms in conditions apply.
Gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gambling.
The football season is full of guarantees.
And here's another.
No weather sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October.
If your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning
or winning money back in fan cash. Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
Winning hits different here.
Must be 21 plus. Gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gambling.
Offer not available in all states. Terms apply.
See Fanatic Sportsbook app.
Howdy folks. Welcome to We'll see you in hell.
This is the podcast that you turn to in your darkest hour.
When you say life's got me down, but I need something to get me up.
How about my boys Pat and Joe talking about some of my favorite films.
Or films I haven't seen yet.
Or films I don't like.
Already been that good.
And that's us.
We're here to do it today.
Last episode was about love actually.
And I feel now that we've gone completely off the rails on this show.
And now we're just kind of talking about almost any movie we feel like talking about.
Well, I didn't know till about five minutes before the end that last one was going to be about love actually.
I said it at the very top of the episode.
I know, but you were like, maybe it'll become, maybe it'll be love actually at that time.
But then it kind of took off.
This one is Cam that we're doing now, right?
This is going to be Cam.
But I will say that love actually does fit into the agenda of our podcast.
It's certainly a fantasy.
It's a fantasy.
People loving one another.
What does this horse shit?
Today will be Cam, though.
Today will be Cam Blumhouse film on Netflix.
Well, let's get on with the show.
And at the same time, let me see if I can work in a song that was just banned by American radio.
I can get you in there somewhere.
But baby, it's jolt outside.
I really can't stay.
Was it banned?
It was banned by radio.
It's a song about the age -old practice of trying to get a woman to stay and have sex with you.
There's been tweets for 10 years about how the song is.
Was it really banned or was it just some officially banned?
Today, they were like, it's too date -rapey.
I think the reason it was banned is because they do stuff like this to keep Fox News humming for like
three hours.
Okay.
Because when something like that gets banned, they can go, can you believe this guys?
They did this and then America won't notice that all of our leaders are going to jail by the end of the year.
Okay.
All right, fair enough.
But yeah, they have apparently banned it.
There is a creepy element to the song.
It's using the snow to keep a woman there to fuck you.
But at no point is she like, I'm leaving.
You're creeping me out and he's like, no, you're going to stay, baby.
It gets weird, yes, but you know, the song was written in like the Meet Me in St. Louis days.
Now, would you ever meet me in St. Louis?
Just out of curiosity.
Okay, I'm going to St. Louis in about three weeks.
But do I mean that?
If you want to meet me there, that's not what I asked you.
Do I mean that much to you that you would go out of your way to meet me there?
Well, you know, I would.
I have family and friends there.
Forget to go to St. Louis.
Let's see, you didn't have fit.
Let's change the location.
Chicago, would you meet me in Chicago?
I love Chicago.
I can't see.
That's a better idea.
But Kipsy, I wouldn't go.
Not even for me.
I just see you when you get back to town.
But Chicago, I'd go and we can have a nice.
What if I said, Pat, I'm moving to Pekipsi.
I'm never coming back.
I might meet you there once a year or something.
All right, that's all I need.
We should tour.
We should tour to Chicago and St. Louis.
And Pekipsi.
Maybe Pekipsi.
You never know, you know,
the fans are in the damnedest of places.
You never know where they're at.
Apparently, as I saw on the Facebook page,
they're doing that show we did at Columbine again.
And frankly, I think we should be on it.
Well, after the smash -raving success
of our 15 -person -attended screening of...
It was attended pretty well.
Many at COP2 at 6 .45 in the morning.
I had fun that weekend.
I had a great time.
But, you know, I'm just saying,
we didn't really set the town on fire.
That's true.
Who's there this year?
I don't know.
I don't know, but I'm hoping we get in.
That's all I'm saying.
All right, fair enough.
Now, Joe and I today...
It was just all over the place.
My sisters in town, I went to a drag brunch.
They were like, come meet us for brunch.
I walk in, there's guys in drag, dancing,
and then aggressively demanding dollar bills.
Just like I was at a strip club.
And I was like, I'm here with my wife and my sister.
This is weird.
And I didn't have any dollar bills.
But, they kept insisting.
The whole day I was thrown off my game.
I left.
I met Joe at some real shitty Italian restaurant.
I'm sorry.
It was all right.
It wasn't bad.
Place sucked.
I enjoyed my meal.
Watch Joey to meet ball.
I had a beer.
We just kind of kept drinking.
We went to the drawing room,
which is a local bar here that closes at 2 a .m.
and reopens at 6 a .m.
That is the darkest bar.
I've ever been in.
It's a dark bar.
I mean, it is windowless.
And for the first time ever, ever,
all the years I've gone there,
the bartender opened the door to let light in.
And even then, because the entire
four -year of the bar is painted red,
all that did was send this like satanic glow
into the bar from the outside.
It did make it feel any more alive or anything.
I feel like it's a bar where the patrons
do not want to be reminded
that there is a bright sun outside.
They want to drink and forget everything.
And it was bleak.
And then we got an Uber over here
and it's been bleak here ever since.
Pat has eaten since we got here.
Two.
Well, they come in a two count.
I assumed one was for me,
but I guess not.
You didn't go anywhere near it.
Two ice cream.
What were they?
Whip cream cookie sandwiches.
Whip cream and surprisingly low in the calories
because it is whipped cream, which is a low -carb dish.
But not a healthy dish by any means.
I saw it at the grocery store.
I go to the grocery store so rarely
that I always want to make the most of it.
Joe Blot supplies to make us nachos.
I've yet to see nacho won.
What can I make them when we're done?
I'm doing screwdrivers for us.
We're having a nice time.
And I had a Whip cream cookie or two, you know.
And we're doing a holiday party.
We're not going to, people are not going to like us at this party.
I don't think they would have liked us.
We're going to ruffle the stage.
I mean, I'm in a state.
I'm in a state.
I remember what's Pat and I went to
in a Sunday afternoon.
We went late morning, about 11, 30 or 12.
We went to the House of Pies here in Los Angeles.
And we both ordered
their version of the Grand Slam, which is like three pancakes, two eggs.
And then I believe in House of Pies.
They give you all three of the meats.
Most places, look, you get a bacon sausage or ham.
House of Pies, they go, you can get all three.
Well, they got the meats.
They got the meats.
Are you talking about the time we went after ghost busters?
And everybody talked about how much they love ghost busters?
No, no, no.
This was in the afternoon, okay.
And we got this thing.
Now, the special, this special that I'm referring to,
on the menu it says it comes with the pancakes,
come with whipped cream and fruit on top of them.
And I said, for God's sakes, please,
do not put the whipped cream and fruit on my pancakes.
This is enough, like what you're already doing.
Pat said, pile it on.
I want it.
We ate this thing.
We were going to go see black mass afterwards.
Wow, this is quite a memory.
That was years ago.
Yeah.
And I felt like I was going to,
dude, I felt like I was in a fucking fever dream after I ate this thing.
And I turned to Pat and you went,
Joe, I'm in a state right now.
I didn't know how we were going to make it through black mass.
We went, we saw it.
We rented a James Adomean, hilarious comedian.
He sat and watched black mass with us.
Right.
It was a good day, but it was tight.
It was tight.
You know, the drink I had at the drawing room today.
I mean, yeah, I had a vodka and soda.
And it was 99 .9 % vodka.
You know, it was painful to drink.
I ordered the shot.
Set me down a path.
I ordered their shot beer special, which is $8.
I saw a poor that thing.
I mean, you had a glass of whiskey.
Yeah, it's a domestic beer and a shot of redemption whiskey.
For eight bucks, she gives me the beer.
She starts pouring the shot.
I mean, it's just, it just, she just keeps going.
It was like a three stooge's gag.
Like, look, look, look, look, look.
And at one point, she's still pouring and I go,
lady, what are you trying to marry me?
Jesus Christ.
Yeah.
She's like, it's the drawing room.
That's how we do it.
I was like, I know it's how you do it,
but Christ, it's 2 p .m.
Like, give me a break here.
Yeah.
And they were married.
I don't know if you remember that, but you were married.
We did get married after.
She hasn't been home since, which worries me.
Folks, let me take it down.
Already.
I mean, why not?
All right, take that movie corner.
I have so many that I'm trying to get through.
I think I have two for this one.
Folks, I watched, I'm going to go with sequels today.
I watched a little picture called
Daddy's home too.
It's on Amazon Prime.
Somehow, it's not a porn movie.
Daddy's home was bad,
but it was not as bad as like get hard
with Will Ferrell and Kevin Hart.
I saw Daddy's home and I was like, God damn it,
because Will Ferrell is not an old man, but like
the other night, I'm sitting at home.
I got home from work and I was just furious.
I often am when I get home from work.
And I told Heather, I was like, I need a little time to myself.
And I turned on the TV and Anchorman was about 30 minutes in.
And I hadn't seen it in 10 years and I put it on and I was laughing
to beat the band.
Hey, can I tell you something?
When you come home and you say I need time alone,
that's what the shed used to be for.
For our dads.
Yes, that's right.
Dads of our age, they'd go, I need some time.
They'd go out to the shed.
And my dad wouldn't let us speak to him.
And whenever the fuck it was,
I don't know what they were doing out there,
but we had a one hour window
on my dad at home where we couldn't speak to him.
I don't do this every night,
but this was just a really bad night.
Right.
I'm watching Anchorman, I'm laughing.
And I'm just thinking like,
it's like I talked about the last podcast with Steve Carell.
You have these brilliant comedians
and they are wasting their time
when they could be viable comedians.
Like Will Ferrell could have done nothing but comedies
and then switched to drama.
As could Steve Carell.
Ferrell's all over the place.
This homes and Watson looks like shit.
Get hard was terrible.
Daddy's homes.
Am I crazy?
I don't think a homes and Watson looks that bad.
It's pretty bad.
But everybody's like, it's terrible.
I'm like, maybe I just was excited to see them doing a movie.
Sure. And I'm going to see it.
But yeah.
But basically, Daddy's home too.
I was like, all right, it's got two new elements.
John Lithgow, who I've always loved
as Will Ferrell's dad.
And Mel Gibson, who I have not seen in a big commercial movie
in 10 years, for good reason.
An interesting fact.
Mel Gibson, who you didn't love
until about three years ago.
Until we started aligning politically, yes.
But you know, Daddy's home too
is just lazy.
And a big part of it is these guys
who did these movies fucked me over five years ago
in my movie career.
Who?
The guys who did Daddy's home, Daddy's home too.
That's my, they chose to do that's my boy
instead of a movie that I had written.
That was ready to be shot.
Okay.
That's my boy lost about $40 million.
That's someone with Sandler.
Sandler, yeah.
Okay.
They also did the bad mom's movies.
And you know, it's lowest common denominator shit.
And I don't love Wallberg.
But like seeing all these people go through these motions
is very tedious.
The story sucks.
The joke sucks.
The set piece is suck.
You know, the only thing that's kind of funny
you saw in the trailer when Will Ferrell
has like a voice activated shower.
I thought that was absurd.
It's so stupid but it's like at least a recognizable bit.
It's one of those things where it's like
even if this is a real thing,
only somebody as rich as Will Ferrell would ever have it.
Like I don't understand who's supposed to relate to this joke.
Like it's just a terrible bit.
And of course the movie made $200 million fucking dollars
and I tell you, the state of movies makes me just as depressed
as the state of the world on a day -to -day basis
because this movie is just so fucking lazy.
Now do you agree with Paul Schrader who recently said
movie sucking now was in the fault of the creators.
It's the fault of the audience.
Honestly, it doesn't want to see anything good
so we can't make anything good.
Honestly, I don't go with him 100%,
but I go with him a lot because I think
every one of these four hour Avengers pictures
that gets released that everybody goes to see and blah, blah, blah.
And then some comes out that everybody's got a lot of heat around
whether it's sorry to bother you or whatever else.
They don't make any money.
And I do feel in the 70s, it was like taxi driver was a fucking hit.
We need to go see fucking taxi driver.
Tax driver by today's standards is a dark and alienating
and off -putting movie.
We have the occasional good film slipped through the cracks
but it's so rare.
And just the, I've read so many articles about this,
the 40 million dollar movie for adults
is a genre that has completely been wiped away.
It does not exist.
If you're going to make a movie for adults,
it's got to be Manchester by the sea
and it's got to be made for $3 million.
It can't be, you know, like even the thrillers,
hand the rocks, the cradle, or LA confidential.
These are 40 million dollar movies,
but they get made and they'd be great.
And we are at a time now where it's either transformers 12
or it's a very low budget indie and you catch up to it.
But the problem is that all these actors know now
the only path to success and respect
is these low budget Netflix style indies.
So you're getting them slumming and doing these performances
that don't feel real at all because the whole motive behind them,
the whole motivation is I'd like to win an Oscar.
Nothing feels genuine about them.
You get maybe three good movies a year.
It's a very dark time for art in general.
When I was thinking about what's my album of the year,
I don't have a top two.
I used to be whittling down a top 50.
Right.
I didn't have two albums this year that I thought
were even better than good.
I, uh, the, the, the, the,
and the tough thing now too is...
I listen to everything.
I would mind top album of the year with Cypress Hills latest.
I haven't heard that.
Wonderful piece of work.
I already don't mind all I have list.
Um, you made me a strong drink too here, Joe.
I made a mistake and I weakened it.
Because I poured too much in and then it's, oh boy.
Anyway, um, yeah, no.
The problem with a lot of this stuff is, you know,
I saw a, uh, do easel's apple last night, as you know.
Uh, and he does the zappa plays zappa thing.
He plays his dad's,
his band, he did tribute to his, for example, his hits or whatever.
Not hits, but, you know, for example, his music.
But, uh, zappa's biggest hit was a song called Valley Girl.
Used in the films of Valley.
I don't know if it was in the movie or not, but, you know, it was a joke.
It was about like Valley Girl.
Okay, fine.
For sure.
She's a Valley Girl.
And then the versus were moon zappa going like,
like, oh my God, that's just so grouting.
Like, you know, it was a joke.
But before they play the song, do easel goes,
this song came out in 1983, he goes, uh,
I believe it was a warning.
For the wave of stupidity that was coming towards us.
Yeah.
Uh, and he goes, nobody seemed to heed the warning because back in 1983,
it was considered a joke to talk like this.
Right.
And now people actually talk like this.
Yeah.
And I was like, holy shit, he's right.
Like, that is like, I was listening to like
this supposedly dated dialogue in the song.
I was like, no, that's like how everybody talks now.
And I think it's, it is a reflection on a lot of what we see in music
and an art and stuff.
It's like, everything is very childish, you know,
and very, uh, I don't know, it's playful to a fault.
Yeah.
I guess is the way I would put it.
You know, but I mean, look, my, my job is anytime
you try to do anything subtle or anything like,
you know, where you just assume the audience will get it.
The network's notes is, can we dumb this down to the point
where you are holding the dumbest person's hand?
And that's my job in a nutshell, and it makes me sick.
And these are just the executives hands we're holding.
Folks.
The standards have slid to such a low point music,
movies, television, and it is not because I said back and make sure
because I would never want to be the guy who's like the only good music
as the music that was made when I was 22 or whatever.
I listen to everything.
I have a very open mind.
I have a very thirsty mind that once new and challenging
movies, music, et cetera, and I am really let down by just
about everything I see and watch in here.
Now, is that what you would name your autobiography,
Thirsty Mind?
That is what I have named my biography, Thirsty Mind.
Okay.
It's, uh, it's called Thirsty Mind to Open As.
The Patrick Wall story and the cover is me on my back,
like a crab with my legs spread eagle.
It's in, uh, adult bookshops.
Uh,
Joe, do you have a picture for?
I do, Pat.
I do.
I watched, uh,
watched a little movie called The Hunger.
I've seen The Hunger and I love this.
Starring David Bowie and Susan Sarandon.
And Catherine Denise.
Yes.
That is a cool cast, by the way.
Very, very cool.
You don't get much cooler than that cast.
That was as hip as it came when this movie came out
and I believe it 1983.
It's a wonderful film.
I really enjoyed it directed by Tony Scott.
It really bummed me out watching it to realize we've lost Tony Scott.
You know, I don't think I ever truly appreciated what a great directory was.
So I saw this because I liked everything else Tony Scott did,
but it was usually stuff like the last boy scout.
It was, it was, there were sort of fun big action movies or whatever that I really enjoyed.
This, I was like, this is really truly like an art house piece.
And it's great.
If you haven't seen it, the best way I could describe it is picture the neon demon
if it was a good movie.
That's basically what it is.
It's a, it's very visually pleasing.
It's got a very music video vibe to it.
A lot of nice work with extreme color and stuff in the shots and the settings.
It's a vampire film.
But it's just, it's just a truly, he takes it the one step further.
The guy that wrote it is also the guy that wrote, oh, damn it.
He wrote the novel.
Oh, you also wrote the novel of Wolfen or the Wolfen, which the movie Wolfen was based on.
It takes it just a step further past that sort of tragic,
visual haunting, beauty kind of thing and gives it enough of a plot and enough of an ending
and enough closure that you feel satisfied at the end of it.
It's a very haunting film.
There are some really truly amazing plot twists in it.
Lesbian vampire sex.
Serandon is terrific.
Everybody's terrific in it.
The person I was most impressed with because it's not somebody that I look at as an actor first
was Bowie. Bowie's not somebody I go actor for.
I look at Bowie's musician first, but Bowie's always pretty good and stuff.
It's great and labyrinth.
I just bought man who felt earth I've never seen and I'm going to watch that this week.
He's great in this.
Have you seen that?
No.
Okay.
But, you know, the whole storyline is basically he's a vamp.
He's been turned.
What's her name again?
Sorry.
Catherine to know.
Yes.
He's been turned by Catherine to know.
And she's like, you'll be my lover forever.
And this has happened hundreds of years ago before the movie began and then he realizes
that she was not truthful with him and that what he does get is everlasting life,
but what he doesn't get is eternal youth.
And he at some point in the film starts rapidly aging.
And he becomes basically like a hundred fifty -year -old man overnight.
Right.
And but he's still alive and he can't die.
And there's a scene where she takes him up into like her attic and she puts him in a coffin
and then it reveals all these other coffins.
And she says, my loves keep him company, keep him warm.
And it's and you realize the she's loved all these men and women and whoever
that are just still alive in this eternal state of death.
Very haunting, very, very cool film, man.
Very cool.
But Bowie, my point was, is Bowie does a really great turn in the aging process.
I really was impressed with his acting throughout that.
All right.
I liked it.
I saw a picture called Creed II.
I want to see it.
I haven't seen it yet.
I'm a big fan.
Obviously of the rocky pictures.
I feel like Rocky.
One, two,
three to some extent.
And Balboa are great movies.
Four, I think it's cheesy shit, but entertaining as hell.
Five is bad.
I like five better than four.
Wow.
Okay.
Four is cheesy over there.
Five at least gets back to some of the like grit of what Rocky is about.
Well, there's a little treat in Creed II for, believe it or not, Rocky five fans.
Really?
They have the Drago shit, which is Rocky for Rocky four fans.
For me, Rocky one is unquestionably great.
Rocky two is very underrated and great.
And Rocky Balboa was fantastic.
I think Rocky Balboa is the second best in the entire franchise.
I might go there with you.
I think the other ones are kind of hit and miss.
I think Rocky or Creed one was great.
Yeah, I very much like Creed one, but kind of on its own thing.
Creed two, I gotta be honest with you, was a huge step down from Creed one
and Creed one I already felt while entertaining was a step down for the Rocky franchise at large.
It's
Stallone seems shoehorned in.
He looks like an old woman at this point.
The plastic surgery is beyond the pale.
I mean, he looks like a woman in Beverly Hills.
It looks like he would be the star of Stop My Mammal Shoot,
but he would be now playing the Estelle Getty role.
He's shoehorned in.
There are two boxing scenes in the entire film.
If you're a fan of Rocky four and are excited to see this because of the
Drago shit, you will be sorely disappointed.
Drago himself is in the film.
Dolph long during he's got like three lines.
His son has maybe one line, but the big fight at the end is him
and versus young Drago.
But it's like it doesn't.
They don't do that well where you're like, hey,
it's already kind of a buy that a guy would care that much
about fighting the son of the guy who killed his dad or whatever,
but they don't handle it well.
And the whole time you're kind of like not that involved and not that interested.
The stuff with Creed and his girlfriend,
hey, every woman in the audience,
gasped every time they showed Michael B. Jordan,
that guy is going to be around for a long time.
For women, he's got that thing where like whenever you see him,
people like faint, okay, he'll be around a long time.
It's not enough to make the movie on the guys got star power.
Tessa Thompson who plays his now wife is good.
Felicia Rashad is good as the mom.
But like everything was done so much better in Creed.
Honestly, it's a worse sequel than Rocky two was to Rocky one.
It's a to me a big slip in quality.
If you were to take your dad over the holidays to kill some time,
I don't think you'd be let down,
but you definitely wouldn't walk out pumping your fist.
And that's what I look for in a Rocky movie.
I expected to cry.
I'm in a very fragile place in my life.
And I kind of needed to cry.
And this movie did not get me within a million miles of it.
I cried last night at the Deweezel's App a show.
Okay.
Hearing them now was episode that I'd never heard live.
Yeah.
It made me cry.
Okay.
I'll say this about Creed two.
I haven't seen it yet.
I want to see it.
I will probably hold my folks over Christmas to see it.
By the way, it sounds like I'm shouldn't on it.
I give the thing a B.
I mean, it passes the time.
It's just not great.
I'll say this about it, which I can't wrap my head around.
And I was talking about the sealant right in the bar.
Rocky four at the time that it came out.
And the reason it's considered a classic and all that stuff
was because we were at war with Russia.
And that film was looked at as America versus Russia.
People saw Rocky as America, as the USA.
He's wearing the red and white striped trunks in the whole thing
that were Apollo's and Apollo dies.
And they're looking at it as America versus Russia.
That's why people love that movie.
The fact that
in possibly somehow, the timing of this Creed II sequel
lines up to when we're beefing with Russia again.
I know.
And they go, okay, we need to do a Creed II sequel.
What can we do?
They go, well, we're beefing with Russia.
We could bring Dragon back.
What's the significance of that?
Oh, Dragon killed Apollo Creed in Rocky four.
We could have his son coming back now to avenge the death of his father.
I can't even get my head around how lucky that is
from a filmmaking standpoint.
But they don't have any phone with it.
No, frankly, they don't have any phone with it.
That's a bummer.
It is,
you know, it's just like, I would say it's perfunctory
to use a big vocabulary.
Boy, aren't you?
It'd take it easy, would you?
It checks its boxes.
It checks its boxes even as like a bringing your dad
to the movies on Thanksgiving movie.
But it does not do anything more than that.
And that's kind of a bummer.
All right, to me.
Go ahead, John.
I don't have anything else from the movie quarter of this week.
But I do have a new psycho and a scary stuff.
Please.
But I'm not ready to be down with mine.
So you don't have anything else.
You can do a third one.
But I mean, we're at the 30 -minute mark.
I don't think it would hurt us to move into
considering the last episode we never got to cam.
All right, but I'd like to do another one.
I've seen a bunch.
All right, we'll do one more and then we'll move on.
I want to do something good
and I will do a documentary that's airing on stars
because I'm worried it'll leave.
It's called Cutting Edge,
The Magic of Movie Editing.
And I tell you folks,
one of my favorite parts of running a show
is editing the show each week,
making funny moments out of things that aren't funny,
you know, looping in a reaction shot
and making a scene 100 % more funny.
I have become obsessed with editing.
It's my favorite part of the job.
And honestly, I thought I could stand
to be more of an expert in this.
I haven't taken editing since film school.
So randomly one night,
The Cutting Edge,
The Magic of Movie Editing was on stars.
I had already seen it years and years ago.
It's narrated by Kathy Bates.
But boy, if you have, if you're a film buff at all,
if you have even a passing interest in movies,
you likely never think about editing.
They talk to all your big guys
and some of your lesser guys
that the guy who does all the Paul Thomas,
Anderson movies, Bougainites, etc.
They show you scenes and like they couldn't figure out
how to make a movie work.
But movies can be completely saved in the editing room.
Stories can be saved in the editing room.
Something that doesn't work at all can be fixed in the editing room.
And I just absolutely loved it.
It's one of my favorite documentaries
about the movie business I've ever seen.
So on stars, on stars, on demand,
I'm sure you can check it out somewhere.
I highly recommend it.
If you're listening to this podcast,
you're a fan of movies and it is a great look
at one of the most integral parts of film making
that gets no respect at all.
I'll tell you this.
I've been listening to an album on Apple Music
that is a series that's a full record,
a collection of Alfred Hitchcock interviews
on film.
Which anybody interested in film should listen to,
just because yeah,
Hitchcock's one of the greats.
Moves interviewing him.
It's a series of interviews from all over the place.
One of them is Tom Snyder.
Many of them are from English reporters,
BBC reporters and whatnot.
But there's one in one of the interviews,
Hitchcock breaks down editing
in the best way I've ever heard it broken down.
And he goes, we call it cutting a film.
It shouldn't be called cutting.
It should be called assembling.
Yes.
Because that's what we're doing.
We're assembling the final piece.
And he goes, here is,
he starts to go into the different ways of editing.
Right.
And the best example, my favorite example,
at least that he gives is he goes,
okay, let's talk about like a simple sequence.
He goes, you see the shot of a man.
Then you cut to what the man is looking at.
It's a shot of a woman with her baby and a stroller.
Yeah.
It cuts back to the man he's smiling.
This man is empathetic.
He's sweet.
He's very nice, right?
And then he discuss, it's a famous test
that was used in this documentary.
Yeah. And then he goes.
And Hitchcock stole, frankly.
He didn't, he probably invented it.
It was like a 1920s Russian test.
Anyway.
And then he goes, so then you take the same sequence,
you take out what he sees and replace it.
You see the man, then you see him looking at a woman
in a bikini or whatever.
Cuts back to me smiling.
He goes suddenly now.
It's the same exact footage, but now he's a dirty old man.
Right.
And he is like, that's the importance of editing.
Like that's the difference it makes.
It's tremendous.
Yeah, I mean, to know like when I get in there
and I'm doing this,
it's a difference of two frames
that can make something funny or not funny.
Comedy editing is the most important of all, really.
I agree.
Timing.
You stay too long on something that's not funny.
You stay too short on something that's not funny.
I agree.
Great documentary.
Check it out.
Joe scary stuff.
Yes.
Playing a game on my Nintendo Switch,
I believe it's available in all platforms.
It's called Mutant Football League, the MFL,
if you will.
Sure.
Really, really fun game, man.
If you are a video game fan and you like the sort of
simple throwback football game,
now it's obviously it's more complicated than this,
but if you sort of like the pick up and play football games
of the 80s and 90s,
NHL 94 is famous for this because it was,
you could just kind of pick it up and play a hockey game.
Tech mobile, of course, was famous for this.
Double dribble.
These old school games where you could sort of just pick up,
play a game and have some fun.
This is a good game for you in the football sense.
And if you're a horror fan,
it's a lot of fun because obviously the name Mutant Football League.
All the teams I play often as the
hella delfia evils.
You know, it's all these goofy pun variations on football teams.
You play on these fields that have volcanic explosions coming out of them
and fire pits and stuff.
And then the team, of course, is comprised by mutants.
It's a really, really fun.
Just sort of pick up and play bloody violent game.
Players die throughout the game.
You can attack and kill the referee if you don't like the calls he's making.
And then the commentary is funny.
You hear a lot about video games where they go,
this game's funny.
It's not funny.
It's trying to be funny.
But this game actually made me laugh out loud a few times.
Listening to the commentaries and stuff.
It's a very, very fun game and I suggested you can get it.
I got it for on a Black Friday sale for 20 bucks.
You could probably still get it for that price to be honest.
But check it out.
It's a lot of fun.
And that's coming from a guy that's not a sports guy.
I got to recommend downloading the shutter app.
They have great movies and it's cheap.
But they had the 13 movie,
Joe Bob Briggs marathon, which to me my favorite movie related thing all year.
I've had a blast going through them.
A lot of stuff I'd never seen.
The stuff you have seen, it's given a whole new life because you're getting
interrupted at the commercial breaks by this guy who loves these movies so much.
And then on Thanksgiving Day, I was here.
I watched the whole marathon and that was four movies on Thanksgiving night.
Those movies were dinners of death.
One, Texas chance on massacre.
Two, the hills have eyes, the ridge, which we can discuss at a later day.
We are going to discuss Texas chance on massacre.
Three was dead or alive to Keishi Miyake's.
Dead or alive, which was insane.
I watched that and then the last was not.
I believe blood feast.
Oh, wow.
But wait, blood feast is the original.
Well, one of the first slash movies, right?
So this was not blood feast.
Blood feast is, or blood diner, Herschel Gordon Lewis, was it that one?
This was, yeah, I believe this was blood feast.
No, no, blood feast was in the original.
Joe Bob marathon.
This one was called bear with me.
All right.
But it was kind of odd because there are no Thanksgiving movies.
No Thanksgiving horror movies except in the fake one in
Thanksgiving.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But Joe Bob did those three as well as
you just can't.
We got all day here, Pat.
You just can't find it.
Hang on.
I got it.
I've got it.
Blood rage.
Oh, okay, I don't know what.
1987.
That's the one I have yet to watch.
But to see these movies with Joe Bob, Joe Bob gets emotional
20 times throughout these commentaries.
Like he can't believe people give a shit about what he has to say.
It's just been a very sweet experience.
I've really enjoyed watching them.
I've seen great slash movies I've never seen.
Stuff I didn't even know about.
I can't recommend enough getting getting shutter for five bucks.
And if you got some time off for the holidays,
you know, you could do a lot worse than sitting down and watching one of these
marathons with your loved ones.
They're very fun.
They're a great time.
I recommend it highly.
Sure.
They're great.
Quick news psycho.
Jordan Peele.
Yeah, announced making an official sequel to Candyman.
We'll be out next year.
Candyman, we've discussed it on the show.
I love the first one as you do.
Second one kind of sucks.
Farewell of the flesh, never saying it.
Third one I never saw.
But I am excited that he's doing an official sequel to the Candyman movies.
And I would only...
It's a related director.
I assume it's a different ride.
I think it's production companies do.
I can only assume that he's going to bring back Tony Todd
and he's going to do like a real sequel to these things
out of respect for one of the most iconic black horror movie.
Characters ever.
Yeah.
So I think it's very cool.
I think it's very cool.
And I do think, even when I was watching the sequel
and I wasn't that into it,
I did think like this is a series that deserves
another sequel like it deserve.
It's a good idea.
It's a good series.
I think it maybe went a little off the rails.
But you know, it's almost like the Texas chainsaw massacre series where it's like,
hey man, they're not all fucking winners.
But it's something that deserves some thought
and some perhaps revisiting.
So I just think that's really cool that he's doing that.
I'm excited to see him.
Great.
On to cam.
It's streaming on Netflix.
Cam.
Give the people synapses.
Cam is basically about a cam girl,
meaning a girl who strips for
people online.
Which was disappointing because I thought it was going to be about Cameron
for Ferris Bueller's Day Up.
It's Madeline Brewer who I had never seen before,
even though I have seen the Handmaid's Tale.
I didn't remember her being in it.
But I mean, just a beautiful, very talented actress.
Yes.
The movie brings back like sort of an 80s level of sleaze and nudity.
At one point, they're riding a dildo machine for five minutes.
And I was like, holy lord, I'm watching it alone in my house,
like kind of looking over my shoulder embarrassed
due to my Catholic upbringing and shame.
Looking over your shoulder at your own dildo machine.
Yeah, I was looking back at the dildo machine I was riding.
The movie for me, I felt like...
Well, hold on.
But the synapsis is she took Cam girl and then something sinister starts to happen
where she is seeing her own self on the cam network
and she's not making the videos.
Somebody has stolen her whole drive of the movie as she wants to be
ranking higher and higher in the top cam girls.
And she sees a girl succeeding basically using her face
and it's like, how did this girl get my face?
Now, we'll get to the ending of this thing.
But for the first hour, this movie was...
It was a lot of very high quality nudity.
And it's a sign of a great horror movie where
everyone is naked and everyone looks beautiful but you're not a rouse.
David Cronenberg does this sort of thing very well
where you're just like, yeah.
I have never ventured into the cam girl world.
It's never been my thing.
I just do straight porn.
It seems interesting and fascinating and I see how guys lose all their money in these worlds.
I think they have personal connections.
The guy who plays the guy who thinks he's got a personal connection with this woman
is very creepy and disturbing.
And for about an hour, I found myself saying,
this movie is great.
I love it.
I almost wish it was a documentary.
Rashida Jones did a documentary about like cam girls that was
at the end of the day, just as exploitative as this but pretended it was above it
and I found that offensive.
This is like a pro cam girl pro sex movie.
But then, folks, as interesting as it is and it sure is,
and also dealing with her family when her family finds out that she's a cam girl,
I was like, this should have been the movie without the horror element.
I wouldn't have said that if they had stuck the landing but I can't think of many movies
and reason histories that have fucked up the landing as much as cam did.
It's an embarrassing ending to this movie.
The movie starts with a riveting and disturbing scene where she's on camera
and one of her funders or viewers or fans, whatever you want to call it,
starts saying to her that he wants her to use a knife on herself to kill herself on camera.
It's very disturbing.
Eventually she does it and then the reveal is that it was a hoax and she was joking
and that she's not dead and that sort of makes her fans go even crazier for her
that she does these sort of death sex shows, right, these suicide shows, I think they're called
on camera and then as we said, eventually she gets locked out of her account
and somebody else who is her identical twin is doing shows and claiming to be her but it's not her
and that here comes the mystery now figuring out what the hell is going on here, whatever.
Up until that point where she decides I need to figure out what's happening here
and who stole my identity literally, she's a very, I find the character to be very self -centered
and very shallow and basically like enjoying this lifestyle of taking money from men that are
clearly sexist and objectifying her and also are very sad individuals, but that's the trade -off,
I mean I was sure for doing that. That's the trade -off. You got to make a dollar. That's the trade -off.
But it's not a, I wouldn't say it's a great existence, in my opinion.
No. She, but when she finds out this person is stolen from me, this person is taking from me now
and the sort of commentary starts about, well who's taking from who? Who's taking advantage of who?
That whole thing and then it starts to become layered because this very interesting story of like,
wow, well now is it going to be like a hostile thing where this person at the center of this
horror is sort of learning the lesson of like, well fuck, man, maybe what I was doing before wasn't
the way to go, maybe I need to now evolve and learn to be a different type of person and unfortunately,
as you said, the landing is not stuck at the end. She does eventually find out that what is taking
her identity is this sort of demonic force on the internet or whatever. And she does beat it at
the end, which I think is great. She does conquer this thing and get her own identity back at the end,
which I think is great. But then the last scene in the movie is her mom making her up in,
you know, in Cam girl makeup and her turning to camera and going, oh my god, it looks beautiful. And
she doesn't, she looks like a satanic clown at the end. She's got so much makeup on. And then she
goes online and starts a new cam channel. And I just don't understand what the pointer that is.
You've gone against this sort of otherworldly satanic force that can steal women's faces and abuse
them and take advantage of them online, which they establish in the film. And then at the end of the
movie, instead of her becoming the warrior that goes, I'm going to put a stop to this thing.
I'm going to make sure that other women don't feel victim to this. She goes, no, I'm just going to do
a new cam channel. And she actually says the words, if it happens to me again, I'll just make a new
channel. And it's like, what? Yeah, I mean, to me, it was a very fascinating subject done in a very
fascinating way, up to the point where she's with that kind of John in the Mexican restaurant.
That was all very tense and he follows her into the bathroom and all that. And then when they bring
in the supernatural element, it's like, this movie is not, there's nothing about it that should have
made it a supernatural movie. That to me was what threw me off. It was not done in a good way in my
opinion. I was not happy with the direction it went. Maybe some were. I thought this is a very
sexy, interesting thriller about something that everyone knows exists, but doesn't know much about
it. And that should be exactly what like a great horror movie should be. But when they brought in the
supernatural element, I was like, all right, then I don't buy it. Everything about it was so grounded in
reality. And they blew it by bringing in this like robot demon. I didn't ever, I didn't have a
problem with them bringing in the robot demon. That didn't bother me. What bothered me was they depicted
the lifestyle of a cam girl. Yeah. And not one aspect of that lifestyle was positive. Right.
Literally not one. The only positive aspect of it was the materialistic thing. Yeah. And even that
was written by a former cam girl. Yeah. I know. And even that was depicted in a negative light.
Like the big materialistic moment when you're supposed to realize like what she's getting out of
this. Yeah. Is her on her phone as her mom is doing her hair and trying to like have a conversation
with her. And she's completely detached buying the $5 ,000 couch on her on her phone. Even that moment to
me from the writing standpoint and the directorial standpoint and the way it was produced and conveyed
was supposed to be telling the audience, look how absorbed this woman is in materialism. Yeah.
Look how absorbed in what's not important she is. Yeah. And then for her to all of a sudden come
in this realization of like, my God, this thing I worked for is not worth it. Is ultimately going to
be my demise. I need to destroy it. And then she does destroy it. I thought was awesome. And then
when she goes right back to it and goes, I'll just keep doing it over and over again. Right. Even if
it comes after me against like, to me that, I'm sorry. That wasn't the lesson of the movie. I'm not
saying cam growing is bad. I'm not saying doing sex work for money is bad. I'm saying though,
if you want me to believe that there's a reason for her to return to this, you better show me a little
bit of a positive side to this in any aspect. There's not one positive element to it. Yeah. It felt
very real and intriguing and interesting and then never kind of did anything with its premise.
And I think there was a lot more that could have been done here. I would like to share a quick
story about work this week with cam growing about my office. And I'm surprised I waited this
long to tell. Does it relate to the film? 100%. Well, maybe. I walked in. So there's my floor,
which has my show, the cool kids and the Orville on it. I have not seen the Orville. I haven't either.
I went out to get my laptop out of my car. I come back in and I go to the bathroom on the first floor,
which is not my floor. So I don't know who's down there. But clearly it can bring in people from
anywhere on the Fox lot. That's where people are like, it's like Starbucks. Anybody can use that
restaurant. All right. I go in. I walk over to the urinal and I realize that the guy in the stall
is listening to either pornography or cam or something at almost full full phone volume.
It's upsetting. Sitting on the stall and I'm hearing like porn music.
And I walk into the urinal. I don't even undo my pants. I'm just like sitting there listening like,
what is going on here? Keep listening. And then I hear the man saying. And it's it's definitely him
and not coming from the phone. Yeah, turn around, baby. Turn around, baby. Turn around, baby.
So like he's talking to a video. So it's either a cam girl or its phone sex or it's a porn that he's
talking to, which is really weird. Turn around, baby. Turn around. I hear the sounds of a man
masturbating. I'm sitting in there. I don't even go to pee. I'm just like so flabbergasted by this.
I hear him clearly stroking his penis. And then Joe, I start hearing
the man is spitting presumably either end of the toilet or spitting down on his penis to
lube it up. That's so upon his penis. I believe it's on his penis. And while he is doing all this,
he is still shitting. And I hear this all. I don't even consider going to the bathroom. I know it's
a loss cause at this point, but I'm like, because you're too turned on, too turned on. I'm like,
clearly this guy doesn't know that I'm in here. I back up very uneasily. I walk out, but I didn't,
I made a lot of noise coming into the bathroom. It was like door opens, blah, blah. I'm in.
So I bring this up to the room and they're like maybe he was on headphones. Maybe he's on his lunch
break and he's on headphones. I think nobody can hear him jacking off. Doesn't matter, doesn't matter.
But really, like we're in a not only a out and about in the public eye, this is a workplace.
Yeah. Well, jerk in it. He's spitting on it. He's talking to it. So I walk out and I go, you know
what? For whatever reason, I need to see this man's face. I'm going to stay out here until he comes
out. 10 seconds later, a guy walks into the bathroom. He's in there for 30 seconds. He comes out,
gives me like a wide eyed look as if to say, did you hear this guy jacking off in there? I gave him
a look as if to say, yeah, I heard it, dude. Right. He walks off. A third guy comes up, goes in. He
comes out looking very disturbed. I wait 10 minutes and then eventually I gotta just get back to my
job. But I walk back in and I know he never saw my shoes or anything. And he's still watching the
porn, but on a very quiet level. So at some point, he realized somebody or people are coming in here
while I'm jerking off. I'm just going to turn it way down. I mean, when you go into a restroom,
you just have to be aware that with in addition to everything else discussing that could go on in a
bathroom that you know about, somebody could just be spraying their load all over the goddamn seat.
This is not a society that we're living in. Yeah, it's a workplace. Yeah, no,
well, barely. I mean, disgusting. Barely. Well, and that's, I gotta say, that's my issue with the movie.
Okay. Or sort of at the end of this flick, I'm sitting there going, what's the lesson here? I
agree. That the greatest victory in life is taking money from misogynist pigs that if they do meet up
with you, they will beat you and try to take advantage of you. Like, I just didn't get what the
I didn't get what the victory was. I just didn't understand it. And then this clearly this
demonic presence online was supposed to be this sort of ultimate version of a predator. Yeah.
And it's like, but that didn't work. It wasn't clear. It's like, why would you, so then why wouldn't
your thing be to fight this thing? Right. In a different way than I'm just going to show my naked body
again online, where it can just take my identity again. Yeah, I just didn't get it. Like, I just,
it started so great. And this is a movie that I thought was going to suck. I started watching this
thing. I was like, holy shit. There was an hour of it where I was like, so into it. If they land
this, this is a really special horror movie. And like, you know, one of the recent really good ones.
And they just didn't land it. They they set up some and to their credit because that's
not nothing either. Movies are hard. Sure. Everything's hard to their credit. They set up a first hour
where it was like tense and believable. And, you know, you completely were on board with the heroin
and interested in it. And they just didn't stick the landing. So that's not a failed movie. But if
they had landed this thing and said anything interesting by the end of it, we could have had a real
classic on our hands. I was waiting for the I was waiting for the Nancy moment, the Nancy and Nightmare
and Elm Street moment. I was waiting for the moment where she turns to Freddie and says, you need
me to be afraid. I'm not going to be afraid. Right. And turns her back on him. And he fails. Yeah,
I was waiting for that moment. And it sort of happened. Well, it did happen at the end when she
faces off with this thing. She beats her own face to challenge it to show that it's fake. Then she
deletes the account. Like, I'm like, this girl is going boss the wall to like defeat this thing. And
then when the when the epilogue is now I just go back online again. I'm like, no, the epilogue should
be you now going to other cam girls and being like, get off of here because this thing's going
to steal your identity. Again, not saying camgirling is wrong or bad. Well, I think I don't understand.
I think that would be the takeaway in that scenario is that camming is wrong. And I don't think the girl
who wrote it thought camgirling was wrong. I just feel like, why are you bringing in this supernatural
presence only to end the movie in this kind of half shrug? They created something very intriguing
and just didn't bring it anywhere interesting. It's yeah. And that's, I guess that's the issue.
Because at the end of a movie about terrorism, you don't want to see a guy go, you know, you don't
want to see Bruce Willis go go into hiding terrorists are out there. You want to see the Bruce Willis
guy go keep fighting. So I get it. You want to see this girl say keep fighting and not succumb to
this thing. Right. But when there's a fucking entity out there, when you when you make the bad guy the
entity that is undefineable and that will continue to do this, then I'm like, so what are you doing?
Because you need to break your face on the desk. Yeah. Every time this happens. So maybe the issue is
is not it's not what she chooses to do at the end. It's the device that makes her do it, which is
okay, maybe it shouldn't have been a supernatural thing. It would have been better if it was somehow
she traced it to this company. Sure. That had a technology and then she took the company down
and then kept camming that I would have liked. Right. You know, she stopped the thing but she doesn't
stop the thing. She just outsmarts it for a minute or like break away from the machine that
like collects most of the money on these cam things and do your own thing. Yeah. Exactly. Exactly.
I mean just spitballing. But the ending here was just really unsatisfying and honestly not
not not satisfying in terms of plot or in terms of horror or in terms of message or in terms
of anything. It was just kind of not there. I agree with you. That's exactly what I'm saying.
It's like we didn't get to see her take the thing down to then root for her for continuing to
participate in the activity. I wanted to see her take the thing down. But to just go, it was almost
like in the ending of like it was almost like Jamie Lee Curtis at the end of the new Halloween. Yeah.
If she had just been like, well, Michael's still out there. Oh, well.
I think you're like, no, I need to see you defeat Michael or at least think you have. Right.
So then you keep going. That's what you get your strength from. Yeah. So anyway,
cam, not a bad flick. I'll give it a C. C plus maybe even. I'd go B minus B for cam because I thought
for two thirds of its running time, it was one of the more exciting horror movies I've seen in a while.
I had a blast with it. And it's not just the nudity. I thought it was like something really shown
a light on a world I was not familiar with and was very interested in. And just didn't sick the
landing. And at the end of the day, you know, it's better than most movies. It wasn't boring for two thirds
of it. And that's saying something. So I think we agree two hog sideways. Yeah. Mine's sideways and up.
Mine's sideways. Straight sideways. I'm going to go on this one. All right. Folks, that's our show.
Joe DeRosa Comedy on Instagram. I'll be at Gotham Comedy Club January 5th,
6th and 7th. Come on out. It's in New York City. If you are around, I'd love to see you. Also,
my first ever published fiction. My stories used to run on fangoria .com, but they were just things
I gave over to fangorian. They put them up on the website nicely enough. But Penn House now
my column has changed. It's not an op -ed anymore. It's now going to be my fiction horror stories.
And the first one ever is going to run in January. It's called Wallace and his checkerboard. And
I first of all, I've ever been paid to write fiction in my life. I'm very excited about this.
So by monthly, my stories will be in Penn House starting in the new years to check those out. They're
all horror sort of weird, you know, weird fiction. Yeah. I am at the padded wash Twitter and Instagram.
The cool kids returns. We have new episodes. I think through Christmas, but also a lot of
repeats as well. So, you know, check your local listings. But some of my favorite ones coming up.
And whenever it airs, make sure you seek out Zodiac Killer episode, which is my favorite we've done.
Check it out. That's it. We'll be back with Texas Chainsaw Massacre. We'll be back with,
what else are we doing? Probably reanimator, but reanimator Mike had bumped for a Christmas
animated thing. We'll do them at some point. Yeah, but we'll try to do a Christmas one. We've already
done Black Christmas. We've already done Silent Night, Deadly Night. We've got to find another Christmas.
We'll find one easily. Don't worry about it. We'll see you next time. We'll see you in hell.
We'll see you next time.