I'm here for Bet Rivers Online Casino and Sportsbook with poker icon Phil Hellmuth.
And now, thanks to the excitement of Bet Rivers, I'm also a slots icon.
That's great.
And a same game parlay icon.
Cool, cool.
A blackjack icon, a money line icon, a roulette icon.
Take it from Phil Hellmuth.
If you love games, Bet Rivers is the place to play and bet.
Bet Rivers.
Games on.
Must be 21 plus and present in West Virginia.
Void were prohibited.
Terms and conditions apply.
Gambling problem, call 1 -800 -GAMBLER.
Firestone Complete Auto Care's epic savings event is the sign you need to stop putting
off your car's maintenance.
And you can save up to $100 on tires and services while you're at it.
Don't wait.
Call Firestone Complete Auto Care for an appointment.
Ladies and gentlemen, this is it.
Episode number one of We'll See You in Hell, the new podcast featuring myself, Joe DeRosa
and my good buddy Patrick Walsh, or PT Dubs as I call him.
Hi, everybody.
How are you?
We're here under the Fangoria Network.
We're going to be offering commentary on horror movies that you can watch along with.
Or if you're so inclined, just listen in your car.
And we're going to try to make it entertaining for those listeners as well.
I like that we're giving the listeners options.
Yeah.
Well, you know, in this internet age, Joe, you have to.
You know, Pat, I've read that people want entertainment their way.
They want it a la carte, Joe.
It's not like when you and I were kids and there was one channel
and you had to watch what Papa government told you to.
And he's not talking about the government.
That's what he called his dad.
Today, we're going to watch Children of the Corn, which Pat has never seen, which made me think
I don't know if this will be a recurring theme or not throughout the show.
Pat is certainly a horror fan.
I'm a huge horror fan.
I think I've seen a little bit more than he has.
I was wondering if there would sort of be this theme where I'm
showing you a movie you haven't seen before.
Doesn't have to be that.
But, you know, we can do it however we want.
But I certainly of the genres, the one I've seen the least of would definitely be horror
sci fi because it's just never I'm a pussy.
You're frightened of it.
At least as a child, I was always obsessed with comedy and other things.
And horror was always off limits to me.
But you are a cinephile.
I'd go as far as to say.
Million percent.
And I've seen most things.
But like when you get into like these considered classics, your children of the corn, all that
kind of stuff, I've never seen.
Oh, well, that's that's OK.
I like that this might be a budding theme here.
We're discovering it on the first episode.
Yeah, I've read it.
I've read all the Stephen King books.
So you read Children of the Corn.
At some point I must have.
Yeah, because I read all those books.
Well, I must have and I read it are two different statements, Pat.
I don't remember it.
But let's start it off.
And this is where the podcast is going to get a little tricky.
But we're going to basically count down.
We're going to start it, hit pause, right?
And then when we're all on the same page, one, two, three, boom.
And then we all go on together if you're watching at home.
Yeah, well, I'll tell you what we're going to do here is what I want you to do is
I want you to pause.
Not yet.
Hold on.
When I count to three, I want you to pause.
I mean, now this is these are these are the hiccups of a podcast, Pat.
We had it all set up here.
And then the Apple TV just chose to.
Go back to the menu screen.
Why did that happen?
Talk to Steve Jobs.
Now, two stars for Children of the Corn.
Two stars is what they're giving her.
I got to tell you, I don't think it's a great movie.
Well, now it's directed by Fritz Kirch.
Right.
Who I have to assume at least has some ties to the Nazi Party.
And at least a grandfather who has killed a Jew at some point.
Fritz Kirch.
I don't know.
I don't know if that's slander or not.
Sorry.
If you're listening, Fritz, I'm sure you're a great guy.
Let's let's look up Fritz Kirch because, you know.
Well, let's start.
I mean, like we got 90 minutes to fill with our with our commentary.
Let's start the movie.
Yes, I agree.
So you're going to click on the play button.
You're going to see the spinning wheel.
Right.
And as soon as you see the first frame, pause it and that'll make sense in a minute.
So on three, pause this podcast, go find the movie, hit play.
When you see the spinning wheel, great.
When it's the first frame comes on, hit pause.
OK, which also looks like a spinning wheel.
Yeah.
So one, two, three, play.
OK, you're here.
You got the first frame paused.
And now one, three, we're going to hit play together.
Here's why we did it that way, because everybody's load times might be different.
You might have shit internet where you're at.
I got the good stuff, people.
I know my load time depends on the lady.
All right.
Disgusting.
On three, we're going to hit play.
You again, you were paused on the first frame of the film.
One.
Wait, is it on three player on one, two, three, then play.
OK, so one, two, three, play.
There we go.
I got audio, Patty.
You got audio of audio as well.
Looking at just the most bargain basement graphic here for image entertainment.
No offense to the people at image entertainment.
Well, I mean, I know some of the folks over at Image and they said, yeah,
they said they chose not to put money into the graphic.
They want it on the screen.
Yeah, they want it on the screen.
Right.
I got the old Fritz.
His full name is George Keith Kersh.
For some reason, chose to take on the name of Fritz.
Yeah, he was like, let's really SS it up.
One of the greatest title screens in this movie.
Look at that title screen.
It pops.
Very commanding.
Pops with a yellow font.
I like it.
Here's what else Fritz is directed.
Tough Turf.
To you, Etha?
Yep.
I don't know.
Very good.
Winner takes all.
Is there anything we've heard of?
You know, don't read all these.
Swamp Thing, but the series, not the many of the movies.
All right.
The Stranger, The Hunt and a Crayola Kids movie.
This is it.
How weird is that?
So your first movie is showed on the quorum, which is kind of a cult classic.
I think probably did okay at the box office.
And then he just does a bunch of nothing.
I'm curious as to what this made at the box office.
Let's see.
I'm going to go to reception here on all we could be.
Oh, not here's budget.
Eight hundred thousand dollar budget.
You ready for this?
Yeah.
Fourteen point five million.
So that's like a you've made 15 times your money.
Yeah.
It's a great deal.
Good job, Fritz.
There will also be bits of math information throughout this podcast.
And from there, he's he moves to the swamp thing series.
I feel like Fritz got a raw deal.
It wasn't the next thing.
It was just down the line.
Maybe he was difficult on set.
I mean, the movie looks like it was made with my dad's old home movie camera.
I'll say that so far.
It does.
And this this opening voiceover has always disturbed me.
It's a little boy talking and it disturbs me because I'm like,
is this boy going to be evil?
Is he is he going to die immediately?
An unreliable narrator is very smart.
Not to have a grown up narrator.
Because then you say, well, that's one of the grown up kids of the corn.
Now, let's talk Stephen King adaptation.
Yeah.
So here here's this guy.
This here's the kid from the burbs with the red hair
that I always called him a poor man's Eric Stoltz.
Yeah.
And the well, the modern day equivalent is the shermanator from American Pie.
Yes.
And I'm not positive.
They're not the same person.
Well, they could be at least related, I would say.
Speaking of shermanator, Linda Hamilton involved, who was the star of the Terminator?
Yes.
Linda Hamilton is in this film.
I don't think I've ever seen her in anything else other than the Terminator series.
I only ever saw her in the Terminator one and two,
which is why I was thrilled for the Terminator Salvation cameo.
Was she in it?
She's in it for her voices in it.
Her voice is so terrible.
It's a terrible movie.
I'm telling you, I don't know if you're going to like this one much better.
OK, I mean, it's a it is a classic.
Yeah, this seems great.
Now you're in it.
We're in a diner.
Things are being zoomed in on slowly.
OK, things are being dumped secretly into drinks.
So something bad is about to happen here.
Corn shakers look mighty suspicious.
Here we go.
Look at this schmuck doesn't know what's about to happen to him.
Look at this guy.
Here we go.
And the kids are all just standing around the perimeter of the dining room,
staring ominously at all the grownups.
Nobody seems to notice anyone cares.
Now.
This kid.
But now did the kid control that woman putting the powder in the coffee?
No, he's just over.
He's overseeing grabbing their throats.
People are obviously choking now.
Poisoning is happening.
And they're look at this lady.
I mean, is that how you choke?
Would you choke like that with wide eyes?
Absolutely not.
Also, here's my question.
Why when people are choking, do they grasp their throat?
The thing that needs loosening and they clench it.
Why do they do that?
Well, I don't know.
I haven't seen anyone choke in real life.
That might not be what happens.
But maybe you're just telling everybody, hey, my throat help choke.
I mean, well, even if that is what you're saying,
though, there goes a hand into a meat slicer.
This scene was also in Kingpin.
You'll remember they put his hand in the bowling thing.
I don't need to see blood splatter on the six year old's face.
Kid seems to be kind of loving it.
Well, the kids are evil, so I can't.
That kid's evil, too.
I don't know.
I don't remember.
If I'm six years old, I got man blood on my face.
I'm going to be like, oh, my God, let me at least wipe this off.
Now, clearly, the kid outside Malachi is his name
that looks like the young Doug Benson.
He's the he's the overseer of all this.
OK.
So everywhere in Gatlin that day, Gatlin's the town they live in.
The kids all murdered the parents.
All right.
So now the kids are running the town, I guess.
Oh, Pete Horton.
Wings?
No, that's Tim Daly and Steven Weber.
Again, Tim Daly, rich man's Peter Horton.
Peter Horton was on 30 something.
Yes.
And he was in Singles.
Yeah.
He was the biker.
I love Singles.
I love it, too.
Underrated movie.
I love Singles.
You know, part always perplexed me in Singles.
Let's talk.
I just watched it when she goes around.
When she goes, I'm going to make a salad.
She makes the most gigantic fucking salad I've ever seen.
She's like hacked apart the cucumbers and carrots with like a
it looks like she cut them up with a samurai sword.
Just these hunks of vegetable.
Who the fuck eats salad like that?
That couldn't have had less of an effect on me.
I it is always.
I've always found it confusing and I always thought like that's
clearly some character trait thing like that's some subtlety
about the character.
I'm supposed to be understanding and I never got it.
I didn't.
I just figured she's making a big old salad and they want it to be
visually exciting.
Yeet salad like that.
You're going to be a fat shit.
Defeats the purpose of salad.
You can eat vegetables all day and not.
I know.
All right.
It was a joke, Pat.
I mean, if we want to pick apart every bit now.
I didn't like it.
Let's talk.
Present day.
Wait, what was that opening?
I didn't notice that that had.
I just saw Southpaw with Jake Gyllenhaal.
Yeah, just is corny, but I enjoyed it.
The character's name is Billy Hope.
That tells you anything about the tone of the movie.
I mean, but they talk for 20 minutes about how he's going to be
boxing at this upcoming charity fight for like the let's say it's
the Boys and Girls Club.
Right.
They keep talking about and talking about and talk about.
Then they cut to the exterior of the fight.
You hear the bell go off and they put up on the screen a title
card that says Charity Fight Boys and Girls Club.
They've not done any title cards the whole movie.
Like the entire theater was like, we know Southpaw.
Well, you don't have to tell us.
Do they keep up with the title cards after that?
At least there's not another title card in the film.
So some executive was probably like, are we going to be confused?
That's ridiculous.
As to where they are and name the guy hope so everybody gets it.
Yeah.
There's also a scene where Gyllenhaal, he has an estranged daughter
and he's helping her with her homework and he's in a really dark place.
And she's like, help me with these spelling words.
And he does one word and the second word is helplessness.
And I bet Pat, I bet you felt helpless at that point in that theater.
It's a very heavy handed movie, but I did enjoy it and I do recommend
I like the film written for Eminem.
And then Gyllenhaal is kind of trying to do the Eminem thing.
And with him, it seems a little like minstrel show kind of offensive to me.
That was how I felt when Ed Norton did it in that dinner in that dinner room.
Couldn't agree more.
It's also very uncomfortable.
Hollywood 50 cent, 50, quote, Curtis Jackson, end quote, sent is not an actor.
We have to stop pretending that he is.
Is he bad?
He's terrible, Joe.
And they give him job after job.
He's better than Common, who is the worst rapper actor.
Well, Common was in Terminator Salvation.
Well, there you go.
No further questions, you're on.
Yeah.
Ludacris is a bad actor.
I like Ludacris as an actor.
Wait, do I?
No, I like.
Well, I like Ice Cube as an actor.
Ice Cube is a fantastic act.
I like ice.
That doesn't mean everybody is.
Yes.
Ludacris.
I remember being pretty good in what's that movie?
Like the racist Pulp Fiction.
What was that movie called?
The Racist Pulp Fiction.
Oh, Crash?
Yeah.
It was like all the races of stories.
Was Ice Cube in that?
No, Ludacris was in that.
With Lorenz Tate, who I haven't seen in a while.
Yeah, I always liked Lorenz Tate.
By the way, we've sort of drifted away from the movie for a second.
Right now, Linda Hamilton is doing a song and dance number.
A strip tease where it seems she's putting more clothes on throughout.
Now, on the rich man, poor man scale, where do you put Peter Horton above or below Stephen Webber?
Definitely below Webber.
Above Daley?
No, I put Daley above, too.
Daley is a solid enough actor, but I really liked him as the screenwriter on Sopranos.
I know you don't like Sopranos.
And Webber, I think, is a very funny, likable dude.
I didn't see him in The Shining for TV.
I wouldn't watch that.
I mean, I don't understand.
Stephen King prefers the Stephen Webber Shining to the Nicholson Shining.
I know.
I don't understand.
I tried watching it because Stephen King said he preferred it.
Yeah.
And, you know, his whole argument was it was more true to the book.
Which, OK, that's fine.
Right.
You could be mad at Kubrick for ruining your book.
I've got no problem with that.
You can say I hate the Kubrick version of the film.
Yeah.
I got no problem with that.
And you can say that the miniseries with Stephen Webber was a better adaptation of the book.
Sure.
What you can't tell me, though, is that that fucking miniseries was entertaining
or that anybody was buying Stephen Webber as a lunatic.
No, it's true.
And, you know, it's just it's simple math.
Stephen Webber compared to Jack Nicholson.
There's no scenario where Stephen Webber acts a scene better.
And I think Webber would tell you the same.
I don't know.
I met Webber once.
Pretty pleased with himself.
Sure.
I met Webber as well.
Webber.
Nice enough.
But he guested on a sitcom I wrote for.
And I don't know if he had like glanced at the script.
I don't know if he had touched a script.
Yeah.
And it was in front of an audience and it got a little tense.
No offense to Stephen Webber, who I do I do like.
I find him very funny.
Handsome man.
Did the fat guy on Wink.
Let me tell you this.
Now, you were on Better Call Saul.
I'm going to go ahead and butter your bread a little bit.
The fat guy in Better Call Saul, who spoiler alert dies at the end of the season
as the heart attack, that guy was great.
And he's also on an HBO show called Getting On or Getting By the Medical Show.
That guy looks identical to the fat guy from Wings,
but they can't be the same man because they're 25 years apart.
Who's the fat guy from Wings?
The fat guy with the mustache from Wings.
Did he ever act again?
Well, I can look it up.
Crystal Bernard on Wings.
Did she ever act again?
By the way, real quick, how much does this kid look like a young Paul Rudd?
Well, it is a young Paul Rudd, is it not?
I don't think so.
I'm going to look it up.
Hold on.
Did you see Ant -Man?
No.
I liked Ant -Man.
I love Paul Rudd.
I like comic book movies.
I don't want to see Ant -Man.
It's pretty entertaining.
It's just Marvel is turning everything into a comedy now.
Age of Ultron was like Expendables level one liners.
I didn't see Age of Ultron, but I think all those superhero movies,
like Terminator Salvation is a perfect example.
You have to have some humor because these movies are ridiculous.
Terminator 2 is a funny movie.
Terminator Salvation, they act like it was Schindler's List with the level of intensity.
Right.
I don't mind a little bit of humor, but I don't want a comedy.
Ant -Man is largely a comedy, and I didn't mind that at all.
Well, and then they...
It's called Ant -Man.
And then they just said that the guys that wrote the vacation remake
are writing the new Spider -Man, and they said it's going to have a John Hughes feel.
What are you doing?
I don't do that.
Well, we don't need another Spider -Man.
God damn it.
You and I saw that last one with Jamie Foxx as the nerd who turns blue.
That was the worst movie I've ever seen in my life.
It was a real piece of shit.
Hey, who can we get to play this nerd?
How about one of the strongest, handsomest men in the world, Jamie Foxx?
That doesn't have straight hair, yet he's going to be balding with a comb over.
Just a terrible movie.
But luckily, it was only three and a half hours long.
Now, Children of the Corn, Joe, where do you put that in terms of Stephen King adaptations?
I've enjoyed Stephen Weber adaptations more.
I don't even know if there are any.
The 80s really were the prime time for your Stephen King adaptation.
It's insane.
This is from the book Night Shift, I believe.
And Night Shift, you know what?
Let me pull this up because it really is an uncanny.
I bought this book when I was home last.
I had never purchased it.
I was home last Christmas.
And I bought it while I was home for something to read.
And I was sitting at the table.
My mom's a big horror movie fan.
And I was sitting at the table with her the day after I bought it,
reading her the table of contents.
I said, Mom, the money that this guy made off of this one book, just this one.
Ready for this?
Yeah.
Graveyard Shift turned into a movie.
The Mangler turned into a movie.
What was the Mangler?
Robert Englund movie.
Oh, OK.
I remember the catch or the phrase.
The famous line in the trailer was he goes, We all make sacrifices.
The Actual Release?
What?
And then they made sequels that didn't make it.
The Boogie Man, which there's a movie called Boogie Man.
I'm not sure if it's an adaptation of that or not.
So we'll say that's a bonus track possibly.
Trucks, which was turned into Maximum Overdrive.
Sometimes they come back.
Yeah, that's a movie.
TV movie.
The Lawnmower Man movie.
Obviously a movie.
Never saw The Lawnmower Man.
It's a despicable adaptation of the story.
The story itself is.
The story itself is great.
It's about a weirdo creepy lawn mowing service.
It's not about a simple minded man that becomes a power god.
Well, from age 10 to 20, I mowed lawns easily 20 a week at 20 a pop,
bringing me a nice little chunk of change each week.
Always an entrepreneur under the name The Lawnmower Man.
Really?
And that might have got me the business because I was kind of like
wink wink.
But I never saw the film.
It's it's it's not good.
OK, not not one of Pierce Brosnan's Shining Loans.
Right, right, right, right.
Quitters Inc.
Not familiar.
And The Ledge, which are both short stories that appeared in the film Cat's Eye,
one of my favorite Stephen King.
Yeah, you and I watched Cat's Eye.
Children of the Corn.
And he also gets a piece of the 12 sequels to Children of the Corn.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, let's let's go to those, actually.
But I mean, I can't I just it's the amount of money.
Oh, wait, here's a OK.
Well, Stephen King, I would wager is a billionaire, right?
He'd have to be.
I mean, he's got to be unless.
Oh, and Battleground also was was turned into an episode of Nightmares and Dreamscapes.
Battleground is the best episode of that.
Well, they hit that mannequin.
They just hit the young Paul Rudd with a car.
I'm going to look up Paul Rudd and see if he was ever in Children of the Corn.
I mean, it's uncanny how much that looks like.
You sure?
Yeah.
But what's your favorite Stephen King adaptation?
Well, you know, we've talked about this.
I go back and forth, but, you know, I think you'd said Misery last time.
And I think Misery is Misery.
Misery probably is the best.
That's a perfect movie, but it's a thriller, not a horror.
Yeah, but I mean, it's I have it in my horror movie section of DVDs.
I don't put it over.
You know, I don't put it in the dramas.
It's just a perfect movie.
You know, you should go sometimes onto Wikipedia or IMDb or whatever and look up
all the actors who they wanted to get before landing on James Kong,
because it's every actor in Hollywood.
Who else do they want?
All your big De Niro, Pacino, Hoffman, Nicholson, et cetera, et cetera.
You look uncomfortable.
Are you comfortable the way you're sitting?
I mean, I'm always uncomfortable, but I'm fine.
OK, good.
They wanted Nicholson.
They wanted Pacino?
Beatty, Pacino, De Niro, basically every actor that was around before landing on Kong.
I think Kong's really good in it, but I could definitely see any of the other people.
I I could not picture anyone other than Kathy Bates playing that role now.
Now they're doing a Broadway musical of Misery with Bruce Willis and Laurie Metcalf.
Is it a comedy?
I assume it's a dark comedy like I consider Misery a dark comedy, but I'd like to see it,
though it sounds like it's probably though.
Oh, that I don't know.
Everything doesn't need music added to it on Broadway.
I disagree.
There's a lot of great straight plays up there.
Sure, but people don't go see him.
He doesn't put asses in the seats.
I mean, look, all I heard about was that one that Chris Rock was in.
Everybody was going to see that thing.
What was that?
I couldn't tell you.
My life depended on it right now.
Pootie Tang the musical.
Bradley Cooper did The Elephant Man.
Was that a musical?
No, no, no.
John Merrick, not known for his song and dance abilities.
And you love The Mist.
I remember you saying.
Yes, that's I was struggling.
I was like, I can't remember what I said when we talked about this.
The Mist is is way up there.
The Mist is awesome.
It's a contender for number one.
I'll probably give number one to Misery and number two to The Mist.
The Mist.
The fact that a major studio allowed a movie with that ending to be released blows my mind.
I love it.
I saw or heard an angry group of people leaving a theater.
I saw it with my parents and we all loved it.
And my mom was visibly shaken by the ending.
Yeah, she was upset.
Well, let's not say what it is.
I bet a lot of people have not seen The Mist and I think that's a shame.
Yeah, it was it was an amazing movie.
And I love that guy.
What's his name?
The guy that played Tommy Jane.
Yeah, Tom Jane.
I'm fine with him.
Tom Jane.
Now I call time and this is not an insult to Tom Jane.
Big fan.
I call him the poor man's Aaron Eckhart.
He he certainly is.
Although Aaron Eckhart does nothing for me at all.
I love Aaron Eckhart.
I love him in the company of men.
Everything else.
I'm like, all right.
I love him.
I love Tom Jane and everything.
Aaron Eckhart just has a higher profile.
All right.
That's fine.
You know, after all, he was I Frankenstein.
Did you see that?
No.
Oh, OK.
I don't like those movies like that was like that when they made Van Helsing.
With Hugh Jackman.
I don't like like those like horror adventure movies.
Yeah.
Well, now they're rebooting all the old classic universals, which.
Well, they did Wolfman three years ago.
Nobody cared.
They're going to read.
Well, it was terrible.
They they fucked it up.
I swear to God, I think Benicio, the tour is an amazing actor.
You watch you watch that movie.
I'm like, he didn't want to be there.
Yeah, he's he's like mailing it in a way where I'm like, I don't like he it's he's
not capable of being this bad unless it's on purpose.
What I find interesting about Benicio del Toro is if there's ever a movie with any
element of drugs, Benicio del Toro is like contractually required to be in it.
And I find that a little weird.
Well, what I mean, he's in traffic.
He's in 21 grams.
There's an upcoming movie for the guy who did Prisoners, which is a fucking awesome
movie that looks like traffic and Del Toro is in that.
OK.
It's just like, why does every every epic drug movie get sent to him?
That that still Oliver Stone movie Savages.
Del Toro was in that thing.
He is.
I didn't see that.
Sure.
Yeah, I he was in an episode of Miami Vice guarantee there was some drug.
Definitely drug paraphernalia in that.
How was Savages?
I really like Savages, but it's just hot trash.
It's really trash.
Well, in what way?
Uh, it's just it's almost like an exploitation movie.
Like it's a lot of like.
Just nudity and people chewing the scenery and Travolta hamming it up.
And it was fun.
It really was fun.
But it's just trash.
All right.
I never I never saw it.
Stone lost me a few years ago.
Yeah, I'll always see what he comes out with, but he's clearly lost his mind.
Wait, what's his new movie?
The Snowden one, right?
Yeah.
Uh, with who's who's Snowden Eisenberg?
I know, isn't it like.
Wait, is it?
No, it isn't like Matt Damon.
No, isn't Matt Damon?
I'm probably not right, but I'm closer than Matt Damon.
Oh, you know, who's playing him is Kyra Sedgwick.
Star of singles, which brings us back to P Horton.
I loved her in singles.
Uh, as far as like dream women in movies for me, uh,
Sedgwick is number one.
And also I'm going to go Holly Hunter in Raising Arizona.
No, I love a Holly Hunter, but I don't.
That's not a dream woman to me.
I love in that movie.
I mean, I really do.
I love the accent, too.
Uh, broadcast news.
Yeah.
Broadcast news.
I see that.
That to me is more dream woman.
Holly Hunter movie opens with her sobbing uncontrollably on a bed.
And I was like, yeah, dream woman.
And you got and you got Albert Brooks.
Joseph Gordon Levitt is playing JGL Snowden.
Good for him.
I like him.
You also got Melissa Leo in there.
Big fan.
Tom Wilkinson.
Nicholas Cage making his theatrical comeback.
What's he going to be?
Uh, he is playing it though.
It's unlisted.
Okay.
So, uh, maybe Barack Obama.
I'm going to tell you it bothers me so much how Nicholas Cage is like a big joke now
because he was growing up my favorite actor and remains one of my favorite actors.
And I'll still see what he comes out with the fact that he has to do made for TV shit
basically to pay off the dinosaur eggs that he's decorated his mansion with.
It's sad, but he's still a great actor.
Well, uh, bad lieutenant port of call new Orleans.
I look, he was amazing in that.
I can test that, uh, it's, it, it rivals the original.
Of course it does.
I mean, it's a masterpiece in my mind.
Honeymoon in Vegas the other day.
That's a perfect romantic comedy.
And he is so funny in that, that it's like, it's almost unbelievable how funny he is.
Like when he explodes and screams at people in that movie, I had to pause it every time.
And then raising Arizona, of course, is as good as movies get for me personally.
Uh, matchstick men's one of my favorite pieces of his work.
I mean, it's him, Sam Rockwell and, uh, in rock.
The rock's not in matchstick, man.
Oh, the movie, the rock.
The movie, the rock stars Nicholas cage.
And also that's how I refer to Sam Rockwell as the rock.
I was going to say dream woman.
What the fuck's the girl's name in matchstick, man?
Uh, and she's in drag me to hell.
Oh, you're talking about Alison Loman?
Yes. When she shows up at the end and you realize she's like a grownup.
Yeah.
And she's like that sexy, like hustler.
Oh, she's a lesbian.
No, she's married with a kid.
I looked it up.
Is she?
Yeah. I'll look up like women that have only been in a few movies like that, that I think are hot.
Like it'd be like, I wonder if they're mad at chance.
Maybe who knows?
Like they show up in the improv one thing.
Maybe her star has fallen far enough that she's willing to entertain a Joe DeRosa court.
Yeah. I mean, who knows?
Yeah. Okay.
Stranger things have happened because you read those things.
You'll see like real hot actress.
You'll be like, who's she married to?
It'll be like she married key grip.
Lawrence Sandy Bullock married a kid.
Yeah. So it's possible.
All right.
She also married that dildo with the tattoos.
Yeah. And he cheated on her, right?
Yeah. How do you do that?
Julia Roberts married a grip, I think.
And Lyle love it.
You know, there's a lady who's willing to explore the darker side of men.
So now what's going on here?
I'm tweeting, by the way, that we're recording the first step so people can send questions.
If they're like, what's going on here?
Well, there's a kid dressed like Charlie Chaplin.
So like really at the end of this,
I can't even really say I've seen the movie because we're just shooting the shit.
I'm going to have to watch it all on my own.
Well, what's happening is.
Is this Bugsy Malone now?
Are they playing like they're adults?
I think maybe these two children are marrying one another.
I mean, they're wearing grown up clothes for some reason.
And is this a straight up cult thing?
Like, like, does this go to places like kids fucking each other or is it not that dark?
No.
Okay.
No, it's just the basic.
The basic gist of this is do you hear him just say, I act according to his rule.
I did in a highly questionable accent.
Him is he who walks behind the rose.
Okay.
Creepy description.
Sure.
The rose of four.
Yeah.
So they're they're they're in service to this God and and the children shall lead them.
And they're, you know, I think they're I think the basic plot is maybe
just wiping out humanity, starting fresh with the children in service of this God.
The corn God.
Yeah.
I just saw a preview of Sinister 2 and I thought Sinister 1 was an excellent horror movie.
Best horror movie of that year.
I thought it was fantastic.
And the opening scene of them like hanging,
like that slow motion scene I thought was like a perfectly shot scene.
Yes.
Uh, but now Sinister 2 seems to have a very children of the corn element to it because
the preview.
There's three people hanging on crosses in the middle of the cornfield.
Yeah.
So I guess they're doffing the cap to see OTC.
Well, oh, very nice.
I like that you already have a nickname for it, even though you've never seen it.
Yeah.
The I can't wait for Sinister 2.
I am a little concerned with the with the whole like,
now we're going to show the other side of it.
Right.
This is going to be more about what the children are doing in their world.
And yeah, well, that never seems to work out when they try to go to the other side of the thing.
You know, like Poltergeist, the other side, which was literally,
although in the Poltergeist remake, the only part that I thought was worthwhile because it,
it made me so angry and depressed because it was so bad and Poltergeist is my favorite horror movie.
The remake when they went into the other side and showed you like the other
world of souls was the only interesting development in the new movie.
I didn't even like that part because they ruined it by flying a fucking drone into it.
Yeah.
Yeah, a lot of drone material on that one.
Which, which, by the way, was the setup for which, or excuse me, which was the,
which that scene where he comes in with all the merchandise and is like,
even though we're broke, I bought all this stuff and explicitly any of that.
It was just set up to be like, I got this drone now.
Yeah.
I mean, they couldn't have written just this thing.
Like, don't tell your mom you're going through a tough time, kiddo.
I'm going to get you this drone.
And then the kid has to hide it from the mom.
And then at the end he pulls it out.
I've been hiding this because you dad didn't want, you know, she spent the money,
but we need it now.
Yeah.
What was that?
20 seconds, 10 times better.
I mean, I, so on my top 10 movies of all time are both poltergeist and national
lampoon's vacation.
We're in a summer now.
We're going to see remakes of both.
I went into poltergeist like, all right, this isn't going to be one of your favorite
movies of all time.
This isn't going to be anywhere close to that.
I lowered my expectations to their bare minimum and I was let down.
And I'm hoping vacation doesn't do the same.
It looks like it might be kind of funny.
I don't know.
You're you're nuts.
You're literally nuts.
I am maybe building my hopes up now.
Here's what I'll say.
I went into poltergeist with only with moderate expectations because you told me
it was bad.
When I heard it was being made, I was thrilled.
I thought the trailer looked great.
Sam Rockwell, arguably my favorite actor out there right now.
Oh, wow.
Yeah, I love him.
But yeah, so I had very high hopes.
I was, I was unfortunately let down and it wasn't that great.
The to me, it was like being kicked in the throat.
The vacation remake on me out.
I mean, I become angered during the trailers.
OK, I mean, just the redoing of the jokes.
Yeah.
And making them like more extreme and zany now.
Like the first vacation movie feels like a real movie.
It's a real excuse me.
It feels like a real story.
It's believable.
The stuff he does is just crazy enough that it's believable.
Now you get this doing it out of love for his family, which to me,
make honestly, there are times, especially if I've had 10, 12 drinks,
where Washington vacation on a Saturday night, I can get a little misty.
Yes.
Because he just cares so much about his family.
And that seems to be lost in this, but maybe it isn't.
I don't know.
I'm sure that element of it is there.
But I mean, it's like my point is, is Chevy Chase driving with
Christie Brinkley in the car next to him?
And when they hit, I don't like that.
You know, it's believable and funny.
And then this one, they redo it and she gets hit.
And Ed Helms just makes that face like, it's like you'd be screaming in horror.
First of all.
Yeah.
You know, the thing with like how now they they have the weird car
like in the in there, like, oh, that that this happened again.
And it's not believable at all.
Yeah.
The joke where Chevy Chase is like, you know, gave me that guitar, Bob Dylan.
And then the kid's like, and the kid goes, wow, you knew Bob Dylan.
He goes, no, no, no, no, just a guy whose name happened to be Bob Dylan.
This is a joke in the trailer in one of the trailers.
And then he goes, but you know who gave Bob Dylan that guitar?
Jimi Hendrix.
And the kid goes, Jimi Hendrix gave your friend this guitar.
And he goes, well, not the Jimi Hendrix.
It's it's it's I'm like, what the fuck?
That's like a 30 year old joke.
Yeah.
It's not going to be good.
Well, I hate I like everybody in the movie.
I wanted it to be good.
It's not going to be good.
I don't know.
I don't I don't get my hopes up about anything anymore in every aspect of my life.
It served me pretty well because I'm always like, yep, there's another disappointment.
Now, when in the Terminator, Jen.
Yeah.
Thinking it was going to be a shit show.
Me and Joe go.
We go see term Termi Jen's front to back enjoyment.
Had a great time.
I enjoyed every second of it.
Yeah, I had a really good time with Termi Jen's.
A lot of fun.
Yeah, a lot of fun.
Certainly better than Salvation.
Good movies this year.
You know, I didn't I didn't I thought it could have less comedy,
but I thought Age of Ultron was great.
Didn't see.
I enjoyed Termi Jen, as you call it.
I think Star Wars is going to be phenomenal.
Sure, you can't call that as one of the good movies of the year.
Oh, I mean, look, I stuck with Star Wars through the prequels.
Definitely fucking up.
Yeah, I mean, we've seen that it is possible.
But I am that's that's literally going to be
the most excited I've ever been to see a movie in my life.
Yeah, I think that's going to be that's the kind of movie
where you like carefully choose who you're going to see it with.
There's like everything about it is kind of important.
And I don't even really give a shit about Star Wars.
I'm more more of an Indy Jones guy,
which is why the fourth one was such a, you know, bottoming out for me.
I saw it alone so nobody could ruin it.
I wish I had so I could have wept silently in the back row.
Saw twice on opening day.
Yeah, I liked it.
I didn't think it was great, but I liked it.
And it's moments.
It had more prairie dog reaction shots than I was expecting.
I'll say Meerkat, Meerkat, Shia LaBeouf's.
Now, what's going on here?
He's got a bloody pair of underpants.
But I got to be honest, we've been talking so much about other movies.
I've lost where we're at in the film.
And that's probably good because I imagine at least half the listeners
are not watching along with children's porn.
Oh, like also, nobody's died in a while.
It's I think look, the Steven Weber guy could be dead by now.
I wouldn't even know there's the kids have killed.
I think they killed his dog.
I think that handkerchief was around his dog's neck.
Now, have you seen the children of the corn sequels?
No, but I'm glad you bring it up because I want to look these up.
So hold on.
Sure.
All right.
Children are the corn sequels and I own one of them.
I know they go at least up to children of the corn 666.
Yes.
I mean, they were just there was a guy sitting somewhere that was like,
we just got to make it to six.
We just got to make it to six.
Yeah.
Children of is it a satanic cult?
Can you at least give me the bare minimum of information on this movie?
It's a yeah, it's a it's a it's a cult involving, you know,
the underworld or black magic or something along those lines.
I don't know that they ever use the word Satan.
Yeah.
But it is sacrilegious.
You know, there's the creation of a weird sort of Jesus
mosaic thing behind an altar and OK.
And as you can hear right now, the choir's chanting.
Anytime there's choirs chanting, it's a little hellish, right?
Yeah.
OK, the film series.
Well, this guy's about to die.
Yeah.
I think.
Yeah, I don't.
And then they cut the old mechanic wins this.
I don't think they cut away.
Wouldn't it be great if he came out holding a kid's head?
Where are they driving, by the way?
Like, I'm not I'm not watching the movie, really.
But like they've been driving a very long time for this to be a movie.
Poor Linda Hamilton spent her entire movie career in cars driving away from people.
Yeah, it's not fair.
She never you know, what what other movie
involves a lot of driving through cornfields is Jeepers Creepers.
Terrible film.
Let me tell you this.
I like Jeepers Creepers a lot and I like Jeepers Creepers to a lot.
I'm going to ruin Jeepers Creepers for you.
I'm going to tell you this.
Both movies were directed by a convicted pedophile.
So that ruins it right there.
The man directed The Fun House.
Francis Ford Coppola produced.
I know.
I like, hey, he molested a kid on the set of this movie.
Then years later, he was allowed to direct Powder,
which was kind of a hit with Jeff Goldblum.
Yeah.
Powder, which is a very strange movie, but kind of OK.
It's a lot of powder being shirtless.
Yes, he was big on that.
Yeah.
And then Jeepers Creepers involves a lot of teen boys pissing in cornfields,
shirtless, etc.
And the whole time I'm like they entrusted a large horror movie franchise
to a convicted pedophile.
Right.
This wasn't that long ago.
And I love that is that his most popular work is Powder,
which is a movie about keeping secretly keeping a teenage boy in your basement.
Yeah, exactly.
And the man's name is Victor Salva.
I'm going to call him out.
Victor Salva.
We all know you molested that boy.
If you're less, there's a dead mechanic, by the way.
Yeah.
But I actually really like both Jeepers Creepers.
I saw them in New York.
I haven't seen them since.
Maybe I'd like them.
Well, let me you won't let me ruin the movie for you.
All right.
Number one, and you know, we are doing this podcast for Fangoria,
and I'm glad this product came out because this is something I've said in a previous
interview I do with Vancoria Fangoria.
Number one, they do the worst thing.
Actually, let me just ruin the movie for you in one sentence,
and then I'll tell you all the other shit that sucks about it.
Just picture the monster who drives a truck even though he can fly.
It's like a big sort of dragonfly bug looking thing.
Yeah.
Just picture the monster who's driving the pickup truck even though he has the
flight having to go to the Getty station to fill up his truck, which he has to do at some point.
Yeah.
It didn't have any shape shifting powers.
Movie ruined.
Did it have any shape shifting power?
No.
That monster has to go to a Sunoco and say, I had 10 on three.
What pump was I at?
Three.
Now, what if he had a debit card and he could pay without it?
Did it look like a town where they had pay at the pump?
Didn't to me.
Well, I haven't engaged with a gas station attendant in 10 years.
Well, that movie came out about 10 years ago.
Yeah, you're probably right.
All right.
He walks behind the rows.
Maybe it had a full tank when he took the truck.
It's his truck.
He owns it.
He lives in a house.
Oh, yeah.
He's got like a house he lives in.
Now, if I'm not mistaken, Juvies Creepers was the first movie to start that horror movie craze
like playing some old song over like an upbeat, old timey song.
Well, I'm glad you bring that up.
Wasn't it?
One of the horrible things about the movie.
You mean the shitty joke that at the end of the movie, you see what he wanted was Justin
Long's eyes and it's playing Jeepers Creepers.
Where'd you get those papers?
Yeah, they have.
I didn't hate it.
They have the worst horror movie trope of all time, which is the black woman with the
ambiguous island accent coming out of like nowhere being like, I'll tell you who the
Jeepers monster is, man.
I know a thing or two about a Jeepers Creepers, man.
It's just it's just a terrible movie.
Yeah.
And you know who loves that movie?
Who?
The guy that played Miles on Murphy Brown.
Grant shot.
Grant.
Yeah.
Grant and I shot an episode of Louie together and we went to lunch.
I didn't realize he was who he was.
We're like halfway through lunch at this diner.
I'm like, so what else have you done, buddy?
He was in Jeepers Creepers.
No, he goes.
I was in I was on a sitcom and I go, what's it coming?
He goes, Murphy Brown.
I was like, yeah, he was always shit.
You were my role.
Yeah.
And he was like, yeah.
And we and we just started talking about it was just the two of us.
We started talking about horror movies and he we hit it off.
We had a great talk.
He's a great dude.
But he was like, go see Jeepers Creepers immediately.
You love it.
And I went and saw it on Miles's say so.
Yeah.
And I didn't have the heart to tell him later when I talked to him later.
And he said, did you like it?
And I just said, yeah, I got to say outside of like Rosemary's Baby,
it's my favorite horror movie directed by a pedophile.
You know, oh, boy, Jesus Christ.
Wow.
Yeah, no, I know.
So these two are just driving.
That's the movie.
Yeah.
It's Linda Hamilton.
That's what she used to do.
She she looks she never aged.
She looks exactly the same age in like Terminator.
Why doesn't she still go work?
Is it because she has a bit of a masculine face?
If you'll forgive me.
Well, I don't think that's what it is because I think she doesn't.
It's because I'm thinking of her jacked up in Terminator 2.
But I think her sort of rugged, slightly masculine quality
is what makes a lot of men attracted to her.
A lot of guys like a girl like that, you know, closeted.
No, come on now.
She's wearing the shorts are terrible.
She's wearing like calf length khaki shorts.
Yeah, I mean, she's not.
She's dressed identical to Peter Horton,
except she's just rolled up the part of the appendages.
But well, the same.
I mean, look at those slacks now.
You couldn't get a female hero heroine, if you will, in a movie today,
wearing that.
Are you kidding me?
Well, here's what I like about your Lindell Hamilton's of the world
is she and same with Peter over here, both good looking people,
but normal looking people.
Yeah, if that couple came into your diner, you'd be like,
these are normal people and be like, oh, these are the hottest people in town.
Where'd they come from?
I am never on board with hot people in movies, and it's it's it's a problem.
You know, Jerry Maguire, I thought Tom Cruise was was really good in it,
but it was supposed to be Tom Hanks.
And, you know, in romantic movies like that, I'm just picking one random example.
When Tom Cruise is struggling to like connect with Zellweger or whatever,
I'm like, both of you will be fine.
It removes the stakes for me.
Right.
Like when Tom Cruise is like, oh, man, I might not wind up with this woman.
It's like, well, you know, who you could probably wind up with
is the millions of women dying to blow you just out of frame.
Zellweger's in that movie, isn't it?
Yeah, it's so wager.
That was her big.
I always thought that that was Joey Lauren Adams.
No, I always thought it was an older Haley Joel Osment.
Oh, you walk.
You fell for it, Patty.
I said you fell for it.
I'm glad to see H .J .L. getting some work these days.
I'm happy he's back, too.
He's great.
And I love the movie Tusk.
It was my favorite horror movie of last year was a disaster.
You didn't like it.
I loved it.
Disturbing, creepy.
I love Justin Long was disturbing.
Why?
It hurts me to say I didn't like Jeepers Creepers.
I shared a 40 ounce with him once.
I played poker with him.
Yeah, we were watching that movie, The Room, that shitty movie that people go see.
Yeah, he knew my friend and he sat next to me and I snuck 40s in.
He was like, can I have some of your beer?
And we shared a 40.
And then he like kind of like toured me tour guided me through the film and was like,
here's what happens at this part.
Everybody's going to yell this.
Very nice guy.
You know, since the moment I arrived in Los Angeles, I have and I, you know,
I love doing all this shit and I feel like I've seen most movies.
The Room I have never seen because I'm always like it's not I can't watch it alone.
And it's got to be kind of an event because it's been built up so much.
So I've just never seen it.
But I want to get a group together and watch it.
I would tell you this.
It's so shitty.
You might be able to watch it on your own and still enjoy it.
All right.
I mean, it's shitty in ways that are like you can't even wrap your head around like.
Yeah, it's not shitty.
Just like, oh, the boom mic came into the frame there.
It's shitty where you're like, why is this green screened right now?
What the fuck is going on?
Yeah, but you like Johnny Depp in Tusk.
I loved him.
I was my mother and I were howling.
You're you're criminally insane.
And so is your mother.
Well, maybe I liked it because it was a movie I could watch with my folks and we all enjoyed it.
You know, and it's it's just disturbing enough.
Yeah, I swear to God, last Christmas Christmas, you gave me your heart.
And the very next day I threw it away.
All right.
Well, yeah, I mean, if you're going to cut me to the chase.
No, I mean, if it's the two nights or something before Christmas Eve,
it was my first night home, my mom, dad and I watched Tusk and then Bad Santa.
Oh, God, I love that.
I mean, I would never watch with my parents.
It was a raw night.
Yeah, I wanted to watch with my parents because I knew in my heart
my dad was going to laugh to the point of tears at them punching each other
in the nuts in the boxing ring.
Sure.
And I was like, if I can just get him on board till that part,
that's going to make his night.
Yeah.
And he liked it.
And then, sure enough, that part hit, man.
He was he couldn't even handle it, man.
When I think back on the on the the hardest I've left in my life.
Thanksgiving morning, I was living in New York and I hadn't spoken to anybody
for two months, probably.
I was like I would have become like Travis Bickle.
I was doing push ups.
I didn't eat.
I had no money.
I had no friends.
And two friends of mine came up from Missouri to visit me in New York.
And we went at like eight a .m.
to go watch the Macy's Day Parade and started drinking then and there
because we couldn't even get a view of it.
So we just started drinking.
We go into like a one p .m.
Bad Santa tripping and falling down the aisles so drunk.
And I swear each of us at different points in the movie blacked out completely,
like just went completely unconscious.
And I was like, I'm going to have to leave because I'm in pain.
And this movie is the funniest thing I've ever seen.
And I still feel that way.
The only other movies that made me laugh that hard were Anchorman in the theater
and Kingpin in the theater.
Now, I have a theory about that.
Kingpin is the hard Kingpin and the original Kings of Comedy are the two movies.
All the Bernie Mac said in that.
Jesus Christ.
I couldn't.
And then and and and Steve Harvey doing the Titanic band unplug cool in the gang,
unplugging the guitars on the Titanic.
I mean, I was fucking crying laughing.
Yeah, that's so rare and such a beautiful thing to happen.
But Kingpin, like in the slow motion comb over scenes at the end or whatever,
I was like, I am going to have to see this at a different time.
I'm going to have to collect myself and come back
because I was rolling onto the floor like an animal.
And I don't even laugh very much.
I'm a very even keeled person.
But once in a while, something will hit me.
And I'm like, I don't know that I'm going to survive this.
That's how my dad gets.
That's how we got during that nut punching scene in Bad Santa.
The part in the part in Kingpin, I was I remember going to see it so high with my friends.
Oh, what a dream.
We were so high.
And we were I had not seen marijuana when I when I went to see Kingpin.
And we were like, let's just go see this Kingpin movie.
Like, maybe it'll be funny.
It didn't nobody thought it was going to be funny
because it was like the weirdest cast.
And it was about bowling.
Like, you know, it was written for.
Yes, Chris Farley playing Randy Quaid.
Yes.
And then he died.
Yeah, it was written for Michael Keaton playing Woody Harrelson
and Jim Carrey in the Bill Murray role.
I mean, and then it got delayed so long that we got this cast.
And if you had told me, hey, we got three of your favorite actors of all time,
Farley, Carrey, Keaton.
And now we're doing to me at that time, I would have been like,
that's the ultimate poor man's version.
Right.
I kind of like Woody Harrelson.
I kind of like Randy Quaid.
And of course, Bill Murray is the best.
Right.
But I was like, this isn't going to be great.
And it blew me away.
That's yeah, it was it was in that weird interim period for Bill Murray
where he the last thing it done was like the man who knew too little
and the elephant movie larger than life.
Yeah, bad spot space jam.
Yeah.
So for me, Bill Murray has never been funnier than in Kingpin.
He deserved an Oscar nomination.
And apparently he every day would read the script,
rip it up and throw it on the floor.
And every line in the movie, every word of the movie,
from what I've heard, was made up.
He when he goes running out of the potato bar.
Yes.
And he does that like hop on one foot and trips and falls or whatever.
She's like, he's so funny in that movie that everything he says is like.
Well, mind blowing.
We were in line.
We were in line for the movie again.
High as hell.
And I turned to my friend and I go, I go, why are we seeing this man?
This isn't going to be good.
And even following Dumb and Dumber, you were Dumb and Dumber.
I didn't know it was the same guys.
And I will confess this.
I didn't like Dumb and Dumber that much.
I think it's funny.
But when I saw it, I kind of equated it to like, you know, like dirty work,
like one of those movies.
I was like, it's funny, but I don't love it.
You know, like I was when I came out.
Dumb and Dumber when I was 13, Dumb and Dumber came out.
So that was it hit me on a really sweet spot.
18 when that came out.
Yeah, that's maybe a little so.
So anyway, I saw.
So we're seeing when I said, why are we seeing this movie?
It's not going to be good.
And my friend said, I forgot to tell you, my mom saw it today.
All right.
She said it's the dirtiest movie she's ever seen in her life.
And then I was like, well, now we're getting somewhere.
And it's PG -13.
It's no, it's R.
No, no, it's R.
Joe, it's PG -13.
There is no way they have since released like an unrated DVD version.
I know for a fact, Kingpin was PG -13.
Otherwise, it wouldn't have been allowed to see it.
All right.
Fair enough.
It is.
And they they get away with a whole lot of shit in that movie that I can't really believe.
But it's an amazing movie.
I was sold from the minute.
Woody Harrelson walks in in the opening sequence.
Actually, I was sold from the minute of the dad
whistling and going sweeter than you who and when Woody Harrelson pizza, right?
Grabbing the pizza and then doing the split and making the ball stop and roll.
Yeah, I was like, this movie is going to be amazing, I think.
And then the hardest I laughed in the whole movie was Bill Murray saying,
that's that's total bullshit.
I pulled out of her way early.
Yeah.
And I was like, I can't fucking believe that this is a movie that I'm watching.
It's just it was it's a fearless movie.
And then the funniest like everything is the funny,
like the funniest drink order ever in a movie.
He goes, the bartender comes over, he goes, Tankeray and Tab Sweets and keep them coming.
I got a long drive ahead of me.
Right, right, right.
Tankeray and Tab.
Right, right.
It's disgusting.
Gin and like like off brand Coke.
And then the asshole in the bar at the end orders the soda and he goes,
Hey, sport Coca Cola.
It's the second greatest drink order of all time.
Yeah.
He tells, you know, when he tells what he has to eat the food outside in the parking lot,
when he tells the women he's not I'm not not you, you.
Yeah.
Why don't you go wash that perfume off and come back to the table?
I did that at a show the other night and the girl did not think it was funny.
No, it's not something you could get away with in day to day life.
I said, look at this girl.
You are so hot.
Yeah.
And the girl next to her was like, oh, whatever.
And I go, not you.
And she was also very pretty.
And I immediately was like, I'm just kidding.
I swear.
I'm just I'm just saying that to be funny.
Right.
And then eventually I got her back on my side, but it took a minute.
Okay.
Back to Children of the Corn.
Horton's wearing some Seinfeld jeans.
It's walking through a crosswalk.
There's a scythe in play.
Yes.
And this whole town does look like the movie that the whole opening
the movie Kingpin takes place in.
It really does.
Scranton P .A. I'm from not far from there.
That's where the office series takes place.
This the quality of this movie like I believe that it was made for under a million dollars.
It looks terrible, doesn't it?
I mean, I don't think it looks terrible.
I mean, it's from 1982 or something.
I think it's like 84.
But if you compare this to the Terminator even, which was released in the same year.
Terminator looks not great if you watch a non remastered version of it.
You know, you just kind of get that first like DVD release of it.
Yeah, it doesn't look fantastic.
And, you know, the special effects are a lot more obvious than you than you recall.
Sure.
But it's, you know, of course, it's a little better than this.
I have a bit of a slight gas thing there, Pat.
I'm sorry.
All right.
Sorry.
Look at that Jesus picture.
That's scary.
For those of you that don't have the visual, it's Jesus with a blue face and big black eyes.
That's very creepy.
The kids did it to the picture of Jesus.
Do Horton and Hamilton return or are they killed or what?
I can't remember, man.
I've only seen this.
Oh, no.
And the sequels.
No, the sequels are as far as I know, unrelated.
But the sequels have anybody in them?
Like sometimes in a horror movie franchise, it's like like the whatever that one Texas
Chainsaw Massacre where they have McConaughey and Zellweger in it.
Not that I know of.
These were all direct to video because that's how long ago they came out.
Yeah.
I mean, oh, look at this.
Charlize Theron's in part three.
I'm sorry.
No shit.
Didn't know that takes the old top off.
I mean, she wasn't against it for many years.
Early horror movies are a great way to find your your big star.
This new children of the corn for Naomi Watts and Karen Black.
No shit.
I bet they do get naked.
I mean, Charlize is naked throughout Devil's Advocate.
Just a really special way.
Oh, I said the guy's name wrong.
I got my characters mixed up.
The Doug Benson kid is in Malachi.
He's Isaac.
OK, because he comes back in Children of the Corn.
666.
OK, and that was the same actor.
Yeah, same actor who had gone away.
Very interesting.
His name is John Franklin.
He's fifty six now, but he had he has.
How can that be?
Because he has a growth hormone deficiency.
Yeah, but he but he's he's almost five feet tall.
But very interesting guy left acting.
And when it became like an English teacher.
OK, and like.
This is his quote after the events of 9 11,
I saw the shallowness of showbiz and felt a great desire to leave a great
a greater legacy than just being cousin it.
I guess he played cousin in the Addams Family.
In the movie?
Yeah.
Teaching the hair thing.
And his face wasn't even shown.
No, I love both of those movies.
I think they're great.
I never saw them.
And absolutely values is even is like way funnier than the first one.
And I think he's married to a man.
I think he's.
If I remember correctly.
OK, I think that's the case for him.
Anyway, mazel mazel.
So here are the sequel titles of Children of the Corn, which.
Again, I own part two.
I've never watched it.
It's called The Final Sacrifice right out of the gate with the final.
Yeah, you never say the final if you're if you're doing a sequel.
No, it's not going to be Children of the Corn three.
Ready for this urban harvest?
Oh, boy.
Children of the Corn for the gathering.
They mailed that one in.
I don't like that one.
Children of the four five back on the horse with fields of terror.
All right.
Was that coming after field dreams?
Ninety eight.
It's quite some time after.
Yeah.
Children of the Corn six six six Isaac's return.
And they and they brought back the realizing.
Yes.
So now you're telling me when you say he has a growth home,
are you talking he's like Simon Birch?
Like he looks like he's twenty and he's fifty five.
No, I mean, if you see a picture of him, he looks he just looks like a small
guy in his fifties.
OK, it's not like a Dabney Coleman thing where you can't tell if he's a kid or not.
I mean, Gary Coleman.
Sorry, sorry, Dabney Coleman.
Look like he's been 60 years old from the first day I ever saw.
But wouldn't it be a hoot if we'd replaced Dabney Coleman with Gary
Coleman and all of his famous movies?
Let's get Mad TV back on the air for that.
Uh, I can actually Isaac looking at him right now.
He looks like he's 50.
Yeah, he's probably like 20 years old there, seriously.
Like like Webster also, Emanuel Lewis.
But not quite as young looking.
Yeah, so got an old man.
He looks like an old Irish guy.
He looks like a small guy.
He looks like basically like the right age and every guy who's 50 in my family.
Yeah, there you go.
Here we go back with the the redheaded kid again.
Are they sacrificing Linda here?
I don't know.
They got her on some kind of corn cross or something.
This movie also reminds me of The Wicker Man a little bit.
Yeah, I've seen both versions.
Now, there's another I didn't hate the Nicholas Cage version of The Wicker Man.
No, I mean, I own the original.
I admire I like a million percent prefer an insane movie
to a boring movie.
Sure.
So the movies that often get like put on a pedestal as being like the worst movies ever.
I completely disagree because they're insane
and there's some inspiration and excitement behind them.
Sure.
To me, just a boring piece of shit movie is always going to be worse.
Like I'm checking my watch a bunch.
The Wicker Man, I'm like, I don't know what the hell I'm watching,
but I watched it till the end.
I wasn't bored.
The original one is nuts.
It is not.
It's a musical.
They do songs.
Yeah.
No, I love the original.
And there's all kinds of tit and everything.
Sure.
We got two more Children of the Corn sequels here.
You got Children of the Corn.
They really male known these last two.
Revelation.
Come on, guys.
And Children of the Corn Genesis, which takes away from Terminator Genesis for me.
Billy Drago started in that one.
Oh, wow.
Who was in Pale Rider.
Oh, wait, I thought you meant the guy who played Ivan Drago.
No, he played in Pale Rider and he was in The Untouchable.
Who did he play in The Untouchables?
I like Pale Rider and I like The Untouchable.
Oh, he's Frank Nitti in The Untouchables.
Greatest scene in the whole movie.
Yeah, I agree.
You know, your friend died screaming like a pig.
Yeah.
What's that?
I said, your friend.
He died screaming like a stuck Irish pig.
You remember that when I beat the rep.
Yeah.
David Mamet.
Untouchable.
Throws him off the roof.
Did he sound anything like that?
Yeah.
My friend Aaron Wexler used to always say in college.
Brian De Palma and David Mamet achieved the impossible task
of making Kevin Kozner sound tough.
Yeah.
Oh, he sounds like a hard ass when he does that.
Yeah, absolutely.
Yeah.
Great.
I love the cause.
Maybe I shouldn't call him that.
I don't want him to get mixed up with Cosby.
Wait, who are you?
You're saying Kozner, sure.
Yeah, I always like Kozner.
I love him.
He's just like he shows up.
You know what you're going to get.
You know what his best movie is to me?
An underrated movie for all you listeners out there
is a Clint Eastwood movie called A Perfect World.
Okay.
That Clint directed and is also starring in.
It's Clint Eastwood, Kevin Kozner, Laura Dern.
For some reason, nobody's seen this thing.
I only saw it because Mrs. Doubtfire was sold out in 1993.
And I was like, God damn it.
I have to see A Perfect World.
So let me get this straight.
You purposefully went to see Mrs. Doubtfire?
Yeah.
At age 13, you're goddamn right.
Mrs. Doubtfire is a great movie.
Still.
Oh, boy.
You're going to speak ill of Robin Williams now.
Listen, may he rest in peace.
I'm sad he's gone.
But I mean, a guy passing the previous work
really gets a whole refacing, doesn't it?
I mean, Mrs. Doubtfire is -
I love Mrs. Doubtfire.
That was like one of the movies that he had to break that schmaltz mold from.
It was like Mrs. Doubtfire, Bicentennial Man.
Joe, Bicentennial Man is an F.
And I would consider it among the worst movies of all time of movie history.
I think without fail, most people listening right now
at least will say Mrs. Doubtfire is a pretty entertaining movie.
Hey, we missed that kid cutting his chest open.
I thought it was -
People back me up.
This chick's 42 years old.
How was she getting passed off as a kid?
She doesn't even have a growth disorder.
People back me up.
This is a call -in show, right?
You all love Mrs. Doubtfire.
I'm going to tweet it and see who writes back.
Speaking of which, we've got questions.
Okay, good.
Bicentennial Man is as bad as it gets and Flubber might be worse.
Here we go.
I love questions.
What do you got?
Let's see here.
First one.
I like the sound of this.
Thank you, Danny 35.
That's at Danny Beat with two E's, 32.
Rob Larrick writes, Isaac looked like a creepy puppet.
Malachi was a toothy ginger.
True.
Who was uglier?
Malachi.
I feel bad saying that.
He's fine with it.
Malachi was uglier.
There's your answer, Rob Larrich.
At Rob Larrich.
Here's from at Clive Gulch.
Traumatize my wife as a child.
You won't watch it now.
Is it that scary?
No.
Yeah, I mean, it doesn't seem to be scary at all.
Like, it's a little freaky.
Look, anybody saying the words to me, I'm under the command of he who walks behind the rose.
I'd be freaked out.
Yeah.
I mean, what scared me when I was a kid were the boxes to horror movies in the video store.
And also like kids movies that were to me scarier than this.
Return to Oz.
I own it.
It still freaks me out.
Return to Oz is scarier than a majority of horror movies.
Hey, let's put Dorothy in an insane asylum.
That's the normal part of the movie.
And they elect and they do electroshock treatment.
Yeah.
How much does the corn factor into the plot?
Could the film exist without the corn?
Uh, that's from Ken Hanley.
His handle is at movie guy.
I guess that Ken Hanley is our man over at Fangoria.
Okay, Ken.
I got to say, corn's factoring in pretty heavily and you're going to want that corn.
I mean, you're going to want that corn.
They've dressed the whole town like in corn husks, like it's Thanksgiving.
Yeah.
So, uh, I agree heavily.
The only child actors this from another one from Rob, Rob Larch or Lark.
Another are the only child actors who didn't grow up to be complete degenerates as adults.
What is that?
How is it possible that the child actors are the only child actors who didn't grow up to be
complete degenerates as adults?
And that's true.
We're just talking about how this guy leads a very healthy, happy life.
Yeah.
Uh, I assume children of the corn was just a drug free set.
You know, they kept Michael Jackson offset.
They kept drugs offset and these kids grew up to be healthy and happy.
Yeah, I just, I, well, I think a big part of it is that a lot of these kids didn't work
again after this.
Yeah, that's true.
The Malachi kid did and, and, and the Isaac kid did.
Yeah.
But nobody else.
I mean, and also when you're, when you're under the good influence of a Peter Horton
and a Linda Hamilton.
Yeah, you feel like they're, they had good heads in their shoulders.
These are nice people.
Yeah, it's not like, uh, it's not like Downey Jr. was showing up.
Like a 1984 Downey Jr. was coming to set with a vial of Coke.
I would dare to say too, that with a film like this, where you have to have
miners acting in violent and murderous fashions, there's probably a little extra
care on set by the adults to make sure that things are pretty light and bubbly off camera.
That's something I've always wondered about.
Like, for example, like there's a movie called mysterious skin.
You ever see that with Joseph Horton?
Love it.
No, it's a Greg Iraqi movie.
It's NC 17.
It's I will never forget it as long as I live.
I'll never watch it again, but it was a masterpiece.
Uh, what's it about?
It's about child molestation.
Oh God.
And there's really graphic shit.
Did you say that already?
No, we were talking about child molestation earlier for some reason.
We were and Joseph Gordon love it.
But you know, like, you know, of course, okay, so he was of age, but in a movie about
molestation or a movie about something happiness where the kid is hurt that his dad didn't
try to molest.
I refuse to watch the film.
I refuse to watch it.
Well, happiness is also a masterpiece, but it's very disturbing.
It's not a masterpiece.
It's the to me, it's the depths of depravity.
These are the only two times I've ever used the word masterpiece.
So I don't know why I'm using.
I don't need to see Philip Seymour Hoffman's come hit a wall.
So have you seen the movie?
I got as far as his come hitting the wall.
Sure.
And then him saying, but you'll watch porn.
But here's the thing.
This is come against a wall used for art.
Here's the thing.
It's one of those things where it's like, I get it.
It's depraved.
He's talking to the woman on the phone.
Then you find out he's a pervert jerking off to her.
Okay, that's disturbing.
Then he comes and you have to see him come.
That's disturbing.
Then you see his actual semen hit the wall.
Then he puts a postcard over it to cover it.
I'm just like, fuck off, man.
And then we're going to get to pedophiles in a minute.
I'm good.
I think it's a great movie.
What's the point of it?
I'm saying.
Give me the point of the movie.
The point of happiness?
It's just everything Todd Salins does is like that.
Oh, sure.
I'm not vouching for the man's entire catalog.
Right.
I certainly have liked most of them.
But he's a provocateur here.
But for what reason?
It's like a comic get on stage and being like, yeah,
I was in Kmart and fucking the clerk in her ass.
It's like, okay, dude, you know, unless you were.
And then it's a funny story.
Well, then, you know, it's just a nice time.
What I'm saying is like that kid who has to play these long,
intense scenes where he's jealous that his father didn't try to molest him.
How do these kids, what do they say to the kids?
How involved are the parents?
How are they making sure that this kid doesn't grow up completely?
Fucked up and destroyed.
How do they do it?
I think that they probably don't show the kid the entire scene.
Yeah.
They don't fully explain what it's about.
They potentially have substitute dialogue on the other side
of the character or camera with the other actor.
Maybe, you know, it's like if I'm a parent of a child actor,
I know these parents are often troubled themselves.
But how do you just let your kid do it?
Like with because there's a risk.
Of your kid growing up with the same trauma of it actually happening,
not on the same level, but like, you know,
unless they shoot them in such a tactful, careful way as to.
Put them in any just disgusting.
The kid asks his father, would you ever fuck me?
His father replies, no, I jerk off instead.
I mean, it's just gross, man.
Yeah, there's no way to make that kid.
There's no way to make that scene fine for that kid.
The kid has to say that line.
Yeah, I just I just I don't I don't get what the point of that is.
I just don't get I understand the point of making a movie
that deals with the subject of child molestation or pedophilia.
I get why a movie like The Woodsman exists,
but something like this where it's like nobody's redeeming.
The kid wants the dad to fuck him.
The dad wants to fuck the kid.
They talk about it, too.
And then the dad tells the kid he jerks off to him.
It's just like, well, I don't need this.
It's something to me.
It's like watching a beheading video.
It's like, I don't need to see this.
Well, they did that exact same scene, basically, on Always Sonny,
where he was jealous that the priest didn't try to molest.
Well, they needed the basketball coach.
It was supposed to be a priest, Mr. Bellamy.
But that's if it's played for comedic, then it's funny.
You know what?
Then it's funny.
And I haven't seen it in a long time,
but that is played for extremely bleak black comedy
because I remember people laughing when I saw that movie.
The movie is a black comedy like it's a comedy.
All right. Well, that gives it a little more slack in my book.
I'd like to watch it again to see if I change my opinion.
I'd like you to watch it again.
All right.
And think about you backing a film like this.
Not backing it.
I'm not saying I love what happens in it or anything.
Big fan of Dylan Baker.
Big fan of Lara Flynn Boyle.
Yeah, for sure.
Big fan of Ben Gazara.
Yeah, it's a great big fan of Philip C.
Philip Seam.
John Loves.
The opening scene where he's getting dumped is such a fantastic scene.
I'd watch it again.
It's Molly Shannon.
Yeah, she's great in it.
I also love life during wartime, the unofficial sequel to happen.
Did you like Welcome to the Dollhouse?
I never saw it, but that's a real rough one, too.
Or it's a comedy as well.
Yeah, I just didn't care that much about it.
But I mean, I think that like to me is like when he's
he, you know, I felt like he walked a better line,
at least from what I know about that movie.
What happened?
Just cut her face.
I thought she was being sacrificed.
Pat, I mean, at this point, this movie could literally be about corn,
and I wouldn't even know.
Linda Hamilton.
I'm not going to say her name exactly like a girl that I know.
I just realized.
Now, have you seen the sequel to happiness called Life During Wartime?
I absolutely have.
And I like that a lot, too.
Now, is it as disturbing?
Everybody's played by different people.
It's not as disturbing.
Storytelling was very disturbing, which is his follow up to happen.
What is the now what is the pedophile, for instance, doing in the sequel?
I don't really remember and I don't know that he's in it.
I don't think he's in it.
What's the Philip Seymour Hoffman character doing here?
You're barking up the wrong tree.
I'd have to watch it again.
I mean, you just you said this guy's your favorite filmmaker.
I thought I definitely didn't say maybe you know these.
I have my buddies, John and Hayden, John Hurwitz, Hayden Schlossberg,
who did the Harold and Kumar movies, went to school.
I might be wrong.
They went to high school with Todd Sahlins's brother,
who is on the FBI's most wanted list for trying to blow up a building.
He is.
I may be wrong about the details.
I would I would make sure you're right about those details
before you say something like that.
So just so you know, you might want to look it up.
But I believe Todd Sahlins's brother is on the FBI most wanted list
for trying to blow up a building.
And then he went to school.
I can look that up right now.
I mean, we're here.
Yeah, I can.
I can't.
Now, this is when they turn on Isaac.
Why are they sacrificing their leader?
Because he got power hungry.
And now kind now is the guy saying, hey, I'm there.
I'm the I'm the guy you should be listening to, not him.
OK, is there any sexual elements of this, like a weird, creepy Amish
Mormon type, we're all banging kind of thing or no?
I think, you know, without them saying that, I think the idea is,
is that they are going to start the new.
Yeah. You know, with everything being rebooted, how have they not
remade Children of the Corn?
Are they remaking children because they keep making these fucking sequels.
There was a remake on sci fi, which I would like to see.
I think this is a very remakeable film.
You know, it's not a lot of special effects.
It's it's very character driven.
You know, I have cemeteries do for remake, too.
And that was a great adaptation.
I love Pet Sematary.
I think they are actually remaking it or they've been talking about it for a while.
It's time.
I'm ready.
I also love the adaptation.
I can't wait for the remake it.
I lost a year of my life to the CBS miniseries.
I couldn't go to the show.
I couldn't take a shower.
I scared the shit out of me.
Do anything with my life.
We all float down here.
Yeah, it's it's scared the shit out of me.
Now, I was so excited because they had the true detective guy, the guy who directed
season one doing the remake.
And I was like, we're in great hands.
This is going to be fantastic.
Right now, he walked off due to creative differences and they have the guy who did
Mama, which is like an average at best horror movie.
Yeah, I didn't care for mama.
It's not going to be good.
I didn't care for mama.
The kid playing the clown looks pretty freaky.
No, it's the kid from We're the Millers.
It is.
You see where the millers.
Yeah, Moses is an all right comedy, but like that kid should not be playing the cloud
unless he had an amazing audition and they're going in a different way.
Wait, it's that same kid.
It's the kid who's like dick gets bit and blows up and all that.
Yeah.
Well, I got to say, oh, yeah, that is him.
I didn't realize that.
That shouldn't that shouldn't be the he kind of looks like a young Tim Curry to me.
That's where I kind of was happy about it.
I just feel like they could have done much better.
I don't know.
And unless the kid's a man, amazing actor, he shouldn't write.
He's also young.
It's like, why is Pennywise the Clown 21?
Yeah, I don't get that.
That's kind of stupid.
Also, will they do that?
The spider ship at the end of this that destroyed the miniseries is how does the book end?
I don't remember.
And I read it when I was about 10 years old and I don't remember.
You read that book and you weren't scared.
The book is way scarier than the movie.
The book is scary.
For me, it's hard to get scared by a book.
But for some reason, the movies always take me in a different place.
Man, that Jesus.
Holy shit.
That was scary.
How much did that scare you?
For those of you at home, my dog just opened the door to the office and walked in.
The dog wasn't visible, so it just looked like a door opening.
And I thought a person's coming into the room.
It was honestly very scary.
Here comes he who walks behind the rose.
As you can see, there was clearly a budgetary restraint here.
Well, they're using the tremors bit with the ground going up.
We just watched Tremors a few weeks ago.
Tremors is one of my favorite horror movies.
You seemed oddly unimpressed by it.
I wasn't impressed.
I liked it, but I like Tremors in the same way.
I like Flatliners or the Lost Boys.
You know, it's a fun movie.
It's not scary.
Sure.
It's just a fun movie.
A big part of it is when you see things.
Oh, my God.
This is the worst special effects I've ever seen.
That is bad.
Oh, my God.
That's terrible.
She is scream.
Listen to Isaac scream.
Did you hear that?
I heard it.
Look, in my life, I have not seen special effects that bad.
And in a major motion picture.
Yeah, I mean, I did just I did an injustice to the video
by saying this looks like an unbelievable.
Yeah, that looked terrible.
Now, Isaac is gone.
I don't think I'm done talking about those special effects, Joe.
That pixelated blob just ate Isaac.
That's very upset.
Look like they did it on an Atari.
Yeah, it looked bad.
Why don't these other kids look evil?
A couple of them look evil, I guess.
Now, here goes Peter, given the kids a speech.
And he's telling them that they're they're on the wrong track now.
Is there no sexual element to this cult?
Pete, I mean, Pat, you keep asking me this question.
Trying to recreate.
Tell me your favorite movie's happiness.
What do you what do you would try to repopulate the human race?
Or what is their goal?
I think so.
I don't remember.
That's going to require some sex.
You've asked me six times.
I can't remember it.
I'm not paying attention.
People are all of age.
They're they're not supposed to be, though.
There's children of the court.
Look at that guy.
The guy looks like he's 33 years old.
Oh, now, Malik, I just tackled Peter Horton for giving a speech about how they shouldn't
be listening with an ear of corn.
Now, here is the plot of Children of the Corn 666.
This is how Isaac comes back.
You ready?
Yep.
Because he just was eaten by a pixelated Atari blob.
He's gone.
Honestly, the worst I've ever seen.
Special effects.
Hannah, the firstborn child of the original Gatlin cult.
So, yes, they had sex.
How do you happy?
We found out now God visits the town of Cat Gatlin to find her real mother on the way.
She picks up a street preacher by the name of Zachariah, whose car broke down.
He tells her about her name and then vanishes after crashing into a cornfield.
A lady sheriff that's described that way.
A lady sheriff, a good title for like a Kristen Wiig movie.
Well, this is McCarthy.
Yeah, finds her takes handle to Hannah to a hospital in town.
Once there, she finds out as Isaac was not killed by he who walks behind the roads,
but instead went into a coma.
That's not true at all.
We just saw him evaporated the flames.
Yeah.
Did you hear that?
Oh, there is Isaac.
OK, he's not dead.
Well, now Isaac has.
That might have scared me as a kid.
A very deep voice, and he has now been possessed.
By the corn devils?
By the he who walks behind the rose pet.
Who's he walked behind the road?
The tremors thing.
Oh, my God.
I mean, you're really not following it.
I haven't heard any dialogue.
We've been bantering.
I've been explaining this to you the whole time.
We've been skillfully bantering.
Now, this part's scary.
Yeah, no, this would have scared me.
I forgot about this part.
I thought Isaac just disappeared into the blob.
But no.
OK, he's alive and he'll be back in 666 in just 17 short years.
Do you like Christine?
I never saw Christine.
I never I just didn't give a shit.
I was like, I don't care about a car chasing people.
Yeah, it's pretty dumb, but I like the book and the movie.
Like Maximum Overdrive, though.
Is a great adaptation.
You know what?
That's way up the list for and it's not a horror adaptation,
but that's way up the list for best Stephen King movies, in my opinion.
Same with Shawshank and Green Mile.
They're not horror, but they're both fantastic, I thought.
Is the Green Mile good?
Green Mile is great.
Yeah, there really is.
My mom loves it.
It's overshadowed by Shawshank, which is kind of a perfect movie,
but Green Mile is great.
Well, Frank Darabelle is amazing in it.
Frank Darabelle behind all three.
Yeah, that's right.
That is true.
Green Mile and Shawshank.
Yeah, I heard Rockwell's.
Rockwell was a bad guy, right?
Yeah, no, it's it's a dream for character actors that movie.
There's like eight great weirdo parts in it.
You never see Green Mile.
No, I never saw it.
I just come over this week.
Watch the Green Mile.
All right.
This kid.
What is this kid from?
We know this kid from something.
Let me see the kid that's going to help him solve the whole thing right now.
I just realized he's a he's a young actor.
That grew up to do other stuff.
All right.
I just just need one cut to this kid.
One cut.
I don't know who that is.
That kid.
What is that kid from?
That is the kid from.
God damn it.
I got to look this up now.
His name is Joe.
How about that?
You think he's like a still a working actor?
That kid was in other stuff as a kid.
I know that much.
OK, I got to find him, but he's telling him how to.
He's telling him how to stop.
To stop the demon that walks behind the Rose.
They got to burn the field.
What else would it be?
Horton's selling this baby.
He is.
He's into it.
How did he never have a leading role after this?
He probably did.
Like 30 something.
Oh, you're right.
It was 30 something a good show.
My parents loved it.
I was always like, I know the Golden Girls make a lot of jokes about it as we learned last night.
They do.
One of my favorite Golden Girls lines ever.
Dorothy, are you upset that you can't find a job?
No, Rose, I'm upset because they canceled 30 something.
I stumbled on it, but with yeah, she delivered it impeccably.
She always did.
I can't find this kid on here.
Hold on a second.
I got to go to the IMDb.
His name is Joe in the movie.
That shot of Linda Hamilton reacting to the danger was not convincing at all.
Well, you know, I mean, I think at this part, she's at this point.
She's over.
Oh, Joe, not Joe, Joe.
Robbie Kiger of the doors was also in Monster Squad.
Crazy like a fox.
I love Monster Squad.
I don't know what crazy like a fox is.
Welcome home, Roxy Carmichael.
Yep.
Used to watch that all the time.
Was also in still crazy like a fox.
A sequel.
Sequel.
One day at a time.
I think that's what I'm remembering.
Happy endings.
What the hell is that?
The show.
Some some movie called Happy Ending.
TV show is hilarious.
I don't know what the movie is.
I'm remembering them from from one day at a time.
Mickey and Maude.
You remember that film?
Dudley Moore.
Yep.
Yeah, I do.
Yeah, I miss Dudley.
Yeah, dad.
What do you die?
Have an aneurysm or something?
He was like 55.
It's some weird immune thing.
Not but it was not not HIV.
It was like some I don't know some weird.
OK, is the corn taking Peter Horton?
The corn is now attacking Peter.
I didn't know the corn was a alive presence.
You know, neither did I.
Yeah.
It's kind of like you ever see the ruins.
That was a cool horror movie.
I own it on DVD.
Haven't opened it yet.
The ruins is great.
Yeah, I got it one day on the when I was working on the Warner Brothers Brothers lot.
They had that gift shop over there.
That's where I work.
I buy stuff there all the time.
Yeah, you get discount DVDs.
Yeah.
I bought the blu ray one day and I just never watched it yet.
The ruins is great and it has some just fantastic nudity.
Really?
Yeah.
How do you still enjoy nudity in a film?
Absolutely.
It really means a lot to me.
Really?
Yeah.
Do you think any female will listen to this podcast?
Oh, yeah.
OK, great.
Yeah, I think I think there's probably a lot of female horror fans out there that are big
fangoria fans and stuff.
Yeah, I guess I guess you're right.
I've I don't encounter many, many ladies who are into horror.
But of course, they're out there.
There's a whole goth subculture.
Speaking of fans.
Yeah, let's get back to the Twitter.
See if anybody else has written us any questions.
We didn't even have to say it because then now if there's not, we're going to look pathetic.
That's our first one.
You know, we're just trying to trying to reach the people.
Well, no, here's a guy with a question for you.
Is Patrick the guy from the Scream Queens podcast?
No, I don't know what that is.
That guy's probably great.
It's a podcast with a guy.
Is his name Patrick Walsh?
No idea.
OK, doesn't say here, but it's a horror podcast.
Here's another question.
The fuck is Malachi up to these days anyway?
Well, we already talked about that.
Oh, not Malachi.
We talked about Isaac.
Let's see.
Malachi is probably still acting.
I know.
I bet you he's been in.
Hold on.
Let's see here.
Children of the Corn again.
Back to the IMDb.
I should just leave this open.
Anybody with that memorable look is always going to have acting.
Courtney Gaines, handsome man in real life.
Look at that guy.
Yeah, he doesn't look bad.
Can't Buy Me Love, Sweet Home Alabama, Back to the Fuge.
What was he in Back to the Fuge?
I think he's like one of like Biff's friends or something.
Look at this.
Eight projects on the docket.
Hey, congratulations.
Texas Rising.
If you can be a working actor for like 35 years, good for you.
He's been on the middle.
Look at this special effect.
The fire?
Yeah, like a weird brain.
No, there's like a cloud.
I just wish he who.
Look at that.
It looks kind of cool.
It looks better than the thing that the kid.
It looks like a brain cloud.
I just said that.
Oh, you did.
Oh, they should rain.
I wish he who walked by in the rose was more.
Yeah, maybe he's more prominent than the others.
I guess that looks OK.
I like the way that looked.
That looked like an old 80s Tron style effect.
Now they just torch the cornfield, the fire spreading.
They're standing and watching for some reason.
You think they'd make a run for it.
There they go.
What blew up that he who walks behind the rose?
Oh, he's made of gas.
I mean, look, I think at this point they were like,
just figure out how to end this fucking thing, please.
Get us out of here.
Just blow the thing up so we can leave.
But as we already know, if you blow up in this movie,
it doesn't mean you're dead.
Do you remember?
Does this is this faithful to the short story or not?
I never read the short story yet.
OK, I have the book.
I still read the short story.
Trying to read the ones I hadn't read yet.
All right.
Nothing better before bed than reading a Stephen King short story.
Sure.
I highly recommend Grandma, which is from the what's the skeleton key?
Is that the one with the monkey on the front?
Skeleton key.
Skeleton crew, excuse me.
Did you ever see Monkey Shines?
I never saw that because the box terrified me.
Yeah, I see Monkey Shines.
Is that based on a Stephen King?
George Romero?
Yeah, absolutely.
Is it?
Yeah.
Yeah, Monkey Shines is good.
But it's I mean, it's just about an evil monkey.
The box is scarier than the movie.
Do they use animatronics or an actual monkey?
No, they just use a real monkey.
You know, it's not like it's like it's like one of those little shoulder monkeys.
It's crazy.
Now, whenever I go back, I'm like, if I were to watch Monkey Shines tonight,
I'd be like the fact that this box scared me for so many years of my life.
And this movie is, I have to imagine, not scary at all for an adult.
It's crazy.
It wasn't scary to a child either.
I saw it when I was a young boy.
It didn't freak me out.
Stuff like that didn't freak me out.
You know, Deadly Friend didn't freak me out.
Anything where it was like a crazy basketball knocks the head off.
Yeah, she's like the robot girlfriend or whatever.
Anything with a robot, anything with like an animal going nuts.
I just never was freaked out by that stuff.
Sure.
It was always like supernatural stuff freaked me out.
The devil, demons, some kind of like deformed monster thing.
Sure.
That's what always would freak me out.
You like Kujo?
No, don't care.
Did you see it?
Rabbit dog.
I don't care.
But Joe, you're an obsessive horror fan who has like the most obscure shit.
You never seen Kujo or Christine?
Don't care about either.
Just the two things are just named machine and crazy.
Now, if it was a man that turned into that dog, I'm in.
I don't care about a dog with rabies.
Dog going nuts is way scarier than a man turning into a dog.
I was never a big slasher guy.
I don't like things that can really happen.
It's just not that scary to me.
I like stuff that can't happen and that freaks me out more.
I can't explain it.
That's so weird because what can actually happen should scare you more.
Insidious will always scare me more than Wolf Creek without question.
I'm the exact opposite.
The 42 year old lady is still alive, by the way.
They just got in the car.
They thought all was good.
She's about to cut off Pete's head.
He blocked it.
I've done a complete 180 and I'm very attracted to Linda Hamilton by the end of this movie.
I want to have sex with her like nothing else and I love this movie.
I think it'd be slow and it'd be tender and it'd be very passionate.
I love this movie now.
I've changed my tune.
Really?
We haven't even been paying attention to it.
I like that part where Isaac came back with the demon face.
Yeah.
Okay.
I like that brain cloud we think thing at the end.
All right.
I want to have sex with Linda.
Wow.
That was an abrupt ending.
He just knocked some kid's head.
He knocked some kid out by slamming her head with the car door.
This is not the final shot of a quality movie.
I'm telling you right now.
And then it just said the end.
Knocks a kid out with a door.
That's ridiculous.
It just says the end.
John Philbin, you think related to Reach?
I mean, I wouldn't be surprised in this town.
Look at this.
That was one of the weirdest, most abrupt end.
It's an actor named Dan Snook.
Great name.
Sure.
We're in the credits, folks.
You made it through children of the corn.
Here we go.
First time out.
I mean, I hope you guys enjoyed it.
I hope you're listening to it.
Hope you tell your friends.
I hope so, too.
I mean, any podcast.
I'm like, I don't understand why anybody would listen to this.
But they do.
People just like these things.
I listen to some.
I mean, a lot of it's, I think, driving to work.
I go on long walks.
I like to listen to a podcast here.
Just by yourself.
Just a long solo romantic walk kind of thing.
Yeah.
Sometimes I don't want to talk.
I want to listen to people talk.
OK.
Fair enough.
And that should be the name of your book.
That's a very long title.
But yeah, sure.
Sometimes I don't want to talk.
I just want to hear people talk.
Yeah.
Well, folks, thanks for tuning in.
This is We'll See You in Hell on the Fangoria Network.
We'll be back twice a month.
Yeah.
And we'll see you on the next one.
And of course, feel free to suggest movies for us to watch on Twitter.
We're trying to stick to movies that are on Netflix instant.
So you can watch them, too.
We figure a lot of people have that.
Everybody can watch it.
But please, if you know a movie we might not have seen,
if you know a classic you want to hear our take on,
if you'd rather hear us do more scene -specific commentary
as opposed to shooting the shit,
let us know what you think.
We're trying to figure this out, too.
I believe the man is correct.
Do just that.
You can find Pat at Patrick.
Go ahead.
What is it?
At ThePatrickWalsh on Twitter.
And I am at JoeDeRosaComedy on Twitter.
We'll see you next.
You'll hear us next time.
And we'll see you in hell.