if
a bonus. Yep, with a big old dick. Wow. Wow. Well, two, two big old decks. Um, I
say you're a big old dick. No, no, I would. I'm hearing a lot of talking in my headphones.
Uh, we're picking up some, um, like, yeah, I got no control over it. Like almost like a full volume
conversation. And then we're also going to be watching a movie. Once the movie starts, you
won't hear that. We're just picking up some, you know, like when a guitar amp picks up, uh,
interference. That's the word. Sure. Uh, Patty, you're ready to do this? Uh,
joy was born ready to do this, which was weird. I came out of the womb. And I was like,
I want to do a horror podcast about a movie that's coming out in 15 years. My parents were like,
whoa, this kid's smart. And then the doctor went, what happened to Goo Goo Gaga? It might
day you were lucky to get Goo Goo Gaga. Then he slapped my ass. They still do that. They still
slap a baby's ass when it's born. Uh, and why did they do it in the first place? I heard a doctor
did it last week and is being sued for harassment. Oh, why did you tell that doctor to do what he did?
Uh, well, let's start the movie. I mean, these, uh, commentary podcasts are endless. We are
giving them to you guys because we love you. We love you. And it's the craft this week. Guys,
listen, we're going to give you a chance to pick again. But, uh, oh, let, let me feel this one.
Go ahead and start the craft. So we're going to do it with a, uh, Netflix, you know,
it's going to be the standard one, two, three play where on Netflix, you're, you're at, uh,
one, forty one, oh, one is on the right side of the screen. That's literally the very beginning.
It hasn't played it all yet. So one, two, three, play. She's playing Columbia, try star pictures.
You think she looks like students ran in our netbending? A netbending. I've heard both. I think more like
a netbending, yes. I'm going all in netbending. And they must have gone out of business and come back
because I started seeing this lady again, uh, before Columbia trashed up pictures like Zathura.
I'm going in at betting a hundred percent. I agree. I like a netbending. Credits just came up.
There's a picture of a crystal ball in a candle where at one forty thirty, we,
thirty, one forty thirty right when I said that. All right, we'll get into the craft. But,
but folks, I thought, you know, last night, Joan, I like, well, what are we going to do a commentary on?
I go, I got an idea. We'll give the, we'll let the people decide. I put it on Facebook by midnight
tonight. Give me a movie streaming on Netflix. Obviously a horror movie, a movie that would fit
into the format of the horror show. Folks right off the bat, there's 15 people saying they want Jackie
Brown. Now, you know, I love Jackie Brown. We've talked about that movie so much on this podcast.
Um, I'm seeing good fellows. I'm seeing these aren't horror movies. A, no, um, but they were
streaming on Netflix. So congratulations there. Then for the next 10 minutes of reading, 150 movie
titles were presented. Not one of them streaming on Netflix. I was shocked. The one that got some
traction was the void. Joan, I have not seen the void and I want to watch it with respect. We'll do
it as an episode of the show. I have seen the void. Oh, okay. And I liked it and I'd love to do it
as a reviewer or a commentary. All right. We'll do that soon. I'm going to watch that. Um, and a few of
you get, you got it right. But I would say 90 % didn't. And it was shocking. And I just think you
should all be ashamed yourself. Um, that being said, we appreciate the enthusiasm. We do. Uh,
he for effort, he for effort. And I, you know, I'm looking, Joe and I were sitting down and I was going to
do a dream catcher, which is awful. It's a movie I saw on spring break in Panama City beach years
ago. And it involves Jason Lee shitting out a demon. Oh, um, but it's not a Kevin Smith movie. No,
that's exactly it should be. But Joe looks it up. He realizes it's like 220. We got a concert tonight.
We're recording a couple episodes. That's a long time. The chat. We just don't have the juice for it
sometimes. This is a nice hour 40. Uh, it was down, which is still 40 extra minutes. That's true.
Of pod. It's true. It was down to the craft and teeth that those both had a few, a little bit of
traction on, uh, we went with the craft. We've heard that this title come up a lot. I don't remember the
movie. I probably saw it when I was 15. I saw it. I feel like you must have. Now I, yeah, no,
you're right. I saw it when I maybe you were 14. I feel like I saw this when I was 16 or
top 17. Well, you don't have to see movies when they're in theaters. Oh, well, I thought maybe
you did. And my day they had a, you know, VHS rental system. Okay. So I saw it a few years later.
Okay. Well, I saw it in the theater with our dear friend, James Pinkstone. Sure. Uh, he talked
me into seeing it. He said it's a witch movie with Nev Campbell. I said, what have you lost your
mind? And he said, no, it's going to be good. I said, all right, because at that, at this time,
Nev Campbell wasn't really Nev Campbell yet. She was still just the, the girl that was on, um,
party of five. Yeah. So I was like, I don't want to go see some fucking Dawson's Creek thing. But
then, uh, but then I really, I really like the movie. I Dawson's Creek was not for me. It was
now he was into film Dawson Dawson. He wanted to be the next Steven Spielberg. Yeah. You know,
who else was in the film at one point? James Vanderbick. Uh, varsity blues, baby. I don't want
your life. varsity blues is a very entertaining movie. He's in my favorite, um,
uh, Brady Snellis adaptation rules of attraction. Yeah. You see how well I know you? I finished
your sentence. Thank you. Thank you. Uh, finish your sentences. Um, the, uh, that movie's awesome.
And he's awesome in it. I love attraction is unbelievably good. And your boy savages in it.
Savage. Savage. Savage is in it. Yeah. Um, and that Roger Avery who was just kind of a cast
aside by Tarantino for Pulp Fiction and Quick Pause. Why did you tell Quentin Tarantino to do what he did?
He co -wrote Pulp Fiction, one of the greatest screenplays ever. Then he makes an amazing movie,
rules of attraction. He makes a really good movie called Killing Zoe. And he's out of the business.
No, you know, he, he, he went to jail because he killed a man drunk driving. Oh,
well, that explains, we're, we're, we're some alleged, hold on, alleged, whatever you got to say legally.
I didn't know that. He was in some vehicular mishap where I believe he was drunk. Somebody was injured
and he like went to jail for it. Well, you know, who else has, uh, lots of people, Matt Broderick,
Ferris Bueller, killed someone with his car. He's still working. He was, he was like 18.
Rebecca Gayheart. She's still opening pictures. You seen her. You seen Gayheart?
Wait a minute, girl. Uh, Varsity Blue. Look at this lady. Rob and Toney, I like her.
Was she in sister of the traveling pants? I think that's right. But I don't know for sure.
And in sister of the travel pants, she's playing a woman five years younger than her character in this film.
Yeah. They came out four years before that movie did. That doesn't make any sense.
She might not be in sister of the travel. Pat, you're thinking of, uh, Alexis Bledel from the Gilmore Girls.
Oh, okay. Well, what happened to Toney over here? As always, we could look this up. We're probably not
going to Pat. I got a microphone in one hand at a tall jack and coke in the other.
Did I mix it too strongly? You mixed it beautifully. Just so you guys know, Pat and I have, uh,
a little table in front of us here with a, I don't know what the big bottles called.
That's the big one. That's your, uh, 1 .75 liters. 1 .75 libert bottle jack. I put ice into an ice bucket.
So we don't have to get up. Is that STP? No, no, it's one of the many ripoff. And they were a ripoff
themselves. What am I talking about? Breck and Maya are ladies and gentlemen, recently dated a friend
of mine, recently dated two friends of mine, but that's not your business. Uh, how, now how I mix
these drinks is I, uh, I poured Joe's jack and coke. Little ditty about jack and diet.
Then I poured the remainder of the coke into the 1 .75 liter bottle. And I'm just drinking from that.
And honestly, it's working for me. I feel good. Now, none of these girls are around anymore.
It even have camels not really around much. Like, but they're rebooting party of five with, uh,
with immigrants. Are they really? They're rebooting every show that's ever been made this season
on television. Wait, with immigrants. Why with immigrants? Um, I, I don't know there. I, that's
just what I saw. Party of five with immigrants. Wait, what was party of five about? Party of five was
about, uh, five children whose parents died in a car accident and then they kind of took care of them.
Oh, okay. Well, that makes sense. So it'd be like immigrate because with the whole Trump thing,
like the, oh, I think the parents get sent back. Okay. All right. What do I make sense?
They're also rebooting. Let me go through these and give me your, your brief thoughts. Murphy Brown.
I, same cast. I mean, they're all in their 70s. I, how old's that ball guy at this point?
He's got to be 75 years old. The, the role in my show that went to Joe Beth Williams, the mom from
Poltergeist. Yeah. I floated the name Candace Bergen. I needed an icy, uh, older woman.
And I floated the name. They were like, she's, she's, she's lost it. She's, she's old. She doesn't
know anymore. She can't remember lines. I don't know what, maybe this thing will never see the light of
day. But Jesus Christ, they're also redo as they're already have done Will and Grace. They're bringing
back Martin. Martin. ABC is redoing Martin. The one on ABC's not Fox. Correct. And it was on Fox.
Was it? All right. It was. The one I'm excited about is Rosanne. I think that's going to be great.
I don't know. Rosanne. But I thought you'd be excited about Martin. You love Martin.
I've never mentioned Martin to my knowledge. And I don't know that I've ever seen a full episode.
Yeah. See, we know each other so well. Haven't you told me that Martin was, oh, no, it was you
thought that you so crazy. Was an amazing standup special. That's what it was. I don't think
that's true either. But I do think Martin Lawrence is very funny. I like nothing to lose.
You saw him in Vegas. Oh, yeah, he has standup. So he was hilarious. I think I said, I was never
a huge standup fan of Martin Lawrence. Yes. And you said you're crazy. You so crazy is great.
I probably said you so crazy, Joe. And then I he's a funny standup. And then you did say,
run, tell that. And I did. I have seen you so crazy. And I remember
I always talking here about how I'd make it maybe 30 minutes into SNL on a good night. And then my
dad would be like, up to two sexual go to bed. And Martin Lawrence was hosting. And he came
out for his monologue and started talking about how women's pussy is be stinking. Yeah, no,
and my dad picked me up. I was probably 11 years old and ran me out of the room. He was banned for
that. He was banned from the show. I remember I remember the, well, and you want to talk racism in
Hollywood. Louis went out there and talked about how pedophilia must be so good that it's
better than a mounds bar or whatever. Absolutely right. But it also was 30 years later. But the,
but he, I remember that I've looked at monologue up on YouTube. And I believe the way Martin
phrases it is, ladies, you got to do a better job of killing clean in the Pilly Packers. He calls
them the Pilly Packers. Yeah. Now here's the audience is kind of like not laughing. It's very
tense. This kid, what happened to this kid? Skeet all rich. Well, I'll tell you what happened.
Don't sound like terms for come. Well, skeet is a term for come. Skeet, skeet, skeet, mother
fucker. I always say all rich myself. All rich. Well, that's because you're masturbating
to shots of skeet all rich in a pair of briefs. Yeah. Skeet all rich was always the homeless man's
Johnny Depp. Yeah. He's also in scream. I just, uh, and I, you know, in scream, which I've
seen, he's a good looking guy. He just walked up here. I'm amazed this guy made it anywhere. He looks,
let's, let's be real ugly. He looks like a ferret. He, it's a look that was big back then. He has
a very like 90s. He looks like Sandler right here. 90s great. You know, I met Sandler finally in real
life. I'd never met him. Yeah. Very good looking man in real life. I think he, he got better looking
as it goes. Not to say that I looked at him on screen and thought he was not a good looking man,
but I'm just saying, like when I was, like talking to him, I was like, he's like a handsome dude.
I've always heard no one did better with the ladies than Sandler and I was primed. Dude, are you
kidding? At the time he was coming up doing all that cute shit, like a ho ho ho ho ho ho ho. Yeah.
God, man, chicks love that. Not threatening comedy. The ladies love it. The, uh, well, it's like
when Russell Brand came out and it was like he would act like sort of a feminine. Yeah. And he would
just, that was like at that time, that's like anything like the way you pick up people of the opposite
sex, whether it's men or men or women, yes, we're of the same sex. Wait, is this a cover of how soon
is now by this month? No, it's the actual version. Oh, it's definitely a cover. It sounds like
it's good Charlotte. No, that's the original version. It wasn't, Joe. All right, well anyway. All right,
carry on. It, by the way, boy, this thing is this thing is like plus two volume. I can't even
know what they're saying. Well, that's the only way I can do this. Uh, and we have the lady.
Which lady? The black lady. Sadly, sadly, sadly, I don't know her name. That's okay.
I've never seen her. That's what I'm saying. I've never seen any of these people again. Yeah.
The only person's name. Well, I knew, well, I know for who's a book and I knew, uh,
Dev Campbell and Skid all rich, but I could. Who was the other kid you called out?
Lincoln Nash Fire. Yeah, Lincoln Nash Fire. Uh, you don't know, Lincoln. That was Breck and Meyer,
who's been in a lot of shit. He was a sitcom star, he auditioned for my pilot. He was in, um,
Josie and the pussy cats and, uh, she and can hardly wait. He's in can hardly wait. He's very
funny and can hardly wait. She played the main guy. Yes. Correct. Okay. Yeah. He was in that movie with
David Keltner, Ethan Embry. That's Ethan Embry. But, but he was, he was the, uh, guy acting black,
basically. And no, that was Seth Green. But he was a friend of his. He was in clueless. I don't
remember. I know who I mean, when I saw his face. No, he was the guy acting black and clueless. Okay.
And he was, if I'm not mistaken, and can hardly win. Okay. Uh, now,
Faruza Balk, as I said before we started watching here, one of my favorite women that has ever
lived, really, it, it kills me that she's never in it. She is, and I would go as far as to say,
intoxicating walk. She has got such a wild look. Her eyes, my band, when I was in college,
I had a band called Bernie, Bernie Headflap. And we had a song called Faruza that the lead guy
wrote about Faruza Balk. And it was about just how she was like the most beautiful woman. And that's
when I, when I like noticed her, yeah, I was like 20 or 21. I was like, Oh, yeah, you're right. She's
like really uniquely beautiful. And ever since then, I, it's never gone away. I mean, uh, looks much
like comedy as subjective. She's never done it for me. Um, I know where that location is in Los Angeles.
I used to, it's right by the Pier One imports. Right. Um, now I've offered, you were in the book,
the bookstore where they go and get the magic book. Right. Uh, now I've heard this Pat, tell me if
it's true. You know where this is because you'll hang around that bookstore hoping a, a gaggle of high
school girls will come in. Yes, that I could cast a charmed spell on in the wheel. Right. Okay. Uh,
although it's now just a Pier One import. So it's just a lot of me sitting on a wicker basket,
kind of, uh, gesturing to, uh, my hog, which is flopping around a pair of, uh, sweatpants that I'm
not wearing underwear beneath. And if that's a crime, I guess lock me up two hogs up, two hogs up,
folks. I just embraced hogs. We're, we're going with it. Well, the fans have spoken. They want two
fans have oinked. They want two hogs up in. I love. Biggies have oink. And that's going to be a great
t -shirt one day. Two hogs up. It's a good t -shirt. Great. Uh, now where was I before I was
distracted by this? Oh, uh, yeah, if I, if I lose it's not from me, I think she is still in stuff.
And she was on some, she was, I think she was on a breaking bad maybe or something like that,
but she's been on big TV show. She still acts. Good. I'm glad to hear that. Um, and she also does
like charity. I looked, I followed her on Twitter, like a couple of years ago. Yeah. And she has like,
she has some very nice cause or something. She does another thing outside of show business where I was
like, oh, that's, that's cool. She's like a normal person. Yeah. I think, uh, all the, I think all
four of these, uh, gals turned out pretty normal. They did an entertainment weekly, uh, 20 years later,
story, interview with them. And they all seem cool and funny. Nav Campbell, by the way,
are those dildos? No, they're candles, Pat. Jesus Christ. Right. That's a matter with you. Uh,
the book, the magic book that she buys is called the craft. That's the name of the book
that she buys. What made them go here? Just for fun? Uh, it was when we were arguing about whether or
not it was a Smith cover or not, they, they set up why they came to this store. These women, by the way,
when did they have a 30, 32 playing high school girls in this world? That was always the case.
I bet Neb's, uh, you know, 22 or something. I had a high school girlfriend who looks so much like
Neb Campbell. It's honestly disturbing to me, especially when I see her young like this. But, um,
we were the homecoming king and queen, Joe. Oh, you were? Are you a popular high school?
Once my skin cleared up, I became popular, but only because I was a friend to nerd and jocke a
like. Okay. I bridged both groups with my humor as humor is the universal language of love and
friendship, as they say. It is. But I would still get, you know, shoved and ridiculed fairly often.
And, uh, when they played our song because the theme of the dance was under the sea, much like
back to the future, the song that I had to slow dance with my girlfriend too in front of the entire
student body was kiss the girl. Oh, nice kill there. Nice kill. Now, hold on. I don't put a pit in
that because I just want to point out the crazy sort of homeless guy is chasing. What's your name?
Tutti. Robin. Tani. Robin Tani across the street. And he's saying, you need to find Jesus. She's
scared because she thinks he's crazy. He may and may and may not be the movie. We don't know yet.
He might really be trying to help her. But that was one of the, and then a truck hits him.
Yeah. That was one of the first movies I ever, it's so hacky now. It happens left and right and everything.
That's one of the first movies I ever saw that device in where. Oh, it happens in every movie now.
Yeah, where the guy with the person gets hit by the car and you're not expecting it at all. And
then they showed his head going to the back tire, which I liked. The, uh, the funniest of those is
in Meet Joe Black, where he bounces between the cars and it looks absurd. It's not supposed to be
funny, right? No, no, no. Uh, Meet Joe Black is one of the worst movies I've ever seen excruciatingly
boring. Um, so anyway, I had to slow dance to kiss the girl from the little mermaid, which you haven't
seen. No, uh, which is sung by a calypso crab. So it's like, she don't say a word and she won't say
a word. She'll you kiss the girl. There's no beat to it. And I had to slow dance to this song.
Right. Palm, sweaty, probably the makings of a boner and my slacks, the entire school watching.
I'm dancing to an animated crab singing in kind of an offensive calypso voice. And about two
minutes into the song, which obviously I didn't pick the song. That guy stands up and goes, excuse my
language folks. Right, right. And at that age and in that year, you feel you rightly deserve it.
When that happens when you're in high school, you don't know what to do. You're just like, I didn't.
I finished the dance. My face turned immediately bright red. I probably started sweating and then
uh, it ended. There's no regardless of whatever name or whatever the person yells at you.
There is no part of you in that circumstance where you go at that age and this time,
where you go, I'm going to go give him a piece of my mind. No, just go, well, that's what happened
to me today. Yeah, I'm homecoming king. I guess this is part of it. Even at the the height of my
popularity, a man still stood and screamed a homophobic slur at me. Now here's a weird parallel
or connection between our lives. You danced to kiss the girl as your song. The theme to my
prom was kiss the girls, the Morgan Freeman film. Okay. And it was held in a basement that
Carrie L was. And we had to figure out who murdered the prom queen. It was a lot of fun. It was a
big, big mystery thing. Remember when every three weeks, there was an Ashley Judd Morgan Freeman vehicle.
Uh -huh. Or Tommy Lee Jones when they couldn't get for him. Or Joe Lee, once in a while, I think,
would pop into one. They're all those movies are identical. Bone collector, kiss the girls,
along came a spider, double jeopardy. Double jeopardy. Let's look. I've seen them all and they're not
bad. Neither of them are any, but let's throw in Holly Berry's gothika or whatever the fuck
never saw it, but I'll throw that in. There's so many of those those movies were so popular back then.
Yeah. Now here they are and she's two. Now I think that Tuddy is very pretty. Robin
Tuddy, Tuddy is like a mobster from analyze this, I think. It's also Tuddy, Tuddy is also the
Fred Gwyn's partner in car 54, where are you? The guy that would always go, oh, wait, the movie?
No, the original sitcom, you never saw it. No, I never saw it. Have you seen that movie?
No, you don't replace Fred Gwyn with David Johansson. I'm sorry. And I like David Johansson, but
and I can't remember who played Tuddy in it, but Tuddy was, Tuddy is also the guy in Goodfellas.
You wasted six fucking aprons on that guy. We got a tough in this kid.
Tuddy, that's what I was thinking of, yes.
Skeet Ulrich was in a movie, so he had a little something for a brief period outside of the
Scream franchise, but I'm pretty sure his solo career begins and ends with a picture called
Chill Factor. And this movie was Skeet Ulrich and Cuba Good in junior in a speed ripoff, except
they were in an ice cream truck rigged to blow. And it was called Chill Factor. And I saw this movie
in the theater. Was your review? This movie is rigged to blow.
It should have been. It should have been. Where's Nev Campbell these days?
Campbell, you see and stuff. I mean, she pops up and stuff. She was in a movie with James
Tobak, beloved Hollywood figure, James Tobak. Yeah. And she gets super naked in it. And she plays
like kind of a rotten person in it, which is interesting, because she usually doesn't play like a
rotten person. But that's, I like that movie. I thought that was a good movie. I was waiting to see
if she was going to, if she had any accusations when all the Tobak shit hit the fan. It was called
what? When will I be loved? Yeah, I forget who else is in it. It was, you know, it's...
Uncle Junior from sopranos was in it. It's like all the Tobak movies. Dominic Shan, they're
disturbing and sad, but they're well done. And I guess well done, you know, none of them are, I don't
think he ever had anything great. No, they're just interesting. He made a mess in his pants,
folks. Did you see the, did you ever see the interview from, oh, well hold on, sorry, I got to
strike their folks. Skiddlework just dumped Tuddy. And they were having a nice thing and then
he just shit on her. So now obviously she's going to put some kind of craft on him, right? Yeah,
from her craft book. I'm going to walk over and grab my phone because I feel appalled that we know
every girl except the black girl's name too. I only knew two of the girls. So don't let me in with
your prejudice. I only knew two of them. I know this girl's another shit. Oh look at that,
young, what's her face? Boy, does she look pretty? Christine Taylor. Ben Stiller's wife. Not
anymore. They split it up. They split it up? That's right. So you're telling me there's a chance.
When did they split up? They, uh, they split up this year. Then they've been together about 20 years.
She is still to this day striking. I'll tell you, and I'm not naming any names, but I know through
the grapevine, this is of course allegedly as well, a former assistant of Harvey Weinstein who said
he was just obviously obviously a terrible, horrible man and a terrible boss, but she said she'd
take Weinstein over Ben Stiller. She, because she assisted him. It's a woman saying this.
But not because, not because Stiller was doing anything untoward sexually, but that he is just that
unpleasant. And I really hope that's not true, but sometimes we sometimes this is TMZ on this
fucking podcast, you know? Christine Taylor just said to the black girl, I don't like Negroids.
Did you see that? I didn't see that. I didn't remember. I forgot this movie goes like kind of
deep with, yeah, with the sexual and that's not the right term, but with the, not just the racial,
but also the gender tensions and all that stuff. Yeah, it's, it's pretty dark. Oh, yeah,
and that's right. Now we're in the hospital. Ned Campbell is, oh, there's the Burralis woman from
Seinfeld. Oh, yeah, it is. Sue Ellen Mischke, the Burralis wonder. This is the thing, remember this
part where Ned Campbell, her back is like burned. I don't remember anything about it. And she has to get
like this skin dressing done. That's her back. Yeah, she was like in a fire or something. And she has
to get skin grafting done on her back. And that's like her. So like the black girl's facing racism.
Tuddy is facing skiddle rich dumping her. Yeah. This girl's got a physical deformity from a fire.
And I don't know what for, and that for us a bulk, I don't, I think everybody just thinks she's a freak.
Yeah. And she ends up being the one that goes nuts at the end of this. I remember like she's the one
where they're like, we got to stop come, come back from the edge. And she's, oh, yeah, some of that's
being familiar to me. So the woman, the fourth woman is Rachel true. That's right. And I don't
feel bad because I didn't even have a guess. But I know what else I know her from. She's in half
baked. Half baked. That's what it is. She's in CB4. Yes. And she's in one of the all -time great
jerk off films, Embrace of the Vampire starring Alyssa Malano. Yeah, when I was a kid, I'd have to say,
skated a few over it just to that one. That's right. I knew I knew her from somewhere. She's,
man, she's, she's one of those ladies, like when she's like in half -baked, I am like, yeah, she's
Hachah. Hachimuch. And then she's 50 years old and she looks beautiful.
She in half -baked, I remember just being in love with her. Yeah. And just like being like, this is
a dream woman, my god almighty. One of just such a brilliant idea for a comedy scene is that
that date he goes on where it keeps a counter of how much money he has. I always thought that was
such a great idea for a scene. It is a great idea. It's very good. Jellis of it. And you do it and
you are terrified the whole time because you know, it doesn't have enough money. And the way he keeps
saving it, it's it's a great exhale every few minutes. Yeah. Why don't we just share one and she
thinks it's cute. Sure. But the Sunday you're like, yeah, it's very funny. Very well done.
Tell me, give me, give me a little Faruza bulk. Yeah, I will. Google. Okay. So,
Bulk's mom is is an alcoholic. Let's see who's playing the mom here. And the dad is too. Look at
this dad. Oh geez, you know, he smacked his daughter on the ass a few times. Yeah. Look at this guy.
Oh, I know that guy. That guy's been on a ton of stuff. Bulk. Bulk playing a 16 -year -old chain
smoking in her bedroom. This is the kind of family she's living with to know where she's at.
Her brother is Judd Nelson from the breakfast club.
The same house. Oh, here's an article called why you don't hear about this craft star anymore.
Those are all bullshit. Those are all bullshit. Those things. They are. I see Brendan Fraser take a lot
of heat in those. I'm like, Brendan Fraser works all the time. He's also back in something that's
like got a lot of critical heat. He's on the affair. Which is very, very good show. The affair.
Maybe that's what it is. And he looks bad. I mean, he's playing like an ogre essentially and he's
they don't have many make -up. Let's put it that way. Right. She was in. I got to know what's
there it is, sopranos. I knew it got dammit. She was an FBI agent in sopranos and she was great
in it. What was she in recently, though? Oh, it says original airing only. I guess they must
have recast her. They did. I remember that. You don't recast for Ruse of bulk. It became a much
bigger role. I'm hopefully I just meant they couldn't get her. But I know exactly what happened
and it would be a spoiler to tell you. She was the voice of Penny D in 2003's Justice League. Whenever
the hell that is. Give me some, you know, post 2010. There's nothing. There's nothing big. No,
sorry. A lot of like kind of low -budge horror. She was in badly tenant port of call New Orleans,
which is a wild and wonderful movie. Oh, wait, she isn't that. Isn't she the, isn't she the chicken
the parking lot that he like shakes down and he makes her like give him a hand job or something?
She I know. I remember that scene. I don't remember if that was her. She was in a master's of horror,
you know, she's in. Pat, I gotta tell you, I think we might have a shot of getting bulk on this
podcast to talk horror. I'd love it. And maybe that's where I propose. Just straight to proposal.
Straight to proposal. So already, it's like I gotta go to this Strange Man's House full of horror
memorabilia and video games. And then to put her at ease, you're going straight to what I imagine
will be a ringless proposal. What if I did this instead? What if I was crossing to sit down in the
couch to start recording my pants accidentally and quotes fell down. And I just went, whoops,
whoops, I think you should do like finger to your lips like whoops. And if you could sit behind
the arcade machine and do a slide whistle sound effect, how about because I think the oops is going to
be a little obvious. How about we slip a sausage in your back pocket and have contact your pants down
copper tone baby style. I assume we're doing this just to reveal your sweet ass to her.
Right. Because how could she resist? Because then if Khan does it, we can make it very sitcom -y like
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, it's not what you think. Right. We're kidding everybody. We're kidding.
I feel like you have to say that right now. We're just kidding. I think they knew we were not
planning to put meat into your pants and have your dog take them down in front of Byruz Abok
who you're planning on proposing to. I don't know that we didn't need to explain that.
One of the funniest lines I've ever read in print ever. Did you ever read Steve Martin's book?
I did. Pure drivel. Oh yeah, I love pure drivel. The thing that the first chapter where it's just
him apologizing to everybody through his life. I remember reading this on an airplane, on a
trip to LA. First time I ever flew out here right after college and just laughing hysterically and he
goes, I want to apologize to my secretary that worked for me from the years 1984 until 1987.
For the time that I was trying to show her my new dictaphone and coincidentally my pants fell down.
Just as I said, ever seen one of these before. I love Steve Martin's writing. I love his books.
I love his serious books. I love his plays and I love his movie scripts. I think he's
yeah, he's great. He's a real talent. I don't know if I'm telling you something you don't know.
He's great. Mainly he gets kind of a bad rap as being pompous and I think he's just kind of an old
daughtering man at this point. He's not as sharp and that's fine. I would like to see that
thing with him in short. I heard it's great. I kick myself all the time. They did it at the
fucking Glendale Playhouse and we didn't go and I didn't go see Rickles before he died. I got a lot of
regrets. I saw Rick at Nev Campbell. Yeah, she's a very pretty stunner. The four of these women are
beautiful. Yes. These are four very beautiful people. They've passed a spell on me for sure.
Which crab? What's Campbell up to these days? She's got to be pushing. I guess now that I'm the
researcher on the show, why you enjoy your beverage. She's about 50 now too, right? I mean, I guess they're
all covering around there. Nev Campbell, I hope she's getting a producer credit on that reboot of
45. I mean, it's funny. I'm like, I'm like, she's got to be 50 and I'm like, well, I'm 40,
so that would make perfect sense. They're also bringing Magnum PI back. Hawaii 5 .0 was already back.
They're redoing Cagney and Lacey. My mom's old favorite show. I can't remember seeing one
episode of Cagney and Lacey. It was just a very generic couple of cops strongly hinted that they
were lesbians, but they weren't. As a seven -year -old boy, I wasn't their demographic, but
right. Wild things. I mean, that pairing of like the Good Girl Campbell and just the
porny Denise Richards. Yeah. When I was, I mean, that movie was my first year, I could see an R -rated
movie alone. I intentionally brought no one with me to the theater. I just wanted to enjoy it alone.
Now, who's the guy in Wild Things? Well, Matt Dillon, Kevin Bacon, Bill Murray, which one?
Bill Murray. But Dillon's the guy they're like seducing, right? Yes. Where's it bacon?
No, it's Dillon. Bacon is the cop, shows his dick as we've discussed on this show. Bacon always
plays the cop. Bacon cannot get a break to play a nice guy. No. In the last 20 years, I haven't seen
play one likable character in any. He's always a fucking trick. And when he does, it's bad. Like the
era up there is a terrible movie where he like attempted to be the hero. I never saw it. Yeah, he's
good in those like woodsman roles. He's good. I mean, I'm playing real creepers. Yeah. Sleepers, he's
so, so great. And he's great in Frost Nixon. I love Frost Nixon. Where he's like crying about like
what has happened to Nixon. I love that movie. Yeah. Cop car is a recent really excellent
picture. If you haven't seen cop car, but he's a bad guy. He's a very bad guy on that. Yeah.
Also starring Miss Cameron Mannheim. I didn't know Mannheim was in there. Yeah. Great movie.
So she, it looks as though since scream four, which was actually fairly recent, she's appearing in
a movie called Sky Scraper with the rock. So that's good. Okay. And it's going to be in 3D. Yeah.
I think the rock makes a movie every three months at this point. Yeah. Oh, she did two seasons of
house of cards. I mean, she's around. All right. That's good to know. I'm happy for. All right. Yeah,
these, it's, it's got to be scary. Like to be in like kind of a big movie. You think it's why people
go insane in the entertainment industry. But if you stick it out long enough and it's sad but true
if you maintain your looks, you'll act again because people have so much affection for these
old movies. You remember them. And then as you get older, you want to hire your idols and etc.
Yeah. That's, yeah. That's, that's real. That's like, that's like, that's like real
kid stays in the picture stuff. Yeah. Yeah. You know, I was down and out. The first kid I have got,
got me coffee, called me. I'm the head of paramount now. I want to hire you back in Evans.
That can happen. Yeah. It can happen. Yeah. So, it's why, and believe me, no one learns this lesson,
but it's why it pays in any industry. But I think especially the entertainment industry,
to be nice to everyone you meet because you're going to meet them again on the way up or down or
whatever the expression is. Uh, I think it's, I think it's, it's easier on the way down than on
the way up is the expression. Be a prick on the way up. But be nice on the way down. I believe it's
I don't think that's right. That wouldn't be an expression. You sure? You'll, I think it's,
you'll see that again on the way that I'm kidding. I'm saying it exactly wrong. All right. They say
be nice on the way up because you're going to see him again on the way down. All right. I was saying
it backwards. So it's an issue of mine. I am always sarcastic and then I can very rarely decide for
when people are being sarcastic to me. Oh, and it hurts me because it makes me feel like there's
something wrong with my, no, brand of sarcastic. It's all me. I think it's tied into being bullied as a
child. I always think people are fucking with me or I get mad. I lash out. Look at those eyes on
bulk. I can't get over those eyes. They're piercing. It's not, it's not for me. The mouth is unsettling.
Look, she's got a real wild girl look to her. I got, no, I'm not disputing that. She looks like
somebody that'll fucking cut a line of meth on the table after you bring her home from the bar.
But I, but I, I like it. I like her whole vibe. Also too, it's hard to not picture her in the American
history. X, you know, because she's, I forgot about that. She's so hateful in that movie. Yeah.
And she's the only, no, that's not true. I was going to say she's the only supremacist that doesn't
learn a lesson in that movie, but that's far from true. But it's been 20 years since I saw it. I
don't, I know I don't necessarily want to see it again, but I remember watching it.
I like American history. X, you know, it's obviously not when you pop in on a Friday night to
have a few laughs. But I like the movie. I think it's a very good movie. Very timely.
Oh, yeah, sure.
This is a man. This is a wild Spaniard putting on her name.
Fy Rooza. I thought there was a name. No, Farooza.
I've always said Fy Rooza. And I dated. You also consistently, consistently still say Tiffany Hadeesh.
I do say Hadeesh. I thought I still think that might be right. It's not right.
Might literally nobody says it that way. By the way, did you see, uh, so they might make sex in
the city three without Kate? Uh, was your name? What? Um, what's her name?
It's Samantha. Kim Ketral. Kim Ketral. So Kim Ketral apparently, it's one of these things.
But I've been here in those three years. Well, but, but apparently there's a guy who I'd rather
not see get another fucking dollar. My former boss, they, they, they, her and her and Parker traded some
insults recently again. Yeah. There's a real beef there. And, uh, she's like, and, and Ketral was
just like, look, I'm not fucking doing the movie because, because Parker gets way more money than
everybody else. And it's bullshit and everything. You know, it was one of those things. Sure. So, uh,
I think those girls would have an agreement where they all take you and equal amount. Uh, I don't,
I don't, I don't, I don't, it was one of those kind of things. So then Parker is on
Ellen. Ellen says so Sam says she won't come back.
Would you do the movie without her? And, and apparently Parker said, yeah, we're still
considering doing it with like a new Samantha or something. Uh -huh. So, Kim Ketral takes to
Twitter very positively. Right. Doesn't say like fuck you. You'll never do it without me or anything.
Yeah. She just goes, I, I, I hope whoever fills my, it takes the role has a great time. Here's
some people I think would be brilliant. Names two actresses. One of them is Tiffany Haddish.
One of them is a woman who I can't remember younger than Tiffany Haddish. She picks two people
who are literally at least 20 years. Dakota fan. Her junior. Yeah. And goes, I think they'd be great
with the role. It's like, what are you talking about? Right. It's it's not, it doesn't, it's not
even close. Now, how did you see any of this if you're off Twitter because I'm sure as hell didn't see?
I read it on, uh, like, you know, on like the movie websites. It was like, uh, apparently the
section in city three might still happen. You know, I'm clicking on that link. Of course. And, uh,
I mean, you don't, you can't do it without Ketral. Look, the only reason I want a third movie is
because the fucking, see it with Haddish. The first two were fucking dog shit. They like the first one.
Oh, it's terrible. It's about three hours too long when I like the first one. I, they're both
terrible. The show is so beautiful and that the movies are so terrible. And I want them to just have
one good movie. And I want it with Ketral. And I want them to finally tackle. This is especially
why I want it with Ketral. I want them to finally tackle sexuality and being an older woman. Like,
truly tackle it. These women are in their late fifties at this point, tackle this for real. Like,
you, Ketral is probably 60 years old. You know, it's like, that would be such a cool, interesting
movie like older women and like their sexuality and how like they still have it. And it's not a
thing that comes. It would be such a statement to make. And they've just never made it. Yeah. I mean,
they might not want to acknowledge their aging or something, but that would, that would have to be
the next step. They went marriage. Then they did babies. Oh, no, the second one was just racism was
the theme of the second one. Um, the second one was so terrible. It was so bad. It's one of the worst
sex in the city movie and take them out of New York. That's literally like if they were like,
hey guys, all right, this Han Solo movie is coming out. He goes to Earth in it. Yeah. No, no,
don't, please don't do that. Please don't do that. It was a, a travesty that movie. Absolutely.
Uh, um, so hope, look, nobody's looking for this recommendation. If you want a really great movie
about sexuality when you're older, and I see nobody saw it because the subject makes people
uncomfortable, unfortunately, hope springs with Tommy Lee Jones and Marl Street. It was such a sweet
entertaining movie. And I loved it. I wanted to see that movie. I heard it was very bad. It's not.
I mean, so many things you just hear, you hear a bad and never see them. I don't mean you. I mean,
people in general. And then you check something out. Sometimes you're right. They're right. But that
was a movie that I thought handled that so well. Just a, there's so many married couples.
Most people's parents, I feel like where they just, they haven't even thought about fucking in 25
years. Right. And you know, she's like, I want to fuck again. And she's trying to get her husband
out of his shell. And it's a great, great movie. It's really entertaining. Therapist in it.
Corel. That's right. I almost should Steven Colbert. It's a really sweet movie. I liked it a lot.
And if you want to see Marl Street blow Tommy Lee Jones in a movie theater, I recommend it for
that reason as well. Holy cat. It's going on here. Neville's, Neville got her skin thing fixed in
her back. Did she also get her net implants? No, I'm calling her Neville. No, I think that's all Neville.
Holy moly. And she's coming in like kind of, kind of showing it off a little bit now. She feels like
pretty for the first time because her back doesn't have all that shit on it. Right. And God bless her.
Show it off, Neville. Work it around that campus. I mean, this is a classic Hollywood, you know,
the thing that always bothers me is it's such a trope of Hollywood sitting in the quad.
Well, yeah. The first one of the outdoor high school sitting in the quad never happened.
Really? Well, where's this high school? But then also maybe I'll, the four of the hottest women
I've ever seen in my life. And they're like, they're outcasts. They can't get a date. A, they're outcast.
And B like no one is even glancing at these four women at the men's horneous time in their life.
Yeah, you got skied all rich up there looking like, you know, like somebody
turned Johnny Depp's face inside out. Yeah. The not another teen movie was a very funny spoof
of a lot of these tropes about the girl who like takes her hair out of a ponytail and everybody's
like, who's this babe? She was so fucking disgusting before. Have you seen another teen movie?
No, seriously. It was too late. It came out after there had been too many scary movies at that
point. It was just it's, it's got some really funny stuff in it. All right. It, it does, you know,
the scary movies eventually became like they just thought recognizing what movie was being spoof
was the joke. Right. Do anything to it. Not another teen movie goes into like very, very specific
aspects of teen movies and spoof them. And it's much funnier for it. Yeah, I, I, I, I don't doubt
that it's funny. Like I said, it just came out the wrong time. And I was just like, you know,
I didn't have any interest at the time. Sure. It was like the reason I never saw fatal instinct. Sure.
Which might be very funny, but it was just too realistic. Fatal instinct sucks. Fatal instinct sucks.
Armando Santé. There's another guy. That's a man who's not funny. I'm sorry. But he was,
he was going to be like the next deniro. Yeah. And then like, he just made a couple bad,
he's still in ship, but he just made some bad decisions. I like the mombokings. That's what put him on
the map. Yeah. The mombokings is great. You know, I love in the mouth of madness.
I see him. Oh, wait, no, sorry, that's Sam Neil. Sam Neil. Armando, I love Gotti. Did you ever see the
hoffa? Yes. Hoffa man. I mean, Davido does not direct enough. That is a guy who does some really
cool things with a camera as a director. War of the Rose guy looks. He directed the shit out of
the world. Scotty Landis. He looks a lot like Scotty Landis. If you don't know who Scotty Landis is,
he's a writer friend of ours. And there's a guy in the craft that looks exactly like him. Yeah,
he plays the lawyer telling Farooza Bulk and her mother how much money they're inheriting when the
dad dies. It might be Scotty. Has Scotty been aligned this all this time? Is he actually a 55 -year -old
character director? I'd buy it. Scotty Landis, by the way, has a horror movie being made,
starring Octavia Spencer, directed by the guy who did the fucking help. I mean, I'm so proud of him.
It's awesome. Yes. I'm very excited about that. One of the rare good guys in the
this world. It's awesome. I was in the Astro Diner with him when he told me about that.
Yeah. And then a month later, I saw the announcement on Movie Web, which I thought was very cool.
I would have been there where I not hung over from hanging out with you the night before.
It was a different time that you weren't there because you weren't invited to this other time.
It just wasn't about it. Yeah. No, that was a night where I never do this anymore. Tonight,
I'll probably have three, four whiskies. Have a great time. Go see it. We're seeing a concert.
But that was a night where I was in a bad mood. I had been drinking whiskey with a friend and Joe
pours me a large glass of wine. Red wine. You can hear on the podcast, Joe, going, drink the wine.
I'm two glasses ahead of you. Sip the wine. Well, I'm about to start again. You've had this
full glass of whiskey for 55 minutes. You're an enabler, Joe. You can't bring wine into the mix.
That's fine. I'm not saying we've got to pound these things, but you know, we're also recording
several podcasts today. I know. You know, paste yourself. I don't want us to be talking later,
and you're like, so anyway, I'll tell you something. You piece of shit. You know, finally I tracked
him anymore. Well, that could never come out of my mouth. No, that's me. That was me to you.
Oh, yes, yes. All I want in life is a jukebox. I agree. Oh, that plays nothing but county
Francis records. I disagree. So I would love a jukebox. Why don't I have a fucking jukebox?
Faruza just to bring you up to see what the jukebox.
Well, you know, I don't know because I was about, I was trying to find that out recently
by asking a person that worked in bars and stuff like what it cost. And they said they didn't know
because they were all rented for so many years. Yeah. Like those style ones we picked the record
because it was a mob thing. It was a mob thing. They were like, we're going to put this jukebox in
your bar. And then we're going to come and take all the money that people put into it. Like,
and then that was it. Like that was right. So I don't, I have no idea what a jukebox would call.
I would guess that that nice one they just had there in this day and age three grand. Yeah,
probably. I mean, now they're all fucking digital. And it's like, it's like everything else.
Do I like going to the bar and being able to play any song in the world? I do. But do I sort of
prefer having to choose from the hundred that are presented to me? Yeah, I do. I like being like,
oh, they got this album. That's great. At least the E rustic still has the old version one.
Um, I don't think E rustic does the drawing room. They replace that. Anyway, well, they had the old one.
They did a couple of years ago anyway. Uh, drawing room definitely does. Look, I still,
I still very much appreciate what I can say to somebody. Good bar, great jukebox. Yeah.
You know, but now any bar that has the, the, uh, computerized one has every song. It's kind of
cheating. Yeah. Yeah. And it's, you know, I hear you. And they, and it is become, it has become
like Spotify or anything else like where it's like, no, it is every song now.
Yeah. It's not just every popular song. It's like, no, all of the Fugazi catalog is on there now,
too. Like, yeah, everything that you can think of that never saw the light of MTV or anything is
on there. And what blows the mind is that there's a still one person every night who thinks, I bet this
group of people wants to hear hotel California. Yeah. That they haven't heard hotel California in a
while. Well, Vince and I, I don't know if I've ever told this story on the podcast, Vince and I were
in the, uh, roost one day. This guy came in, man. Had to be 70, 72 years old, put in easily $10
worth of Al Yankovic. Oh, wow. Weird Al Yankovic. No, I, I know. Uh, you meant, I didn't think it was,
uh, normal Al Yankovic. Well, I think Al Yankovic is a polka guy from the 50s. Okay.
Look, I, I used to be obsessed with weird Al when I was a child. Yeah. Then he goes outside,
misses all of it. Oh, comes back in. It might have been a prank. No, and he's like, did I miss the
weird Al? I did I miss all my weird how? Who's really upset? And then he started talking to us about
weird Al. Yeah. I was like, buddy, I don't, I can't, you know, Jesus Christ. I don't know what to tell
you. Like God bless you. All right. You like weird Al was you playing the classics or like,
there's some albums I haven't heard. I'm pretty sure he played some of those deep polka cuts.
Like the polka medleys. I like the polka medleys. When I went to, I was out on, uh,
Alapalooza, the Jurassic Park album. That's when I got out. That's when I got out too. That was
the one that had a, if I'm not mistaken, the, the Phantom Menace American Pie parody on it.
That's the one out. Oh, that's running with scissors. Yeah. Uh, I got out on, um, I got out way before
that. I got out on like, uh, dare to be fat. Even worse. My last one was the last one I did.
But, uh, when I went to, uh, I don't mean to name drop, but Craig Ferguson. Uh -huh. Good friend of mine.
When I went to his Christmas party, I saw, uh, I don't mean to name drop, Chris and Shaw,
another friend of mine. Uh, and I went over to say hi to her and her wonderful husband. And, uh,
and, uh, they were talking to somebody and I turned and the guy goes, hey, I'm out. And it was
weird. And it was a very weird moment to be like, oh, yeah, you're, yeah. I've heard he's one of
the nicest. He was very nice. His daughter and his wife were there. They were very nice. And
I would tell you, Joe, about meeting weird out at six flags. No. When I was, you can't, when I was
nine, 10, I was crazily obsessed with weird out. And I saw that he was coming to six flags
over mid -america in St. Louis. And I had never been to a concert before. I asked my mother to take me
and she obliged. We went and I'm so excited about the show. I was like shaking all day. I was going
to be at like eight, nine o 'clock. We're riding the rides and we're at the Buccaneer, which is the big
ship that goes all the way up and all the way down. I like the Buccaneer. It sucks up your stomach,
but I like it. If you sit on that back seat, you lift off the seat. Right. Yeah. I like that.
So I said, hey, mom, so I was dabbling in joke riding even at this young age. I said,
how much does corn cost on this ride? She said, I don't know. And I said, a Buccaneer.
Ah, okay. Very good. And she laughed. And then she looks over and she goes, wait a minute. Isn't that
weird out over there? Weird out was there with a beautiful young blonde woman.
Now, what era of weird hour are we talking? Are we talking afro, like Jewish afro mustash?
Are we talking like straightened long hair? We're talking straightened long smells like neurona days. Okay.
I'm trying to hear what song this is. I couldn't believe it. I was blown away. He was
10 feet away from me and this beautiful model on his arm. And my mom goes, you should go tell him
your joke. And I was like, mom, it's stupid. She goes, go tell him your joke. He's a funny guy.
He likes jokes. I walked over my mom hot on my tail. I said, hi, Mr. Yang, I'm a big fan of yours.
Can I tell you my joke? He was like, I'd love to hear your joke. I tell him my joke. He laughed.
Although, let's be real. It was probably a fake laugh. He offers an autograph. Doesn't even make me ask.
I ripped off some piece of paper. He signed it. I still have the piece of paper somewhere at my dad's house.
Or excuse me, my dad's studio apartment.
Low blow to dad. No, that's not a blow. I'm just telling you, that's where you're at.
All right, all right. The way you said it is. I'm sure he threw it away, honestly, because that's
something that doesn't survive the trip to a studio apartment. But who could have been nicer?
Good to have been nicer. Good. Good. That's all.
Now that you see him perform that night?
So I'm performing. He was great. I have heard to this day he's great, because it's weird.
He'll do like a surgeon and come out dressed as a doctor.
Yeah, he comes out in the fat suit for fat. Then he runs backstage, comes out in the fat suit, and you're like,
how do you do that? It's very cool. What did he open with?
I believe he opened with Edit. Okay.
Bam, bam, bam, bam, bam.
Because I've seen recent shows online. I think these days he's opening with like a polka
medley kind of thing. He always does on his albums of polka medley. I think they're ingenious.
I think they're great. They're very good. And I really like the one where he does closer by
nine inch nails in it. You let me buy you late. Yeah.
Yeah. And every time I want to fuck you like an animal, fuck is replaced with like a cartoon.
I poke noise. Yeah. Yeah. He's funny. And of course, I love UHF, and I used to have a VHS
collection of his videos. And those were great too. I was over Vince's one night watching some sort
of wrestling pay -per -view. Not to brag. Not to brag. And everybody had cleared out. It was down to
me, Vince and Georgia's wife. And Vince and I were, we were pretty tuned up at this point.
Sure. We were a little stoned. And he started talking about VHF, man.
And I was like, yeah, I love the movie. And we were laughing hysterically just quoting it.
I kept yelling, you idiots at him, you know, the dad, the mean dad or whatever. And he put it on,
Georgia's like, you guys have fun. I've had enough. It's not a movie that the ladies love.
But I mean, I will tell you this. We watched it. We were pigs and shit. We were dying.
Yeah. And sure enough, the mean boss dad's first line is you idiots. I didn't know that was his
opening line. Yeah. So when he comes in and yells at immediately, we were like, we were coming to
fucking pieces. I bought the special edition. I have not watched it in 20 years. I need to
actually watch the thing. But I saw UHF at the drive in theater. I remember it well.
What is in the special edition of UHF? You know, documentary. It's, it's, uh, shout factory.
Great Bob Oden Kirk joke. What's that?
Remember Suncoe's video? Do I remember Suncoe's video? Yeah. He goes, uh,
spent most of my childhood there. This is a normal joke. He goes, I was at a Suncoe's video the other day,
saw a DVD, bofinger special edition. And he goes, what could possibly be in the bofinger special
edition? I pick up the box. It says does not contain the movie bofinger. All right.
Why go after bofinger? Look, I like bofinger. That's a really funny, well written movie. Why go
after bofinger? I like bofinger a lot. That's a very funny joke. Yeah. It's a joke that could have
been so much funnier. And I don't mean you got to go obvious. Like go, you know, 50 shades of gray
or something. But I was written before. I know. You know what I mean? You don't have to go with
a notoriously terrible movie. But bofinger is, is like a very good comedy. I like you would think
Golden Kirk would enjoy it. I like bofinger. Look, what do you want for me? It's a joke. He made a joke.
It was very, maybe the joke is that he actually literally saw bofinger special edition. I thought
that's ridiculous. That's true. And then just wrote that punch line for it. It was a funny joke.
All right. My favorite bobo to Kirk stand up joke ever is he said, he goes, I was walking down
Hollywood Boulevard. I walked past a costume shop. And in the window, it said Santa's costumes.
Not Santa costumes. Santa's costumes. Possessive. Yeah. And he goes, so I don't understand.
You go in the story of the guys like, well, over here, we have Santa's pirate costume. Now, of course,
if you're going to rent this, you got to rent a Santa costume to wear under it or it doesn't make sense.
I don't think of him as a stand up. And the times I've seen him do it, he always seen very nervous and
kind of reading off cards. But that's probably just because he's not, that's not his number one thing
anymore. I think he started as a stand up. Yeah. But it's very funny. And it's, I love the man.
I just don't care for his shots at bofinger. It's that kind of humor. It's all very Mr. Show. Right.
Ask. You know, why are these dolphins dead? What's happening?
They're, oh, they're praying. Okay. So they're praying now to the black god, not black like race.
Like, uh, you know what I mean? Like the black magic god. I mean, yeah. And, uh, he's a black magic god.
Is that David Bowie? No, it's Santana. Oh, she's a black magic woman. Um, I think like,
that's why Faruza Balk was yelling, I'm your daughter now. He's everywhere. I think they're saying
where if a ruse is going too far, not yet. They're, they're all still with Faruza except Tutti.
Tutti's starting to be like, what's wrong? We got to cool it. Yeah. Yeah.
I mean, she's running red lights obviously. Well, no, she made the red light turn green. Oh, okay.
She's powerful. Okay. She's got power, but it with great power comes great tits. Come on. I'm
kidding, Pete. That should have been the tagline. This was a time where that could have been the tagline
of this movie. Not anymore. And I think probably that's what the best. This movie is making magic
in my pants. You had wand right there. You didn't go with wand. Oh, okay. Sorry. You always have to
outright me. All right. You always have to one up me. Not one uping. Isn't anything good enough?
No, I'm fair enough. I agree. Uh, yeah. I mean, so here we are. This is the thing with these
commentaries. You hit a point where you're like, well, I'm done talking now.
We're at, we're at an hour three. That's usually when we end. Yeah. No, it's just past when we usually
work. An hour three. We've got another 37 minutes. Look, we're going to make them sizzle for you.
And we, and this is a special, this is a bonus, this is a bonus app, which means we can't do any
segments. That's right. And I, I will say this on the regular app that we're doing today, which
will be when we discuss Winchester. Oh, don't give anything away. Oh, yeah. Uh, I'm going to bring
back an old segment that we haven't done in a while because I don't really have anything for,
for movie corner. I haven't really been watching much lately. Okay. But I'm going to bring back the news.
Remember, I said I wanted to do a news thing where we talked about a horror story in the news.
Yes. Yeah. So I got a great one. Oh, okay. All right. And I'm going to bring that back today.
And I'm thinking the title could be, now I'm not as good as the puns as you are. Uh, I think
we called news psycho. Yeah, that's pretty good. Like called Walter's thing, news cycle. Yeah. Yeah.
Uh, but I got a great, ooh, it's a good one. It's a real good story. Um, you're going to be
disgusted. I can't wait to be disgusted. I always am. Now, here's something, Joe, and I remember this
pretty vividly, when all my friends and I would go to see any movie, especially once we were able to
see our rated movies. Something that always infuriated us would be a, as I'm talking when I'm 18 or
some, a shower scene like that where the girls are all wearing towels, the girls are all wearing
towels and you start to feel like the scene's going to end and they didn't even put somebody in the
background walking through naked because this is all we had. I did not have the internet. And I
would be livid. This is not an R rated movie. The craft is definitely an R rated movie. I don't think
it is. I think it's PG 13. I don't want to bet, but I don't think it is. They haven't said
fuck once. It's an R rated movie. Look it up. I bet it's PG 13. I couldn't see it. I know that
everything before I was 17, I know the rating of I guarantee they haven't said one real curse word
yet. I wish you'd bet. They said one or two slurs. I wish you'd fuck it. Even the slurs, they turned
into like weird variations of the slurs. There's been no nudity. There's been no sex. That's right.
But why? I'm not the MPAA. I'm not Jack Valenti. Who's the head of the MPAA? You know? I don't get it.
There's nothing that didn't curse. There's no nudity. Well, maybe they couldn't. One day ago,
this news story came out. The craft star, Robin Tunney, would love to do a sequel. That's a news story.
What's Tony up to these days? Let's check on Tony. And then we're also going to check on
fucking true. Yeah, of course. We did. We already checked on true. But you didn't see what she was
doing though. She's not doing anything. You just showed me the picture of her being the hottest woman
I've ever seen in my life. Robin Tunney, oh wow, she was on the mentalist for 10 years. Now she
made a lot of money. Let me see what Tunney looks like these days. It looks the same, right?
Essentially, yeah. She was on prison breaks. She's been acting forever. All right. She's in good shape.
So she wants to do an older craft. Oh, no, I'm in the mentalist fan page here. Jesus Christ.
Or maybe it's a thing where they show their daughters, the black magic. Yeah, it would be,
they'd probably be the moms. It's probably what they do. It's like that now and then movie.
Remember that doesn't bulk die at the end of this. I don't recall, but thanks for spoiling that.
Well, you know, I mean, it's, it's not like we're real invested in this thing. We're, no.
Tunney is, oh, look, well, here's a, this is graphic. Skeet all rich is trying to rape.
Tunney right now. So I forgot that yeah, this really gets dark. I'm wrong. It gets very dark.
Um, hello, Tunney. Yeah. How does exactly the same? All of every girl in this woman in this
really looks exactly the same. How does it happen that all, well, not all, I guess, but for the most part,
Agresses kind of look the same throughout their lives. Is it just because they're so beautiful at a
young age? Or is it that the business forces them to, you know, I mean, she doesn't like it up. She's
they, these, the, the cast of this movie is aged very well. Yeah. They've aged very well.
For some reason, Rebecca Romaine is Stan, Stanis. Well, no, it's just Rebecca Romaine now. Oh, yeah.
Is trending. What do you think she's trending back? Tell me what true is up to. We know. I mean,
she's, she's not really doing much. Her, her credits that came up were like from the 90s.
Well, why would she, maybe she's just a family now. Well, you didn't let me watch that seven minute
video about why she doesn't act anymore. No, that was about bulk. Oh, yeah, you're right. Yeah.
Rachel true. Former fashion model. She was on the UPN sitcom Half and Half that ran for four years.
That's something. What the hell is half and half? Never heard of it.
She was in Noah, which I like the Russell Crowe movie. Russell Crowe, yeah. Okay. Who'd she
play in there? She was in. Oh, she was a voice. I guess that's not as ideal. Okay.
Dawson's Creek. Yeah, it looks like she's things have thinned out the most for Rachel true.
She was in Sharknado, too. All right. Blood Lake, Attack of the Killer Lampries.
Attack of the Killer Lampries? Things, things have dried up. Land bulk,
bulk sounds like it slowed down too. But maybe this is by choice. Maybe they just don't want to,
you know, well, Joe, I think what it probably is is that actresses far more than actors age out of
Hollywood. They don't want them once you hit a certain age. It's a sad but true fact. It's a
disgusting fucking business of course in town and city. I'm ashamed to live in it quite frankly
because if you're going to be a love interest in a movie, you need to actually be 15 years younger
than the male to 15 to 20 years younger than that. Or in the case of a Clint Eastwood movie, 40 to 50 years
younger than the male. So it's unfortunate. That's what it is. And nobody's making like a racial
true vehicle, you know, she's got to kind of take what she can get. But Campbell and Tony are
still working. That's true. That's true. I think, you know, they're just names that stuck in the
public consciousness more than the other two. Okay. Balk is now seducing Skid all -rich.
And he's going to hurt him. He's shoving it. Well, she's seducing him to, I think, to hurt him.
But he shoved her away and he's drunk. Now she's going to do something like she's upset now because
he shoved her. So she's going to do something really. See, this is why you're not attracted to Balk is
because she's able to play this thing so well. Yeah. Like this insane. She plays crazy very well.
Yeah, it's intimidating. Well, the truth is, I did my time dating crazy people and I don't
ever want to go back to it. Well, I don't think she's actually crazy. I'm just saying I think she
plays crazy well. But I think that I think you're right. That I don't respond well to it to the
crazy. And that sets you off. That's me off, yes. Tony going at it. Tony going at it.
All -rich getting more than he deserves certainly. So all Rick got to make out with all of these
gals in the course of one movie. No, only her. He and, oh, I guess Bull Bawk, right?
No. Bull tried to seduce him. He pushed her away. And then she transformed into Tony. Got you.
And he just rolled with it. Well, that's a bad wig. Well, she went bald.
Still, you could do better than that in the wig. Well, I think the point is that she was the
popular hot girl. No, you know, she's obviously wearing a wig because she lost all her hair.
Right. What were you going to say? Did he what? Uh oh, now the real Sarah walks in.
And Bawk is there. Nice prank Bawk. But I'm saying he saw her morph, correct?
Yeah. So why did he just roll with that? I don't know. But the first thing he yelled was
he shit faced. And the first thing he yelled was you're a witch. That's what you'd yell. You
wouldn't be like, I had too much. I gotta get out of here. Right. Her face just shamed. I gotta get out.
I've had a lot to drink. I never thought that a lady turned into another lady in my presence. Yeah.
Well, sometimes they look a little different the next morning. But uh oh, yeah.
Lee Lee Lee. Um, now this is a very good Jack and Coke you made here. But uh it's
giving me a little acid reflux for some reason, which I don't care for. That's not on me. I'm not
saying you did it. I'm just saying it's on drinking whiskey and Coke. Two things that cause acid.
Oh, look at that classic witch move. Yeah. Like the feet, the toes dragging on the floor. She floats.
That is a classic witch move. It's kind of a feminist picture here.
Uh, well yeah, it's about four women underdogs. Yeah. You know, fighting back.
And uh, and they all do a good job of it except bulk goes a little, bulk goes a little bulk. Let's be
honest. Yeah. She goes a little Faruza in this thing. I think she's gonna kill him. She's gonna kill
Skate. There he goes. Skate. Skate. Skate. Motherfucker. Skate goes out the window onto the, look,
now this is an R rated movie and they don't show him hit the fucking pavement.
I'm starting to wonder if they didn't intend to go for a PG 13 because there's also a shower scene
where everyone's wearing three things. I'm showing you they wanted it to be PG 13 and the God damn suits.
Said it had to be art. They haven't said fuck wants. I bet if it was man, which is they would have gotten
a PG 13 rating. Have you seen the film Bert Wunderstone? Of course.
It's one of the funniest movies in recent years. It's pretty funny. Uh, it was directed by my, uh,
my friend, Mr. Don Skardino. He's a nice man. Yeah. Uh, I think it's a very, very funny film,
but I like it the beginning when he does the trick, the magic trick for young Steve Buscemi and young
when I thought the movie had plenty of laughs and the cast for God's sake, Gandal Fanny. I like when old
Steve Buscemi, uh, says he's doing charity work by bringing magic kits down to starving children
in third world country. And then they're showing the b -roll footage on the news and the kids are
trying to eat the magic kit. Yeah. Yeah. That's a dark joke. Very funny. Now I'll say, and I'm still,
I'm not even halfway done here with this drink, but I, I need to eat. I need to order some food.
I ate a late lunch. Oh, you're okay. You're better off. But we can order something. You want to order
pizza? That'd be nice. And we can eat it during the next podcast. That'd be real nice. Yeah,
you're, I mean, this is what I want to hear us, uh, chew. This is crazy. Sorry folks. That's ice.
Look, it's a party vibe. I hope you're enjoying a cocktail while you, while you watch the craft
with us. I think people are listening to this at work. Yeah. So I'd say if you're enjoying a
cocktail at the moment, you might want to look into something. Right. But program, uh, I mean, it's,
it's, it's one thing to drink a little slowly in patient. This is absurd. And I have an hour on a
drink. Oh, right. Oh, Jesus. The peer pressure. It's not peer pressure. I just don't want to feel like I
have a problem. Well, can you talk while I pour this? Yeah, please. Talk while you pour it.
Folks, the podcast itself, um, we got some stuff coming up. We got before I wake,
the Netflix picture is going to be on Monday. What are you dropping this this week?
This will be out sometime this month. Okay. You're going to have before I wake or maybe you already
have it. We're also going to do Winchester starring Helen Mirren, uh, which Joe and I saw
at the theater together in Las Vegas. We'll also be discussing our time in Vegas on that podcast.
And then we're doing, uh, blade. And let's, let's say it blade two. I've never seen blade
Trinity, but we'll be talking about blade one and two. So if you want to prepare, those are the
ones to look out for Trinity. We can skip. I, you know, I don't hate Trinity, but it's the worst of
three. And it's a lot of Ryan Reynolds and Jessica Beale. Nobody needs that.
What role does Patton Oswald play? A nerd? Uh, I believe he plays the nerdy comic relief,
surprisingly. And in a movie where Ryan Reynolds is apparently doing nonstop comic relief,
they need additional comic. I don't remember if Reynolds is, I don't think Reynolds is funny in
it. I think it's before Reynolds became like Mr. Deadpool. Well, he was always van wilder
ring any bells. Yeah, no, but I don't. Waiting ring any bells. I can't just friends. That's a fun
movie. Just friends is a very underrated comedy. If you haven't seen it, I'm sure it's streaming
somewhere. Ashton, Kutcher and Eddie Murphy honeymoon movie. Oh, Brittany. It's like Eddie
Murphy. So you're talking about what happens. Not what happens in Vegas. You're talking about, uh,
yeah, that movie was okay. Not great. Yeah, no, I know you're talking about. Uh, yeah, Ryan Reynolds
was a guy who for years, I was like, I know I should hate Ryan Reynolds, but he's funny. How
is this guy not connecting? And then he, he did at age, whatever early age he is, 45. He's very
funny. Yeah, he's very funny. I watched the new Deadpool trailer and I thought it looked funny.
I ain't seen the trailer, but I enjoyed Deadpool. This is again, but that's by not only the
pair one imports, but also jumbo's clown room. Oh, was that the jumbo shopping center?
It's like right by there. Yes. Now, uh, Tuddy is back in the witch store. She realizes things are
going wrong here. It's just a store for witch things. In a store mall. Yeah, where the proprietor is
always wearing a flowing robe of some sort. And you're supposed to think nothing's up. This proprietor
they should have gone for like sissy space, or somebody a little nod to horror past. Yeah,
you know, somebody with a little something behind the eyes that made you wonder if they were okay.
Yeah, this lady's a little bland. And basically used to do all this shit. She was in
fucking blast from the past with Brendan Fraser. You want to talk about a bad movie?
Was that movie bad? Oh, Fraser could do no right back then. George at the jungle, uh,
Dudley do right. Dudley do right. More like Dudley do wrong, folks. Uh,
blast from the past, uh, mummy quick, uh, war of the scorpion emperors or whatever the fuck that
last mummy was called. Yeah. Yeah. Boy, I hated the mummy movies. I know a lot of people have some
love for them. I think you're probably a kid when you saw them as the only explanation I could think.
They're not bad movies. They're just, they just were at a time where CGI was not ready. Right. And
it's obvious. I mean, Lucas was the only guy at that time that could come even close to making it look
passable. Right. Anybody outside of that was, it was just like, it looked like made for to sci -fi shit.
Yeah. You know, played had some questionable effects as well. The first one. It does. It was
kind of on the line. It does. There's some bad blood effects in it. Yeah. But we'll talk about that
but uh, but yeah, but I'm looking forward to the blade discussion because I were special effects you've
seen in a, in a theatrical release. Uh, I thought final destination five's effects were so bad. It
I couldn't even keep watching it. I don't know. And people say that's a good horror movie. Uh,
Texas Chainsaw, the 3D one that came out a couple of years ago, horrific. Okay.
Terrific effects. Uh, those are the two that come to mine right now where I was, I was pissed off
at how bad I thought the effects look. I'm usually forgiving. It's been since the 90s since I've heard
people like laughing at effects. Well, what's giving me a bad one? I don't think my, my memory's going
to be good here. I don't know, but I mean, people would really like yuck it up in the theater.
I just, yeah, I don't know. Like I can't, uh, I'm trying to think like, yeah, I remember, yeah,
the Texas, I found the final destination five. I, I, again, I didn't finish watching it but I was
willing to give it a little more leeway because it's final destination. And, right, again, these are
horror movies that are sort of bred and, and spawned out of the sort of Dawson's Creek kind of thing.
And, you know, it, who cares, ultimately, like it, it wasn't the end of the world. Texas
chainsaw having computer animated effects in it. I found a wholly offensive, uh, to add,
there was no reason to add fake blood to Texas chainsaw. Right. Except for the fact that they wanted
it to be 3D. And they wanted, I guess, the blood to come out of the screen. But even then, no, because
there were plenty of horror movies that were made in 3D in the 80s. And they used real blood
and real objects and whatever. So I just was very, very offended by that. Have you seen that latest
Texas chainsaw that was like streaming leather face? The prequel? No, it got really bad reviews.
I saw a few that were all right. Um, I also didn't like that they called it leather face. There's
already been a Texas chainsaw sequel called leather face that was good. Um, I also don't need yet
another fucking prequel to these movies. Sure. Um, I remember just massively depressed by that
one with Jessica Biel. I just thought it was so relentlessly miserable that I, it's pretty miserable.
I like it. I wanted to be out of it. I liked it. But, uh, yeah, it's dark. I mean, it's not, you know,
but, uh, you know, I don't know. I just, I think I think they need to let the franchise go. I think
it's just there's, you're never going to recreate the magic that Toby Hooper created with the original.
You're never going to recreate the fun he he created with the sequel. It's just leave it alone. It's
just done. It's done. There's no way to get back to any of that. Uh, so I don't know. But, uh, I do
hear, and I'm very happy about this. I've been reading reviews of the latest hell razor film,
which comes out. I think in a week or so on Blu -ray, it's supposed to lead pretty good solid sequel.
First good sequel in a long time. Is it Clive Barker? It's not. But, and it's not Doug Bradley either.
It's pinhead. It's a new pinhead. But apparently the new pinhead is good. And apparently the movie is
a deserving sequel. And it harkens back to the original films much more than all these other sequels they
made that weren't so hot. The why and Bradley on it anymore is too old. He turned it he turned the last
two down. I understood why he turned down judgment. That was a terrible terrible movie. But I didn't get
why he turned down this one. And the director said it was over a non -disclosure agreement. Bradley said
he would read the script. They sent him an NDA and they said he got really pissed and refused to sign it.
Huh. And he was like, yeah, you know, basically like I am this fucking franchise. How dare you ask me to
sign an NDA like I'm offended. Okay. And the director was like, it's just kind of just like part for
the course, man. Like it's not right. Like, you know, I'm not trying to demean you. Yeah. So I don't know.
Oh, that's gross. Yeah, this is gross. This whole sequence. It's a lot of snakes and scorpions and worms
coming out of toes. This is kind of a playoff of which, which is a vestic. Yeah. Well, if you'll remember
Skidil Rick earlier called them the bitch of the vestic. He did? He did. I didn't see that. Did you like
which is a vestic? I love which is a vestic. Yeah, it's very under time. And this is similar.
It's from the director of Mad Max, the which is a vestic. This is similar. It's under. It's a group of
underdog women who are having a tough time. They start using magic to get ahead. It goes a little too far.
You know, Faruza Bulk is sort of the Nicholson character. Right.
But man, she's really, yeah, Bulk's Bulk's off the fucking rails.
She's, she's now telling, uh, Tuddy to kill herself. Did you like the witches with Angelica Houston?
I found that movie very entertaining. I own it. I think I love it. It's a wonderful kids film.
It's genuinely scary. Yeah. The witches are really scary in that movie.
I agree. They don't even do more kid stuff that's actually scary, man.
For some reason, that just stopped. I mean, unless, you know, kids are scared of things that were not
or something. But when I was kid, I was traumatized by the shit that it's still very scary,
including starring for Faruza Bulk. Return to us. The scariest of them all.
Return to us. Dark crystal. Yeah. Labyrinth. Uh, scary shit. Uh, you've pointed out before
little monster. That's terrified me. Yes. Sorry. I know. Come on. I'm teasing you. I'm teasing you.
So, uh, now, does Bulk have Campbell under a spell?
And true as well. Is that why they're following her?
It would appear that way. Now, I'm seeing a similar effect here to that episode of Perfect
Strangers where they're floating up in the ceiling. Yes. This is much like the haunted house episode
of Perfect Strangers. I wonder which influenced which.
I would think that this was inspired by Perfect Stranger. I think you're probably
right. I think most great horror movies are based on key episodes of sitcoms. Yeah. Yeah. That's
what I think. Pat, I'm really getting tired here. It's too long to talk. It's too long to talk.
People always request a return to the commentary format. I think because they enjoy
hearing us in a position of torment and torture. At what point are people saying I'm loving listening
to this? You know what? Like, like, at this point, they are for whatever reason they are. We did
on this show, the fucking shining, which is, let's say like two 30 or two 30. And I, in my mind,
by the end of that, it was unlistable, boring horse shit. And it gets sighted a lot. People love
the episode. I don't know. Now, here's the one thing I don't like about this film.
Oh, is the girls can, the witches can do anything they want. Yeah.
It's, there needs to be some limits to the powers. First of all, because making notes written by
Tutti appear out of thin air. Yeah. She's filling the house up with snakes. Like, you gotta come on.
You can't just do anything you think of. You know, I agree. You know, give it a, you know,
come on. Like, then, then there's no, that's like, look, she just cut her wrists from, she was floating
in the air and she slid her wrists open. Like, she's like, for us, the bulk slit Sarah's wrists open.
It's like, well, if you can do that, just cut her head off or something. Like, you, you made
skater would fall out of a window with your mind. Yeah. Just make her head explode or something if you
realize Faruza reminds me of Mary Elizabeth Ellis, who plays the waitress on always sunny,
and a very nice person. The wife of Mr. Charlie Dan. She is somebody else who I find has,
I've never met her. She's stunning. Dunning eyes. Beautiful. Beautiful person. Woman,
whatever you want to say. Eyes just, her eyes just, they sparkle like the Nile. Oh my god.
And I'll give you a recommend dish. Mary Elizabeth and Artemis Pepdoni, who played art plays,
Artemis on always sunny. Always one of my favorite characters. They used to do this show at UCB called,
it was a spoof of lifetime movies called Mother May I Sleep with Mary Jane's Fist.
And it was such a funny stage show and they did it with Tim and Eric producing on adult swim.
And it's extremely funny if you can find it. It is, they aired it as everything on adult swim
and aired once at midnight. I don't know if you can find it again. But it is about a young troubled girl
who is a ballet dancer played by Mary Elizabeth. Artemis is the instructor and Artemis starts
fisting her. And then at some point Mary Elizabeth starts really enjoying it and they form this
uneasy alliance. And it was just as fucked up as I remembered. I can't believe they aired it,
but I loved it. I loved it. I want to see it. And those two rode it, directed it all night.
Oh, I want to see it. It's great. It's great. All right. I'll have to start tuning into adult swim at
midnight. Yeah. Very dark. When did this come out? Very dark. I watched it about a month ago.
Oh, so it's new. That's correct. Oh good. Do you ever watch the Tim Heidecker murder trial?
No. I don't even know. I think it was, I think you made it for adult swim online or something. But
like, if you go on YouTube, you can just watch it. He just has a fake murder trial. I have not said
it's a lot of him. Just like, they shoot it like C -SPAN and everything. Right. It's a lot of him,
like leaning back and whispering to the lawyers and stuff. Okay. It's really weird. It's really
fucking weird. I like that. I mean, of course, I like the original show, but I also like bedtime
stories, which is their short horror anthology. Bedtime stories is great. It's very entertaining.
I also really like his cooking show that he did for Josh. I ain't seen that. It's what you think
it would be. It's him not knowing at all how to cook and make the most disgusting dishes. And then
calling them like party dips. Sure. We're going to show you to make Tim's party,
Thousand Island dressing. Yeah. And it's like, cuts up a head of lettuce and mixes it with man.
It's disgusting. I tend to not like the grosser aspects of their stuff, but
this is just food. It's just gross because it's food. You know what I mean? I do. I do. Do you
know? Now, Joe, I've been meaning to ask you about this for years now because your whole
desktop is up when we watch these things. Yeah. What is Seaky Muppets?
C -I -K -I Muppets? What is it? Is it a script? It's a segment we did. Seaky is C -I -K -I. That's
right. Muppets was a bit we did on the show that I wrote about. We would play Mark AGM,
myself wrote it, the producer or me. We would play a rapper's voice and then you'd have to guess
which Muppet he sounded like. Okay. Or like which Muppet matched his voice? Okay, got it. So one of
them was, or Jim Henson Creature really it was. So like one of them we played B -Rio from Cypress Hill
and then it was the skexies from the dark crystal. You know, it's like it was a funny bit.
All right. I think Ice Cube was the bear that, or the dog that played the piano.
Rolf. Rolf, who I used to make Blum. Yes. Yes. Oh, I forgot about that. Yeah. I'm sure Ice Cube
wouldn't like to hear that. Well, Ice Cube wasn't Rolf. He wouldn't even know what the hell you were
talking about. I know. I'm just, so now Sarah is making roaches come out of Farooza Bulk's jacket.
Pretty mild when you just slitter rests. And now she's turning her fingers into snakes. Right.
I mean, I don't know. It's just, there's a lot of gross out stuff here in the end. I mean,
it appears to me and I'm going to have to watch it without this commentary because I don't
remember any of it. It appears like a lot of things to be a movie that's really pretty interesting
and then just turns into a special effect deal. And if it's good and entertaining in this home stretch
great, but a lot of movies go this route and I tend to get bored with this shit. You have to do it.
People want the effects. I do agree that it's kind of just like we got to fill out the last 10
minutes. So let's do a bunch of weird effects that aren't really that weird. And then it's never
possible for me to give a shit when everything that's happening, risk cutting, snakes, hands, etc,
goes away in five seconds. How are you supposed to give a shit? Well, that's what I'm saying. It doesn't
mean anything. It doesn't mean they can do whatever they want. Right. Right now, she could have just
made herself because they sure he did it. Faruza bulk just could have made herself look like
Sarah the good guy. Yeah. And convinced the other girls that Sarah was on their team. Right.
You know what I mean? I do. I do. So now Sarah puts a binding spell
on Faruza bulk, which means I guess she can never do magic again.
And now Faruza bulk is trying to do. Could she just do a spell that says, wait, I can do magic?
Pat, I honestly don't know. Faruza bulk is waving a knife violently in Sarah's face.
There isn't one cut happening in this R -rated movie. There hasn't been one drop of blood in this
R -rated movie. Not literally not one. That would be true. So, you know, and then a dresser just
smashed her into the wall. Sarah, who was Tuddy. I'll say this. Rob and Tuddy was an empire records.
Remember that movie? I never saw it though. That was sort of the precursor to high fidelity. Sure,
mystic pizza at a record store. Rob and Tuddy is wearing a wig because she shaved her head for
empire records. She's wearing a wig in this movie. That's correct. Well, she's, that's a great wig.
I can't tell. Actress Faruza bulk is actually a wicking and real life. That's interesting. You gotta
deal with that. I know a dear friend of mine is a wicking and it's very positive religion actually.
I'm just not into it because it's a religion, you know. If you said to me, she's a Christian,
I'd really get it. The Sarah Gilbert character on my show is both wicking and a juggolo.
She's a juggolo. Wow. Though she cites those as sort of equal religious influences in her life.
The director Andrew Fleming, who I'm pretty sure also did Dick, which is a very entertaining movie.
You ever see Dick? It's like all the president's man with cursed and dunce. Yeah, I know. Isn't a David...
No, Bruce McCullough is in that. Dave Full is in it too. I was going to say David's
best fade. But doesn't McCullough play Bernstein? I think so. I mean, it was a crazy idea.
Did McCullough direct no kids know nothing about Nixon?
Dick McCullough directed it. Andrew Fleming, the guy who did this movie directed it.
McCullough wrote it then. McCullough had something to do with it. I don't think.
But Andrew Fleming says a PG -13 rating was sought. They followed all the guidelines to earn that
rating. But in the final outcome, the film was rated are simply because it dealt with teenage girls using
witchcraft. How about that? As opposed to what? I don't know. They just thought it would be a bad
influence. There's no way that's a wig she's wearing, by the way. Look at her hair. You can see it
connected to her scalp. That's not a wig. They're saying it's a wig. I don't know what that is. Maybe
she's got extensions in. Maybe. Or maybe they like weave to wig into regular hair. But I mean,
Jesus Christ, you can see the hair sprouting out of her fucking neck. See that to me looks like a wig.
I mean, they can get them right. Can they? Yeah. Yeah. All the teen actresses were in their 20s at
the time of filming and Rachel Tru was 30. She's 30 years old. The black girls. Yeah. She's 30?
That's correct. Jesus. She looks younger than anybody else. I know.
A lot of fun facts. Though the song, How Soon Is Now, was originally performed by this mess. Love
spit love. You got to wave your cock and everybody's facing. Nobody needs it. Nobody seems to
complain. Angelina Jolie auditioned and not get the role. Seems like she should have
done it. Same year as Nev Campbell and Skidolder did scream. All right. There were plans to release
a direct DVD sequel, focusing on Ferruza Bach, but those plans were dropped for unknown reasons.
So the movie ends with Bach in an insane asylum. Yeah. And so yeah, that would be a good sequel.
If she gets out of the crazy house and then you know starts fucking wrecking shit, right? Right.
I'd be into that. I agree. The movie ends with her strap to a bed saying I'm flying. I'm flying.
I can fly. That's dark. Yeah. So she doesn't die. Yeah. Okay. Well, that's good. They could have brought
her back. And Andrew Fleming also did Hamlet II with Steve Cougan, which is fucking hilarious.
I heard it's a great movie. Hamlet II was fucking hilarious if you haven't seen that. And it's
weird. He's a comedy guy. He did like Lady Dynamite, Red Oaks, difficult people, some really funny
shows. But Hamlet II was his last movie, crazily. What happened to him? I don't really win
to television. It appears and he directs the best of TVcom. And the writer was Andrew Fleming,
not Bruce McCullough of Dick had nothing to do with the film, Joe. All right. Well, I'm just
wanted to get all those your wrongs out before we wrap. Well, folks, that's our show. The credits are
rolling. Folks, I think we've proved what we don't do the commentaries were fantastic for an hour.
And then really treadwater till the end. And if we had done fucking Jackie Brown or Goodfellas,
there'd still be an hour to go. But this is for you guys, and we hope you enjoy it.
Thank you very much. We'll see you next time. We'll see you in hell.