Summer is here, and Bed MDM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer.
Or check out our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz, only available
at Bed MDM Casino.
Spin on Spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 fortunes, Mystery of the Lamp, Raken
Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bed MDM Casino right from the palm of your hand.
Download the Bed MDM Casino app today and get a piece of the action.
Bed MDM game sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices. Bedmgm .com for teases and seeds, 21 plus to wager.
Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania, and West Virginia only, games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as normal throwable site credit slash bonus best unless otherwise
provided in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamber.
The football season is full of guarantees.
And here's another, no other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October,
if your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning or winning money back in fan cash,
guaranteed. Switch to fanatic sportsbook, winning hits different here.
Must be 21 plus, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamber.
Offer not available in all states, terms apply, see fanatic sportsbook app.
Howdy folks, welcome to, we'll see you in hell.
My name is Joe DeRosa, and I'm here with Pet Walsh to bring you the news and the latest and the
greatest and all your favorite. John Reflix, today we discuss, stragged across concrete.
I know it was supposed to be pet cemetery, but that's coming next week we promise.
Plus, it's a new one, gives you a little more time to see it.
To be honest, I ain't seen it yet. I was going to see it this morning, but we pulled a ui
and went with this. No, he didn't mix it, is that okay? I did it already.
All right, I want to make sure everyone can hear each squeak of cons ball.
Sack, that was directed at cons, who is being a little noisy.
He's an annoying dog sometimes.
How are you, Walsh? Well, I mean, better than you, Joe, it sounds like.
I walked in, I said, how are you, Joe? He said, I wish I was dead.
Yeah, now everybody calm down. I'm not going to kill myself for anything like that.
Let's all just pump the brakes, but it's just, you know, one of those moods where you're just like,
every day, I go on Instagram today. That's part of the problem.
I go into it for my phone. I got to take it. If these fucking gigs, if I didn't have to plug
these fucking gigs, you know what, I might just stop plugging them.
You know, it's like, it doesn't do anything.
You know, it doesn't look good to the clubs and so forth.
I'm really starting to not give shit. Why do I get followed by so many comedy clubs?
I don't know. I mean, it's like I was ever like a fixture on the LA comedy scene. I did stand up
30 times. You were one of the most famous groupies in LA comedy history.
They all talk about sucking and fucking you.
I'm a chucklefucker, they call it. Yeah, comedy groupie.
Anyway, I go on Instagram today.
You ready for this? Yes.
I see an account for Leo the cat who is one of the four cats that plays church in the new
Pet Sematary movie. You follow Leo? No, I just saw, you know, how it tells you like, people you
should be following. Yeah, yeah. I click. So right there was that the depressing part that you
should be following. That's the beginning of it. Okay. I click on it in a month's time.
This cat is generated almost an equal amount of followers that has taken me six years
of constant posting and whatever else to amass. I mean, it's the second week in a row. You're upset
about somebody else's Instagram followers. You need to definitely even at my weirdest obsession with
these stupid things. I never was like, how do I not have more followers than this cat?
Well, I mean, but I mean, doesn't that put a star? He's a movie star. Let alone a cute cat.
You're neither. You're not a movie star. You're not a cute cat. That's your answer.
I'm a cool cat. Doesn't that go for anything these days? You're a cool cat with two
keys, of course. Just what a world are we living in? What's happening? What's a sick world?
That's everything unfair. Nothing is right. From the top on down, nobody's in the position they're
supposed to be in. The untalented rise. That almost sounded like an old Dylan lyric.
For the time. Oh, down. No, this isn't. It should be in the untalented rise. Then everybody's
gotta pretend like it's a good song because the lyrics are decent. Don't sticks. I like him.
I have not listened to a Bob Dylan album in five years. I had a period. I was never obsessed.
I need a melody at the end of the day. Jesus Christ. It's got a sing, baby.
Some guy talk it over a fucking acoustic guitar. Yeah. Is it ever done a Bob Dylan impression?
No. Nobody ever does is nickel sin. We're walking. Yeah. That's gonna be my three. When I finally put
myself out to pasture and become a cruise ship comedian, when I finally just surrender to it, those will
be the three impressions I've worked on. And Joe, then the Instagram followers will come.
Because you'll have dumped yourself down to America's level. Smash cut to me on a cruise ship
screaming at an audience. What do you want me to do lick my own asshole? Is that what'll get me
followers as fucking cat? Yeah. Pants down, straining your neck to reach your exposed asshole.
Then your neck creaks and freezes in that position. End of the movie credits roll.
Folks, were we in the middle of a story that really jumped around? You're not doing well as
what you said. I'm just depressed. I'm not. And when I say I wish I was dead, I say it, you know,
I'm speaking euphemistically. I don't, I'm not gonna kill myself or anything. I feel like you
need to say that these days. You said it several times. Yeah. But I mean, well, I feel like you really
have to say it because he thinks the lady doth protest too much. You know, you tweet out
these days, somebody writes on Twitter like, yeah, feeling a little blue. And then people are sending
you like hotline numbers and shit. Right. You know, I'm just, I'm just, you know, I'm speaking euphemistically.
I'm just, I'm just, you know, it's a bummer. Everything's just kind of a bummer, man. I don't know.
People also do like feeling a little blue could use some support in the DMs or something. I mean,
look, please reach out where you need it. But when I see people reaching out to their Twitter
followers to like talk them out of killing themselves, I'm like, you need a stronger support system,
my friend. Yeah, you need a pal. You can call on the damn phone. You need a Joe, if I may. And I'm sure
you would say on me, I would. I would say and I'd be referring to myself. Yes. The, uh, no. Yeah.
I mean, well, that's, I think that's part of why I'm sad. It's like, this world, everything is so twisted
up. Like it's like, yeah, I get very depressed at the sterilization of, uh, of, you know,
sort of culture and society and interaction. And the fact that there is so much levity put on the
social media now. I mean, that's why I depressed. I don't give a fuck that people don't want to
follow me. What I care about is is some asshole in a fucking office somewhere looks at that and goes,
sorry, man, you know, I'm enough, you know, I'm enough going on here. And it's like, dude,
when did this become the, the complete worth or value of a human being? It's fucking insane.
And then if you're an up and coming comic, who just wants to avoid it, like, not be on social media and
hone your craft, I wonder if you can make it anywhere because they just feel like you don't exist.
Yeah, it's not. You would know better than I. I don't know. Well, I mean, I told you I'd deactivated
my Twitter account months ago. Yeah. And I recently went back on and I was going to, in a moment of,
I don't want to say weakness, but in a, in a, in a, in a, you know, there was a
fleeting moment where I said, you know what? Let me go back on and activate this thing so I don't lose
all the followers and everything. Right. And then I can deactivate it again. Who cares?
And I went on and activated it for like 10 seconds and I was gone. Oh, my followers were gone.
So it's officially over like I don't have a Twitter account anymore. Huh. I thought
that couldn't have. No, I think don't they come back over time? I think if you were to reactivate it
that it would take a while, but they would come back. And it's like some weird glitch.
Oh, is that what I might be wrong? I saw somebody complaining about that the other day.
My followers and following were at zero. Well, well, maybe it's not, but it doesn't matter.
Like the, I get, I'm actually more disheartened to hear that than it might just be a glitch because I was
like, okay, that's closure. It's done. Right. That's it. Um, I saw this gentleman on Twitter, um,
who's always just kind of going after targets, basically. And he makes great points.
Stores, you mean the what? The stores. Yes. Yes. He's had it. Yeah. But you know, he's a funny
guy. He was a writer for a while and can't seem to find work and just exposes. I know why you can't
find work. He exposes the hypocrisies, the lies, the bullshit amongst people across the industry.
From the top of the pops, the appetals, you know, all the way down. Okay. And uh, do you know who
this guy is? Are you just not saying his name? I could say his name is a very, his name is Jack
Allison. He goes by Jack Allison, LOL on Twitter. Okay. I've never met him. Um, but I like his work.
You know, he's always like, Hey, at Adam McKay, and I'll be like, interesting that you claim to be
on the side of the working man when I wrote an entire Will Ferrell Toyota campaign for you and made
like $400 and they aired on tell, you know, like he does shit like this all day. Good for him.
And good for him. That was a real one. By the way, I didn't make that up. The only thing that
might be wrong is, is the Toyota. But, you know, they'll get on their platform and start going off
about how they're, you know, Aptower, whoever it may be. And I'd be like, interesting because
and summer stories from his own career, summer things. He's read summer articles. And the people
get very mad because he's almost always correct. And these people cannot handle being called in their
ship. So McKay really, because no one calls him on the ship because why would you call out
somebody who's like the biggest voice in comedy, but this guy does. And I think that's why he, you know,
he struggles, but he's a fascinating guy. He's had a lot of great stuff to say on the writers' guild.
But he had a huge battle with a bunch of showrunners recently, because this showrunner was saying,
just so you know, showrunners definitely read your Twitter to decide if they want to hire you or not.
If you're going to talk shit about somebody's like movie with a third act problem or something,
just be aware it could be a potential hire or they could be a good friend of a potential hire.
This is a small business, small world. And A, it made me want to delete this entire podcast.
But B, I was like, huh, something about that doesn't seem fair to me as I read it.
And I'm a showrunner when I read people's samples. I didn't go to their Twitter and like search my name
and see if it ever said anything bad about something I wrote for. I've said bad shit about things
I write for. Who cares? But this guy, Jack Allison, really starts going after it and was like, how dare you?
Like police people's Twitter and wouldn't you want somebody in your staff who has the balls to say to you
there's a third act problem. Right. You want you just want to ruin people saying everything you do is
amazing. That seems to be what all these showrunners want. Right. And it's not what I want. But it is
something that you struggle with in these in writers rooms, I would say, guys, it's not helping me at all
to say your draft was perfect. Right. Like we all talk about each other's drafts and fix it. I need
that same process. Right. I'm not perfect. You know, and it takes a couple of times saying that
to break down people's defenses and have them say, yeah, I think we could do better here or there
because it's the boss. And I think you're going to be pissed. That's not a way to run anything,
especially a collaborative effort like comedy. I thought it was a very interesting argument. And I
think you should be allowed to say what you want, tweet what you want. If you're going out for a job
on the Conners and you've got 8 ,000 tweets about how much the Conners sucks, well, then that's
different. Yeah. That's different. But to search back in like in 2012, he said something bad about a show
I created. It's like, that isn't fair. It isn't fair. Well, it's also, I mean, you know, I've had in
passing, you know, people say to me about this show, you know, man, you know, you guys really hate
on a lot of stuff. It's like, dude, nobody's hating on anything. Yeah. We're given honest reviews of
things. And sorry, that's how this works. If it sucks, you're allowed to say it sucks. It's nobody's
looking to shit on anything. Nobody's looking for something to be terrible. I mean, aside from me with
Marvel movies, but, you know, like nobody's looking for any of that. Like it's just, it's that's what
criticism is. That's, that's how it works. And there are plenty of artists out there that
double was critics. I mean, Kevin Smith does it all the fucking time. You know, and Kevin Smith
will unabashedly go after movies he's friends are in and be like, this thing is fucking joyless this
picture. Like, you know, like, yeah, I mean, I, I think you should be able to, although I get that
artists quote are sensitive people and things are going to bother you and so forth. But it's just like
how much are we going to take away? To what point is it just going to be everyone going like, I
love everything. Everything about this was amazing. That's not a conversation that holds any interest
from me. And it is like when you go to brunch with people in LA, it's like, did you all see the
premiere of Stranger Things, the entire table in Unison says, yes, we always really liked great. I
don't think you got a shit on everything. We're not going to be shitting on today's movie. I can
tell you that much. Well, but yeah, it's like talking about stuff and then, you know, that's my
probably a feel. You speak honestly about it. But we live in this, this, the climate right now
is this bullshit celebratory thing. Everybody's a fucking champion. Everybody's a winner. And you know,
if anybody says something slightly negative about you or your project or whatever it is,
you've been victimized and it's not fair and it's close. We have lost, we have just completely lost
an ability to understand what criticism is supposed to be. And on top of it, when you are somebody
that's willing to speak honestly about how you think or feel about things, a lot of the times you get
this fucking label put on you that you're that you're a pariah or that you're negative or that you're
that. And it's like, yeah, sorry, I don't have my head up my own ass and yours 24 hours of fucking
day. Right. Telling you that, you know, it's, it's sunny and, and smells great up there. It's just,
it's just fucking crazy, man. It's just, ah, this is see, this is, now we're back to the beginning.
This is why I'm in a mood. It's like, I'm just, everything sucks. Where's the fucking action at,
man? Where's the danger? Where's the fun? You know, nobody's fucking, where he's living
fucking health. Everybody sucks. Folks, welcome to. We'll see you now. It's time to get on with the show
and on with the Joe. Thank you for shaking and helping with that tambourine accompaniment. Come,
you made it sound a little better than it would have. I had nothing. There are times where he'll do
that, right, when at a key moment, when I'm like trying to tell somebody something. Yeah. And boy,
if you don't want to sell a dog out of window, sometimes when he does it, um, uh, good to see,
Walsh, uh, let's, this is not a screen. Let's, let's call this little thing just right here, a bonus
screaming in. Yeah. Because I've got some stuff for the actual screaming, man. When we get to it, but
I just want to talk about speaking of hating on shit. As I say, nobody's allowed to criticize
anymore. Hellboy remake. 10 % on rotten tomatoes. I don't, uh, pay attention to a scribe too or have
an interest in a rotten tomato score. Uh, it is getting bad reviews. It's getting terrible reviews.
Story broke today courtesy of a movie web that apparently the, the remake was, was riddled with
reshoots, rewrites and David Harbor had walked off set a few times like because it was too many
takes. I mean, I can't imagine shooting an entire movie in that makeup. It's got to be fucking hell.
Hellboy. Yeah. So, uh, but anyway, uh, apparently this thing is, is not good. It sounds like they tried
to go for a sort of Deadpool, uh -huh, which I guess is how the, I never read the Hellboy comics, but
they said like, it's just profanity and gore to a point of like violence rather to a point of
just like, like, it's ridiculous, you know, it's, it's, uh, it just, it's, to, to, to its own
detriment. So, uh, it sounds like they went for something that didn't work. I really liked the original
one that Del Toro did. And I thought Pearlman was a perfect Hellboy. I found them both relatively
entertaining. Uh, I'm not going to say this no one. I don't care. I just don't care.
I don't understand why you don't just do a continuation of the Pearlman, of the
Pearlman movies with Pearlman. Why do you reboot it with a new actor? It's a guy caked in makeup.
He could be 90 years old on it. It doesn't matter. I think Pearlman's a little annoyed as well.
I mean, it's just, you know, if you need to recast the people around him or whatever, okay, fine.
I mean, I, I don't think you should, but, but you know, it's like, dude, just do the fucking,
just keep it in that universe and have Del Toro produce it or whatever. I mean, I guess maybe he didn't
want to. I don't know. Del Toro couldn't get the third movie made. Yeah. He couldn't get it made.
Right. And then they're like, no, we're going to do a new one with the guy that
six people know from stranger things. I do find that very odd. And I don't think any of those people
know that guy's name. No. And it's very weird to me. And I'm a David Harbor fan. I think he's
great. But I mean, that the, you know, he's not a household. He's one of these guys where somebody
just decided he's going to be famous. Right. And they're just, they're just going to push it now.
Well, I mean, publicists do that. But he's a good, solid character actor. I think he's great.
I don't know why we need to do all this. Do what? You know, make the man hell boy.
Oh, yeah. No, I think he's, I think he's great. That man, what was the trail? Because we saw it
right before dragged across concrete the jokes. This poor bastard that they're making them say in this
movie where he's like, she's like, we're meant to be together. And he's like, no, we're not because
I'm a Leo. And you're a crazy bitch. You know, like that's like one of the bits and the,
that's actually better than what it was. But that's the, the warm up guy on two broke girls used to have
that joke. He would go, you know, you know, my ex -wife and I recently split up over religious
differences. She was a Protestant. No, I'm a Protestant. And she was Satan. It's the same joke.
Boy, hell boy, stealing from the two broke girls warm up there. You're good. And then he,
and then my favorite take on that is the guy fucks it up. I just fucked it up. Yeah. But he's trying to
do like this cute little benign joke. And problem is she was a Protestant. Fuck. And then he just
has a full on meltdown just screaming profanities at an audience waiting to see two broke girls.
I used to open my, when my band would play in college, I would walk up to the microphone and say,
just flew in from the coast. And boy is my plane tired. Fuck. And then we would start playing.
It's a good, good kickoff. It is. I thought you were saying it really. Fuck. And then it'd be like,
two, three, four. We weren't British, but you know, bad. Yeah. Hey, ho. Let's go. That was your
opening right? Yes. We would, uh, we were the Ramones. I was Patrick Ramone. Uh, you want to dance
us down to the corner? I do. But first I'd like to ask you, Joe, why you told Lori Laughlin,
and Felicity Huffman to do what they did. I've finally, I've been answered for this question.
Quite frankly, I was sick of both of them. And it worked. Yeah. Now we're rid of them. Felicity Huffman
played. I don't know anything about Felicity Huffman. I've seen her in a couple movies. Trans -America.
A very trans -America. Trans -America. Yeah. I think she's a very good actor. Uh, she is. Uh, but she plays,
there's an arc on Frazier. Yeah. Where he dates her and she plays the most horrible human being on
earth. Okay. So convincingly that I'm like, that's, that's coming from somewhere. Right. Uh,
there's an amazing, amazing episode of Frazier where, uh, he starts to get serious with her. Yeah.
And he wants to back away. And at the beginning of the episode, he's talking to Niles about it. Niles
is like, you need to commit to commitment. You need to stop looking for these flaws in these people.
Right. She's perfectly fine. I'm sure. So Frazier sleeps with her immediately. He's like, you're my
girlfriend. Like, starts planning trips to like Italy with her. Uh, then the family comes over. And
she just, she's just the worst human being in the whole episode is Kelsey Grammer trying to like,
put the face on and be like, this is the woman I love. And there's a great scene where she's in the
bathroom. And he's like, he's like, yes, she's, she's wonderful. Gone are the days where I would have
said I've made a ghastly mistake. It's really, it's a really, really, really fucking funny episode.
She eventually chokes on a peanut. Nobody tries to help her. Uh -huh. It's a wild ride.
I sort of abandoned it around season three. I got to get back in. This is in the last season.
This is like one of the final episodes. Okay. Uh, not final, but, you know, it's in the, it's
in the final season. Anyway, uh, Lori Loughlin, I have a, less of an opinion about it. All I know
her is the full house lady. I've never seen her anything else. I would like to say, uh, speaking of
Frazier, um, I wrote a cool kids very much in the mold of Frazier at the kind of a door slamming
farce, a lot of misunderstandings and shit. Um, and that will air this Friday, thinking ahead of
when we're airing this, that will air this Friday. So check it out. Great. Uh, it's a really funny one.
Good episode. We're seeing it. Um, Lori Loughlin, the star of rad, a BMX biking movie that uh,
oh, really? I absolutely loved. Contains a scene where the, the, the, the hero crew Jones
has his arms wrapped around her waist from behind and she's a little like looking out and she's like
crew. This is the most beautiful scenery anyone's ever shown me. Thank you for taking me here.
There was an open sewer pipe in the back of the shot. That's how hilariously bad the movie
ran. Now you don't think that that was, uh, you know, a metaphor shot. No, there was a director was
about, I mean, you haven't seen this thing. Please check it out.
Uh, all right. Let's take us over to Pat's movie corner. I saw the beach bum. Oh, nice.
I was at Harmony Karin's new movie starring Matthew McConaughey, Jonah Hill, uh, I love Fisher,
Snoop Dogg, and Martin Lawrence. Um, it was insane. But like,
I don't like the, the films of Harmony Karin. I, I see them all
except I found springbreakers to be a masterpiece. I saw it in theaters three times.
I was smoking a lot of weed at the time. But I fucking love springbreakers. I still throw it on
all the time. I think it's just perfect. Um, the beach bum, I thought was going to be like a companion
piece. It looked like it was exactly the same movie, but with McConaughey. And it just, it feels like
scenes that you'd watched deleted. It feels like a whole deleted subplot from springbreakers that was
rightly left on the cutting board. Is it a comedy? Yes, it barely limps to like feature length.
Uh, McConaughey is doing his thing. Uh, you know, he's just a complete wash up. His wife
is kind of cucking him with Snoop Dogg. Snoop Dogg is good in the movie. There's a 20 minute segment
where Martin Lawrence and, and McConaughey go out on a boat and they're like chasing dolphins.
And I mean, it's how's Martin Lawrence rough stuff ever seen him in a part like that. He's not good.
You know, I mean, I can't say he's not good. He's fine. He's doing his thing. But like,
he just wish it was better for him to finally go away from these big like 20 million
dollar movies and try something. It's like why this? No, tell me five bad boys stories about to come.
Yeah, that's true. I'm excited. But um, all the pieces are there. I love just, there's
something I love about a sleazy, fun, trashy movie. It was beautifully shot like all a harmony
Karen's bigger budget stuff is. It just doesn't quite work. All right, fair enough. I'm not going to rush
to say it, but I do want to say it. Speaking of a movie that does work
in very much in the vein of a Karen style movie, a predecessor if you will. Well, Karen is known
for kids, famous coming of age movie, but 10 or 15 years before kids was a little film called
Suburbia. You've never seen it. Penelope's Ferris directed it, right? Yes, who also directed all the
decline of Western civilization and Wayne films and Wayne's world and also the Beverly Hillbillies.
Yeah. Which he also wrote. Yeah, that was weird. It's a weird choice. But anyway,
she's really wonderful. This movie is one of the most depressing films I've ever seen, but it
is a fucking fantastic, fantastic film. It's a coming of age piece about like gutter punks and
Los Angeles in the early 80s. It is a thing that Penelope does with her films and she does this in
documentaries, obviously, but she somehow figured out a way to transfer it to scripted stuff too,
which is not easy to do. The film doesn't tell you what to think. It doesn't tell you really who's
right or who's wrong. You just kind of come out of this thing feeling like a camera was just
set on some people and they showed you what really happened. And a lot of that is very disturbing.
But they're, but after these disturbing sequences, there is no sort of, but the moral here is this
or here's the reckoning for that bad behavior. It's, I guess, ultimately in the film you could say
that there is some of that, but it's just an amazing capturing of what I assume life was like for
people like this at that time period. I assume she came out of that scene because she seems to know
it like the back of her hand. So uncompromising, if you will, is this vision?
And it's a great flick. It's worth seeing, man. It's really worth watching. It really laid the
groundwork for the movies like kids and that sort of stuff. It's on Hulu, right? I think it is. I can't
remember where I was. I think they also have dudes, which was Penelope's various as like follow -up to it.
And it's got John Cryer. I think I'm going to watch both. I'll do a double feature.
Dudes is more of a buddy road movie, isn't it? I believe, but I think that's also Spheras.
Yeah, no, I think it is. And they look super punk like they have giant mohawks.
Yeah. Yeah. Anyway, Suburbia, check it out. It goes under a different title sometimes.
Yeah, because there's the Bogosian movie as well, which is linked later.
Yeah, with what's his face? I was going to say, we're busy. Yeah.
I've never seen that. I've heard it's good. Bogosian stuff is usually pretty fun to watch. So
I'd like to see it, but I'm not talking about that one. I'm talking about the other one.
Okay. Interesting. I thought two movies couldn't have the same title, but then sometimes they do.
Well, I don't know if that's what I was saying. Suburbia's got some alt titles to it, so I don't know.
Anyway, folks, I saw stop making sense at the will turn the talking heads. Nice.
Live concert directed by Jonathan Demi. Have you seen this, Joe? You seen this thing?
I have not seen it. All right, man, I saw it years ago. I was kind of stoned like in college,
you know, but I haven't rake. I absolutely love the talking heads to get to see them live in like
their ultimate prime with this amazing, like funk backup band singers, dancers, you know, keyboardists,
several guitarists. It is, I think easily the best concert movie of all time. I don't think anything
comes even close to it, but I would say seeing it at the theater, and I went out, we talked about this
little last week, is a requirement, whether you even like the, obviously, if you like the talking
heads, you're going to like it more, but it's a requirement. I had a giant grin on my face the entire
time. People were fucking dancing. People were having fun. People were clapping after every number.
Sounds fun. The movie is one of Demi's best. Opens with, of course, David Burnt. I used to watch it
over and over when I was a little kid. First cool music I got into. Used to roller skate around
in my basement, listening to the talking heads. The weird kid. I'll say it. But David Burnt walks out.
He sets up a boom box to play a little drum beat. He's playing an acoustic guitar and he does
psycho killer by himself. Then out comes the bassist, Tina Weymouth. She joins them. He just shows
you like building a song. So each new song, they add a new element. Then the drums come out. You
know, like, oh, it's like a three piece punk band. Like how the talking heads got their start. Then
out come the backup singers. Then by the end, you've got like this giant like funk collective playing
these incredible songs. Everything sounds amazing. I can't recommend it enough. A plus plus plus.
This is the best music concert documentary film ever made. Does burning down the house play a pivotal
point in this, have a pivotal point in the set list? Is that like the first full band number
or something like that? Yeah, it's up there. It's early. It gets a huge response. The audience
shots are great when they never really come. It's like they don't cut to the audience to the last
song because they're like, why would you ever want to go away from how amazing this band is?
Right. And you know, burn kind of set up the whole movie with Demi. So like they've choreographed
everything so carefully and the cameras are coming in. When they wheel in new like little sets,
you get like a cruise I view while the song's going on of like the crew pushing out the new set.
All these little touches, it shots so well. Can't recommend it highly enough. If you've never seen it,
do yourself a favor. If you've never seen it at a theater, do yourself a big favor. Very cool. Excuse me.
I watched Joe Bob. The new last driving series is really great. I watched the premiere. I've not seen
the latest. I watched both. Well, I didn't watch society in the second. I've already seen society.
Never seen them. What's the other one? Cue the wing serpent. Never seen that. That's what I watched
because in the chat episode he talked about how Cue the wing serpent was the, you know, was a Larry
Cohen masterpiece and how it was the superior version of Chad. And I agree. Cue was a lot of fun.
It's a wild fucking movie. It's crazy. I mean, there's about a fucking drag and flying around
New York, decapitating people. Yeah. But it's, it's a really killer movie and the thing that everybody
talks about or that is it's most noted for is Michael Moriarty's performance in it. Rex Reed apparently
said in the middle of all this Dreck, you have this astonishing method performance by Michael
Moriarty. He said that's one of the producers of the film. And the producer goes, well, the Dreck
was all my idea. But anyway, you know, and they didn't hate each other people because you people
could just talk like that at one point. Yes. Anyway, there there was a it was it was a really fun
watch. It was a really, really fun watch. I watched it tonight because I'm excited to see the new
Joe bomb. Yeah. And then of course, as we've said before watching it with Joe Bob is just a treat.
I turned my mom on to Joe Bob Briggs and she loves him. Great. She loves him. She had never heard
of him. And then she said, do you think it's weird that a 71 year old lady likes this stuff? And I
was like, well, I gotta be honest, man, I don't think he's that much younger than you. No, he's
right. He's late 60s. Yeah, I was like, you're seeing right eye to eye with this guy. Yeah.
And he's I just love how edgy the guy is. I love that he's pushing buttons. And I wish when you
get into those like movie 10 of 13 on the original marathon, because now I finally watched the whole
marathon. My God, I'm like, are they going to come in and shut this down? But he's got his opinions
and he's saying him. It's funny. Um, he's just an awesome guy. Yeah. The the Q the wing serpent one
opens with him going. He's like, what's the biggest faux pod driving movie? Having your headlights on
coming in late with your headlights on. Yeah. And every time we catch a guy with his headlights on,
the guy'd say, I didn't know how to turn them off. That was always his excuse. Some jackass and a nice
fancy car. I didn't know how to turn them off. Yeah. Well, let me tell you something pal. We'll figure
out a fucking way to permanently turn them off. And then you can drive back to Fort Worth like that.
Let's see if you learn your God. You're like, you know, I like that he's like a beer swillin. You
know, yeah, shit kicking dude. Like he's, you know, I don't know if shit kicking is derogatory. I
don't mean it to be. It's not. Uh, I'm a huge fan. Uh, if people love being told that they
kick shit, you know, I am a huge fan. And this being on shutter right now, it's, it's why, you
know, people are going back to vinyl and all this shit. Like, hey, it, you know, the simple reason is
it reminds you of your childhood. But like, it's just there's something about it that's like of a
simpler time watching these old movies with this guy. It reminds me of being a kid. I just love it.
It's why I go back and watch all the old sitcoms. Yes. Rewatching married with children now. Yes.
And this joke bear is repeating because you did laugh heartily when I texted to you. But uh,
great sight gag. Episode opens. Peggy's reading the national inquirer and the front page of it just
says joke found in Howie Mandel's act. That's good. That's good. Yeah. Anyway. Uh, and then my third,
I watched a documentary based on a book that I had read called full service. The story of Scotty
Bowers. Um, and now the movie is for some reason not called full service. It is called Scotty and the
secret history of Hollywood. Scotty Bowers is a very interesting character. He's about 90 at this point.
He is a guy who ran or worked at a gas station right up here on like Hollywood near Taitown. Hollywood
Boulevard. Okay. It's no longer there. Now it's that big firehouse. And firehouse. There's a firehouse
of Hollywood Boulevard. Right. But not not all the way down to Grommons, but about halfway. And he
would facilitate gay sex for closeted actors, closeted people, but little by little, it worked
its way up and people talked to people and one thing led to another. And then some of the biggest stars
in Hollywood were coming to this gas station. And Scotty Bowers was going over to their house and
bringing his dudes and then dudes. There's like a pimped for guys. Pimp for guys. He claimed to be
bisexual. He's married to a woman now. I get the feeling he's gay, but who knows. Sexuality is a
fluid thing. And he basically hooks up. Man, Carrie Grant Spencer Tracy. You know, Carrie Grant
was dipping his toe on that pool. I didn't know that. Well, Carrie Grant lived with Randall Scott in a
mansion for about five years. And there's pictures of them like swimming together. And everyone was
just like, these two really are good friends. Now I thought he lived with Willard Scott. No,
as the actor Randall Scott, they were gay couple, but they go into this shit. All right. You know, like
Cole Porter, the songwriter, he's like, Cole Porter would call me up and say, I want to suck off
15 guys one after the other. Just line him up. So I'd call up my boys and we'd go out. You know,
there's a lot of great kind of salacious stories. However, there's something about the book
that I just sort of found this like fascinating alternate history to Hollywood documentary is sort of
weird and like seen the guy makes it weird because the guy is stranger than he seems in the book. And
what I found out about it is that they keep pushing this question of, should you be writing this
fucking book? Like these guys trusted you. They're dead. They have families. Why are you doing
that? It's a shitty thing to do, I think. And he's going, you know, he's got these book signings and
he keeps getting lambasted. Like, so the book is just the story of the book. And the documentary is
sort of the story of the book, but also the aftermath of it. And it made it much less enjoyable to me
because I guess it makes you think about the moral issues of it. But you know, like they're like,
don't you think these people's families are upset? And he's like, why there's nothing to be ashamed
about about being gay? Like, yeah, but you know, you start up to you to decide your choice and there's
90 -year -old relatives out there who are like, I don't want to hear this about my son. You're messing
up families and so forth. He was like, no, I feel like I'm doing a good service. And it's like,
you weren't, you weren't maybe doing a good service back in the day. But I don't know what a
pimple needs to do when he can't pimple anymore. Yeah. Making money by pimping still in a different
way. That's what you're doing. I mean, it's the same reason I remember it was all rightly pissed at
Perez Hilton when he used to like out people. And it's like, dude, we finally rid of that guy.
By the way, you're going to have somebody kill themselves or something. She's still around.
He is, yeah, very much still around. I think he's a scumbag. But you know, sort of a more
moralistic discussion than the book. I do recommend the book. But you know, why was I reading it?
It's like salacious details about, you know, it's the reason anyone reads any of those. It's why I read
the superhead book, Confessions of a Video Vixen. You know, sometimes you want to hear some trashy
taudry tales. And it serves that purpose. But there's also sort of a queasy moral aspect to it that I
didn't love. All right. I'm going to skip my third in the interest of getting over to scream
in and as we run a little long time here. There's a big screaming in for me. People, I'm not one to pat
myself on the back. Okay. But I got to say when I'm right, I'm right. Two days ago story was released.
Again, I got this courtesy of movie web. Thank you guys for giving movie news.
Sometimes I believe it or not that wasn't a paid ad. Yeah. Sometimes I gripe about them. And you
know, sometimes they're a little sensationalist. But sometimes they do it, you know, spot on. Netflix
or old friends Netflix are trying to actively purchase the Egyptian theater here in Hollywood. They
are trying to purchase that really broke my heart. Yeah. I go there at least once a month and see a
double feature. I've had some amazing nights there. And this really sucks. So as I said last week,
now we, you know, our last episode, or maybe it was the one before we now go into a deeper circle of
hell with Netflix. It started as we provide you with any movie you want. We'll hook you up. We're
the Scotty at the gas station. Yes. Then Scotty starts saying, just I'll suck your dick and do all
that shit for you. All right. Just let me do it. We'll provide the content. We'll make the content
ourselves. And now Netflix is trying to get into the fucking theater game. Yeah. Which if you think it's
going to stop at the Egyptian theater, no, that's going to be their landmark theater. That's going
to be the, you know, the hub, if you will. That's going to be the tourist attraction theater for them.
And they will undoubtedly, and I am calling this right now, they will move into buying up one of
these chains that's about to fold. AMC is struggling. I don't know how, what's the other one?
Lose. I don't know how Lose is doing. I can't imagine they're doing great. Pacific. And the next,
and I know I'll take it even a step further after they buy one of these ailing chain where in
Berg, they're going to then provide the new movie pass. They will provide the new movie pass.
They are trying to corner entertainment entirely. And it is no coincidence that this is all
happening as notable a listers like Helen Miran are publicly giving their grievances about Netflix.
While not saying they hate it, saying they like the service, but saying for Christ's sakes, pump
the fucking breaks. You still need to go to movie theaters and experience things that weren't made
by fucking Netflix. So, you know, you know, what I think this is insane. I think this is so beyond,
this is to me is up there with like what the banks were doing. This is up there to me with
Trump. This is up there to me with the biggest of the big. This is too big to fail bullshit.
It seems harmless because it's under the guise of entertainment. But the arms of this thing,
spider web, in so many fucking directions, I mean, when you start to take into account how product
placement works with all this stuff, how sponsorship works with all this stuff, the employment
that goes into these projects. This is a big fucking deal. This is a major industry thing that happened
so fast. I still remember 10 years before anyone was talking about it. Finding out in college,
I was 23 years old, 22 years old, that there was a website that would get you, I could get any
criteria on as the reason I was excited about it. They had everything and they would send it to your house.
Let's say I was 20. I was still living at home. So 2001, I didn't know anything about the stock
market. I still kicked myself for not buying fucking stocks and Netflix at this point. But the red
red envelopes had come to the house. I talked to my friends. They were like, I wouldn't just go to
the video store. Nobody even gave a shit. I did it for years and years and years. Finally, the door
to door system started catching on. In my memory about 2007, the streaming thing, I remember there
was a DVD you had to put in your DVD player to activate streaming. I remember each step of this
thing and at no point thinking I should perhaps purchase some stock because I had no money. But
it's less than 20 years time. I've been doing comedy for about 17 years and this Netflix came
out. 2001, I would say is Netflix came out after I was doing comedy. 2001. So it's less than 20 years,
which makes it more astounding to me. And I remember even, you know, you want to talk about this
exactly what point to what we're talking about here. When they first started doing the streaming thing,
Netflix had a deal with stars. And the deal was, we'll stream all the stuff that people need to pay to
see. And I remember when that fucking deal collapsed. Yeah. This, I'm telling you, they keep cutting out
other companies, other entities, other people. Of course. And they're doing it all under one roof.
I mean, people I've been to the building. It is a, it is a fucking fortress, this place.
It is a fucking fortress in the middle of Los Angeles. It is, it is one of the most insane buildings
I've ever been inside of. I thought they were just buying the Egyptian to show their movies,
throw them in here for a few weeks so they could get nominated for Oscars to like, as a loophole,
they were going to destroy this awesome Los Angeles theater just so they could throw them. And
that probably is what they're going to do at first. Yeah. No. I think they'll absolutely do that
because the theaters are going to start banning their movies and they, they know that that's ahead.
They know the theaters are like, fuck you. I'm not playing your movie. Your Netflix, you're trying to
kill us. They can have their own theater say, hey, it played for two weeks in Los Angeles. So
yeah. And then eventually, like I said, they're going to buy one of these ailing chains. Right.
And then it's going to be the AMC is going to be called the Netflix theater. Yeah. Yeah.
You know, 22 at the Netflix, whatever, staple center is going to be the Netflix center by, you
know, by the time I'm 40. Yeah. So I mean, it's just, it's just nuts, man. It's just nuts. And it's
something that you need, you don't need to do it. I can't believe I'm this passionate about it.
I usually don't get caught up in these kinds of things. But this one is really, really bothering me.
By the way, Amazon's no better. And there's, you know, new things every day about these people. But
most troubling to me is I, and I can't believe anyone would voluntarily put an Alexa spy device
in their home, but although I had hooked my phones with the exact same way. So, but
they said there are like people in Russia or whatever who listen in and when they hear a keyword,
like Taylor Swift in like, if you and I are talking about Taylor Swift, then you get that ad.
And it's like, Hey, do you want to see Taylor Swift's new album? So they do listen in on things.
They listen to samples like the FBI tapping wires. Then they said there have been times where people
will hear something that sounds like, for example, sexual assault. Amazon offers counseling for
people who have to hear something like a physical assault or a sexual assault in a home. They offer
counseling for them, but tell them it's not our job to get involved. So they just let those things go.
They do latch into the Taylor Swift. If they hear a rape, they are instructed to let that go. But they
do offer counseling. Now, when this woman said, I did listen to a sexual assault and I would like
counseling, they did not provide it. It was just like an in name only. Everything you read about these
companies, you're like, Oh my God. So should I stop using Amazon? I think, I think a lot of people
who question anything they do at all, the ethics of what they do would have to have huge issues
with Amazon. I do as well. However, when I'm like, Oh, this album is $40 at Amoeba and $17
in Amazon, it's hard for me to look at those. Now, that's gross. I have to recognize that about myself,
but I do definitely, lately try anytime I can to wean myself off of Amazon prime prime serves one
major purpose for me, which is Christmas time. It makes Christmas. I can't leave the house around
that. Yeah, it makes Christmas very, very easy. And it helps me find the exact things I'm looking for
for people. You shoot them right to their door. And then also as a video game, as a pretty
avid video game and media collector, and this applies more to the video games than anything else,
I am able to find things on there that I can't find anywhere else like a battery for an Nintendo
Game Boy Advance. Right. You know, like shit that you can't just go over to Best Buy or wherever
and buy. Yeah. And even video game stores don't have this shit. So it's like, that's my main
thing with Amazon is using it for those types of things. But I mean, I don't know. Maybe I
got to rethink that now, too, because you know, I don't think it did the damage that people,
I think it did some damage to brick and mortar stores. I don't think it did the level of damage
that people thought it was going to do. It did a lot of damage. Oh, it did a lot of damage.
I mean, clearly, because once it infiltrated like, like my dad orders shit on Amazon,
that means it is penetrated deep. Well, here's the thing though. I kind of look at that as,
okay, well, what's it taking away from Walmart? You know what I mean? And honestly, it's all,
it's all bad. And honestly, I don't scream on Walmart because Walmart, I know they do a lot of
shitty stuff. But I also know there's some single mom of three that needs a fucking job at Walmart
in some place. You know what I mean? I do think Walmart after, you know, that documentary and some
other things, I think have improved their policies somewhat. As far as, you know, Target is infinitely
better than Walmart, like all these corporations have a little bit of blood on their hands, you know,
what goes on in the warehouse might not be ideal. I know Amazon does like these 24 hour work days
that break human beings in their warehouse, which is why you're able to get anything you want in
two days delivered to your door in a giant cardboard box that's way too big for it and destroying
the ozone as well. But like, I mean, I had a wild one with them with an elliptical where I bought it.
Yeah. And there were all these issues with returning it. And they literally go, just keep it.
They give you your money back. They do that shit all the time. It was a thousand dollar
legal. They just gave me that shit all the time. But, you know, yeah, it's always good to look for
the lesser of evils when you can't. Target is a company that by all, I don't know why we're back
to Target again, but like they do all their shit right. And that's a big company that makes sure
their employees are paid and good benefits and so forth. That's good. Yeah, my cousin.
Walmart does not.
All right. Anyway, the picture is Craig Zoller's drag to cross concrete. This is the,
well, the man made Bone Tomahawk, which we loved on this show, Riot and Cell Block 99,
which we love. That's the second. That's so weird. I just did Doug loves movies and he called it
Riot on Cell Block 99. Well, there's a lot. There's a, I think there is a riot in something block movie.
And I was drunk. I thought he was saying ride. And I was like, what movie did you watch?
He wrote puppet master, the littlest rike, which Joe and I are going to do on this show. I haven't
watched it yet. I can't believe I've made. I can't remember. I think I did watch it and I forgot
about it already. I'm just curious as to what he did. I think he just produced it. I know he wrote it.
We did write it. And now he's also done a few other things. He's a novelist as well. I read about
him because I am officially a big fan of this guy to do, to see like three movies where you're like,
wow, these are great. And also I think improving really. He's fantastic. And his company is his best.
This is his best. It is. This is the best thing he's done so far. I can't wait to see what he does next.
His company, Santa State, they bought Fangoria. Fangoria was going to fold as you know because we left
the network. That's why we left the network because the magazine was folding in Santa State when he's
doing, this guy's just doing all the right stuff. The Santa State is an amazing company to produce his
movies and publishes books. That's his company owns. It's him and another gentleman who I actually
have met and met with and I'm blanking on his name at the moment. But his partner comes from the
publishing world and Craig comes from the movie world and they joined forces and made this amazing
company that puts out all this cool as genre stuff from print to screen. And you know, in the
latest screen release, it is obviously dragged across concrete, Vince Vaughn, Mel Gibson, Don Johnson,
Michael Jay White, Jennifer Carbender of Dexter Fam, has a particularly memorable little subplot.
And then we should, the newcomer to this thing. Yeah, I forget his name, but he should look
him up because he was absolutely excellent. His name is help me. No, why don't they just put
them in order? Yeah, I'm going to kill somebody. Why is the lead actor halfway down the page?
Well, a hilarious and weird performance by Fred Malamond, who was in a serious man as
Sy Abelman, one of the greatest characters of all time. That was one of the oddest fucking things
I've ever seen. I was like, his part is he plays a bank manager. Well, look, I mean, we'll get to
the learning. I'm going to get this guy's name. Can I do one fucking thing? Well, I'll just say this
real quick. He's I'm not going to Tony Kittles. I thought that can't be his name, but his name is
Tony Kittles. He's great. What's the guy's naming in from serious man, simple man?
The actor, the guy you just said, Fred Malamond. I won't give it away. I won't give away what happens
in the sequence, but he plays a bank manager who's welcoming an employee back to work. And it's
it's odd. It's like, he's like, your majesty, we have been absent, sick, sick, and by the absence of
your majesty, welcome, like it's well, he taught it's so crazy the way he talks. I think
Malamond was in a cell block. So he knew him or he was in one of this guys movies. And he probably was
like, I got a little part you could come in and do, but I'll make it, I'll make it better for you
or some it seemed like that kind of thing. They made a bit part more interesting for a great actor.
But that's really what he does. I mean, learning he was a novelist made so much sense to me.
I think you really got to discuss the Jennifer Carpenter segment, which was its own tiny little
movie. Yeah. And it's a scene when you think about heat or dark night or all these bank high scenes,
where they just kick open the doors and then somebody gets shot and you're like, oh, okay,
lady got shot. You know, this thing takes you home with this woman in five minutes by the way.
Yeah. I mean, always spoilers. This is available to rent for, you know, $6 .99 or whatever on
Amazon and iTunes. It already is coming out by the way on Blu -ray in like two weeks. Okay.
Well, yeah. But in five minutes, you know, everything about this woman, it's so beautifully written.
It's the kind of scene that unquestionably would be edited out of a Hollywood version of this story.
Um, and my god, does it make her plight so much more sympathetic and sad and everything in the movie
is done that way with that level of detail. The dialogue is excellent. While it's sometimes being
a little flashy for its own good, there's a Tarantino influence or yeah, it feels like the Jackie
Brown style of Tarantino. It feels like occasionally a little heightened, but mostly very realistic.
It's not a kill bill or even a pulp fiction where there's a lot of like goofy hijinks. It just feels
like the very real, very funny, very interesting portrayal of like awesome crime drama events and
everybody acts the hell out of it because they're given stuff to do for the first time in decades.
It's, it comes in from all angles. You got the cops. You got the crooks. You got the pedestrians,
the bystanders, and they show the perspective of all of them. And they show it very honestly,
and it's, it's a weirdly sympathetic film to all sides of that coin. You feel sorry for the cops.
You feel sorry for the crooks. Yeah. It's, it's kind of back to what we're talking about at the
beginning of the show. It's like everybody is just part of a shit world. And they're just trying
to figure it out. And nothing's fair to anybody. Yes. I mean, in terms of,
heat is a very valid comparison because it does that. But like in its weird way, you know,
heat is a masterpiece. I love it. I could watch it all day. This, I feel like it's going to in
five years time be a heat level thing. I feel like I'm going to be watching this a lot. I feel
like people are going to be discovering it and sharing it with their friends. And it's going to become
one of those kind of word -of -mouth classics like a Donnie Darko or something. It's fantastic.
A truly, and by the way, a truly amazing movie that not only celebrates diversity in its cast,
that not only celebrates the climate and the culture and the discussions we should be having
with its, with, with its themes and its message, that not only makes cinema in the way, in like that
run -and -gun Scorsese style taxi driver fucking way, that's this fucking thing will never get
mentioned once. No. Anywhere. Anywhere. No, this, this thing for all they bitch about it, all the
award shows how this is what we need and we need art that enlightens and we need diversity in our
cast and we need to show more sympathy and gender roles and so that this movie hits every one of those
fucking notes and you will never hear about this fucking thing. I think the reason for that is that they
cast Vaughn and Gibson. Vaughn is known as a Republican, I believe, Gibson is known as a lot of
worse things, but - But I'm glad he redeemed himself. I was thrilled to see Gibson back. He is,
he is in his like lethal weapon ransom time here. He's so fucking great and it makes you just sort of
forget how great he was, you know, and that, that is a guy where obviously a controversial figure,
if I'm just going to the movie and watching the guy and doing what people used to do and just go
and watch a movie and not know anything about the lives of the people, you know, some cases I'm
willing to do that, some cases I'm not. This case, it's like the guy is good when he wants to be and
he's really fucking good in this. He also like, we're in an age now where like, did wreck it Ralph,
just take a shot at Donald Trump and you're like, no, like what, what? And it'll be a huge article.
This movie, like, is discussing everything, sometimes explicitly, sometimes implicitly.
In such an interesting way and a way that so all politics now is, oh, you fucking snowflake liberals
and oh, you fucking racist rapist Republicans. Right. And nothing in between. This movie is covering
all of it. And it's, it is a more balanced portrayal than even the news because it is lending a
full sympathetic ear as Joe said to all sides. I know on all sides and on many sides as a bad
connotation now too, because of the president. But like, it is looking at all sides of each issue.
It is like the scene with Don Johnson, where Vaughan and Gibson sit across his desk. Don Johnson by
the way, just like, comment on the screen. I don't, I don't like him. And he is so fucking good
in this movie. It is, it is up there to me with like, it's like the Baldwin scene in Glen Gary.
That's right. He's in one scene. And I'm just like, this guy is killing it right now.
He is incredible in the movie. And they have this scene where the three men talk. And it's like, okay,
you're going to hear some things in this five minute talk that you don't hear from sympathetic
leads in movies anymore, because it aligns itself with like a Republican outlook, etc. So that
people at brands, this guy or Republican filmmaker, he doesn't even really talk about it. Like,
I don't know if he is or isn't. I'm just saying in this scene, you're hearing some things that are
uncomfortable at times, some things that you'll agree with at times. But it would, it definitely does
is sound like three cops alone with the door shut and what they would be saying. And it's not
as horrific as it might be in, you know, another kind of movie where it's like, we got to go out and
kill all these minorities or something. You know, where they're painted as villains. But it's also not
all scrubbed up like, look, I just want to make a difference out on the streets. It sounds like
men having a conversation who have very difficult jobs and who are trying to make sense of this
new fucked up world and this politically correct world. Also too, there are real. There are conflicting
opinions in that scene. It's not one side. It's absolutely not. Johnson is the more liberal voice in
that scene. But then also too, here's a thing this movie has that you don't see anymore. Character
development. Well, I mean, that's what I was saying with Carpenter even down to the most minor
and even more minor than her, the bank boss. I mean, everyone has fleshed out so beautifully.
So it's like a novel. My point is is where these characters start at the beginning. Again,
the cops and the crooks because it covers all sides is a very different place than where they all end
up at the end of the movie. And that's what's so great about it is is and that's what's up with
these issues too. When people argue these issues about, and I just mean this very broad sense,
like the idea of like being more tolerant to one another, whatever it is, when we argue these issues,
we tend to have trigger words and trigger phrases that set us off. We have our defenses way up and
whatever. And then nine times out of 10, when somebody starts to experience what the other person
is going through, they start to say, wow, I was a little too wrapped up in my own shit. And I
have a broader idea of this now. And that's what happens to a lot of the characters in this movie.
You start to see them brought in their understanding of things. And it's fucking beautiful,
quite frankly at times. I agree. The friendship and the chemistry between Vaughan and Gibson,
again, feels very, very real, very, very natural. The movie stops for two minutes to watch Vince Vaughan
eat an egg salad sandwich. It's more to Della, he says later. Gibson eats the most egg salad.
Pat and I were laughing about this after the sound design of this movie is impeccable.
Every punch is like, and they got the sound cranked up. Well, Vaughan has eaten this sandwich.
I mean, you're here. It sounds like you're inside his mouth. It's one of the honest choices I've
ever seen in a movie. Yeah. And, you know, the whole, and it works brilliantly because they're on a
stakeout. And he's, he's trying to show you like, how fucking annoying would this be? Like if you had to
sit next to this guy in a car after two days and listen to this, you'd want to fucking strangle him.
It's very, very funny. Gibson's like, are you fucking done? You know, at the end of it,
it's an awesome bit that would be at gunpoint taken out of a Hollywood movie or a studio movie.
So this is two and a half hours. I've heard a lot of people bitch about it being too long,
being too boring. I did, this is the only movie I haven't checked my phone in a year.
I was completely riveted, start to finish. All the performances are amazing. Man, I wish that guy
had a more memorable name because I think he'd be a bigger star if he did. But Tory Kittles,
I got a Tony or Tory. Tory. I got to stamp that into my head because he was excellent in this. He
was also on the latest season of True Detective. But man, he was fucking good. Everybody was fucking good.
Was he the lead guy in True Detective this year? No, that was Maharashtale. Oh wait, that's right. That's
the guy from a green book, right? Yes, correct. Okay. Who by the way are people call this out? You were like
you know, couldn't he have some Oscar stuff. He had actually won the year before from Moonlight.
He did? He did, which I had forgotten as well. I've never seen green book. I've never,
I didn't see True Detective. I have no idea what I think. I wouldn't know him if I fell over him.
I would have no fucking clue. Really? I didn't know his name. I know nothing. I gotta go back and watch
Moonlight. I love Moonlight. I really did. But it's not what we're talking about. We're talking about
sweet, sweet, dragged across concrete. Yeah, two hours, 39 minutes. I had no idea. I thought it was
90 minutes. At a time when 90 minute movies feel like four hours. Yeah, that's pretty impressive.
Because I could have watched another, I guess I could have watched like an eight hour mini series
of this. I mean, well, if this had been a series and this is a guy who like an FX should be bang
his door down to get this guy like to make the next shield. Yeah, like he's got the next great
cop drama in him. And he'd make more money. I'll tell you that much. I just a huge thank you to
everybody involved with this picture. Thank you for showing. I mean, it revived. It's the best movie
I've seen all year. It reinstated my faith in cinema. I mean, we walked out of this thing and I
turned a pat and I go, that is what a fucking good movie is. Like it's one of those flicks when you
watch it. I found myself going, I have bullshitted myself through so many cineplex movies. Yeah,
you know, and said like, yeah, it was pretty good or it was this or it was that or like whatever.
And then I've guilted myself for thinking things sucked when everybody else liked it. And then I saw
this thing and I was like, no, I was right. That is what a good movie is. That's what a good
fucking movie looks like. And it was just thank you to everybody that made this thing. It was just,
it was just, it makes me, it gives me hope. And I will say back on the theater bit, Joe and I,
you know, I was like, hey, we should go up and see this at the theater. We could have rented it for
five bucks. We went up and they charged the ticket price. 18 a pop. I was like, you're fucking
kidding me. It's gone up at the art slide. And I'm so glad I paid it. I'm so glad for a variety of
reasons. I think it deserve to be seen on the big screen too. When you're at home, whether you want
to admit it or not, you're checking your phone, you're going over, you're going to the bathroom
but leaving it running, you know, you get a phone call, you're not paying attention for a second.
This movie, if you do watch it at home and more power to you, save yourself some money. But
please shut your fucking phone off for two hours, 40 minutes. And just enjoy the hell out of this
movie because I think it's easily the best of the year. It'll be on my favorites of the year,
the end of the year guaranteed. Great performances all around. Tory Kittles, Vince Vaughn,
Mel Gibson, Craig Zahler, man to watch. If he is getting these offers to move over into the Marvel
universe, like every guy with a well -made indie movie is nowadays, I sure hope he keeps turning them
down because I would hate to lose this guy to bigger budget movies. He's making great pictures.
Well, and that's the thing too. If he does slide over in that direction, I hope he does it for strategic
reasons, like the way Bouchemi did, or even a Clooney where he was like, yeah, I'm going to
make Batman and Robin. It's going to be a pile of shit. And then I'm going to be able to do whatever
the fuck I want. And then the next thing I'm doing is leather heads. You know, like he's like,
because they wouldn't have made this if I don't do. Well, sometimes they're right, by the way. Yeah,
in the case of leather heads. Anyway, that's our show folks. I will be at the Moontower Comedy
Festival next week, starting on Wednesday night in Austin, Texas at Cap City on Wednesday with
Dudley and Bob for the kickoff podcast. I don't know exactly who else is going to be there,
but I will be there for that. And then I'll have several shows throughout the week and weekend,
definitely doing the goddamn comedy jam twice while I am there. I think I will be potentially judging
roast battle while I'm there, but I'll be doing stand -up shows too. Love Austin can't wait to come back.
And that is, I think that's it for now. Yeah, let's leave it at that.
Joe DeRosa Comedy on Instagram. Can you get me more followers than the fucking cat, please?
As for you boy, P -Walls, you can find me at the Patrick Walsh on Twitter and Instagram.
And I believe that's all I got. Check us out at the Hog House page on Etsy for merch.
Check us out on Facebook on the We'll See You In Hell page. Always a great discussion over there.
Almost pulled the plug on Facebook the other day, but again left it up because I love reading what
you guys have to say. And Instagram, we are on See You In Hell pod. Thanks to Emily for running that.
We are looking to set up a potential, I don't want to say where, but we are looking to set up
a potential show in America that will not be in the Los Angeles area. The start of a little perhaps
tour of the globe. We will see you next time with Pat Cemetery, all things Pat Cemetery,
and we will see you in Hell.