I'll see you in hell.
And when the sound of your screams becomes a thing of my dreams, you know I'll say.
You know I will.
I'll see you in hell.
Folks, it's we'll see you in hell.
We're back to talk about a movie about a woman who becomes pregnant.
And she isn't happy about being pregnant, but it's at the result of a bunch of nuns and priests.
And believe it or not, the movie is not the first omen.
It's a different movie.
Yeah, almost identical, except one's good.
Can you hear this insanely loud chain song in the background?
No, I'm too busy listening to the constant thumping up and down the stairs of my neighbors who don't send their children to school.
Let me shut this door. This is unbelievable.
I'll talk while you do that, folks. That's what I'm dealing with in my neck of the woods.
I got some neighbors who do not send their kids to school.
The kids are just home all day.
And I don't know what's going on, and I don't want to get involved.
But I will tell you, it's very noisy.
Speaking of chainsawing.
Losing my mind.
Speaking of chainsawing, I thought you might appreciate this, Joe.
But they are showing in the cemetery here in Los Angeles, the Texas Chainsaw Massacre for the 50th anniversary.
Presented by?
I feel confident I could give you 500 guesses and you wouldn't get it.
Black and Decker.
No, I mean, it's a person.
Oh, oh, like a person's presenting the movie.
I honestly do want to guess. Give me a second.
Take one guess, but I mean, it's impossible.
Dan Levy.
No.
Janelle Monae.
Who?
The pop singer.
Who I like. Who's like gorgeous.
She's an actress.
I mean, it just struck me as completely insane.
I don't know who that is, but she's great.
I've seen her in concert.
But yeah, sometimes they pair these people and you're like, what's going on?
They had a Ramones slash pulp fiction night once.
It's like guys pick a lane here.
Well, Ramones because Johnny is buried in that cemetery.
They do stuff in there every weekend.
I'm going to see pulp there on Saturday night.
Wait, wait.
Hollywood Forever Cemetery, you said?
Wait, right?
Yeah.
Okay.
Pairing it with pulp fiction is the part I don't get.
Oh, see now I'm making it more confusing.
I'm going to see the band pulp on Saturday night in the cemetery.
Yeah, yeah.
No, I know what you meant.
Yeah.
I didn't see it tomorrow night at the Palladium, which is a venue that I hate here in town.
I love pulp.
Well, these weird pairings.
I sent you this where it's Larry David in conversation hosted by Tom Brady.
I'm like, what the fuck is going on?
What are we doing?
Yeah, just stupid. Stupid.
They're not going to have good questions for Larry David.
But everything is...
Sorry, folks.
I'm smoking.
I'm at the end of my tether.
I'm trying desperately.
Always smoking lately.
Always smoking.
Yeah.
I'm trying desperately not to crawl into a bottle of fucking whiskey tonight because I'm
trying to stick with my diet and only drink on the one or two days a week on the weekend.
But I will tell you, I am as close as I have ever been.
Holy shit.
Everything you say to me.
Take me one step closer to the edge and I'm about to break.
Is that My Mind's Blown to Pieces, that song?
I think that's Licken Park.
Whose son is yelling publicly about the band.
Yeah, a lot of controversy.
You can't do anything nowadays.
Although, if they didn't vet this woman, they're stupid.
You got to vet everybody nowadays.
Rob Snyder's daughter taking shots at him in public.
It's like, can you keep it to Thanksgiving like the rest of us?
Jesus fucking Christ, man.
Anybody.
But what I was going to say about the Tom Brady, Larry David thing.
It's like, plug another famous person in.
Just plug another famous person in.
You know?
Right.
I mean, we don't even try to get interviewers anymore.
That used to be a job because people were good at it.
You'd get Tom Snyder or whatever.
Yeah.
These days you don't even get the guy that played Snyder.
There you go.
God damn it.
Are you a Pulp fan, Joe?
Pulp, the band.
Oh, now I know why you said that.
Because you said Pulp Fiction.
I didn't even catch that.
I don't know any Pulp.
I only know the one.
Are they boys who love girls, who love boys, who love girls?
That's blur.
Is Pulp...
That's also blur.
I don't know.
Pulp is Common People, which is probably my favorite song of all time.
That's a great song.
And they have many other great songs.
Lately, I've been kind of obsessively listening to them because I'm going to see them and they're reunited.
And they have a great documentary, which I'll talk about in the movie corner.
But I've been super horny and paranoid lately.
Oh, boy.
That's not a good combo.
No.
And today I'm out walking the streets.
I'm doing 15 ,000 steps a day lately.
Walking the streets.
Not a great phrase to tag onto.
I'm horny and paranoid.
I do my 15 ,000 steps a day, which is keeping me sane, keeping me rational.
And, you know, Pulp, I realize listening to them 18 hours a day is probably not helping because these are the most horny and paranoid songs ever written.
The man Jarvis Cocker is a sexual deviant.
The songs are all about being obsessed with somebody from your past.
Yeah, I need to stop listening to them.
But I'm excited to see them live.
They're great.
I thought...
What was I going to say?
Oh, Common People.
I like very much the...
I like the original version quite a bit.
But I also very much like the Shatner Ben Fold version.
It's surprisingly great.
Which I never knew until the other night.
This is Kismet.
We're talking about this.
I, for whatever reason, looked up the song.
I never knew Joe Jackson was the other guy singing on that.
The guy that sings Stepping Out.
Joe Jackson has never sounded more fierce than he is on that song.
Like you can hear like the spit coming out of his mouth.
He's disgusted with the people the song is about.
Not the people, the person, the main character that thinks it's all very funny.
And then a lot of people don't know this, but playing bass on the track is Shoeless Joe Jackson from the film Field of Dreams.
Yep.
And Jesse Jackson produced the song.
RIP to the great James Earl Jones.
Yes.
Joe, why did you tell Diddy to do what he diddy?
Oh boy.
Diddy Dum Diddy Doo?
He's fucked, man.
That's a rap on old days.
He's fucked.
Folks.
Yeah.
When they deny bail.
I was talking to Chris DiStefano about this last night.
He's like, when the FBI apprehends you and then they deny bail, you're not coming back out.
That's a rap on there.
I mean, he walked free there for an additional couple of months.
It's crazy how this stuff works.
Well, Chris made a good point.
He was saying, and I agree, he was saying when the FBI gets you, they build a case and they wait until they have more than enough evidence so it's bulletproof.
And then they come down on you.
Which is why it took them so long to get Fogel, because they were building the case for so long.
But yeah, Diddy's, they got him on trafficking.
I mean, that's a rap.
And I wonder, do you think, I'm curious, because Cosby went to trial, but then the trial, the case they brought in that actually went to trial,
wasn't strong enough that it got judged a mistrial or whatever, and then he got out.
And then I don't think Weinstein might get out or something, but Weinstein isn't facing what everybody believes he should face.
Do you think that because of those missteps, we'll call them, with past offenders, that they, when the stuff started surfacing about Diddy,
they were like, okay, we got to do it the right way to make sure that this sticks?
Or maybe they were just building the case on this guy for years?
Yeah. I mean, I think Harvey Weinstein is basically just going to die on his own at this point, so they're kind of just dragging it out.
But Diddy's a young kind of man in his prime, and it looks, I don't know, they're not going to put him to death, but I feel like he'll be in jail for the rest of his life.
Yeah, or like, you know, 30 years and he'll get out when he's 82 or something like that.
No, it's crazy. It's crazy.
I just rewatched Black Mass, and I was reading up on Whitey Bolger. I didn't know this. I knew he was apprehended late in his life.
I didn't know he died from being beaten to death in jail. And I was reading about it. He was beaten so severely that they said his eyes were like gone, basically, and his tongue was almost cut out of his mouth completely.
And they interviewed somebody that was, I guess, a family member of one of his victims or somebody that knew who he was his whole life or, you know, a guy that was familiar with Whitey Bolger and wanted to see him go away.
And the guy's quote was, he died as I always dreamed he would. I was like, wow, that's a heavy quote.
Yeah, I'm going to Alcatraz. I'll be in Alcatraz next Friday. I'm meeting friends from high school up in San Francisco for the Cardinals game, St. Louis Cardinals.
Okay.
Have you been to Alcatraz?
No, I've never had an interest in going to a prison.
I'm kind of pumped. I mean, maybe it's the So I Married an Axe Murderer scene that takes me there. But yeah, I'm pumped. We're going on the night tour. So I hope it's going to be extra creepy.
Is it like supposedly haunted or anything like that?
I don't know about that, but there's definitely been a lot of horrific things that have gone on there and horrific people have passed through those those doors.
Nothing gets you out of paranoid horniness.
Like going to a defunct men's prison.
That's probably haunted.
Right around Halloween at night, right after a horrific mushroom trip.
Yeah, I had had a bad mushroom trip. Did you talk about it on the solo?
I did. I talked about it on the solo corner, but definitely the next several days have been a little rocky, just like it was a game changer for me for sure.
I don't trust myself anymore.
Well, I don't think I trust you and I think you should trust yourself, but I also think a bad trip will put you in a bad way for a while.
Yeah, I've been there. I've been there. It ain't fun.
The fear would be that next time I would be like obsessing like don't go. I got to just make sure I don't go back into a bad place this time. And the thinking about it would send me there.
Yeah, no, if I were you, I would not do mushrooms ever again.
But, you know, that's why I don't get these these goddamn like retreats where people go off and do ayahuasca and peyote and shit.
And they're like, I saw a demon and I faced it.
You're like, yeah, I don't want to do that. It sounds horrible.
Yeah, there's a mutual friend of ours who keeps trying to get me to do that.
And I'm just like, no, she's like, well, you'll probably shit yourself and you'll probably puke.
But like you really get to this amazing place, but you're surrounded by people who are all also going through it.
I'm like, yeah, that sounds horrible. Horrible.
Yeah. And then also, I might have said this before in the pod, but people always do it.
And then they go, dude, it's like a year of therapy in one night.
I'm different now. I'm like, well, are you different or is your brain just recalibrating to the fucking horror you put it through?
I don't know. Yeah, I feel like a different man with a bad after a bad hangover.
I don't think it means it was necessarily therapeutic.
I think sometimes it's just. Yeah.
I mean, the people say like, well, I, you know, I learned that I want to be a mother or I learned that I'm gay or I learned that I'm these big revelations.
And it's like, I can't imagine that this thing is bringing these things out of you that you never thought about before.
That just doesn't see. And if it is, then why are you trusting it?
That's crazy. Yeah.
Can you hear this chair terribly as much as I can? Okay.
Anyway, I think I had a new psycho here.
Yes, and shout outs to Tony from hack the movies, which is a great YouTube movie show.
I went over and did his show today.
The episode will be out in October around Halloween.
Keep an eye out, but just want to give him a shout out since I talked about our show on there.
And he's a fellow movie reviewer, primarily horror focused, but a good man and a good show.
Um, uh, new psycho.
No, all I, no, all I had was.
The Daily Beast.
Said that Dennis Quaid's Reagan.
Yes, is the worst movie of the year.
I know a few people have seen it, so it was kind of fun, campy.
Now.
The Daily Beast, of course, I would assume would think of movie that is sort of in its own way, celebrating Ronald Reagan would would be not, they wouldn't like it.
It's not for this group, but.
They did say that this is a really, really bad movie.
And, uh, and they said he had Reagan in the movie is not presented.
Merely as a charismatic actor and an effective statement, statesman, but as God's chosen warrior.
In a titanic battle between good and evil.
Yeah, there's a small, very successful, like faith based movie world that goes on out there.
Just movies we'll never see, but that make a lot of money.
I think when you see these people that like, look, you know, you like Trump, whatever.
It's not my business who you like.
I don't care.
But these people that I'll see say, like, I firmly believe God has saved him.
It's like, yeah, and he didn't save Martin Luther King or Malcolm X Gandhi.
Right.
You know, it's like, it's just such a crazy note.
It's so nuts to me.
Like, what are we?
What are we talking about?
You wonder why we can't get anywhere as a culture?
People still think these things.
God saved this person.
What do we talk?
What the fuck are we talking about?
But gave him dementia.
Oh, yeah.
All right.
I watched the trailer today from Mickey Seventeen.
For what?
Mickey Seventeen, the new movie from Bong Joon -ho.
Mickey Seventeen.
I'm not, I don't know what that is.
I haven't heard of it.
Well, Bong Joon -ho did Parasite and Mother and The Host and a lot of great movies.
But this is his follow up to Parasite.
Robert Pattinson, Steven Yeun, Tony Collette, Mark Ruffalo.
It's been delayed several times, which is usually not a great sign.
I saw the trailer today.
It's like a $150 million movie that looks like a crazy art movie.
And those always bomb.
Always.
Terry Gilliam, you know, they just, they give him this big budget.
It gets too weird.
Megalopolis definitely going to bomb as well.
And it just looked too busy.
It was like a comedy, but nothing was funny.
Futuristic sci -fi comedy.
It also looked to have the exact same plot as Moon with Sam Rockwell, where Robert Pattinson keeps cloning himself in space.
I don't know.
Maybe they'll prove me wrong.
I mean, Bong Joon -ho is an amazing filmmaker, but it looked really horny and dumb.
Speaking of cloning yourself, Michael Keaton just said in an interview, they said, you know, you just redid, you did read, went back to Batman, went back to Beetlejuice.
What character?
Is there another character you'd like to revisit?
And he said, multiplicity.
Yeah.
Hey, love it.
Do it again.
Yeah.
I don't think it was a big enough hit.
I also thought the trailer for the new movie with Josh Brolin and Peter Dinklage looked kind of funny.
I was like, OK, we're starting to see some R -rated comedies again.
It looked kind of funny.
Yeah.
And there's the thing in the end of the trailer where it's insinuated that Josh Brolin is fucked by an orangutan.
Yeah, it's strongly insinuated.
I mean, I'll check it out.
I think it's just called Brothers, not the most clever title, but I'll check it out.
I'm excited.
And the trailer hasn't dropped yet, but I'm excited for this.
Tim Robinson.
Paul Rudd.
Yeah.
For sure.
I think it's called Friendship.
Yeah.
Can't wait.
I'm excited for that.
Oh, speaking of trailers, another new psycho, the Ellen DeGeneres trailer.
Oh, yeah.
That's what I wanted to talk about.
She's trying to change the whole narrative.
This woman is just trash.
She really is.
Oh, just because I said I was nice and be kind, everybody jumps on me.
I wish I would have said fuck you.
And then everybody, it's like, no, no, no.
Stop, stop this.
Stop denying it and admit it and accept it and embrace it.
You were awful for decades to people.
Stop it.
Stop joking about it.
I was surprised at how jovial the trailer was.
I actually, I guess, tipped my hat to her at least for that much.
I was like, well, shit, she's coming out and she's doing like the Ellen everybody wants,
except she's, I guess, talking about this stuff.
You know, I will say in the jokes where she's setting up like, you know,
I got into this business because I was a damaged little girl.
Like every moment in the trailer where you think she's going to go into some pukey,
feel sorry for me thing, she does misdirect it and then make a joke.
And I'm like, all right, maybe it will just be a straight up comedy special
and she's just going to make fun of herself.
I don't know.
But yeah, that is a that is a real cop out.
If I had ended each show with saying, go fuck yourselves,
then everybody would be surprised how kind I am.
It's like, but you're not kind is the problem.
That's what we're talking about.
And it's just it's like politician shit.
It's like she knows what she's doing and people are dumb, so they fall for it.
Yeah.
Do you think there will be any part in this thing where she's like,
Look, man, I fucked up.
And, you know, having a talk show is stressful and I fucked up, you know.
Let's take me down and you down to the movie corn.
I will start with pulp colon, a film about life, death and supermarkets.
This is from oscilloscope.
We have a hellion out there who has provided Joe
and I with lovely gifts from oscilloscope, which is a great,
very small film distribution company that did Dear Zachary,
which is one of my favorite documentaries of all time.
Almost too painful to finish, but it's an amazing movie.
And Dark Days, which is about the mole people of the subway.
They've done a lot of great stuff.
We need to talk about Kevin is oscilloscope.
Pulp, a film about life, death and supermarkets is a really great documentary.
I think whether you're a fan of the band or not,
it's half interviews with the band, half them, you know,
kind of coming to terms with reuniting the band 20 years later and going out on tour.
And then the other half is talking to the people of Sheffield where the band is from
and talking to them about pulp.
They, you know, there's a song they have called Help the Aged,
which is about fucking older people and throwing them a bone.
And they have a group of senior citizens sing that song.
You know, they do a lot of really kind of neat, fun,
fun ways of presenting the music of pulp in addition to just concert footage.
It was very creative.
I really enjoyed it.
It's a tight 90 minutes.
And for me, this was one of those bands that I've loved since I was in high school,
but I had never even really seen them interviewed or didn't know what they were about.
Sometimes you have a band like that.
The Pixies were like that until they finally had a documentary.
Some bands just don't tell you anything.
So this was great.
This was a great opportunity to see more about them as I'm going to see them live this week.
Joe?
I listened the other day to Marcy, You Are the Quarry.
Love it.
There's a great song on there called The First One to Die.
It's a beautiful song.
First the Gang to Die?
Yeah, First the Gang to Die, sorry.
What was really making me laugh though is the way Marcy hard swings from these beautiful lyrics,
like in that song, where he's like,
you know, you haven't been in love until you see the reflection of the stars in the reservoirs.
It's these beautiful images and whatever.
And he's sold from the rich and the poor and the not very rich and the very poor.
They don't have a song where he's like, America, take your cheeseburgers and shove them up your ass.
He gets so literal and so poetic.
It's very odd.
My theme for the movie corner today, given the distress state of mind I am in, will be positive.
The theme is positive.
Things I watched that I very much enjoyed, that it took me out of my bad mood.
But also too, just on a positive note, I want to thank everybody that came out to the special.
We shot it last Saturday.
It was a smash success.
Everything went off without a hitch.
I cannot be happier about the results of that.
I'm very serious.
I'm excited for all of you to see it.
Stay tuned.
I will keep you all posted.
But amidst that beautiful experience, I've been dealing with some other headaches that have put me in a tense state,
so to speak, when I'm home.
Anyway, positive.
By the way, RIP Tito Jackson as well.
Oh yes, absolutely.
I watched, finally, I don't know why it took me so long, but I've been watching Baskets.
Oh, at least early on, I love Baskets.
Louis Anderson, incredible.
It's an amazing show.
It is so funny, and it's so absurd, and then it gets so beautifully heartbreaking and endearing.
And the best example of it is Louis Anderson playing Zach Galifianakis' mom.
And it's such ridiculous casting, and it's so crazy, but it makes so much sense.
And it's such a funny character that you think they're just kind of throwing in there from left field for a sort of wild take on something.
And then they start to actually get into the relationship between Zach's character and Louis' character.
And you see how much they actually love each other.
You see where the troubles they have have come from.
And God, man, Louis Anderson's amazing.
Like, there are those moments where he's coming, where she, the character, is coming to terms with her food addiction and her weight and everything.
And it's beautiful. It's heartbreaking.
It's a really, really funny show.
Martha, I'm forgetting Martha's last name.
Yes, she's wonderful in it.
Zach, he's always great.
Louis Anderson's great. The whole supporting cast is great as well.
Very well directed.
I forget who directed it.
I thought Louis CK did, because I guess he created it with Zach, but he didn't direct it.
A lot of it's Jonathan Krizzle, who did Portlandia, and now he's doing English teacher.
He does a lot of stuff for FX.
It's a great show. I'm about two seasons in.
I've been putting it on at night and just kind of leaving it on.
You see the Easter one? That was one of my favorites with Louis Anderson.
That's the one I'm talking about, where they're in the casino at the brunch, and then they have the fight.
And then Louis Anderson sits next to him with the slot machine, and he's like,
my mom shamed me out of eating a dessert, and you feel so fucking sorry for him.
And the mom is so disappointed in Chip, who's Zach's character, that he smokes.
And the way she makes amends is she hands him an ashtray.
And it's this moment of like, I realize you're a grownup and we're different people, but it's okay.
Just a really, really wonderful, wonderful show.
Which, by the way, gets way less into clowning than I thought for a show about a clown.
It's not very clown -focused at all.
Well, they learn pretty quickly. People don't like clowns, I think.
But I don't remember how far I made it. I think maybe two and a half seasons.
Oh, boy.
Pat knocked his mic out, everybody.
But how?
I don't know.
Yeah, okay.
There you go.
Yeah.
Yeah, I didn't finish the show, and it wasn't because it got bad.
I think they just waited too long between seasons. Sometimes that's the problem.
But I was a fan. I remember a hilarious moment with a water bottle with Louis Anderson
that I rewound about 100 times in the first couple episodes.
I don't know if you remember that.
She spills a water bottle all over herself or something.
It really made me laugh really hard.
The gag they do in the pilot episode where they pull up to the drive -through to get a soda,
and he names every soda that a drive -through would never have.
It's such a classic Zach Galifianakis gag.
And it's so right there for the taking, and you're watching it, and you're going,
I can't, how has nobody ever thought of this joke? It's so funny. It's right there.
Drink orders are always funny. Tanker and Tabs, sweets keep them coming.
Orange Whip, Orange Whip, Three Orange Whips from Blues Brothers.
What else we got?
Jack and Dyett, to use an example from my real life.
Okay, I will go on to Queenpins.
This movie is currently on Netflix.
I was sort of curious because I saw a very funny scene pop up on TikTok
with Vince Vaughn and Paul Walter Hauser.
And the movie is a very average comedy, but nice to see a comedy.
You know, always nice in this day and age to see any comedy.
But it's Kristen Bell, Kirby Howell Baptiste.
They are sort of coupon thieves.
They, you know, like out of Punch Drunk Love, they're sort of scamming the coupon companies.
And they have sort of an Ocean's Eleven style heist involving coupons.
Joel McHale plays.
Kristen Bell is a sort of verbally abusive husband.
It's got kind of a stacked supporting cast.
You see a lot of funny people in it. Jack McBrayer, Annie Mumolo, Stephen Root.
A lot of great people pop up.
But the only reason I can recommend this is there are some absolutely hilarious scenes between Paul Walter Hauser and Vince Vaughn.
I don't know how this happened, but Paul Walter Hauser plays like a coupon investigator for the government.
And he's very lonely and sad and pathetic.
And then Vince Vaughn plays like the fast talking FBI guy who comes in to pair with him.
And the scene that you might have seen on TikTok is they're on a stakeout and Paul Walter Hauser falls asleep and he wakes up and he's like, oh, sorry.
But every when I wake up, I just immediately shit.
So, like, I'm going to shit and Vince Vaughn's like, well, you're not going to shit in the car.
And he's like, no, it's it's coming out. I'm just going to go ahead and shit.
And he's like, no, no, no, you shouldn't even be talking about this.
You should be going to the bathroom. Why are you in the car?
And he shits himself and Vince Vaughn is reacting and there's a lot of improv or whatever.
This scene honestly is worth the two hours of the movie.
But all their other stuff is great.
It makes you wonder why.
And I bet the producers tried. They probably only had him for a couple of weeks.
But this movie should have been balanced the other way because it's very funny when they're on screen and kind of dull when they're not.
But not a bad movie. Entertaining for sure.
Well, I'll see your Vince Vaughn and I'll one up up the ante.
I watched Bad Monkey.
It's not finished yet, but I'm up through all the episodes up to that have been released.
And same same thing, except what you're saying.
That should have been the which this is.
It is a Vince Vaughn starring television show about a mystery unraveling around a dead or around a disembodied arm that is discovered floating around in Key West, Florida.
And it goes from there.
And it's a caper mystery comedy, never gets too heavy, never gets too dark.
Some fantastic twists plays a lot like the lighter Elmore Leonard stuff.
Like if you ever saw The Big Bounce or if Jackie Brown were a little less sinister in places and a little bit goofier in other places.
That's the vibe.
It's very, very funny.
It's very enjoyable.
The entire cast is stellar.
But of course, you've got Vince Vaughn right at the helm being Vince Vaughn.
Like it's like the it's like we missed him.
You know, he he he was doing a different thing.
Vince Vaughn will kind of do the Vince Vaughn thing for a little while.
Then he'll you know, then then something will take him away from it.
So like what last took him away from it was the first time we got him swingers and all that.
He kind of got pulled out of it and was doing like grittier stuff and more indie stuff and whatever.
Then he came back with Old School and he was Vince Vaughn again for a bit.
And then he started doing sort of broader, more family style comedies where there was a little bit of that stuff in there.
But it was, you know, it was a different vibe.
And now he's swinging back into it again.
And and it's great.
It's great.
And and I can only imagine he ad libbed this line.
But my favorite joke so far has been when he's flirting with a coroner that he wants to go out with and he asks her out and she goes, sorry, I'm seeing somebody.
And he goes, is he big?
And she goes, he goes, is he big?
Is he bigger than me?
And she goes, he's a sniper.
He's on the SWAT team.
And he goes, it doesn't matter how big you are.
If you're a sniper, you just have to learn how to live with the darkness.
I can only imagine he riffed that line.
But it's a great.
It's another scene where they're talking and to be able to talking in Russian and he just goes, it's a beautiful language, isn't it?
Because it is not.
Anyway, Bad Monkey, I recommend it.
And I might want to check out the guy that wrote it.
Some of his space on a book.
Yeah, Carl Heisen's written a bunch of books.
He wrote strip tease, which became to me more movie and a bunch of stuff.
But yeah, I want to watch it.
They Apple TV and them all send out screeners at the end of the year.
And I'm like, I'll just wait till Christmas time.
Watch Presumed Innocent and all that shit.
I rewatched Anna Melissa, which I saw back when it was like a further consideration movie.
This is the least known, least appreciated Charlie Kaufman movie.
It is a puppet film, correct?
Yeah, it is one of it's a serious drama with puppets.
It is also a very dark comedy, like a lot of Charlie Kaufman stuff.
There's some very funny stuff in it, but it's a difficult, weird, strange movie.
His other one that he did for Netflix.
I'm thinking of ending things.
The first time I saw it, I just kind of shrugged.
I didn't give a shit.
Second time I saw it, I deeply loved it.
And I think he's just that kind of guy.
I think his movies get better with repeat viewings.
So this is David Thulis from Naked as the voice of our lead guy who was like a sad middle -aged dude
who's married, staying in a hotel and basically calling through his phone trying to cheat on his wife.
This is our hero, so it's very sad and depressing.
He's in town to do a book conference and there's Jennifer Jason Leigh, who is a fan of his,
who is staying in the hotel and they have a super awkward sex scene beyond the Team America sex scene.
This is like played realistically for all the awkwardness of like, I mean, think of your worst sexual encounter.
It's tough.
You get to watch it with these puppets, puppet pubes, puppet dicks.
And then Tom Noonan from Silence of the Lambs plays everybody else in the movie.
The movie is kind of about -
Wait a minute. Everybody else?
Men and women, yeah.
And that's part of it.
In the same voice?
No, not the same voice. He alters it slightly.
But that's part of what the movie winds up being about.
It winds up feeling almost like a long -form Twilight Zone in a weird way.
It's 90 minutes long and like all Kaufman stuff, it's like silly.
It's crazy.
It's like got, you know, dirty sex humor and like embarrassing humor.
And then suddenly it'll be really profound and moving.
But I really like the movie.
It's crazy. It's cheap.
It was done by the same studio, Joe, where we used to do our podcast, which is what was Dan Harmon's studio?
Starburns.
And in the lobby, when you walked in across from the receptionist desk, they had like a setup from this movie, which was always mildly disturbing.
Yeah, really, it was kind of a strange move to do with Puppets.
I think it would have worked just as well as a little character study and probably taken much less time and been cheaper to do.
But I dug it. I like all of his stuff.
He's just always giving you something and something different.
And I appreciate that.
Sometimes a critic review will make me not want to see something, not because they say it's bad, but because of the way they praise it.
Sure. Yeah.
And I was turned off from that movie.
And this is my problem.
I should give the movie a chance.
But I was turned off when it was released.
And in the trailer, it said the most human movie of the year.
And I was like, eat my pussy.
Yeah.
Everybody, please.
Who would have thought that Puppets would bring us the most human movie of the year?
Taken almost verbatim from the ending soliloquy of Terminator 2.
Judgment Day.
Playing Midnight at the Vista this weekend, I believe.
Oh, that's cool.
I mean, yeah, that's a good thing for you.
Are you going to go see it?
Perhaps. They've been doing a lot of great shit there.
A lot of great midnight movies.
He's stacking it.
Old movies, new movies.
It's cool.
It's great to have in the neighborhood.
Would have been on your street, Joe, if you had just stayed here in Los Angeles.
Beautiful Los Angeles.
I'd be dead if I had stayed.
That was the best of your places.
You shouldn't have left that place.
I know.
We all make decisions with that.
I saw actually, just before I do my third entry here,
I saw a YouTube video where Quentin Tarantino, speaking of the Vista,
and speaking of James Cameron, talked about going to see Aliens on the day it opened.
My God, man.
That guy praised this fucking movie.
It was like the most I've ever doubted my opinion on a movie was hearing his praise of this.
I was like, I clearly am, I must be very wrong.
It's a pretty great fucking movie.
I don't think it's bad.
I just like that the first one's a horror movie, and the second one's an action movie,
and I'm just not as interested for whatever reason.
But his take was not that.
His take was that it was elevated and elevated, whatever.
Doesn't matter.
It was a very compelling argument.
I'll do for my third entry, because I already mentioned it.
And I've talked about doing this.
I've done rewatches of this already in the movie corner, but I'll do it again.
I rewatched Black Mass again.
This is a movie that I have now gotten into the habit of putting on roughly once a year.
I gotta tell ya, it gets better every time I watch it.
This is a fucking great movie.
Now, we saw this in the theater.
With James Adomian.
James Adomian.
In the front row.
At the Vista.
At the Vista, when it was not Tarantino's.
And by a chance running with Adomian, by the way.
Remember we just ran into him.
We were like, we're going to see Black Mass.
You wanna go?
And he's like, yeah.
We liked it.
I remember we reviewed it, and we were like, it was fine.
It was good.
Subsequent watches, man.
This movie is a fucking tour de force.
Every actor in this thing hits a grand slam.
And goddamn, dude, you forget.
You forget in such a short period of time, Johnny Depp was an unstoppable force as an actor.
This was kinda his last time at the Big Boy Plate, if I recall correctly.
It was, Pat, not only was it sort of the last time, it was the comeback one.
It was the one where they were saying, like, Depp is back in full swing here.
Because he had had some missteps.
My God, man.
He's terrifying in this movie.
He is Whitey Bolton.
You believe it.
I never am going, that's Johnny Depp.
The movie's just fucking awesome, man.
I think it's one of my favorites I've ever seen, Jesse Plemons.
The supporting cast, for the most part, are actors that I'm not too familiar with.
Meaning, like, the henchmen of the mob and stuff like that.
Who's Depp's wife?
Well, Depp's wife is...
I think it's Dakota Fanning, right?
No, no way.
I'm sorry, not Dakota Fanning.
Miami Vice.
Don Johnson's daughter.
Dakota Johnson.
Because she was in the remake of Suspiria, right?
Yeah.
She's Depp's wife.
Oh, and then...
What's -his -name is fucking incredible in this, man.
Oh, Julianne Nicholson, I like her.
Julianne Nicholson plays...
No, she plays Edgerton's wife.
She's great.
Yeah.
Edgerton in this is fucking tremendous.
I like Edgerton.
He's fucking tremendous.
Kevin Bacon?
It sold me, I'll watch it again.
I don't remember anything about it, really.
God, man.
It's just a really, really good gangster movie.
But I will say that I think the show stealer, aside from the more prominent characters,
is Peter Skarsgard playing that fucking cokehead down in Miami.
I mean, it is so believable.
You're like, he is this guy.
This man is a cokehead that lives in Miami who is out of his fucking mind.
And there's an awesome scene where you see that Depp realizes he needs to kill Peter's character.
He's too much of a liability.
Peter's supposed to do a hit on this highlight guy named Wheeler.
And they have a meeting and Depp realizes that this guy is too much of a liability and he has to kill him.
And they do this scene.
Depp's got a bag of $20 ,000 sitting with him.
And he goes, he goes, I want you to take the money and I want you to leave right now.
And Skarsgard's like, I don't get it.
And he's just being a fucking moron.
And Depp is going, take the fucking money, walk away.
And he's like, so you want me to do the hit?
He's like, no, I want you to not do the hit.
Take the fucking money.
You're not going to do the fucking hit.
And it's such an awesome scene where you're watching two characters play it so perfectly,
where you know exactly what's about to happen to this guy.
And this guy doesn't get it.
And he's playing it the perfect amount of freaked out, confused.
He's laughing nervously.
It's just an awesome, awesome movie.
It's an awesome scene.
I highly recommend Black Mass.
There you go.
Folks, let's talk about another Black Mass immaculate.
A story about a young nun played by Sidney Sweeney.
Joe, walk us through the plot because I read the Wikipedia today and I was like,
this movie is about nothing.
Yes.
Which is why the Seinfeld music playing at the top of it was not as what do you mean?
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
Oh, because it was about nothing.
Well, I remember not, I couldn't get into it at all because the plot wasn't really hitting
for me in any way.
And then I remember trying to read the Wikipedia at the time and I was like, this doesn't even
hold together as a story.
And reading it again today, because I hadn't seen the movie in a few weeks, I feel the
same way.
I don't even know what I was watching.
The movie's about, I mean, it shaves so incredibly close to the first Omen.
Yeah.
And they came out like the same day, basically.
And this is one of those things where you're like, look, you can have very similar scripts.
Like, it happens.
It happens.
That's not, I'm not saying anybody stole anything from anybody else.
But what I do think happened was one of these things got greenlit.
Somebody with inside info at another studio, you know, at a competing studio, knew that
this script was sitting on their desk and the other way around.
And they're like, hey, fucking fast track that thing because we're going to go up against
the other one.
I mean, they're just too similar.
It's very odd.
But and for them to have been released so close together is what makes it odd.
But I mean, but that movie just had so much more style than it needed.
It brought in great character actors to elevate it.
The story was pretty good.
The way it was filmed was really, really cool.
And this just kind of doesn't have anything to offer.
I mean, it looks particularly weak in comparison.
I got to tell you, this was so underwhelming.
I started in my head going, wait, does the first Omen suck too?
Did I just see that first and I'm not realizing?
But it's the same plot.
A nun from the States goes to Italy to be part of a convent.
She realizes the convent has very strict policies upon her arrival.
She befriends another young nun who kind of spits in the face of the authority a little bit
and is a little bit of a bad girl for a nun, just like in the first Omen.
Suddenly she becomes pregnant.
Now, that's where it differs from the first Omen.
Our main character becomes pregnant fairly early.
But then the similarities come back in because once she is pregnant,
you realize there are other women at the convent that are jealous of her that she's pregnant
and that they had become theoretically pregnant.
It's insinuated at one point, but for whatever reason, it didn't happen.
And it unfolds from there.
Some sinister things happen. Some spooky moments happen.
There's a priest.
That really is identical to the last Omen.
I mean, it's the same thing.
There's a priest sort of guiding her through all this, just like in the last Omen.
You don't know what his motives are, just kind of just like in the last Omen,
until they're revealed, just like in the last Omen.
Now, in the last Omen, it turns out that the priest is actually trying to help her.
In this one, it turns out he's kind of behind the entire thing.
Why? What's happening?
Well, they have a nail in the convent that is supposedly one of the nails that was used to crucify Christ.
He has taken DNA from the nail because the priest, before he became a priest, Pat,
now I don't know if you caught this detail.
Probably not.
Was a biogenesis, or geneticist, excuse me, before he became a priest,
which, I mean, you're getting into the Pope's exorcist territory there where it's like,
what are we talking about? What?
He became a priest.
He used the DNA and he's trying to, instead of in the first Omen,
what they're trying to do is raise the Antichrist in order to bring people out of fear
by giving them an enemy back to the church.
They're trying to resurrect Christ and bring people back to the church.
So, a little more of a pure motive at least, theoretically,
despite the pregnancy against the women's will part,
but then you find out there are women there that want to be pregnant and want to do it,
which means it's fucking pointless because in the first Omen,
why it's so sinister is because these women don't want this.
And it's a horrible sinister plan.
In this movie, they're trying to do something that's theoretically just,
that I can only imagine the average nun would leap at the chance to be the mother of the rebirth of Christ,
yet they still do it with subterfuge, which makes no sense
because then there are other nuns, like I said, that are aware of the plot that want to participate.
None of it makes any goddamn real logical sense.
There are a few genuine scares.
There were a few genuinely creepy things.
The cold open is pretty cool.
You've got a woman trying to...
The end is really gross and much exactly like the last Omen.
You've got a woman trying to escape the convict and the convent in the cold open.
You don't know why yet.
And as she's escaping, she's chased by these sinister figures in these black veils.
And in order to prevent her from escaping, they take her leg and they break it,
and they show the break happen through the skin.
And it's pretty gross and jarring.
Sydney Sweeney, let's be real, gives a really bad performance,
as she did in the romantic comedy with Glenn Powell.
I like her on Euphoria,
but she's just not bringing anything to the table here at all.
I thought she was good.
Okay, alright.
Look, I've never watched Euphoria.
I don't have any interest.
Again, this is all me being me.
I realize this is an unbased thing of judgment that I have with certain things.
But my assumption was kind of always,
you know, oh, they were on Euphoria kind of eye roll.
Like, okay.
It's like the new Brat Pack or something.
I just kind of don't care.
So I was surprised at...
Again, my problem to assume that Sydney Sweeney wasn't going to bring emotional death to it.
I thought she actually did.
I found her convincing as the nun.
You know, I found everybody in the film pretty convincing.
I just didn't care.
I cared for a period of time.
And for a 90 -minute movie, in fact, I think it's 89 minutes.
Which we appreciate.
I mean, at about the 45 -minute mark,
I was hitting enter on the remote to see where we were in the timeline.
And I was like, Jesus Christ.
Like, this only has 30 minutes left.
I feel like I've been watching it for like three hours or something.
It's...
You know, it's one of these things where once she realizes the plot and what is going on,
it's hard to imagine she couldn't find her way out of this place in some way, shape or form.
My justification as I was watching it was,
this is clearly a period piece, it's the 70s,
it's not as easy to just call for help, whatever.
And then she plans an escape route by she takes a chicken,
and she takes the chicken's blood,
and she covers herself in it to make it look like she's miscarrying
and she has to go to a hospital or she's going to die.
That I thought was a cool little detail.
And I was like, oh, wow, that's a real desperate measure and whatever.
But then as they're driving her to the hospital,
two things I had a big problem with.
The way they find out what she did was, they find the dead chicken under her bed.
Right.
So first off, I'm kind of like...
That's kind of on you, Sidney.
Yeah, wouldn't you hide the chick, throw it out the...
Something, I don't know, put it in a fucking sheet or something.
Like, I don't know.
So there was that.
And then the second thing is she's in the car,
and the way the people driving her to the hospital
find out that she's faking this thing
is they get a phone call and the priest whips out a cell phone.
And I'm like, wait a minute, this is present day?
This is present day?
The whole time I thought it was like...
Honestly, that didn't even register for me.
I just assumed the movie was 100 years old.
Honestly, I didn't even notice this.
That's how out of it I was.
You find out that there have been a bunch of mistrials
with these babies, just like in the first Omen.
They've kept the specimens of these mistrials
or a record of them.
In this movie, it's specimens.
In the first Omen, it's just pictures.
But they have them in jars of formaldehyde or whatever.
And what the explanation for that is,
is that they didn't have an actual virgin
or somebody who was pure enough or something like that.
But Sidney Sweeney is pure enough.
She is a virgin.
She is somebody who fits the bill
for what they're trying to do.
And then in the end of the movie,
when she has the baby, finally,
as she is, again, escaping,
in a scene that I had to mute,
because it's her not screaming directly into camera
in an extreme close -up for three straight minutes.
It is so, like, just horrid to watch.
And I don't mean horrid where, like,
wow, it's challenging and it makes you think.
I just mean, like, it's like,
guys, I don't want to watch this.
This is awful.
And also, if anybody can hear this coming from my house,
they're going to call the police right now.
I think that all the time,
because I watch it with my door open out of the deck,
and I'm like, I'm just blasting the neighborhood
with sounds of, like, a woman being tortured right now.
So anyway, she has the baby on these, like, rocks,
and then she stares at it in horror,
and it grunts or something, and she realizes,
you don't see it, but you realize,
oh, it's another malformed whatever.
And she kills it with a rock,
and that's the end of the movie.
And you're like, I don't know
what I'm supposed to feel here right now.
I don't know what's going on.
It would have made at least some interesting sense
if the baby did somehow come out pure,
and there was some ambiguity that,
what if this is Jesus Christ?
And then she ran off into the wilderness with it,
and you're like, dear God, where does this go?
And then that's where it ends?
But instead, it's like, no, it just ends
where the experiment always ends.
And then this, it's terrible
that she's impregnated against her will,
but then on top of it, this poor fucking animal baby
just got murdered with a rock.
Like, this is horrible.
I don't know what I'm supposed to feel right now
about any of this.
So that's where it ends.
That's where it ends.
The director was Michael Mohan, who did The Voyeurs,
which was a Amazon Prime erotic thriller
starring Sidney Sweeney,
that I actually thought was pretty good.
You know, I love an erotic thriller.
But yeah, this just felt real convoluted.
For the life of me, I don't understand
why they would have just shot it.
It just clearly needs another draft,
some more time in the incubator
that the story is not storying.
But yeah, hog down, unquestionably.
This was hard to even pay attention to.
Yeah.
My Hog was also down.
Maybe not quite as down as Pat's.
But down.
You know, down.
Where the down boys go.
You know, down, down.
What did you say this director is also done?
Sorry, you just said it.
Did The Voyeurs, which was a Sidney Sweeney
erotic thriller on Amazon Prime a few years back.
Okay.
Nudity, the whole nine.
And that's it?
Not bad.
Yeah.
And a couple of TV things or whatever.
What's your take on this euphoria show?
I've never watched it.
I have seen every episode.
I mean, it's only been two seasons.
It's clearly very chaotic behind the scenes.
It's hard.
I mean, it goes off the rails every week.
And it's hard to shake that it feels like
it's irresponsible and inappropriate.
It feels like watching something that should be illegal.
It's granted it's 29 -year -olds playing teenagers,
so it's better.
But still, it's like, this is weird to me.
It's a lot of very young sex and nudity.
And is that the show where the creator guy has
there's been some scrutiny about him?
Or was that the Johnny Depp daughter show?
Both.
He did both shows.
Oh, okay.
But both shows are just like extremely graphically
obsessed with sex to a point that's kind of
oppressive almost.
And the shows get very, very dark.
Now, on Euphoria, you've got Zendaya there.
And her story is about her battling her drug addiction.
And it involves no sex.
And it's just, she's great.
And her story is always very moving.
And her mentor or her sponsor is Coleman Domingo,
who is, of course, a great actor.
And it's got really great moments in the show.
But then, you know, they'll do like a half hour of
what just feels like gross treatment of these
young actresses at a certain point,
especially because the guy writing and directing
every scene is this kind of creepy guy in his 40s,
Barry Levinson's son, Sam Levinson.
Now, he has his wife as a producer,
which I think is probably there to be like,
but my wife's here.
This isn't creepy.
But when everything you've ever made as an artist
is about young people fucking,
it starts to look a little weird.
It starts to look like Larry Clark,
who did, you know, kids and bully and great movies.
But also, you got to kind of look at that guy like,
what are you doing here, pal?
You know.
All right, folks.
Well, we'll be back with, I believe, the deliverance.
And I believe Godzilla minus one.
And, you know, we got some stuff in the pipeline.
It's just not out yet.
You know, Heretic is supposed to be very good,
but it hasn't hit.
Oh, yeah.
I'm excited to see that.
Theaters yet.
This new Halle Berry horror movie,
I thought looked pretty cool.
The trailer was all right.
The early reviews are not great, but, you know.
It's half as good as Gothica.
I'm joderosacomedy on Instagram.
And I don't know, TikTok.
It's joderosacomedian, I think.
You know, I got shows, people.
Summerville, Massachusetts, December 7th.
Big holiday show.
Come on out for that.
It's going to be all new material.
And then the official tour starts in January,
the joystick tour, all new material,
hitting the clubs.
Dates are available on joderosa .com,
but I'll be in Toronto and San Diego and Chicago,
just to name a few.
And as always, come on out to Joey Roses.
If you're in New York, joeyroses .com.
And thank you all for your support.
We love that this Patreon is going strong.
Pat and I are in the talks now
of what potentially the next live event might be,
and we will keep you posted,
but we're hoping that we have something interesting
in the works.
Oh, it's interesting, folks.
I'm at ThePatrickWalsh on Instagram.
We've been loving the...
There was some weird issue with posting the Patreons
where it was like a live update,
so it led to a lot of commenting,
which was really cool.
It was fun reading everybody's comments.
But that was just a mistake.
We weren't trying to, like, do some weird live event
or anything on the Patreon.
But we love you guys.
We love reading all the comments.
We are at SeeYouInHellPod on Instagram.
We will see you next time, and we will see you in hell.