I'll see you in hell.
Welcome to We'll see you in hell.
It's your favorite podcast when it's time to talk genre flicks.
I'm talking horror, I'm talking sci -fi, I'm talking fantasy, I'm talking action, I'm talking,
you know, medieval Conan, dragon riding and around the pit of flames and the fucking witches of Eastwick fame.
Okay.
Yeah, here we go.
I'm Pat Walsh, on tonight's show we're talking about a picture called Dr. Sleep.
How are we talking about Dr. Sleep?
Dr. Sleep, DDS, he's a dentist who performs operations on your soul.
The Dr. Sleep is the unofficial, well it is official, sequel to The Shining.
I have not read the book written by Stephen King, I have read The Shining, I have not read Dr. Sleep.
Joe Hasen will hopefully be able to provide some context there.
I hadn't read all of it, I read some of it.
Oh, but I've read, well then, I read the important parts to know what was the dirty parts for what was different from the movie.
Yeah, well the rest of the pages were stuck together.
No, I've read, I got the audio book I'm excited because it seemed like a lot of stuff was left out of this movie
because the movie is surprisingly clear, we'll get to it, of course.
But it definitely seemed like the book would have really gone into that band of gypsies, you know,
and their day -to -day life and etc.
Shurking went there.
In the book they moonlight as a sketch group, they do a lot of improv stops.
It's unnecessary.
The ending, well we'll get to it, we'll get to it.
We'll get to Dr. Sleep.
In the meantime, we're sitting here, we got two micoltrus that now on the bottle say pure gold.
Or is that a type of micoltrus?
I got to say it's not a good beer.
You don't like it?
I like that.
It's not great.
You know, light, whatever you want to call it, but it's essentially water.
I thought you would have went for one of those support rows in there.
I wish I had.
Yeah.
But you know, you're drinking a shot, you want the smooth on the side.
But is this...
I mean, this is all they had.
This is not the normal micoltrub bottle.
The normal micoltrub bottle was dark.
No, this is organic light.
This is a whole new thing.
Okay.
But you know what I...
That's why it's called...
That's why it's called pure gold.
But you know what I think they did is I had last night a corona premium.
And I was like, what is this?
I look it up and it's a corona light.
Eventually, enough people thought corona lights sucked.
They were like, we got to change the marketing for this.
So it's actually...
No, it's not premium.
It's called corona premiere.
But all it is is corona light.
And it sucked.
Yeah.
That's how they took light off of the cigarette packs.
Not because people thought it sucked because the government was like, you're not allowed to say these are less dangerous.
Yeah.
Right.
So now you got to go...
I still do it.
I go in and you go...
Camel lights and they go...
What?
And you know...
Sorry.
Camel blues.
Oh wow.
I didn't know that.
Yeah.
You have to do it by color now.
Okay.
But...
But I'm excited because Miller...
Miller High Life has always been my favorite beer.
Miller Light.
Champagne.
It is.
And Miller Light is my usual go -to for light beer.
And now there's a beer called Miller 64, which is their, like, mic ultra.
Okay.
I'm excited to try it because Pat, I'll tell you.
Miller Light.
And I know it's Bud Sluggan, but tastes great, less filling.
Yeah.
I got no beef.
Where do you rank Bud Light, Miller Light, Coors Light?
I will do the Coors Light any day.
I do not like Bud Weiser and I do not like Bud Light.
Okay.
San Luis's own.
I was at the brewery this week.
I feel bad.
Like, I wish I liked Bud Weiser.
I love the bottle.
Yeah.
I love the idea of it.
It's just Bud Weiser and Bud Light tastes too sweet to me.
Yeah.
Where do you stand on the Bud Bowl?
Do you remember that?
I remember the Bud Bowl.
They also now have Bud Select, but it didn't replace Bud Light.
It's like supposed to be a more premium brand.
I mean, they're all just bullshit.
Wait, are you skipping right over the Bud Bowl?
The Bud Bowl was Bud Weiser and Bud Light.
Bottles.
Bottles animated poorly, like South Park style.
Having a baseball game.
Our football game, right?
I thought for a second.
You went so fast to Bud Select that.
I thought you thought the Bud Bowl was a type of drink.
I didn't have much to say about the Bud Bowl.
I remember it, of course.
It was, when I was a kid, I loved it, man.
I could not wait for the Bud Bowl.
What a weird marketing thing that worked.
It was.
Did you watch any of the dog show this year on Christmas Day?
Uh, Thanksgiving Day.
My mom was watching it.
Westminster.
vehemently.
And I am shot.
I will say this.
It's the first time I really kind of,
they watch it every year.
Yeah.
I've never really paid attention.
This is the first year I kind of listened in.
And I was shocked.
And how.
J. Peterman looked.
So that's where I was going.
No, no, no.
I was shocked in sync.
Perfect.
The best.
The best in show script.
I mean, literally it's just a transcript to one of these things.
I was like, my god almighty, it really is like this.
What I couldn't fathom was that every.
Every almost every dog handler is a woman.
And they're all wearing the dumpiest dresses I've ever seen.
Like these things that look like they wrap themselves in a down comforter or something.
You missed the, you missed the 60s when they showed a little leg.
And I was like a little like.
At the end.
But J. Peterman is in the Fred Willard role.
And I was enjoying hearing a smooth voice from Seinfeld, whatever.
But then they get to show him.
And I was like, whoa.
But then you remember it's been 20 years since Seinfeld.
I get it.
What is he just not a swab?
He looks like he's aged.
But who amongst us hasn't.
He was one of those Steve Martin guys where he had like white hair at 30.
Right. Yeah.
He's lost some swab for sure.
I think he's the one that said.
And this is when I was like, my god, it's if it is the Christopher Guest movie.
He goes up next, you know, the poor guy nicknamed Jackie D.
Actual name Jack Daniels.
That's a name I have said a few times at a bar.
And I was like, I was watching it at that exact moment.
That's when I turned it on.
And we didn't turn it off.
But yeah, and I think the bulldog won.
Yeah.
Even though they had the most gorgeous golden retriever I've ever seen that I was like in love with.
They have some ugly fucking dogs that took the Afghan wolf found comes out.
And I was almost vomited.
That would have been a cooler name for Afghan wigs.
Yes, exactly.
There are some real ugly dogs, but the golden retriever was gorgeous.
I wanted it to win.
I didn't even like that kind of dog.
But that's who my mom had.
My mom's money was on the golden retriever.
She was right.
Your mom was right.
Yeah.
The bulldog won and Heather told me I was in the shower.
But apparently the woman fell over in shock when the bulldog won.
She gasped her chest and fell over.
The owner of the bulldog.
Yeah.
Not the owner of the golden retriever out of like Joe.
But it was a fun day.
I enjoy watching dogs do their thing.
I love my parents dearly.
But I don't mean to shit on them.
But you hang out with your folks sometimes.
You're amazed at how much they don't know.
Oh, sure.
So when the bulldog won, my mom goes.
These bulldogs.
It's so any wonder they can breathe with their.
And I'm like, they can't.
This is a common problem with these bulldogs.
Yeah.
Like everybody knows they have these horrible.
Respiratory stories.
They got to stop breathing them because they're in pain their entire lives.
Yeah.
My mom had no clue.
I'd never tell you when I was watching.
Bohemian Rhapsody with my mom and her husband Tom.
At the two hour mark, he paused it to go to the bathroom.
I think it's up because boy, this star is born.
It's pretty good.
No way.
Two hours in.
Why would I make that up?
Why would I make up that elaborate story?
I'm not saying you made it up.
I'm just saying was he drunk?
I probably had a glass or two, but I don't think it was drunk.
It was just a funny mess.
Now Joe, I want to hit you with some news that I don't have to ask if you're sitting down.
I can see that you are, but I'm glad that you are because it's going to rock you to your core.
Okay.
Because on December 31st, not only will we say goodbye to another decade,
we will say goodbye to Frazier on Netflix streaming.
Is it going to NBC streaming?
I have to assume, but who knows when that's even going to launch.
Listen, man.
Now, meanwhile, I'm midway through season four.
I can't make it to the end of the month.
I know you could, but I can't.
Oh, you could do it.
It just takes a little commitment.
You just got one of the rough seasons eight and nine.
It gets...
No, I think like...
I'm not a huge fan of the season where like...
Niles...
This is grandchats, by the way.
Somebody has where this segment went.
This is grandchats.
It's somewhere around six or so, like Niles, like his love of dafty comes out in the open.
And but she's engaged to Donnie, his divorce lawyer.
And Niles.
Cooper tries, Donnie.
I forget the actor's name.
You know him.
He plays the...
He plays the dentist on curb when Larry doesn't want to roll his sleeve up.
And the guy's like, I don't have time for this.
Oh, not the dentist.
He has to give him the shot or whatever.
Okay.
That guy.
He's a character actor.
He's great.
He's great on the show.
But...
That season, and then like during that period Niles ends up marrying this other woman who's very
marriage -like.
And then like, she turns out to be awful and he's got to get rid of her.
And then he's got to pull dafty up.
It's just a very...
I'm just not a fan of that whole storyline.
Okay.
But once dafty and Niles are officially together again, like together officially out in the open,
to me, that's when it starts to get good again.
All right.
But there's some great stuff coming up.
Because you're right in where Niles is getting finally divorced from Maris.
I think.
Or like it's about to happen.
It's about to happen.
And there's really, really funny stuff where she cuts him off completely financially.
He eventually has to move into this apartment building called the Shangri -La.
Okay.
It's like, you know, like one of these like open...
It's Seattle, but it's basically one of these like open -air LA apartment complexes.
Right.
And he starts wearing like Hawaiian shirts because he's trying to fit in with everybody.
He's having like a nervous breakdown.
All right.
I'm into that.
Yeah.
It's...
You got some good stuff coming up.
But look, that show...
I'm not even sad to hear about it going off streaming, because that show has given me so much.
I will happily just purchase the box set at this point.
I owe that that much.
It was...
So I bring the moment up to...
That brings me in at my next point.
We're drinking.
Cyber Monday.
And Black Friday all that.
Okay.
I don't go out to the stores.
No.
But, you know, I always get on Amazon.
What are the deals, whatever.
And as recently as five years ago, you'd get on Amazon, which is an evil corporation.
We all know it.
Somehow they don't pay taxes.
Nobody understands it.
But, you get on to Amazon.
And they would have the most amazing fucking deals.
Really, all I looked at was Blu -rays and vinyl, whatever.
But I would get on there and be like, holy shit.
Like you can get whole seasons of things for $5.
You can get...
You know, some...
I think the Warner Herzog box set I got for like $20 or something.
Like right after it came out.
That's crazy.
They just have these amazing deals.
And now as they've become the richest corporation in the world,
the deals have dried up to the point where every Black Friday,
they're putting up the same shit that nobody wants.
This year they put up the Dark Shadows box set.
The series, which was like a soap opera.
So maybe that shows good.
Maybe it was.
I never saw it.
I hated the movie.
But it's the Dark Shadows box set.
You know, it's like 50 DVDs or something.
And the cost on it is $299.
On Cyber Monday.
So you're like, you know what?
If you had made this $40, I might go,
I'll roll the dice and check out Dark Shadows.
Right.
Clearly they just have this warehouse full of shit that nobody wants.
And they're not even lowering the price on it.
So I scrolled through page after page of bargains that weren't bargains.
Fuck you, Amazon.
Fuck you.
I wish I'd gone to Best Buy.
They always had good deals on Blu -ray's on North Cybership.
I didn't go Blu -ray this year at all because as you can see,
my shelf is, yeah, you're moving.
Yeah, it's, it's, it's stacked.
I'm way behind.
But I got, I'll tell you the video game deals this year were insane on Amazon.
Amazon Best Buy.
I didn't even look.
Walmart and GameStop.
GameStop particularly.
The deals were fucking insane on video games like $60 or games for like $10.
It was crazy.
So I spent $100 total.
I got like six PlayStation 4 games that are all like five star games.
But that's all I did.
I didn't, I didn't have the energy.
I went to the DVD page on Amazon.
I couldn't do it.
It was like, I was trying to scroll through and then it was doing that thing.
I hate when they do this on Amazon.
It shows the movie and then under it is a price range.
Oh yeah, yeah.
I think what is this?
Yeah, they also love to do deals that have already passed.
So you get on there to see what they've got and it shows you like,
oh, there was one good thing at 7 a .m. this morning and I missed it.
Thanks for letting me down again.
Yeah.
Why do you got to tell me what I missed?
I missed it.
Yeah.
It was you Amazon.
I was with a friend of a friend.
She wanted to, this was the best deal I saw of Black Friday.
She was saying how her six year old kid or whatever.
All he wanted was a PlayStation 4.
Yeah.
And we went to GameStop.
She got a PlayStation 4 with three games for $200.
So I was like, that is an insane deal, but you just can't watch this PS4 normal.
That would have been probably 400 bucks.
Okay.
You know, I mean, it was, it was a really, really good deal.
I got mine for judging a film festival.
A PlayStation film festival.
Have you played it ever?
And I've never played it.
And I want to play it.
And I have games and I have not played it.
I'm sorry.
You should play it sometime.
I would like to.
I always just feel like with anything like I don't need another vice.
I'm all vices.
So like, I don't want to get addicted, but I should give it a shot.
I don't think it'd be a vice.
I think you just have a fun time.
You know, you probably play in the game.
All right, Joe.
I'll do it.
You know, just a little way to entertain yourself.
I'm going to participate in scary stuff, but I'll do it.
Well, that's fine.
You don't have to.
Speaking of scary stuff.
I got a quick one.
Where is it here?
I get it in my phone.
I keep a list of this stuff in my phone because I can't fucking remember shit anymore.
Actually, this was a great, a really great Amazon deal.
It wasn't a black Friday deal.
I got the universal monster's box set.
Meaning the complete box set, which is all 80, whatever it is, universal monster.
The classic movies on Blu -ray for 50 bucks.
This was an insane fucking deal that just it was on like a random Tuesday.
Yeah.
But this box set, if you don't know about it, it's worth checking out.
Unfortunately, it usually runs for significantly more, you know, much higher price than that.
I have the universal monster's box that was the essentials, you know, the biggest.
I had that one.
Yeah.
For a while, that was the only one you could get on Blu -ray.
I was like the main eight or whatever.
But they have, they have finally released the full, complete universal monster set.
Minus maybe three movies.
Again, it's like 80 movies as an exaggeration.
It's probably, but it's probably fucking 50 movies.
Right.
But it's every Frankenstein, every werewolf, every creature of the black lagoon, every vampire one.
It's incredible.
It's out there.
It got the best.
Well, it's the price of the bat.
No, because it's the classic.
It's every variation of the classic.
It's every franchise film from the classic monsters.
Do you know what I mean?
Oh, I remember seeing that box and each, each thing in the middle of it has like five movies, like five Wolfman movies.
Exactly.
And it also includes all of the Abbott and Castello meat dot dot dot movie.
Right.
I'm going to sell me the invisible man.
I'm going to sell me Frankenstein.
Yeah.
So if you want this, it's currently $83 .64 on Amazon.
That's a great price for what you're getting.
Right.
And these things look beautiful because I had the truncated set and it looked amazing.
This is just the expanded version.
But it's worth grabbing.
In fact, while I'm talking about this, I am going to not forget to pull my truncated sets so I can now trade it in for other things that I would rather have.
Okay.
Because now I've got the bigger set.
But there's a good scary stuff for you.
And a good Amazon deal.
But not anymore because it's over.
But I got it.
So you're like what I just complained about.
You're telling people what they miss.
Yeah.
The one thing I don't like that they do in the expansion set.
Okay.
So this is the original.
A original horror classic classic and high -definity than the one I have.
This one actually came with a nice little booklet.
Yeah.
And some postcards of the different monsters.
The new one has the.
The expanded one has the postcards.
I don't think it has the booklet.
But you know, whatever.
It's not the end of the world.
But yeah, this is a nice little.
It's very nice.
You don't have this.
I have a similar set.
But it's thinner and it looks different.
It's got 3D glasses for the creature of the black ogoon and blah, blah, blah.
Well, it's American.
Yours is British.
Oh.
That little 15 at 15 in the center or 16 sticker.
But you've got these movies.
I do.
Yes.
All right.
I was going to give it to you.
Oh.
I mean, I don't.
Yeah.
Well, that's that's good.
Thank you, Joe.
And let's get on with the show 20 minutes in.
And also on with the hard and Joe.
She's got it all but fucking every night.
She is but fucking every night.
She's always but fucking her down the way over.
It's a great song sports.
The soul is my favorite Huey Lewis song.
Mine too.
That's the best Huey Lewis album sports.
Sports is fantastic.
Uh, and that is my favorite.
My band, my old band used to cover that song.
Okay.
Uh, that's a fun, fun tune to do.
Uh, what's, uh, any of that box?
Yeah.
You, you check it out.
No, I got the, it's a different set.
But like I said, yours is British.
Mine isn't, so I'm not going to, I'm not going to take it.
You can sell it.
Make some money.
All right.
Well, if you want to take it and, I don't know.
I was just trying to give you something.
I appreciate it.
Let's head over to the movie corner.
I'm going to start things off if I may with a picture called Lucy in the sky.
With diamonds?
Uh, just no, no diamonds.
It is a movie.
Sorry.
Uh, you know, it's one of those like when I work to blockbuster these movies and show up.
And you'd be like, wait a minute, this is two big stars, a big writer director.
Why did I not hear about this coming to the theater?
And then you realize it's because it doesn't really work.
This is a movie you may have heard about.
It's sort of between, uh, theaters and, and DVD now.
But it's called Lucy in the sky directed by Noah Holly who does the Fargo TV show,
which I love.
And it stars Natalie Portman and John Ham.
Natalie Portman is playing the astronaut who becomes obsessed with the other astronaut and drives cross -country.
This, this movie.
Okay.
The most interesting aspect of the story was that she wore a diaper as she drove cross -country.
So she could just shitter pants because she wanted to get to him so much.
Um, and that is not in this movie.
So they cut that probably because they knew that America wouldn't sympathize with a hero who is
shitting her pants throughout the entire movie.
And I get it.
I do.
Uh, but Lucy in the sky is a movie that does what a lot of movies have been doing lately.
A lot like in the past year.
And I hadn't seen it since back in the day.
Spike Lee's Kirkland does this amazing thing that at the time I was blown away by where
it's that Kirkland is an awesome movie about a family in the 70s.
Delroy Lindo and Angela Bassett and a bunch of kids.
Whenever she's with her family and having fun and singing in dancing at the Jackson five and whatever else,
it's a standard widescreen shot.
When she goes to live with her aunt who is very strict and religious and closed off,
the aspect ratio changes and it shows her squished up and everyone there is squished up.
In a theater, this caused people to go insane.
They were like, what is this?
What's wrong with the projector?
What's wrong with the movie?
It really was a big problem because people hadn't seen it before.
Spike Lee gets no credit for being such an innovator.
Now this messing around with aspect ratios happens a lot.
The lighthouse with Bobby Pattinson and Willem Defoe has giant black bars on the left and right of the screen.
Two -thirds of the screen wasn't being used.
I've been seeing that a lot waves.
The movie waves toyed with different aspect ratios.
I really think they all got it from Kirkland, frankly, definitely waves.
But this movie does it too.
Almost for every new scene, there's a different aspect ratio.
It's a lot.
The movie was not interesting or artistic enough to pay off this choice.
So really, you're just watching a movie that doesn't work,
but also is changing aspect ratios every five minutes.
So it's like going through the settings on your Blu -ray.
And it just doesn't work.
It's passable enough.
It would be good for a plane because it's just below average, but it's also okay.
I can't recommend it, however.
It's not a great movie.
All right.
But watch the Fargo show, especially seasons one and two.
Fair enough.
9 -11.
Excuse me.
I'm going to try to stick with the theme here of bat shit movies.
Okay.
Because the news psycho that we're going to do before we review Doc's sleep is about a bat shit movie.
That's a teaser.
But on the recommendation of our friend Jared Logan,
I bought on Blind Faith and watched a film called The Devil Doll starring Lionel Barrymore.
Never seen it.
It's an old horror movie.
It is from 1936.
Okay.
Right off the bat.
Any movie from 1936.
That's horror is going to be a little extra creepy.
Yeah.
I'm just going to read you the synopsis here.
Wrongfully convicted of a robbery and murder Paul Lavon played by Lionel Barrymore.
Breaks out of prison with a genius scientist who has devised a way to shrink human beings.
Okay.
When the scientist dies during the escape, Lavon heads for his lab using the shrinking technology to get
even with those who framed him.
That's the basic plot.
What that really means is,
is Lionel Barrymore, yes, relation to Drew Barrymore, shrinks down these people,
and then sells them as dolls to the people that wronged him.
So these dolls can then help him exact his revenge, you know, when the lights go out
and the people don't realize the dolls can move around.
And the way he does this is he pretends to be an old lady.
I was with you till right then.
Okay.
So the entire convincing is the costume.
It's pretty considering it's pretty convincing.
All right.
It's very Mrs. Doubt.
It's like a Mrs. Doubtfire.
Right.
Like he, it's as convincing as Mrs. Doubtfire.
Okay.
You know it's not a little lady,
but they don't know and you kind of get why they don't know.
Right.
But that's basically the whole movie is him going in and being like this old lady
and being like, please buy some of my dolls and then they do.
And then it's him walking around a corner and pulling the wig off and his fucking hair is crazy.
And he's like, I'll kill you all.
And Jared thought this was funny or scary or both.
He, not scary.
That's definitely not scary.
No, he was just real quick.
Are you in town Saturday?
Yeah.
Well, Saturday night I have plans.
But yeah, I'm around Saturday.
Can you see misery at midnight at the Vista?
The misery on the big screen.
I might, I might be, I'm supposed to go to a party that I was going to actually invite you to go to.
Well, I'm leaving at 1130 go to this movie.
I got to see misery on that big screen.
Damn.
I might be able to.
I don't know.
The, if you're in town, it's December 15th.
Come by and see at least me and me and Joe.
Don't talk to me too much.
It'll be midnight.
I'll be high as a kite.
Anyway, go watch the, no, Jared did not think it was scary.
Jared was like, I believe it was that his daughter's baby shower.
Yeah.
I think that was the, he just, he cornered me.
We were talking about movies, but he got real intense about this movie.
And he's like, you got to see this fucking thing.
It's crazy.
I'm going to, I'll watch for it on TCM.
It's probably on next week or something.
I love to see him lately.
I got it in a box with, who else was in this box?
Doctor X and mad love.
Okay.
Those will be the other films I review on this.
Mad loves also, Lionel Barrymore, right?
I think so.
Did you buy a Lionel Barrymore box that?
No, I bought a classic horror movies.
It was like one of the, in fact, I think it was one of those goddamn
Turner classic movies box sets.
Okay.
I'll, I'll figure it out.
I'll figure it out.
All right.
But anyway, that's the first in that shit movies that I'll be talking about this evening.
Okay.
I saw high life.
Speaking of Robert Pattinson, which I was doing with the lighthouse a moment ago.
We may do that on a future one, or we may not, but I'm not going to talk about it in case the lighthouse.
I'm sure a lot of people have a lot to say about that.
High life.
Star of Robert Pattinson is directed by Claire Dennis.
It is a movie that opens with Pattinson and a baby on a spaceship.
And right away you're just kind of like, well, I've never seen a baby in a, in a spaceship in a movie.
It was kind of cool.
But they're the last survivors of this dangerous mission to the outer limits of the solar system.
And they're heading towards a black hole.
And you kind of learn what happened on this flight to space.
Andre 3000 plays a role.
There's some other actors you might recognize.
But Pattinson is great.
The movie Gene Triple Horn is in the film.
And actually, there's no way that's Gene Triple Horn.
There's just no way.
Why would I say that?
Let me look up who it really is.
Would you wait?
Would you just wait for me to see who it is?
Oh, Juliet Benosh, sorry.
She actually looks a lot like Gene Triple Horn.
But high life is an insane film as well.
Juliet Benosh is basically trying to create life.
And the entire fleet or flight has to be celibate.
So sexual activity between the prisoners is prohibited.
They're trying to create a child through artificial insemination.
Usually is amongst prisoners.
Yes.
On this ship, the ship is equipped with something called the box.
This is a box where it's not a term you use when you're trying to prevent people from having sex.
Is that that same car?
The same car.
People go into the box to masturbate because they're not allowed to have sex.
So you're watching this and little by little, it is more and more obsessed with sex and masturbation
and specifically semen.
Semen is very precious commodity.
I can't even begin to tell you how much semen talk and et cetera is in this movie.
I found it baffling.
I found it confusing.
It is very original.
Do not get me wrong.
But it just wasn't for me.
It made me feel stupid.
Maybe one of those space movies that you watch again and suddenly are like, oh, I get this.
But really, it seemed to me like jizz in space.
It was just a two hour movie about jizz in space, the procurement of jizz, this desperate attempt to artificially make a baby on a spaceship.
And I know people love it.
It got great reviews.
I gotta tell you it wasn't for me.
All right.
But I also wasn't bored.
So take that for what it's worth.
All right.
Next on my list is also from this book said it's a film called Mad Love as I said.
Not the one.
Interestingly enough, there's a movie called Mad Love with Drew Barrymore.
I was gonna say yeah, not that one.
This is not Lionel Barrymore.
All right.
This is based on a novel called The Hands of Orlock.
Okay.
It starts Peter Laurie as a man named Dr. Goggle.
Probably named for him.
I love Peter Laurie.
Yeah.
The plot revolves around Dr. Goggle's accession with a young actress named Yvonne Orlock.
When Stephen Orlock's hands are destroyed in a train accident, Yvonne brings him to Goggle, who claims to be able to repair them as Goggle becomes obsessed to the point that he will do anything to have Yvonne.
Stephen finds that his new hands have made him an expert knife -thrower.
Okay.
There you go.
How was this thing?
I got to be honest with you.
Yeah.
It's considered a cult classic.
I watched it front to back.
Yeah.
I can't remember a fucking stitch of this thing other than Peter Laurie is out of his fucking mind in it.
He always was.
I mean, it's the guy couldn't have been regular in life, right?
I guarantee you creep people out on set.
He was trying to peek into other trailers.
Yeah.
All I remember is he is just fucking batshit in this thing.
I don't remember a lot of the plot points.
You know, Laurie's great in it.
He's fucking great in it.
You know, he just he just reeks of sweat throughout the entire thing.
And that's it.
I guess I probably shouldn't have done this one because I don't really remember it.
Okay.
But I did enjoy it enough that I wanted to keep it and I do want to see it again.
It's got 100 % approval rating on right.
Well, old movies always get a pass.
There have been a few remakes.
I'm trying to see if the Barrymore version doesn't know.
That's not a remake.
Folks, last night I went to the new Beverly cinema here in Los Angeles owned by Quentin Tarantino.
And I saw what I thought was one of the greatest double features they've ever put together.
Fargo and a simple plan.
And it's what you want in a double feature because these are two movies I knew I loved very much.
But there's something that happens when you watch two movies back to back that they can't help but like inform each other.
Make you look at each other, think about each other.
These are two snowy thrillers from the mid to late 90s.
Set in the Midwest about people doing increasingly bad things.
Simple plan probably got green lib because of the success of Fargo.
It's based on a phenomenal novel by Scott Smith who also wrote the ruins, which became the movie the ruins, which I liked a lot too.
He's a great suspense writer.
Stephen King called it one of the best thrillers ever written and I honestly agree.
Watching them last night, here's what my experience was.
Fargo is a masterpiece. Fargo is one of the best movies ever made.
No one in the world doesn't love Fargo.
You're watching it. You're just delighted by it. It's funny as shit.
It has three of the best performances ever.
William H. Macy is incredible as Jerry Lundergaard.
Francis McDormand is incredible as Margie Gunderson.
And Steve Buscemi is incredible as whatever his character's name is.
And at the time, they were all pretty much new to my eyes.
So I was just like, who are these three amazing actors? This is incredible.
I love this.
And on the big screen, Roger Deacon's cinematography, Roger Deacon's is our best living cinematographer.
I talked about him on the, my other Pat's movie podcast.
He did 1917, which I had seen.
He is an amazing photographer seeing those shots.
Every shot of Fargo could be a painting on the wall.
Seeing on the big screen was great. I loved it.
The movie ends.
And a simple plan fires up.
I would have always said, simple plan is a masterpiece too.
It's amazing.
It is such a great underrated little movie.
But watching them back to back, here's what happened.
For 10 minutes, you're watching a simple plan.
And I'm like, it couldn't help but suffer in comparison to Fargo.
Right.
You're like, okay, this movie I thought was so great.
Now I'm watching it after a true, perfect movie.
And I'm feeling it kind of be a little sluggish, whatever else.
Okay.
By the end of a simple plan, my friend agreed with me.
We looked at each other.
My friend had never seen simple plan.
He loves Fargo.
We both agreed that the two movies are equal.
I'm prepared to call a simple plan an equal movie to Fargo.
Because by the end of it, yes, it's much slower.
Yes, it's much sadder than Fargo.
It is a depressing as hell movie.
I've never seen simple plan.
It's sadder than Fargo.
You've never seen a fucking simple plan.
No.
You want to come to the house and watch it?
That's what we should do tonight.
Maybe.
I'll watch it again one night later.
Then I don't want to spoil it.
Don't thrive it.
No, just you can sit.
It's okay.
No.
It is the ending.
We spoiled everything on this podcast.
My God, this movie is depressing.
But it's about the human nature, the human spirit.
But it's a realistic portrayal.
And that's what I love about it.
It is dark as fuck.
And so good.
The audience was clearly just riveted by it.
I think a lot of the theater had not seen it.
And by the end of it, I said these movies are equal
because while it doesn't have the originality
and the freshness of a Fargo, which was like
what the hell is this.
It takes every situation and every character
a lot more seriously.
And at the end, you are devastated
and there's tears in your eyes and etc.
Fargo doesn't come anywhere near that.
Simple plan is a much deeper movie than Fargo.
A much more interesting movie than Fargo, frankly.
And I consider these two to both be about perfect films.
The reason for simple plan success is the direction
by Sam Raimi, who is obviously a great director,
evil dads, drag me to hell, etc.
But why does he not work in this genre more?
He tried it again with a gift, which was about half as good
to decent movie.
It's got Katie Holmes topless.
But simple plan seems to be his wheelhouse.
This is a genre of films that not many people can do.
But he does such an amazing job with it.
He knows just how to tweak the tone,
just how to let things be funny,
but not let them be so funny they distract from the story.
And honestly, Raimi is like best friends with the Colin Brothers.
I would almost guarantee he showed them this movie
and I bet they were jealous of it.
It feels like a Colin Brothers movie without the humor
and the snarkiness that they can't help but do.
And I think it's all the more effective for it.
Bill Paxton's best performance of all time.
And I'm a huge Bill Paxton fan.
He is incredible in the movie.
Bridget Fonda is incredible as his wife.
Brent Briscoe, who you don't know by name,
but is a big fat hillbilly,
is amazing in this movie,
should have been nominated.
And Billy Bob Thornton, who was nominated,
is one of the best actors of all time.
And I think a simple plan is slight,
it's on an equal par with his sling blade performance
because it feels more real and lived in and less like a performance.
I love sling blade as one of my favorites.
Billy Bob in this movie is like so many guys
that grew up with him Missouri.
The movie feels real.
It almost feels like a documentary at times.
It was a revelation for me and I already knew I loved it.
It's an A plus.
Bargo's an A plus.
Two great movies.
I've talked long enough.
Well, I think that's an interesting point you bring up
about that movie versus Bargo,
even though I've never seen this movie.
I think the Coen Brothers make excellent movies,
but on an emotional level,
they come from much more of a newer approach than a personal approach.
A lot of the time.
And I think that that's an interesting insight.
Well, and Bargo, you know,
both movies are kind of noir.
Both movies are kind of the same thing.
People stumble upon a lot of money
and everyone goes nuts trying to get it.
But like, they're also both super moral.
Fargo in the end,
it narrows it down to that one minute speech
by Francis McDorma,
where she says,
you know, here you are.
And it's a beautiful day.
And all you want is a little bit of money.
Don't you know there's more to life than a little bit of money?
Don't you know that?
That's a scene that can kind of miss me up.
I don't think the Coen Brothers are devoid of heart or anything else.
No, no, no, no.
But I hear, I completely hear what you're saying.
Simple plan leans completely into it.
And it feels so moral
that even though the movie is violent and has like,
I mean, this,
the theater was sheer like it was a grind house movie at certain points.
But I'll be damned if it isn't just like,
really, really.
I mean, it's so character driven that you care so much about everybody in it.
But it's very moral.
It almost feels like a movie you could,
you could show it like a church.
Because it just,
it just goes to show you what can happen when people agree to you,
when people are awful.
And it goes to just darker.
It's almost like a parable and darker and darker places.
I fucking love that movie.
And I hope,
Sam Raimi who I assume is in director Jail because of that God awful fucking James Franco Wizard of Oz movie.
I hope he's looking for something like this.
I hope he uses his cloud to get another little movie like this, man.
I know Ben Stiller tried to make a simple plan for like ten years.
It was his dream project.
And he loves dark movies like that.
I get it.
But I'm glad it was Raimi because he was the right man for the job.
Nice.
All right.
We're all closed with one we've both seen.
There's also bad shit.
And then I got to get to this screaming in because man.
Oh man.
Dead and buried.
I recommended this to you.
And it's fucking nuts.
Yeah.
I heard about it.
Full credit on 80s all over,
which is tragically now defunct the Scott Weinberg and Dreamy Queenie podcast where they went through every movie released in the 80s.
And I had never heard of it.
They raved about it.
I saw it out and holy cow.
It's essentially the plot essentially is.
It opens with a guy photographing a nude woman or I'm sorry a guy photographing a woman who he has just met.
And she starts to become very seductive during the photography session.
It starts out sort of innocent enough.
And then she starts taking her clothes off and coming on to him and.
It's a great setup right off the bat because they established this guy in the first few minutes as seemingly at least what I thought was going to be the main character.
And you know this girl gets this guy basically on his knees because he thinks he's going to have sex.
And then these town folk descend on him and murder him brutally.
And that sort of Sullivan opening.
Yeah.
It's a great opening throws you for a curve.
And then that's our that sort of thing.
It happens a few times throughout the first act in a half of the movie until our main player has realized something weird is going on in the town here.
What's happening.
And the big reveal.
This is why it's bad shit.
Is that the grandpa from Willy Wonka, Jack Albertson, who is also the town corner is taking the dead people in town and reanimating them.
Which it's a weird thing when you finally confront the reality of this in the movie because it's it's not that bad of a thing.
It's bad that they're murdering people obviously in order to get this done.
Sure.
But the main character is very against becoming one of these zombies.
But when you see the way these zombies function and live, they kind of just live like normal people.
It's very weird.
It's not like you're wandering around, you know, needing to eat brains or anything like that.
Right.
They're just sort of just people that just live and stay young and whatever and once in a while they got to kill a fucking tourist.
So it's a different approach to the whole zombie mythos.
It's crazy low budget.
But it's a fun movie.
It's a very fun movie.
It's really fun.
And he plays, I mean, it's so weird.
I don't know that I've ever seen that guy from Charlie and the chocolate factory and anything else.
But man, he is a fucking prick in this thing.
Yeah.
He was a character actor.
I mean, he was in a lot of shit, but this is like the first time he played a villain, I'm sure.
I'm not sure.
And he's not a villain really till the end.
That's the twist is that, you know, he turns out to be the mad orchestrator of this whole, you know, right, crazy scheme.
But, but it's a fun flick, man.
And it's worth seeing.
And it's one of those ones that I've passed by a million times on like Amazon Prime or whatever.
And the cover or the thumbnail they use for the version of the poster they use is.
It's like a person's face, like coming out of the clay and the imprint of a person's face coming out of the clay and the ground or whatever.
It's sort of a weird poster and it's a little misleading because you're not quite sure what it is.
But I'd passed it a million times and you said you got to see this thing.
And I was like, yeah, I don't know why I've never watched it.
I've always just kind of scrolled right past it.
But the name alone dead and buried.
I mean, that sounds like a fun movie to watch.
Very fun movie.
It's on shutter.
And what I've learned about shutter is sadly they don't tell you when things are dropping off.
So you got to just watch for them.
Yeah.
But shutter remains great.
I can't get enough of the sight.
They're making no money off them, but it is what it is.
They're wonderful.
Watching those three homelands with Joe Bob was great.
I'm so excited about the Chris.
I'm not home alone, Jesus Halloween.
I was like, what?
I'm very excited about the Christmas thing whenever he's got coming up.
I was trying to say Halloween but thinking of Christmas.
By the way, I'm going to do one very quick bonus.
There's a new documentary on Netflix called The Movies That Made Me.
They just added to the site.
I saw that.
It's probably the guys to do the toys that made it.
The movies that made us.
I haven't seen toys that made us but.
That's a great show.
I'm going to check that out.
It's about one toy each week.
Each episode is a toy.
So the first season is like Masters of the Universe, Star Wars and Barbie.
That's cool.
You know, and then the second season is like GI Joe Hot Wheels.
Right.
You know, it's fucking awesome.
The Masters of the Universe episode is fucking incredible.
Yeah.
It's really funny.
It's really crazy.
Okay.
The whole story.
It's awesome.
Yeah.
I will watch.
I saw that picture of me this weekend.
I looked through a photo album, saw me dressed as Orco from He -Man for Halloween.
And I was like, I don't think I ever liked He -Man.
Why would I be the last year?
Yeah, last year.
Well, anyway.
Anyway, it was.
I'm about to board a plane back to LA.
And I downloaded all four episodes of this.
I watched them all on the plane.
My God, if you're traveling for Christmas, you couldn't do better than to enjoy a drink on the
plane and watch four episodes of the movies that made me.
It's mindless fun.
And the four movies are Dirty Dancing, which I have been to Leehead.
Very little interest in, but I watched it anyway.
Home Alone, which was my favorite of the three.
They talked to Chris Columbus and Daniel Stern.
It's great.
Ghostbusters.
And Die Hard.
And they have great stories.
They talk to the screenwriters.
They talk about all the problems behind the scenes.
Usually, these documentaries act like everything was peaches and cream.
But what I loved about it is they dug deep.
They talked about how home alone was originally set up at Warner Brothers.
Warner Brothers was like, the budget's getting too high.
It was $13 million.
So they cut them loose.
And it went on to, you know, gross $300 million.
And people got fired and et cetera.
But they really put people on blast.
They tell you who got fired.
They tell you everything.
All the gritty details.
And it's a great series.
Please watch those.
The Home Alone One is my favorite.
All right.
And let's get to the picture at hand.
Joe, tell them what Doc sleeps about.
Hold on.
Oh, what?
I got to do this.
Oh, okay.
I got it.
We're going to go a little longer.
But I got to do this screen at hand.
This comes to us from movieweb .com.
This is the link I see for the story.
Far as come to script exists.
And it's pretty crazy.
I'm like, what could far as come to possibly be?
Roth, the writer, explains that he written a sequel.
The first one was this fucking runaway hit.
Yeah.
You know, the biggest movies of all time.
They thought it would be good.
They thought it would be big.
But not, I don't think they expected to be that big.
So he says, I literally turned in the script the day before 9 -11.
Tom and I, director Robert Semeckas, got together on 9 -11 to sort of
commiserate about how life in America was and how tragic it was.
We looked at each other and said this movie has no meaning anymore in that sense.
So 9 -11 sort of killed Far as God because everything changed.
Old America went through a growth spurt, if you will.
Into New America.
So this is what the movie was.
The story, this is the commentary, then I'll go to the quote.
The story was going to take place with Gump in the 1990s where his young son,
and now let me just jump to the quote because it's going to spoil it.
Here's the quote from the writer.
It was going to start with his little boy having AIDS.
So Jenny gave Haley Joel Osman AIDS.
No, Haley Joel is the young forest.
No, wait.
Oh, you're almost Haley Joel.
Jenny had AIDS in 4 -0.
Okay, no, no, no, that I know.
But I thought, I thought Haley played far as when he was young.
He plays the kid.
Okay, sorry.
I was going to start with his little boy having AIDS and people wouldn't go to class with him in Florida.
Oh, boy.
Ready for this?
Yeah.
Next line.
We had a funny sequence.
Where they were busing in Florida at the same time.
So people were angry either about the busing or kids having to go to school with a kid who had AIDS.
I'm so sad I didn't make this.
So there was a big conflict.
That's this is the quote.
There was a big one.
One scene I had forest in the back of OJ Simpson's Bronco.
He would look up occasionally but they didn't see him in the rear view mirror and then he'd pop down.
The big event in the movie, which you could see was only diminished.
No, no, sorry.
The big event in that which you could only see was only diminished in tragedy.
I guess because it's the same tragedy.
Okay, every day he'd go wait for his Native American partner.
I guess far as comp was dating a Native American woman.
She taught nursery school at like sort of a government building in Oklahoma City.
And he was sitting on the bench waiting for her to have lunch and all of a sudden the building behind him blows up.
So they're going to have him sitting in front of the 20.
All right, they got to make this movie.
They got to make this thing.
I had him as a ballroom dancer.
Never forget, Jenny.
Yeah, I had him as a ballroom dancer.
I guess that was going to be like the ping pong thing.
And then eventually just as sort of a charity kind of thing.
He would dance with Princess Diana.
Yeah.
Jesus Christ, dude.
That sounds amazing.
And the Bollywood remake of First Gump just came out.
Who's about to come out?
I remember once sitting in the Vegas strip, Bubba Gump shrimp alone.
I had just lost some money.
I was depressed.
And I wanted to know what the Wi -Fi was.
And I couldn't find it anywhere.
And I just guessed Jenny, the password was Jenny at Bubba Gump.
And I was right.
Oh, boy.
That's great.
I remember Kurt Metzger wrote, I think it was for a submission packet for SNL.
It was when the Fars Gump Bubba shrimp company first came out.
Yeah.
He wrote a sketch about a couple going into the Bubba Gump shrimp company.
And then like put then all the specials where terrible things from the movie.
Uh -huh.
So they were like, you know, what's the such and such appetizer?
And they're like, well, that's what the waitress gives you a hand job under the blanket.
Right.
Yeah.
That's where your mom has to fuck the principal.
You can go to school.
Those were like all the menu things.
Yeah.
I remember they were scum, man.
I don't know if I could sit through it now.
I liked it.
I'll admit I liked it when I was 13.
But man, that movie was insane.
By the way, you know what I miss and I will do on a future movie.
What is my segment called?
Movie corner.
Jesus Christ.
Holy shit.
I watched Welcome to Marwin.
The latest Robert Semeckis joint.
With the the Karel thing.
I'm going to get into it.
I'm going on a future episode.
It looks absurd.
Oh my God.
It's so much worse than you even realized.
It looks absurd.
I hate it.
I bought Forest Gump on Blind Faith at Sam Goodie.
Yeah.
The day it came out on video.
I bought it because I had heard all this great stuff.
And I bought the double fucking VHS cassette.
Yeah.
For like, you know, $30 whatever it was.
And.
Suncoast.
No, Sam Goodie.
Remember Sam Goodie.
Did you have a Suncoast?
We did.
Okay.
I bought stuff at Suncoast too.
But remember that when that was the only.
It was the worst man.
It was like $30 for Suncoast.
Yeah, it sucked.
But yeah, I got it at Sam Goodie.
And I watched.
I was too old.
Not too old.
I mean, a lot older people liked it.
But I was probably 16 when it came out.
Yeah.
And I fucking hated it.
I was just like, what the fuck is this, man?
Thank you.
And it'd be bolt fiction, folks.
So anyway.
So that's where I was sticking with our batch hit movie theme.
What I will say is, would you believe that in the movie,
welcome to Marwan Steve Carell as a man who is obsessed with
and loves to wear women's shoes?
Nope.
It's Carell's worth performance.
You're not going to believe this movie.
Joe, tell him what Dr. Sleep is about while you're in it.
Doc Sleep.
All right.
So Doc Sleep, an interesting picture,
bit complicated, a little convoluted in the sense that
Stephen King famously hates the Kubrick adaptation
of the Shining, which is mind -boggling because he praised
the latest remake of Pet Cemetery.
He also said that the mini series version of the Shining,
starring Stephen Weber, was superior to the Kubrick version.
Stephen King, as of late, I get it.
He's an older man now.
He's probably less vehement about these things than he used to be.
But the shit he signs off on, and the adaptations of his work
that he says are great while he sticks to hating this version
of the Shining by Ku.
I can't wrap my fucking head around it, man.
You know, he talked about that new dark tower, and he was like,
you know, it's not my movie, and I said you should do it different,
but it's good what they did.
You know, I'm like, what are you talking about, man?
So anyway, that's what makes this film interesting because
it's an adaptation of Dr. Sleep, which is Stephen King's sequel
to his novel, but this adaptation of Dr. Sleep
is also a sequel to the Kubrick take on the Shining.
So a lot of things are adjusted and made different in this film
to link up to the original Kubrick film that are quite different
than the events and the way the events transpire in the book.
Because in the book there are a lot of differences,
which is important to, I guess,
it doesn't matter what you like is what you like.
If you like the original Kubrick Shining, you don't really need to know
any of the shit that happens in the Stephen King book.
If you like the Stephen King book more than the Kubrick adaptation,
Dr. Sleep might bother you a little bit.
So some of these differences are, you know, at the end of the Stephen King book,
the Shining, I mean, you know, it ends with the Nicholson character,
Jack, yeah, Jack, Jack, Jack, right?
I don't remember. Whatever, you know what I mean?
The Nicholson character, he ends up heroically blowing up
the overlook, overlook, overbook Christ.
I can't remember shit.
Overlook hotel.
Heroically to save his family, he has a moment of clarity,
which is very interesting because he's an alcoholic,
and he has a, you know, that's a term that alcoholics use,
as I only know because I've seen pulp fiction a million times,
and Samuel Jackson says it at the end.
But anyway, the movie does not end with Scatman Crouters being murdered
by Jack Nicholson.
It does not end with Jack Nicholson freezing out in the maze,
and it does not end with Jack Nicholson remaining the villain.
It ends with him coming to his senses,
blowing up the overlook to save his family,
and him being a sort of hero to his son,
which is really what the gist of that original book is.
It's about the relationship of the father and the son,
and the terrors of alcoholism.
Kubrick obviously changed a lot,
and I personally prefer the Kubrick take on it.
I don't really care for the father coming to his senses at the end.
I like the idea that this guy descends continually into madness
to the point of his own extinction at the end of the film.
King always said that his problem with the movie was Nicholson is crazy
from the jump, and there's nowhere to go from there.
I don't agree with that.
I think Nicholson's transformation in that movie really works.
So on to Dr. Sleep.
The movie does a very, very good job of paying respect to King
while also being a sequel and an homage to the Kubrick vision.
It picks up with Danny Torrance,
who in the first story obviously is a very young boy.
Now he is fully grown, played by you and McGregor,
and you and McGregor are solid, but to me never excellent actor.
Solid.
I saw this film with a friend of mine and said to her after the movie,
we were talking about it.
You know, McGregor is not a bad actor.
He is good, but there's something odd about it.
And I said, you know what I think it is?
I don't think he ever questions the script.
I think he very respectfully goes,
it says I'm supposed to say this, so I'm going to say this.
I don't think he's a guy that goes, dude,
you would never say this out loud to yourself.
It would sound ridiculous.
I think he just is like, no, that's what it says.
So I should just do it.
Yeah.
And I think he's right.
Yeah, I just, I think that creates some awkward moments for him.
Yeah.
Because there are things that writers put in the script sometimes.
You go, you didn't say this out loud to yourself.
Right.
It doesn't sound right.
Yeah.
So anyway, it picks up with, you learn that Danny is a young boy after he,
after the events of the overlook.
He's very traumatized and the spirits of the overlook are appearing to him.
And then I forget, what's the Scatman Crothers character name?
Hmm, I don't know.
Sorry.
Well, anyway, he teaches Danny to do this thing where he can entrap these spirits
in his mind.
He can imprison them in these boxes in his mind.
And the first question I had sitting down to watch this thing is,
well, how was Scatman Crothers talking to Danny Torrance?
Because he died in the first one.
Excellent fucking fix by the writer of this movie.
Mike Flanagan.
Mike Flanagan, who does great stuff.
Danny can see Scatman Crothers.
Just like you can see any of these other spirits.
This guy can still appear to him.
I thought that was an awesome, awesome fix.
Anyway, jump forward to Danny grown.
It's you and McGregor now.
Dick Halloran.
Dick Halloran, yeah.
And Danny, just like his father, is a hopeless alcoholic.
And potentially a drug addict.
And the reason that he is so self -destructive is because these substances help him keep these spirits
and these terrors from his past at bay.
And he does this until a young girl who also has the shining starts communicating with him
from sort of a cross, I don't know, the country somewhere.
She's somewhere far off.
And he slowly realizes that he can use his,
in this sort of inspiring and fruitful relationship he forms with this other psychic girl.
He realizes he can use his powers for good.
He starts to do so.
He works in a nursing home.
He gets sober in the nursing home.
He becomes this guy they call Dr. Sleep because he knows when people are going to die.
And he goes and he sits with them and he helps them go in peace.
And it's actually quite beautiful.
But then a band of gypsies who prey on people that have the shining
and kill mainly children that have it and suck their, they call it steam,
out of the kids to enhance their own, to give themselves immortality basically.
He finds out that these people are out there, that these people are harming people,
that this little girl he's been communicating with knows of them,
and is also potentially in danger.
And he kind of has to now jump into the fight again.
So classic, classic setup and execution of, you know,
the old superhero that hangs up his cape.
Right.
Has to kind of get back into the fight more so than he ever wanted to.
And it just kind of unfolds from there.
That all said the movie I thought was fucking awesome.
I loved it.
I thought it was super fun.
I thought it was super disturbing at times.
I thought it was super creepy.
And I thought the ways that they connected it to Kubrick's movie were just fucking amazing, man.
I just, you know, and unlike the Irishman, which we talked about recently,
they went the other way with this thing.
They didn't do a de -aging thing.
They didn't do a computer CGI thing.
They just got actors that kind of looked like the people and could kind of recreate, you know,
so they got a guy that looked kind of like Jack Nicholson to play the Jack Nicholson part
in these weird like hallucinations that Danny was having.
And when they needed to recreate scenes from Kubrick's movie,
they got a kid that looked like the little kid from the shining.
They got a lady that looked like what's her name?
Shelley Duval.
I wish it's Sally Field.
Jesus Christ.
What they do have, Shelley Duval and Nicholson, you see them in this movie.
Where?
What do you mean?
That's what threw me.
I mean, I liked it, but you see footage of Duval and Nicholson in the movie.
No.
All the footage is recreated.
Really?
Yeah.
Like when they showed Nicholson busting the scene where he's busting through the door
and Shelley Duval was screaming with the night, those are the new actors.
Really?
Yes.
Yeah.
Because then, in fact...
So when he was the bartender, I was like, okay, this is not Jack Nicholson.
No.
When little Danny Torrance is sitting with his mom, I was like, that's not Shelley Duval.
But in other scenes, I could have sworn.
No, they literally recreated it like...
I got to complete the mimic.
I thought they used a mix.
No.
Was I read an article about that where it was like this movie kind of makes the argument for
you should just use younger actors or new actors or local actors.
Wow.
That's interesting.
I got to say it again.
But anyway, Rose the Hat is the character who leads this band of evil gypsies.
Gorgeous.
She's wonderful in that she's so evil.
Disactors.
So I looked her up after I'd never really seen her.
I think everyone who saw it looked her up after.
Yeah.
She's just a rotten mother fucker.
She's great, man.
I hadn't seen her.
I think Rebecca Ferguson.
She's so good at it.
Yeah.
And it's just a fun, you know, like I talked about Pinkstone, Pinkstone Red Doctor Sleep
before I did.
And, you know, all I had read was the first 20 pages or first chapter, whatever the book.
And the first chapter of the book is fucking horrifying.
Yeah.
One of the scariest things of all time because it's young Danny after the events, the overlook,
with the witch from room 230, whatever, appearing in his bath.
It's so fucking scary.
Yeah.
And I said to Pinkstone, how's the rest of the book?
And he said, well, that part's really scary.
He goes, but the rest of the book isn't really hard.
It's more like a psychic adventure kind of thing.
And this movie plays similarly.
But because they wanted to make it a sequel to Kubrick's thing, and this is why I liked what they did in the changes they made,
they up the horror percentage quite a bit in this.
They made it real freaky at times, which I thought was really cool.
For me, the same with Jacob Tremblay from Good Boys and Room.
And, you know, one of the biggest child actors there is.
He comes in for a very small part, but I see why they fucking got him.
That seemed where they drain the life out of Jacob Tremblay.
Yeah, I didn't realize I was him.
That seemed where they drain the life out of Jacob Tremblay and her story.
Holy shit.
I mean, I was, that's one of the biggest freak outs I've had in a horror movie in a long time.
I was very upset by that.
I couldn't believe that.
And look, man, this is one of the things I really want to tip my hat to this movie.
Porturing a child.
I'm just, and I said this about Joker.
I'm just so happy to see studios making stuff that straight up disturbing again.
Yeah.
Agreed.
Like, that are pushing the envelope with this stuff.
That scene is so fucking morbid and disturbing.
Yeah.
And here's what's funny is like, you haven't heard of people about it.
You haven't heard of all these trigger warnings in these movies.
It's like, Jesus Christ, guys.
This movie is a scene where they kidnap and torture a fucking 12 -year -old kid to deathly.
And the kid is literally screaming for his, it's horrifying.
And our cutest and most beloved actor.
Yeah.
You know, so, you know, I thought the movie was good.
At the beginning, you know, there's some, some dark shit.
He steals money from a single mother who's kind of passed out drunk and drugged up whatever.
But little by little, like, there's a moment in this where it takes a huge swing,
which is where he's like flying through the fantasy world.
You know what I mean?
And it looks kind of not amazing.
Like, they didn't have a lot of money for the special effects.
But it feels super 80s.
And that's what I can say about the movie as a whole.
Is that it felt like watching a horror movie in the 80s, where it was nuts.
It felt like you didn't know what was going to happen at every moment.
There was all manner of scares.
You know, there is jump scares.
There's also just really disturbing shit.
And you don't see many horror movies that are just getting scares out of things being disturbing and weird.
When he's floating through space in this, you've never seen anything that really looks like it.
And I think it was just because they use a lot of cool, practical effects.
Now, here, this is a huge spoiler.
So if you haven't seen the movie and you don't want to know, hit mute.
If you haven't seen the movie and you want to know why, you might want to see it.
This, to me, I mean, this, this scene I'm about to describe.
It just blew me out of my fucking seat.
So in the Stephen King book.
The, as I said before, the overlook has been destroyed.
And this sort of breeding ground for psychic energy or whatever that was the overlook hotel is now the campground where these gypsies live.
That are running around and praying on these kids that have the shining.
So in the finale of the book, Danny Torrance and this little girl have to go to the campground to face down, to do the showdown with the gypsies.
And in the final battle, Danny summons the ghost of his father and his father comes in and helps him and blah, blah, blah.
That's fine.
You know, whatever.
I think it's kind of corny, but it's not for me.
In the movie, because it's a sequel to Kubrick's thing, the overlook is still there.
So you want to talk about a fucking climactic payoff in a movie.
There's a scene where you and McGregor said the little girl goes what we like, where do we have to go to like fight this woman?
And you and McGregor goes, I know where we have to go.
And you know, it does like, I'm getting chills. The camera fucking goes up.
You see the overlook on the hotel.
It plays the fucking shining music.
Right.
And they start driving up.
And then they start mimicking shots from the shining like the camera going over the water and everything.
It is so fucking awesome.
Like I got hype.
I got hype the way like, you know, you get hype at the end of like a Schwarzenegger movie or something.
It was awesome.
I love that so much when they go up there and every single review I've read, be it friends on letterbox, be it critics, whatever is like, it's a great movie until they get to the overlook.
And I couldn't disagree more.
And I'm so glad to hear you feel the same because I thought it was awesome.
And the stuff there at the end, they didn't have people doing like intense Jack Nicholson impressions, you know.
They handled it all really, really well.
All that stuff works.
And the fact that everyone hates it, I just don't get.
And then also it's definitely pumps you up also because you in or sorry because Danny Torrance needs to destroy this evil woman rose the hat.
Instead of in the book his dad coming and in a touching moment heroically helping his son from beyond the grave or whatever.
Instead, Danny fucking unlocks all the goddamn chests that Dick Haller and taught him to use to lock up these evil fucking spirits and all the fucking creepy ghosts from the shiny show up and like descend on this woman.
So it's so awesome.
It's so awesome how he turns it on her.
And then this was really cool.
The finale of the film is you'll McGregor sacrifices himself by blowing up the overlook.
So this guy puts the ending of the original shining book into this movie now, which again better ending to this to this story to me.
I know Kings book couldn't have ended that way.
It wouldn't have made sense.
But I just thought it was fucking great.
I just thought it was fucking great.
And then in the last scene, Danny Torrance is now appearing to the little girl, the way Dick Haller and appeared to him.
Right.
And he's kind of guiding her and whatever.
It's just I just thought it was fucking great, man.
I really, really like a very, very smart way to handle all that I agree.
I'm about to listen to the audio book of Dr. Sleep.
They were so excited by the footage they saw of Dr. Sleep.
They wanted him to start working on a third one.
I believe it was called Haller and maybe I'm not sure.
But they pulled it immediately because no one went and saw this.
But as it's typical now with entertainment journalism, which is ever bit as annoying as every other kind of journalism is.
I remember seeing on Thursday, meaning the night before Dr. Sleep comes out.
Like a Hollywood reporter article saying something saying Dr. Sleep, what went wrong?
It hadn't come out yet, but they knew it wasn't going to do well.
It didn't do well.
Here's what went wrong.
Here's the answer.
You released the only horror movie that was out at that time.
The week after Halloween.
I have never seen such a stupid marketing move in my entire life.
I think it was like some weird vote of faith because they were like, oh, this might be an Oscar contender.
It's not going to be.
And when Halloween came around, there was no movies except that one about the app that kills people.
Yeah, which yeah, like it was so fucking stupid.
And I saw the shining.
Is that one with the work of Hallex kid?
No, there's nobody in it.
I don't think.
Is that movie out yet?
Yeah, it came and went.
Countdown.
I think it was called.
No, no, no.
The one like Bixby or not Bixby.
Oh, that looked terrible.
Was that a comp?
That was sort of like a hard thing, wasn't it?
It goes crazy.
Countdown was an app that tells you the day you're going to die.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
But I saw the shining in the theater with friend of the show Karen Coguerreff and my wife.
We had a blast.
And they showed a trailer for Dr. Sleep and everybody was like, oh, wait, the trailers we've seen have looked kind of corny.
That trailer looks fucking awesome.
It was a great trailer.
And they were like a special engagement the night before Halloween, but it will open after Halloween.
What is Warner Brothers thinking?
It makes no sense to me.
You're putting the shining in theaters to remind people of the movie you haven't seen it.
And then you've got this amazing horror movie and you bring it out on like November 3rd.
I just, I don't get it.
But I hope people discover it and keep discovering it because the party line,
when something doesn't do well, is that it must be bad.
This is a very, very good, serious horror movie.
Mike Flanagan is a guy who did hush, which was very cool.
Oculus before I wake with Jacob Tremblay.
Ouija, Ouija Origin of Evil, which we did on the show.
Gerald's game, which was very cool, which we did on the show.
And now Doc Sleep.
I think he's going to have a nice long career.
He takes this all very seriously and some of it I think could have been really ridiculous.
I think if you would have gone too far with the humor in this,
it would have started to seem like completely.
I think the guy, I'm not a huge fan of haunting of Hill House.
He didn't do it.
Yes he did.
That's his show.
Did he?
Yeah.
Why am I looking?
Oh, you're right.
Sorry.
But I'm not a fan of those types of shows.
I'm not a fan of, you know, 10, 10 hour plus episodes.
Sure.
I feel like it just gets way too involved and it takes away from the meat of the thing.
But I will say I love Gerald's game.
I loved Ouija Origin of Evil.
And the positives that I can say about haunting of Hill House are,
I think the guy has an extremely great strong neck for creating extensions of things
that creating true reimagining of things that really do work in the way that reimagining
and a reboot or a sequel should work.
He understands it.
He knows how to capture the spirit of the thing with also adding his own flavor.
And I think he did that tremendously with Ouija Origin of Evil.
He's talking about a franchise that was dead on its fucking feet.
Right.
And his sequel was fucking tremendous.
He's clearly a very smart guy.
Yeah.
And I think he's going to be around it a long time in horror.
He does a great job of like creating dread, which is for some reason missing from horror movies,
which is the best part where you're like, oh god, that trembling scene is like a horror scene for the ages.
It's like you don't get that feeling in horror ever anymore.
It kind of almost like that extrace is feeling where it's like should I be watching this kind of thing.
And I love the movie.
I had a blast.
I think my only real issue is that Ready Player One kind of fucked it.
I bet Ready Player One and it also were the two things that got this movie greenlit.
But like them seeing what a reaction that scene got where they go to the shining is probably what made this movie happen.
But it does suck that this movie didn't get to own its trip back to the overlook.
Imagine how much cooler it would have been if you hadn't seen that piece of shit.
I agree.
Yeah.
Two hugs up.
For Doug Sleep.
Joe DeRosha Comedy on Twitter and Instagram.
Yes.
And Instagram and Joe DeRosha comedian on Facebook.
I am the Patrick Wallsha Twitter and Instagram.
I'm excited to see this movie become the cult classic it deserves to be.
Check it out.
We don't know what's up next.
But thank you all for keeping us afloat via Patreon.
We love you.
Have a great day.
You know.
We love you.