Summer is here and Bet MGM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer or check out
our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz.
Only available at Bet MGM Casino.
Spend on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 fortunes, Mystery of the Land,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand.
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action.
Bet MGM game sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bet MGM dot com for T's and C's, 21 plus to Waiter, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and
West Virginia only.
Games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as normal, durable site credit slash bonus bets unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
The football season is full of guarantees, and here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October, if
your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning, or winning money back in fan
cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
Winning hits different here.
Monthly 21 plus, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gampler, offer not available in all states
terms apply, see Fanatic Sports Book App.
This is a head gum podcast.
Hey folks, welcome to We'll see you in hell.
Oh, this is your favorite podcast that talks about horror, horror movies, sci -fi movies
and fantasy films, you know, we discuss them, we commentate on them, we review them,
we do everything we can to have our way with them.
These movies we love them, and you love them, and that's why you're here, I think, I don't
know.
I'm Joe DeRosa to my front on his knees in front and front and down is pat looking up at you
greedily. Hello everybody. Pat Walsh in the house. We're gonna be talking today about the Netflix
instant picture. Actually it's just streaming there. Wasn't designed for the app. Super dark times.
a movie that lives up to its name, and I'm excited to get to it. Joe and I have not shared our opinions.
But what's going on, Joe? Well, I'm doing some laundry today.
All right. Which is why I'm dressed like this at the moment.
Yeah. Joe's wearing an almost an umbro style short, and what appears to be an inside out t -shirt,
But I think it's just that faded a bad religion t -shirt with a cross and a
Ghostbusters sign through it. Yeah, this is the bad they sold the t -shirt like this to look they printed it on the inside pre -worn
Yeah, they printed it backwards. So it looked very worn very punk rock guys
I gotta say between the way I'm dressed and the way I'm sitting if you were a female co -host
I'd feel the need to go put some more clothing on right I agree. There's sort of a
A open leg to the short, a droopy sort of feast your eyes, kind of quality to the fabric.
Yes, there's a basic instinct kind of thing, and I'm Newman, sweating off to the side.
But that's fun.
How did they never, with all the times on Seinfeld,
that they spoofed, I know, like a movie scene?
How did they never spoof Newman
in the basic instinct scene?
That seems to me like a, like I bet Larry David
had a lot of little things he would not do.
And that's probably like too much of a wink
or something like that.
You know what I mean?
Sure, but I just can't think of anything better
than like if they had like one of like the crazy like if it was like Mrs.
Costanza in the Sharon Stone seat, you know, well now Newman is in JFK and of
course he reenacts the yeah Keith Hernandez bit so he clearly that was not a set
rule maybe they just couldn't figure out a funny way to you know they're like
how do you do up of the giant flash without doing of a giant of flash you know
No, Heather, my girlfriend is younger than I,
not to brag, it's required here in Los Angeles.
16, is it?
She's 14, thank you.
And, but you do have the parents approval.
Yes, not her parents, but my dad gave me a high five.
We were discussing base against it.
And sometimes I get, you get an interesting perspective
when you're when you're when your partner's a bit younger than you and she was she had missed base against it
She was not familiar with it. She would have been seven when it came out. So obviously your dad's not taking her to the multiplex
Whereas I was 1213 and all I could think about was how badly I needed to see base against him
Even though I didn't really know why because what you're ultimately seeing Sharon Stone is was incredibly
beautiful at this time
But to just have a woman on cross her legs and a brief flash of vagina, was it that
titillating even at the time?
Well, it was just the taboo or what is it?
I have never seen basic instinct.
Okay.
I have.
I know I've seen that scene once or twice because of all the hoopla around it.
Yeah.
But this is something I can never remember.
Do you actually see like vagina or do you just see like the bush?
I feel like you only just see like the bush and everybody was like whoa it requires a very
Quick pause and from what I recall
There's no bush. Oh, it's just a shaved right and from what Sharon Stone says now which you know all right
I don't know who to believe in this case. I know Paul Verhoeven is a real luck weirdo, but she claims
She was not told it would be shown
in the picture. I can't imagine that was the case. That sort of thing requires heavy signing and
agents involvement and everything else. But I know it was really built up in my mind and it started
in me a feeling of that. When I was a kid, like a woman with her legs spread wide in a magazine,
I mean, never got to me as much as a nice boob shot
or a lady, you know, presenting her,
looking over shoulder at me, you know.
I'll tell you that the,
it's too graphic, I can't ever agree with you.
We didn't like the shape of water,
but we also didn't like the sex scene
between Michael Shannon and his wife,
because it was just weird.
Yeah.
But I was more turned on when his wife pulls that
like heaving breast down her top.
Yes.
to like flirt with him, then I was, by the time I saw the Sharon Stone,
as she refers to it in interviews now, the clam jam scene.
That's not true.
I don't know why she calls it.
Don't want to get mad at me.
I didn't say it. She said it.
I'm not getting mad at you.
I'm doubting the veracity of your clam.
Yeah, I don't know.
It's just, it's just never called to me in terms of singing in a movie.
Like, I've never been like, oh, I hope she shows her vagina.
I did like in loaded weapon one when they spoofed it, and when she crosses her legs, there's
a beaver smoking a cigarette in the seat.
Right.
I got back to it.
Kind of stolen from naked guns, classic beaver jump.
I just had stuff.
And that's the loaded weapon is truly the height of a mond, our sauntais.
Oh, wait, that's not him.
He's loaded weapons, Emilio.
He's in fatal instinct.
Yeah.
Yeah, low to up in his Emilio Estevez and Sam Jackson.
Well, it's not Sam Jackson yet.
No, it's not, but he's funny in it if I recall.
I saw that at the dollar show, probably rented it 25 times.
Don't remember anything about it.
I'm gonna watch it again soon.
I remember it having some good jokes.
All right, well, Shatton or the villain?
I never saw it.
Oh, national ampune's loaded weapon.
Yeah, when it came out, I remember being like,
this doesn't look, it was already like around
naked gun 33 and a third time.
And I was like, these movies are not,
they're just running their course.
They're not as good anymore.
If memory serves, it is about as good as 33 and a third
and not as fun as the hot shots pictures.
But I'm sure Shane was talking to Estevez and was like,
you gotta get into this stuff, man.
Or maybe it was like a Frazier Niles scenario
where it was a competition among brothers.
Shane won.
And then for the next 25 years, Shane lost.
now he's truly lost folks. He's off the reservation. Speaking of sheen, and sheen types,
Feldman who has these, Cory Feldman, who is a crew of, because sheen used to call his
girls that lived in them like the angels or whatever, correct. And then, and everybody
thought was gross and then Corey Feldman came out and said, I have Corey's angels which is my
thing where I let extremely hot women live with me to get them into a better life and for some
reason people though that was somehow good. But I read that apparently one of them now has made
some allegations about sheen being in about Feldman being inappropriate. And Feldman is now claiming
that those are false and this is part of a takedown for his attack on Hollywood pedophilia.
can he's just such a sad case I believe that I believe he was assaulted I believe there's
a pedophilia ring. Do you see Barbara Walters like a month ago? You see this clip? No.
We'll talk about the fucking epochs. I mean Corey Feldman is insane and has been badly
damaged. I didn't care for it that she kept referring to it as Maoist station. I thought
Accutations about that that people in Hollywood are pedophiles. Why are you doing this?
And he's like, well, it's true. He's like it's it's an epidemic. It's the biggest problem I know of in Hollywood
Anytime it starts to bubble up it's shut down, but it's true. Sure. Yeah, and she cuts him off and she's like, how dare you?
How dare you speak that way about the industry that raised you? These are good people. Are you serious?
He's a good peep.
This is two months ago.
Walter's is challenging.
It's the kind of clip you're gonna see
in like five years once all this stuff comes out
and Bar Walter's gonna be, you know, humiliated.
Dead by that.
She'll be dead.
I would think, but she shames him.
She like hits him on the, on the snout with a newspaper
for saying he was molested on national coverage.
She's like, you're lying.
Hollywood's a beautiful town full of beautiful souls.
Like maybe if you're a multi -multimillionaire.
Well, that's her, that's Walters, that's her classic.
That was what she got shit for on the view
because every time things would get like tense,
she'd be like, okay, so, you know.
And let's bring out the guy going to make the cake.
Or whatever, you know, and they,
I think they were always annoyed with her
because she was always like kind of like dodging everything.
That should be where a show like that lives
is for people with different opinions.
Chewing at an event for cake recipes.
I would say I wouldn't do an all cake recipe show either.
No, you spruce on a little cake, but the discussion should be the heart of those kind of show.
Yeah, the button every week should be the cake recipe and pre that molestation debates.
Everything that gets set on the view is greeted with five to ten minutes of unbroken applause.
On either side, which is crazy. I one time saw Dennis Miller on their debating
out the war yeah and like being pro W Bush right and I guess it was whoopi or
Joy Joy it was at least Joy Behar I like Joy Behar and whoopi saying the yeah
saying the opposite obviously and the crowd was equally cheering for both
yeah it doesn't work like this what is going on right now well it's it's I I don't
know if she came up with it but I first heard it from Tina Fagclafter and it's
something that she's disgusted by, where you say something with that intonation that forces
an audience of unthinking sheep to clap, and you just go up at the end and kind of
look smug at the end. Bill Marr is the key practitioner of Clapter, where half his show
is a pause for him and then him smirking at it.
My favorite thing I ever saw in real time, and I was not a George W. Bush fan, but Christopher
Hitchens was on and he said something pro W Bush and the audience in unison booze him.
He turns, gives the audience the finger and goes, oh, you fucking sheep.
I'm no fan of him, but that sounds good.
It was the only time I've ever seen somebody pull a move like that with that much blowback.
I just thought it was really fun.
I just like when everybody's somebody like, oh, fuck yourself.
Yeah, well, I mean, that shows the ultimate.
You wanna talk about a guy who presents himself
as a rebel.
He packs his audience with people who treat him like God,
says exactly what they wanna hear,
and then backs in them cheering.
I mean, once in a while goes too far,
and everyone gets all edgy.
I got a Dennis Miller style joke for Bill Mar.
Go ahead.
I went to church the other day,
and the choir wasn't there,
because they were in Bill Maher's fucking audience.
Ah.
It's good.
Maybe you get a job writing for Dennis Miller.
I don't know what he does, but, you know.
He's on strict right -wing radio.
No, he doesn't have that show anymore.
Oh, okay.
He doesn't lose it for saying something.
No, he just stopped doing it.
Okay.
He sort of disappeared a bit since Trump, right.
And I have never heard a straight answer.
He was very much like anybody with Hillary.
That was kind of his whole thing.
Right, but I've never heard him flat out say
whether or not he likes Trump since he was not elected.
I mean, so I wonder if he's kind of laying logs.
He's like, well, I buttered my bread with the sort of Trump crowd,
but maybe he doesn't like them.
And yeah, or maybe he does and he doesn't want to say,
I don't fucking know.
So he's doesn't done much lately.
I can't go down that road just here in the name.
I can't go down that road this morning.
We don't need to go down any road.
I'm just speculating on Dennis Miller.
Let's lighten things up a bit and let me ask a lot of people.
Things are light, baby.
Why did you tell Aziz Ansari to do what he did?
Well, in all fairness, he didn't follow my instructions properly.
And that's all I'm going to say.
I'm kidding.
Of course, I'm kidding.
I'm not, you know, we're not making light of anything.
We're just joking to cope.
We're joking to cope, folks.
We're coping.
We're coping by joking.
It's almost like a combination of joking.
Somebody called back that joke though, because we do that every week almost.
I made the joke on Instagram that Saudi Arabia, the first movie they showed after the cinema
ban was the emoji movie.
Yes.
I made the joke.
Credits rolled.
They had immediately reinstated the ban, folks.
You wrote Saudi Arabia said this is the worst thing that's ever happened here, folks.
folks. But then one of the listeners wrote Joe, why did you tell T .J. Miller to do what
he did? Which at first I didn't realize was a nod to the show. Yes. And I was like,
why would this guy write that? Cheat? Oh, wait, no, he's doing it. I say it pretty much
ever. Yeah. Yeah. And I haven't even covered a fourth. No, we got, that's going to be a
running. That's people being accused. This is going to go on forever. That's a runner. Yeah.
Yeah, although I do wonder who's still sitting on their accusations now, let's get him out
there.
Uh, I don't think, yeah, I don't think there's going to be a problem with that.
So, you know, well, we'll, you know, we'll just play, just keep reading the news.
See how it goes.
We're going to dip into, I'm glad you lightened it up.
Do you want to dip into Pat's movie corner?
I do.
Because I have a few things I'd like to talk about.
I am stressing out for the sheer amount that I have, and I'm going to do quick cuts.
I'm going to do three and then over to you.
Three quick cuts.
All right.
I have two.
okay here we go the mountain between us don't know what it is don't know who
plays in it by the title alone I never want to see it well it's Kate Winslet
and Idris Elba and they crash in a small plane and you know they have to kind of
survive in the wild and maybe find love I love wild survival movies I the edge is
one of my favorite movies ever I thought the edge was lacking a romance between
balled -win and hopkins I did want to see them get so desperate that they fucked
prison style in the woods like they just thought they were never gonna get out I
love the edge I've I've known the edge for years mountain between us you are
know the edge of course not it was just a lame boring
trudge you know you're there in the wild anything can happen to them and they
it just kind of sit around and it's just boring.
I don't know, it wasn't great.
Logan Lucky, the new Steven Soderberg picture,
stacked cast, Channing Tatum, Kylo Ren, Daniel Craig,
I had a blast with it.
It's like Ocean's Eleven, but with Hicks and NASCAR.
Okay, yeah, I wanted to see that
because Craig, I've never seen Daniel Craig
play a character like that, so it looked interesting.
He's really funny in it,
and the movie was very entertaining, very amusing.
Soda Burgess makes a great move, I don't know what to say.
And the picture is stolen by my favorite,
Mr. Dwight Yalcombe, who plays a prison warden.
He has a scene where he's, the prisoner's in,
the prisoner are negotiating to get out.
And he's going through their demands
and one of their demands is for the new Game of Thrones books
in the library. And he's telling them he's like, now I know you guys want fire and ice. George
are our Martin. I checked the Wikipedia page. He has not completed fire and ice. And then
some one of the prisoners raised his hand. He's like, but everything we're hearing is that this,
this, this, this, this, this happened. And then y 'all comes like, well, apparently at this point,
the television show has gone beyond the books. Martin is I was dying laughing. There's a lot
a lot of weird funny shit in it.
It's funny.
It's a great picture.
And then last one, I'd say Logan Lucky slipped onto my top teneless for last year matter
of fact.
Then stronger with Jake Gyllenhaal, he's in the bombing, you know, the Boston bombing loses
his legs.
I mean.
Okay.
Okay, these movies are just made to get people Oscars.
It's not going to happen.
Is Wahlberg in this, too?
No, that's the other one about Boston bombing.
Wait, there's two Boston bombing movies.
This one is David Gordon Green, Jake Gyllenhaal.
You know, it's like a woman standing by her man when he loses legs.
It's not worth your time, folks.
People really love this movie, too.
I don't get it.
It should have called it weaker.
I always have very mixed emotions about like a tragedy movie. Yeah, like a recent tragedy
movie. It was like when when Oliver Stone did World Trade Center, there's something just a bit
suspect about it. The only one of those that I thought was really great was United 93, which
I will never watch again, but I was just blown away by how it felt like a documentary about it.
Right. Now that I wanted to be on that plane, but I felt like I should have been on that plane.
Sure. Sure. I saw two, I rewatched two classics because I got them on a blu -ray. I got
to Menace the Society, the director's cut on Blu -ray.
Hold up. Great. Yeah, it still holds up. Okay. You know, it's funny. We did an episode,
one of the, one of the bonus epses. I think it was the first bonus up we did was scary
a scene, not in horror movies. I don't know how we missed Menace the Society. Lorenz Tate
as ODog. One of the scariest fucking villains I've ever seen in a movie. He's out of his mind.
And in the bonus features, they talk about how originally in the script ODog was supposed to be
still like a 16 year old kid, but very big for his age with scars on his face and a guy that looked
like he had been through the ringer and they said they kept bringing guys like that to read. It wasn't
Right.
Send the Hughes brothers called casting
and they go send us all the reject tapes.
And they're like the first reject tape
we got was Lorenz Tate, who we didn't think would work
because he had such a Disney look to him.
And then we brought him in to read
and it was 10 times more terrifying.
Cause he's like a baby -faced kid
but he's clearly a psychopath in the movie.
Right.
He's fucking awesome in it.
Tyron, I can't remember his last name.
the main character of the place, Kane, he's amazing in it.
Great cameos by Samuel Jackson, Bill Duke, Charles S. Dutton.
Jada Pinkett is great in it, she's not a cameo,
she's the female lead but she's great in it.
It's awesome, it was just awesome rewatching it again.
It's so gritty, they talked about in the special features
how they got, they didn't get a tenth of the blowback
they thought they were gonna get.
They thought they were gonna get a ton of blowback.
but they said the one harsh criticism they got was from Oprah.
We're told people don't see this movie
and they said they thought that was good
because they were like,
we're not going for the Oprah press at that time.
Roger Ebert gave it a four out of four
and they said they modeled it, which is funny
when I was watching it again.
I was like, this reminds me of Goodfell
and then sure enough, they said,
we modeled it after Goodfell.
It's like we wanted to make a movie about criminals
that existed in the underbelly of the black community,
just like Scorsese made it about
the underbelly of the Italian community.
And it is very much like good fellows.
It's not that there's, if you've never seen it,
it's not that there's one hard plot.
Like this happens and then they gotta do this.
It's just sort of a series of events
that occur in the lives of these characters
and the evolution of these characters
over a finite period of time.
And you see how it goes and it's great.
that president's fan?
I love dead presidents.
I wanna go buy that now in Blu -ray.
You are from Hell fan.
Never saw it from Hell.
From Hell's good.
And after that, I'm looking now,
but I don't know that they made many movies.
They separate, they made Book of Eli,
then they separated and started doing different movies.
But the one dude wrote,
he directed that new movie.
That's coming out that we keep,
you and I've been to the theater couple,
there's that Goddamn Wolf movie.
that I kept saying I thought, look dumb, but I don't know, maybe it'll be good.
They were great directors.
I don't know.
You think they were fighting or they just had a money issue?
No, I think they probably, I'm assuming for monetary reasons or career reasons, they
needed to kind of split up for a bit and couldn't just keep doing projects together because
it was probably too hard to sell them as a team, I guess?
I don't know.
I really don't know.
One of their names on the Dr. Dre, other defiant ones.
Yeah, I guess they did some of those.
But they're great.
I also got the 25th anniversary blu -ray of juice.
Another one of my favorite films.
Sure.
Great, blu -ray, great transfer, all that stuff.
The movie still holds up, but I guess in rewatching it,
I'll talk more about the bonus features.
again this one has a documentary or a couple featureettes where they get into what the behind -the -scenes
business was and it's really great. It's really great. It's Ernest Dickinson, I think it seems
the director, he who also directed Demon Knight, what a fucking phenomenal film. And Jews did have
a scene, Spike Lee's cinematographer for many years. Yeah, and Jews did have a scene in our scariest
some scenes, not in horror movies, which was the two -pock hallway scene at the high school, but
it was, he said he wanted to do a film noir that took place in Harlem and
that sort of reshaped the movie a bit for me because it does feel very much like a film noir.
It's just fucking great, man. It's just fucking great. There was like bonus footage of Sam Jackson,
and once again as the arcade guy that didn't make it into the final cut that was really funny
that's in one of the featureettes. But the most interesting part was he said the earnest
Dickinson said they had to change the ending. The original ending was Q trying holding two
Bishops hand and trying to make sure he didn't fall and then he goes in the distance
you hear the police sirens getting closer and closer and as they get closer
Bishop starts to let go. Q is desperately trying to save him and Bishop goes
I'm not going to jail man and let's go and falls and he was like it was such a
strong moment it tied it back to the beginning where Bishop's father is
traumatized because of prison right and it showed all the strength in the
character that he was going to decide his own faith and he said the studio was
like we will not support this movie in the way you need us to if you let the
bad guy determine his own fate he has to fall and scream as he falls right so he
said uh... two pop came in to do the 80 our scream and two pop goes this is bullshit
and he goes yeah I know it is bullshit he goes can I do a half -ass scream and he
He goes, yes, so he goes, that's why the scream
at the end of juice sounds stupid.
And like half ass, he goes, because I was hoping
that one day I could reinstate the actual ending.
Right, so they put it on the thing,
but you have to watch it separately.
They show like the raw footage of it
in one of the features.
That's never effective really at all.
What do you mean?
When they do that, it's always like cool to see,
but then you watch it and you're like,
it always looks like shit.
And you're not, you haven't watched the whole movie,
so you're not into it.
And yeah, but I I'd love to see I'd love to see a director's cut of juice
But I don't think if we didn't get it for the 25th anniversary. I don't know if we're getting it probably not
Anyway
All right, well, that's the movie corner. Let me give you three more three more. Let me let me get this list crossed off
They talk about patty cakes
It's a movie I absolutely refuse to watch
It's also one of my favorites of 2017 one of your favorites. It's eight
mile with a very overweight young white girl. Yeah, it's so weird they made
yet another movie about rap music that centers on a white person. I fucked that
movie. I'm not watching. You know, if you want to make it into a controversial thing
you can it's it's it's an extremely entertaining and fun movie. It's not a
movie about race in any way. No, they know it's that it's just a
appropriating the piece of art.
Well, that's, I mean, that's rap.
You know, that's what rap has become.
It's an inspiring story and it's a better movie
than eight mile, which was critically acclaimed.
I felt unduly.
Eight mile was okay.
And I was willing to roll with it with eight mile
because Eminem is actually an awesome rapper
that did that and had street credibility.
Whereas, you know, you're gonna make a movie
about a kid that wants to be a rapper
And then you make it a white kid on top of it. It's like make it make it a black kid
Why not? I don't I don't get why it has to be a white girl
All right, I don't it's just my take on it. I'd tell you to watch it
You started the segment by saying you'll never watch it
So I don't know why I would but it's it's extremely entertaining. All right
The wraps are good the music is good. I really liked it. I thought it was a funny movie and very entertaining
Spider -Man homecoming you see this thing
No desire, no interest, not going to see it.
Even with your love of all these superheroes.
I don't have love for all these shabies.
I don't like them any more than you do.
I had, I was thinking of folks, what are you talking about?
I was holding out hope for DC because I love Batman.
I love DC.
I have been increasingly more and more disappointed
despite my love for Batman Superman.
Right.
You know my take on Marvel.
Well, I hate it.
I can't stand all the jokes.
I can't stand the comedy.
I didn't need to see a third Spider -Man reboot
in 10 years and couldn't agree more.
You know, if it was the,
look, if it's the best one, then great,
but I'm Spider -Maned out.
I don't give a shit.
You know, I fell for it as I often always do.
This, I started seeing on all these top 10 lists.
This is the superhero movie.
This is the great one.
This is the one you gotta see.
But there's a twist in this thing.
they were talking about the twists, like it was six cents.
It's a boring movie like all the others.
The kid and the kind of puberty angle
is done a little better because they're younger.
Tome of wire always felt older to me.
And there's kind of a fun twist.
You also have Michael Keaton as the villain.
At least he brings a little life to the proceedings.
I heard he was good, but you're talking about a movie
that's if it wasn't two and a half hours it felt it you know I'm sick of this shit sick of it
I'm gonna go ahead and say this I believe now this is just a prediction I can't see the future pet
despite what you think my prediction though is that the the Star Wars episode nine right which
will be the final installment in the Skywalk or series of films.
I predict that that will potentially be
the last Hollywood film I ever go see in a movie theater.
I'm gonna predict that, right?
Which one?
Star Wars Episode Nine.
Why do you think it's gonna be that bad?
No, because I think at that point,
I will have completed a cinematic journey.
I've been on since childhood, and I want to complete it,
And I'll enjoy it because it's Star Wars, right?
But I think after that, even the thing I love so much
like Star Wars is gonna go completely off the rails.
I'm done with the damn superhero movies.
I just couldn't care less anymore.
And even the sort of indie fare
that Hollywood is putting out there right now,
I don't like that stuff either.
So it's like at this point, unless it's A24,
or I'm sure there is a handful of other companies
I'm not recalling right now.
I don't like the movies anymore.
I just don't like everything I see.
I'm underwhelmed, I'm bored.
I'm seeing better horror on Netflix, on Shutter,
and all these other streaming services
that are making the stuff either originally
for their own content, or licensing things
that were made for little to no money.
And it's better.
There's so much good content out there being made
by people that really give a shit and I'm just kind of tired of it all. I'm tired of it.
When I saw like I'm sorry I'm not trying to rag on Blumhouse because I like a lot of what they've
done but even when Blumhouse is putting out these movies where you're like give me a fucking break man
I just feel all hope is lost. Well Blumhouse I don't think it's the gold standard of quality you're
holding it to. They've always made a mix of shit and good movies. I mean get out is not their
brand, that would be the exception to the rule, I would say.
I would just think a company smart enough to put out, I mean get out to no brainer, right?
It's a no brainer, it's, you do horror, this is an excellent horror movie, Jordan Peel.
What are we, what are we thinking?
Let's put it out.
Yeah.
But a company smart enough to have put out a whiplash to announce to a whiplash.
It's a dumbfounded whiplash.
And it's like, that's insightful, man.
That's like, this is a movie on paper
that nobody wants to see.
What's it about a kid learning how to play drums?
And his teacher calls him slurs
throughout the various kinds of the film.
Nobody wants to see this on paper.
Then you see it.
Somebody told me when it was about,
I was like, it sounds like the most boring fucking movie.
And they're like, no, trust me.
I watched it reluctantly.
Yeah, and I was like, oh my god. Yeah, it's good. This is a fucking tour to force
How do you put that out and then go?
We're gonna put up the you know truth or dare we we think you're given too much credit to the studio the studio
I have very little creative saying anything. I
Think a studio. Well, I don't think that's true at all
I think studios like to give lots of notes and like to get involved
I mean as far as like hey, we've got the fix that you know
that's never going to be the studio.
They didn't shape that script I'd doubt.
They might add a couple notes.
And it's cool that they put the movie out.
It's cool.
I'm just, no, I don't think the studio got behind.
I'm not saying they shaped Whiplash, right.
I'm just saying, I think this studio knows better
that when you see your fan scorers coming back lower
and lower and you keep producing the same thing over and over.
It's like, come on, they don't realize that.
Of course they realize that.
At some point it becomes about,
They'll just see it anyway, and we'll get the money. Who cares?
That's definitely the mindset that gets you an insidious the last key.
And it's a bummer because horror is one of two genres right now, keeping the fucking movie theaters open.
Right.
Give people something good, man.
There's no reason not to. There's no reason not to.
So anyway, that's my prediction.
Episode nine, possibly the last time I said foot in a movie theater, I don't know.
That won't happen.
Well, it could.
I am done because we should get to the picture in hand.
Um, wait, I gotta see if I have a scary stuff.
Okay.
Uh, I don't.
I don't have one.
I haven't been spending a lot of money.
I know what I do have one.
My friend Jamie gave me this for Christmas.
It's a very cool little thing.
The Hellraiser Omnibus, uh, get it at your local comic book store.
or it's a collection of the Clive Barker issues
of the Hellraiser comic book that came out.
I think about two years ago, it's a direct sequel
to Hellraiser II.
It ignores the other sequels.
It takes place in real time,
in the timeline since, meaning 20 years after Hellraiser II
or whatever it's been, it picks up in present day.
Kirstie from the first two films is the main character.
pinhead is a big character in it. It's great. It's a great, great fun story. I've read it twice,
and I really love it. So go check that out. It's a fun fun horror comic. Hellraiser,
omnibus, and it is far better than the atrocious Scarlet letters, which was supposed to be Clive
Burke Barker's ultimate conclusion to the Hellraiser franchise. And it's one of the worst things
of a red. You see the trailer for the new hell raise or that's out right? No, the next
sequel's coming out. I will see that. I think that trailer is online. I've seen the trailer.
It's the movie's not out yet. I said you've seen the trailer for that new. Oh, I thought you
said the movie are they were seeing the movies out? You don't listen to me. Why would I?
anyway let's get to the show the review let's get to it super dark times I have a
feeling because you've been saying nothing that you're not gonna agree with me
I found this to be a very exciting horror thriller offering and I'm very
excited to see what the gentlemen have made this movie does next I loved it I
loved it I thought it was great oh great all right I thought it was great little
Disappointed only by are we gonna do we're probably gonna do spoilers correct yeah
We are gonna do spoilers. This is a movie where it is important. I think it's on Netflix go hit pause and go watch it
If you want to participate in the discussion, you don't think you're gonna watch it keep listening, but we're gonna spoil it
Super dark times a story about a group of teenage friends
Who they're they're an accident happens meaning one of them accidentally kills one of the other ones and then it's sort of
unfolds from there with his older brother, Sword. Like, I thought like that first half hour,
I read one review of it that I sort of agreed with until I loved the last half hour so much.
But this reviewer was like it so perfectly captures like being a 14 year old boy
like hanging out with your friends that he was disappointed when the thriller elements started.
Sometimes I feel that way about about things that's so hard to get right like kids
Like they cuss way too much, you know, yeah, like they're showing off for each other
There's the one who's like annoying to the point where the fact kid where he's annoying almost at the point where
He's like a psychopath like every young group of friends has that friend. He was great. He turns out not to be the psychopath
Yeah, he was great. I loved I loved I
I googled all the kids after I was very happy to see that and you were you added the word
Nudes, but you Google the kids to be fair news search off just yeah to be fair
Nudes is always in the bar and that was an accident. Yeah, yeah, the
No, but the I was very happy to see and I didn't even realize it when I was watching it the kid that plays the psychopath
I was also placed scarecrow on Gotham and scarecrow this this new rendition of scarecrow on Gotham is
I love it. It's a great read it now
Speaking of which Gotham that's the way they should be doing super hero shit dark gritty fun
But but that's another argument
But anyway, he's he's great on that show. So I was excited to see that
but he kills the fat kid with a sword by accident.
And then it kind of unfolds from there
where you start to realize maybe this wasn't an accident.
Yeah, maybe this kid's just got some problems.
There's a lot of hinting that that brother
he keeps referring to might be dead
and he's not talking about it
because he seems to be very ambiguous
about when they're like,
Where when does your brother come home from the war takes place during the first Gulf War right which I thought was great
You just left weeds sitting out and yeah, none of it kind of makes sense
And then you you finally see their mom and the mom's kind of a weird yeah like lady. That's like not attentive to the kids
Right
I thought it was awesome. I thought they nailed
14 -year -olds it like not since super bad have I seen as I have I seen a movie that nails 14 -year -old so well
Yeah, just just as accurately but with a darker twist to it and like inappropriate jokes the thing where they're looking through the year book
And he's like what the fuck happened to that kid and the other kids like dude you can't say that he was a burn victim
And he's like well as burns made him look weird, you know like just kids being shitty
Yeah, and like you know like like South Park there every other word is fuck to where to point where it's almost annoying and like exhausting
And I was thinking back to hanging out with my friends like we tended to be more in the Nerf camp
But I had a lot of friends who would do shit like that like hey check out this knife
Yeah, I got my a lot of friends in Missouri and then you know people have guns all the time Missouri the fact that there aren't
Way more deaths like the ones in this movie with the kid, you know actually falling on the sword
It was crazy to me.
It made me think back to all the different dangerous shit I used to do when I was that
age.
We used to seesaw on this tetanus -infected rusty grain silo, right, like it was gigantic
and it would go up 30 feet in the air, but it was a seesaw.
So you'd have to have three kids hang on to one side and like yank it down.
I remember once my friend was sitting on it, seesaw style, and we were like, you don't have
enough support, whatever.
and he goes all the way up 30 feet,
flipped him right off the back
and he came down and just landed straight in his chest.
We all thought he was dead,
just knocked the wind out of him, but it was horrifying.
Jesus.
And then we would just pick ourselves up
and go on to the next thing.
There was this farmer that used to shoot at us.
It's a dangerous, I don't know if that goes on anymore.
Parents are probably too watchful of the shit,
but throwing stars and throwing Chinese throngs.
Yeah, all that stuff.
Yeah, it's I remember the kid of the bad kid in our neighborhood tying scissors to a string and swinging them around his head
Okay, you yeah, kids doing terrible things to cats straight cats. That's serial killer behavior
Yeah, with like firecrackers and shit Robbie who eventually killed himself used to drown cats in my neighborhood all the time
You also once sat on my chest and forced several worms down my throat
So, looked me in the eye and held my mouth shut as I swallowed, worm after worm.
You remember it as worms, it was probably something else.
No, I remember it very vividly.
But this movie depicts all of that very well and then it becomes a thriller because it shows
how that can go horribly, horribly wrong.
Also the sex on the mind, when you're going through the yearbook and he's like, I would
have sex with her at the talent show in front of you.
kind of shit you say when you're young like you're so horny all the time yeah and and
honestly you know this is something that I've you know it's dangerous to talk about in this day
and age but you also get really angry and that can that can go into a bad way with kids as it does
with the kid in this movie where you like there's a girl you see every day it was so hot that makes you
angry because you know she'll never talk to you most people when that happens bury that away wait
until a time when they're older and have more to offer a young lady.
But some start to get in this mindset of, she really owes me something and I was worried
that it was going to go to a sexual assault place with a girl when I saw her tied up in
his room.
I assume it didn't.
We weren't shown any of that.
So I don't think it did.
That's good.
I think it was a kid feeling, I don't think he was angry about, I can't have this girl as
my girlfriend.
friend. I think he was angry at feeling rejected in every way. Yeah, but there was another
form of rejection at his friend. She liked his friend and that kind of drove him insane.
Yeah, I think it was rejection from all levels. It was feeling rejected by his best friend
for dating the hot girl. Feeling rejected by the hot girl because she didn't wasn't interested
in him. Feeling rejected by the bullies that were beating him up. Feeling rejected by his
his own family because his mom doesn't clearly doesn't give enough of a shit about him.
Any fucking snaps, I'm assuming for the first time, I'm assuming he didn't have a history
of doing shit like this.
But it was just a cool thing.
My only disappointment was that it is sort of just a new take on like Mean Creek or bully
or one of those movies where shit, we killed a kid who was being a dick, we don't think
we mean to kill him, what do we do now, hide the body and don't say shit? I was hoping
there was another layer to it than that, which I thought, I guess there was, because I thought
there totally was, and that's the last 20 minutes of the movie.
Yeah, that's a good point, because me and Craig, to me, I thought this was better.
and bully, I think, is a masterpiece, frankly.
But this, when the kid finally turns,
and you see that not only is he tying this girl,
maybe gonna kill her,
but then he's just, like, willing to kill his best friend,
instead, like, when he first stabs his best friend,
that kid was awesome too, the lead kid.
Yeah, there, everybody was good.
It gave me a feeling you should have more often
and horror that I haven't had in five, 10 years
where you just feel like sick to your stomach.
like, when I realized that this kid was just like gonna kill anybody in his path, it really
bothered me.
It felt very oddly real to me and the neighbor running over and almost like he was breaking
up two kids, rough housing or whatever, everything felt like it would really happen.
Yeah, it was great.
It was very, very well executed.
Now, at the end, do the two, the one girl lives, but there's the friend live.
I got, oh, and she had the marking on her neck.
I, the friend wasn't dead when he went into the room, right?
I couldn't tell because, and also he didn't know either
because he kept saying, are they all right or they are right?
But I also, I guess she might be dead.
It's also interesting that they don't show you what happened
with the lead kid because there is a chance that he just said
we did this terrible thing and covered it up.
Yeah, whereas I know what I would have fucking said he killed our friend. I think oh, yeah
You know, I would have rolled over real fast, but when you're that you can just be like he threatened to kill me
If I told anybody would I just make get him in jail by any means necessary, but because it is true
That lead kid didn't do anything except try to help his buddy out when his buddy was in a jam because his buddy fucked up right
but
But what do you what did you make of the opening scene?
I thought that was gonna have more significance.
And I guess in a metaphoric way it does,
but with the deer that like ran through the window
into the school and the cops had to like,
stop it to death.
Well, that, when it started, I was like,
well, this is the whole movie.
That's what I thought.
That's the importance it gives it.
It also reminded me of Donnie Darko.
That's right, I thought, which I'm glad it didn't go there.
I was like, if this whole fucking thing comes back,
that the lead kid got killed by a deer,
right and and these all in his head or would have fucked that but I'm glad they didn't do that.
In my I thought the movie was felt so accurate and I would imagine that the
screenwriters grew up in upstate New York around that time because it all felt so
real to me. That feels like something that in discussing the script remember that
time a deer get into our school wasn't that crazy we watched this guy kick him
the death then it just got into the movie to kind of set up the dark tone of like
Sometimes you got to put things down whatever you know, oh yeah, that's interesting. Yeah. No, it's yeah
It was definitely a tone setter
The lexas just went off. I don't even know what what did she just say? I can't believe a guy as as paranoid as you has an
Alexa in his home. Oh speaking of Alexa. Did you see I meant to mention this in the movie corner?
I watch cat Williams new stand -up special. I can't wait. I love cat Williams. I've not seen it. It's called great America.
Okay, okay, it's so fucking funny man. I'm checking it out. It's so fucking funny. All right. It's really good. It's really really good. Oh,
anyway, we talked about Alexa and Siri. Oh, okay, I feel like I'm having a threesome.
Anyway, I uh, but yeah, uh, it's a great flick. Go check it out. I mean, I think everybody at this point has
netflix. Yeah. No need to miss this one. I am excited as well to see what this director doesn't ask. I want
to see what these kids do next because aside from the kid that plays the crazy one, not
any other kids, they're barely in anything at all.
Well, it was really inspiring in a way that independent movies used to be where I watched
it.
I was like, this probably cost a quarter of a million dollars.
Why aren't I doing this?
It was like, why aren't I getting some investors and making a movie?
It felt like a labor of love.
It was a really well -acted, really well -shot.
I can't recommend it enough.
A lot of people on the Facebook page had seen it already,
and we're saying they all hated the twist
at the end, the tonal shift, they weren't buying it.
I bought it completely.
I had no issues with it.
What, did the mean kids a serial killer?
They were like, I think they should have set that up
a little better or something.
I'm like, well, then you don't get the twist aspect of them.
No, I thought they set it up very well from the jump.
As soon as that kid in the opening scene,
as soon as that kid says, I'd fuck her
in front of the entire school at the talent show.
And then his buddy, that's the line that his buddy draws
where he goes, dude, whoa, that's gross man, what the fuck?
That's immediately when I was like,
something terrible was going to happen
and this kid is gonna be the crazy kid.
And I bet, although this was a movie
We didn't really pull any punches.
They were like weird kind of sex fantasy type scenes
with amongst 14 -year -olds.
Well, I think didn't real life.
These kids are probably 19, 20 -year -olds.
Well, mate.
I just thought that line in real life
should have been much more graphic.
I mean, my, I have friends now who are fully functional adults
but they would say things when I was a kid
where I was just like, wow, I might have been a prune.
I don't know, but there is always that moment
with your friend when you're that age
where like the one problem child kind of steps forward.
And you're like, this kid might have a problem.
You realize that about your friends,
and it's a scary time.
Yeah, well look, maybe it was more graphic
and they were like, can you reel this in a little bit?
Sure.
I get that.
I just, I thought it was very, very accurate.
It took much more care with these kids
than one of these movies generally would.
Great scripts.
You want to talk about, you want to talk about a way
to actually depict kids in a struggle
versus the fucking dog shit job
they did with the new It movie.
Oh yeah.
I mean, you just compare these two things.
It's, that's what I'm talking about
with these Hollywood releases.
It's like, it's disgrace, it's not disgrace,
I'm being too harsh, but it's embarrassing.
It's like, this is what real characters look like.
Yeah, I agree.
This is what troubled teenagers look like.
Show that.
I think you could have gotten, you could have done just as big a box office with a little more
You can't go full super dark times with a huge release like it, but just have that have the guys who wrote this movie
Do a pass on the kids in your movie do a pass on those characters and make them better
Yeah, you don't have to go you don't have to go super dark times. You just have to go as far as I don't know a TV fucking mini -series
Right goes with it. That's right
Anyway, I'd like to take a quick moment to talk about how, maybe it's a whole
another episode. It's a big, but something I think about all the time. When I was a
kid, a big part of my life, and I know this is pathetic, but it kept me going and
kept me excited, was looking for movies. And I had this book, 100 greatest movies in
every category. I would go from video store to video store, like seeking out this
lost movie, or you know, you didn't have Amazon whenever you look around for
Where can I buy this movie? Where can I see this movie and it was exciting and fun when you watch it at felt like an event?
The downside of Netflix is you have every movie in the world one second away
It takes all of that fun away. Yes, it makes every movie feel exactly like watching any other movie
There's no excitement to it. Yeah, and that sucks. However, I
Don't know that I would have ever seen or heard of super dark times
And I love that Netflix opens up your average folk to a lot more interesting and adventurous
indie type fair.
I think that is a very good thing about it.
I agree.
In fact, we were going to do something different, but I think that actually would be a great
topic for the bonus episode this month.
Our top three or five event movies of our lifetime.
That would be great.
So that'll be the bonus episode.
It'll be out before the end of the month.
I'm Jota Rosa comedy on Twitter and on Instagram penthouse column
You let me down is available every month if you subscribe to penthouse also I will be in Vegas
Performing with Bobby Slayton
February 2nd and third I think it is
Whenever that Friday Saturday is it's you know the first and second or second and third
I'm also headlining Gotham comedy club the weekend. I believe of the 15th in New York City
and the following week, I will be on the Patrisso Neal Benefit in New York.
Those are all going to be a lot of fun, so I hope to see you guys.
I am at Twitter, Instagram, at the Patrick Walsh.
You can hear me this week on the Good Christian Fund podcast, which released this morning, where
I am anyway, it's Wednesday, and Living Middle Glute premieres September 26th on CBS.
Thank you very much.
We will see you next time. We are still planning on doing black mirror everybody keeps asking about that by the way
We'll do it. All right. We'll do it. No, it's all right
We'll do it and also merch is coming so keep your eyes out merch is very
Very much really coming this time and could even be out as early as next month
Thank you all for your support. You love your patreon love your comments your feedback have a great week