I'll see you in the next video.
Hello everybody, it's Patrick Walsh.
I'm here with my good friend, Joe DeRosa.
You're doing the intro.
Love it.
You'll be appointed to me.
I went with it.
I don't know what to do.
You were talking to me to unmute, I guess.
That's okay.
I like that you did the intro.
I say jump.
You say how high I point like rena cop.
Pat and I are like you interrupted my intro.
I'm sorry.
Go ahead.
It didn't seem like you were in support of it.
Since you didn't let me do it.
I'm sorry.
Go ahead.
No, it's we'll see you in hell.
We're talking about why can't I remember what we're talking about.
Final destination.
Christ.
Well, it's because we talk about this stuff for months.
Like I see stuff so many months before you see it that sometimes it works out that way.
And I'm just like waiting to talk about it.
By the time it comes up for talking, I ain't seen it in a while.
That's true.
That's a good point.
I got a great top of show here.
Yeah.
If you want it.
Of course.
And you do want it because we haven't talked about it yet.
Whoops.
I hit the mic.
Ladies and gentlemen, the gods of the universe have blessed us with a second naked gun
remake reboot sequel trailer.
We have not talked about this.
We have a lot of things to do in this one.
Yes, you have.
We do you talk about we were texting about it.
We talked about it.
I thought you meant a second one since that.
No, no, no, we talked about the teaser on here.
We have not talked about the full trailer that has been released.
We had a little hurt with the teaser.
We had a little hope.
We're like, this might be all right.
Our old well, to me, the biggest thing was my manager raving for five minutes where he
could not catch his breath giggling.
This is a man I rarely see laugh about how funny the movie was.
Now his taste is called into question or else the trailer is showing us the worst of the
film I don't know.
But you know, Joe Ramone, trailer, it happens.
Joe Ramone, our boy, sent us the trailer and it was pretty unanimous.
It just kind of really brought the house down in the bad way.
It made my house sad when I watched it.
And I guess what I would say, Joe, is not that they would ever showcase the worst parts
of the movie intentionally.
But sometimes with a broad comedy like this, they're showcasing what they think will appeal
to the most people as opposed to the best jokes.
Still, everything we were shown here sucked.
This fucking thing.
Oh, God.
There are ladies and gentlemen without exaggeration.
Not one.
Not two.
But three.
Three.
As the owl once said, stolen jokes in this trailer.
There is the take a chair and she drags the chair out of the room, which is an old three
stooge's bit from the 30s from disorder in the court.
The most famous three stooge's short.
You talking too fast.
Okay.
Slow it down.
He's saying you're stealing a joke from 90 years ago.
90 years ago.
Yes.
Like comedy should have changed by now.
Like when I saw that, I mean, the joke is simply like take it, take it, well, a, everybody
says take a seat now.
Even that's changed.
He goes here to take a chair and she picks up the chair and walks out of the cell.
Now if you want us to have that as one of the five jokes per minute in your naked gun
remake, fine.
You're showcasing that in the trailer that has me scared.
Well, scared and Joe pointed out to us.
He said it's the top comment where it was like that chair gag and classic naked gun.
He goes, this is currently the top comment.
I went fishing through the comment days later because I was in one of my, which I'm
even frequently, I want to enrage myself moods.
So I said, I'm going to go read the comments because I got into a full blown argument on
a text thread with my friend Scott about the space ball sequel and the naked gun sequel.
Yeah.
And how much both are going to suck and he was defending them and I was getting so mad.
So that night I went and looked at the YouTube video and I thought, a trailer and I thought
there's got to be other people on my side here.
I can't be the, the last sane man on earth.
Every single comment is, oh, that chair joke tears in my eyes.
Here we go.
Leslie Nielsen would be proud.
I'm like, dear God people.
Well, as Ramoni said it, and he sent us the three students clip.
It says it's the hottest joke of 1936.
But the number one comment on YouTube is apparently that chair joke is pure 100% and
naked gun.
By the way, the three students version of it isn't better.
The three students version of it.
They're in court and they say, take the stand and curly picks up the chair and goes,
where should I take it?
Yeah.
Take a seat and then take a, to me, no one has ever said, take a chair.
It's, it's too set up.
It doesn't seem conversational.
It just seems there as a set up.
Take a seat.
The joke still works.
She takes the seat out of the room.
And if, obviously, if we're pitching these alts, you can imagine the trailer is just not
funny.
It's bad looking.
It looks like every non-descript Liam Neeson action movie, which maybe was their goal.
But like, I liked it when a comedy made me feel good.
Like it just was depressing.
You got Pam Anderson, who I guess has immediately turned her back on the, I'm not doing any
makeup.
I'm not doing any sex pot rolls.
And now she's full on miming, giving a blowjob to a broom handle in the naked gun trailer.
In the second stolen joke that they just stole from Austin, how Austin powers joke.
Yeah.
The silhouette where it looks like she's blowing him.
Yes.
And then it cuts to the interior of the house where you see what's actually happening.
And she's scrubbing a oven out on her knees with a, with a long handle scrub brush.
Yeah.
So then that's so, so yeah, that taken from Austin powers.
And then the third stolen joke for the love of God, the first two, you're like, these were
good bits when other people did them the first time.
The third stolen joke, they steal the worst joke from Friday.
And an overall impeccable comedy.
But the worst joke in Friday is, is the dad driving around.
After he ate the burrito, having to take a shit.
Because he, and it might even be next Friday where he's, he eats the burrito with too much
hot sauce and he has to take a shit.
That's part two.
That's next Friday.
Yeah.
So, okay.
So they're stealing from next Friday and they're stealing the worst joke in next Friday,
which by the way is saying a lot.
Because next Friday ain't Friday.
You take Mike Epps out of next Friday, you ain't got nothing there.
They take the worst, after next is what you got.
But Friday for next is better than next, I think is better than next Friday.
I never saw it.
Maybe I didn't see it.
Fred both have laughs, but they're not good movies.
Friday is, is a good movie.
They steal the worst joke from next Friday with Liam Neeson eating chili dogs in his car
and then desperately having to pull over as he's commenting to himself about how much
he has to shit.
Guys, what the fuck is this?
What the fuck is this?
Yeah, it really bummed me out.
It bummed me out because it was just something I was kind of looking forward to.
Like maybe you never know.
But I feel like you know.
When you know, oh you know.
There's your top of show.
I got to, by the way, I am going to in the spirit of this.
Yes.
When we get to the movie corner.
Again, from movieweb.com, I hate to give them credit, but I got to tip my hat for this
article they ran.
I got an article, I'm going to use it.
It's lengthy enough that I need to use it for my movie corner.
But you're going to enjoy it quite thoroughly, quite thoroughly.
But go ahead.
Well we discussed on Sunday, but we did not discuss now that the trailer for the naked
gun also uses that's the sound of the police.
Jesus Christ.
From the bad boys trailer, from every cop movie trailer.
And by the way, by the way, by the way, by the way, by the way, by the way, instantly
memorable naked gun theme song.
Not just every cop trailer, every comedy cop trailer.
Yeah.
Cop out.
Fuckin bad boys.
Anytime there's a comedy cop movie, they use sound of the police, which is a hip hop
anthem and an awesome song and one of the best carers once long is ever.
And these shit bag fucking comedy trailers are making me hate a song that I goddamn love.
The naked gun world and the world of hip hop have nothing to do with one another.
They simply have nothing to do with one thing.
Nothing.
And the theme song of the naked gun is great.
At least give me sound of the police segueing into the theme song at the end.
But do you think they're going to do the, the, the gag at the beginning with the siren?
I think so.
Yeah.
I think, I think like most of these legacy sequels, they will do the thing you needed to
do at the beginning.
So you feel like you're watching the thing that you love.
And then the second that nostalgia thing ends, you will go, I think we're in trouble now.
That's what that's what it is.
You know, it's, I mean, Jesus Christ.
Now I loved, I loved the last Indiana Jones movie and a lot of people did not.
But even in the last Indiana Jones trailer, did they play, uh, sympathy for the devil?
Yes.
And we were like, well, this is an overused trailer song.
We've heard it a million times.
Yeah.
And it's not very Indiana Jones, but I get it.
It's the 60s.
They're trying to show us these in a different time, whatever.
But that's still transitioned into boom, boom, boom, boom, boom.
It's still went into the music.
It still did the thing.
They just don't get it with this.
It's like, guys, the whole point of naked gun is it's a spoof of old, new, old, old,
bar detective movies and TV shows.
That's what it is.
That's why the theme song is what it is because the theme song in and of itself is a parody
of the theme music of those old TV shows and movies.
If you're going to update it, update it to a modern thing that you're satirizing, which
you're also not doing.
There's no satire in sound of the police playing in the fucking trailer.
Yeah.
My guess is this is not a satire of what's going on with cops right now, which is not
a funny topic, of course.
But like you could update it somewhat.
You could do something.
I don't know.
They appear to have not made any positive choices.
And my mom knew how much I love the naked gun and she would always laugh when I'd be watching
it.
And she brought it up the other day.
And she was like, I just thought it looked really stupid.
And I was like, yeah, and she goes, and I know that it's a stupid movie, but just this
looked like bad stupid.
And I was like, yeah, that's pretty much exactly right.
There's you get it.
It's also like the cockiness.
It's an impossible needle to thread.
That's why these guys were about the only people who were good at it.
And I was initially excited when they said, okay.
I'll overphrase.
Originally, they were going to do this with Ed Helms.
Yeah.
I was like a worst choice.
And I like Ed Helms, but I was like, no, that's a bad choice.
Yeah, I was like, that's a bad decision because Ed Helms is a comedy actor.
You can't do it with a comedy actor.
That's the whole reason naked gun is so awesome.
It's because Leslie Nielsen at that point was not a comedy actor, except for airplane.
Or police squad when it started.
So I said, that's a mistake, don't you know, and then they said, we're not going to do
that.
We're going to do this thing with Liam Neeson.
And I was like, wow, okay, this could work.
This is a really dry kind of gritty dramatic, you know, sort of melodramatic actor.
And this, okay, they get it.
They get it.
And then what do they do?
They take Liam Neeson and they make him buffoonish.
And not buffoonish in the way where Leslie Nielsen always played it very straight in these
movies.
And his idiocy was what caused the ridiculousness that ensued around it.
Liam Neeson is so in on the joke and so trying to be funny throughout this trailer.
People that keep saying the part where he's driving and somebody hands him a coffee while
he's driving is hilarious.
I'm like, what the fuck are you talking about?
What the fuck are you talking about?
The definition of a throwaway gag.
To me, it boils down to in three movies, even the broadest and worst of them by far,
33 and the third, which has its moments.
You will never see Leslie Nielsen in a little skirt with his dick and balls hanging out
in panties wearing a Girl Scout uniform and pig tails.
It's like that's not, they just got it fundamentally wrong as far as I can tell.
And it might be the kind of thing where I actually, when you're out here next week,
Joe, I'm going to ask him, if he can get us into a screening.
And if it is that trailer for 90 minutes, I'm going to fire him because he laughed so hard
talking about it.
Now, then I don't trust his taste.
Look, speaking of ad Helms, hopefully I'm wrong because when the ad Helms vacation trailer
dropped, I was like, this looks terrible.
What are they doing?
Bob, blah, blah.
Then I saw it.
And I was like, God, damn it.
That movie was really funny.
So maybe I'm wrong.
It may be.
It's all going to be funny.
And he was a good continuation of Clark.
I got to say, we'll never see it again, but I liked it.
Yeah.
Anyway, I don't mean I'll never see it again.
I might never see him as Clark again.
What did I, where were we?
I just got carried away there.
Got lost in the solves.
Well, are we onto the movie corner?
I can do as a segue, because as I said, my movie corner is more of a news psycho because
I really got to read you this.
So I can go through this article and then you can do a few movie corners.
And then we can move on to the film of the day.
Just to remind you, Pat, it is final destination.
I fear you've forgotten already.
But it is where you're going to talk about it.
I got it.
And I saw the new final destination, although I am forgetting that one.
So we better do that sooner rather than later, which I thought was really cool, by the
way, the new one.
Highest rating of all the movies.
92%.
I'll have to see it again, but I was like, this might be the best.
It's always been a franchise that's a little more clever than it had to be.
Which, you know, mausole.
I find, oh, God.
So I was just going to say I find two to be superior to one.
It is.
I did not see three, four, five.
The reviews are sort of diminishing returns on three and four.
And then five is well regarded.
And two is also very well regarded.
Yeah, I'm going to go through them all again.
I haven't yet, but I'm going to go through them all again.
So movie web ran an article.
And we're big fans here.
And we'll see you in help pod of critics giving scathing reviews to things.
It always makes us laugh.
Rex Reed is the is the queen.
I'm sorry, Joe.
Quick pause, though, or I'll forget.
I was just watching SCTV season five.
They do 12 angry men, but they're closeted.
And they call out actual quote, closeted actors of the time.
And on the list, and this was 1980.
Rex Reed.
I was like, he was this big.
And I mean, SCTV always went for more niche stuff, niche references.
But it's like, man, Reed's been around.
Oh, yeah.
Anyway, all right.
Carry on.
Sorry.
I read web ran an article Roger Ebert's 10 funniest bad movie reviews.
So I'll go through them each movie and just read his little blurb.
My favorite of his, I think, is the village.
Is that on there?
I don't know.
I don't remember.
One of Shyamalan's worst.
I believe the village.
I like the village, but still I like the village.
Go ahead.
Number 10, Charlie's Angels.
Charlie's Angels is eye candy for the blind.
It's a movie without a brain.
And it's three pretty little heads, which is to guarantee it's Drew Barrymore and Lucy
Lou.
This movie is a dead zone in their lives and mind.
The cast also contains Bill Murray, who likes to appear unbilled in a lot of his movies
and picked the wrong one to shelve that policy.
Number nine, Armageddon.
Here it is at last, the first 150 minute trailer Armageddon is a lot together like its
own highlights.
Take almost any 30 seconds at random and you'd have a TV ad.
The movie is an assault on the eyes, the ears, the brain, common sense and the human desire
to be entertained.
No matter what they charge to get in, it's worth more to get out.
And how much worse did action filmmaking get after Armageddon?
Crazy.
Freddie got fingered.
Tom Green, a friend of mine.
Tom, I'm not taking shots at you, but God damn this review is very funny.
The movie doesn't scrape the bottom of the barrel.
This movie isn't the, oh, let me start this one over.
I remember this review.
The movie doesn't scrape the bottom of the barrel.
The movie isn't the bottom of the barrel.
The movie isn't below the bottom of the barrel.
This movie doesn't deserve to be mentioned in the same sentence with barrels.
Yeah, that's probably one of the more influential pieces of writing I ever read to be honest
with you that sense.
Oh my God.
Transformers Revenge of the Fallen.
A horrible experience of unbearable lengths.
Briefly punctuated by three or four amusing moments.
One of these involves a dog-like robot humping the leg of the heroine.
Such are the meager jokes.
If you want to save yourself the ticket price, go into the kitchen, queue up a male choir
singing the music of hell, and get a kid to start banging pots and pans together, then
close your eyes and use your imagination.
Okay, didn't like that one.
Number six.
What was that one?
Transformers Revenge of the Fallen.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, I mean, there's proof positive that action filmmaking would get worse same director.
This is a movie I've never even heard of.
Little Indian Big City.
You know what?
I guarantee that's not going to hold up in a 2025 quarter-law of that movie, whatever
it is.
Little Indian Big City is one of the worst movies ever made.
I detested every more like minute of it through a stroke of good luck.
The entire third reel of the film was missing the day I saw it.
I went back to a screening room two days later to view the missing reel.
It was as bad as the rest, but nothing could have saved this film.
All right.
Number five, the village.
Here you go.
It's so witless, in fact, that when we discover the secret, we want to rewind the film so
we don't know the secret anymore.
Wait, that's the village.
Yeah, I just said that's the village.
Then keep on rewinding and rewinding until back at the beginning and can get up from
our seats and walk backwards out of the theater and go down the up escalator and watch the
money spring from the catch register back into our pockets.
Yeah, that's what I was going to read and I love that, but they cut off the best part
of it.
So it says eventually the secret is revealed to call it an anti-climax would be an insult
not only to climaxes, but to prefixes.
Love it.
And then we live in a world where Ebert can write that on a Thursday morning and probably
make a hundred bucks and the writers of the naked gun give us take this chair.
Brown bunny, this is a this is a quick one.
He said the worst film in history of the con film festival.
I've not seen every film in the history of the festival yet.
I feel my judgment will stand.
That's good.
This started a huge beef with him in Gallo, Vincent Gallo.
Yeah, he went on to say of Vincent Gallo.
It can be said that this talented actor must have been out of his mind to a make this film
be allow it to be seen.
Yeah, I remember them going at it in the press.
That was a fun time.
I think Gallo was like, you're a fat ass shut up for whatever.
Yeah, you pig.
He called him a pig.
Number three, battlefield earth.
Oh boy.
I watched it in mounting gloom realizing I was witnessing something historic.
A film that for decades to come will be the punchline of jokes about bad movies.
Not that funny, but very true.
Yes.
Number two, doose big.
Oh, you're being jiggle about which this is big of me.
Laugh harder than anything.
Rudd and I'm 77 minutes.
Not a lot of fat on that.
Here's what he would have to say.
How much he charges.
I'm not sure.
But the price is worth it if it keeps him off the streets and out of another move.
Called Schneider a third rate comic.
Well, that's fair.
But Schneider is correct and Patrick Goldstein has not yet won a Pulitzer prize.
As chance would have it, I have won the Pulitzer prize.
And I am so qualified, speaking my official capacity as a Pulitzer prize winner, Mr. Schneider,
your movie sucks.
That was said by Goldstein, who the Pulitzer, I'm sorry.
No, no, that was said by Ebert, who did, we'd be able to win a Pulitzer prize for what?
For film criticism.
Jesus.
For criticism.
Yeah.
Number one.
Are you ready for this?
Yeah.
I'm starting to like it.
Which is Coppola, correct?
No, Rob Reiner.
Rob Reiner, yeah.
Man, Rob Reiner, we've talked about this.
His back half, that back nine on the Rob Reiner cattle.
That makes you wonder if this guy ever knew how to make a fucking movie to begin with.
I mean, which is also like confidence, also like Coppola, where you're like, was any
of it good?
Yeah.
This is like what?
Here's Ebert's blurb.
I hated this movie.
Hated, hated, hated, hated, hated this movie.
Hated it.
Hated every simmering stupid vacant audience insulting moment of it.
Hated the sensibility that thought anyone would like it.
Hated the implied insult to the audience by its belief that anyone would be entertained
by it.
Jesus Christ.
Bro, imagine waking up to that.
Have you seen North?
Is it that bad?
No, and if you, I mean, it's not great, but it's basically a little boy looking for parents
and he goes to like 40 different sets of parents all played by pretty big comedic stars.
So it's like hitting mists, but it's, and it's definitely a step down, but it's all right.
Good cast.
Fair enough.
It's, it's not great.
Don't get me wrong.
So when I was a kid, um, I watched.
Not dog the movie.
Okay.
They claim that they're the first movie to be called something the movie, which can't
be true.
This came out in 1984.
But it is one of six, seven, maybe more ski movies that were all the rage in the 80s,
always sunny, did a spoof of, of, of this one in particular, but also a few others.
And they were excuses for TNA and the snow.
We had hard bodies and fraternity vacation and all those kind of movies that would be TNA
in the beach.
Yeah.
And then we had some snow movies.
Um, I remembered incorrectly that the first nudity I saw was in hot dog the movie and
actuality was in something called hamburger, the motion picture, which is also a ski movie,
correct?
So it's, it's not.
Um, it's, I believe it's a movie set in the high stakes world of fast food.
And then there's also a movie called fast food starring Jim Varney, who was earnest that
had the exact same plot.
Hamburger, the motion picture is about, it's a teen sex comedy.
The film centers around a character who finds himself way too distracted by women who want
to have sex with him.
So he enrolls in Buster Burger University to become an owner of a fast food franchise.
What a great plot.
These movies were one step up from pornography.
I mean, when, when people talk about skin amax, they're referring to stuff like this.
Joe Bob, when I was in my teen years was hosting, uh, not horror.
He was hosting USA up all night.
And he would introduce these kind of TNA movies.
And actually always because it was on USA with the TNA cut out or obscured.
So you're watching the war, I'm a kid watching the worst movies of all time in the hopes of
seeing nudity, even though I was never going to see it.
Very frustrating.
Um, anyway, how to talk the movie is bad.
It's one of the only other times I've seen David Norton, who was the star of an American
werewolf in London.
Yeah.
And of course you still see Griffin done all the time and things, but where was David Norton?
And it's only a few years down the line.
Yeah, actually only a couple years down the line.
And he's already in hot dog.
The movie.
It's kind of a bummer that you could start out in a classic and just never, but you know,
there's millions of these stories.
I think too at that time, though, that was like, you know, um, I don't know what the equivalent
of the modern day equivalent would be, but it would be like that.
The, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the,
the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the,
the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the,
the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the,
the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the