I'll see you in hell.
Welcome to Will See You In Hell.
Your favorite podcast, when you need to check on.
And what's happening with the movies in your life?
The genre picture.
We discuss it here.
We review it here.
Horror, sci -fi, action, fantasy, comedy, drama, we even lump those in sometimes.
Wouldn't you say, Joe, that in today's world, the genre film is king and not really a subset
anymore?
The Avengers is a genre film.
That's the biggest you can get.
Yeah, I guess I would.
I hadn't really thought about it until right now.
So really to take some time with that question.
I mean, I'm sorry to blow your mind so early on a Thursday morning, but yeah, I mean, the
world has changed.
It's not like, you know, like when Batman came out, it was kind of this like weird comic book
friendish thing and that was only 30 years ago, exactly 30 years.
Here we are.
That's the dominating picture.
That is interesting.
I think that's why the argument often comes up now that, you know, why can't these films
be not like, for instance, the big one was why couldn't Robert Downey Jr. be nominated
for an Oscar for carrying this franchise for the last, which, hey, man, I don't disagree.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
They thought he should have been nominated for like Avengers, as what best actor?
Yeah, yeah.
Me a fucking brain, but hold on a second, here's the only reason I don't sleep walking
through it.
The only reason I don't disagree is, well, I would say it's fair because they, you know,
Johnny Depp got nominated for pirates.
All right.
Um, but that was much more of a performance.
I think if you were going to nominate him, you could do it for the first Iron Man and
beyond that.
Give me a break.
I will say there's something to be said that he is carried a franchise for this long.
Like he is the main guy.
But there's 50 people in it.
Yeah, I know.
I saw a quick little update.
I have now seen all the Avengers movies.
Sorry to hear that.
I have the AMC Stubbs A -List, not to brag, but it was called the Fast Pass.
Both Stubbs A -List and Fast Pass sound like perverted orgy clubs.
I agree.
You would belong to Jeffrey Epstein was the founder of it.
And while we're at it, Jill, why did you tell Jeff Epstein to do what he did?
I call him Jeff.
I thought he should kill himself.
And I thought it was a good idea to tell him to kill himself.
And he did it.
They said this morning, he had his neck was broken.
And they were like, there's a slim chance it could have happened from hanging, but a very,
very, very strong chance.
He was joked at that.
Um, he was sent in, somebody was sent in by the powers that beat a murder.
Almost.
Did you read the funniest, I mean, it's hard to, hard to say, funniest when this is the story.
But, uh, the guard comes in, I, uh, do you read this story?
They're like, who are you?
Because they didn't recognize the guard and he goes, my name is Jeff, or, you know, whatever,
Jeff, I guess.
And they go, Jeff, what?
And he goes, Jeff, jail.
That's a, that's a true news story.
That's the guy who was on duty.
Jesus, what is this?
A scene from Indiana Jones?
Honestly, like, that would be too brutal.
Yeah, but guard puts on the uniform.
That's a naked gun scene.
That's not even a, even, even the, even the current Indiana Jones would not say he's Jeff
jail.
Uh, any who, what the hell were we talking about?
Ep, oh, a list.
So yeah, I went to see a whole story.
I went to see Avengers, uh, the latest.
I watched the, the second, the last one that we did on the show, even though I hadn't seen
it.
I watched that on Netflix, sort of half in, half out.
But I saw this new three hour and 15 minute one.
Have you seen this thing?
No, no.
Who's got the time?
I don't have the time.
I will say that while you're watching it, it's, it goes quicker than the one before it,
even though it's much longer because every two minutes, you're like, oh, there's Michael
Douglas.
And he has one line.
Yeah.
Then there's Angela Bassett.
She has one line.
Everyone in Hollywood is in this thing.
Yeah.
It's like, it's a mad, mad world at this point, and getting mad at all the time, folks.
The, the, the Marvel universe has turned into the cannonball run exactly, uh, of superhero
franchises.
I mean, it's just, but back to Downey getting nominated to further support your argument
that he shouldn't be.
I saw an interview with him recently.
I mean, you want to just talk about it, real fucking asshole thing to say.
Okay.
He goes, uh, he goes, uh, I don't have any disregard for the script.
I don't have any, oh, sorry, I don't have any regard for the script.
Maybe it's hubris.
Maybe it's the fact that I'm born from writers, but my job is to get it done.
And for me to be there to do it the way that I feel I can do it best and to be in a good
mood and happy.
And that means like, I'm going to kind of do my own thing with the words, man.
Like that's just, it's just like, oh, fuck you.
Fuck you, dude.
Well, and it's like, oh, that's why every movie you're in, you're playing Iron Man.
It's because like, yeah, he's essentially like lifted.
At this point, now I'm really going to backtrack on me saying he deserved a nomination.
He's essentially lifted Vince Vaughn's thing, which is like, I'm going to be the snappy
fast talk guy.
And then just been like, I'm just going to do this.
Like I don't care what the fuck the script says.
I'm just doing this anyway.
Well, if he is improvving heavily through these Avengers movies, it fits right in with the
other little quips everyone else has.
They're not any more clever or anything else.
Everyone's got their little stupid quips.
It's why I tuned out from the movies when they start, when every character started to
act like Tony Stark.
I was like, this is stupid, right?
Downey deserved the nomination that he received for Tropic Thunder, where he gave a performance
that would not exist today.
Yeah.
And he's been good in many things, but like, come on.
But Tropic Thunder was also pre -Iron man, which was Downey Jr. come back phase.
So you can see in that, he's not fucking around.
He's like, you know, he really came to fucking play in that movie.
Because a lot was riding on it for his career.
And then Iron Man blows up, and then Iron Man 2 blows up, and then the Avengers blows up,
and suddenly it's like, I don't respect it.
You know, I don't care about the words, man.
It's not important, man.
Right.
You were sucking off prison guards 15 years ago, Downey.
Yeah.
They weren't calling you Downey for nothing in that prison.
I think he was like going into people's houses on drug overdoses.
Remember that?
How did he like, strolled into someone's house in the middle of the night?
So did Rip Torn, R .I .P.
It's just proof that if you come from enough stock in this town, you can really get away with some shit.
Well, he is an inspiration to us drug users that you can be that sharp after destroying your brain for that long.
And he was a real drug user.
He was really like, he was doing like, cracking shit, right?
Hard court.
Well, Leslie Jordan, the delightful Leslie Jordan of Cool Kids,
short -lived famed, shared a jail cell with him.
Leslie was in there for meth, which he freely talked about.
I'm not telling tales.
And yeah, Downey was in there for like crack.
Now Leslie is another guy, I don't understand because I've watched, I follow Leslie on Instagram.
I've watched his videos where he'll start crying and be like,
y 'all, I was homeless 20 years ago.
Yeah, meth addict.
And now I live in this big, beautiful house.
I'm like, how does a guy go from home?
I have never been a meth addict.
I can barely afford rent.
How was this guy living in this fucking mansion now?
Well, he's living in an apartment near the grove.
Do you see what he's got in this apartment?
Yeah, I guess.
Every video is him taking down some sculpture and being like, ain't this just precious?
Up about this in the south of France.
Well, you're missing that key element, years of meth use.
That's what you got to do.
I got to, I guess like, you know what?
I might give it a whirl.
You know, it's true.
I always respect the person who's like, I got 10 years sobered, shut up about it.
Like I fucked up my life.
I don't deserve praise for getting off it.
I sort of agree.
I know if I was 10 years sober, I'd be annoying and talking about it all the time too.
But it's like, why do we praise these people so much who destroyed their life for years
and got out of it?
What should we praise in the people who never destroyed their life?
It's one of my favorite Dennis Leary jokes from no cure for cancer.
And it was like right at the time that started happening.
It was such a spot on joke where he's like, he's like, I can't wait to get famous.
I'm going to drink my face off.
I'm going to do coke every fucking day.
I'm going to smoke apex.
I say, I'm going to beat my fucking kids.
And then after 10 years of that, I'll be on the cover of People magazine.
Sorry.
Yeah.
And I was like, that's a, that's a really, at the time, that was like a really fucking spot
on commentary.
And then he went on to trash the people that did that.
Did he get it from Bill Hicks?
Or was that his own?
That Bill Hicks.
You know, man, I'm a Hicks fan and a Leary fan.
And I worked with Leary on some stuff a few years ago.
I never, there was never, and I'm not just saying this, there was never one part of Leary
that I thought was thefty or I prefer a Leary to Hicks.
Hicks never did anything for me.
There were like, there was like one joke that was pretty similar.
Yeah.
And, you know, and then also it's tough with Bill Hicks, because Bill Hicks was a sort
of, was a, was a, was a, was a punchy dude.
Yeah, I'm not punchy.
That's the wrong term.
It's a scrappy dude.
Yeah.
So I don't know if Leary did or didn't, if he did, it was when he was fucking 20.
Right.
You know what I mean?
It's like, you make mistakes.
But I don't even know that he did.
And I'm going to say after working with a guy and honestly going through all of his stuff
and looking, you know, digging through it and stuff, and like while I was working with him
to see what he had done and performed in and whatnot, I didn't see anything in his stand -up
that even resembled anybody else's.
It's something that's followed him forever.
I don't know the specifics, but he co -created Rescue Man, that was a hell of a show.
Yeah, I don't know.
Like, yeah.
So I hope he didn't.
And he was always a nice guy to me.
I recently watched two Dennis Leary performances and I wasn't like trying to do a retrospective
there was just a coincidence, Demolition Man, a ludicrous film.
Leary is in Demolition, man.
He's in it.
He's like the secondary villain who comes in with 20 minutes left in the picture.
And he does a full minute of his own stand -up.
Oh, he's like, he plays against a funny villain?
Yeah.
Like, and it's completely out of place, but he's like, I mean, I want to be shoving cheeseburgers
in my fucking throat.
You know, like, it's just from his stand -up.
Yeah.
Then I watch Judgment Night.
He's awesome in Judgment Night.
He is.
He's the villain in that, too.
He doesn't stand up in that movie, too.
Does he?
Yeah.
He does like a riff.
And it's so clearly the producers were like, just throw it in.
We love it.
I don't remember him being at all funny in Judgment Night.
I remember him being really sinister.
And then I remember when he killed Jeremy Pivot.
I was like that part.
Yeah.
Even before I hated Jeremy Pivot.
Now when you want people to kill Jeremy Pivot, nobody will do it.
I'll tell you folks, I'm tempted to go to get within Jeremy Pivot's reaching distance
and roofie myself in the hopes that I'll grab my cock so I can get him out of my field of
stand -up.
I mean, I just did a gig up in Rochester every night on stage.
I was talking about that.
So I'm like, you know, Jeremy Pivot and Tom Arnold, you know, these are all people that
like go through these, I go, does anybody else want to treat my fucking full -time life
commitment?
Like, it's a day at a water park, you know, like we're, let's just breeze in and give this
a shot.
Well, hasn't Arnold been doing it for decades?
Look, Arnold's been doing a lot for decades and none of it's ever been good.
Okay.
True laws.
I mean, I now know how every fucking, now I know how John Goodman felt on the set of
Roseanne.
Right.
Now that I've had to split a fucking lineup or be on the same lineup as Tom Arnold, I
like, oh, I get it now.
That's why Goodman, there's the stories I'm punching the concrete wall in between scenes
on Roseanne.
It's like, how dare you get out of here?
I hear you.
Who's dick did you suck besides Roseanne's?
Come on now.
Well, I'm not saying she's got a dick, I'm just saying, you know, it's like how can just dating
Roseanne get you in like, it doesn't get you this in.
It's got to get something or else, why are you?
It got him.
Well, look, you got him in as the guy on the Roseanne show, right?
But how in the fuck, like what?
Any had his own show?
Jackie Thomas.
Yeah.
Who owes this guy a fucking favor?
I hear you.
Jesus Christ, man.
Funny and true lies.
I'm not saying the guy is incapable of ever being entertaining, but, you know, you're talking
about, oh, was he funny in the James Cameron billion dollar film where anybody could look
could?
Yeah.
Paxton steals true lies, but like two scenes, he pisses himself twice, Paxton pisses
himself.
Yeah.
I don't remember that part.
Schwarzenegger's scarism.
Oh, okay.
He's very funny.
Paxton.
I love Bill Paxton.
That's my Bill Paxton impression.
Um, hey, we're, that's not a good impression.
That's it is.
We're already in danger.
Paxton.
It's getting worse.
We're in danger of getting too carried away.
Uh, let's get to, if, if I may, Paxton movie court.
Yeah.
You may not.
Oh, how about that, folks, I, no regard for my authority.
I have been seeing just an absurd amount of films.
Uh, so, you know, I really could talk for days, but I'm going to narrow it down to my usual
three.
Oh, by the way, our movie today is the child's play series.
The movie is, yes, we'll be discussing the new child's play with Aubrey Plaza.
We'll be discussing the entire franchise.
I very recently watched the OG trilogy.
We've done cult of Chuckie on here.
And, uh, you know, I've seen all of them bride and all that.
I, I have very little remembrance of them, but we're going to be discussing the entire franchise
much as we did with pet cemetery.
Notice how I was able to say all that and just saying the child's play series, but I wanted
to tell you that series pretty much covers it.
I mean, it's only, it's only eight movies.
It's not, there's not like spitting off TV shows and shit.
There is coming, isn't it?
Not yet, though.
Not yet.
But an interesting stand.
Live in the moment.
Interesting stand to take when there is a TV show coming.
I'm just saying, you didn't have to be like, we won't be covering the novel, the novella
series.
Oh my god.
Damn it.
Uh, all right.
So what have I seen last night?
I saw a picture called them that follow.
I hear this is a great picture and my, oh, it sucks.
Oh man.
I was excited to see Gaffigan's my buddy, and I was excited to see him in this creepy snake
movie.
And I heard it's a really cool movie.
It's not.
Gaffigan, I love as a comic.
I thought he was really good in it as a dramatic performer, but he's got a small part.
He's the husband of recent Academy Award winner Olivia Coleman.
This movie is so boring.
I was open mouth snoring at one point in the theater.
But yeah, it's about weird Pentecostals.
Walton Goggins plays this pastor who like, he's like, you know, they try to use snakes to
decide if you're truly faithful or not.
And the story just takes forever to take off performances are decent, but like, man, there
was so much potential for like a good, creepy time.
There's nothing thrilling about it.
Nothing really dramatic about it.
I just did not like the movie.
And Olivia, oh, that's the lady from Peep show.
Correct.
Oh, she's in it.
Jesus Christ.
It's a stacked cast.
Wow.
Talk about.
They hand you that script.
Here we go, baby.
Yeah.
Here we go.
Oscar money.
That's a shame.
It wasn't good.
It was dull.
I've got three.
I'm excited to talk about.
All right.
I'm going to save my second two more surprising ones.
I'll start out with safe spaces, which is a movie I saw at the Traverse City Film Festival
curated and started by Michael Moore, the filmmaker.
I was out there doing some live podcasting with Doug Benson as a guest of his.
And we were allowed to see as many movies as we wanted to.
I unfortunately didn't have a ton of time.
Them that follow was there.
I didn't get to see it.
But one of the movies I was able to see was.
A little picture called safe spaces.
Starting just in long.
And my friend Kate Berlant was in it.
Sure.
I know, Kate Berlant.
She was wonderful.
First stand up show I did.
She went on after me, bombed harder than I've ever seen anyone bombed.
She's got to not act.
Yeah.
I mean, this was real odd.
I told her when she came off.
I was like, I love that.
And she was like, fuck you.
I said, I did.
I know nobody laughed, but I liked it.
She's great.
She's very cool.
She's wonderful in it.
Richard Schiff is in it.
He's wonderful in it.
Fran Drescher is in it.
She's wonderful in it.
Justin Long is really sure.
Drescher plays the mom.
She's fantastic.
Drescher.
Dare I say.
Like you've never seen her before.
All right.
So she doesn't do the laugh.
No, she plays, she plays a mother in it.
It's about Justin Long is basically the main character.
He's fantastic.
Yeah.
He plays a teacher that gets into to a bit of trouble at school.
And the situation at school is paralleled with his grandmother,
who's his best friend, is dying in the hospital.
Drescher plays the mother in mourning.
It is a wonderful, wonderful film about family.
And it also, hence the title, deals with the current climate right now.
And how saying the wrong thing could get you in trouble.
And I don't mean saying the wrong thing like, hey, nice ass.
Right.
Just the wrong discussion taking place in the wrong environment can affect people
in a certain way that you might not understand.
Sure.
And also can backfire in your face in a way that you may not expect.
And it kind of hits that thing, that argument, that discussion from every angle.
It doesn't have the hand it from one way or the other.
It just really opens it up to all sides.
And I watched this thing in a theater filled with Traverse City.
You know, it's a very liberal city.
As you can imagine, that's the Michael Moore Film Festival.
Right.
And it was met with great applause.
And, you know, people were crying.
And it was just a wonderful film.
Okay.
And it did not wave a white night flag.
It really was, you know, you feel bad for Justin Long when he gets in trouble.
And you're on his side.
But then when you start to understand why he's in trouble, you start to see the other side of it,
where the person is coming from.
I don't want to give away too much.
But it's not like, I do want to say one thing.
It's not like he does anything fucked up.
He doesn't like, right.
He doesn't like, grow a woman or anything like that.
So you'll have to see it to see.
The director was a man I befriended.
And I also befriended the producer of this film.
They were two wonderful people.
Courtney Johnson was the producer.
And Dan Schechter was the director.
Courtney's worked on several films, including, I think, I think she told me she worked on...
Oh, Christ, what's the one with Steve Carell, the wrestling team?
Fox Catcher.
Yeah, I think she said she worked on that.
I don't remember.
Okay.
Dan Schechter, as a director and writer, I'm not sure what else he's worked on.
I'm aside from one movie called Life of Crime, which you and I have seen and like very much,
which is essentially an...
It's based on a no more Leonard novel.
That's a prequel to Jackie Brown.
I told him, like, I hung out with him a few days and we were drinking and stuff.
And I was like, hey, man, you know, I love Life of Crime.
And he was on Doug's podcast, too.
And he was like, thank you.
Like, he was so touched.
Yeah.
You know, but this movie I would say is the superior film of the two.
And it's a really excellent movie and it's very, very, very funny.
I'm excited to see it.
Yeah.
Save spaces.
Yes.
All right.
Go check it out.
I saw a new picture called The Nightingale.
This is from the director of The Boba Duke, Jennifer Kent.
And it's a tough watch.
It's set in the early 1800s.
It's about this girl Claire.
She's like 21 Irish.
And from the jump, she is being sexually assaulted.
Her husband is sort of kept from her.
Her baby is sort of kept from her.
It's a real rough watch.
You watch for 45 minutes as this woman is just tormented, used, abused.
Actually, I said her baby and her husband are kept from her.
She lives with them, but her body is basically under the control of these soldiers that she has been captured by.
The woman, Jennifer Kent, is like, it's not a rape revenge movie.
Don't call it that.
That upsets me.
But the movie is this girl tracking these soldiers who assaulted her through the woods to kill them.
That is a revenge movie.
I don't know why she's so passionately against it.
But it's got a little more in its mind.
She has a black man and aboriginal guy guiding her.
And basically, there's a lot of discussion of colonialism about how the white man takes so much from women, so much from the blacks.
And that stuff is all interesting and pretty well done.
Ultimately, though, when you're forcing an audience to watch 45 minutes, not unbroken, but essentially, of abuse, rape.
She is raped in front of her husband at one point.
I won't get into specifics of what all is done to her, but it's very brutal.
And you want to see her get that revenge.
And again, I'm not going to spoil anything because it's new to theaters.
Where it goes is not as satisfying as it could be.
And all I'm saying is, if you're going to have death wish, you want to see Charles Branson blow these motherfuckers away.
The movie I know is getting some criticism, which is surprising, because even as a female writer director, she has taken a little heat with people saying, hey, lady, what's the point of this?
Like, this is just, this is really just a brutality on film.
Like, we're not, you know, like, you know, I guess you're trying to say something here, but like, you know.
So, I don't really have much interest in seeing it.
That gets into, that gets into that wolf creek territory for me where I'm like, it's just a psycho with a knife to a woman's throat for an hour and a half.
It's like, I don't, this is just bad news.
Like, I don't, I'll watch the news if I want to see this shit.
The second soldier, there's one who's truly evil, and the second is sort of a, I guess, equally evil, really.
But he's the guy who played Charles Manson, and once upon a time in Hollywood, just a real punchable face, really hate that guy.
But I saw it at the brand new downtown Alamo draft house.
You and I have been to the one in Colorado where we did our live podcast.
We, I've been to the one in Austin.
And it's the, the LA one is the LA one.
It's, it doesn't quite have that feeling of community yet.
They do have an amazing video rental section.
You can rent two a week for free.
I have a rages thing that they have.
I love it.
I think it's awesome.
I can't rent my head around.
How that's anything more than them just being super cool.
It's super cool.
And I think they realized that with it being downtown, they're going to get some light fees.
But I think they also had this huge DVD collection, probably from its video vortex.
So I'm sure all these video stores when they went out of business need something to do with it.
Why not let people rent these movies?
It's a very cool system.
I rented to myself.
And they have tons, which you rented Debbie does Dallas.
They have tons of porn.
And Debbie goes to Washington.
I rented Dead and Barried, which is I heard about on the now deceased 80s all over podcast.
It's supposed to be a great loss horror movie.
I'm excited to watch.
And I rented Shoot the Moon, which is a very intense good divorce drama with Diane Keaton and Albert Finney.
But they have all this out of print shit.
They do have a lot of pornography.
It's really cool.
And my issue is the Alamos whole thing is that you're not allowed to talk and not let it text and all that, which is great.
But you are ordering food and people bring it out to you and they bring it out to you throughout the movie.
So what was troubling to me is I'm literally watching a woman get gang raped
while trying to see well enough to order my Kenwa bowl.
And then I'm trying to eat it while watching her get raped again.
And I was like, this is fucked.
No, why you would pick that movie at the Alamo draft.
You go to the Alamo draft house, you go see like black belt Jones.
It was the only thing I had to say.
I wanted to try it out.
But if you are in the LA area, I highly recommend it.
You're describing like a fucking clockwork orange rehabilitation scene right now.
It was rough.
But go for nothing else to check out the video store and to see the amazing posters they have.
They have all these foreign posters for like the blob, the fog.
It's really, really cool.
Let me lift our spirits a little bit with my next entry into the movie corner.
Okay.
I revisited a little comedy special called Dorf on go.
Wow.
Where is this airing?
It's not.
I was watching a rerun of married with children that had Tim Conway in it.
And Dorf or?
No, as Peggy's dad.
Like Peggy's like Hick dad in it.
Okay.
It's such an unfunny scene in the show.
And it's not all Tim Conway's fault.
A lot of it is the writing.
I'm sure it's not Conway's fault.
It's hilarious.
This scene made me beg to differ.
I was like, man, was Tim Conway not funny?
Because the scene is so bad.
I was like, you know, I want to go back and watch like.
And I was kind of scoffing like, I'm going to go watch Dorf on golf.
I bet it's on YouTube.
I looked it up, but I'm like, I bet this is so stupid.
I bet this guy wasn't funny at all.
Five minutes into this thing.
I'm fucking howling.
It's like, all right.
It was the writing on married red children.
And Dorf is just a man who puts shoes on his knees and is short.
Is there anything else to the character?
The physical comedy of it is pretty impressive.
Like the way he bends back and forth and what he does with his body
because he is on his knees, but it looks like he's standing up.
Right.
It's really funny.
Victor, who's the guy from Ghost that plays the Ghost on the Train?
Oh, I know who you mean.
I don't know.
Victor Shrely or whatever.
Vincent Shrely.
He plays his caddy who's like a brain dead like idiot.
And then like, you know, it's a typical thing.
Like this is like a mild mannered guy who's a golf expert.
And then everybody around him is an idiot.
Right.
And slowly but surely he's like coming unglued throughout the thing.
And dad always loved Dorf.
And dad's loved Dorf.
I went and looked at the Dorf series on Wikipedia.
You know, you eventually, you know, you're getting pretty deep.
Dorf goes to Olympus.
Oh, yeah.
It's like, you know, you don't need...
Dorf on golf was enough for me.
Thirty minutes.
I was in.
I was out.
But I enjoyed it.
It put a smile on my face and it didn't make me laugh out loud.
All right.
Yeah, I'll stick to theatrical releases this week.
I saw a picture.
You should really check out.
Called the art of self -defense starring Jesse Eisenberg.
Who was an actor I can kind of go either way on.
But he is so perfectly cast here.
I assume him and Michael Sarah just gets sent every script together.
And it's like which one of you wants to do this?
I feel like he became the new Michael Sarah.
He did.
Sarah essentially retired almost.
But look, it is a very, very dark movie.
I would say the best way to explain it would be like Fight Club mixed with Napoleon Dynamite,
if that makes any sense.
That's how I'm hearing it described.
That's a pretty good tonal comparison.
But the movie is a guy, a nerdy, dorky guy, who gets attacked.
He gets attacked by a group on motorcycles.
They beat him nearly to death.
And he goes into a karate school to try to get, you know, the skills of self -defense.
But the filmmaker, it's this guy Riley Sterns.
He directed a pretty good little indie called Faults about two people stuck in a hotel room.
It's a really cool little movie.
This is a massive step up in my opinion.
It tries to ride a nearly impossible tone of extreme violence, extreme commentary on like men and masculinity,
while also being very absurdist and funny.
I'll say it takes a few tonal missteps here and there.
But by and large, it works like gangbusters.
The guy who did it's name is Riley Sterns.
He's a real talent.
The movie's become a nice little hit.
It was weirdly sold out when I saw it.
But Eisenberg is great.
Imogen Poots is great.
And stealing the show is the great Alazandro Nevola, who you know from face -off American hustle.
He's been in tons of movies.
You definitely know him.
I think he's in the new sopranos prequel coming up.
But he is the many sense of new work.
He's going to play Dickie Molta -Santi as a young man.
But he is so good in this.
And he's an actor who's always good, but just really gets the big parts.
I recommend it highly.
The audience was howling in spots, gasping in spots.
The comedic tone is so strange.
That's why I compare it to Napoleon Dynamite.
It's almost like they're inventing kind of a new tone.
And I always really admire that.
It's a big risk.
If you're on its wavelength, you'll enjoy it very much.
Go see it.
I will close this out with a little piece of magic called BH90210.
The Beverly Hills 90210 reboot.
Okay.
Curiosity got the best of me.
I didn't even know this thing existed.
And I'm listening to the radio the other day as I'm driving.
And it's going today.
The biggest reboot in history.
Beverly Hills 90210 season premiered.
I'm going.
They rebooted that like three years ago.
Like who cares?
Like it's just the new season of that new 90210 show.
Right.
And then I realize, holy shit, no, it's a fucking reboot of the show.
Of the original show with the original cast.
Not that I was ever a fan, but I was like, well, how are they going to do that?
I'm curious.
Because there was a lot of behind -the -scenes drama.
I turn it on.
On Hulu.
The opening scene is all of them arriving back at the peach pit,
which now, Dylan, not Dylan, Jason Priestley's character.
Brandon.
Right?
Walsh.
Yeah.
Brandon Walsh.
They used to call me Brenda in high school because of.
Oh, okay, good.
Brenda Walsh.
I've never seen the show.
I've never seen any episode about it.
So he now owns it.
By the way, they already rebooted it.
No.
Well, they rebooted it with young people.
Okay.
This is, yeah.
Anyway, they all show up at the peach pit.
I'm watching this thing and I'm like, my God, this is fucking terrible.
Like everybody walking in like, hey, stranger.
You know, like it's just like the worst written reunion type scene
you could ever seen.
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
And then Tory spelling wakes up.
She's on a plane.
I was like, hey, you got me guys.
She was dreaming.
And then I quickly realized they're playing themselves.
They're playing, they're not doing a reboot of the show.
They're doing a show about the actors rebooting the show.
Okay.
And I was like, all right, guys, like I respect the extra step there.
I like that you kind of went at this with a different way.
From a different angle.
And then I was skeptical because I was like, well, what do you guys think?
You're Larry David.
You think you're going to be funny, right?
In playing like these weird versions of yourselves.
But then again, they got me again.
I quickly realized, oh, what they're doing is,
is they're taking all the backstage drama of the original show,
all the rumors, all the gossip about these people and the cast and all that stuff.
And they're implementing it into the story
and making it the dramatic arc of them trying to redo the show.
And I was like, this is actually pretty fucking smart, man.
Like, this is pretty sharp.
And there were some funny parts.
They're all taking huge fucking digs at themselves, particularly Brian Austin Green,
which made me really like Brian Austin Green,
because I always thought he was kind of the one that maybe took it a little too seriously.
I was very wrong.
He's very much just like, nobody gives a shit.
Like, I'm done. I'm out of the spotlight.
My wife is famous.
That's where I'm at.
I really enjoyed it, man.
I don't know that I'll watch it every week as they premiere or whatever,
but it's certainly something I wouldn't mind watching again to see where it goes.
I'm curious to see how they're going to handle the Luke Perry thing.
They haven't mentioned Luke Perry?
Not in the first one, because I don't think he was supposed to be in the pilot.
And I think he died.
He was actually contracted to do some episodes.
So maybe they actually got him in a few.
I don't know.
But I think that was supposed to be a big mystery in the first episode.
Like, is he going to come back or not?
Just like how he was only on the show for a little while.
Right.
And I enjoyed it.
I enjoyed watching these people make fun of themselves.
And I enjoyed watching them play like these ridiculous versions of themselves.
Reafant of the original series?
No, I never watched it.
Then what possessed you?
That's always my question.
I explained all of this over the last five minutes.
I mean, clearly you were just zoned out.
I know what you're saying, but what would make you want to watch Beverly Hills 902 when I'll read it?
I don't get it.
I said I didn't even know this was happening.
Right.
And I was like, wait a minute.
The entire cast came back?
Well, there was all this drama.
I'm just curious.
How are they going to do this?
So I turned it on.
And then quickly realized, oh, this isn't a reboot.
This is them doing this weird meta reboot.
Right.
And then I just kept getting more and more interested.
Like, how are they doing that?
And the more I realized how they were doing it, the more I was like, you know what?
This is kind of cool.
Okay.
All right.
And I did like that like in the interviews and everything about the show.
They were like, we didn't want to do reboots have been done to death.
We didn't want to do it.
Yeah.
Like we didn't want to come out and just be like, here are the old characters.
We didn't want to be the last people to the party on that.
So we figured out a different way to do it.
Okay.
Which I think was cool.
All right.
I know.
Listen.
It's no beef.
I think they've dumped the entire writing staff.
So there's probably massive problems brewing already.
I believe so.
I mean, look, it's not an expertly written show, but it's written well enough.
Yeah.
All right.
For a Fox prime time fucking TV show, you know, no, I mean, what I was trying.
I was asking is I assumed you had affection for the original series and learning that you've never seen it.
I was.
No, no, that's why, as I said, I explained all that.
You didn't say you didn't say you'd never seen the show.
I did.
You maybe we should rewind the tape.
And we show because every time we do, I'm proving right, but it's not true.
I just didn't hear it.
I know.
Come on.
I'm breaking false a little bit here.
But yeah, I've never seen the show myself.
What do you say we get to our first.
Let's get on with the show.
Oh, shit.
And on.
That hurt.
I like that one.
Childs play the series then and now.
Childs play.
Let's start with the original, I guess, right?
Well, then jump up to the remake.
Sure.
I mean, this is a franchise that is much like the Beverly Hills 90210 franchise is currently going through a lot of growing pains.
Another show that shouldn't be rebooted.
And also a franchise that gets super meta.
Correct.
Yeah, but Don Mancini did the original child's play.
He's done a lot of great work in the low budget horror genre.
And basically, MGM had the rights to child's play, but not its sequels, just child's play.
They decided to do this movie without him.
He is doing his own sort of reboot as a series on shutter.
If I'm correct, I don't even think it's a reboot.
I think it's a continuation of the movie.
Okay, continuation.
He was very angry with the filmmakers because, you know, it's Hollywood.
I don't know why you thought he'd be treated with any degree of respect.
But I know I have the answer to that.
Okay.
They went to him and said we would like to do this.
Would you approve?
And he said no, I don't.
Yeah.
And then they did it anyway.
Exactly.
He was like, you know, guys, like what the fuck?
You asked me, you know, and then they want to put his name on.
And he's like, no, you're not putting my name on it to try to legitimize it.
I said no.
Yeah.
And, you know, the new movie bombed, but we'll get to it.
The deal is child's play won 1988, written by Don Mancini and others directed by Tom Holland.
And it's super fun.
I mean, I watched it recently.
The thing holds up like you wouldn't believe.
I'd say the chucky effects are better in child's play won than the rebake.
I agree with that.
Well, that's back when they'd be like, we built 67 dolls.
Yeah.
You know, like one with a curious face.
Right, right, right.
Yeah.
They don't do that anymore.
No.
But the original is great.
Cereal killer is dying through black magic, throws a spirit into a doll.
Then the doll becomes possessed with a Cereal killer and starts to kill people.
Yeah.
We can't get any more straightforward than that.
It works.
Brad Dorif, the voice of chucky.
The story is just very clean.
You know, all these movies are like a tight 90 or less.
And child's play won from my money remains the gold standard of all the franchise, the reboots, the reinventions.
It just really works as a good horror picture.
It's scary.
It does a perfect.
It's one of the better balances of comedy and horror.
Chuckie is obviously very funny.
And from then on, you know, I think they kind of ran away with people loving the comedy.
I think it's a lot of comedy of a doll cursing and that became the defining trade of the franchise.
I would say, and we don't have to go over every film, but I would say, what is a classic?
Two is a worthwhile watching sequel.
I really like two.
Yeah, it's a decent sequel for sure.
Three, you're in it for a couple good kills and not much more than that.
Three is bad upon watching it recently.
The actor's in its suck.
The idea of having it at a boarding school doesn't work in any way.
They also replace the actor that played Andy, which is boring.
Yeah, he ain't good.
The other kid in it is not good.
He lost me with four and five seat curts seat of Chuckie and bride of Chuckie.
I was I was out.
Those are the ones that got super meta where they became about the movies.
Yeah, behind the scenes, but then Chuckie was actually real.
Right.
They just became flat out comedies at that point.
Horror was second.
At that point, he was basically doing these like spectacular B movie kind of things.
Right.
I appreciate it the shift in the vision.
I appreciate it that he was like, well, what if we took this in a real exploitative direction?
Yeah.
Interesting.
Not for me.
However,
Curse of Chuckie,
second best in the franchise, in my opinion,
complete return to form.
Awesome.
Straight up horror movie.
And they ties it in to the entire franchise, not just even the Curse and bride, or seat and bride movies.
Which I found impressive.
We did cult on this show.
If you want to go back and listen to a more in depth, which I thought was pretty unsuccessful, but some decent moments.
Cult is a lot like three where, hey, you're going to have some fun, but it's not really a good movie.
I recall, you know, watching with some friends in a basement, bride and seed being kind of like trashy fun.
The movies are, none of them is a waste, you know?
It's not like, usually when you get to number seven in a horror franchise, you're watching just the absolute bottom of the barrel.
And I think Mancini does a really good job.
And he's, you know, the credited screenwriter on all of them, sometimes with others, but usually just him.
He does a good job of keeping things fun and inventive and mixing up the formula.
And I think for that reason, it's one of the more successful of these franchises.
It's certainly better than, say, a puppet master or something like that.
And he directed, he started directing them, I think, with seed.
I think it's when he's directed.
Yes, correct.
Seed person cult, he directed.
Did you know that two and three were only like nine months apart?
No, but it's obvious when you watch three.
Yeah.
I guess that's why they got a new actor for Andy because he wasn't, they wanted to jump ahead a bit.
Right.
And that actor was eventually brought back.
I got drunk with him once at a horror convention.
Okay.
Nice.
I mean, I was drunk.
I thought he was.
Maybe he wasn't, but he was probably scared for his life.
Yeah.
Well, I had him pinned against a wall.
Sure.
I was whispering into his ear how much I love the movies.
Chuckie is do say things like sometimes I feel like I'm Andy.
Yes.
From what I heard from him, the exchange ended with you on your back asking him to change your diaper.
Which I just was appalled.
Yeah.
And I kept saying Chuckie been a bad boy.
Right.
He didn't like that.
I was wrong.
It's not on shutter.
The show is called Chuckie and it premieres on sci -fi in 2020 apparently.
Brad Dorif is returning to play Chuckie.
In the new film, it is Mark Hamill who does a really good job, I would say, a great choice.
Mark Hamill does a great job in the new, yeah, let's get to the new movie.
Let's, so let's talk about the pros.
The new movie, as you said, Mark Hamill, right?
Yeah.
Mark Hamill does a good Chuckie.
In fact, I thought the whole cast was pretty good.
I didn't think I was going to be able to buy Aubrey Plaza as a single mom, but I thought she was good.
I thought Plaza was excellent and to me, she has the edge over the original Chuckie series because she's got some bite tour.
She's a more interesting character.
She's not the just kind of like the moms in these Chuckie movies.
I don't even really remember.
But Plaza brought some bite.
I thought she was funny.
I thought she was good.
I don't know why they had her dating a 55 -year -old man.
I didn't get that idea.
But that guy played a great asshole.
He was good.
Yeah, I mean, Plaza's in this thing.
I think you see her in her undies at one point.
Just smoking.
Yeah.
They got her hooking up with this guy that looks like he fucking, it looks like Ron Howard.
Yeah, exactly.
He's a ginger.
Apparently he was in lights out.
I don't remember that movie really, but he was the bad guy.
I think.
I just realized.
Then Brian Tyre Henry, who is absolutely phenomenal on Atlanta,
which is a great series on FX that you've probably seen.
Brian Tyre Henry kind of steals the show from me.
And here's where I thought this movie really shone.
The character of Brian Tyre Henry lives across from Andy and his mom.
And he's just, he's got a lot of warmth to him.
The relationship between him and his mother, who's elderly,
is very sweet.
Obviously, you know, these characters are all probably going to die.
It is a horror movie.
As they start to die, I cared.
And that is such a rare thing in horror these days.
I was genuinely, you know, there's always suspense and horror.
But I felt like, don't kill her.
Don't kill her.
You know, like, I really got into it.
They did a good job with it.
I was very pleasantly surprised until, which I'm sure we'll get to,
the ending is not great.
But the remake of, of child's play, I thought was almost entirely successful.
I had a good time with it.
I was surprised to my surprise, completely invested.
Yeah.
For the first two acts of this movie, I was enjoying myself.
I thought, man, they really did it.
I, I wanted to hate this thing.
I predicted that I wouldn't like it.
I was completely wrong.
They made the right changes.
This works fantastically.
I'm loving this.
And then act three begins.
And it's just a nonsensical shit show from there on out.
It, none of it makes sense anymore.
To be real, it's a different movie.
It feels as if you're watching a completely different movie.
As it clicks, like you can almost watch the studio dial.
Click from act two to act three.
It falls apart.
Yeah.
Clearly some fucking moron at the studio, as usual,
came in and goes, we need it bigger.
We need a big finale.
Right.
And then you get this ridiculous fucking finale,
where Chuck E is somehow controlling every electronic device
in the store.
Yeah.
Because at that point in the storyline,
you realize the company that has made Chuck E
apparently makes every electronic anybody ever uses.
So it starts out as this interesting commentary
on like Google Home and Siri and Alexa and all these things
that they say are kind of spying on you.
And, you know, a smart home and everything gets absurd
because Apple, just for example,
doesn't make every single fucking product you buy.
Yeah.
They got this company, by the end of this thing,
you see that it makes the hearing aid the kid way.
It's absurd.
Right.
The hearing aid, by the way, the main character Andy wears.
Never comes into play.
For some reason, this kid's got a hearing aid to the entire movie.
It's a horror movie.
You think at some point he'd lose it and he wouldn't be able to hear.
Well, that would create suspense.
Yeah.
You do the copland ending once the long gets his hearing blown out.
But like clearly to me,
if the screenwriter knew what they were doing at all,
and I think the first two -thirds show that they really did know
what they were doing, obviously that must have played in
to the ending.
And that's why I think there must have been some tinkering at the studio,
because why on earth would the hearing aid not play a key role?
It's a great horror setup,
and they really don't explore it in any way.
Did you like the new way in,
which is this guy as sort of a last -ditch effort?
He kills himself, the toy manufacturer,
and puts the evil chip in the doll.
I thought it was interesting.
I went along with the ride.
Because the way that works, if you haven't seen it,
they don't do the serial killer thing.
They basically, the guy at the factory,
it's basically like a switch.
It's supposed to, it's clearly supposed to be a sweatshop,
but they were like, the studio is clearly like,
you can't have them hitting a 12 -year -old boy.
Yeah.
So it's a 48 -year -old man working at a sweatshop, right?
Anyway, he's getting yelled at by the boss,
or the guy that runs it, whatever you call,
a sweatshop boss.
And to, out of an active defiance,
he takes off the safety governors in one of the chucky dolls.
Yeah.
And what that means is these dolls are AI.
They're able to learn in mimic behavior.
But there are certain behaviors they are shut off,
too, kind of like when you curse at series,
you won't curse back, or you're whatever it is.
So he takes off these governors
and then kills himself because he somehow knows
that this will be horrible.
And then the doll starts to pick up the wrong behaviors
and becomes more, as he becomes more and more protective of Andy,
becomes more and more deadly to do so.
Now, and that stuff, I thought, worked beautifully.
I thought that worked really well.
You know, you actually start to believe, like,
I'll tell you this, you feel for the doll at times
because you think the relationship between
he and Andy becomes is way more based on like a boy
and his dog or something.
Where you see that the thing loves him,
but it's doing the wrong things to show it.
Right.
Like cutting off someone's head and putting it in a watermelon hatch
and a very bizarre thing.
Yeah, because it doesn't know any better.
Yeah.
So, you know, so that I bought that.
Look, if it were me, here's what I would have done.
Because this is also a commentary on today.
I would have had it that a serial killer himself hacked
into the doll and was controlling it remotely from somewhere else
and going on a killing spree.
And then that way the doll could talk evil
and all that shit.
That's personally how I would have done it.
But I was willing to go along with the way they did it.
I didn't think it was a bad idea.
I thought it was cool.
I enjoyed it.
The problem is, is at the top of Act 3 or the end of Act 2,
wherever you're at, they destroy the doll and they rip this chip out of it
because they know that this is what's causing all the harm.
This creepy, super intended in the building,
which that's another weird twist that goes nowhere,
suddenly you realize the super intended in the building is a peeping tom.
Yeah.
And you're like, what?
And I think they do that just so you don't feel sad when he gets killed.
It's like, guys, just kill the fucking super.
Who cares?
Well, they killed the unbelievably sweet grandma
who I was talking about loving and you really feel for her.
That's why I don't know why they needed to demonize somebody else.
They certainly didn't demonize her.
So I thought, you know, again, that's studio tampering.
We can't have too many nice people die.
Why would we root for this doll?
Right.
The fuck up.
Anyway, he finds the doll, which by the way,
this guy looks so much like Jack Black.
One of the reviews of the movie I read that was a bad review.
They go, then the super intended comes into the movie.
I don't know the actor's name, but he might as well change it now to,
I'm not Jack Black.
Yeah.
That's how much he looked.
I thought it was Jack Black.
Yeah.
Anyway, but he rebuilds the doll and orders a new chip to put into it
and then puts the chip into it and then the doll is still evil.
Right.
In fact, more evil for no apparent reason.
It makes no sense.
Right.
It just disregards all logic in the top of the third act immediately.
And then Chucky for some reason, which is never really explained,
has the ability to not just control the devices you link him to,
but every device ever made by the company.
So there's a big showdown in, or finale rather, in a department store
where he sets off all the dolls in the store
and then all the dolls go into killing spree.
And what makes this triply unbelievable is you've got a gaggle of people
behind like a ribbon that they're waiting to cut for the midnight release of the new doll.
And they're all chanting, buddy, buddy.
And you're like, guys, this is fucking absurd.
Like, people don't even do that for the new iPhones anymore.
Right.
And when they did, they didn't chant.
Yeah.
Like, this is crazy.
And like, the people aren't listening.
And like, he's trying to warn them that something bad is about to happen.
It's like a SWAT team trying to control people trying to get a doll basically.
Yeah, it just goes off the rails.
And then Chucky becomes full asshole.
Well, Chucky somehow is able to tie Aubrey Plaza up completely.
Right.
What is happening right now?
Chucky controlling everyone was really baffling to me.
Chucky controlling every doll in the store.
It does not track at all with what we've seen.
It's ludicrous.
It makes no sense.
And then really, it's setting up the stage for this sort of act three stranger things,
ask finale where the kids team up to get Chucky.
And that's again where it's sort of smacked of like,
yeah, bringing that stranger things element, you know.
Meanwhile, kids can't see this movie.
So why?
But there were children when I was watching it.
It's insane with parents.
For sure.
People, can you parent your fucking kids, please?
If I see one more TV show, about 12 -year -olds,
where the 12 -year -old kid is like, hey, mom, what the fuck?
Yeah.
And it's just like fine.
I know.
I'm like, who are these parents?
Who doesn't turn around and go, if you say that again,
I'm going to knock your fucking block off.
Don't fuck, don't talk like that.
To this day and I am not kidding,
I have never said fucking front of either of my parents.
It's outrageous.
They would not be cool with it now.
And I say it now, but, you know.
I said the movie didn't do well.
I was wrong.
You forget that all these horror movies turn a great profit because they're cheap.
Costs 10 million made 42.
That's good.
For me, I definitely think it's worth seeing.
It's going to be out on, you know, video on demand streaming.
Surely I would imagine.
There's a lot of fun in it.
I mean, when they've got, he's got the head wrapped up.
And it's almost like a Frazier -style farce scene where he pretends
it's a gift for the lady next door that's wrapped up head.
Yeah.
You know, there's some really unusual and fun stuff in it.
And I think, you know, some poor third -act choices are not enough
to make it a not recommend.
I just think it could have been a lot better, but I'm happy it was at least very entertaining.
And I go see a child's play too.
This is off to where we part ways.
My hog is down, based on the third act.
That's Fiasco.
But, you know, if you're not, I would say this, if you're not too worried about that.
And you just want to see some fun lead up.
Watch the first one.
You know, there are rumors circling now that the next movie might center around
one of the bare dolls that comes to life.
I mean, who wants to, you know, I got Teddy Ruckspin.
Well, because, remember, some of the new dolls at the end of the movie are bears.
Yeah.
The fuck wants to see that.
I don't give a shit.
You know, I'd say it.
I just think it's an unquestionably fun premise to watch a doll kill people.
And I'll probably go see all of them that they make them.
But here's my other thing and we're going to review Annabelle creation too.
We criticize Hollywood a lot in the show.
They released two killer doll movies, one week apart.
Yeah.
The child's play we make an Annabelle creation.
Folks, if that doesn't tell you that this is the stupidest industry in the world,
I don't know what does.
They're spying on each other.
Yeah.
And going, uh -oh.
Well, your universal Scott one coming out.
That's green like quick.
Rush that one, even though we thought it sucked.
Yeah.
It's so stupid because it's never Annabelle.
I'm sure thought, well, we've got the bigger franchise.
We'll just blow them out of the water.
It's like, no, you'll steal each other's thunder.
And neither of you will be special and you'll be out of theaters quicker than you would have been.
Remember when the illusionist and the prestige came out on like the same day?
I do.
My buddy was like, there's been a movie about magicians in 38 years in this country.
Two come out on the same week.
It's the dumbest strategy.
All right, folks.
Jotaro's a comedy on Instagram and Twitter.
A back, baby.
Whoa.
Reactivated the accounts.
I didn't even see it on there.
It's mainly just for promotional purposes, but we'll see how it goes.
And that's it.
And then the November or December issue of Penthouse, I supposedly have a new article coming out in that
about my deletion of Twitter.
So I don't I believe that maybe it will maybe I don't know.
You never know until it's in the goddamn thing, but hopefully it'll be in there.
So and watch you let me down, Joe's comedy central series.
Thank you, Patty.
Very funny.
I am very rarely on Twitter and Instagram at the Patrick Walsh.
That's what I got going.
Movies that are still to come.
Annabelle creation.
We're going to do the fly the gold bloom.
And what else, Joseph?
Mid -summer.
We already did it.
I know, but it's not out yet.
Well, we don't know what order these are coming out.
And that's true.
I think.
Yeah.
Scary stories to tell in the dark.
There's just shit coming out.
Yeah.
I like to give people that.
I know.
I don't know what order we're going to release these.
I don't want to get all confused.
We're doing scary stories telling the dark.
Or we've already done it.
That's the thrill of this podcast.
You don't know.
Patty, which timeline you're in.
Yes.
We'll see you next time.
And we'll see you in hell.