Folks, we're back with part two of the Q and a, uh, and let's keep it going.
Sean wants to know, would you love to hear, would love to hear
your take on the movie climax?
I don't know what that movie is.
Climax is from the guy who did irreversible.
Um, it is not quite as unsettling as irreversible, but it's pretty close.
Gaspar or no.
Um, I fucking love climax.
I own the soundtrack to climax.
I, when that guy is, is firing, he makes some truly amazing, uncomfortable shit.
I actually think he's a great filmmaker, irreversible.
Maybe I'll give another chance someday.
That was too much for me, quite frankly, but, uh, enter the void.
I love, I've seen it 10 times and I think climax is great.
The opening dance sequence is something I watch all the time.
And the final 45 minutes is like, it's a, like a horror movie mixed with a musical
mixed with, uh, psychological thriller.
I think the guy does great shit.
Very, very original, interesting shit.
Matt asked, do you guys just collect boutique Blu -rays or all sorts?
I collect all sorts, although lately I go mostly for 4k.
Which are your favorite brands?
I really just want a detailed vision of your collections.
Yeah, maybe I'll do some sort of tour through my collection someday.
I don't know.
Um, that might be a good movie corner actually, but, um, you're right.
I mean, obviously Criterion is a favorite of mine and Arrow is a
favorite of mine, Shout Factory, Scream Factory, the vinegar syndrome.
They tend to go too obscure and I'm just never in the mood to spend $60 to take a
chance on a movie I've never even heard of, you know, they go a little obscure for me.
Uh, I also all sorts, uh, and all, you know, 4k, Blu -ray, DVD, VHS, my favorite
brand, I actually, you know, uh, arrow probably is the most fun to shop with.
Uh, you know, and, and, and they don't do sales often and stuff.
So when they do, it's a pretty big deal, but I, I'd have to say vinegar
syndrome as a company is probably my favorite, not, not because of the content.
I just really appreciate that they put their money where their mouth is.
They have a store, you know, it's a real sort of mom and pop style operation
up there in Connecticut.
They're very courteous when you go to the store, they help you out with things.
They're schooled on what they're selling.
They support all the other labels.
I just think that they do it really right, regardless of if every movie
they put out is for me or not.
Uh, Joe, Matt asked Joe, any plans to release, uh, all of your specials
physically know that's in the hands of comedy central and they'll probably
never do it, uh, unfortunately.
And it's not up to me as a collector of media.
I think that that would be really fucking cool as a box set.
Well, Matt, so do I, but, uh, the public and comedy central
slash Viacom would disagree.
Uh, onto Steven's question, Joe, fuck, marry, kill Elizabeth Moss, Ari Aster,
Alf, I guess I'll kill Alf because I don't want to fucking or marry a thing.
You don't want to be Eskimo brothers with me.
Yeah, I'm going to go ahead and fuck Elizabeth Moss since she's the only
one I could be physically attracted to in any way, and then Ari I'll marry.
And maybe we grow old as two men that disagree on what cinema is really all
about Pat, when are you going to be featured on the get all right people.
He'll be on the goddamn show when he comes to New York, Jesus Christ.
Uh, Ian asks, what is your honest take on the future of film?
Will we ever have a PTA Tarantino style artist or have the studios and
technology made it so we will only ever get lazily constructed schlock.
I'm looking for something to believe in, but it don't look pretty.
Look, things are bad right now, but to, to assume we'll never have another
like great filmmaker is absurd.
Of course we will.
Um, you look through the most dire periods of film history.
There's always somebody shining through, making great stuff.
So I'm not, uh, I'm not wringing my hands about the future of film.
I think more and more people will go low budget.
They'll find other means of getting their shit made.
And as always, they'll be good stuff and bad.
I think the big budget theatrical experience is probably fucked
for a minimum of five years, but we'll still get good movies.
So yeah, I try to be somewhat optimistic.
Uh, that's how I feel too.
And I think if people, you know, said it about these strikes
on other podcasts, I'll say it here.
You know, the problem with the future of the film industry is people
want to still rely on daddy.
They want a big fancy studio to do all the hard work and give them the keys
to the kingdom so they can feel special and, and be taken care of securely
and all these things and blah, blah, blah.
I'm not saying that people shouldn't want to be treated fairly when they
take those jobs or anything.
I'm in the unions and I stand by everybody, but the biggest problem
that will come out of the result of this strike, these strikes is these
studios are going to give nothing.
Uh, people are going to then just go, okay, well, this is how we work now.
Instead of walking across the street, Glen Gary, Glen Ross style, buying
your own list of clients and starting your own business with a couple of
phones in the office, as he says in the movie, if people would truly utilize
what is at their expense and some people really do or at their, not at their
expense, is that the right term?
At their, what they have access to.
You can still make great art and you can still make it the way you want to.
And people are out there doing that.
And the more people do that, the better it will all become.
Uh, that's my take on it.
Um, Amanda, Pat, what do you revere as the best written screenplay in film history?
Oh geez.
I mean, saints of Newark, the many, yeah, the many saints of Newark.
William, Bill William Goldman, um, is probably the best, like classic film
screenwriter and his books about screenwriting are amazing, but like he
did the Princess Bride, Marathon Man, Misery, All the President's Men,
Butch Cassie and the Sundance Kid, many, many other films.
His screenplays are ones that I look at in terms of perfectly constructed stuff.
That's also like popular entertainment.
Um, I think the Cohen brothers had a run there that's pretty unparalleled.
Fargo is, is amazing screenplay.
Raising Arizona is an amazing screenplay.
Um, you know, I got many favorites.
Joe, what do you find the most difficult part of business ownership to be?
Uh, uh, the most difficult part is I've learned a lesson that most people, no
matter what capacity you are trying to utilize their services for, whether
they're a contractor, uh, or whatever it is, doesn't matter.
Uh, I found that most people want the absolute most amount of money for doing
the absolute least amount of work.
And I have been repeatedly, repeatedly disappointed in that scenario
over and over and over again.
It has certainly made me have regret about the time in my life where I
might've done that with somebody who was paying me to do a job.
You know, we all like to think that we don't do that.
Unfortunately, a lot of us do.
Uh, but I would say the extent and the link that the average person will take
that to and take advantage, uh, and, and be entitled is, is astounding.
Is this absolutely astounding?
So it makes me very angry when people start to talk about, can you believe
that business went over there and did this and did that and did, and, you
know, and, oh, that place used to be great and whatever it's like, try
running that place for three weeks and see what they're dealing with.
And then wonder why they have to make the decisions they have to
make to keep the doors open.
So that's been tough.
Tom has a question.
Joe, would you be open to doing another review of last Skywalker
and of the sequel trilogy?
Uh, not really.
I loved the last Skywalker when we reviewed it for the show.
I have grown to, to really not like the movie.
I appreciate your interest last Jedi.
I still, God damn it.
I just don't, I've tried.
I just, it just sucks.
It's got its moments, but it sucks.
Uh, and, and let's go rise a Skywalker.
I just, nah, I really don't care for it, but there you go.
There's my re -review of the two.
Uh, love the show.
Thank you for the 300 plus.
Wonderful EPS.
Thank you, Tom.
Appreciate it.
Uh, next queue.
Kayla full asks, what's your favorite trope and least favorite trope?
We've discussed this somewhat on the pod as well.
I am just going to blurt one out that comes to mind for me, the most
irritating trope that I see in tons of movies is a man or woman saying to
somebody of the opposite sex, like, um, well, you really are something.
Joe DeRosa saying the full name.
It's usually in a romantic context, like, boy, I wish I had met you
sooner, Elizabeth Montgomery, something like that.
It makes me sick.
Nobody talks like this.
Nobody says somebody's full name when they're talking to them.
This is a trope that I really, truly hate.
Um, and then favorite trope.
I don't really know what to tell you.
I do love when a man has retired, think Rambo.
He's like retired to a cave or something and, uh, his boss shows up
and it's like, we need you for one more round.
I always enjoy that trope.
Uh, I hate when somebody says an insulting thing.
And when somebody says an insulting thing and then goes, and then the
other person goes, good to see you too, Don.
I fucking hate that.
And they both go, ha ha ha ha.
Favorite trope is always going to be the judge standing up and he's got no
pants on behind the any gag of no pants on favorite person stands up is great.
Luke asks, what is your Pat?
What is your favorite sandwich or Joey roses?
Well, you've only been there once.
You've only had one.
I've only been once.
I think I might've tried two sandwiches because I had one at
like three in the morning also.
Um, so I don't remember, but both were excellent.
I mean, I, I'm not a picky eater, um, but I, I would put Joe's
sandwiches up amongst any, they were delicious.
Thank you.
Both ones I have.
Gus asks Joe, what's your opinion on the PlayStation one?
Uh, one of the greatest systems of all time.
Absolutely excellent.
I just got a lot of hate comments for when I was on Barstool sports on KFC.
And I said that the N 64 was a bad system and aged poorly and
the PlayStation one conquered it.
Uh, but that is how I feel.
Uh, and any favorite games on there?
There's a lot of great games on that PS, that PS one.
I just got, in fact, starring Dana Gould.
I just got gecks, uh, which I look forward to, to playing for the first time.
Um, I never played it back in the day.
Uh, what did I just finish on there though?
I just finished.
I mean, it's just great.
All the side scrolling stuff, platforming stuff is awesome on it.
Um, but I just finished, Oh, I finished a rebel assault too.
And I had a lot of fun playing that.
I love the PlayStation one life changing, game changing, changing console.
I remember it in college.
It was mind blowing.
Matt Ruiz asks, what podcasts do you listen to without fail?
There are not many for me.
I listened to the best show with Tom Sharpling as I have every week for 20 plus years.
I listened to double threat with Tom Sharpling and Julie Klausner,
which is their latest podcast.
And one of my all time favorites, which no longer exists is eighties all over
hosted by Drew McQueenie and Scott Weinberg, which I have talked up on here
before two guys, much like me and Joe, just big film buffs who are friends.
Walking through every single movie released in the eighties.
Unfortunately, they only made it up to 1984 because talk about a time consuming
project, but, um, that to me is one of the all time great podcasts for sure.
Uh, and Joe, you don't listen to any, do you?
No, I'm just trying to think.
No, I don't listen to any, uh, my friend, Tom Rhodes, great comedian.
He's got a podcast called smart town.
And I texted pot Tom yesterday and said, every time I watch one of your
clips, I learn a little something.
Your energy is great.
It's something I need more of in my life.
I'm going to start listening to your podcast.
So hopefully that will be my ride or die.
Uh, Sean asks, do either of you have a book you think you would make that would
make an incredible movie, but most likely will never be made into one?
Uh, that's a good question.
I always would have said, what's eating Gilbert grape.
When I was a kid, something about that title fascinated me and I found the
book like randomly, almost like how the kid finds the never ending story.
And I remember crying, reading it.
And I was like, this book is amazing.
They'll never make this into a movie.
And then they did like two years later.
Uh, so you never know that that book in particular is like an insane, the fact
that it's a guy with horrible teeth, his mentally handicapped brother, his 400
pound mother, uh, that's an insane one that got made.
That's not what you asked, but I would say don't rule out anything
could be made, you never know.
Uh, I think it's an overwritten and very boring book, but I think that
insomnia by Stephen King could actually make a very fun, cool movie.
The, uh, I think what the book is lacking and it, and, and the movie
could make up for in brevity and also in visuals.
And I think that Tom Hanks would be a perfect, uh, main character to be
cast in that, but I didn't read it.
But speaking of Stephen King, I definitely always thought that
Harold's game was going to be another unfilmable novel.
And they did a bang up job on that too.
So it's really just finding the right person.
I'd love a watchable version of the stand.
That doesn't bore me to fucking tears.
Uh, or, or, uh, or, uh, I love the mini series of it.
I'd love a real true R rated adaptation of it, not this last fucking thing they
did, a real version of it.
You know, it's, it's like Peter Jackson did Lord of the Rings.
They're not for me.
That's just not my bag.
However, I recognize that those people, those fucking nerds got the definitive
most perfect version of their dream thing, Lord of the Rings.
And then if they don't like that one, they have a four hour per movie version
of it, extended versions of it.
Like it's so rare that you get that.
And they've missed, they've missed it with Stephen King more
than pretty much anybody else.
They missed the stand, uh, back in 94 and by the five minutes I saw the
new one, they missed it even harder.
It's they haven't gotten right.
Um, it's a shame.
It's rare that they just give you that slam dunk.
I remember reading dream catcher right before seeing that movie.
So, I mean, Stephen King can go even worse, believe me, but it's hard.
It's a hard thing to get these beloved things as perfect as you want them to be.
Steven Scott asks, are we getting an Oppenheimer episode?
The answer?
Uh, I don't know the answer, but I'm seeing Oppenheimer today.
And if Joe wants to see it, I think we'll definitely do it.
I don't know if I'm going to see it.
I I've tuned out with Nolan since I never even saw Inception.
Uh, you know, he's gotten very long with these movies.
Uh, I hear Oppenheimer's great.
I do like the work of Christopher Nolan.
Um, but I, oh yeah.
Krumholz is in it.
I forgot.
I would like to see David in the movie.
It's not that I don't want to see it.
I'm just not chomping at the bit.
I also got to see this damn insidious so we can review it.
So, uh, well, we might in all three today, I'm seeing Barbie insidious
and Oppenheimer, unless Oppenheimer is a total drag, in which case I won't.
WC asks, will you guys be doing any more watch along movie commentaries
like the original days of the pod?
Yeah.
I mean, at some point possibly it's just a lot of moving parts with the zoom.
And we already have enough internet issues and things, and then also
streaming a movie while we're on here, you know, and it's, it's, it just
makes it a little harder.
So that's possible.
I wouldn't say I wouldn't rule it out.
We just logistically haven't had the best scenario to do it.
Yeah, sure.
Um, Felix inquires Pat, what is your, I am working in show business Hollywood
moment that still haunts you to this day.
And the question for Joe, um, look, I never worked the like assistant route.
That's where I think people get like computer screens thrown at
their head and shit like that.
I've had maniac bosses, uh, for sure.
Many a fucked up moment.
I think when I really realized the egos of people was probably when I
was working at Saturday night live.
And that was the sort of situation where like Paris Hilton hosted one week.
If Paris Hilton was like, I could kind of go for some Mr.
Chow, um, then it would be my job to go into, if it was a blizzard, no matter
what it was going to the city, to this restaurant, sometimes the restaurant
will be closed and come back home.
No matter what it costs with this dish that Paris Hilton wants.
And I would go out, it would be zero degrees.
I would be banging on windows.
I would be gone for like two, three hours.
People texting you, where is Paris's meal?
Whatever.
Then you get back, you give it to her.
She has no recollection of even asking for it.
Doesn't even want it.
There was a billion version of that stories of just stars demanding something
on a whim and expecting it immediately.
Um, it's a bad business full of bad people.
I have learned that lesson a million times.
Joe, your question is if you could go back in time, what advice would you give
to angry 2000 Joe as if that angry Joe is gone?
Is that what you're suggesting?
The best advice I've seen is Tom Hanks saying this too shall pass is that he's
asked a question of what would you go back and tell yourself?
Yeah.
It's the best advice.
It's a viral clip.
It's, but he's right.
He's like, Oh, things are going great.
You think it's you're awesome.
This too shall pass.
You think it's nobody's ever had it worse than this.
Yeah.
You get the point, but I think that's the best advice you could ever give somebody
who's emotional and reactionary the way I am.
Uh, so that's what I do.
Zach asks, might I run into the man himself at Joey roses?
When I stopped by the bar for a sandwich next Saturday, the 29th.
No, I will be out of town.
No, I'll be going to NYC for my 30th.
Well, happy birthday, Zach.
Thank you for coming to the bar.
I will not be there.
Uh, but I hope you enjoy yourself.
Happy birthday, Zach.
30 is a good year.
Philip K asks Joe and or Pat, what are some of your favorite record
stores you've come across in your travels?
Joe, which ones had the best hip hop selections?
That always seems to be the weak point.
That is always the weak point in vinyl stores.
Interestingly enough.
Um, yeah, I mean, we always talk about Amoeba.
My big recommendation is, is my all time favorite vintage vinyl in St.
Louis.
This is the first trip to St.
Louis I've had in my entire life where I did not, uh, make my way over there.
And I regretted it strongly.
I was on the plane last night, like, fuck, I didn't go to vintage vinyl,
but that's a great one.
Nothing ever beat for me the original Amoeba.
Uh, that experience was wondrous every time I stepped into the store and they
did have a magnificent hip hop section.
So, um, I, I, that was unstoppable for me.
Uh, but I would like to shout out forever changes in Phoenixville.
My hometown, uh, this guy, Sean, who's really cool.
It's a little shop, but he's got a great little curated selection
of vinyl in there and it's awesome.
It's just a great shop.
And he does have a really nice hip hop section.
So, uh, if you're in Phoenixville, check out forever changes, Joe, any
advice on starting a small business?
Don't folks, uh, Chris T 1000 says, gents would, would gents, what would you
each consider to be the greatest television series finale of all time?
Um, the finale moment, nothing in my opinion could ever, it's not my favorite
finale, but finale moment, nothing beats Newhart waking up in the bedroom of
the original Bob Newhart show with his original wife and then going, I had
this crazy dream that I owned an inn and he starts talking about that is,
I get chills when I think of that overall, all in the family is the
greatest gut punch, uh, uh, uh, finale.
In my opinion, I'm only on like season three.
I've been watching it for awhile, so I don't know how it ends.
Beautifully for me, for me, look, there will never be, uh, a more memorable
moment than the final moment of the sopranos, everyone I know calling
each other at the same time, hearing screams in my apartment complex,
like it was the super bowl.
Um, however, the last episode of sopranos is definitely not one of my
favorite episodes of the sopranos, not even close, so I can't say that.
I think what I might lean towards, um, and I liked the Seinfeld finale
more than most, but I get people's issues with it.
I think six feet under, uh, had one of the greats and the fact that every
finale rips them off now says a lot.
It did that moving ahead in time thing to show you where these people
were, uh, five years later, that has now become the most
cliched thing in television.
Every show jumps forward.
But, um, that was sort of the first time I had seen that
and they did it just beautifully.
It's like, that's, that's a hard episode of television to watch
without breaking down.
It's basically about life itself.
Uh, very, very good, very good episode of TV.
The shield also ended fantastically.
Well, I must say people have kind of forgotten the shield, but having
just recently rewired or watched, uh, justified and, uh, the Americans,
the shield kicks both of their asses for sure.
Luke asks for both of you.
What is the best live music performance you've ever seen?
Favorite movie soundtrack.
Uh, I've been saying over the last two years, nobody puts on a better,
more energetic show than KRS one.
I've seen him many times now and every single time I'm
equally as excited and enamored.
Uh, so I'm going to go with KRS one.
Favorite movie soundtracks, uh, judgment night.
It's just always played a very special place in my heart.
It's what really helped for me and Pinkstone's friendship.
It's what got me interested in, in rock and metal and grunge by having
the hip hop artists paired with them.
It was a unique thing that hadn't been done before.
This is pre rap rock and all that stuff.
And it's better, a better approach and version of rap rock than any of those
rap rock bands ever did with the exception of rage.
Uh, it's, it's, it's a great soundtrack.
Uh, best live music performance that I have ever seen.
For just for a variety of factors was a, uh, a Coachella I went to.
It was very early on in my, uh, longest relationship.
I was on Molly, the Molly hit as they walked out.
It was going to the Stone Age, but, um, Queens of Stone Age on the second hand
stage and then the main stage was Muse.
So Coachella is a pretty shitty audience and 99 % of this audience went
to go watch Muse, so there was like this tiny group of devoted Queens
of the Stone Age fans, there was a wind storm going, so all these palm
trees were blowing in the wind.
The Queens, the Queens of the Stone Age are a desert band.
So we're in the middle of the desert to watch them and they
came out just ready to rock.
I'll remember it forever.
Uh, the Molly hit basically as they strummed the first note and it's the dream.
I don't know if you've ever been to a concert where like the drugs hit two
hours before your band goes on, but that's the worst it doesn't hit.
When the band does come out, that's the worst.
Sometimes you time it just right.
Uh, and my favorite soundtrack, even though I listened to Jackie Brown more,
the Pulp Fiction soundtrack really kind of changed my, uh, my game.
That was like the coolest thing you could own back in the nineties.
All right.
Next Europe, is this mine?
Sorry.
I, I, I minimized it.
Joe, what's your favorite Patrice story asks bow.
Uh, well for me personally, um, oh, there's a lot of them, geez.
Uh, but, uh, the funniest is probably, and, and like for me personally,
personally, like was when he, we were on Opie and Anthony and I was talking
about Alfred Hitchcock and he kept saying, Alfred Hitchcock stinks.
I was going, shut the fuck up, Joe.
Alfred Hitchcock stinks.
Oh, I'm a fucking director.
Here's what my shot means.
Shut the fuck up.
And I was getting so mad at screaming at him on the air.
You don't know what the fuck you're talking about.
I was losing my mind.
And then they went to commercial and he went to the bathroom and I had to go to
the bathroom and I walked into the bathroom and I was ready to be like, you
know, dude, you're, you're an asshole.
And as soon as I worked in the bathroom, he was peeing at the urinal.
He starts laughing his maniacally, uh, with his like classic Patrice laugh.
And I was like, what?
And he goes, you're too fucking easy, Joe.
Alfred Hitchcock's a goddamn genius.
I started laughing.
I was like, I'm a fucking idiot.
All right.
You got me.
Yeah.
That's a, that was a fun one.
I used to fall for that shit too.
I used to get so upset.
And then finally one day something snapped me where I, that person has
their opinion and you have yours.
And it changed my entire life.
Uh, Michael asks, what exactly gets a sag?
Guys, come on.
Can't just, can we keep it sort of in the ballpark of the show?
What exactly gets a sag president elected?
What makes it how Fran Drescher became the, uh, how Fran Drescher became
the president of the screen Actors Guild.
It's just an election like anything else, but I think it's the kind of
job that nobody wants.
It's usually somebody whose career has.
You know, not ended, but is, is on the decline, let's say, but the previous
president, I think was Gabriel Carteris from 90210, uh, the current president
is Fran Drescher of the nanny.
And basically it's people who have to, they get, they're immediately in over
their heads.
I mean, Fran Drescher probably did not want to be in charge of this thing
during a nationwide strike, but, um, I do think they do their best.
You know, I, I don't, I, I'm in sag.
I don't go to the meetings or anything.
I know more about the WGA, but these people are, are fighting for us.
So I, I root for them.
I have always liked Fran Drescher.
Michael Wits had asked, what do you think of the X files?
Haven't heard you guys talk about it.
Um, the first thing I ever saw the X files was the movie fight the future.
I had never seen the show.
I went and saw the movie with my friends and I thought it was kind of neat.
They didn't like it.
They were fans of the show.
Um, at some point I watched the first season and liked it a lot, but it's
one of those things where you start watching it and then realize you've got
like 400 hours of television ahead of you.
And eventually I lost interest, but, um, yeah, I've seen a few of like the best
the one with the family of the inbred mutants or whatever.
And I was like, wow, this is fucking horrifying to be on Fox.
You know, that's a, I get that it's ahead of its time and a great show.
I just don't know it very well.
I never watched it.
I have admiration for it.
I mean, it's the Breaking Bad crew came out of that.
So, um, you know, uh, and I appreciate that it's got such a big
following and the fans love it.
I have seen that mutant one.
It is really creepy and intense, uh, but I've never watched it.
But, uh, maybe one day I will, um, I should sit down and try to
spend some time with it.
Uh, Hey, Samantha Kiefer asks Joe, which Twilight Zone reboot do
you have the most fondness for?
That's easy.
The eighties, the first season of the 1980s one is great.
Uh, and I re I own it and I revisit it often.
And I revisit the forest Whitaker one too, which is not very good.
The only one I don't revisit is the Jordan peel.
And maybe I will in time, but I just, I don't mean to pick on Jordan.
I just found that iteration to really miss the mark in all ways.
Um, unfortunately, Pat, do you have a favorite Peloton instructor?
I absolutely do.
Emma Lovewell.
I, uh, you know, I am in love with her.
I don't really know how else to say it.
You do have sort of a personal relationship with these people.
Um, but yeah, it's, it's, it's a big part of me actually sticking with
my Peloton plan is that I want to see Emma Lovewell each day.
I think she's great.
Favorite male instructor is probably Dennis Morton, although he talks too
much and generally I want the instructor to be quiet.
Uh, that's your take on all, on all women.
You've said you want them to be quiet.
Just more quiet, not totally quiet.
Um, Matt Robin asks Pat and Joe, would you ever do a live podcast in Michigan,
Detroit?
Absolutely.
We'd love to.
Joe, I saw you in ham tramp a few years ago and accidentally got so hammered
with you after the show that I blacked out and woke up on the sidewalk outside
the bar with a broken phone to this day.
I have no idea if I was thrown out or if I politely excuse myself to gracefully
tumble out of the bar, either way, I think I had fun and would love the
opportunity to hang with you both.
Granted with a tad more discretion this time.
All right.
Well, we'll see you in Detroit.
Hopefully at some point.
I threw you out of the bar and broke your phone for no good reason.
I was blacked out.
No, I don't know what happened.
I don't remember seeing anybody get thrown out.
So sorry that happened to you.
I hope you're you've recovered and, uh, yeah, we hope to see you out there.
Uh, Dirk, no Dirk.
That's the third.
Come on, Dirk, stop.
Well, he's asking if we ever take, we do it all the time.
I won't entertain it.
I won't entertain a third question.
Okay.
I'm talking through it.
All right.
It's not fair.
Charlie, Charlie thoughts on RFK guys, please.
I know I have been, uh, I've been keeping entirely out of the news for my mental
health, which has been great for me.
I don't even know what RFK junior is doing aside from like shirtless pushups.
I don't know what his political stances are.
I don't, I don't have any thoughts.
I will say this, whether you hate his takes or not.
He got in some trouble the other day for saying that COVID was genetically
targeted to affect certain races more than others, uh, and he got some trouble
for that, um, whether you like his takes or not, uh, I don't follow the man, but
I know he's quite controversial.
I am, and this is a controversial statement.
I am happy that Cheryl Hines, his wife is still working and not getting shit for it.
I like that it, it's the kind of thing we need out there.
You need to be able to continue to live your life and work.
Even if you're married to a person who the bulk of people in your industry
might not care for as far as their takes go.
And, uh, whether she's getting some special pass or privilege, I don't
know, but I can tell you a guy that is vehemently against the vaccine and
has conspiracy theories about COVID is not somebody who's going to be popular
in Hollywood, and I'm glad that she can still work and have her relationships.
And I think that that's how, that's how it works when you're adults, uh,
or should work.
So I think that's good.
Uh, as far as his opinions go, no comment.
Charles asks always, what is your podcast partner's worst and best or
most pleasantly surprising opinion on a film?
Um, you know, that'd be hard for me to think of specifics, but for me with
Joe, it always goes one of two ways, you know, or one of three ways, let's say.
I can tell when we're texting about a movie before we discussed it on the
podcast, which one of these three camps it'll fall into, but it's always one
of three number one, we're both pretty much in agreement, which lately tends
to be where we're at, boy, this movie sucked or boy, this movie was great.
Then there's the second camp, which is everything Joe says is the craziest or
stupidest opinion I've heard about a movie and he's dug in so hard on it
that it enrages me and I spent the whole podcast angry.
Then another one that happens just as often is that Joe speaks so eloquently
and correctly and beautifully about a movie that he changes my opinion or
makes me realize something that I loved about it that I didn't notice when I
watched it.
Um, so it's one of those three things.
That's probably how you listeners experience Joe's insanely varied
opinions as well, but, um, okay.
With Joe was midsummer for sure, or maybe, uh, hereditary my, the, the time
that I think that Joe is the craziest is discussing James Cameron, uh, in
particular, just completely writing off aliens and Terminator two and all that.
I can't even wrap my head around that as a, as a fan of genre film on a genre
film podcast, time is certainly a camera.
Time is certainly telling with Cameron, funny, all the things I said about
Cameron, people are saying about his new movies.
Oh, there's not really a story and the characters are paper thin and yeah, no,
that's what I've been saying about him for years.
That's what he does.
Avatar is like one of the biggest movies of all time.
I mean, he, the man still makes the hits.
He's keeping things afloat.
Um, subway, subway chain, you know, dog shit.
Uh, look, let's not, let's not judge it up again.
I'm just saying when I'm asked, what's the craziest thing I can't get behind.
It's probably James Cameron on the movie end or Ari Aster where it's like, wait,
you want different crazy shake them up kind of horror, but you don't like Ari
Aster.
I don't get that either.
And then television wise, it's always going to be his just refusal to get into
Sopranos, which, um, what can I do?
What can I do?
Uh, okay.
Well, I will say with Pat, we're going to talk, I'll talk to the infuriating
side first, and then I'll say a positive.
If you're inside with Pat is he will take one episode of a show, usually with
comedy where it's like a mediocre episode.
You're like, it's nothing special, whatever.
And he'll be like, just a dismal, pathetic effort on their part tonight to try to
carry us through that.
I'm like, it's one like mediocre episode in the season.
Like the season is pretty good though.
And, but then at the same time he'll talk about like, you know, Zach and Kirby
need wedding dates, sorry, Zach Efron or something.
And I'll be like, fuck off.
I'm not watching that.
You'll be like, you know, Joe, there were two laughs in it.
And for me, that's enough these days.
So I don't understand that pendulum swing with Pat.
When it comes to comedy, it can be infuriating.
It could be my mood far too much.
It affects my opinion of, of movies and my mood is all over the place.
So that's often the issue.
I would say that that is a frustrating aspect is that he, I'll be like, he's
just in a good mood, so he doesn't feel like talking about how shitty this was,
or he's just in a bad mood.
So he's being way too hard on this thing.
So that's the infuriating side of it.
I can't speak to specific things at the moment.
Like Pat will always with me have the gripe of midsummer and the sopranos.
I don't know that I have those on the other direction with Pat that I can
remember, but on a positive note, one thing Pat has done, and it surprised
me is like, we'll watch some Joe Bob style thing, and I'll be like, I hate
this, I don't need to see, you know, a scene where a guy drinks a 40 ounce of
this is disgusting or whatever, you know, and Pat will be like, man, this is
like that classic grind house dry.
It's just fun.
I think it's wild.
And I'll be like, ah, you're right.
All right.
You're right.
So it's weird because Pat was the one that wasn't into horror.
I threw the podcast helped to get him more into it.
And now he's the guy that kind of gets me to appreciate some of the more wild stuff.
So, so that's, uh, that's, that's where I would, that's my answer.
Anyway.
Yeah.
All right.
And a recent example for me of Joe talking so, so, uh, passionately about
something and changing my mind on it was the recent Indiana Jones, like when he,
I, of course I got that the movie was about getting older as a hero or whatever.
But, uh, when Joe really laid out his take on it, it definitely helped me sort
of appreciate the movie much more.
That happens often.
Nice.
Um, Lee, here's one.
During the strikes, does Pat and other writers and the actors get paid during a
strike or do you have to apply for workers' comp or unemployment?
Well, I'm in the unions too.
I don't know why you're just saying Pat.
I'm part of it.
Uh, we do not get paid.
Um, we also, because I'm incorporated, I also can't really ask for unemployment.
So you just wind up screwed essentially.
Honestly, this podcast certainly helps.
So thank you.
Vincent asks, uh, what were your family's go -to movies to watch?
Uh, it's a good question.
Never had that one.
You know, look, I've seen just about every star Wars movie in the theater with my
dad or my dad and my mom.
Uh, we saw all the Indiana Jones movies in the theater.
I'm going to try to get this last one in with them as well.
You know, there were the ones that we all kind of saw, but I would say our
go -to funny enough, and I talked about this on Doug loves movies, it was
pirates of the Caribbean.
There was a period where they were putting a Pirates of the Caribbean out
like every summer and we went to all of them.
And that was like a thing, like where we were like, Oh, there's a new Pirates out.
Let's go see it.
And it was just enough for me to give a fuck to like, want to see it.
They were excited about it.
The perfect, like middle ground, sort of brainless, not challenging, but fun
enough, funny enough and entertainment and entertaining enough big popcorn movie
franchise that we were able to, to, to bond over.
Yeah.
With my family, the only one we watched every year was Christmas
vacation without fail.
Usually, uh, gather up some friends and other neighbors and stuff and watch
Christmas occasion and just, you know, that was the one and Christmas story
were the two bigs for sure.
The ones I remember my whole family going to see a movie together.
That was actually very, very rare.
I feel like usually either just, I went with my dad or me and my mom and my
sister went, but I remember going to see the Adams family and home alone as
too, that I was just super excited about whole family events.
Uh, those are movies that felt kind of adult, even though they were for the kids.
So I felt like I was having a night out at the cinema kind of vibe.
That's all.
Um, and then my parents were killed.
Uh, I was actually the inspiration for Batman.
They left the theater and were assassinated in the hallway, the alleyway.
All right.
You're up.
Uh, Jason Kurtz asks, will there be a folks shirt?
Possibly the theme song for a ringtone.
We do have an Etsy page with some merch.
Um, Google will see you in hell Etsy.
Um, also see you in hell pod on Instagram, which posts a lot of like classic
clips of the show and current clips of the show.
But, um, it's a good idea though.
Theme song for a ringtone is a good idea.
Uh, April joy says, yeah, I got a question for you.
How dare you bring so much joy to my life.
Oh, thank you, April.
Glad we could help.
Sawyer asks, uh, I'm sure this has been a discussion.
At some point, have you guys considered collaborating on a motion picture?
Uh, we have not, uh, we, you know, I don't know.
We, we, Pat and I certainly in the past talked about what if we wrote something
or, but we never, it's a lot harder.
Uh, you know, unless you're going to go, like I was talking about earlier, that
completely independent route of, Hey, we're going to go raise money and we're
you know, which is a commitment.
Of course it's, it's a lot harder to collaborate with your friends than
you'd think in the Hollywood system.
So no, not really, not yet.
Yeah.
Almost everyone I know who has been in some sort of partnership or working
with a buddy or whatever it may be.
It just tends to sour, you know, like there's never a situation where both
parties are like, yes, we're both doing 50 % of the work, you know, somebody starts
presenting somebody.
I mean, for me, my reason and the whole, the whole reason this podcast got more
civil is that I just can't, I can't lose Joe as a friend in my life.
So I think that's why we don't work together.
Joe was saying just the other day, never work with a friend.
You never work with a fucking friend.
And I was like, yeah, I think that we, we take that advice because
it's just too risky.
And I wasn't, by the way, just in case anybody's wondering, I was not
saying that about Sal or my, or my business partner at Joey Rose's, I was
saying it about like, sometimes you try to hire people, you know, and you want to
help people out and it often ends up being a very bad idea because it's awkward.
You can't go, Hey, what the fuck?
You know, you can, that's going to get weird.
So anyway, Alex asks from a script standpoint, what do each of you think
is the best written horror movie?
The Exorcist, I think it's almost inarguable, but that's my take.
The Exorcist is, is a template horror movie for sure.
But, but so much of it is what Friedkin brought to the screen.
Um, I don't know.
I, of course I love Poltergeist for its, for its, oh, here's a second, uh,
climax for you at the end, the movie ends.
It's been on enough time and then it has a whole nother action climax.
I just, it still gets me every time that there's more movie to come.
Um, and the Shining, I don't know if that's a triumph of the screenplay either.
That's kind of all, or sometimes is more vibe and mood than the script.
But, um, I love like Rosemary's baby.
There's a bunch I love.
I think seven is a near perfect horror thriller script.
Mm hmm.
All right.
Ajim, I hope, uh, asks, what are your thoughts on the
Ninja movie craze of the eighties?
It's crazy.
You should ask because I went to at the new Beverly Tarantino's theater, an
eighties extreme action marathon the other night that I'm going to talk
about on the solo corner, but one of the movies was American Ninja two.
Um, I had never seen any of these Ninja movies of the eighties.
American Ninja two is considered like one of the best worst and it was a blast.
The action was a blast.
It was very, very funny, but I wasn't watching Ninja movies as they
were being released in the eighties.
That was just not something on my radar.
I don't know if it was for Joe or not.
I was never big into them as a kid.
Uh, I don't really have much of an interest in them now.
I do think it's interesting that that was such a big genre.
Uh, or there was a boom of it.
Uh, but as far as eighties and that sort of actiony, whatever goes, I'm, I'm
tempted to start purchasing the Burt Reynolds, you had, Pat had mentioned
doing heat by Burt Reynolds on the show.
At some point we saw Sharkey's machine in the theater and we loved it.
I kind of want to get into that era of Reynolds, like Malone, uh, heat
rent a cop with Liza Minnelli.
Yeah.
I I'm just very fascinated by it for some reason.
So, uh, that's sort of an answer, uh, Franco, what two actresses would you
like to have seen play Maris and Vera?
Uh, if either of them were, oh, had ever actually appeared on Frazier and Cheers.
You don't know who would be a perfect Maris is Aubrey Plaza.
In my mind, in my mind, my vision of who Maris is.
Um, and also then you would know that Frazier had like a total type, like
BB Newworth, Aubrey Plaza is this generation's BB Newworth, like, you'd
know they'd style her exactly like her.
And I would buy that Frazier would just always marry the same woman.
That makes sense.
Well, Niles is Maris, not Frazier.
Your is Niles is right.
You're right.
Then you know what I'm trying to say.
The boys got a type, the brothers have a time.
Uh, I agree with that.
I like that casting, uh, Vera on Cheers.
It's Roseanne.
Vera was Norm's wife, correct?
Yeah.
It's a thousand percent Roseanne.
Like, yeah, that'd be funny.
It's that's, it should be Roseanne.
They didn't do a gag sometimes where they brought her and his wife and it was
like Cindy Crawford, that would have been a very funny gag, wouldn't it?
Yeah.
No, you never, you never see her.
You never see her, but yeah, it's, uh, uh, okay.
Uh, Kyla says, please do the Barbie movie.
We, we might, uh, there's a good possibility.
I need to see it today.
So I'll either do it on the solo corner or we'll do it together.
I ran my mouth harshly about it on, uh, one of the earlier episodes from this
month without having seen it.
And then it turns out my understanding of what I was reading about it
might be very incorrect.
So I want to try to be fair.
So I do hope to see it.
What movies did we do this month earlier?
I don't even remember.
The hell did we do?
Mission Impossible 2, Mario Brothers.
Oh, that's right.
Mario.
Yeah.
And I can see how you could forget doing Mario Brothers.
Uh, Chris Swaljay asks, what sort of hours did you both work when you were on
staff or running writers rooms and is there a correlation with the number of
hours worked in the quality of a show?
Uh, good questions.
There is no correlation with the number of hours and the quality of a show.
None.
Um, never work with somebody who hates their spouse because they're just going
to want to spend their entire night at work and like get home when their husband
or wife is asleep.
I've definitely been on shows where you're there until 2 AM every night.
I don't think maybe when, you know, maybe when I was in my twenties, that
might've worked for me, but I know that I shut down creatively around 10 PM.
Um, so a lot of times it's just some weird power trip.
The boss is on.
I've been on shows where we work till 2 AM.
I've been on shows where we work nine to five every day.
You know, the quality really boils down to the people in the room and whether or
not you have a good premise and whether or not you have, you know, a million of
the things that have to be in the right place for a show to be a success.
Um, so yeah, I wouldn't say the amount of hours worked works correlates with quality.
I will say you can't make something great in like a couple hours.
You have to really put some time in, but I think there comes a point where
you're just jerking off basically.
Yeah, that about sums it up.
I think, uh, Tyler asks, Joe, have you ever thought about doing a YouTube channel?
Yes, I have.
I think about it all the time and I probably will eventually.
It's just, I've been dragging ass a little bit on that.
Uh, but thank you for asking.
Ethan asks, is there an unmade sequel?
I'm sorry.
That actually said, have you, you and Joe ever thought about
so actually I was supposed to be included there, but that's fine.
So the answer is no.
We know we haven't.
Ethan wants to know, is there an unmade sequel or prequel that you really.
Hey, we didn't get.
Well, we talked about that earlier.
Pat talked about the Godfather stuff.
When they were rattling around DiCaprio, um, in a Godfather four,
that was very exciting to me.
Uh, Neil Blomkamp's alien five.
Look, I'm always going to go see a new alien movie.
I love the alien franchise.
Blomkamp.
I think the fact that he's still up there, like in the top of filmmakers
after the amount of massive flops this man has had, this man made
Chappie for crying out loud.
Now I love district nine as much as the next guy.
I did not see Elysium, but Chappie, that's the kind of movie that usually
they just send you back home after that one.
Yeah.
I, he doesn't do it for me.
District nine was fine.
You know, it was, it was fine.
Yeah.
Elysium was really in Chappie.
I couldn't even, I was like, I can't even with this.
Uh, I would say, yeah, the star wars, I wish we would have got the star
wars sequels that we should have gotten and not what we did get.
Uh, Raffy asks, have you
John Hughes, sorry, John Hughes was discussing doing, um, Ferris Bueller
taking a day off work for the entire nineties that popped up again and again
and again, and then John Hughes died.
And obviously now it's not going to happen.
Instead wrote that's one that I always home alone three, he wrote.
Yeah.
And baby's day out, uh, dumb, dumb, squandered his final years.
Raffy asks, have you guys ever considered having a book corner
segment on the pod?
Absolutely not.
Yeah, we don't, I mean, occasionally a book will pop into a scary stuff,
more on Joe's end.
I tend to read mostly biographies of people in the entertainment business.
You know, I don't have a lot of, uh, stuff that would make sense
to talk about on this podcast.
That is the purpose.
That is the very purpose of scary stuff is to do the things that are
ancillary to movies, but still relevant to the genre.
Um, right.
So, yeah, so that the, the scary stuff is really the book corner or, or
would that be one part of it?
Uh, Jason asks, when are you guys going to work on a God damn?
I, we don't know.
Well, we also did work on a project together called living biblically.
Joe was in that pilot.
It might be very hard to find at this point, but we did work together
and we do a podcast together.
Pat watched as they threw my carcass to the side of the road.
And it didn't save the show.
What do you know?
Um, Vicki Rogers says, Pat, you've said many times that Zodiac is
one of your favorite movies.
Unquestionably, I fell into a Zodiac level obsession with the
movie Zodiac for about a year.
Have you seen the myth of the Zodiac killer mini -series on Peacock
that theorizes he never even existed?
And if so, what are your thoughts on that?
I haven't, I tend to not go into the more crackpot, um, theory
documentaries, cause I don't want to waste.
It's like that room 237, the Stanley Kubrick one, where they have all
these crazy theories about the shining.
It's like, that to me is kind of a waste of time at some point.
I could also go talk to any maniac in a, in a subway station and
hear some other crackpot theory.
I don't know why I'm devoting time to yours, but, um, if you're saying
it's good, maybe I'll check it out.
Vicki, maybe I'll check it out.
Ah, I think the Zodiac killer existed.
Of course.
Tom asks thoughts on Joe Dante's 93 film.
Many, I never saw it.
Uh, I don't know why I've never seen it.
It looks like a fun biopic.
Uh, it's Joe Dante, uh, who I'm a fan of and it's Goodman who I'm a fan of,
but I've never seen it, but, uh, I'm open to.
Mantenae is great.
I own it.
I love it.
And Joe, you would also love it.
It's, uh, it's very good.
It's right in Dante's wheelhouse.
Cause it's in the fifties, but it's kind of a satire, kind of funny,
kind of horror, et cetera, et cetera.
Tyler Salas asks favorite lesser known actors, directors, and writers.
Two lesser known actors I'm fond of are Christopher Abbott.
I love Christopher Abbott and Logan Marshall Green.
He's great too.
I really liked, uh, his very short lived show on the Cinemax network called
quarry, but I think he, his, his fatal flaws that he looks too much like Tom
Hardy, so he's not getting work for that reason is my guess, uh, until they
brothers, but, um, favorite lesser known actors, directors, writers, Joe,
who do you got?
I think Craig Zoller will always take the top of the list for lesser
known million percent and a guy that I feel like unfairly, or maybe he's
by choice, not working, but I feel like he's unfairly not getting to work.
You know, during the me too stuff, that producer that worked for his
company got into a lot of trouble.
They got rid of the guy, but amidst that, all of this press started coming out
that his company was built to make right wing leaning cinema, which is not the
case.
And even if it was who gives a fuck, they're good movies.
And I feel like his politics that keep them out of the big time because he
does, his movies do have a bit of a political bent, even though it's just
right of Hollywood.
I wouldn't consider it right wing cinema by any means.
And then you look at a movie like dragged across concrete that takes a more
sympathetic and diverse approach to cinema, to all sides of an issue than
I've seen.
And, uh, you know, but, uh, he, he's top of the list as far as actors.
Um, that's a great pick.
Yes.
Great.
I, you know, uh, he's not lesser known at this point, but after seeing him in
Blackberry, I'm like, why is Glenn Howerton not starring in everything?
And, and also another great thing.
I went with Brian Quinn the other night to watch the middle -aged dad jam band
with David Wayne and Ken Marino.
And Brian goes, I was like, I'm, we're fans of both of them, but we were
talking about Ken Marino and Brian's like, how the fuck is this guy not
starring in like the supporting role of every Marvel movie?
And you know what I mean?
It's like, it's astounding to me that Ken Marino does not like, he's amazing.
He still has a career.
I mean, he's got a great career, but yeah, he was supporting on the other two,
which is a very funny show and he was very funny on it.
And, and I, as I talked about last time, please watch that new season of
party down because he's very, very funny on that.
And he still works, but yeah, there's something about him that in the, in the
lead role, he never quite clicks with people, but I always love him.
He's great in wander lust.
He's great in so many movies.
You put him, you know, he should be, he should be, he should be
like a Martin Freeman.
Yeah.
You know, like, you know, so anyway, uh, Miss Manny.
Oh, hey, Miss Manny's.
Uh, I had a dream that I was, could I answer that one?
Joe, could I perhaps answer that one?
Aye, aye, aye.
Uh, for lesser known, uh, writer directors.
I want to shout out, you answered it.
I thought already.
No, I was reading their answers.
Christopher Abbott and Logan Marshall.
Oh, oh, I thought you answered it already.
Now I see the confusion.
It's okay.
Uh, for writer director, I want to shout out Carlo Mirabella Davis, um, who
directed this movie called swallow wrote and directed it.
I know I talked about it on the pod, but the other day I was just
like, what happened to that director?
Cause I rewatched swallow, which I think is a pretty brilliant movie, like
one of the better Polanski type thrillers of recent years.
I love it.
And I was like, what else have they been doing?
And the answer is really nothing.
Directed some episodes of servant, the M night Sean Milan show for Apple.
But, um, that's a director that I hope they give another shot because I
swallow on a very small budget is a really fascinating and creepy movie
that I want to recommend again.
And then I would just back up Joe's picks.
I mean, it's hard to argue.
Uh, Howard to me had some great picks there for sure.
Uh, Miss mayonnaise.
I had a dream when I was roommates with Joe and like six other
people who were shit bags.
Uh, at some point, two of them stole $5 ,000 from me.
I kept asking Joe for help, but he kept freaking out and Pat kept looking at
me, shaking his head as if to say, I knew this would happen.
What do you think it means?
Well, I'll tell you this.
When I lived in Williamsburg pre girls, this was when Williamsburg was a
horrifying place to live.
Um, but somebody took my front door off its hinges, stole everything that I
owned and nothing of my roommates.
And eventually the trust issues that grew between us drove us apart and I
had to move out and that reminds me of your story.
Otherwise I have no idea what you're talking about.
I'll give that.
Okay.
I'd say that's where it comes from.
You told that story on the pod before, and I think that's what fueled the dream.
Oh, okay.
Maybe it was Damien Joe, who is your favorite Southern hip hop
artists or group ghetto boys hands down.
You didn't ask me, but I'll cast and I don't care if that's a cliche
to answer, I, I still listen to outcast all the time.
I love them.
Jacob Parrish asks, would you guys rather fall deeply in love with the person
you're supposed to be with or finally track down that porno you lost track of?
Come on, Jake.
Um, I know what you mean.
I definitely have some like one that got away type porno clips that I'll remember
forever and I'll never be able to find again, cause you think they'll just always
be there and then some, someday they're gone, perhaps the copyright changes or
somebody gets sued, something like that.
But, um, no, I, I hope to either fall in love with the person I was supposed to
be with or never fall in love again.
Never fall in love again.
Uh, um, I'll take porn over love any day of the week.
Marcus asked definitely the worst time to ask this, but do you have any
advice thoughts for a non -entertainment writer?
I write for a marketing agency to break into the industry.
Marcus, I, I, your guess is as good as mine.
You know, I just got interviewed by Vulture about the 10 year
anniversary of the Pete Holmes show.
And the last question they asked was, what is the legacy of the show?
And I said, well, for the public, I have no idea.
I can't speak to that for me.
The legacy of the show is it was one of the last moments in time.
Where people who had no experience in making a TV show were allowed to make a
TV show because they believed in an idea.
They believed in the guy at the center of that idea and they let him put a
thing together and, and, and explore it.
And that will never happen again because they will force you to hire influencers.
They will force you to put the latest musician who's popping on
TikTok into your starring role.
Uh, you know, some person's kid, it gets to be the script writer because
they're the, I don't fucking know anymore how, how to crack into any of
this or what sense any of it even makes.
So I don't mean to sound nihilistic, but I don't know what you would do.
I'm somebody with writing experience who is saying, I will go to
people who run and own a chain of, uh, uh, shoe stores to ask them if they
want to invest in, in an independent film as first time investor producers
before I will try to sell something in Hollywood again.
So I don't know.
I really don't know.
Yeah.
I often, when people would ask would not that I loved being a mentor or something,
but I would always enjoy sitting down for an hour with somebody and kind of
telling them how to break in or not, you know, cause I had no contacts.
I knew not a single person in the industry, um, and was coming from
Missouri, did not go to an Ivy league, et cetera.
So I know, I kind of know what you have to do and what you have to like be able
to sacrifice and so forth, but, um, the issue is now everything has changed.
And I broke in 15 years ago, so everything is vastly different.
And when people ask me what they should do to break in my advice, even for people
I know and love, and I know they're talented would be to go do something else
because it's, it's not the same world and it's nearly impossible at this point.
Um, I have friends with tons of credits, tons of experience, undeniably talented
who are packing up and moving back home.
So there's no inspirational tale at this point in the industry.
I would say, consider something else, at least until this industry writes
itself, which maybe these strikes will help, but it's probably going to be
something that happens a few years down the line is my guess.
Um, they won't, it's not going to get any better.
It's just going to get worse.
Yeah, that's true.
Uh, you got, I was, I was like, Oh God, I hope I'm not too negative.
And then Joe sinks the ship even further.
You got, I mean, you got the executive saying, we're going to make
them lose their houses and then you got Ron Perlman putting up basically
a public threat to the guy and we're, none of us are even worried about Ron
Perlman potentially going to a man's house.
I know it's where it's, this is it.
We're at the breaking point here.
This is madness.
It is ending.
I mean, in this day and age for a man, especially a man of his size to like
get on there and be like, I'm going to come to your fucking house and kill you.
Like it's madness.
Um, and I think that's about where we're at.
It's nuts.
Yeah.
The, the, uh, did you see the video, the picture of the industry, the studio
that cut all the branches off the trees?
So the protesters couldn't have shade.
I mean, I wrote all about it.
Yeah.
Uh, and then they were like, they go, Hey, sorry, we do this every year.
And then the writer's guild looked into it and they're like, no, you don't.
You don't, you don't cut these trees every year.
And they w they had all the proof.
It's terrible.
John, he asked who recorded the intro song.
I feel like it oddly sounds like Joe's voice.
I was Joe.
Uh, he does not get enough credit for it.
I am very excited about this new salsa windfall album.
I know very little of Joe's music, uh, except that I love our very
catchy intro, which is performed and written and sung by Joe.
Thank you, Pat.
Thank you, buddy.
Uh, you're welcome.
Are there any red pit boy 88?
Are there any plans for a commentary episode?
You know, maybe I look, let's say as a, maybe a Christmas gift this year.
We'll do one.
That's a good, that's coming up even quicker than I fucking thought.
Jesus Christ.
It's a bit of a hassle for us, but we'll try to get on at least
getting one more in the bag.
Um,
yeah, we were thinking about it.
That's also a second question slipped in by the old rad pip.
I don't think I didn't catch that.
Uh, currently in Nicholas says he's currently in rehab over an Orange County.
Sorry to hear that, sir.
14 days sober, congratulations.
Congrats.
That's good on the sobriety.
Any suggestions for sober fun out in this part of the country?
Well, Nick gun to my head.
Couldn't recommend one thing.
No, don't listen to him.
Nick.
No, I'm not being disheartening.
I'm saying I got, I'm the wrong guy to ask.
That's all.
If you're in Orange County, 14 days sober, you're past the hardest part.
Kudos to you.
Congratulations.
My guess is you're there for 28 days from what I know from the Sandy
Bullock movie, 28 days, um, which is not 28 days later or 28 weeks later.
Um, I'd say you're in a perfect place to do it.
You know, like on intervention, they always wind up going to Orange County
because they know that it's a beautiful, peaceful, serene place for you to get
healthy and get better and heal yourself and get sober.
So like Orange County, this is, they got mini golf.
I was just complaining the other day about how there's
somehow no mini golf in LA.
Um, bowling, you know, sit by the beach, chill.
Don't sit by the bar.
Part of the beach.
Sit by the beach.
Part of the beach, um, rent a convertible drive around.
You know, it's Orange County.
It's beautiful.
Just, uh, try not to go to the bar scene is my advice, but good luck to you.
Yeah.
I think, uh, look, the little I know about sober behaviors, uh, it seems
that nature is a great, uh, environment.
No pun intended to try to, uh, explore new activities and things.
I find that when I go through periods of not imbibing, uh, creativity flourishes.
It's great to spend time being creative in any way you may be able to.
You don't have to be great at a thing.
You can just explore a thing.
You've always wanted to explore.
There's a lot of world out there.
There's a lot of, uh, uh, life out there to explore.
And I would say, you know, when I moved to LA, Bill Burr said to me, the
biggest mistake you'll make in LA is trying to make it be New York.
It's not New York.
Enjoy it as LA.
And I think that's the same thing with sobriety.
The biggest mistake you can make with sobriety is trying to
make it what drinking was.
And you can't, it's, it's new activities.
It's new things.
It's new excursions.
And not just redoing the things you did when you were drunk sober and then
going, why isn't this fun?
You know what I mean?
Yeah, my, my dad just this weekend was saying that when he got sober, he had
to, um, sort of figure out an entirely new way to live.
He was just like, I suddenly had an extra 60 hours a week.
And, and, uh, nothing to do.
So that's, it's, that's something I would work, whether it's ceramics or, you
know, what, you know, I don't know what, what you want to do, get a naked lover
and put a ghost style pottery wheel in your living room and feel each other up.
Um, they say that not to fall in love while you're getting sober.
I kind of disagree.
What better distraction than bone in somebody don't start hooking up with a
drug addict, but, and don't replace your addiction with love.
That's a mistake.
A lot of young people make as well.
We'll be back with Dr.
Drew in a moment.
And also say, don't start dating your ex dealer.
Probably a bad idea.
And don't start dating your ex in general.
Always a mistake.
Final question.
Final question asks, what are, what are your thoughts on Bill Lawrence and scrubs?
Um, I would just like to interject by, by quickly saying I've known Bill
Lawrence for many, many years.
His development executive is who gave me my break into this business.
And Bill is one of the nicest, uh, insanely wealthy people in history.
But, um, so I'm not going to say anything bad about Bill Lawrence.
So I think he's a great guy, but he, he did, uh, he created, I think spin
scrubs, Ted Lasso, um, shrinking, you know, many, many huge, huge shows
over these Cougar town.
Um, what is shrinking the Jason Siegel show?
Yeah.
The Harrison Ford, Jason Siegel show.
So, um, yeah, I know Bill pretty well.
It's odd that you would even, uh, bring that up, but I don't think
Joe watches any of those shows.
I remember loving scrubs.
I don't know how it holds up or how it dates, but I loved it at the time.
I'm a big Zach Braff fan.
Uh, uh, you know, scrubs.
I've never really watched it, but what I've seen is funny.
Uh, and there you go.
There's your Q and a folks, uh, these will actually come out.
They were going to be the back half episodes of August.
I actually think we should make them the front half episodes.
So you'll, you'll, so that way all the patrons can hear them,
but you'll hear these two.
Well, I'm probably going to put up all four at once, but the point is, is these
will be the first two episodes of August.
And then the second two will be our reviews of mission impossible, dead
reckoning and the super Mario brothers movie.
We will be back in September with, uh, Wow, Christ, who knows a bunch of stuff.
Well, probably some combination of insidious Barbie, maybe Oppenheimer, or
there's a lot of movies out there that might be done.
Uh, I got to squeeze some plugs in because I got a lot of tickets to sell here,
but, uh, number one, first and foremost, uh, the salsa windfall album is out
this Friday, August 4th, it's called artificial birth on all digital streamers.
If you want it sooner than that, you can purchase it on bandcamp for eight 99.
What a deal.
Uh, I hope you purchase.
If you don't, I hope you listen streaming wise.
Uh, we also, uh, or we, I also am going on a major tour starting in September.
I'm hitting a lot of cities, Avenal, New Jersey, Toronto, Philadelphia,
Pennsylvania, Denver, Salt Lake city, just to name a few, uh, tons of dates,
more being added all the time.
Please go to joderosa .com for all ticket information, all venue information
and all ticket purchasing links.
I hope to see you out there sincerely.
We appreciate all of you.
Thank you for being a part of this show.
And that's all I got to say other than come on through to Joey roses.
If you're ever in New York, Joey roses, NYC, thank you all.
We love you fans.
And thank you Emily for curating all of these questions for us.
Thanks to all.
We love you.
The Patrick Walsh on Instagram, a guest on the good Christian fun podcast
discussing the film contact, um, very funny and that's it.
We'll be back soon.
Have a great summer.
Be safe, get out there and enjoy some sun and some fun and some buns.