I'll see you in hell I'll see you in hell
And when the sound of your screams becomes a thing of my dreams
You know I'll say
I'll see you in hell You know I will
Folks, it's We'll See You in Hell, the penultimate episode.
So, Pat, did you ever think you'd see the day
where we were in the ultimate stage?
No, I thought one or both of us would die
before the podcast would end.
So that's a happy ending that we're both still alive.
Thriving's pushing it, but alive.
That last episode's not done yet.
Anything could happen tonight.
That's true.
How are you, man?
I am alright.
LA's getting that vibe where it's like,
was there a zombie apocalypse?
This happens here kind of often.
Like, I go out, I walk for two hours,
I walk around the reservoir, I walk to the post office,
you know, getting some steps, listening to some music,
and you don't see anyone.
I walked around the Silver Lake Reservoir this morning at 9 a .m.
and I saw no one.
I don't, what is that?
I mean, it's hot, but it's always hot.
Well, I would think half the city burning to the ground
has something to do with that.
You're probably right.
I mean, restaurants have taken a hit.
Christ, I think people just don't have money.
Which makes sense as well, but it's like,
every restaurant I go to it's me and two people at like 7 p .m.
Well, the funny thing is, too, you know,
the main industry of L .A., obviously,
is the entertainment industry.
Yeah.
When there's a gaggle of open rapists from one industry.
Like, think about if you lived in Pittsburgh,
and it was a steel town.
Yeah.
And one day you're talking to your wife and you're like,
the seventh rapist has been busted in the steel factory.
You'd be like, you think it's time to move?
Something's going on around here.
You know, I went with my lady friend and we saw something,
some movie.
Oh, Weapons, which I loved.
And I guess we're sadly not going to cover on the show,
but I'll tell you, you know, if you want my opinion,
I fucking loved it.
I think it's great.
And I'm really pumped about Zach Greger, who I kind of know.
It's like, he's really coming up.
But yeah, we saw a trailer for the new Tron.
Tron Arez.
And the hero of the new Tron is Jared Leto.
Yep.
And like, we went from this,
I hate even saying the word now because of how overused it got,
but we went from this cancel culture thing of like,
you tell a woman she has a shapely bottom,
and you're thrown out of this industry into like an Icelandish prison.
And now you can be very credibly accused for a decade.
Then somebody can write a massive expose about all the underage women
you've assaulted and you're starring in the biggest movie of the summer.
And you're featured in the trailer.
It's, it's crazy.
It is crazy.
I bet you, I mean, I wouldn't,
I bet you wouldn't be surprised about this,
but I bet you there would be,
I bet you there's like a strategy with a publicist.
Like when you're at a Jared Leto level,
you're dealing with a publicist that has strategies and techniques and tactics
that the common man such as you or me will never be even kind of familiar with.
They've got tricks up their sleeve.
I bet you one of the tactics is Jared,
why don't you play really crazy villains for a little while?
Yeah.
You know, you're not, there's a little backlash.
And if you go out there, try to play a good guy, it's going to really get worse.
So let's put you in some supporting things as a villain.
It's going to let you work.
People will just subconsciously accept that.
And then, you know, we can make the full turn back to, you know,
that's not a crazy thing in this fucking sick business, you know?
Yeah.
I actually heard Jared Leto just took on as his publicist fictional character,
Ray Donovan, which I thought was just crazy.
I've never seen somebody bring on a fictional character as a publicist.
Is Ray Donovan a publicist?
He was like a fixer.
I only saw the first episode.
It was Liev Schreiber as a guy who like,
I think the pilot was like a famous actor killed a woman in his hot tub or something.
And then Ray Donovan goes over and cleans it up.
Anyway.
I just yet another show I don't give a shit about.
I got yelled at last night again by people because I said I didn't like the Sopranos.
I mean, I agree with those people.
I know.
I think that should continue.
It's like when they would say like, we should never let these people rest or never.
We should be attacking them in restaurants.
That is how I feel about people who refuse to watch the Sopranos.
I was out with Tony last night and this might be the only thing you agree with Tony on.
But I was out with Tony last night at a bar and he was like,
the Sopranos is the greatest show ever.
And I was like, no, it's not.
And he was like, what are you fucking stupid?
What are you talking about?
Just bitching.
And I was like, I don't know.
I don't like it.
And he said a lot of the things you say.
He was like, I was like, it's too cartoonish.
He's like, that's the fucking point.
So then when it gets serious, it's fucking incredible.
Don't you get it?
I was like, no, I don't get it.
He is right.
I mean, it's darker and darker and darker and darker and more into depression.
And I think you would love it, but I'm not going to push anymore.
I can't push anymore.
Folks, we can all find some common ground somewhere.
We're introducing our follow -up podcast, which will be a Sopranos,
a rewatch for me and a first time for Joe.
And every episode will end in a veins bulging out of the head screaming match.
It'll be brutal.
I didn't bring that up to plug, but I might as well plug.
I am on the new Kill Tony Netflix episode.
It came out today.
We're recording on March 25th here.
So that's the day, Kim.
I'm sorry, August 25th, excuse me.
And that's the day it came out.
So by the time you hear this, it's definitely out.
But I'm on the new Kill Tony episode that they shot at Madison Square Garden.
And go check it out on Netflix.
It was a wild, fun time.
Hope you like it.
The tell is on it.
Jim Norton, Jeff Ross, Mark Norman, Matt Reif.
What is it?
The criticizing of the comedians?
It's just his podcast.
But they did it at Madison Square Garden.
And it was sold out.
It was wild.
Meaning like people sitting and talking into microphones?
Podcasts?
If you've seen his podcast, it's just his podcast.
You've seen it.
You came to it at the Comedy Store with me once.
Oh, it's where the comedian gets up and everybody shits on him.
Well, no.
That's what people like to reduce it to.
That's every clip I've seen.
As a comedian does something and then they're like,
what the fuck's wrong with you?
No, it's a roasty show.
Everybody gets made fun of.
But plenty of comedians do great.
And are praised.
And go on to nice things.
I always say, too, with the roast element of it,
everybody knows what it is.
Nobody's going in going,
I can't believe that you made fun of it.
It's a roast show, variety show,
gong showy, kind of whatever.
But when he does the big ones,
it doesn't matter.
I'm on the goddamn thing.
His friends got up and did,
a few of his friends got up and did like
three or four minute sets.
I was one of them.
Harlan Williams was one of them.
It was fun.
It was very fun.
And seeing a podcast at Madison Square Garden
is insane.
It felt like wrestling.
It was wild.
Kind of similar to when
you and I played that lesbian
bookstore in the Lower East Side.
That's what I was going to say.
Pat and I will be playing the hot dog stand
at MSG.
Not the stand, the cart.
We auditioned for the stand
and they didn't pass us.
Couldn't fill the stand, boys.
Got to move it to the cart.
And I haven't told you this yet, Joe.
I'll just tell you on the air.
But they did agree to pay
in cash and not condiments
as they originally wanted to pay us
in ketchup, mustard and relish.
I was willing to do a half and half.
You can take half and half.
I'm doing half bitcoin, half relish.
Yeah.
It's a
wild time.
I find myself
always asking myself lately
are you getting old
or cranky?
Are you just like Matt?
For me today, have you
ever gotten locked into one of these things
where you're
trying to just log into
your Gmail and it says
log into your phone's Gmail
so that we know that
you're, I must have some sort of
factor, authentic.
And my phone's downstairs.
We're trying to get on this podcast with you today.
I went up and down stairs seven times.
I just, I always am thinking
about old people and
how they must just want to kill
themselves every second of every day
because you have to live in this world.
It's not like our parents where
it's like we went from
regular TV to digital TV.
You don't have to do anything to make that
change, you know. Old people
today are at the mercy of
these fucking apps and
two factor authentication and
their brains cannot understand
that shit. I just don't.
And it's only going to get worse.
I saw, it's the most despicable commercial
I've ever seen, which is
saying a lot.
But I saw a commercial
it was playing on
I don't know, you know, like when you watch
like Roku free TV
or whatever.
The free TV channels, they're called
fast channels that they have now on all
smart TVs.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah. Like when you watch
a TV and they'll have like the all in the family
channel or whatever.
How do those things make any fucking
money? Like whenever I'm in an Airbnb
in Atlanta for two months, I'll see that.
And it's like, how is a channel
just showing a 24 hour
loop of Sanford and Son making money?
It changes because it'll change.
It'll change like it won't always
be Sanford and Son. It'll be Sanford and Son for
like 12 hours and then it'll go to like I
dream of Jeannie or something like that.
My question remains.
Well, here's how.
It's
they do it with podcasts now too.
So like it's
podcast based
style, stylized advertising, meaning
there's like three
sponsors that just
keep playing on repeat, which is
the way a lot of podcasts work. Every week
it's kind of the same sponsors or wherever.
So it's the same
concept. So you'll see the same
commercial literally every commercial
break. And some guys, you know, they
go big and you'll keep seeing
it over and over and over. So the one
that I kept seeing
the last time I watched one of these things,
which was like a week ago, was
and by the way, it's
completely made with AI, which makes it even
more insulting. The voiceover is that
generic AI voiceover that you
hear on Instagram all the time, where
it's like the top five, tap, tap, tap, tap, tap, tap,
tap, tap, tap. And
it starts with here are the common mistakes
old people make with their iPhone.
And it's about storage.
But it starts with that. It starts
literally with ageism
saying
these are the mistakes old
people make.
You see them at the Apple Store,
you know, trying to learn. And these people are like,
well, you have to turn it on.
It's like they don't know.
Well, that would that would annoy
me a little. Well, I'm exaggerating. But you know what I
mean. They have a very condescending attitude.
Yeah. Well, I think how about
this? I lost my phone
in New York.
Yeah.
Stone sober
three o 'clock in the morning. Just lost it.
Of course not, folks.
I was hammered.
I was going to say something,
but I did.
I don't know. I left it in the fucking Uber.
Yeah. And I'm such a slob.
What I did manage to
carry out of the Uber were the four food items
I had brought home. Sure, sure.
And I get out of the
Uber, I immediately realize I don't have the phone.
I'm like, God damn it.
So I got to go the next, you know,
of course you messaged the Uber driver 45 times.
He just doesn't respond. At that point
to me, that's not lost. That's theft.
Yeah. He stole it.
My guy did that. He tried to
get me to pay him to meet him and return it.
Disgusting. Yeah. So
the next
day I go to the Verizon
store to get a new phone
and they turn
the phone on. And
it's like you got to let
notification was sent to an
Apple device. You're going to have to let yourself in.
I'm like, guys, I'm not here
with my MacBook. Yeah.
I got to turn the goddamn phone on.
They're like, yeah, you're going to have to
you have to wait till you get
home so you can let yourself
into the phone. This is ridiculous.
Yeah.
It's a brand new phone. I'm standing in
the store with my government issued ID
and the
credit card that has the same information
on it that I was approved for.
Trying to
activate a new phone.
A phone that you're paying
entry price $800
on.
I luckily got it.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to cut you off. No, no, no.
I luckily got it for free.
How do you get a free phone? Verizon's
got this promotion now where
if you open a line, they'll give you the device
for free. Now, the catch is
you have to stay with the line for
three years. Yeah.
If you get rid of the line, then
they charge you like what you would
theoretically own into the device ownership.
But if you stay with it
for three years, you never pay for the device and then
it's yours at the end of the three years.
My guy told me at Apple
when I got the phone, he's like
make sure you do this tonight.
Go in and cancel it.
They give you, they charge you a phone
upgrade fee of $35
that they think you won't
notice. So it's like
you pay $800 minimum to upgrade
the phone and then there's a charge.
And I'm upgrading from your company
to your company.
So I'm being penalized for my loyalty.
You fucks.
There should be some sort of
oh thanks, you've been with our company
for 25 years. Here's something
for you. Not a penalty.
Yeah.
Well that used to burn me up
when it would be like
T -Mobile, new customers
get a blow job.
You're like, well I've been with you for six
years, where's mine?
Sorry, just for new people.
And there's nothing
better than those Verizon blowjobs too.
The softest lips.
They really hired some
great, great suckers.
Let's get to that movie corn.
I
would like
to start with
close encounters of the third kind.
Oh boy. I went
and saw it in 70 millimeter.
I think there's a few more showtimes
here in LA.
And look, these screenings
are, it's as cool, it's like the
4K experience of like, I have
never seen a movie look this awesome.
You can do that on the big screen with these
70 millimeters. And they,
LA is really good about it. They do them like for a
couple months a year, they have all these screenings.
This was a brand new print.
So they said, they were showing
close encounters of the third kind at the
Cinematheque.
And it was a digital
projection, meaning they're showing a blu -ray
but blown up. And
the guy announcing the movie said, Paul Thomas
Anderson called the theater
and said, hey, I noticed you're
showing close encounters and I really wanted to come see
it, but I can't believe you're showing a blu -ray.
What the fuck?
And they were like, well, there's no like prints.
And he goes, let me, let me text Stephen.
So Paul Thomas Anderson
text Stephen Spielberg and he goes, we're going to
get you guys a 70 millimeter print.
And then it shows up as the first print of its
kind ever. So you feel like you're kind of watching history.
And it looked fantastic.
Close encounters along
with Blues Brothers was always my dad's favorite
movie. When I watched it
as I grow up, I realized this is a movie
about a man who looks exactly
like my father looked at
that age, Richard Dreyfuss, who
decides he wants to leave his
family to go play with aliens.
He literally walks out on his family
within a day he's
making out with like an alien
groupie woman and
he flies to Mars.
He abandons Terry
Gar and his young children to go
to space. And by the way,
the wife, I mean, this
is just, I'm not one
to talk about the male gaze, but you
want to talk about the male gaze. The wife is like, go
honey, go. We support you.
Leave me with jobless with the kid.
You need to go explore
the stars. You need to do this. Yeah.
It
was almost laughable
to me seeing this as an adult.
What a male fantasy
this is. And I never talk like this.
I never say shit like this.
But it was just thinking about my dad
age 30 being like, what have
I done? I hate my
wife and children. I need
a better life than this.
Seeing Close Encounters must
have just been sweet, sweet
fantasy to him. Like one day maybe
an alien will take me to space
and away from these children who bog me
down. So I wound up
disliking the movie, to be honest.
It really kind of stuck in my craw.
It's a celebration of selfishness
to such a degree that
it should have come out in the 80s.
The 70s was not really
the most me decade. It was more
an 80s thing. But yeah, it's
an annoying
movie in a lot of ways. What's cool
about it is the effects,
which still look amazing.
still so cool
communicating with the aliens
through those five notes in the music.
That's an all time great
sci -fi creation.
There's brilliant shit
in the movie. You're also
that we were seeing the director's cut.
There's three cuts of the movie and I've
seen them all and I don't know which one I even prefer.
But man, it gets bogged down
just like The Exorcist kind of does
in that initial
fifteen minute prologue in The Exorcist
when you're like, what is this?
Close Encounters does that a lot.
I love that in The Exorcist, but I agree with you
about Close Encounters.
I argued with somebody about Spielberg
the other night.
They said he could be our greatest living
American director of all time.
And I disagreed.
I think he's a fair
candidate, obviously. But they
brought up Close Encounters and I was like,
Close Encounters stinks.
It's so boring.
Dreyfus playing
with mashed potatoes for 90
minutes before you get an alien
at the end. It's all about how
we communicate through music.
Oh fuck that movie, man.
I get it at the time.
They're no threat.
They're the beautiful, loving aliens.
Yeah.
Look, I like the movie,
but I always just kind of thought
like sometimes when a movie is hailed
as a classic, you're just like,
well, yeah, Spielberg made all these masterpieces
and you start rattling them off. I will
no longer include Close Encounters on
that list. And it was his
Jaws follow up. It's such a fucking
step down from Jaws.
Was it?
It was acclaimed at the time, correct?
It made a lot of money. Oh yeah. Yeah.
And to this day, there's stuff to like.
Don't get me wrong, but like this is not
even a top ten Spielberg.
God, the 70s
were such an odd time. I was telling
my friend Matt Edgar, who's a very funny
comic. Check him out if you can.
And a great guy.
Matt's 40, I think.
But we were in a
bar yesterday and
Eastbound and Down by Jerry Reid started
playing and I was like, oh man, what a great
song. And you know, I never realized
that's what the McBride show is named after.
I wonder why they picked this?
And he was like, well, this is
he's like, this song is from Danny McBride
Show. And I was like, no, it's from Smoky and the Bandit.
Yeah. And he's like, oh, I never saw
Smoky and the Bandit.
Dude, you gotta see it. It's so funny.
And he goes, popular, I guess,
right? And I'm like, it was the
box office second to only Star
Wars the year it came out.
Yeah.
A big, a big adjustment
for me. And it has made me
so much, I think
just a better human being
is to not
snap at someone
who hasn't seen something.
Which I had done for most of my life.
I'm so glad
I stopped doing that. It's
an opportunity for you
to be the person who introduces something
amazing to somebody.
And you immediately destroy that
opportunity by going, what?
What are you, a fucking idiot?
You never saw a movie that came out
ten years before your birth?
It helps no one.
Like, we've all got our blind spots.
I was so
excited to tell him about it.
To tell him about Smoky and the Bandit.
And to be like, you have to see this.
I've gone, in the last decade,
I've always gone the route of,
and truthfully,
I've always gone the route of
I'm jealous of you
that you get to see this for the first time.
Because boy, oh boy,
are you going to, my ex -girlfriend,
bless her sweetheart,
she's such a good person,
you know, to show her
Seinfeld
and literally say,
I'm jealous that you're getting to see this for the first time.
You know, and I think I started
with the outing.
Yeah, you can't start
season one. What's that?
You can't start season one.
I've tried that on several girlfriends,
and they're like, what is this ancient,
nearly black and white piece of shit?
The best you can do
is, the earliest
you can start,
and even this is a little dicey,
is the pony remark
episode of season two.
You could start with
the revenge in season two,
and you'd be in pretty decent shape,
but you really want to start season three
forward. Well,
what's interesting, I remember watching it with my
ex, and it was like,
a woman, at least
the few women I've watched the show with, or
parts of the show with, really
light up, and it's the reason that Friends was
ultimately a more beloved show
than Seinfeld. Equal, but like,
to me there's no contest, to a lot of people
Friends is the clear winner, which I don't understand,
but the second
you realize Elaine and Jerry used to
fuck, and then they're going to fuck
to save the friendship, a part of
a woman's brain lights up, like,
oh, so now I'm into this show.
But the beauty of
Seinfeld is they abandon that in seconds.
It has no interest to them,
Jerry and Elaine's relationship.
Whereas Friends, that's the whole show,
the relationships of these people.
And whether they are
hooking up or whatever, but
I got the 4K of Seinfeld,
which I didn't even know if that was smart or not,
but they do look really, really
great, and I know I'll never have to buy it again,
and I'm glad I did. It's also
pretty much sold out, like Amazon
sold out of it, so if that interests
you, I'd buy it quick.
Yeah, Amazon on Prime Day
was selling the DVD set
for $65. I'm like, guys, this
was 58
years ago. Well, here's
what happened to me. They had the
4K on sale for $150, which
is not great, but the
price had been over $2.
So I order it for $150.
It tells me it's coming
for three months, then it tells me
they're out of stock, and then it's sold out
everywhere. So I'm like,
God damn it. So I order a used copy,
it shows up looking like somebody
threw it into an active volcano,
but at least the discs work,
All right. I have, well,
I guess an opposite
from
your rewatch experience.
I rewatched
Bright Lights, Big City.
Never seen.
Read it. Never saw it.
It is
based on the
novel by Jay,
God damn it, I always forget his name.
McCearney. Yes. And I did see it during
the pandemic, sorry.
He is
a great writer.
The book is, man, the book is awesome.
I really like that book
quite a bit. It is,
it's heavy shit, but it's
great. If you're unfamiliar,
it's,
well, the book
is written in second person,
so it's
the main character talking
to himself. You think
you do this, and you think you should be this
kind of guy, and you should, whatever.
I don't think in the book
the character's ever even named,
if I remember
correctly, but he's basically,
I don't know about a cocaine
addict, but he's
in the throes of the 1980s
fast life scene.
He's doing a lot of coke.
He's drinking heavily.
He's failing at his job.
His wife has left him,
not due to his substance abuse, but because
it was a bad relationship, and he was
blinded by her beauty.
She's thriving overseas as
a model, and he is
disintegrating on a personal level.
His mother died
a year prior of cancer. He doesn't
talk to his family anymore. He's not able to
come to terms with the fact that his mother's died.
Hanging out with
the wrong people, blah, blah, blah, blah,
blah. And the movie
follows that same basic
concept and storyline. In fact, Jay
wrote the script.
And I
think he wrote a decent script.
I think this probably
was hurt a bit in editing.
There are some
moments in it where I can tell, like, well,
that should have been cut in sooner,
and it would have meant a lot more to the story
or whatever.
But it was directed
again, of course, I'm forgetting the guy's name.
Let's see here. I hate when
I have to type as I'm talking
about it. Bright lights.
Big city.
Say again?
No, I just, whenever I listen
to it and you hear it, it's like the typing is very, very
obvious whenever we listen to the show.
I apologize. No, I do it
too. I hear this. I do it on the solo
corner because I got to check myself all the time. You hear like
It was James
Bridges' final directing
film. He wrote
White Hunter, Black Heart,
which is a Clint Eastwood movie. That was
the only thing that was released after this before his
death. But
Bridges also directed Perfect
with John Travolta
and Jamie Lee Curtis, an odd film.
He directed Urban Cowboy,
also an odd film, but a classic.
The China Syndrome.
The Paper Chase.
Those are the big ones.
How do you go from
those important movies like China
Syndrome into Perfect?
I think because he and
Travolta had a hit with
Urban Cowboy and it was off
beat. They probably thought
this will be fun. Let's reunite on this thing
and it'll be a drama
about the world of
calisthenics.
Yeah.
Exactly. I think
also it's like a sort of, isn't it kind
of like a murder mystery too or
something? I've never seen Perfect. I did recently
watch Staying Alive, the Saturday
Night Fever sequel, which is absolutely
terrible. Staying Alive
sucks, but as I've said on the podcast before,
the end when he goes,
and it's all you want at the whole goddamn
movie. Yeah. And he's like on top
and he goes, I want to strut. And he walks
out and the music starts and he's walking
around. You're like, this guys,
this is what we wanted. This is all you
need to do. Yeah. It's
very hard for me to like, because of
how many movies I've seen, to have
that thing where you see the parody before the
thing. Yeah. But I
laugh so hard at that because that's a Bart Simpson
moment on The Simpsons. There's an episode that
ends with him saying that I need to
strut and then walking through Springfield. And
it's great.
Anyway, Bright Lights, Big City. I
didn't like the movie.
I saw it as a kid,
as a Michael J. Fox fan, and he was still
on Family Ties.
And boy did it upset me, seeing
Alex P. Keaton as a
cokehead. I did not enjoy that.
I watched it
again a little while
back after I had read the book and
was disappointed because it wasn't the book.
You know, the book is just better.
But then
upon this
last rewatch, pardon
me, it just hit me
emotionally in a different way. And then also
learning that the author of the book had also written
the movie gave me a little bit of a more
open mind toward it. But Michael
J. Fox is truly tremendous
in the movie. I think it's his
best acting role ever.
And it's a shame that it's in a movie that wasn't
terribly well received.
Kiefer Sutherland is great
in it. Diane Wiest is
great in it.
You know, you got John Houseman in
there in a cameo. You got
Robards is playing a
fall down drunk in this thing.
I fucking love Jason Robards. God
damn. He's awesome in this.
Robards and Magnolia.
I get Tom Cruise getting nominated for Magnolia.
He's awesome in it.
What about fucking Robards?
Yeah, I know the guy's on his literal
deathbed. On his
deathbed, but like I've never seen a more
convincing portrayal
of being on the deathbed either. Yeah.
And I enjoy the movie. I think
it could have been edited a bit
better to drive the thesis of it
all home a bit
more
strongly.
But I enjoyed
the movie. I really
liked it. And also
the fact that I've been dealing with some
health stuff with my mom
and there's a lot of scenes
in the movie of flashbacks of him
with his mom. My mom's not
dying, but it just
resonated with me.
And then also that he's dealing
with the fact that this woman that
he loved left and she's
not who he thought she was
and he's confused by all that
and he doesn't understand. Again,
not my exact situation, but in going
through a breakup and
the emotions that come with it,
this just hit me. And then also
quite frankly, hey people, I'll
open up. We're at the tail
end of this thing.
Going out and hitting the bars too hard
because you don't want to sit home and deal
with the emotions of everything and whatever.
It hit
me. Now the parts I couldn't relate
to were
doing coke at 7am with a
bald woman
until you have a nose bleed or whatever.
The woman you do coke with
at 7am has a full head of hair. She has a full
head of hair.
I enjoyed
the movie. It's a nice little piece
of work and I think
also the fact that it was released by a
major studio heard
it. If this had come out in the later
90s
as an indie
during that Magnolia
pictures boom
and
whatever.
What the fuck was Weinstein's company?
Mirror Max.
In honor of their late mother,
isn't that sweet?
I think it would have been a very
very different
reaction.
Anyway,
check it out.
I recommend Bright Lights Big City.
It was streaming on
Paramount Plus maybe.
I still don't have P Plus.
I
mentioned May
on last week's episode and
occasionally as a guy who's kind of
seen it all I get asked
what's like a movie that nobody's heard of
that you'd really recommend? May's a big one I
throw out there. Another one
I love to mention is Breakdown
with Kurt Russell.
And it just came out on
have you seen Breakdown Joe?
No.
It is
so good.
And my god does it hold up.
I saw it in theaters.
It is directed by Jonathan Mostow
who did Terminator 3
which is pretty, you know, not great but underrated
I would say.
And he's a great action director.
This movie has such a
cool, small,
relatable premise.
And when you compare it to the movie we're discussing on today's show
the pickup I was just like
man a movie just used to be able to be
about what it was about. It didn't have to be
so fucking convoluted. This movie
is Kurt Russell and his wife Kathleen
Quinlan
who was the wife from Apollo 13.
They're on a car trip.
Their car breaks down in the desert.
A truck driver played by
one of the all time great sleazebag
character actors JT Walsh.
No relation.
He pulls up in his truck.
He's like hey can I help you guys?
It's getting hot out here you know.
They're like ah no Kurt Russell's trying to be the man.
He's like I can figure it out. I can figure it out.
The wife's skeptical. She goes I'll
go with him into town. You stay here
with the car. They're like
alright. She goes with the truck driver and
then Kurt Russell's supposed to
meet her at a diner but she's not there.
And everybody in the diner is like
I don't even know what you're talking about.
Then he runs into JT Walsh
and he pulls him over and he's like hey dude
what the fuck?
Where have you been? Where's my wife?
He goes I've never seen you before in my life.
What a
gripping fucking half hour.
It's a Twilight Zone movie.
There's so many great examples
of a Twilight Zone movie where like
the premise kicks in and you're like ooh man
like where's this fucking going?
Breakdown is a perfect example of
that. That first half hour
it is
so well written,
well acted. This is Kurt Russell's
best ever everyman
role I would say. He's got
snake plus skin or whatever. Many
many memorable characters. This is his best
like generic guy role.
He's so good in it
especially when he
starts losing his temper. Because
for a while you're like is this guy some sort of cuck?
Like why isn't he fighting back
and when he's not fighting back so
that when he does you can be like oh shit.
Kurt Russell yelling at
JT Walsh and like just being like you
motherfucker. Like you forget it's rated
R even. It just kind of seems PG
and then Kurt Russell goes nuts.
What a blast. What a great movie.
JT Walsh never takes his
performance above like a 3.
He's playing it just
like he did the guy in Sling Blade who's
casually talking about how he fucked all those
women and killed them. He's just so
cool and calm and chilling
and great in this movie. At
one point he's talking to Kurt
Russell about his wife and he
goes he goes yeah
she couldn't have been more than what
120? 30 %
of it just pure tit.
There's just these lines where you're like
Jesus Christ.
And I'll say this watching
this as an adult. They don't make
it clear whether or not they are having
sexual fun with
Kurt Russell's wife. That's not made clear
which makes me think it was
made clear and then people were like
that's too much.
It's just a fucking
great gripping thriller
and the action is so fucking good.
There's all these car chases in it that just
feel like you're watching actual
shit. It's like Smokey and the Band. There are
these 70s car chase movies
where you never for one
second feel like you're watching something
that isn't exactly how it would happen.
And it is able to make
it possible to make
a movie that's that exciting
just by presenting the events
how they would occur. We don't
need all the other shit.
I love Breakdown.
Check it out. It came out on 4K in
the Paramount scares box set
volume 2 which is
weird because it's not a horror movie at all.
So that's the only way you can get
the 4K right now and it doesn't look very
good to be honest. But Breakdown
is a Paramount movie which means it's probably
on Paramount plus. Check her out.
Pardon me. Excuse me.
Well
I got one more.
I hate when I don't have a theme
but it's okay. I finally watched
I can't believe it took me this long to watch this.
I finally watched Kings from Queens
the Run DMC
documentary.
When did that come out?
Twenty
I don't know. I think a year ago I think.
2024, 23,
somewhere in there.
It was
what is it on Peacock? I don't know. It's on one of
these fucking things. Anyway
it's a two
episode documentary or it might have been
three. I think it's only two though.
About the history of
Run DMC.
I love
They are to me
the Beatles of rap.
They were the first musical
love. Well Michael Jackson
was the first musical love of my life
when I was a child.
And I swear it only went
as far as the music.
But Run DMC was the first
everybody loved Michael Jackson.
So I'll say Run DMC was the first real thing
I can remember where I was like I
love this mom you have to take me to the store
to get this.
It was the first cassette
I ever bought where my mom
insisted that she had to listen to the whole thing
with me before she would let me have it
because she knew there would be curse words on it.
And we did and she let me
keep the cassette.
I just worship these guys man.
They're iconic
isn't big enough of a word
to describe their effect
on how they change
the face of rap music.
Not just sonically but in
bringing it into the mainstream they were the first rap
group to ever be on the cover of Rolling Stone.
It's like they
literally changed the world
with the way the
world looked at music.
So they were
long overdue for documentary.
I think they deserve a biopic.
But the doc
is great.
It only suffers from being not enough.
They really glazed
over some things
that were covered a little more heavily
in the behind the music.
Primarily DMC's
vocal issues where he
lost his voice literally for a long
time and didn't think he'd ever be able to perform again
but then they kind of fixed it and now he can perform
again.
But that
side, the documentary is awesome
and it's just so cool as they tell
their story
they're referencing
things that I knew
about because of the lyrics.
So like
one of the lyrics, Sucker MC's
was their first big
popular song whatever.
But there's a line in that song where he goes
Larry picked me up in his Cadillac, the chauffeur
drove off and we never looked back.
I never knew what that line meant.
I just thought it was a cool thing. I got picked up
in a Cadillac with a chauffeur.
They're talking in the beginning of this documentary
this guy Larry who's like managing them
and they talk about when
Russell Simmons brought them to the studio
for the first time to record anything and runs
like so Larry sent
a Cadillac for us and we got in
and drove off and
it all changed from there and I was like holy
shit that's what that fucking lyric means.
There were a lot of moments
like that in it that were so cool.
And it's wild.
Full
brand new interview with Russell Simmons.
Yeah.
Live from Bali.
Just down in Bali. Bali
dressed like a yoga teacher. Bare foot
cross you know sitting
with the feet up on the couch.
He's like what? Like Polanski? Like if he sets
foot on US soil he's arrested?
He's got, well that documentary came out
I mean he's got some pretty hard
rape accusations against him and Bali
has no tradition treaty and I guess when you have
a zillion dollars you
could just be like well I guess I moved to Bali.
Yeah. So that's where he is.
But I was watching
the Russell Simmons interview and I was like this has got to be
old footage. They didn't. And then
sure enough the next scene
was with you know the little
the, what's that called?
The board, the slate whatever.
It's the slate and it's like
my name is Russell Simmons and this is my interview
for Kings from, I was like holy shit
this is a new interview.
Holding a copy of today's paper.
Anyway, Kings from Queens
fantastic
especially if you're a fan of Run DMC.
That's all I got
for this final movie corner. I won't say
final because the next episode folks
we're just going to have a good time
and chat but
that's it. That was my last movie corner.
Maybe ever.
Last corner
and we go on to, I mean
just an appalling choice for the final
film we're going to discuss.
Just appalling.
This final month it was like
okay naked gun fine
happy Gilmore
2 real bad
and then although I think we're going
to have a little bit of a disagreement here
this almost didn't qualify
as a film to me. And I think the
worst studio today
the worst people making movies in the game
is Amazon Prime
MGM. The comedies
in particular that they are releasing on
Amazon have been the worst
I have ever seen and that's just the ones I've watched.
They also brought out the Ice Cube
War of the World that Joe mentioned on the last
episode. What's happening over
there? What is happening?
Amazon is making content
the way
they
that reflects their products
on the store site.
It's like you can buy something from Amazon
that's the greatest thing that's ever been invented
or you can buy the biggest piece
of shit and you go I don't understand
there was good reviews and the pictures
are good. How is this what I received?
They're doing that same thing with content.
They really are
I mean I feel like they
just have a if you have this
actor this actor and this director
will make it. We don't even need to read
the script. That's the kind of vibe they're giving off.
The pickup
the plot of
this thing is
I almost couldn't believe what
I was seeing but
you find out about halfway
through that Kiki Palmer's father
well wait set up
the Kiki
who she is so she and Pete
seduces Pete Davidson
who's a security
guard.
Eddie Murphy is the old too old
for this shit security guard. Yes.
And Davidson's the new one.
They're partnered up together. Yes.
Kiki Palmer who has still
not been given a good role in a movie
seduces Davidson
immediately like upon meeting
him and then you learn that it's
to find out
how to rob this casino.
How they can get in and do it.
They're armored truck drivers that deliver to a
casino. Kiki Palmer seduces
Pete to get all the information about the route
of the truck so she can hijack
the truck and rob the casino
because the casino gives them 16
million dollars every Monday.
60. 60 excuse me
million dollars every Monday you
know as their deposit or whatever to
the bank and
it's a bit of a convoluted
affair.
The fact that she
would know because they also go
this is again this logic issue
they go out of their way to show
that random people are assigned
the drivers are randomly
assigned to these routes.
So the way
then they do that immediately. Eddie Murphy
it's his anniversary. He's married to Ava Longoria.
It's his 25th
wedding anniversary which some
sort of studio note
required Eddie Murphy to say
a thousand times.
In the first half hour of this movie
it's like you know
it is my 25th anniversary tonight so I got to
get back for that. Otherwise well you know
how it is when you forget about your 25th wedding
anniversary. I mean I've been married to this woman for 25
years so you're like
guys I got it.
This is the plot of every sitcom since the dawn
of time. We get it.
But he goes
to work the day of the anniversary after he promises
his wife a wonderful night and
Andrew Dice Clay who plays the
dispatcher is like you're on
this route today.
Yeah he goes you're on this route today
and Murphy's like
no I can't do that route today it's my anniversary.
So my point is they show you that
the routes are kind of randomly
assigned so then you're like
well then how would she know that Pete was on
that route.
So whatever. It's a big
ask but
and it goes from there. It's pretty
paint by numbers.
They rob the casino.
Kiki's motive. Pat
as you were saying which is revealed halfway
through.
It's a revenge
heist.
Her father
was a security
guard at this casino
20 years ago or whatever
and there's a robbery
and he leaves his post to
go rescue the people in danger
and the casino
doesn't
honor his memory like
doesn't pay him off and doesn't
so that's why she's robbing them
for 60 million dollars is to get back
because they didn't honor or respect her
father. Well it's not it's
sorry not to
it's that
he does
a thing where people were going to get trapped
inside of a safe or a vault
and he goes and he holds
the door to make sure
that people don't die because they'll suffocate
to death. In doing
this he ends up getting stuck in the
vault. The casino
instead of paying the insurance money
to the family says
he shouldn't have left his post
and she says their money
was more important to them than my father
so I'm going to take their money
and that's why are we
not seeing that scene as a flashback
if that's going to be
our entire motive. It's an
exciting and visual scene. She
could narrate it over it. We didn't have to
hear any dialogue or anything.
It would have been a great cold open.
Yeah.
The movie is
basically a three -way buddy
heist movie
between Kiki, Pete and
Eddie. Eddie and Pete have
no chemistry. Kiki and
Pete have no chemistry. Kiki
and Eddie have no chemistry. Eva Longoria
has no chemistry with anyone.
She comes in and she's like you
knew when you married a Latina that I was going to
have a fiery temper.
That's her entire
point in the movie.
That's what your wife would say when
she's 100 % sure you're cheating on her.
She'd show up on your anniversary and go
you know you married a Latina
what are you talking about?
What are you fucking talking
about?
All of these people feel like they met
right before they shouted action.
There's no lived in
fun
camaraderie. I don't know.
It left me ice cold.
The plot was convoluted.
The action was average at
best and the comedy was
not there. Occasionally Eddie Murphy
is riffing or improving something
kind of like the new Beverly Hills Cop where you're like
alright that was kind of funny or that jumped out at
me as being a funny line.
But for the most part no. I didn't
find much to like about this movie.
Um
I look
the movie
in and of itself is
you know it's not good. It's
as paint by numbers as you can get and if you watch
the trailer the trailer just shows you
the whole movie.
But
it held me
and it held my attention. Why?
There were
four times
where where Eddie Murphy
or Dice made me laugh
very hard out loud.
Um Dice steals the movie.
Yeah Dice
when he's like yelling for Pete and he's
like asshole head
his head looks like an asshole like
that really made me laugh like
um felt like it had to
have been improv because it was like the only wit
in the movie. He says it in his act
he'll be like look at you asshole
so he clearly just yelled it out.
But yeah yeah but that really made me laugh.
Dice like
freaking out when the truck is stalled
when the truck gets hijacked and he's watching
it and he's
like what kind of assholes let their truck
get hijacked and then he realizes it's
Eddie and Pete and he's like you're the
asshole like just doing a classic dice.
They're my assholes.
That made me laugh. I didn't understand
at the end did you see when they came back after
the credits though not after but a few
seconds in. So the credits
start and they do this post thing
and it's not
dice. It's some
other actor the back of another actor's
head like Steinbrenner.
It's a much younger man
and if you watch it again it looks nothing like
Andrew Dice Clay's head and they're super
imposing his voice. It's very odd.
Like at least get an actor who resembles him.
I uh
and you know
Murphy's scene there's a scene where
Murphy has to one of the hijackers he like
fights the hijacker and throws him off the truck.
Yeah. And Pete
like he comes and it's happening in the
back of the truck and he comes and he sits back in the passenger
seat and he's all out of breath
and Pete's like that was
fucking awesome man you were like Jason Statham
and Eddie
Murphy does the classic Eddie
Murphy where he's doing the crying voice
and he's like oh mama niscus
oh fuck my back up oh
Jesus Christ like that made
me laugh really like I rewound that
I was like that's old Eddie Murphy shit man
that's really really funny
and there was enough
of that when he's in the pan
when he's in the diner
when he crumples up the pancakes
that's how I like to eat
my pancakes when he
press him in the ball and throws him
on the plate cause she's trying to make
him eat pancakes after she kidnaps
him and then he starts
doing the Shaft song for no reason like
that shit I was like man this is like old
Eddie Murphy shit this is really fucking
funny there wasn't enough
of it unfortunately but there was
well there was enough to keep me watching
if there was truly
enough I would have been like
alright man that was like the golden child
not a great movie but good enough
but I'd say the movie
as is
my hog's not down
it's not down it's
certainly way more up than Happy Gilmore
2 and it's
probably a little even
with Naked Gun if I'm being honest
damn I mean
yeah I
I'd put it on a par I guess
with Happy Gilmore 2 I just didn't
find much to like it was a big
expensive hunk of junk
where the only like
moments of life were
those improvised moments from Dice
and Eddie Murphy
really just not even clear what Davidson's
doing in this movie and Kiki Palmer's not good
either and
but yeah I mean Eddie Murphy
is always gonna show up
and give you something but he does seem pretty
checked out of this particular
picture
yeah I like and by the way
I'm happy
for Pete
I saw an interview with him recently where he
said he is not smoking weed anymore
he seems healthy
he's having a kid I saw him on
some press interviews for this
he just seems healthy even in his
performance in this I was like
he's present he's there
yeah like so that's good
it's a positive thing for him
and I hope he stays on that track cause there was a
long time with him where I was like
man I don't know how this is gonna end
so I'm glad to see
that but
that all said
I can't recommend
giving somebody in that position
you know 15 million dollars
a picture is always gonna help
those issues settle down
for sure yeah well it's nice to see
he went the opposite of Edward
Furlong which was
hey if you can get your shit together we'll pay you
a lot of money to go do a big movie and use it
okay got it
anyway
that's our show folks
we will be back with the
final episode of we'll see you
in hell
uh
quotes or quotes
Jesus Christ my brain plugs
cause I don't wanna plug on the final episode
um
I will be
in uh oh god
well where am I going
Pat I don't know September
uh
Tampa Florida second
weekend of September third weekend I got
at side splitters third weekend I got the
first weekend of October
I've got the punchline
uh soon to be
announced some more shows coming in December
and then I've got some stuff in the new year
go to joderosa .com for tickets
subscribe to my YouTube at
joderosacomedy watch that
special if you can I'd appreciate it
I never promised you a rose garden
available there
and if you wanna buy it unedited
without commercials
unedited meaning I think there might be a few bleeps
on YouTube but you can go get that
at disruptorcomedy .com
uh
and if you're in New York come see Joey Roses
have a sandwich
have a drink maybe I'll see you there
Pat
folks I am at the
Patrick Walsh on Instagram we are
at see you in hell pod on
Instagram I would say that page will stay
up for the foreseeable future
even though the podcast may not
um we'll remind
you on the last episode of course but if you
want to forever keep
these episodes of the show by all
means download them now
don't say I'll do it when I get to it cause
one day you're gonna log in and it will not be there
and you'll hate yourself so get it
done Miss Pat season 5
starts I believe October 24th
uh I
recorded a commentary for Airplane 2 the
sequel which is coming out from Keno Lorber
on September 23rd in 4k
and blu ray we will be back
with our very final
episode of the we'll see you in hell podcast
so we will see you next time
we love ya and we will see ya
in hell