I'll see you in hell, it's the podcast you turn to when you want to hear a little bit
discussion on your favorite genre films and quite frankly the genre films. You
don't like that much. My name is Joe Derosa and the films that aren't genre films
at all. My name is Patrick Walsh. We talk about anything on this show,
anything and everything. You know that now, you're a private patron. Remember, and
you've probably been listening for upwards of six years. Yes. We like to rely on
our routines and our habits because that's what makes us feel centered and
an increasingly uncentered world.
Yes, that's true.
We've also switched to a sort of life coach format.
So I will be sort of motivating you this week
to stay in shape, to bust the Thanksgiving five pounds
that you gained in my in Joe's case, a combined 50.
But we're doing well.
No, I'm not doing well at all.
I'm going to apologize in advance to the listeners
for the dark, undercurrent that will be carrying me
through both of these episodes.
I am in a bad place, but I'm going to try to shake it off
for the paying customer.
See, I really am too.
And I think we can get through it, but the world is at war.
The world, you know, I started laughing today,
but it's really, there's nothing funny about it.
And this isn't a political talk at all.
You don't care about the mayor or the governor
of Los Angeles, but this man gets on the news every day.
As you know, we saw him, you know,
being on a personal intimate dinner with like 15 people
indoors a couple of weeks ago.
He gets on and apologizes.
And then like, by the way, he tells you
you're not allowed outside.
Correct.
So he's like, look, some of us make mistakes.
We just got to make sure those mistakes.
And it's like, dude, you are the one person
because it makes everything else fall to shit.
It basically means anyone in a in a bodega screaming,
I don't have to wear a mask.
Now can say the governor doesn't wear one
when he's at private.
It's just such horseshit.
Oh, yeah, it's like when it's like when a Pelosi.
Yeah, I got to be honest, Pat, at this point, I call her
Hello, see, oh my God, the woman's a living hell.
You should send that to Don, by the way.
He loves those nicknames.
Yeah, Pelosi's strolling around the barber shop
with no mask on.
And then she's like, I was set up.
It's like, no, you weren't set up.
You went, you went, you didn't wear a mask after you.
This is why nobody's listening.
But Garcetti, he get, is it, is it fucking Garcetti?
What's the man's name?
I get them all confused.
Garcetti is your name or some, excuse me.
Greer governor is Newsom.
Yeah, Newsom, yeah.
And Newsom's the one who did the meal.
He comes on to real shit move, man.
Of course, because Newsom's a real fucking
blowhard with the rules.
Of course.
So Newsom gets on today and he does this every day
and he talks to the people of Los Angeles
like he's putting your mind at ease.
And he's like, hey, I warned you Saturday.
I warned you Sunday.
Now I'm warning you on Monday.
Guys, if we don't follow the strict restrictions
that were a little stricter than the other ones,
even though I never really told you which ones
you're supposed to take seriously,
if we don't take them seriously,
I'm gonna add in another round of restrictions
and then you'll have to stay inside even longer
except you can still go outside
and you can still kind of do what you want.
And you can still wear a mask and police officers
don't wear a mask and I don't wear a mask.
It's like, I think everyone should wear a mask.
I have a mask over my microphone right now
to stop the pee sounds.
I come in hot with the pee.
That's how much I care about it.
But that's what you said to your wife
when you're wedding night, right?
But if 50 % of people think this thing is a hoax
and they don't care what we can't just be this sloppy about it
and the rules can't change every 24 hours.
And you know, I don't know how people just aren't going
and say, I guess they are going insane
but everybody's crushed.
It's over, everybody's losing it.
I can't, let me just first off, a shout out to the fans
before I say the negative thing about the celebrity
that I'm going to trash in a second.
Okay.
Positive thing about the real celebrities, the fans,
the real stars, the fans.
You make it possible.
Yeah, you do.
And shout out to you guys for supporting and sticking
with us through this period
because I am ready to give up on everything.
I'm ready to start, you know, just walking around
no pants outside, like I'm done.
I'm at the end of my rope here.
And not even in a sexual way.
You know, I don't give a shit way anymore.
Oh, it wouldn't be sexual.
No, it wouldn't.
But with, so hello, thank you again to all of you.
And then when I was going to say that it's negative,
it is fuck you, Ellen DeGeneres.
Oh, sure.
Fuck you, lady.
I got so mad the other day.
I'm watching a clip of her on YouTube.
Why do I watch things purposefully on YouTube
that I have to seek out that will make me furious?
I feel it gives me some sort of power or extends my life
or it does feel that it fuels me in some way.
But I mean, I'm just tired of this shit.
It's like what you're talking about.
What you're governor, it's what I'm about to talk about here.
It's like she's sitting there with Tiffany Haddish
and their six feet apart.
And they're like, we're just so everybody knows.
We're six feet.
They've measured us and we're six feet
and we're sitting here.
And it's like, hey, I'm fine with that.
I got no beef with that.
But if you get to do that, Ellen,
then I get to do that inside.
So stop fucking telling me that even with the distance inside,
it's not enough.
Stop fucking telling me that you might be able to transmit this
any even farther distance than six feet.
Stop fucking telling me that the rapid test aren't reliable
because these are all the things you're doing.
Once you can have your little fucking talk show,
okay, and ask Tiffany what it's like
to date common this week.
It's sickens me, man.
I'll tell you what it's like.
It's probably pretty boring.
I would think so.
I mean, a lot of motivational cassettes.
There's no more boring screen presence than common.
I love that.
I think she can do better, frankly.
I could look at Man, don't care less about either.
I don't give a shit.
Do well, great.
I have no ill will towards any of them.
I don't, you know, it's like,
or either of them.
It's like, I just don't,
and honestly, there was a time,
and there are times when I'll get very mad at somebody
who refuses to wear the mask or whatever.
And then you see this shit and you go,
no, I get why that guy's being an asshole now
because they have shown us time and time again
that these rules and the science seemingly doesn't apply
to people with a certain amount of status
and a certain amount of money.
And, you know, if it's an indoor acoustic poetry bar
in New York City, it can't possibly function
or put on performances.
If it's SNL, it's okay.
It's all bullshit, man.
I'm just fucking tired of it.
I'm tired of it.
And I play by the rules.
I wear the damn mask.
I do what's right.
But that is the issue.
I play by the rules, you know, as well as I possibly can,
the mask to me is non -negotiable.
The way I see it is this, put the mask on
and you go outside, are you taking a risk of your own health?
But you can't just say kind of do what you want to everybody
and also show them the example exactly like you're saying
that we, the rich and famous can do anything.
This SNL thing going up six Saturday nights in a row
with 50 people standing shoulder to shoulder,
you know, doing like kissing scenes practically
in these sketches, what are you doing?
This goes out every Saturday and then people go,
well, wait a minute, I'm being told I can't leave my house.
And then the whole Twitter world is don't leave your house.
How can you be so callous as to leave your house?
There's huge extremes all over the place
and all it really boils down to is that no one has looked
us in the eye and told us what to do.
Now that responsibility falls to the president,
that's a lost cause, but somebody has to look at us
and say, here's what's going on and here's how we beat it.
Or we don't.
There's nobody to do that.
There is a time where I solely blamed Trump
for most of this.
I'm so far past that, fuck all these people.
Your governor is a Democrat.
My governor's a Democrat.
They're doing no better of a job.
Everybody ran their fucking mouth
that we can run our state the way we want to.
We don't have to listen to you.
People, Republican and liberal governors
said that about their own states.
And yet none of them are doing it.
Yeah, none of them are running their state
in some unique fashion that's working better than another.
It's all bullshit.
None of them know what to do.
And they'll keep fueling this.
The media sickens me.
I mean, it's just disgusting.
This whole thing is disgusting.
We should be ashamed of ourselves.
And now let's review some movies.
Well, yeah, no, this isn't up.
You hear enough about this stuff.
But it'd be so far.
It'd be stupid also to not address it.
We're all living through this.
And we're just thankful you guys still like to laugh
and we'll try to keep the focus on the funny
and you keep supporting the Patreon.
Cause that's what's keeping us afloat for sure.
And keeping us doing it.
But two things keep me afloat.
Something I call the Patreon.
Yes.
And a little lady I like to call Jack Daniels.
Sure.
Here's to you.
I'm sipping it down there.
I think she's a man judging by the name,
but I don't.
I could be sure for Jackie.
That's a real old school clothes
made a way to look at gender.
I guess that's true.
I shouldn't assume the gender of bourbons.
I'm working on a reboot of sent of a woman.
Yeah.
Where instead of John Daniels, the line is,
tell him I want it wall to wall, Jackie Daniels.
Jackie Dan.
And then he goes, it's Jack Daniels, he's a man, sir.
And he goes, when you've known her as long as I have son,
she's a woman.
Just, you know, something a little more
for the current times.
Sure.
Is that, now I've recently rewatched the movie.
I think it's really a hammy,
pachino performance, and I don't care for the film.
I think O'Donnell is a zero.
And they're surely could have been a better performer
in that role.
I guess what I'm wondering is, when he says sent of a woman,
is he referring to pussy?
No, he means the perfume.
He says, yeah, because there's a line.
And he's also kind of pervy.
Yeah, no, there's a line in the movie
where he says something about like I can still smell
or perfume or something.
There's a line in there somewhere.
Okay.
All right.
It's not, yeah, he's not talking about like crotch stink.
You know, I mean, it doesn't have to be stink.
But I'm just saying, that's outrageous.
There's a movie was named after General sent.
That's crazy.
I agree.
No, it's, yeah, he says, yeah, it's like the, you know,
it means because he can't see her.
It's her smell.
It's the scent of a woman.
I know, but you have a heightened sense of smell.
So I'm just saying, maybe he's like, ooh.
So the lady has to be wearing perfume for him to smell her.
That doesn't seem like much of a gift.
I just say he's not wearing perfume.
The blind man smells, the remembers the scent
more than the look of the woman.
Well, he couldn't remember the look.
He's blunt.
That's what I'm saying.
Fair enough.
And the movie, I agree with you.
It is hammy.
It is sort of cookie cutter Oscar fair,
a little darker than some of the,
that type of movie we would usually get.
But I will say this, it's worth the price of admission
just for the climactic speech.
That scene where he comes in and like saves Chris O'Donnell
and gives like the greatest Puccino speech ever.
You know, you can't beat that.
You can't, it brings me to tears.
It's just the issue at hand is so silly.
It's like a school prank.
Yeah, I remembered it being like,
you know, like a few good men type conflict.
And when I watched it, I was like, wait,
this is like the kid who did something?
Everything's on the line because Chris O'Donnell
was at the school and a scholarship
and because he's trying to do the honorable thing,
he will lose it and his parents don't,
he will lose his scholarship and his parents don't care
about him and this is his chance to be a kid
that came up in nothing to become something.
So that's enough stakes for me.
I'll take that.
I guess my issue is that I don't,
I didn't care about Chris O'Donnell.
The movie wouldn't be made today.
Did you hear, I think I might have told you Joe,
they're rebooting Finding Forester.
No, I texted this to you and we can't.
Yeah, I love the,
a movie even its most ardent supporters would give a
B plus probably.
But it was Sean Connery and a black teenager
and Sean Connery mentors the kid and says things
like the only memorable line from the movie.
Oh, the man now dog.
Yeah, it's terrible.
Yeah, done by Gus Van Sant,
I believe right on the heels of Goodwill hunting.
It's the film he followed with Goodwill
and right after that went right back to like,
I'm gonna do a thing about a school shooting for 150 grand
and then I'll see you guys later and I get it.
So this, the new one is a black teenager
who befriends a reclusive lesbian author.
Yes.
And it's like fine, fine.
Make that, make that a movie.
I don't care.
Why are you calling it Finding Forester?
I don't get it.
I never.
The name means nothing to anybody.
Just make a movie about a lesbian,
call it the lesbian mentor.
I'll see that.
Yeah, it's a TV show by the way.
Call it that.
But I mean, whoever thought Finding Forester
had the legs just be turned into a television series.
Let me tell you this.
This thing could have been Finding Forester
starring the last ever run of Sean Connery,
you'll ever see on the screen.
We shot it in secret before he died, pre -COVID.
I still wouldn't watch this fucking thing.
Same, same.
So getting even farther away from the source material
isn't making it any better or more intriguing,
more intriguing.
It's just making it confusing
because nobody gives it shit about the source material.
It's just called a different thing.
Nobody's gonna get excited about this.
Yeah.
They had, my wonder is if like Sean Connery died.
Somebody didn't go to their IMDB while he was hot.
Found a movie that they thought could be up for reboot
and just called a studio and said this word.
That's probably how it happened, honestly.
I think that's how uncreative this business is.
Oh, Sean Connery, he just died.
We should do that show.
Even though he has nothing to do with it.
It's all just rights issues.
It's all, we have the rights.
What do you drink in there, by the way?
Gatorade.
Oh, just gatorade, huh?
I don't normally, but I've been feeling dehydrated
and it's not from hardcore alcoholism.
Minus.
What was I gonna say?
It's all just, it's all just rights bullshit.
It's like we have the rights to this.
We might as well do it again.
Like let's option it, you know, so we don't lose it.
And it's like who cares?
Yeah.
If you lose it, I had a meeting with Paramount
and they're doing it, they're going into television.
Or they've been in television,
but they're basically looking to, this is their whole MO.
We're looking to make our old movies into shows.
So they're doing Grease, you know, like,
rise of the pink ladies.
It's called rise of the pink ladies.
Everybody's favorite characters in Grease.
The pink ladies.
The original show was supposed to be called
Rydell High, which is a good name for a show,
especially if you like Grease.
Rise of the pink ladies.
Like they're superheroes or something.
And that rise brings them to a level
of being maybe a second tier level of popularity
at the high school.
That's the rise we're tracking.
Or are we going to follow them?
And they're going to become broad burners.
Jesus.
What is that?
What?
My, I have two folding chairs on my balcony
and they just got blown into the glass
and it's scared the shit out of me.
All right.
Jesus, that scared me.
All right, so is it a windy night?
Apparently, unless there's a man out,
maybe the invisible man is here.
Or, you know, I did, I did have a tumultuous
semi abusive relationship with that scientist.
That's true.
The work did not.
So maybe he's here.
Anyway, go ahead.
So basically, I have this great meeting
and I'm like, yeah, you know, of course,
I'm a fan of some of Paramount's movies, you know?
Let me think about it.
Do you have something like you're really targeting
that you think would be a great fit?
Or, and I was sent the Wikipedia page
for movies released by Paramount.
Just an endless list of films from 1919 to the present.
And it's like, yeah, you know,
I think people are definitely ready
for a television version of the changing lanes
with Ben Affleck and Samuel Chex.
It's like looking through all these average movies.
I don't know.
Maybe something else sparked me.
Simple plan was Paramount, you know?
I'd love a simple plan type show.
Who knows, but it doesn't do that.
You love that movie.
Maybe I will.
I just, it was depressing to me
that a big television studio was like,
here's our plan, Wikipedia entry.
Well, here's the thing.
Paramount, I mean, you look,
I don't want to knock your potential future bosses,
but it's, I don't think these studios
don't know how to handle this
because you look at Paramount that was like, you know,
top five players in the movie game, you know?
They were right there with 20th century Fox and whatever.
And now they're trying to adjust
and transform as television becomes much more focal
as home entertainment becomes the norm.
And now the Paramount network is like,
I mean, you're talking, it's like behind FXX Spanish.
You know what I mean?
Like it's like, yeah.
It's nowhere near like a competitor with FX,
with Fox, with HBO, with, with, you know,
with any of the, you know, even like lifetime and Sundance
and all the, they're just, they're just so far behind
the curve at this point.
And I think they don't know what to do.
So then they go, well, we'll put out a success before.
Oh, our movies did.
So we'll make movies, we'll make TV shows
out of our movies.
That's sure, that's surely gonna hit.
And it's the same mistake every one of these networks
in studios makes is they think the same roles
apply to television and they don't.
Yeah, they don't.
It's far more of a dice roll.
There's, there's, the machine is not in place
that, that is with the, with that studio system
that, that function so well for so long.
You think there have been more good TV shows
made into movies or movies made into TV shows?
I think, I can't think of one good TV show
made into a movie.
Well, I can't touchables.
Well, yeah, I don't count that as much as a family.
The original, not the cartoon, which I walked out of.
All right, untouchables, I don't count
because that's based on somewhat on real people.
And they were also called the untouchables.
So like, mission impossible.
Okay, that's good.
All right, also a paramount.
Join.
You got two, you got the Adam's family
and mission impossible.
There's a few.
Okay, there's a few.
Brady Bunch sort of movies.
I think, yeah, that's a good one.
Movies becoming TV shows really doesn't work much.
I mean, Hannibal is one I can think of beyond that.
I don't really know.
I don't even know if it's any good.
I don't watch the pilot of Hannibal.
I've heard it's great.
I'd like to watch it.
I can't think of any movie that's ever been turned
into a TV show that was, you know, you got Uncle Buck.
Oh, yeah.
Do you know that...
Clueless.
Uncle Buck, the TV show starring Mike Epps,
which I did not see.
No, that's the second version.
The original is the Kevin Meeney version.
Yeah, right.
I did watch that when I was a kid
and I was like, this guy ain't John Candy,
even though I like Kevin Meeney.
Not the right role for him.
But it was pitched and made into a show
three or four years ago, starring Mike Epps.
And I believe that the show was originally going to be called
Black Buck.
And thankfully, Wiserheads prevailed on that one.
Wow.
But yeah, Black Buck.
Joe, I was looking up to tell you where my brain is at
that article I sent you about the New York Times
shows the 25 greatest modern actors
and to tell you where my head's at.
I just Googled 25 guest stars with two R's in stars.
And believe it or not, it didn't bring up the article.
I was looking for 25 best actors New York Times.
Uh -huh.
But um, the list is insane.
I haven't heard of half of the list
and I'm obsessed with film.
So it's this just kind of mess, you know,
number one, they got right, Denzel Washington.
I kind of kept hoping as I went through like,
just tell me they end with Denzel
and that he's not been left off this list.
And there he was at number one, which made me think.
They got Denzel one, they got like Viola Davis at like five.
They got Defoe at like 14.
There's a couple of right moves on that list, not many.
I mean, it is, it is a diverse list.
I would say I would argue to a fault.
It is, it is choosing one of each, which just is not diversity to me.
But um, you know, like West Stoodie is on this list.
The Native American actor.
I love last the Mohicans.
I just rewatched the film.
And I think it's amazing.
I went through his Wikipedia.
He's in like direct to DVD movies.
That's what I think that's right about.
He's got a supporting largely non -speaking role in last
of the Mohicans, which is an amazing movie.
But it's like, why is he on this list?
What are you talking about?
Um, but that's just what I'm saying.
It just feels like, oh, wait, we don't have a Native American actor.
And I feel like that is, uh, it's, it's very transparent.
And it's grossed to me.
It is gross.
And by the way, the, this, this industry, this disgusting, racist pig industry,
they could call West Stoodie up and give him stuff.
If they believe that he is great, they won't do it.
Yeah, they won't do it.
They'll put a guy like that on their lists.
And then they won't hire him in anything good.
No, people I mean, they'll still be in direct to DVD stuff.
Yeah.
Everybody came out of the woodworking way.
Oh, my God.
Poor mirror.
So Irvino and Harvey Weinstein's an animal.
And we need to stand by this.
It's like, give her jobs.
Yeah.
Well, mirror.
So Irvino got a CBS show.
And then they recast her.
I think it's insane.
It's like, so I know that we hired you because of the horrible emotional trauma
you've been through, but we're going to let you go.
Great.
Uh, number 11 on the list is an actress who more and more recently, I think,
is not a good actress.
Her name is Julia and more.
I used to love Julia and more.
I think lately, she's a hot mess.
You never know what's coming.
I feel like her accents are always ridiculous.
Their Boston accent is the worst in the game and she keeps doing it.
Um, I think I, she lost me when she in the imagined video,
wasn't she one of the people in the, I'm sure she was.
I don't know, man.
It's just, they're, the list ain't great.
You know, I, um, you can go and read it.
It's got some, some good, some people it's hard to argue with.
But just, you know, we got, we got Zhao Tao at eight.
Who?
That's what I'm saying.
I, not only do I watch a lot of movies, I watch a lot of foreign films,
Zhao Tao, and then it lists three or four movies.
I don't know what they are.
So which, what are they?
They are the world from 2005, 24 city from 2009 and still live from 2008.
Now, uh, I could see if I was,
I, you know, some, some more on who doesn't watch any movies other than
Hubey Halloween, I might be, I might be furious about this list.
But I really pay attention to fucking movies.
And that number seven right after her is Tony Servilio or Tony Servilio.
No idea who that is.
Uh, note from Mike, thank you.
Mike, she wasn't an imagined, she's right.
She's in the worst one.
The I take responsibility video with her and like Stanley Tucci.
Oh, yes, you watch their eyes move left to right as they read it off of their screen.
Yes.
Uh, you know, it's just so gross and transparent and it's like, give me a, by the way,
correct me if I'm wrong.
I read this list, didn't see one actor that was in parasite in it.
Oh, no, there, there's not.
Here's something that won Best Picture a year ago.
And, and, and they're looking for a diverse list.
And they don't, it's, it's incredible how much they undercut themselves with
their so called and show that they don't really believe in any of it.
That they just pick things out of a hat to try to make themselves look good.
It's so gross.
I completely agree.
Uh, and, you know, less do you think I'm, I'm only having a problem with foreign
actors, my biggest issues come a little further down in the top 10.
Uh, so number six, actually, Joe, number six is
Song Kang Ho from Parasite.
So, okay, sorry, all right.
Um, but, you know, again, I would say probably a little high on the list.
Um, number five is Nicole Kibman.
Uh, give me a break.
I just finished the undoing last night.
I mean, there, there are lines in every episode that she just says in a full Australian accent.
She's, you know, playing in New Yorker, but the accent just wildly comes and goes.
Her performance is kind of laughable at times.
She's playing it like it just really bad and over the top.
And the worst, uh, problem is that while watching it each week, Heather would go,
what the fuck is this theme song?
I hate this theme song.
And it was this kind of off key woman singing an old standard.
Look it up.
It's Nicole Kibman.
Oh my god.
Who I supposed insisted on singing the theme song to a serious murder mystery thriller.
By the way, uh, with, uh, who, who print the listing in New York times.
And, and just before I get off it, I do want to say number four is Kiana Reeves.
Number four, I mean, that is fucking ridiculous.
Who for decades has been the go to name you use when you're talking about a bad actor.
Now I like Kiana Reeves and I like the new journey he's on.
But that journey is one where he excels and rolls that don't require acting.
So what are you talking about?
That is fucking absurd.
Notice two New York times in your precious little fucking list.
Don't see too many old faces on there.
None.
Well, you see any Maggie Smiths or Judy dentures or Anthony Hopkins.
You know, yeah, it's awfully funny.
Everybody seems to be in a certain age range, very bookable age range.
Fucking scumbags.
I agree.
Oh, what can we talk about that might put us in a better mood?
Um, well, let's go to the movie corner.
I mean, why fight it?
I don't want to fight it anymore.
We always have fun down at the movie corner.
Yeah, let's go down.
Oh, yeah.
I feel like you are dynamic now is like me and Heather.
Heather, uh, continuously just tries to find some shred of light inside me.
And it's, it's increasingly hard to find.
I, uh, I'll start us off, Pat, please.
I watched a little picture that I had for years written off as, as probably terrible.
Yeah, I'd never seen it.
Uh, but after my love of hubby Halloween, I said, let me give it a shot.
It's called you don't mess with the zohan.
Sure.
Sort of theaters.
Uh, I'll tell you right out of the gate, two minutes into this thing, maybe even 90 seconds.
I was a hundred percent in.
I was laughing hysterically.
Sandler doing that like dance with no pants on through the whole opening beat sequence.
Sure.
Catching things in his ass crack.
Uh, and then you know, he plays in his really soldier like super soldier who secretly
fakes his own death.
So he can secretly move to New York to become a hairdresser, which he always wants to do.
Uh, family laughs him out of the apartment when he tells them that he wants to do that.
Uh, heavy use of the term, Faggala, which I don't, I'm assuming has connections to the American
slur, but pretty sure it's the same thing.
Yeah.
Um, by the way, I've been rewatching the office, the American version.
Corel uses the Fag word dozens of times.
Dozens.
Yeah, it's crazy because that show that show feels like it just went off the air.
I mean, I, I was kind of blown away by it.
Carry on, Joe.
Anyway, uh, he, he then sandwich sneaks off to America, does become a hairdresser.
And then the plot basically from there on out is he only knows dated hair styles.
So his customer base is all older women, uh, who he fucks incessantly throughout the movie.
Yeah.
I love this picture.
I loved it.
Front to back.
Yeah.
I laughed the entire time.
There are some really, really funny gags.
There's a scene where he makes a fucking eight year old kid start crying uncontrollably.
And then he pinches the kid's neck and the kid just goes like instantly to sleep.
Like a, like a Spock death pinch.
It's very funny.
Uh, you got Dave Matthews in this thing.
Wild part for Dave Matthews playing like a hillbilly racist.
Dave Matthews in just go with it, starring Adam Sandler and Nicole Kibman and Jennifer Aniston.
Uh, I, that was the only one I had never seen.
And when I watched it recently, Dave Matthews picks up something with his ass in that movie.
So it must be something Sandler's obsessed with.
Yeah.
So they've even been a call back to Zohan.
I don't recall.
Um, yeah.
So he, uh, he, uh, it's, it's a very funny film.
Uh, it's a very, very funny film.
Nick Schwartzen's in it.
He's really funny in it.
Sandler's a writing gag.
Sandler's console having sex with Nick's mom.
Yeah.
Uh, I loved it.
I loved it.
And I think there should be a box set for Adam Sandler.
The consists of happy Gilmore, Billy Madison, the wedding singer, Zohan, uh, and, uh,
Hubey.
I would buy that box.
You know, there's, there's pretty close to that box that available now.
You can buy four packs of Sandler very easily.
Um, I wouldn't put Hubey on that list, but so be it.
Well, I think I would say this is the funniest after wedding singer.
The funniest movie I've seen him do.
I should rewatch it.
I'd go big daddy, but I just watched, I won't do it as a review.
But I also watched big daddy.
It was two.
It's, it's got its moments, but it's very schmaltcy and it's, it's like, it's just, like, I like
Zohan because it's like, we know what this is, guys.
Yeah.
You know, the, uh, uh, and with my favorite joke in the whole movie is he does a video profile on the
favorite films.
And it says, uh, lethal weapon, lethal weapon to lethal weapon three, what women want.
That's the right.
Is this favorite movie?
Yeah.
He loves because it's like a, it's right around when Mel Gibson got trouble.
So he loves the three with the lethal weapons that don't feature a black lead character.
Chris, Chris Rock is in part four in, uh, in a lead role.
And then what women want?
It's a cover.
Huh?
I knew you're right.
Oh, jeez.
How's wrong with you?
I kept trying to put it together.
What you were saying.
And then I was like, I think Joe thinks, uh, I thought that joke was smarter than I, than
it did.
Oh, well, it's good.
I think they just should have picked different Mel Gibson pictures that don't prominently feature
of a black hero in them.
Yeah.
That's true.
Shit.
And well, um, any who I recall enjoying Zohan quite a bit.
Homest gag.
A lot of hummus jokes.
Yeah.
They're like pouring it in their drinks and stuff.
It's pretty gross.
It's funny.
Yeah.
No, it's gross.
Um, was that written by Smigel Sandler and appetite?
Smigel and appetite executive producer.
I don't know if they wrote it or not.
Smigel did.
I don't know.
But I'll tell you that.
I think it was.
No, I think Sandler in the guy, you know, like I think it's his like classic.
The guy that wrote co -wrote and directed Madison and co -wrote and directed Gilmore and co,
you know, like that guy.
The human guy.
I'm looking it up, Joe.
All right.
Why don't you look that up?
Okay.
Um, is there a love interest in Zohan?
Yeah.
Really hot.
Oh, yeah.
The growth of mantra.
Oh, what?
Like Sandler's Spargo Apatel.
All right.
God, I'm sick of being right.
Sick of it.
I'm sick of it, too.
Uh, yeah.
The growing it is, uh, she manual chicory.
Yeah.
And she will be playing a lot of lang in the new.
Superman and Lois TV show.
Okay.
That explores the problems of a superhero trying to raise a family.
Whew.
All right.
Oof.
Anyway.
Uh, I, I do recommend that people watch silly funny things during this time.
It can help.
It's been the only thing that can pull a laugh out of me these days.
Um, I saw, let's go to last the Mohicans, which I had not seen in ages.
I watched the definitive director's cut.
Michael Mann is a guy where like half the people say Miami vice is a masterpiece.
And the director's cut ruins it.
The other half who love it.
Say the director's cut is a masterpiece.
The real version of it.
Do it with every one of Michael Mann's movies.
Really director's cuts to me mean you didn't get your movie ready in time for its theatrical release.
Uh, and now you want more money to do the same thing twice.
I mean, that's usually the case.
Uh, it's certainly the case with Copola, who's now just like, uh, geez.
The winery is not pulling in what it used to.
Let me reboot Godfather 3.
But I do want to see the new recut version comes out next week.
14 bucks on Amazon for the Blu -ray right now.
And I'm going to watch the thing proving that I am a sucker who helps these people do these things.
But last the Mohicans, the director's cut tends to be the slightly preferred version.
Um, it's one of those things where you can't find the original anymore, which is rough.
Somebody told me it was on Hulu.
It might be, but, um, you can't like buy the Blu -ray of the movie that you saw in loved in theaters.
It's the same thing with 40 -year -old version.
You can only buy the like uncensored version with 20 minutes of additional scenes in a comedy that's already two hours.
So last the Mohicans is an awesome movie.
I don't usually like that period, I guess.
It just kind of boars me.
But the action is relentless Daniel Day Lewis, who you might know from the New York Times 25 greatest actors list.
Number three, he's really good in it.
Kind of the, Amy, he's playing a, he's not a Mohican.
He's just a guy who was raised by Mohicans, but he's, it's kind of the most normal he's been.
You know, I'm so used to seeing him talking with crazy voices and stuff, gangs in New York, and there'll be blood and all that.
So he's very good in it.
Madeline Stowe remains one of my all -time movie crushes.
She's great in the film as well.
Or she bit.
You know, it's, the business is not kind on the old, as you said earlier, John.
She's, she's probably the same age or younger than Daniel Day Lewis, but he's working.
She's not.
Madeline Stowe and Pacific Heights.
Woo!
You're thinking of an lawful entry?
An lawful entry.
Woo!
Yeah, she's unbelievable in them, which is a good movie too.
I love Blast the Mohicans.
I thought it had some shots that I just paused and looked at.
There's a scene where they're all like trying to escape underneath a waterfall that's incredible.
There's all these battle scenes that look like paintings.
Michael Mann is the shit.
In the 90s, he did Blast the Mohicans, followed by heat, followed by the insider.
That is a run close to unequaled.
I know a few people have, have had longer, better runs, but that's a really impressive run of films.
I love the film.
Go ahead, John.
She goes out with Brian Ben -Ben.
Does she?
Good for him.
I think.
Well, here's her with Mill Gibson.
No, actually, that is right, because I have looked up her marital status before.
Not that I've had a chance, but yeah.
I like that guy.
And different.
Based on my love of Zohan.
Yeah.
And I thought to myself, here's a movie where one of my favorite comedy actors,
who I felt fell from grace, played a character with an accent and a crazy wig.
And I didn't really want to see it because I thought it's going to suck.
And then I watched it and I loved it.
And then why not give a shot just like this to another movie I've written off for years.
And maybe I'll be pleasantly surprised again.
So I turned on Mike Myers, the love guru.
Oh, wow.
I got as far as the Indian sit -hard cover of nine to five.
Yeah, I remember that.
That opens the film.
And I shut it off and I'll never look at it ever again.
There's no way the movie is good.
I saw the picture in theaters.
And it was walkouts left and right at the free writers guild theater.
People were like, uh, audible groans.
You know, at certain jokes.
Talk about Mike Myers.
Well passed.
Well passed even his prime trying to convince us that he's dating Jessica Alba.
And talk about a hard left turn.
I mean, this is like a year after Austin powers three.
Yeah.
Like this is it.
He did this and then that was it.
Like, well, it's crazy that it shut him down.
Because I mean, I don't know anybody alive who wouldn't kind of want to see a new Austin power is pictured.
But, uh, like I liked him in, um, in glorious bastards.
And there's a guy in the crown who completely reminds me of that character.
Like I think Mike Myers could very easily age into a beloved British character actor.
And people would say that's crazy, but I'm watching the undoing last night.
And I'm like, Nicole Kidman, Hugh Grant, and Noah Joupe, this kid playing a New York family are all British actors.
Right.
Which is just absurd to me.
You never see it go the other way.
But that's the only thing I could see Mike Myers doing is either come back with an Austin powers or just be a character guy.
You tried to do it with 54, but you needed to be the star.
Maybe you're not going to be the star anymore.
Well, he was.
He didn't receive praise for 54, even though it's not a very good movie.
And he did.
He's in, um, uh, bohemian rhapsody in that way.
He plays the.
That's true.
Pretty, uh, you know, whatever the exec.
Uh, so that's British character role.
That's right. Yeah.
Yeah.
Maybe that's what he will do.
Uh, I've heard he's a notorious asshole.
But I mean, uh, for the Wayne's worlds and the Austin powers is alone.
I think the man deserves a special place in American comedy.
So I'm married next murder is fucking funny.
Yeah.
Joe, I watched, uh, I mean, when I say an F, I'm talking about an F minus.
I'm talking about one of the worst pictures I've seen in a very long time.
And you'll see it up, uh, up the Oscars this year.
He'll billy allergy.
And this thing is getting trashed.
The fact that we're still doing an Oscars when there's going to be like six movies
to choose from is.
It's crazy to me.
I think it's going to be hilarious.
And they believe this is the year they've added a category too, right?
Well, they added most popular film and then they pulled it when they realize how
that completely diminished what they do and have done for a hundred years.
Yeah.
He'll billy allergy is bad.
It's bad.
And it is bad from the jump.
The dialogue is horrible.
Glenn Close is playing her role with the subtlety of Vicky Lawrence's
mama on Mama's family.
She, and by the way, you know, I love Mama's family, but that is a multi -cam sitcom.
This is supposed to be an Oscar bait serious drama about drug addiction.
So Glenn Close, as she's playing, want to make sure I get the character's name right,
Mama with two W's.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Amy Adams plays her daughter.
And then in the worst lead performance I've seen since the heyday of Sam Worthington,
Gabriel Basso announces himself as a talent to be reckoned with.
He's the son who goes to Yale, but he keeps being brought back by his family drama,
this hillbilly family.
Who's Gabriel Basso?
I had never heard of him looking now.
He was in super eight and I guess he was the voice in a film called Scared Shrekless,
which I believe is a direct to video Shrek holiday offering.
But yeah, Scared Shrekless, a play on Scared Shitless.
Do you, I'm going to come back to this, and I'm sorry if I said this on the show,
but Tim Hurtin wanted to name Beetlejuice.
Beetlejuice.
I'll say it no more, because I don't want him to come, but the studio Warner Brothers
was like, look, we can't call a major motion picture Beetlejuice.
And you sort of get it because now the name just kind of rolls off the tongue,
but it is a gross thing.
So Tim Hurtin is like, what do you want it to be?
And they're like, well, we want to give you the freedom to come up with something.
So he comes up with the name Scared Sheetless.
Oh my God.
As a joke, and he thought, I'm going to give this to them.
They'll say, okay, you're right.
If this is the best you can do, let's go back to Beetlejuice.
He turns it in, and they fucking loved it.
Oh my God.
They were like, that's it.
Baby, you've done it again, Tim.
And then he had to fight them.
And they're like, but you picked the name.
And he was like, it was a trick that didn't work.
Anyway, this kid, Gabriel Basso.
I just looked him up here and he's from St. Louis, Missouri.
I always tried to root for my own, St. Louis, Missouri.
But it's a really, really bad performance.
And the movie, I'll say you have to see it to believe it.
But I don't want you to see it.
I had a buddy ask me last night, hey, is that thing funny or funny bad?
I mean, I'm sorry.
Is that thing bad or funny bad?
And I was like, it's both, but it's not like the room or something
where you're, it's much like the Danzig movie.
You just feel like you've wasted your time.
You don't like laugh.
Like, I can't believe this thing.
It's not like that.
It's just a really bad picture.
All right.
And directed by Ron Howard.
You know who, aside from me liking him as a person
in every interview and everything I've ever heard about him
has been positive.
He's made a lot of really good movies.
And he did the actor -to -director thing better than anybody.
But I think this is sort of an announcement that it's enough.
Because no true salad director, I don't think
would make this movie.
He might be past his prime.
I'll close this out with a positive on Mike Myers.
I did a rewatch Wayne's World 2.
Love it.
I don't love it, but liked it.
Some big laughs in it.
It leans a little too heavy into the spoof curve.
You know, the first one doesn't do that.
The first one's just its own thing.
This one, there's a lot of scenes that are like,
there's the Jurassic Park scene that kind of makes no sense.
Yeah.
You know, there's a lot of that in this.
That I didn't care for.
I remember as a kid seeing this and loving the,
when he has to fight Tia Carrera's dad
and it's like the Bad Kung Fu movie.
I used to watch that over and over and over.
Yeah.
Now I'm just like, oh, God, this is bad.
But overall, I really enjoyed the movie.
They're both great in it.
Kim Basinger is great in it.
Tia Carrera is great in it.
Take me, Goth.
Where?
I'm a little on gas and you need a jacket.
Yeah.
My favorite scene and I laughed.
Well, my favorite two scenes.
The number one remains the Kevin Pollock eye scene.
Very funny.
I mean, it's just, it's just great.
Which is not the lowercase J's,
which he did read.
He basically read it in Austin Powers 3 with Fred Savage
with the mall.
Yeah.
It's just great.
And then my second favorite scene was,
you know, there's the running thing in the movie
where he keeps getting brought into the desert by Jim Morrison
and like in the door of the movie.
And like the fourth time he goes to the desert,
Jim Morrison is there talking to Sammy Davis Jr.,
played by Tim Meadows.
Yeah.
And he's just, he's,
it's just an absurd interpretation of Sammy.
It's great.
And then he goes, I gotta go, man,
I gotta go hang with some cats.
Yeah.
We, I mean, just be glad they didn't bring in Billy Crystal
in blackface to play because I'm sure he angled to get the part.
I swear to you for a second,
I wasn't sure if it was him or not,
because it was such a ridiculous impression.
I was like, yeah.
They could Billy Crystal to do this.
I just wanted to give a quick shout out to Tim Meadows.
Tim Meadows never connected for me on SNL.
Like I kind of liked the ladies' man,
but he just never really connected.
And he has become one of the most welcome people to see in a comedy.
He is so funny and walk hard.
He is, he steals pop star.
Yeah.
He just, every time, he stole Heuby Halloween,
him and my Rudolph.
I love seeing the man.
He's so funny to me.
Yeah. He's a guy you drop him in
and like, he's, he's burning rubber through the scene.
Yeah.
But anyway, it's a fun movie.
I got instantly sad at the end when they pull off Wayne's stock.
And you see a crowd of very happy people listening to Aerosmith
at an open air concert.
And you remember what life was once like.
Right.
Also got sad at the donut shop scene.
Remembering what it was like to hang out in a place you love with friends.
Yeah.
Or like, I got sad all the scenes with Rip Torn
because I used to hang out with him so much.
Rip Taylor.
Rip Taylor, sorry.
Yes.
It's okay.
That's okay.
And then Ed O 'Neill has a great cameo as the crazy donut shop guy.
He's hilarious in the first one.
Why do they come to me to die?
It's what a creepy line.
Yeah.
What's in the first one?
I think I have this one.
I can do the whole movie of Wayne's world so I won't.
But when he pulls the camera aside and he's like,
I've never done a crazy thing in my life until that night.
You remember that one?
Yeah.
He goes, why is it when you kill a man?
What's the line?
Well, why is it when you kill a man in the heat of battle?
It's called heroic.
But when you kill a man in the heat of passion, it's called a crime.
And we're kind of doing the movie over here.
Pull it away.
Very, very funny stuff.
But who plays the asshole record exec in the first one?
And the second one, it's walking.
Frankie Sharp of Sharp Records.
It's a nobody.
It's just kind of a big fat guy.
But no, who's the guy through the movie?
Oh, it's Rob Lowe.
Who's right in that movie?
Oh, he takes over the station.
That's what it is.
Well, Joe.
And you see who's on my shirt, Greg?
Oh, I can't see.
Well, I'll rip my headphones out if I stand.
It's wine and garth, and it says excellent.
Oh, nice.
Yeah.
They should do a third Wayne's world.
You know, they got them back for like an MTV movie awards, cold open.
And like, there were already guys playing 10 years younger.
So like, I mean, you could do a Bill and Ted, I guess,
but you'd have to address their age.
On the MTV thing, they were still trying to be 22 or something.
They did it on the last SNL anniversary show, too.
Yeah.
And it was fun.
It was funny, you know.
Yeah, you know, but anyway, it's an enjoyable film.
Tia Carrera is enough to make you, you know,
make you fall to your knees and thank God you're a man.
Lover.
And they had in the first one they had the great joke that she learned
English through the police academy movies.
Right.
I thought that was so funny.
Yeah.
Okay.
So yeah, you don't need my take.
But Wayne's world is one of my favorite comedies.
And I thought Wayne's world too was great.
I'm scared to revisit it because of Joe said that Carrera
is saying and funny.
I don't know.
I also used to love the village people saying.
I bet that didn't hold up too well.
No, no, no, no.
That scene was still funny because the naked Indie
and the keeps taking him into see Jim Morrison is part of the village
people all of a sudden.
Yeah.
Now, that's seen still funny.
No, the Carrera scene, the only reason it's not funny now is because
you've seen that done so many fucking times where it's like
get it like the dubbing is bad and when you know it's just kind of
right.
And it goes on for too long.
That's all.
I watched the new showtime documentary called Belushi.
It is about John Belushi.
And working title was overrated.
I got to tell you, I was halfway through the thing and I'm going
I don't need to hear another word about John Belushi
as long as I live.
Documentary is perfectly fine.
It's perfunctory.
It tells the story.
It's got some funny clips.
But yeah, like Heather came in and she was like,
do you love John Belushi?
Like I've never heard you talk about him.
And I had to really just sit down and think about it.
And I said, no, I don't.
And she said, but you love the Blues Brothers.
I do.
I love Animal House too.
But I do not love John Belushi.
I think if you go back and watch those S and L sketches,
they'd go on for 12 minutes with him going cheeseburger, cheeseburger,
cheeseburger, my dad used to do that when he'd make dinner.
Cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger.
It's what is funny about this.
What is funny?
What was funny?
I guess everybody was on drugs.
I always say, I go, you watch those old S and Ls and you're like,
this is what this was hilarious when you were sad home
in a Saturday night and did lines and smoked puff.
You know what I mean?
And this guy comes out as a samurai like,
oh, what the fuck?
It was so of its time.
And, you know, he doesn't come off as being a particularly cool dude.
You know, it's not the kind of thing like with candy or,
I'm sorry, John Candy or Chris Farley,
where everything you ever hear about them is that they were the sweetest people
and they just couldn't stop themselves.
And he couldn't stop themselves.
But he comes off in a lot of these interactions just being an asshole.
And I don't know.
I watch the whole thing.
If you're curious in his life, check it out.
But, you know, it's really not that good, a doc.
Yeah, yeah, I just say.
I went, we had a running joke on Bonfire radio show.
I wanted to get a shirt made that said Jim Belushi was the good one.
I still might get that made.
That's a funny shirt.
Well, it's like I was telling you the other day, Joe,
like, Belushi's a perfect can't, like we'll never see a documentary accurate.
But, you know, who's way funnier and had a much longer and more interesting career,
including writing as well as acting, including coming up with Crystal Skull Vodka
in a Crystal Skull head and Acroid.
So we'll never get it because he didn't die at 32, like John Belushi did.
Right.
And I was telling you, I talked to a buddy who was, we were playing a Zoom poker game
and he very casually said that, well, obviously Nirvana is better than the Rolling Stones,
but blah, blah, blah.
So I said, well, look, let's just look at it from, like,
let's put together a list for Rolling Stone here or something, the magazine.
Take our personal views aside, Nirvana made three albums.
He died at 27 years old.
The Rolling Stones have been making number one albums for 50 plus years.
So the two can't even really be compared,
but for you to dismissively say obvious Nirvana is better.
I'm like, what kind of music, what kind of shit do you think Kirk Cobain would be making now?
What kind of music do you think Chris Novicellic, who was a fucking Trump head at this point,
would be making now?
It's not going to be great stuff, guys.
It's not going to have the consistency that the Rolling Stones had not to the present,
but they had for 40 years.
So I think...
I'm not going to Stone's fan and I think that's a ridiculous thing that guy said.
There's this weird thing.
My example is with Joe, if Paul Giamatti died after sideways,
we'd always talk about him as being one of the greats.
But because now he's on a show, this billion show,
and he's putting money on his family's table,
and he's taking the job he's got to take,
we'll never think that about him.
I mean, talking about a guy that should have been on that list.
Absolutely.
Just carrying projects for years now.
Yeah, but in their mind, he sold out by doing a TV show.
It's weird to me.
Well, Pat, why don't we get to the movie at hand today?
It's one that, quite frankly,
I haven't really looked forward to discussing,
but I have a lot to say about it.
Yeah.
And about what it speaks to in the horror genre these days.
Little piece of magic called The Lodge,
done by the same cats that did Good Night Mommy,
which I also did not speak highly of on this show.
I don't recall exactly what I said,
but I recall liking it to some degree
and finding it kind of disturbing and creepy fun,
but not a great movie.
So The Lodge is a picture about a dad who has two children,
whom he loves very much.
He is divorced from his wife portrayed by Alicia Silverstone.
Great to see her again.
Great to see her.
At the beginning of the film,
he tells Alicia Silverstone that he's taking the kids to the cabin,
or The Lodge, that they own, or whatever,
or their vacation lodge, for Christmas,
and that he's bringing his girlfriend,
which obviously upsets his ex -wife,
and then he breaks the news to his ex -wife
that he will be marrying this girlfriend.
At which point, Alicia Silverstone returns to her home,
sobs at her dining room table,
and in one of the most alarming scenes I've seen
in a while in a horror movie,
blows her brains out.
What was on that?
That scene made me think,
okay, those guys showed a lot of promise last time.
Now they've made their masterpiece.
So I was so on fire after that scene.
I was like, that made me the whole theater jumped.
I thought it was terrifying.
And yes, go on.
Yeah, and you're like, here we go.
Yeah.
And then what happens is as they all go up to the lodge,
sorry, I'm interrupting, but sort of a similar
to like a scream or a psychotype trick,
where you're killing off the biggest star.
You know, so I thought I was going to see a movie
with no stars in it, and you're like, oh shit.
And so just like they killed Drew Barrymore,
and they killed Janet Lee, very early on,
it was doubly shocking for that reason.
So they all go up to this cabin,
and the kids seem to suspect they don't like the girlfriend.
They're clearly bitter that the dad is left the mom.
They don't want to get along with the girlfriend.
And they start to slowly dig to try to find proof
that this woman is a problem or has a sorted past.
For any ammunition they can use against her.
And they start to find things that she was in,
you know, this weird religious cult,
and she does have kind of a murky past.
And it is questionable.
But the woman is putting her best foot forward,
and you're kind of led as the viewer to believe
that's behind her, and she isn't evolved human now
and whatever, but they get snowed in.
Her medication that she's on is unable to be refilled,
or the supply runs out, or whatever happens.
And all of a sudden now, things start to get worse
and worse and worse and worse.
The father leaves to go back to the city to tend to business.
And now the kids are stuck there, no phone,
no way to communicate, no way to get out.
They're running out of food.
And this woman is getting crazier and crazier
with each passing moment because she doesn't ever meds.
And put paws.
Yeah.
This was one of the last movies I saw in the theater.
I saw it as part of the LA Film Fest at the Egyptian.
And basically, I spent the entire time thinking that it was a great set up
and a great, it was being executed very well,
and I was very into it for about half the time.
So I saw it a very long time ago, almost a year ago.
And when Joe was explaining just up to that point now,
like the halfway -ish point, I was like,
this sounds fucking awesome.
I was able to, since I haven't seen it in so long,
step back and recognize all the elements were there.
For a great movie.
Go on.
Yeah.
And you're kind of waiting to see what's happening here.
Is there something super, because weird things are happening.
Yeah.
And you're, is the place haunted?
Is something supernatural afoot?
What's going on?
And you're waiting for that big twist,
or the triumphant climax, where the dad returns and saves the kids,
or something.
Yeah.
And what ends up happening is, is the dad finally catches
wind of what's going on.
He rushes back to the cabin.
He is immediately killed by the crazy girlfriend.
And the movie ends with her, or the insinuation of her,
sitting around the table with them,
and she's going to now kill them.
She's going to shoot them both.
And that's your move.
Got the dad's dead body propped up,
and sin taped over his face, which is what they had.
At the, at the cult she was in.
And that really is the movie.
The, the, the crazier part that maybe you're leaving out
intentionally, I don't know.
But is that the kids, when she wakes up, try to convince her,
or at first you don't know what's happened.
But it's January 9th.
The presents are gone.
The dad is gone.
She's like, oh, okay, Christmas is over.
And correct me if I have this wrong.
But she's like, oh, okay, Christmas is over.
But what happened?
And the kids like, well, I dreamed about a gas leak in the house.
I'm worried we were all passed out for all this time.
Right.
Then it turns out they were playing this like gas lighting trick
on her where they hid all their stuff in the attic
and they were just trying to fuck with her.
This is such an elaborate plan that they go through.
And the, and when it ends, you're just sitting there.
And for me anyway, I spent every one of the last 45 minutes
of this movie going, but wait a minute.
What?
But wait.
And I kept going back to, okay, but that doesn't make sense.
And then as you think each new thing is going to be explained,
it just doesn't.
And the fact that these kids could be this diabolical
to construct a scheme where they convince her it's the future.
And then.
And that she's losing.
It's all, it's all the time to make her crack
because they want to break this woman because they don't,
they resent her.
And for obvious reasons, they resent her.
But it's also not this woman's fault, you know.
It's not like that she was having an affair with this guy.
He's divorced.
But yeah, it's, they're trying to provoke her
and get her to kind of break.
And then they finally come clean.
And they sort of come clean just as she's completely coming unglued.
And that's that.
It all ends on a very sour, sad, dark note.
There is no payoff.
I hate a movie where it's where in the end, it's like,
oh, exactly what you said at minute 22 is what happened.
Yeah.
It was just a misdirection for the last 90 minutes for me to wonder
to, for me to think that wasn't going to happen.
And then it just happened.
I don't care for that.
But my, as you can tell by my tone, I didn't like the movie.
I really didn't.
I was much like you very much in for a while.
And then all of a sudden, I was like, what the fuck?
Come on, man.
And then the end was just so hopeless.
And, you know, look, have a hopeless ending on your movie.
Fine.
I don't give a shit.
But make it interesting at least.
You know, this is so point A, just to point B directly with action
and occurrences that just take you off the path,
that distract you from the path you're on for two seconds.
They don't lead to anything new.
They don't open any new doors.
And in the end, it's another one of these horror movies
that is being so celebrated right now, or the type of horror movie
that's being so celebrated right now.
I'm sick of this shit.
I'm sick of, but the humans are the real monsters.
I'm sick of the emotional depressing journey of this
is what the real horror comes from.
I'm sick of nobody wins.
Everybody loses.
It's all just depraved and sad.
I hate it.
It's why I hate Ariaster and his, I hate his films.
I don't hate him.
It's why I don't like that.
It's very prominent right now in horror.
And you see these things being marketed as horror movies.
And then when you sort of, you know, I never saw it,
but it comes at night comes to mind.
I never saw it because I heard, no, it's another one of these things
where nothing really happens and it's just a sad portrayal
of a bunch of people stuck in a shitty situation or whatever.
Yeah, I missed that one too.
But you just see these trailers for these things that are being marked.
You know, I liked the mother, but mother is another one.
These things get marketed as horror films.
And then when you do like the tiniest bit of research,
you're like, this isn't a horror film.
This is a very, very dark melodrama.
And it's just a wholly depressing experience.
And I don't dig it, man.
I'm not into it.
Yeah, I would certainly not recommend this to anyone who is struggling now.
It is a very depressing movie.
And when I saw it in the theater, this is one of those L .A.
Like at the Egyptian, it's all film nerds.
And the screen is usually very rowdy and fun and have guests and everything.
And every other screening of the festival was that,
no matter how dark the movie was.
But after this one, everyone just kind of stayed in their seat a little too long
and nobody seemed to even want to get up.
And I looked at my buddy I saw it with and we were both just like, ugh.
It just leaves you feeling gross.
Oops, sorry.
Which can be fine.
I mean, that's horror can leave you feeling gross.
I love to reddit area in midsummer.
I consider those horror, you know, it's kind of semantics.
But I love those movies.
I thought they had way more going on than this.
This movie doesn't really even have any themes that it's working with.
It's just kind of misery for misery's sake.
And almost like the new thing instead of torture porn back in the day back from 10 years ago,
the new thing is kind of emotional porn.
These like really violent, emotional, horrific things happening to people.
And if I'm being honest, that interests me more always.
But when it's done badly, it sucks.
And this movie does eventually suck.
When I read the Wikipedia page, they said that the people who did Good Night Mommy got the script loved it,
but said we knew immediately we had to rewrite the ending because it just didn't work.
So it does make you wonder if maybe that ending made a little more sense.
If maybe that might have been a better option because what we have here certainly doesn't work.
I don't know why they would have even thought that it did.
But what annoys me about this stuff is not even the grind of just them being kind of depressing.
Is that the big thing now is to leave everything blank.
So when I looked at or not answer any questions.
So when I looked up on Rotten Tomatoes, what this movie got, it was like an 80 % tons of good reviews.
And it was just saying over and over.
Look, just don't go in expecting to have every little thing explained.
And you'll be great.
Treat it like the old geolos where, you know, it's not important what happened, you know.
And no, because those were at least fun to look at.
That's exactly right.
I was just like, that's not a good comparison.
All of you are basically what they're saying in their review is I didn't understand this movie.
And I'm still saying I love it so that I can seem smart.
And I think what happens is people are scared to say these movies suck because it makes them seem not artsy or whatever.
But sometimes I guarantee if you pin the director down they would have no fucking idea what their own movie is about.
And I think this is kind of that case.
There's nothing confident about it.
I will say Riley Kio, I have loved and everything.
She was in Soderbergh show, the girlfriend experience, which I loved.
And I just think she's a great actress.
She's very good in this.
As a Silverstone, as are the kids.
But we didn't work.
Nope.
Didn't work.
Hogs down.
Big dogs down.
Oh, sorry.
Next episode is going to be maximum overdrive.
Did we like it?
Did we hate it?
You'll just have to tune in to see.
In the meantime, let me plug away.
The Joey Rose's sandwich shop pop up is now open at the stand in New York City Wednesday to Friday 12 to 4.
Come on by get a delicious sandwich.
Eight sandwiches for eight bucks a piece.
You will not be let down.
I promise you.
And the no pressure network has launched myself.
Sal Volcano and Chris the Stefano have launched a podcast network.
There is a no pressure network channel on YouTube.
Our launch shows are hay babe featuring Chris and Sal and taste buds.
A show where Sal and I debate foods.
Both of them available.
As you are listening to this, the in fact launched the everything launched today December 1st.
So go check it out.
Subscribe to us on YouTube.
Subscribe to us on Instagram.
Subscribe to us on Twitter.
Each show has got their own handle and you'll find it.
And also follow me.
Joey Rose a comedy on Instagram and Twitter.
And I hope you will all join us for the taste buds experience and the no pressure experience as you've joined us for this experience.
Thank you.
I am the Patrick Walsh occasionally at Twitter and at Instagram.
And I just posted before the holiday a hour long Pat's movie corner solo Thanksgiving edition.
So give that a listen if you want some bonus content.
It's a real long rambling one all over the place.
A lot of movies talked about in that time.
And that's all I got.
We will see you back here for the next episode which is Maximum Overdrive.
And then we are more than likely going to do our Christmas episodes.
Which I think Joe should we just announce Fat Man as one of those episodes?
Well it could be Fat Man.
It's not going to be available outside of renting.
So you know I know we try that.
We try to not do something that's only you know that you could stream.
That's right.
Let's wait till Fat Man comes out on Hulu which will probably be January or something.
But let's figure it out.
Maybe we will be making people pay money for the stuff.
We haven't done a Q &A in a long time.
Maybe we'll do a Q &A episode and then a Christmas film or something.
Sounds great.
That's it folks.
See you next time.
And we'll see you in hell.