I'll see you on the train.
Curse film season two.
Our review may episode two.
Joe. Oh, shit. Yeah.
May episode two.
God damn.
I know you always hit me in the car in the way home when I correct you on the air,
but I had to do it or at least raise the hand.
Yeah, give you an old, uh, hey, why don't you shut up like in, uh,
the most awkward scene ever in gun hole.
Remember that part with Keaton and the wife at dinner?
No, what do you place the wife in gun hole?
In my head, it's Annie McDowell in every Keaton movie, but it's not.
It's not they're not actually married.
Wait, Keaton and gun host that tells his wife to shut up at their, yeah,
they're talking at the, they're at the dinner.
They're at like the Japanese guys house for dinner.
And they're like having like a sort of heated discussion about where the company
needs to go.
Okay. And his wife goes, well, what if you guys just said this and he goes,
Hey, why don't you shut up?
Wow.
And it's like this, it's very awkward.
And then like they're driving home afterwards in the car.
And she's, you know, yeah, you know, and he's like, I'm sorry.
I just, you know, it's pretty, pretty rough scene.
The, uh, it's, it's Mimi Rogers, the gorgeous, maybe Rogers.
I just rewatch a little bonus movie corner here.
I just rewatched Mr. Mom last night.
I love it, but can't rewatch it because of Martin Moles appearance in the film.
I don't want to trigger myself.
Well, I actually wanted to give you some good news about that.
Mole is such an unlikable prick in the, in through the entire movie and looks
like such in life, well, that's what I mean.
Well, I'm saying though, but like in life, he's so unlikable through the movie
and comes out looking like such an ass in the end.
You, I think you would revel in like, okay, I'll get back to it.
It's been a long time.
I'll get back to it.
But he's so I'm like, he was wrote that one.
I didn't know that.
Yeah, John, he was wrote Mr. Mom in a weekend.
Great line though.
I forgot.
I forgot when he's, he's, his, he's got the, I mean, when I was a kid, I hated
the sequence where he goes to shit and upset me.
Now that I'm older, it's my favorite part of the movie when he gets depressed
and grows the beard and like, uh, and he's in the, uh, he's in the bedroom,
a Terry Gar, and she's like, what's with the beard?
Cause she, you know, she's trying to be like your, your fallen apart here.
Yeah.
And he's like, hun, just an awkward phase right now.
It's in that middle stage when this comes in, it's going to look, and he goes,
who's that movie star?
And she goes, Orson Wells, and he goes, he does this laugh where he goes.
And he goes, oh, I get it.
Cause I put out a few pounds or so well.
Yeah.
She goes, he grabs a blanket and a pillow and she goes, where are you going?
And with a mouth full of pizza, he goes, I'm going to go downstairs and see
for the fat couch if I could fit through the door.
All right.
Yeah.
I got to check that one out again.
Uh, classic key.
Have you guided us into the movie corner already?
No, I was just saying a bonus outside of the movie corner.
I'm just going to throw one at you.
Fair enough, fair enough.
Talk about, uh, how much I enjoyed seeing Keaton in, in Mr. Mom last night.
I understand.
Yeah.
Uh, is Tambor in Mr. Mom?
Yes.
Yeah.
He plays a guy.
What a cast.
He plays a guy named, oh, God, I got to look it up.
His character's name is ridiculous.
It is, it is really funny when you look at like basically any movie made before
the year 2000, it like you can go from the first person on the call sheet
down to like the 20th person on the cast and they will all be white people.
Yeah.
It's one of the white, it's a big, uh, Jeffrey Tambor.
Damn, please have man named Jinx Latheman.
Wow.
That's a big swing.
Uh, it says Christopher Lloyd is in it.
I do think he's in it briefly.
I don't really remember.
But, uh, you know, Terry Garret or most charming and wonderful and Gillian.
Remember, Anne Gillian?
I do remember, Anne Gillian.
Um, from, from, uh, it's a living fame, uh,
Anne Gillian plays like a sort of sex pot divorcee.
It's very funny in it.
Frederick Culler plays the oldest of the kids and he's really great in it.
Um, yeah, it's a great flick, man.
It's a great, directed by a guy named Stan Dragati.
Yeah.
And what else they do?
Like, easy money or something?
Like he did.
What?
Uh, uh, Mr. Mom, the man with one red shoe.
She's out of control.
Ooh, boy.
And ready for this necessary roughness.
Yikes.
That's their roughness is better than the dance of the Milano vehicle.
I'll tell you that much.
His first out of control is a nightmare of a movie.
Do you remember my stepmother as an alien?
Oh, yeah, it's, again, it's another, I say this a lot,
but it's another one of those movies that even as, as a kid,
I was like, this could be sucks.
Same.
I, around the same time I rented, she's out of control.
And, uh, the one I just mentioned and it's like,
there were some comedies back then that were just
unbelievably terrible.
I guess that still happens to this day, but
my God, just like things you couldn't even believe.
You know what?
I saw the other day when I had this point, it's been your earth girls are easy.
Never liked it.
Scott, it's moments, but like there's like three musical numbers.
You can't do three musical numbers.
You can do 10 or you can do one.
Yeah, one is like a joke.
You can't, you're either a musical or you're not,
but you can't do three musical numbers.
That was Hollywood's lesson and don't let
Julie Browne steer the ship.
Yeah.
Um,
man, I now I need to look up the film career of Julie Brown.
You know, she was in that, she was, you know,
she was like an MTV VJ that like caught fire.
I know, but she was on the edge, which was actually a pretty funny sketch show
with Jennifer Aniston that I watched around the time at the Ben Stillers show.
I mean,
she was what it was.
Plump fiction.
This was a spoof of pulp fiction.
Yeah, I remember that.
Oh my god.
terrible.
That came out when a repossessed came out around that.
No, the repossess was earlier, but that was when all those like direct to video
spoof were happening when like naked gun took off and then like they would just do
these direct to video spoof.
I got to be real.
I rented repossessed several times, multiple times.
Loved it as a kid sent.
And it scared me also as many companies did because I had seen actual horror movies.
But I talked on the solo corner that I do on Patreon the other day about revisiting naked
guns who want to have right before I left LA on my break.
A buddy of mine and I went out and he was talking about how he's seen naked gun a thousand times
and it's one of the funniest ways ever.
He was, it's crazy too because I never saw either of the sequels.
We were on like tequila three and I was like we are going back to my house right now.
And again, movies have a hard battle with me these days because I am,
I'm deeply depressed.
But it was the first time the movie did not feel like a classic to me.
It was the first time that I thought there's no competition between one and two.
One is a much much better movie.
I always thought one was a better movie, but I too, the jokes and two,
I mean, God damn, they hit the thing is, one is a perfect movie.
It's perfect.
Two is not perfect, but the jokes that hit, hit harder, when they hit, they're,
they're a little higher hits.
Harder hits too.
They do.
And Nielsen's almost better in two.
He's just like fully got what his thing is at that point.
Anyway, three is, you know, you got to be in the mood for it.
You know, it's just, it's there, you know, it's there.
Joe, I'm going to give you a screaming and hot off the presses.
This just hit deadline.
I go to deadline each day to read about the entertainment news and deals and to feel bad about myself and my own failures.
And today, this one, this one just went up on deadline.
Omen prequel.
The first Omen
set up at 20th century studios.
So a directorial debut from a woman named Arcasha Stevenson.
Okay.
She's handling the writing as well.
You got David Goryer producing.
He never does anything bad, so that's exciting.
And let's look what it is.
Let's see if they give us any plot points.
It's called the first Omen.
The first Omen.
Which is so stupid.
That's why I bookmarked it.
It's about the birth of the Antichrist.
There can't be a first that there's one.
It reminds me of the last exorcism or whatever.
I'm like, what do you mean the last ex?
How can you make that claim?
But okay.
So Stevenson, the director, you know her from her short film Pineapple, which debuted at the 2017 Sundance
Film Festival, right?
Anyway, they sold...
Oh no, they did brand new cherry flavor.
Which was at least interesting.
This has no details about the film at all.
So I thought I was going to have some hot new scoop for you.
Anyway, they're making the first Omen.
Sorry, I didn't read that until now, but...
And it's a prequel to the Gregory Peck Omen.
They're acting like the Leab Shriver Omen didn't happen.
Well, that's just a remake.
It's the same.
I think the writer didn't even get credit on the remake.
Yeah, that's just a remake, so that makes sense.
But I mean,
they're...
It just doesn't make any sense.
Jesus, fucking Christ.
All right, whatever.
All right.
What are we missing in the news?
I guess, well, I know.
Oh, I got it.
How about a half hour on Roe vs. Wade?
Now, I believe that a woman's body...
I've got a perfectly awful Hollywood here for us,
that we...
This is a segment we frequently do, but when we do it,
it's usually pretty fun.
But I mean, this her depth trial.
I bet that's it.
This is outrageous shit going on in this thing.
Wild.
I had to pull out.
I was like,
what I want somebody listening to every detail
of my relationship now.
I mean, it's crazy.
The amount of exposure this thing is getting.
But I get it.
Several clips of depth and his lawyers laughing hysterically.
There's a new clip out now
where herds on the stand and she claims
an untrue claim that a depth hit his first wife,
which his first wife has come to his defense already.
And they cut to the lawyer
who turns to the legal team
and goes, like, pumps his fist
because now that the ex -wife has been named on the stand,
they can now call her in as a witness.
Oh, okay.
Herds was caught plagiarizing the talented Mr. Ripley.
Now, explain this to me.
What was she saying?
Dialogue from the film to describe depth or what?
She was describing something and she says a paragraph
for five sentences long.
And there's a guy on YouTube called Mr. H. Reviews.
And he plays the video for her
and then he has the text from the talented Mr. Ripley next to it.
It's verbatim.
It's fucking insane.
And she's not quoting it.
She's just passing it off as well.
Oh, she's just talking.
She's just being like, and you know,
and when he entered the room,
the sky's parted and she's talking.
There's a clip where her attorney asks a question
to a witness.
And then the attorney goes,
and as the witness is talking,
the attorney goes,
objection, your honor here stay.
And the judge goes, it was your question.
It's bad shit.
I've never seen anything like this.
It's fucking crazy.
It does sound crazy.
I saw a clip.
Well, some of it seems fake.
When they said they thought she was snorting cocaine
out of her clean acts,
I was like, all right, now you're stretching.
Yeah. I think it can be true
that both of them are pieces of shit.
I don't know enough details to make a call.
I just think neither one of them has
the clearest of consciences throughout all this, probably.
I will say it's, he does,
it's not that it makes depth look like a saint by any stretch.
But I will say it is certainly putting a lot of holes in her case.
Because the clips I'm seeing are not clips for the most part.
It's not like clips, you know,
I referenced seeing the one on the Mr. H thing.
But like, I'm not seeing like slanted clips.
Like these are clips from like court and trial TV
or what you know what I mean?
Like it's just like, look at this thing that happened
with no narrative or anything put to it.
So we'll see what happens.
But it's, I mean, these things are,
you know, I watched like four of them.
So now my homepage, my landing page on YouTube is already,
like it's feeding it to me.
And every day I'm like, oh my god, this is wild.
Yeah, yeah, it's, I mean, 10 years ago,
this would have been the biggest story in the land.
I think basically everyone just just sees depth as a hasman at this point.
But it is fascinating.
He was one of the biggest stars we ever had for a while there.
I'll tell you this too, man.
You want to talk about nobody got out clean from this,
from this lockdown.
Two of the most beautiful people on earth,
Amber Heard and Johnny Depp, they look like shit.
Like they're, they're both bloated.
And oh, you know, like it's like everybody came out of this thing
like off their game, man.
Physically.
Somebody on that first day posted like we did it.
Johnny Depp is officially a Persian strip club DJ.
And the picture was so perfect.
It's just like, yep, that's a Persian strip club DJ.
He looks, he looks now like the guy in Tim and Eric billion dollar movie
who impersonates him at the beginning.
Yeah, yeah, like he looks like Johnny Depp, but something's a little off.
Like he's too tusky or something.
It's, you know, but anyway,
well, they use impersonators all the time.
That guy might have actually been a Johnny Depp impersonator.
He is.
I looked him up.
That's how he makes his living.
Let's take us to that movie corn.
That sweet buttery movie corn.
Mm -hmm.
I, Joe, look, I ain't seen much.
I ain't seen much.
But what did I watch?
It's not letting me log in to my letterbox.
Well, I'll do, while you look, I'll do my first one.
Please do.
I finally watched thief.
I bought it during the criterion sale based on a strong recommendation
from both Pat and my business partner, Paul, who said that's my favorite movie.
And I knew that one of the inspirations for our bar
that I'm partnered with, with Pauline was the bar and thief.
So I was like, it's kind of a crime that I not only have not seen this movie,
but that I don't own it.
So I just bought it for 20 bucks.
And boy, oh boy, what a smart purchase that was.
They don't make movies like this anymore.
There should be a box set,
a Michael Mann box set with this,
heat, and collateral.
Those are his three neo -noir movies.
Heat and thief, in particular, have so many crossover themes.
You know, it's -
For sure.
Yeah, the man who prefers to be alone doesn't want to make attachments, yeah.
Yeah, but God Almighty, what an awesome,
just an awesome, awesome movie.
James Connid is best.
You know, it's just impeccable.
Who plays the gangster?
The main gangster is a guy I love.
I can't remember his name, but he's in Hoffa.
I know it's got Farina Jim Blush.
Farina doesn't have any lines.
Farina just shows up in a car at one point, which is above her.
Yeah, Willie Nelson stellar performance.
Oh, you're talking about Robert Prosky.
Yeah.
Love that guy.
He's been in a million things.
Willie Nelson's great in it.
Balushi's great in it.
Maybe like Balushi again.
Balushi was great in a lot of things back then.
He's great in Salvador, the James Woods,
the Oliver Stone movie, and lots of chill out the show.
Do yourself a favor if you haven't seen thief.
Great flick.
It's about a thief.
Why don't you check out the quick fucking around and watch the
and Michael man, by the way, it's like it's like peak,
not peak, but you know what I mean?
It's classic Michael man.
It's everything smoky and neon and, you know, it's, you know,
I got to shout out this new season of Barry,
which is a show that I enjoyed season one.
I liked more season two.
And good Lord, they hit their stride.
They, Bill Hader directed the best episode of season two.
This very action packed insane episode of season two.
I think it was episode five.
And it was so good that they turned over the directorial reigns of all 10
episodes of season three to Bill Hader.
The guy is a is a big, big talent.
He's written himself like the showy Emmy dramatic scenes.
And he is killing them.
You don't even hate him because you know that he wrote his own stuff.
It's just like he is, we wanted to show that he is a really good actor.
He's incredible in this season.
His directing, he's the best TV director working.
And he's some, he's an SNL comic.
He's an excellent director.
I know he's a huge film buff.
He's clearly learned a lot.
So many shots in this.
There's only been two or three episodes of the new season.
But so many shots I ever wound to check out again.
Henry Winkler,
the renaissance this man has had.
He is on fire in this show.
And to me, I don't know where it goes from here.
You know, it could all fall apart.
But I'm telling you three episodes in.
Barry is the best show on TV right now.
I urge you to check it out.
It's a great show.
It really is.
I love it.
And it's funny as hell.
They're doing a lot of his girlfriend this season is doing a TV pilot.
So there's also a lot of television satire about how stupid a lot of executives are
and things like that.
That's catnip to me, obviously.
But I tell you, it reminds me of
gross point blank.
And that's very, very high compliment because it's genuinely funny.
But the danger and the action is always awesome too.
Great show.
My theme is movies from the 80s that I hadn't seen.
I think Thief was the 80s, 1980, 1980.
Might have been the late 70s.
But anyway,
81.
Year above.
And these are all three movies that I bought.
Blind faith on Blu -ray.
Because I saw a deal and I wanted it and I want to check it out.
Second one is Transformers the movie.
The animated feature from the mid 80s,
based on the popular children's cartoon.
Never saw it as a kid.
Why?
Because I heard that Optimus Prime died and I vowed that I would never watch it.
But now that I'm older, I realize that was a ballsy, dramatic turn.
And very daring only to find when I watch the special features.
Creators in the movie were like,
we didn't know kids cared and kids were traumatized
from us killing Optimus Prime.
We did it because we had to get the new line of toys out.
We had to introduce all the new characters.
Right.
But little did they know they created an incredible dramatic arc
in a children's movie by killing off a character.
Everybody loved so much.
It's just an awesome movie.
It's a lot of fun.
It's wild.
It's so weird in places.
The soundtrack is really cool.
Everybody knows the one song from Boogie Nights
that they recorded in the studio is from Transformers.
Yeah, they talk about that at length in the documentary.
And never once mentioned Boogie Nights, which is weird.
There's a whole battle sequence with Dare to Be Stupid playing in the background,
which is so weird.
But it's weird to Alice Dare to Be Stupid?
Yeah, yeah.
But it kind of makes sense.
It's hard to explain.
I can sing you the everywhere in that song right now.
That's how into weird L .I.
Well, it's an awesome song.
Highlights of the film for me were Orson Wells playing.
I'm going to sit on the crime.
Galvatron, I think his name is in the movie.
And then also Megatron,
no, I'm sorry, Megatron dies and becomes is reborn as Galvatron.
And then he comes in and Starscream challenges him.
And he
ISIS Starscream just turns him into ash.
Which if you're a Transformers fan,
you know, that's a long time coming.
That's a real big payoff there.
That's son of a bitch.
Who the fuck does what's Orson Wells' character's name?
That's what he plays a planet.
A planet -sized robot.
Imagine being the agent who's going to call Orson Wells and tell them
they've offered you the role of a planet.
Well, what's funny is,
are not funny, but like what's interesting is,
is they said that he was so sick
and in bad shape that when they recorded him,
they had to, he was just like in a chair
and like literally like in a reclined chair.
And they had to, where the fuck is this?
Why can't I find it?
They had to just put a mic up to him
and then distort his voice completely.
So, you know, so it was usable.
And like, you know, that sounds awful,
but Unicron, that's his name.
But it sounds awesome in the movie.
It actually was a lucky accident on their part.
So, pretty cool fucking flick.
Letter Nimoy voices Galvatron.
What's his name?
Judd Nelson voices Rodemus Prime,
who becomes the new leader after Optimus dies.
Peter Wilker, of course, is Optimus as always.
Frank Wilker, right?
Frank Wilker, excuse me.
It's a cool movie.
It's a really cool, and that's that cool 80s animation, man.
It's all hand drawn and it just looks great.
Very cool.
Oh, and they also say shit in the movie, which is wild.
Really?
Yeah, one of the human characters says shit.
They're liking a jam and he goes shit.
You're like, wow, that's like, why risk alienating half the parents
in the audience who would get upset about them?
I guess it just wasn't as big of a deal back then.
I don't know.
That's what that's what you think now.
Certainly, when you watch it, but yeah.
My second up and do not worry about spoilers here.
I would not do that to you, but I watched the final
seven or eight episodes of Ozark.
This was also part of my goodbye to Netflix weekend.
Look, I watched the Ozark pilot when it came out.
And I remember I had a friend visiting from Texas.
And we were like, now let's just watch this.
We're killing time before we went to the airport.
Riveted by it.
Was like, oh shit, this is great.
This is going to be one of the great shows.
I love Bateman.
I love Lenny.
Julia Garner, I like a lot who is kind of the,
became the breakout character of the show.
Four seasons in.
You know, the scene start to show a little bit.
A lot of people will talk about Ozark.
Like I've heard, and it's usually dumb people.
They're like, look, it goes sopranos.
Ozark breaking bad or something like that.
You cannot talk about Ozark in the same conversation
as the great shows of all time.
I have heard it said a lot.
Ozark is kind of a cheap show.
It's, it's gimmicky.
It's a little dumb.
Every single year, they follow the exact same pattern.
A new FBI agent comes to town who's following them.
There's a new danger in their life that they have to deal with.
It winds up being the same season four times in a row, basically.
That said, Jason Bayman is extremely funny in it.
Well, you know, dark, that dark kind of funny.
He's not trying to be funny.
But to me, he's funny.
And the way that Gabriel Byrne was funny and hereditary,
just like shrugging at how insane everything's getting.
For some reason, I always thought that performance was really funny.
Bayman's kind of the same way.
He's just kind of like, yeah, this is our horrible life now.
This is, you know, like yeah,
we're people trying to kill him.
It's okay.
So he's subdued.
But of course, everyone who I know who watched the show was like,
I cannot wait for the day that Bayman finally goes nuts on this show
because he has put up with so much shit.
That moment when Bayman does go nuts is beyond satisfying
and amazingly well -directed by Laura Linney, actually,
who proved herself to be a very good director.
But Linney's the shit on the show.
Garner's the shit on the show.
The characters are great.
The Garner.
Jennifer Garner?
Julia Garner.
She's pretty young girl, but to me,
you know, I started seeing the formulas.
I started kind of getting ahead of the show.
I got a little bored by the show in the home stretch.
I think when you have a show that big
and they're ending after four,
I appreciate it.
They're admitting to you.
They've kind of run out of stories.
It's a four -season show that probably could have.
Maybe should have been a movie.
However, I was very entertained by the whole thing.
I can't point to like one episode as being terrible.
And it also had brilliant moments in it scattered around.
I just don't think pound for pound,
we're talking about one of the great shows.
It's a solid watch, a good binge.
And it's one where you'll watch like five
before you even realize what happened to your Sunday afternoon.
I like those are quite a bit.
My last one, and it's a scary stuff as well,
is the Sword in the Sorcerer.
This is a, this is a, well, Sword in Sorcery movie
from the early 80s, 1982.
Directed by a guy named Albert Plain.
I don't know how you say it.
I think he's only directed this and then it's sequel,
which he made like a few years back.
On like video.
Because he never got it made back in the day.
It was supposed to be made because they tease it at the end of this movie.
But look, it's a, it's a big epic, you know,
epic might not be the right word,
but you know, it's one of the, it's like dragon slayer
and those kinds of movies.
It's about, can I ask, speaking of Romero,
it popped up and I meant to ask on the last episode.
Have you ever seen Night Writers?
No, it looks ridiculous.
It does, but it might be awesome.
It's, there's no, it's about a traveling cult bike show group.
I actually, I brought it up while you were talking in the last episode.
And one of the plot points was like,
Leroy comes to terms with his homosexuality.
And I was like, in Night Writers,
that I suddenly became very intrigued by what the hell the movie's even about.
It's like a movie where skeletons ride motorcycles.
I don't think so. I think it's, it's like a,
retelling of a Shakespearean tale starring Ed Harris.
Okay, I think if that's the dirt bike one where it's like, it is.
It's just one lately.
I've started seeing people mention more and more
being like a lost favorite or something.
Maybe, maybe it's better than I thought it would be.
You know, an evil lord in this movie,
summons a demon played by Richard Maul,
which I always enjoy Richard Maul when he plays like an evil guy in makeup.
He's very good at that.
And a lost prince needs to come back and reclaim his kingdom.
Basically, this movie is what I thought the Northman was going to be.
And if you took all the fun out of it,
whatever, we might do the Northman, so I won't say much more.
But we are going to do the North.
Yeah, so, um, look, if you're in the mood for something,
a bit campy, a bit fun, practical effects,
very, very cool cold open in this.
This is worth a watch.
It's not going to break your brain.
It's not going to redefine storytelling for you,
but it's a lot of fun.
And it's a scary stuff because shout fact,
or screen factory just did a 4K re -release and it looks great.
And it's a fun watch.
So check it out.
My next picture is 365 days.
Part of my Netflix close out.
This was one I just saw a lot of people talking about.
A lot of people said it was nuts.
And I thought I would check it out.
Knowing nothing about it.
It was very controversial.
A lot of people thought that it glorified sexual assault.
It absolutely does.
It's an insane movie with an insane premise.
But it's a Polish movie said in Italy, I believe.
It's a mobster who watches his father get shot.
At the same time, he's looking at a beautiful woman dancing on the beach.
And he becomes sexually fixated on her.
Because he happened to see her when his father got shot.
That makes no sense to me at all.
But I guess it would be an edible thing if it was his mom.
But watching your dad get shot,
the fact that you would sexually link to the woman you were looking at at that time
is a pretty big leap that this movie hangs a lot on.
But he's fixated on the woman.
He has her kidnapped.
He's a very wealthy.
He inherits the mob basically.
And he has her kidnapped and he's giving you 365 days to fall in love with me.
If you don't, I'll let you go.
And I promise I'll never rape you.
They have 15 scenes where he almost rapes her.
He brings in a woman to suck him off in front of her at one point
while she's tied to a bed with her legs spread.
At one point, he forcibly,
I would say almost orally rapes a stewardess.
And this is the hero of the film.
That scene, even though I'm sure it was a prosthetic,
you watch this woman like sucking a dick for an extended period of time.
The fact that this is even on Netflix is crazy.
I would qualify it as a somewhat more explicit
than normal softcore porn, not up to hardcore status.
But it went beyond 50 shades of gray.
There's lots and lots of sex in it, weird sex,
kinky sex, freaky sex.
The sequel just came out on Netflix.
I don't know.
Joe always teases me about this because porn is available.
Why do I so enjoy an erotic or rated movie?
I don't know.
I think it because it reminds me of like,
innocence of childhood discovering sex and nudity, etc.
I don't know.
But the truth is, this movie is horrible.
The plot is terrible.
But the leads have insane chemistry.
They're two of the best looking people I've ever seen in my life.
And they are fucking from start to finish in increasingly graphic ways.
So I enjoyed it in the same way.
I would enjoy watching an evening of pornography.
All right.
And that brings us
to cursed films.
Yes.
Season two, season one involved some classically cursed films
like the exorcist and the omen.
In other movies where everybody died.
Yeah, yeah, exactly.
Other movies that have been, you know,
storied for some time now.
This season went a little further off the beaten path.
We had, well, it's because how many films are cursed?
I can't believe that this was like a series.
It is straight up for multiple seasons.
Not many films are cursed.
Yeah, they always have to be horror films too.
We had, well, I guess not because the first one in this season was Wizard of Oz.
Ah, that's true.
I'm just reading on the website.
It says some of Hollywood's most notoriously cursed horror film productions.
But season one, I'm looking at it now.
Exorcist, omen, poltergeist, the crow, twilight zone, the movie.
Twilight zone, the movie.
That's a cursed film.
That was a rough one.
Yeah.
But we all knew the stories of these.
The second season, I didn't know any of it,
except for the some of the stuff from the Wizard of Oz.
Yeah.
The Wizard of Oz is the first one up.
And I love that one.
I love all the legends of the Wizard of Oz.
I've been hearing the one about the munchkin hanging itself in the background for years.
I was, I guess, I don't know if I ever mentioned it on the show,
but I was doing a pilot with Simon Pegg and Kid Harrington.
And I did a lot of research into the Culver City hotel
where the munchkins were alleged to always be having drunken orgies,
because that was a part of the show.
The guy was detected who worked at a pawn shop.
So a lot of my research involved artifacts of Hollywood history.
So it was like the last surviving munchkin
was coming in to pawn a piece of the yellow brick road.
And he had this amazing story involving rape and all sorts of things
that was going to be the plot of this series.
So I did a lot of research into it.
None of this was really new to me except Judy,
except how much the munchkins hated Judy Garland
for going on that talk show drunk and just being like,
ah, I all fucked each other and they would drunks,
which apparently was not true.
I think the, as I told Joe, the show just felt cheap to me.
I think they got a big budget upgrade,
because I noticed I was like, I really liked the music
on this new season of curse films.
And I saw it was this woman weighs blood
who I own her album.
I love her.
So I think they put some money into it.
It feels like a little more professional show.
It feels a little classier this year
and a little less like a VH1.
We love horror kind of show.
Yeah.
And goes a little more in depth.
These are at least they felt like hour long episodes.
Yeah.
And season one was like 27 minutes done on the cheap down the fly.
So it, I appreciated that it looked like,
it didn't look like your typical cheap shutter documentary.
And the Wizard of Oz one I loved.
The other one.
Okay.
The Wizard of Oz one I was just a little bored.
I just, you know, you've heard the munchens
hanging himself story a million times.
I've heard the paint, you know,
this Tin Man's paint poisoned the first act.
By the way, the first actor who was supposed to play a Tin Man
was the guy that played a Uncle Jed on a Beverly Hill prize.
I'd ever do that.
But, you know, that he got almost died from it
because it was poisoning him the paint.
And I've heard all this before many times.
And again, like this was one where I was like,
these aren't curses.
These are just like some like minor,
I say minor mishaps.
Like cursed is like in the first season when it was like,
there's a major decapitation scene in the Omen.
And then in the Mo, in real life,
one of the actors almost got decapitated in the same exact way.
Like that to me is like, wow, that's eerie.
This was like a makeup department didn't know what they were doing
and put fucking paint on a guy.
And he was died from it.
You know, the munchkin hanging himself thing
seems to be disproven.
Except for true believers like Neil Hamburger
who I forget is real in the end,
but he's in this because he's a big collector
and a proprietor, always good to sit.
Greg Turkin, Greg Turkin, I got to say,
I don't think he came off very well in this.
I think like, yeah, I mean, he's a he's an anti -coffment type.
You never know what you're going to get with that guy.
He is, but I thought like what made him look bad was when they were like,
he was talking about how valuable that VHS is
with the supposed and munchkin hanging clip in it
because there's only one version where it's out there.
And the guy going, well, you got it from a soldier to you.
Like did the person just not know what they had?
And he goes, oh, they did not know what they had.
And it's like, yeah, maybe you don't revel in the fact
that you kind of ripped somebody off or whatever.
But you know, whatever, it's that episode just didn't do it for.
I love the Wizard of Oz.
It made me appreciate the movie a bit more.
But I thought it was a kind of a boring episode.
To me, that just felt like a bonus feature on the blue ray,
where I was like, this is just shit they'll talk about.
It was kind of an odd kickoff to the season,
especially considering it's not a horror movie.
And you're premiering on shutter.
But you know, and I'm not saying I'm complaining.
They didn't go into it because who hasn't heard this,
but like maybe explore the dark side of the moon myth.
Or that started because these things are all myths.
But what I really wanted from this episode was to know where they came from.
Don't just tell us what we know, dig a little deeper.
So that's my criticism of the show,
is that I didn't come away learning much.
The most wild thing in the whole episode
is when the guy talks about how the head of the studio slapped Judy Garland in the face
because she wouldn't stop laughing.
And he's like, so is that what he should have done?
Possibly no.
But this is a man with a schedule.
And you're like, dude, what are you talking about?
Sometimes women need to be hit.
Can we go back a few minutes on that or end of late that?
No, it's, I liked it.
I liked the episode.
I was excited about the Rosemary's baby episode
because I love Rosemary's baby.
And I thought, well, what beyond
Polanski's sexual issues could they really go into here
and they didn't go into much more?
I mean, it's basically they talk about Sharon Tate
and shit, we already know again.
I thought, well, see, I disagree here
because this one shook me to my core
because I knew you know that we all know the Tate story.
I never knew how much it eerily intertwined with Rosemary's baby.
That fucking freaked me out.
And the most chilling thing was the interview
with the surviving Charles Manson girl
who like wasn't there but like heard the story's first hand
from the people that lady I assume is a banker.
She's just like a 50 year old Larath, you know,
maybe a little older lady.
So your mom's like best friend or something?
Yeah, you know, I was, my name is Sad Tracey McGee
and I was one of the original Charles Manson girls.
It's insane.
It's really fresh.
And then the interview, the one actress who like blacked out
and doesn't remember shooting her husband.
Yeah.
And she's the one that kills herself in the movie
like out of like without having will of her own
or whatever.
And then like in real life she shoots her husband
and she doesn't really remember doing it or anything.
That now we're kind of cooking with some gas here.
But like the story of the Manson killings,
when the, when the, when the historian says
when people are asked what evil is defined by,
they say Charles Manson and Adolf Hitler
and Roman Polanski's was directly affected
by both of those people.
That was insane.
True.
Yeah, I mean, that great book, The Long Goodbye,
which I don't know if I ever mentioned on here,
but it's, it was easily my favorite movie book
for the last couple of years.
I read it over the pandemic and it's about the making of
Chinatown and then of course they go into everything
around that Robert Evans and everything else.
The Godfather, all that shit.
Great, great, great, great book.
I recommend it highly.
But they talk about a lot about Polanski
and Sharon Tate and all that.
And wait, what did you just say, John?
Oh, that Polanski was affected by his parents
were killed by Hitler or whatever,
and then his wife was killed by Madison.
They go into, you know, his Holocaust shit.
I mean, and it was actually, I think a big part of the reason
that everyone gave him a standing ovation
for when he won for the pianist,
even though he wasn't allowed into America,
I think a lot of people are like,
well, the guy was affected by the Holocaust
and so forth, that they're willing to look past the other stuff.
But look, that's your personal choice,
whatever you want to do there.
But I'm saying the man clearly has had more tragedy
in his life than most.
I mean, what a horrific life.
Pretty fucking bad.
Yeah, like, oh God,
and then when the lady's telling the story
of the killing and like,
Sheran Tate begging for her baby to live,
I was like, Jesus, I got like maybe sick to my stomach, actually.
Yeah.
Very disturbing.
And and weren't you picturing Margot Robbie?
Isn't that the power of movies?
I was picturing Robbie the whole time.
It was crazy.
But I don't really know what Sharon Tate looks like.
Sharon Tate, you know, it's funny.
I didn't really remember which he looked
like either. I'd seen her before.
But then when I saw her pictures in this thing,
I was like, she looks nothing like Margot Robbie.
They're just.
Yeah, not only that, I was like, she doesn't look like Margot Robbie
and she doesn't look like what I thought Sharon Tate looked like.
So I don't know what I was thinking about.
I can't help but think Sharon Stone for some reason,
but share of like the name, obviously.
But that, I love the photographer who,
like he, like talk about like, I love in a documentary like this,
when they have a sound voice in the midst of all the Hollywood craziness,
but the guy that was the photographer,
the Polanski had brought up to the house to take the pictures
after the murders happened.
And they were like, what did it feel like?
And he's like, I didn't want to be there.
I felt horrible.
I felt like he was like, I was like exploiting death,
but like he wanted me to take these pictures of everything.
And then when he goes to the cliff and looks at the site of the house,
and he goes, that's the house.
That's where it was.
Now look what's there.
There's a home four times a size,
which folks, I've been to that house.
And I could tell you who lives in that house,
but I won't, but I've been to that house if you're a party.
I feel like maybe it's kind of giving away where a person lives.
Maybe you should -
Was it Marilyn Manson?
Yeah, and it was.
A person, a famous TV creator lives in that house.
I'll leave it at that.
Okay.
But I've been there for a party.
And I remember when I was there,
somebody saying, this is, you know,
this is like, we're standing on the ground where the tape thing happened.
And I was like, what?
Yeah.
But I love when the photographer goes to that cliff and looks at it.
And he's like, look at that.
Like that monstrosity.
It's four times the size of what was there.
And I remember when I was at the house being like,
this is absurd.
I wouldn't want to live like this.
And when the guy goes, this is Hollywood access to the extreme.
Like, he just seemed -
I love when you see a guy who's living in the eye of the storm
that understands how fucked up the storm around him actually is.
Yeah.
And my mind that photographer guy was
Jake Jillin Hall's character and night crawler.
Like a piece of shit that just tried to -
Yeah, well, maybe, yeah.
No, I just, I just mean like, he was so creepy in that movie.
And that guy had a creepy vibe to him too.
But you can tell he had just, he had seen too much.
Like, he kept it together sort of,
but you can tell that guy's had some rough nights for sure.
But you're right.
I forgot about that character.
He was fun.
I liked all these.
I mean, any movie documentary,
I can sit and watch and be happy.
So stalker, the third one, Joe admitted he could not finish.
I couldn't get through it.
I tried to watch stalker as a kid.
And I was a very open -minded kid and watched all kinds of shit.
Even if I didn't get it, I would try to struggle
through all the classics.
But stalker, I couldn't finish.
And I own it.
I own the criterion.
I know it's hailed as a masterpiece.
I've always been meaning to try it again.
But it's Tarkovsky who did the original Solaris,
which is a notoriously dull film.
But yeah, I got to say, I have no idea why they would pick this.
I have no idea why they thought anyone on Shutter
would want to know any of this.
It's maybe a criterion thing.
But stalker is not a movie you ever hear anyone mention.
Even though it's hailed as a masterpiece.
I mean, they want to see it.
Talked at length about the footage that had to be reshot
because it got contaminated,
because of the nuclear, whatever the fuck, or the radiation.
Well, that was sort of interesting
that everyone who was in like one scene,
it was basically like a Chernobyl lake
and everybody got like the same disease.
I thought that was actually sort of interesting.
I did interesting, but it's not a curse.
You swam and it got them nuclear leaks.
It's not a curse.
I've been swimming in raw fluid.
I love it.
I'm making a gun two and a half.
My favorite episode by far,
and it's about a movie that I don't love.
I like the serpent in the rainbow,
but I don't love it.
What a great episode.
It's the first one I watched for whatever reason.
But I was like, this season is amazing,
because I thought the serpent in the rainbow episode was so great.
And it did what you always hope,
and it does what like screen factory and shout factory does so well,
is a movie that maybe didn't get a lot of love.
Can sometimes lead to the best recollections
from people who were there.
You know?
I like it.
Like there's fascinating stories because it's not jaws.
You haven't heard the stories a million times.
You've never heard serpent in the rainbow stories.
And they were pretty interesting.
I got a pitch for you.
Pauli sure in the directive video spoof,
the surfer in the rainbow.
I think it's got legs.
I might go the surfer in the rainbow.
There you go.
Brendan Frazier comes in.
And there you go.
It's a hundred pound.
We actually have him gain more weight for the role.
I like this episode quite a bit too.
How cool is Bill Polman, a quick pause?
He seems awesome.
You know, like I've never been like,
I fucking loved Bill Polman in that movie.
And yet, I love him as the heel
in so many romantic comedies.
You've got male, which is a masterpiece,
why you were sleeping, which is a great movie.
I love him in all those movies.
As like the guy who's getting cheated on.
And when I said you got male,
I might have met sleepers in Seattle.
I think I did.
But I love both of those movies.
Paulman, then in action mode,
you've got him in space balls in comedy mode.
You got him in lost highway doing the David Lynch shit.
You got him in Independence Day doing the presidential speech.
Like, he's not amazing.
But there's something so great about him.
And then to see him in this older,
grayer,
but man, he's just, he's as likable as you want him to be.
I don't think I've ever seen him on a talk show.
So it was great to just see him talk about this experience.
I was excited to see him in an interview too,
because I'd never seen it.
So it's like seeing like Dennis Quaid in an interview.
You know, like you just don't ever see it.
And I loved it.
The stories were insane.
You know, this was all based on a book or inspired by a book
that a guy wrote about voodoo culture.
And the purpose of the author hates the move.
You can tell he despises the move.
Well, he says he was like, I wrote this book
to take the stigmas away from voodoo culture.
These racist and, you know, sort of regionalists,
sort of concepts of it.
And he goes and then they made a movie in my book,
and they went back and did all the goofy horror shit
that movies of Hollywood has always done to it.
And it made him notorious with that community.
But then it's interesting,
because the movie starts and ends with a screening of the movie
in, I believe, Haiti.
Yeah.
And at the end, one of the viewers says,
this is the best movie I've ever seen on the subject of voodoo.
And it's a shame that nobody from our own country
has made something this good.
We need to step up and take the crown away from Hollywood on this one.
So I'm not quite sure how anybody really feels about it
who knows about voodoo.
I don't really have an opinion one way or the other.
But because I...
Pro voodoo.
But what is funny is the guy goes,
I just want to get away from all the negative stereotypes
that come along with voodoo culture.
And then when they're talking about making movie,
they go, well, you'd ask the local woman
to get us a bunch of bone props that we needed for a scene.
And we realized she had dug up actual graves
and brought us real bows.
You're like, well, guys, there's some validity,
I think, to some of these crazy ideas.
I don't know.
This 40 -minute thing is just chock full of stories
of like, and it's Mel Brooks's brother who was producing it.
And he tells some stories that I know.
But he tells some stories that kind of implicates them
in like crimes.
Like there's several stories where they're talking
and you're like, you know, I don't think you should say this on camera.
But...
Well, Prave and Sun says it at one point.
He's like, I don't know if I should be telling these stories.
Yeah, no, and he shouldn't.
But yeah, you get a lot of talk about Prave and Sun.
Prave and Sun takes the opportunity of a documentary
about Serpent on the Rambo
to talk about what a bad father he had,
which I relate to very much,
because I would do the same thing.
And I just...
I got to tell you, this was the first one I watched
and I texted Joe.
I was like, holy shit.
Like they took such a step up this season.
This show is the best.
I'm so excited to watch the other ones.
And the other ones aren't as good, unfortunately.
If you're gonna start with one,
the Serpent and the Rambo episode is fantastic.
And because they showcase some of the best images from the movie,
it makes the movie look like a masterpiece,
which it isn't.
But it's got some scenes in it
that really are troubling and stay with you
with West Prave and was always great at.
It made me want to revisit the movie.
I have it on that.
We didn't we do it on the show?
No, we did some Craven movie
where I had to buy a four pack that had shocker in it.
And I have that same four pack
and that's how I watched it for the first time, actually.
But I think...
Well, I know we didn't know him right now.
I'm sure I don't know what else we did.
There it is down there, Craven West Craven.
I don't know, I'm gonna revisit
because I remember as a kid trying to watch it.
I was like, this isn't even a horror movie.
This is like, what?
And they say that in the movie.
They're like, it's not really a horror movie.
It's more of a thriller and whatever.
Craven saw it as a shit in there.
Yeah, we did people out of the stairs, Joe.
That's why I bought it.
It's a shit being remade by Jordan Pill.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, it was just...
It was gotta do it.
I'm excited to see what he does with it
because the racial subtext there was very obvious back then.
Yes, I agree.
It's, there was a set.
It had shocker serpent in the rainbow.
People upstairs.
I got the same set.
Something, and it doesn't matter.
The point is is...
I think it was Deadly Friend.
Terrible.
Every Roch Deadly Friend.
I also, this movie also made me want to...
Actually, it made me want to rewatch Deadly Friend
because it made Deadly Friend look way cooler
than I remembered it being.
But anyway,
as a kid, I remember just being like,
I'm not into this.
It's like too dramatic or something.
And I remember on Revisit's not being that into it.
But this maybe, I was like,
there are some really cool horror elements in this.
So, I don't know.
I kind of want to rewatch it.
My favorite anecdote in the film is,
I don't know, he was a...
You know, somebody on the crew
who had a complete mental breakdown.
They'd went to it at actual Buddha's ceremony.
And like, you know,
everybody in this thing talks in a way
that convinces you that this shit is real.
This guy had a complete breakdown
and apparently he was naked outside of West Graven's hotel room
in the morning, like, just talking complete nonsense.
And they put him on a plane, sent him home to his wife,
and they were like,
did your husband just fucked up?
They couldn't put him on a plane.
The guy had to fly him home.
He had to be like, guided home.
And then they said, Bill Paxton had a nervous...
Hope Bill Coleman had a nervous breakdown.
And then when they ask him,
he's like, I don't want to talk about him.
Yeah.
It's like wild stuff.
And then they eventually got literally chased out
of the country by an angry mob of extras
that they took advantage of, basically.
Yeah, right.
And in the...
Whenever they talk about Brooks' brother, he's like,
oh yeah, you know, we'd give him, you know,
40 cents a day.
It's weird how open they are
about how fucked up the whole production was,
but that's kind of the beauty of the...
It's the kind of behind -the -scenes thing,
like on the Alien 3 DVD.
That's the kind of behind -the -scenes you always crave,
but you never get where everyone's being honest.
It's very rare when people are like,
yeah, things were really fucked up.
I love that.
And then I don't think you even knew this,
Joe, because I just discovered it last night,
but there's also a fifth episode.
There are five episodes, seasons,
Cannibal Holocaust.
And...
On the son of a bitch, really?
I started to watch it last night,
and then I was like, I don't want to see
that turtle being desheld again,
and I stopped watching it, but...
Well, I want to watch that episode.
I want to hear...
Because that's it.
There's some creative...
But again, I bet you it's just going to be like...
And everybody thought it was real, but it wasn't real.
You know, but like, I don't know.
I'm curious.
I'd like to see that.
But my hog is up for Curse Film Season 2.
I'll tune in for Season 3.
If, look, at its best,
it's showing you freaky shit
that makes you think a film might have actually been cursed.
And at its worst, it's just cool special features.
So I'm in either way.
My hog is up too, especially in a world
where we don't get movie special features anymore.
You're lucky to get a trailer on a goddamn Blu -ray these days.
So I've always loved this shit.
People just shoot in the shit and tellin' stories
about movie making.
I could watch it about a movie I don't care about.
I just like hearing this stuff.
Some are better than others.
Surfing in the rainbow is for sure the one
that you want to lead with.
But I think overall,
I'd watch another season of this shit.
My request for my hope
would be that they would focus more on movies
like Surfing in the Rainbow.
Where are you saying Serpent?
Serpent, that's how you say it.
Serpent.
Yeah.
But I've heard both.
I've heard Serpent.
Really? All right.
And you can spell it with a pH.
But they spell it with a pH and I should say Serpent.
You're right.
No, no, no, it's okay.
I just was confused.
I would hope the next season would focus
more on movies like Surfing in the Rainbow
and less on movies like The Wizard of Oz
when we've heard the stories a thousand times.
And if you are going to focus on those stories,
tell us more about them than just stating what they are
in my opinion.
Right.
So for me, that's where this series really shines
is giving you behind -the -scenes looks at movies
that would never normally get that kind of treatment.
We will be back.
I am having a bit of a hard time watching movies out here
because I'm working an incredible amount.
And also, the only theater within 10 miles of me
is currently showing Dr. Strange
on nine of its 10 screens,
and the 10th screen is Father Stew.
So movie about a bunch of dads that open a soup restaurant.
Did you know that Father Stew's,
which my mother loved, by the way,
but starring Marky Mark and Mel Gibson
was written and directed by Mel Gibson's girlfriend,
who has never done anything before.
But my mom loved it.
My mom wants to see it real bad.
I'm not going to see it.
Maybe the Northman next time, maybe.
I will find a way to see the Northman
and I'm going to go and I'm going to have to just drive,
you know, a half hour into the city and go see it.
But I need to see the Northman
and I'm most excited to see everything everywhere
all at once, which everyone is obsessed with.
Maybe Joe can check that one out too.
But yeah, I'm hoping to see that too.
But we'll be back with the, you know,
the suffering is also, I think it's called the suffering
as a new zombie movie on
Shutter that has been described repeatedly
by different outlets as the most disgusting zombie movie ever.
I think it's called the suffering
or the sadness or something.
I read about it in Rumorg magazine a half a year ago
and now it's on Shutter.
So I don't know if we've got to change the title of my autobiography
from the suffering to something else.
But we'll be back this month with two more folks.
Thanks for joining us.
We'll see you next time and we'll see you in hell.