I'll see you in hell.
Welcome to We'll see you in hell.
Oh, the movie podcast where they get reviewed, they get discussed, they get broken. I'm Joe
DeRose, and I'm Patrick Walsh. I really thought your voice was going to break there on
that one. It seemed like maybe the first thing you said allowed today or what. No, I had
a, I've talked quite a bit today so far. I got up pretty early. I had an hour long conversation
with Mark Normand on the phone about stand -up comedy. And then my, oh, yeah, super positive. And then,
and then, you know, my usual mutterings and, you know, son of a bitch bastards, you know, as I
look out the window, I was stuck in my toe, that kind of thing. Sure. I just woke up. Just woke up.
You look good. Seriously, yeah, you do. I'm saying you look, you look pretty put together for having
just woke, I'm being serious. I'm not being out. I mean, I was, I was looking at myself when
the, you ever like, when you wake up to like piss or something, you go into the bathroom and turn
the light on and jump at your reflection, like how bad you look as if you're in a horror movie
and it's a jump scare. Because I do that on zoom all the time. I love that they give you that second
to like look at yourself before the other person sees you because I'm always like, whoa. I was
getting some spackle and I'm glad you brought that up. It's like a big, like a big
rouge circle on my cheeks like a doll dolly. That reminded me of a bit of like a classic like three
stooges style bit that I keep thinking about and laughing really hard when I'm alone. Which is most
of the time. But it's the, I'm going to try to set this up correctly. Like they would do a bit
on those old thing, those old movies and TV shows where the guy would be like, give me a,
you know, I'll be like, you know, and I'm trying to think of it. Hold on, let me think of the telephone.
I guess is the one, you know, they'd be like, tell me the telephone and then like the guy would hand him
like a, you know, like a banana and then he go, he go, that's not a telephone you idiot. That's a
banana. Then the banana would ring and then the guy would go, yeah, that, that move is one of my
biggest comedic influences. I usually only do it for my own amusement. But like if, if the miss is
glares at me or something, like I make some comment, she glares at me, I'll always go, like jump.
It's pretty reliably funny. Yeah. I also like it when a dumb, they used to do this too in the old,
in the old movies when a dumb person says something that surprises a smart person. I can't
remember the name of the movie, but there's, there's a scene in a party and they have like that archetypal
bimbo character who's like, hi everybody, you know, they should always have her in those old movies.
She goes, there's like a, there's like a sophisticated matriarchal woman and the, and the ditz goes,
I read a book once and the matriarch goes, yeah, so startled by the fact a hand on the chest.
Yeah, that, that character's gone, gone away. It was the like the gangster's girlfriend or something
that would be some blonde with huge tits who was always like, I'm not, you know, very, very similar to
like a bunker wife, archie bunker wife. I think the last time we saw it, but she was, it was a smart
version of that character was in white man, can't jump. That's kind of what Rosie Perez's character is
like in that movie. Like she's, she plays those like tropes, but, but then the thing, the twist in the
character is that she's like, brilliant. Yeah. Mira sort of, you know, did it as well and, uh,
oh, yeah, the Woody Allen picture. Mighty, Alfred, daddy, which was after, so I've actually
bettered your answer, but, um, is that after white man can't jump? Yeah, I think it's a 92 and a 90,
always a competition with this guy. It's a big fix on, Alfred, daddy, if I'm not mistaken.
Yeah, go, go, no, no, you go ahead. No, I was just gonna say I watched the first part of the, uh,
the Woody Allen doc, uh, HBO. How was it? It's uplifting. Fun.
Ron, it was terrible. You know what I'm seeing a lot of on Twitter lately is fuck both of these people
and, and that's kind of refreshing, you know, it's like, I think people have realized that this
family is just, you know, doesn't deserve our love at this point. And, uh, and, and we don't need
to point specific fingers at specific actions. We can just say, yeah, I think the Allen's suck.
Yeah, it's a, it's a damaged family. Yeah. I just think of that, that I read was that Pharaoh, um,
you know, they're, they're digging up some, some thing of Woody Allen date in a 16 year old girl and,
um, Pharaoh allegedly had a threesome with the two of them. Yeah, that's, that's kind of been out
there for a little while. It's like looking around. Is this Caligula over there? It's, uh,
Jesus Christ. I mean, I, I'm imagining a proposing a threesome to my wife, you know, in, in any sort of
serious way, it would obviously get a huge laugh. But then I say, by the way, she's 16.
And I'm 20 years older than I am now. Yeah. And imagining my wife going, okay,
right. Let's try this. It's just, I mean, it's Hollywood, baby. It's very, very Austin powers.
Yeah. Yeah. The, uh, the best take I read on the whole situation and, you know, you're in trouble,
folks, when the New York Post is giving clarity to a situation, but they were somebody wrote an article.
Now, I'll grant it. They were more team Woody than team Mia. But the crux of the article was saying,
regardless of whatever happened or whatever the truth is, I just feel sorry for this kid. I feel
sorry that this has become like her. This is what she's defined by. This has got to have, this must have
been horribly destructive to her life. Yeah. In any, any, any shake out of any truthful version of
this story, whatever it is, it was horrible for this girl. And I, and I feel the same. I feel bad for
of course. And then to have your adulthood be right, essentially reduced to an incident in
your childhood, it's, it's, it's fucking terrible for everybody. Yeah. But did that, was a nice
segue to what I wanted to talk about. Yeah. I'm proposing a new segment. I don't know what to call
this other than my favorite things I've ever heard happen in Hollywood that are terrible.
But I couldn't think of a catchy name for this segment. This came about last night. I stumbled
on to, to, to Tatum O 'Neill online. Yeah. And through her went to read up on Ryan O 'Neill.
Joe, I recently did an O 'Neill dip myself, but carry on. So Ryan O 'Neill, Tatum O 'Neill,
were very estranged for a very long time. He still estranged to some of his kids.
Ryan O 'Neill, one of his quotes was, and I'm paraphrasing, but it was something along the lines of,
I don't think I was ever cut out to be a father. Look at my, look at the living proof.
They're either in jail or should be, I think was his statement about his own children.
So I was reading down to see like, you know, what he did, you know, and this was,
this man, this just leapt off the page. By the way, quickly, Ryan O 'Neill now is not known.
You know, I would say, I would say three -fourths of listeners will have no idea who Ryan O 'Neill is,
but a quick synopsis. As he was a huge star of the 70s, he was the biggest box office draw,
you know, usually vying with Bert Reynolds, but his horrific behavior, alcoholism, etc.,
derailed his career. I recently listened to the Polly Platt podcast, so you must remember this is
a fantastic podcast by my old boss, Karina Longworth, about scandals in Hollywood history,
and they did a ten -part exposé of Polly Platt, who was a production designer on, you know, a lot of
James L. Brooks movies, last picture show, etc., she was married to Peter Bogdanovich, but he left
her for Cybil Shepherd on a movie they were all three working on together, and Ryan O 'Neill just
comes off as a monster throughout. Polly Platt was also the production designer on Bad News Bears,
which starred Tatum O 'Neill, and what's up Doc, which I watched two nights ago is Bogdanovich
Streisand and O 'Neill, and then you got Paper Moon, which is Ryan O 'Neill, Tatum O 'Neill, Peter Bogdanovich
and Polly Platt. Fascinating, if you want to read more about him, but I never thought he was
much of an actor, Carrie Anja. So he's got a kid named Griffin, who he's still, as far as I know,
still doesn't talk to, so here's the thing. O 'Neill eventually married Farah Fawcett,
right, when he was married to her when she passed, I believe. O 'Neill refused to allow Griffin to
attend Fawcett's funeral in 2009. In 2009, O 'Neill infamously hid on Tatum at Fawcett's funeral,
not recognizing her as his daughter. Holy shit. Holy shit. I never heard that one,
because they'd been so estranged or what? I don't know. I mean, I'm assuming he was fucked up.
First of all, but you're fucked up. You recognize your daughter. First of all, it's a funeral.
Second of all, it's your ex -wife or maybe even current wife's funeral. Yeah.
Third of all, you don't hit on anyone at a funeral. You're hitting on somebody. You could certainly
argue you don't hit on anyone at your wife's funeral, and you could unquestionably argue that if
you are going to hit on somebody at your wife's funeral, it shouldn't be your daughter, baby.
That's great. I want to find more of these as we move along in our show over the years and
months, whatever. I don't know what fans send in segments, suggestion names. I don't know what to
call it. Other than it's got to be so horrible. It's amazing. That's the point. Well, O 'Neill's
a treasure trove. And as is Peter Bogdanovich, we could do a week episode on Bogdanovich,
you know, the guy who really has cats. Yeah. Just a monster. Oh, I didn't know that. What's
give me some of the, I thought we thought he was like a decent guy. Would give me some of the juice.
He, I mean, he was despised in in Hollywood by all these directors. He was just a complete
ego maniac. Polyplat, there's a good case to be made that when she was on set with him helping him
out as his wife slash partner, the movies were classics of all time. Last picture show,
paper moon, what's up doc? Soon as she left, the man was never able to make a decent film again.
And there's all these tales of her saying, like, I was wondering if I could maybe get a credit or
associate producer, this is wife. No, no, this is my film. Wow. Ryan O 'Neill, by the way, if you've
never seen star 80, which I think I recommended on here, it's Bob Fossy's best in my opinion. One
of the bleakest movies ever made, but it stars Eric Roberts as the man who killed Dorothy Stratt
and the playboy playmate in the Roberts on the map and Hemingway. Both of them. Yeah. And
Dorothy Stratton was the mistress slash wife of Peter Bogdanovich. Again, he went to plat,
shepherd, she did on shepherd with Stratton. And if you want to know how much Bogdanovich has
hated, where do you see the guy playing Bogdanovich in star 80? You know, he's just they clearly don't like
them. But Ryan O 'Neill, also when his daughter Tatum was nominated for best supporting actress for
paper moon at age nine, she was like, oh my gosh, and celebrating. And O 'Neill was not nominated for
best actor. And he hit his daughter because she was excited that she got nominated and told everyone
in his circle that he was livid. He's like, if you're not going to nominate me fine,
but you don't nominate my fucking nine -year -old daughter and humiliate me. So she's trying to celebrate
this and he's just screaming at her. Great dude, great dude. That's a great bit in the David Spade book.
Polaroid guy in a Snapchat world, the chapter on how easy it is, how easy acting is.
We talk about like all the children who get nominated for the highest award. And then my favorite
part is he talks about Jennifer Hudson. Jennifer Hudson, who came in seventh on American Idol in her
field of expertise, came in seventh, waltzes over the acting. First time out, Winston Oscar. He's
right. Yeah, it's very funny. Bob, Bob, Robert Evans, the hilarious Paramount dude who has like the
funniest autobiography of all time devotes 50 pages to how much of a piece of shit Ryan O 'Neal is.
Well, that's big talk, too, because Evans, I mean, look, I don't think Evans is a piece of shit,
but he's definitely a swinging kind of guy. He's, you know, let's say he's loose. It was.
It was, did love story. And I believe O 'Neal stole his wife, Ali McGraw, away from,
from now, that was, that was an O 'Neal that was Steve McQueen, I believe.
True, but I don't know that Ryan O 'Neal didn't also. Oh, Jesus, it's a bad scene.
I have a quick news psycho. I just read this before we hopped on.
It comes from movieweb .com, Netflix is launching a Terminator anime series. So,
I mean, first of all, when is dead, finally dead with a franchise? And second of all, Amazon,
Amazon, Netflix, who's launching it. Netflix, when is it enough? How many things are you going to do?
I, so yesterday, they released promo photos for the new masters of the universe toy line.
And I was, I was excited to see them because they were, they're based on the new show coming out.
I was like, I want to see what this new show looks like. It's supposed to be this big
continuation of the original series. I look at it, they look nothing like it. And I'm,
I start getting aggravated. And I'm like, why is this Kevin Smith series a continuation? If they
redesign the whole thing, that's stupid. And then I read these aren't for the Kevin Smith series,
mind you. These are for another masters of the universe series that Netflix is also doing.
It's like, what is, what is the goal here? What is the end goal? It's too much. It's ridiculous.
It's laughable. I mean, my, my big news psycho for this week is very similar, which is Paramount Plus.
And I'm, I'm not being critical of Paramount Plus. In fact, I'm currently in the running to
perhaps do something with them. But Paramount Plus announced 50 new projects. And every one of them
was based on an existing thing, an existing movie, an existing book, whatever it may be.
There, I think I might have talked about on this podcast. I got sent a list of every movie ever
released by Paramount on Wikipedia. And it was like, yeah, these are all up for grabs. Yeah,
they're just going through and letting people remake their movies as TV shows. And I get it,
you know, when Paramount steps up to the plate, it's like, what are our assets? We've got all these
movies. But what, what is to become of this business? Is it like, is anyone trying to do anything
original, you know, and every meeting, I take a lot of meetings these days, you know, just killing time,
meeting interesting people, you know. And the meetings are like, well, what, it's never what's a great
idea that you have. It's always, here's a book that we have the rights to. Here's this, here's that.
Now, they've always made books into movies. That's nothing new. They've always remade movies,
but it was at least half and half. I mean, we're at 95 five at this point. I think it's a degenerative
business, like any other major institution at this point. I think it's like government and
politics. I think it's like major banking. Yeah. Anything. I think Hollywood is just that now. It's,
it's not going to get better. You would never, it's whatever can reduce their risk in their,
in their mind, not that every one of these things is a fucking success. And the way any of one of these
fields has always worked is you do it until you go, I don't recognize this anymore. And you step
away. And then the next batch of people come through and they go, this, and then in 20 years,
they'll be going, what happened to this business? You know, so I just kind of take it as my cue to,
you know, continue to be a part of it in my own way and try to get things done that I want to get
done. But at the same time, less than my expectations greatly, I, we just can't, look, the positive
side is, is you can turn to shutter or, you know, sometimes, or wherever there's, you know,
there is independent content out there. It's just you're not going to get it, you're not going to
get the unique stuff from Paramount anymore. It's just a bummer. It bums me out that they have the
phrasier, because I am excited about the phrasier reboot as I would be. But I, I'm mad it's not on NBC.
But I guess it was a Paramount show or something or property. Yeah, it is. I mean,
they're not, they don't have pierce yet. Mahoney is dead. You know, Joe and I were kind of
discussing what it would look like. Obviously, it's going to involve the sun, I would say. And either
the sun's blue collar and phrasiers, the uptight one, or it'll be the sun is because what they did in
the original show was like a genius move, give phrasier a brother who's more stuck up than he is.
Right. You know, so they might have the sun grow up to be worse than phrasier, who knows? But
that'd be interesting. If it was like he's looking at the sun now, like, what is wrong with you? Super
woke. You know, I think that sort of pitch would appeal to Kelsey grammar, who's like a notable
Republican. He might just be like, yo, yeah, like so since that works so well the first time,
you know, phrasier is considered this elegant man, but even he's crashed by today's standards of
the man, you know, that'd be good. I'd like that. And I'd like it to if the kid was, I mentioned
this to you like, I think it would be good if the kid did something deemed as blue collar that
phrasier turned his, you know, you're hardward graduate. How can you be working in the peace
corps or whatever it is? You know, right, right. And that being a point of contention for them.
And because that would exemplify his own snobbery and everything, I think that'd be funny. I
mean, I can't imagine they're not going to get hide peers and at least for half of you know,
maybe it's not going to be they all live in the same town anymore. But I would think it's maybe,
look, maybe they go back to Boston and maybe like some of the cheers people start coming back in.
I wouldn't, I wouldn't hate that. I wouldn't hate it. No, not at all. So I mean, here's a quick run
down there. They're bringing criminal minds back, which was just went off the air after 15 seasons. It's
back flash dance flash dance by a madman writer flash dance is coming back. But you know, and what sucks
about it is they're not going to make it sexy because things can't be sexy anymore.
Halo based on the game is not a good movie. No, it's a bad movie. Like what? This is what I was saying
about Cobra Kai. I love Cobra Kai. I'm a fan. I'm in. I want to keep watching. But I also do take
issue with their bringing elements from like the third movie that when it was a new thing, people
were like, this is terrible. Yeah. So it's like, why are we all of a sudden just pretending that
because something is 30 years old, it's automatically good. It's not. It's it's also strange to assume
that kids today will like something from 30 years old. I mean, karate kid has stood the test of time.
Dad's love showing karate kids to their sons and moms to their daughters and et cetera. Flash dance
is not a movie that gets handed down. Well, I'm going to want to disagree with you. I have to see
flash dance. I'm going to have to disagree with you there. My father and grandfather and I would watch
flash dance often with like warmers. Like warmers. Yeah. Granddad would run in place. I'd say
that's not dancing. He'd say, well, it isn't a movie. That's my impression of your grandfather.
Isn't that from something? Isn't there some movie where a gruff guy is singing? I'm a maniac,
maniac. Or am I just, uh, well, Farley does it in Tommy boy. That's running in the gas.
That's right. They're they're cleaning him off with gasoline. Love story from the makers of
a gossip girl in the OC. That's a Ryan O 'Neill, Ali McGraw picture there as well where a man falls in
love with a woman and she dies. That's the plot of love story. Oh, Jesus Christ. All right,
let's do beaches while we're at it. The Italian job. There's been two movies of the Italian job.
Dear God. A heist. I mean, what are you doing? A heist a week? That's a lot of heists.
Somebody's going to catch on. The man who fell to earth. The, uh, Bowie film is, which, you know,
is a cult movie at best and is only palatable because David Bowie sort of seemed like an actual
space man at the time. It's the only thing that makes it sort of interesting. They're doing it with
Chiuatel, Eddie O 'Four, who was just a normal guy. Just a guy. Oh, for Christ's sakes.
Good. At least do it with the guy from the flaming lips or something. Do it with like some weird,
you know what I mean? Yeah. Yeah. Uh, the offer, that's the one I am excited about. It is about the
making of the Godfather. Uh, a 10 episode series about the making of the Godfather. That I'm down for.
I'll watch it. Yeah. How many times have we heard that story? Oh, they followed him around set. He
almost got fired every. Yeah. I know. I know. Right. They didn't want Pacino. You know, yeah, I know.
You know, you know, you know, Brando had cue cards in the, yeah, I know the oranges in the fuck. Yeah,
I know. I know. I know he put cotton balls in his cheeks. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I started the, uh, the
extras on the Godfather Blu -rays. And I was like, I've heard, it's like jaws at this point. It's,
the stories are as known as the movie. Yeah. Uh, parallax view based on the Warren Betty movie,
which is a great movie, but that, you know, no one talks about it. I've never even heard of that.
They're doing an avatar. They're doing door of the, wait, wait, they're doing an avatar series
on top of the three movies, Cameron's putting out animated avatar series. Oh, Jesus,
Christ. By the way, look at that. Listen to this sense. Avatar studios will produce for parent
Mount Plus a wide range of avatar content ranging from spin -offs and theatricals to short form.
We got only coming back in 3D. We got, uh, like Pixar style Rugrats. They bring
Rugrats back every four years at this point. You know, it's, it's like Mr. Bean. You're like,
this isn't done yet. Oh, there's another Johnny English. What the fuck? Star Trek
Prodigy, the first ever Star Trek for the kids. Big brother live feeds 24 hour live feeds
from the big brother house. Road rules is back. Real world's back. Real world road rules
challenges back. Frage Greece, the rise of the pink ladies. We've discussed that before. Uh, that's
just hold on. Let's just take a moment for the worst title I've ever heard of anything. Rise of
the pink. I mean, I've never heard something so benign. Sound more sinister in my life. Tells
your sister Jane founded the pink ladies. Yeah, it gets into the red tape of the pink ladies.
Would it, you know, yeah. Inside Amy Schumer's back. Yeah. Yeah. I mean, good for Amy. I hope
maybe I'll get a part. She gave me parts on the show all the time. No, that's awesome.
Fingers crossed on that one. I'm a monstrous asshole from what I recall. Yeah, always. But she,
now, but Amy's at least, at least she's only doing specials. That's it. It's like that makes
a little bit more sense to me. Like, yeah. You know, I actually liked her show about her pregnancy.
I thought it made me like her a lot more. She was funny in it, relatable. It was a good show. And
I will actually say too, even the Star Trek thing, which I have no interest in. Zero. But at least
you're like, okay, it's Star Trek. It's a huge franchise. I get it. But like, yeah, these other things,
it's like, I don't, I don't like, is there a young, is there a group of kids out there that
loves Greece? I just don't even get like what they're, she's who they're aiming for here.
Get what they're hoping, I guess, is this is like, you know, Cobra Kai, my guess is that it caught on
because parents were like, oh, yeah, well, I love this movie when I was a kid. Let's watch this.
And maybe you introduce them. But it was that. And let me just jump in. It was that. And it was also
crazy viral videos about the karate kid crazy viral videos going around about Daniels actually,
the bad guy. This and there was, there was, there was some proof of concept that was there. Yeah.
There's no viral videos about Greece, except Travolta just sort of did the dance on TikTok.
I'm glad I didn't see that one. The one title that made me laugh is Reno911
the hunt for QAnon. That will probably be good. I will watch that. That's a guarantee.
They're doing a new beavers and butt head movie, new work, a hallux movie, fine.
They're bringing back, bringing back behind the music, bringing back unplug, bringing back
YoMTV wraps. It's just going to be a, we're reliving our life, but worse. And then the butt,
beavers and butt head movie, I'm happy to see beavers and butt head back. But it, there's also a show.
Why are you doing a movie and a show? Just let the show breathe. And then if that does well,
do a movie. Agreed. Agreed. Jesus Christ. That's where we're at, folks. That's where we're at.
Well, are we, are we ready for the movie corner? I would say so. I'm ready for anything at this point.
Look, I'll kick us off with the bad news bears, the remake, correct? I watched both last night.
Okay. I felt both. I like them both. The original I prefer. Well, yeah, I think everybody does.
I started with the remake, though, because I was just in a, you know, sometimes you get in the mood
during this pandemic thing. I'm still without booze. Yeah. And you know, you're sitting around
and the thoughts get sometimes a little heavy. And you say, I just want to just kind of
check out. And the bad news bears is a great movie to do that with. Very funny. I was like, I'm in
the mood to see Billy Bob Thornton act like a piece of garbage, which is always fun. If you haven't
seen the remake, you know, it's basically a toned down bad Santa, you know, it was perfect casting
for Billy Bob Thornton to play this coach. I'm surprised at how much of the original made it in
to this remake. They cut out a few things. There's a couple of lines that are very racial,
that they cut out, because they were like, look, regardless of if we think it's funny or not,
it's just not going to play. I remember when it came out, when they said that. And then the thing I was
a little bummed about is at the very end of the movie, when he gives the kids beer, it's in the remake,
it's non -alcoholic beer. I bet that was a big fight. I'm sure it was. But here's the weird
part. And it's a funny movie. The original is better, but the remake is fun and fun and fun
enough. The weird part to me is this, it is a scene for scene remake, dial everything. There are so
few differences. This is like Gus Van Sant, Zant Psycho style remake. Yet the original writer
doesn't get writing credit. If he gets a based on credit, but he doesn't get writing, it's like,
no, no, no, his exact scenes and dialogue are in this movie. Like his whole story is in this movie.
And the only thing I could surmise was that Bert Lancaster's son wrote the movie, who's dead.
He also wrote the thing. He wrote two movies. This makes him write there one of the best
screenplay writers of all time. So I'm like, I guess maybe because nobody's around from that
estate or his camp, they're just like, we can get away with just not having to get into the legal
battle of paying a third guy that's not a, I don't know. I just don't understand how you could
write a script. And it could be adapted this marginally by two other writers, two, two, two
other writers to adapt this thing. There's no changes. I think they were the bad Santa writers too or
among them. But it's always confusing. I mean, sometimes it's just is the person alive and well
and willing to fight it and go to the writers guild. That's what I think sometimes.
Sometimes people don't want to make a stink and so on. The writers guild's usually very good about
solving these disputes fairly and accurately. But the Omen is another such example. They are bringing
out the Omen remake with Leo Schreiber, whatever that was 2006. And it was pretty far along in the
process before the writers guild stepped in and were like, no, you're going to have to give the original
writer credit on this film. It's too similar. And they did. But it does seem odd that they only do it
occasionally. Yeah. And the guy who wrote the Omen, I don't know that he even got credit on his own
script because he stuck so closely to the original material. But I love the bad news bears the
ridge. Mathaus amazing in it. And I anti -demonial by the way. And I really love the remake with Thornton.
Link later when he is in, when he's in extreme indie mode, like, you know, like his animated shit,
waking life and all that, he's too pretentious for me. When he's in his extreme commercial mode,
school of rock, bad news, bears, I think he's one of the best people making mainstream comedies. He
doesn't do it very much. And then I always love his movies that are in between the two. And he does,
he knows how to shut it off. I mean, this thing is a paint by numbers Hollywood comedy. Yeah, you know,
but I mean, I was, he had the kids singing along to cocaine, but the air clapping song. I remember
that being very funny. They're not singing to it. It's playing, though, at the, at their like party or
whatever. But I would say this too, link letter. I mean, this thing is like, when I say shot for,
I mean, I'm like, I'm talking about like transitions are exactly the same. I mean, you know, when the
they're he's in the lounge chair at the pool. Lupus makes him a martini. Right. You know, he gets
too drunk. It dissolves to him on the mound, shit face. It's like, it's like the same, it's the same
movie. But that's my, that's my favorite was I think it's like link letters favorite movie. So maybe
he just, maybe he was just slavish to it. I don't know. That's my favorite line in the original
arguably is when Lupus brings Math Al the martini. And they're like, tell us about when you
struck out so and so. And he's like, it was a fine day for baseball. You know, he starts on the
story and he sips it. And then like mid story, he just looks back at Lupus and he goes, this is
excellent, by the way. And he just goes back to the martini. Very funny. You still haven't seen
school Iraq, have you? I think I might have seen it, you know, when I was in college, I don't
really remember. I never had much interest in it. I'm not against it. I just filmed. It's a great
thing. All right. I'll go back and check it out. I'd love to make the bad news bears as a
thing. As an urban kind of thing, like I'd like to make it with like an inner city baseball team.
I think that'd be a lot of fun. You know, who would have been almost too good for that is Bernie
Mac yelling at kids. Bernie Mac, I fantasized that length about it last night. I was like ice cube or
Mike. Mike apps would be great. Yeah. And maybe instead of does he get the movie made? That's the
question I get asked 20 times a day when I'm trying to cast this movie. I'm doing. I mean, Mike apps
as a raging pot head trying to coach the team would be hilarious. Yeah. Oh, that's a hit.
All right. Anyway, good. Even Sam Jackson. I mean, he's aged out of it now, but if they could make
it all right, it would have screaming in kids face. Well, you have Sam Jackson as the, as the
canier, you know, you have Sam Jackson as the asshole and the other team. Oh, God, oh, Mike,
we're cooking with gas over here. See, I don't remember the other team in the original bad news bears
having a canier. What's that different? It's Vic Morrow is the guy. Oh, fucking asshole.
Yeah, yeah. That's right. That's right. That's right. He's great. He's the there. Canier makes it a
little funnier. Yeah. And it's a little more like canier's character is a little more like you're
just kind of a dildo and you don't get it. But Vic Morrow was way more like, no, this guy's like a
fucking piece of shit. Yeah. He's a bad guy. Great performance. I saw last night
I was just in the in the right mood for it. I guess I don't know. I wish Joe Bob did more of this kind
of picture, even though it's not horror, but it's called 10 to midnight, starring Chuck Branson.
And I realized when it started that outside of like, you know, guns of Navarone and like 60s movies,
I don't think I've ever seen a Charles Branson movie death wish I've seen, but nothing from like
75 on. So this was from his like real trashy period when he's like really old and he teamed up with
this really sleazy director. And now I'm excited to watch all these movies because 10 to midnight was
absolutely insane. I really enjoyed it. It's it's not a good movie folks, but it's just trash. I
listened to Tarantino and Edgar Wright talk on the the Empire podcast. They talk for three hours
about movies. You mostly British movies, but all kinds of movies. And Tarantino goes off at length
on this director J. Lee Thompson who did he says he's never made a bad film. The guy's made like 100
movies, 20 of them starring Charles Branson, but they discussed 10 to midnight and good lord. It is
it Branson's a detective. And there's a killer who's based on a lot of different serial killers who
whenever he's about to kill a woman, you generally a naked woman, he strips completely down to
bear dick. This guy kills 20 people in this movie. So half of the film, the villain is literally running
around doing physical things, jumping on women, doing, you know, leaps from from from place to place
completely naked. I've never seen this in a movie. You know, you the the dick is is visible a lot,
but you can tell they're trying to hide it. It leads to some scenes like that are like Austin powers
when they're trying to cover it up with like the the face. You know, there's a scene where he's in a
woman's bedroom trying to kill her and the bed frame is covering just his dick. And then he like
takes a step and there's like a sink covering is it's the same bit as the Austin powers thing,
but it's not played for laughs. Branson at one point when he's got the man in custody, this is the line
that I saw most talked about online. He brings out this pussy on a stick like dildo machine.
Charles Branson and he wags the pussy on a stick in the guy's face and he goes, what's this?
It's for jack and off, isn't it? Charles Branson screaming, it's for jack and off, isn't it?
That's what a movie should be, you know, that's what a movie should be.
It plays like the filthiest Friday the 13th movie. It's just a slasher. I highly recommend 10 to
midnight. By the way, what does the title 10 to midnight have to do with the film? Absolutely nothing.
I really recommend 10 to midnight. All right. I'll keep it light here. Watch the little piece of
magic called you've got mailed. Never saw it. Love it. Never saw it. I was about halfway
to the Tom Hanks Meg Ryan vehicle sort of an un sort of a spiritual sequel, if you will, to
sleep us in Seattle rekindling the old magic to star cross lovers who don't know what the other
one looks like. Doesn't really know who the other one is, but correspond through a series of emails
in this film. Turns out, turns out Tom Hanks is the big bad evil bookstore owner who brings in the big
corporate big box bookstore that shuts down Meg Ryan's mom and pop bookstore that was owned by her
mother and adored by the neighborhood. So she hates Tom Hanks, but little does she know he's also
the man she's in love with over AOL title comes from it used to say you've got mailed for your young
kids out there when you logged into AOL. This is probably the also a remake, a remake of the shop around
the corner, the Ernst Lubish film starring Jimmy Stewart. I didn't know that Tom Hanks are Jimmy Stewart
as many say. Sure. This is one of the only movies we've got a safe private Ryan.
Turner, get me hooch. You say that's hooch. You know, he makes slobber a lot, but he's got a great heart.
This is one of the only. Tell me, how am I going to go up against a volcano? I'll lose.
Right? Yeah. Yeah. There's only only movies ever based on a product that's actually good.
You know, this like, you know, you see these product placement movies like, you know,
Stuber or whatever the hell. You know, you're like, oh, actually, I never saw Stuber.
The other one that Kamal was in that had to do with Uber. What was that?
Those lovebirds. The lovebirds. Yeah. Not to, not to, yeah, it's another time. But you see these
product movies and you go, oh, Jesus, we bitch about to burn here all the time. However, you got mail
and you're a remake inspired by the AOL email service at the time. And it works. It's an
endearing film. Texted Walsh about halfway through it. I said, it's a very charming movie.
Have it laughed once, but I find it very charming. And then all of a sudden, it just got really funny
after that. And it's the last time we ever saw Tom Hanks in a movie. He's great in that movie.
He's Tom Hanks in it. He's doing all like the Tom Hanks head things and the squeaky Tom Hanks shit.
And he's being Tom Hanks in it. Like, and it's like, we haven't seen that since.
Meg Ryan, as always, incredibly stupidly endearing and lovely.
Dabney Coleman is great. Play's a real prick.
Maureen Stapleton, lovely, wonderful. Steve Zahn, Dave Chappelle, hilarious.
Chappelle. Parker Posey, great in the market.
Parker Posey, just a nightmare playing like that, that she's playing like the best in show lady on
like 10. She's great in them. Yeah, and Keneer, right? Keneer, yeah, plays like a ponytail,
like bleeding heart, yeah, writer who every even the liberal people think is annoying.
It's a very funny movie, a very sweet movie. It ends spoiler alert, obviously, with them meeting
and falling in love. And she reveals I hoped it was you because they despite her shopping clothes,
they forge a friendship and Hanks is apologetic for it happening. And then at the end,
they meet. Finally, she realizes he is the love of her life and vice versa. And they kiss and
the camera pans up to the sky. And it says the end, which is my only gripe with the movie. It's like
guys, let's not just glaze over that he shut down her legacy, you know, like give me a little button
where you see his story is still there and her shop is too because he paid to have it re -opened
because he's rich or something, like I thought that was like kind of undercutting her a little bit,
like, oh, that's enough. She falls in love. And it's like, no, that's not enough. Like what about her
shop and her mother's legacy? Like I felt a little, little shortcut on that. But other than that,
I thought it was a good movie. Well, you didn't see the 15 -minute post -credit sequence.
I do have the 4K Blu -ray 3D version of the film. It does have several deleted scenes.
I don't know. Which by the way, that was, I text you about that. What the fuck is that awful
Wimbleton movie? That tennis movie? There's a lot. You know, I'm a Wimbledon? No, I'm not Wimbleton.
The Dunst movie. Not Wimbledon. That's called Wimbledon. The one I texted you, the picture
that said that it's about to be released on Blu -ray. It features tons of deleted scenes.
It was, what was it? With Dunst? Son of a bitch. It's not Wimbleton. It's the Wimbledon.
It's the other one. It's the one by, I want to say it's Chris Columbus.
Tennis? Oh, shit. It's a big tennis movie. I thought it was. You're talking like the Correll
and the Stone one? No, it's a romantic comedy. It's not match point. It's not Borg McEnroe.
No. The only romantic comedy about tennis and it's called Wimbledon is Wimbledon. Maybe it's not
about tennis then. All right, well, my mom tries to get me to remember a movie. This is going to kill me.
That's the guy from... What was that show? Then she'll start trying to remember the show that
the guy was in and I'm like, Mom, you're getting even further away from the answer. I'm going to try
to find it while you review your next film. All right, I would just like to add that I fucking
love you got mail. I think it's even better than Sleepers and Seattle. I saw it on a date. My junior
year of high school, imagine like it's Christmas time and you go on a date and you Christmas shop and
go see you've got mail when you're 17. How great would that be to do that now? Oh, be
awesome to just add your whole life ahead of you. Maybe you get a hand job after.
Doring. New York City movie theater is reopening by the way. Very excited. Oh, wow. Not a
peep from LA. Well, out of stipulations, but you'll be able to go sit and watch your movie again.
All right, I'm going to find this while you talk. You said that before.
I saw Irresistible, which is a film whose title I took great issue with because I found it
quite easy to resist. This is a movie written and directed by John Stewart. John Stewart did a movie
Elizabeth town Elizabeth town. That is really bad movie. She followed up Wimbledon with Elizabeth
town and I set you the post that said Elizabeth town is being released on Blu -ray with tons of
deleted scenes. Well, I think that movie has deleted scenes because they had to like re -shoot it and change
everything because everyone hated the movie. Elizabeth town, I remember because Cameron Crowe was one of
my heroes and I was vanilla sky. I remember being like, okay, it's a departure for Crow, but I like it.
And then Elizabeth town, I said, boy, he's starting to lose it. And then when you hit a loha for
Christ's sake, there is no worse movie than a loha. You have to check that out if you haven't seen it.
It's worth seeing because of its badness. So Irresistible, John Stewart wrote and directed a movie
five plus years ago called Rosewater, which was like a, you know, an Iraq movie and that didn't work.
This works a little better than that, but it's just not good. And it's odd. I respect and love
John Stewart, but he's that guy. He's, I think he's way better at it than Trevor Noah. He's way
better at it than a lot of people that have done that type of shows since. Being a political dude who,
you know, makes quips, but for some reason his long form writing just doesn't work.
This movie is a bit of a disaster. It's Steve Carell playing a pundit. One of my favorite reviews I
saw in Letterbox was it just simply said this. Has Steve Carell ever not worn a fleece in a movie?
I was like, that's a good point. The man wears a lot of fleece. But it's Carell. He's a political
pundit. He goes to, you know, the inspiration for the movie seems to be like Joe, the plumber,
which happened 10 years ago, where they go to see Chris Cooper, who's an actor I love.
And he's this like small town hick that John Stewart thinks can be Arjo, the plumber, like our man
on the street, who helps humanize the party or whatever. So it's kind of trying to do, you know,
a Frank Capra type thing, but it's not a feel good movie in any way. Carell has this romance going on
with a 30 year old woman. He's 60. He looks 60. She looks 20. So it's even more awkward.
The romance doesn't fly. He's got these scenes with Rose Byrne, who's normally very funny, as like his
his Republican adversary. She licks his face at one point, which is unexplained. I'm not sure what
that was about. It's just a movie that takes a lot of swings. Occasionally it goes for like a sketchy
comedy moment that really feels weird and out of place. Tonally it doesn't work. There are no
laughs in it. I see why the movie was so hated. And you know that if Hollywood is coming after John
Stewart, that the product must be pretty bad because the guy's gotten a free pass now for 25 years.
It's not a good movie. It's on HBO Max right now, if you'd like to check it out. All right.
I'll close it with a picture called Kill the Irishman that I always wanted to see gangster movie.
Got a guy with the last name of green Irish guy muscled his way to the head of the teamsters union
in Chicago. And then basically single -handedly went to war with the mob. Yeah. Stars Christopher
walk in the actor who plays green. I'm blanking on his name right now. Directed and written in
Seth Green, right? Yeah. It's Seth Green. He's a little short for the role, but he pulls it off.
Yeah. It stars Ray Stevenson, directed by Jonathan Hensley, who also wrote die hard with
vengeance. He wrote Armageddon. He wrote and directed the Punisher. He wrote and directed the ice
road, which is I guess coming soon. I thought that was I was thinking of the ice storm. Anyway,
you know, it look, it's a mob movie. It's not the best. It's not terrible. It's pretty good. I'd
say it's an enjoyable 90 minutes. You're in and out. There's a lot of humor in it because this is
a man. The real -life story is that they tried to kill this guy 35 times and couldn't do it and then
finally killed him. Paul Servino pops up in it playing fat Tony Salerno. Always great to see Servino and a
mob flick. It's got to be nice to get that script at your house. What role do they want me to play?
Fat Tony is the role looking for. I would be like, God damn it.
So, you know, it's on Netflix right now and it doesn't tie into Scorsese's The Irishman in any way,
except for the fact that both stories featured Fat Tony Salerno. But it's here. Like I said,
it's an interesting enough film and I enjoyed it. All right. I will close with What's Up Doc
if we're going to do such a heavily Ryan O 'Neill episode of the show for whatever reason. Just kind
of happened that way. What's Up Doc is, you know, Screwball comedy was like one of five genres
in the 30s and they made a bunch of really great ones with just amazing dialogue. The stars were
always like Catherine Hepburn, Carrie Grant, Jimmy Stewart. People talking a mile a minute. The
Cohen brothers did a homage to it with HUD soccer proxy. I love trouble. It was a really terrible attempt
to try to bring them back with Julie Roberts and Nick Nolte as the best sort of modern screwball.
And at this point, it's 50 years old, so it's not modern anyway. But the best one is What's Up Doc.
It is written by Buck Henry who wrote the graduate. It is directed by Bogdanovich in his absolute
prime. It stars Streisand in her best performance and Ryan O 'Neill who is fine in it. Honestly,
I wish there was somebody better in his part. But it is a screwball comedy. You know,
basically it's the classic like there's four bags, four identical suitcases in a hotel. One
they keep mixing up the suitcases, you know, and there's doors slamming and running around and people
keep taking the wrong bag. I know I'm not making it sound great, but it's very, very funny. The
comedy is directed, especially in the home stretch. They have like this big car chase during a parade
in San Francisco that plays like the comedy version of Mad Max Fury Road. It's just beautifully
put together so many setups and payoffs. It's a really good funny movie. I recommend it highly.
What's Up Doc? All right. That's your movie corner. And our film today is a little picture,
big picture I should say called Promising Young Woman. Now, Joe, since we probably have more to
talk about with us, should we do VFW? We could do VFW. I think I have more to say about VFW, but
all right. Let's do VFW. You're right because you're at the end of the day. Yeah, I agree with you.
Let's do VFW. Okay. Seems tonally also to fit more into what we're talking about today.
I have a problem. Well, I'm saying, well, well, promising young woman's pretty heavy stuff,
you know, doesn't really fit into laughing at Ryan O 'Neill hitting on his own daughter.
Right. Right. Yeah, VFW. This is a small film.
A non -shudder. Made for Shudder original, I believe.
Tremendous cast. Let's just start there. You've got your George Wint. You've got your William Sadler.
Right. You've got Steven Lang from Avatar. Steven Lang. He's in Avatar. He's the villain in Avatar.
He's a great actor. He's been in so much shit. He's great. He's great. Don't breathe. Yeah.
You've got your Fred Williamson. You've got Martin Cove. You've -
Robracot. That's about it. That's those are the main people. There's a lot of other people in it.
But those are your heavy hitters and they play a gaggle of war vets. Vets that, you know,
have long since been in the shit as they say. And they hang out at a VFW. That's their local
American Legion basically type place. And it is run and operated by Steven Lang's character,
who also is a bit storied amongst them as being sort of the baddest of the bad as soldiers are
concerned. Not bad meaning bad, but bad meaning good. And the whole thing is sort of a take on -
It's almost like a running man style throw back to that kind of 80s movie. It's about a
drug called hype. That's a new street drug that people are obsessed with, which was funny,
because when that first came on the screen, Pat and I were - we watched it at the same time in
separate locations. We were texting each other like, you know, making jokes like, oh god,
it's going to be one of these like fake drug movies or whatever. And then you realize, no,
they're doing a nod to like Robo cop and all that shit. So even a nod to that like street
trash that Joe Bob did, which was the disgusting move where everybody's blowing up. All those movies
start with like, there's a new drug on the street called anal crunch. People are getting too high,
they're dying, you know, that was - Crunchers, we call them. Yeah. The plot of most 80s movies was
that most 80s action movies was trying to get a new illegal street drug off the streets.
So your basic storyline here is it's a one location horror survival. It's - or action survival really.
It's about a bunch of drug addicts who are addicted to this thing that they will do anything to get
their hands on. Three or four kilos of it end up inside the VFW because a girl robs the drug
Dan across the street and tries to take refuge in the VFW. And then these guys are locked into
the VFW and these lunatic drug dealers and their super high -jonesing customers are trying to break
into the VFW and kill everybody to get their drugs back. I mean, that's - that's based - it's - it's
really night of the living dead except without zombies instead with drug addicts. And man,
it's a lot of fun. God, it's a fun movie. It's very well - Yeah. It reminded me of like a
salt on precinct 13. There's a big kind of John Carpenter influence on it for sure. And also - I don't
know if you remember this movie from mid -90s called Original Gangsters, which Fred Williamson was
also in, I believe, but it was kind of bringing back the old heroes to get one last score.
VFW is - you know, if that premise intrigues you like some - some 80s heroes coming back to kick some
ass, you know, it's - it's the perfect example of that kind of genre. It's not a masterpiece, you know,
don't want to oversell, but if you like that kind of low -budget action with some old dudes,
Vietnam vets kicking ass, you know, it's a really good example of that kind of movie. Very fun.
Practical effects, great violence. It's all done. Stopping on heads and they're blowing up,
you know, like really, really surprisingly, gory. Yeah, there's a young soldier that comes into the mix,
played by an actor named Tom Williamson, who I'm not familiar with, but this is the first
of my resort. I wondered if he might be Fred Williamson's son. Yeah, I didn't even realize that's
all right now. That's a good point. Anyway, he comes in and he's sort of the new soldier with the
old heroes, whatever, and they respect him for being a young guy that signed up and he respects them for
being the vets. And he's got a scene where he punches a man's face into nothing. Yeah, it's a crazy
ridiculous, I can't even explain it. There's a wink to camera with all of it. It's not,
it's not violence that's disturbing like when you watch it and you're like, oh my god, like what's that
movie with Maria? What's her face? Mary Magdalene from the chick from Twin Peaks. The hell was her name?
The hot woman that's always in his dream. And David Lynch's dream. What are you talking about?
Monica Balucci. Monica Balucci. That movie she was in where they beat the Twin Peaks?
Yeah, the new one. The movie, remember that movie she was in though? They beat the guy's face in
with like irreversible. Yeah, irreversible. Yeah. It's not a reversible place that, you know,
to deeply traumatize your soul and this take to a different direction. This was absurd. This is
supposed to be fun. It's crazy. It's ridiculous. And then also they kind of do the thing of like
the they they make the bad guys such assholes that and they keep getting killed worse and worse. It's
in Rambo, you know, like, you know, it's there's a wink to camera. They get everything they possibly
can out of one location. I mean, it's impressive. And much like Mandy, which I'd say this is a kin too.
I could see this being in a box set next to Mandy. It's got that 80s vibe and it feels to me
like this guy made a movie that he wanted to rent when he was a kid that he never could find,
you know, like we said that about I said about Mandy. Mandy feels like the movie you thought you were
renting when you saw that awesome cover in the video store and then you got home and it sucked.
This is one of those two. Like, if I would have saw this, if I'd seen this movie,
when I mean, it's even got the scene where they make weapons, which is like a classic 80s trope,
you know, the old filing down the pool queue into a spear kind of vibe. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
we're going to make grenades out of tennis balls. Right. So, oh, David Patrick Kelly is in this too,
who's another staple of all, you know, he always plays a fucking sleigh. He's actually a nice guy
in this, but he's, you know, he's the, he's the main asshole in the warrior's. He's the creep in,
uh, he's the creep in, um, Ford Fairlane, he's the creep in DreamScape. Um, he was also in Twin Peaks
the return, uh, just a fun group seeing, seeing them all together. Uh, it is. I, I asked Joe like,
you think these guys got in fist fights every day or they were dear friends, but the, the, the
camaraderie by the end of it, the chemistry makes me feel like they got along in his pounded shots
all day and had a great time. It's, uh, it's a fun movie. And it reminded me, Joe, of how you
introduced me to the wonderful VFW here in LA and then immediately left so I cannot go there anymore,
which sucks. They're doing movies there now. They were showing Wonder Woman in the parking lot the
other night. Well, you should go early there. They must be hurting for finance, but you should go.
Yeah, well, I didn't want to see Wonder Woman again, believe it or not. Oh, that's a good point.
All right. I mean, I would go just to be outside and drink. Sure. Uh, Tom Williamson is not
Fred Williamson's son. I made that assumption simply because they were both black and I apologize
for that because they have the same last name that's, you know, yeah, and the same last name. And I
thought I assumed he said to the director, you know, my son would be great for this part. I created
a whole dialogue between the men that didn't exist. He's not a son. But, um, yeah, I think anyone
listening to this podcast, uh, you know, I think would get a kick out of VFW. I don't want to
oversell. I think Joe liked it a little more than me, but it feels like the kind of movie you stumble
into, laid on cable, you stumble into because Joe Bob loves it. I hope he does it on the show and
has some great stories from behind the scenes. Um, it's a, it's a really fun movie, you know,
I had a good time with it. So it was fun for me to see Martin Cove play a guy you were rooting for.
Yeah. Exactly. Because, you know, I know Martin Cove's been in tons of stuff and I know he's not
always playing a bad guy, but, you know, obviously, I think most of us associate him with, uh, with
Cobra Kai and, uh, and the karate kid and being the worst human being that's ever lived. So, uh,
it was fun like rooting for Martin Cove and seeing him like have jokes
before the shit hits the fan in the script, seeing that, you know, again, the camaraderie amongst them.
Fred Williamson is really funny in it. Um, he, he kind of steals the show.
Uh, and Stephen Lang, I said the two of them are really the heavy hitters. Um, the young woman in it,
she's new, um, and she's great, but her name is Sierra McCormick. She plays a character named Lizard.
Uh, Travis Hammer plays the head drug dealer real prick and Dora Madison plays his,
like second and command drug dealer. Everybody's really great in it. I really liked it. Like I said,
this was 90 minutes to me of bubblegum, eat in and out. It's pure escapism.
And it, it's one I'd like to put on the shelf because it feels to me like the movie I was trying to rent
every time I went to the video store when I was 12 years old. So,
hats off to the director. His name is, uh, Joe, uh, Joe Begoes, Joe Begoes.
Max, Joe Begoes. Yeah, he's, he's done a bunch of independent stuff. He also did a movie called Bliss
that actually looks completely froze up, folks. So I don't know if you caught that. We might have had a little audio issue there.
Can you hear me? Yeah, it's been steady throughout, but not worth commenting on. That was just a complete freeze.
So we might want to get out before it shuts us down. All right. But you can hear me now. We're good.
Yes. Yes. Yeah. There you go, folks. There's a little peek behind the curtain for you.
Anyway, check out the, check out the other work. Yeah, the other worker Joe Begoes, Max Braille,
or Matthew McCartle wrote it. Check out their stuff. Thumbs up, hogs up for old VFW.
Hog is up here for VFW as well. And for drinking at VFW, which is fun.
Folks, we'll see you next time with promising young woman, and we will see you in hell.