Summer is here, and Bed MDM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer.
Or check out our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz.
Only available at Bed MDM Casino.
Spend on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 fortunes, Mystery of the Land,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand!
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action!
Bet MGM in Game Sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 Plus to Wager, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and West Virginia
only, games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as non -mustrable site credit slash bonus bets unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
The football season is full of guarantees, and here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October, if
your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning or winning money back in fan
cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
Winning hits different here.
Monthly 21 -plus, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gambler, offer not available in all states
terms apply, see Fanatic Sportsbook app.
Hey everyone, welcome to the We'll see you in hell podcast now a part of the Fangoria
podcast network for more information about the network, including other programs, how
to follow the show and find past episodes of We'll see you in hell.
Please visit Fangoria .com now on with the show and on with the Joe hi Joe, Derosa, I'm
good. Uh, it's good to see you. It's been about a month since I've seen you in a month
since we don't turn it on now. Because before we started recording this thing, I said to you,
you know, Pat, I haven't seen you in a month. I'm happy to see you. You look like you could care
less than I'm even standing here. Don't, don't you dare turn it on now for the fans. Um, I think it's
important that they think, you know, we're like parents with, uh, you know, the children can't know
the friction between mom and dad. We need them to think that things are okay. Yeah, you are right.
I want to let it out now, but we should save it for the autobiography. You know, we didn't get
along. We wouldn't speak for months of the time, except for when we were recorded. If I don't jump
into Joe's arms like, uh, you know, the poster of I now pronounce you Chuck and Larry,
then Joe gets his feelings hurt. But I play it a little closer to the vest.
Well, but by jumping into my arm's pat means
even hinted a smile
I mean it just walks in he literally looks like his dog was just raped in front of him like just just just
Just sorry was that too rough image it would be if I had a dog yeah, if you'd said cat
I would have walked out my sweet sweet cat. I mean you but you well, okay
You walk in like you just found your cats head in the mailbox. Come on. It's some kind of told you. I didn't need this message
I text him today. I go, Hey, man, what do you say we we bar hop around my new neighborhood after we record the pod tonight because there's a lot of great spots.
He goes, yeah, sure, that's fine. And I go, okay, cool. And I go, it'll be fun to explore a bit. And then he writes back explore. We're not hiking the Himalayas. I'm like, how about you say, sounds fun. Well, how about you sounds fun. Here's the truth. Here's the truth. It's my birthday, or it was yesterday.
And I of course had to do a little birthday dinner with the Mrs
But today was gonna be my birthday hang I said look I got all these cupcakes and treats liquor
Why don't we come by my house smoke a little pot have some drinks the big beautiful house ladies out of town
You know have a nice time. I asked Joe. I asked a couple other friends. Joe's like sounds fun
Oh, actually you said oh, yeah the red lions right by your house, which it isn't a
But be yeah, there's a bar so there's another option than being trapped in your beautiful home. Let me just let me say this
Let me finish you didn't say you didn't say let's do this you said I'm happy to do this if you want
I said I'm happy to do whatever at this point because I the alternative is Joe comes to your house
He's on his phone checking it and then he's like we got to get out of here. We got to go hit the bars
Well, it's not fun because I'm sorry if I don't think it's a
as a ripper and Friday night for a bearded man to invite me to his
polatial estate just the two of us and fans and other friends.
One other friend you put in the initial text not looking to have a bash here.
Sounds like a real hoot pack. Well I asked a couple other friends but you know I
thought that would be a real nice time so then I knew Joe was gonna hit me with
let's go to a bar instead. Well let's go be social. Be social with who we never
Talked to anyone but ourselves unless you're looking for something to fuck which is probably the gate. Oh, yeah, dear
Something that's what that's what it is. This is how he phrases. That's what it is
We always sit in a dank corner of a bar and talk to only each other until someone gets up to talk to the bartender to say
Three more please and is it not a great time? Yeah, we we would have had a great time my house
We listen to records. I got all these new records and and what did I say today now?
Now we also go over to Joe's all the time to smoke and listen to listen to music and
drink. I put a little bit of a thing together. I put a little bit of a thing. How many times
of me you have been said over there and done nothing? Let me just say this and I said this
in the god damn text message today, you nasty bitch. I said just for a little while we can hop around
And then we can go back to your place and hang out thinking oh, it's a nice two -parter of a night
Which is what we always do with my place? We go to bars first and we come back here and then you write
Not up for a big
Late hang tonight. Well, because then here's what it is you go out till 10. You're wasted
You don't get to put it in anything. So then you're like no, I guess as an as an afterthought as like a final
option then yeah we'll go over to Pats now then we shove in my house drunk you
guys are over there until two in the morning spill and beer on the floor and
then I got to get up at eight to do man get up at eight I got I got a home
repair tomorrow I'm not that you're doing I got to keep that palatial estate in
order no I'm not doing it but I have to let the guy in at eight a .m. this is this is
the big thing and then I have other things to do that I cannot discuss on this
that's fine but I told you what they can't be a little hungover let the guy in at
sleep for two more hours then go run your errands I don't I don't I'm not
letting my beautiful home be a be a second or third choice because you couldn't
get late I'm not doing it's not first of all I just want to point out how many
times you've referred to women as things that's how you refer no no no no that's
what you just said you said because you didn't get to put it in anything yeah that's
what I meant because we're we're heading the the bar skank crowd so now
every woman that goes to a bar is a skank.
Wait, this is the 20s?
That's what I said.
Every woman that goes to a bar is a skank.
Listen, any woman that's going home with Joe from a bar
is probably a skank.
All right, listen, first of all, please don't make me sound
like some kind of goddamn jiggle -o working the circuit for a couple
of dollars on a Friday night.
Joe has been added to the cast of Showtime's jiggle -os.
All I was saying was, it's fun to go out, it's Friday night,
it's fun to go out a bit on the town, but it's my birthday.
It was birthday yesterday and you chose to spend it. I did not receive a happy birthday from you until today
So I'm counting that as my and I version of your I've never heard of my birthday from you
You want to get on your birthday is you want to get it? I told you when my birthday is coming up on
That's when mine is because I invite you to the party. I have every year and you never say happy birthday
You don't even come to the party sometimes. I've certainly said happy birthday. I've given you gifts before I don't know
I've never given me a birthday. I'll put it on my calendar
you gave me Christmas gifts and I gave you a Christmas gift this year and I've
given you Christmas gifts in the past. Here's my point. Fine, it's your birthday.
We can go to one I upgraded it us at the Black Sabbath show. That was really
great. Get us down on the floor. That was really great. Final show of Black Sabbath.
That was really great. A birthday gift. No, listen, that's fine. That's fine.
Do me a favor. Do you want to rub paycheck stubs in my face right now?
Honestly, yes. Let me go grab one. Look, if you really want to go to your place
tonight we can go to your place. Okay. Now the offer is off the table. Why? Why can't we go out?
I said happy hour drinks. Why is that so bad? To precursor someone to your house and they're like,
yeah, let's go to a bar though. Let's explore. Guess what? I had a little get together on New Year's Eve.
Okay. Guess what I suggested we do beforehand. Let's go to a happy hour for it. It's fun to go to a happy
hour. Then go back to the house. Here's what I don't like. Offer people to my beautiful house,
getting getting proposed other options and here's what I really don't like which is not not something you've done here
But it's a similar thing
It does so a buddy of mine the other night. Hey, do you want to hang out?
This was in Missouri by the way where like you know, I'm I'm in town. I'm visiting
You want to hang out who else is gonna be there that to me is like our friendship is over I
Take it so I take it so badly and I shouldn't perhaps but don't say who else is gonna be there because that means you're not enough
And that's why I feel you're your beautiful home is not enough for what's bugging me about you right now. All right
For for for years this guy has has thrown his big Vegas dick in my face
How great Vegas is how he goes he wins all this money out there and ask you to go several times
It's a great time and everything. I finally get a gig in Vegas. I call him up. I go Pat
I got a gig in Vegas. It's it's one night. Maybe two come with me, please
So it will have fun he was I can't go you know I can't go everybody because this fucking psycho went to Vegas
two times within a week and a half of each other one of those times for six days
I don't know what kind of lunatic goes to Vegas for six days and then before it is
Before that he texted me he texted me about a casino bitching
That they're not copying him a room or something also not true and I said I said that's why I hate Vegas
They got they got they got no class some joke or whatever and then he writes back
I'm not in Vegas yet. I'm in St. Louis
You couldn't wait till you got to Vegas to Campbell you had to go gamble in St. Louis
And then go down to Vegas for the second time in a week and a half. It was too much
That's what I'm saying to you. You're right there. I needed you this time. The truth is I was already going on New Year's Eve with my lovely girlfriend
We had plans to go and have fun the room was booked
We're gonna go see and we did see the weekend who performed for 45 minutes on December 30th while the crowds like still getting drinks
He's done and that's what you get for going to see the weekend
It was in fury now because he's been amazing in the past
But now that he's huge he's like fuck you and it really pissed me off then I go see Elton John who's been doing it since my parents were kids
And he gives the best fucking show I've ever seen now I saw I wanna let's get on the same page for a minute here
I saw John two summers ago who is again, as you just said, one of the best shows I've ever seen. He's incredible
He came out open with the bitches back. He did just night as well
And then right into Benny and the Jets. I must have been doing the same
Yeah, hit the hit the first piano chord of Benny and the Jets the place went fucking berserk
Yeah, stood up. Yes like give me some more
Did he do the thing where he pounds the top of the piano like cheer louder? Yeah, it was awesome
Then he's like now I'm gonna play a 12 -minute song about the plight of the Native American and I was like
Okay, and that was great. What was that song he didn't do that was pepperin and some old you know
Obscurities and then he fucking closed with circle of life
Oh, see I was thrilled he left that out of the city. No, I was happy
I wouldn't have been happy with can you feel the love tonight. I was happy with circle of one he
I saw I saw my the outside lands festival, which is yeah, it was one of your hip her music
He left out all the Disney bullshit. Yeah, he went straight hits front to back
I mean, it played for two and a half hours and it was non -stop hit.
I'm still standing.
I guess that's why they call it the blues.
Yeah.
Saturday night was made for fighting.
I think that was the closer.
Yeah, but they know the hit.
Yeah.
All right.
It was a great show.
You don't have to condescend that I'm enjoying a memory.
That's great show.
But I'm not done.
I mean, you do railed my story.
This is why you haven't heard the bad Santa story, though.
No, this is not why.
We both agree that you'd save it to their silent night deadly night episode and we both
forgot to tell it in that.
You skipped the segment you're like let's just get to the movie because we had to get out of there and you said you agreed
You said you didn't go no Joe. I got to tell the story. I go no
We but we forgot I went along with it. We forgot but folks tell me god damn bad Santa story
We had it we had four nights in Vegas for New Year's Eve now my buddies sold a movie
I can get a free room there whenever I want they're like we're gonna go out and celebrate
There's a three of my good buddies who I never see I'm like, you know what that'd be a blast
I went out I realized as I rolled into the second Vegas trip
It was too much. I told my girlfriend. I don't want to go for a really long time. So I'm not going to go two weeks later now in St. Louis. I
Guess I will tell you this. They have a casino there, but it's also a beautiful hotel. It's one of the nicer hotels there. I go
I'm going to go in. I call them at six o 'clock. Can I get a room tonight? They go. Sure. I show up at 9 .45 we gave your room away
There's no more rooms. Whoop to tell them why you call them to get a room. You were gambling for many hours
Well, I had gambled there. Sure. I gamble with my family. That's what I like to do. You weren't just calling and saying can I have a room?
You were calling and saying I've been gambling here. Can you caught me a room? Yes. Yeah, can you?
Well, that's a key part of the story. Well, you had already said that. So I thought they knew that
They I said can you caught me a room for the night? They said sure
It's I call them at six. I show up at nine forty five. They go Mr. Walsh. We've given your room away. I drove about an hour to be there
I go what are you talking about?
They said well, we gave it away. I said I have a reservation here
That's what a reservation is. It's like the sign felt bad anyone can just take them. I'm like, what are you?
What are you saying? They go well our policy is at nine o 'clock
We give away the rooms if if you're not here. I said that policy is insane. You have a hotel room for the night
That's not a policy. Well, it is our policy. I said, where is that posted?
Why was that not said to me on the phone?
They well, they should have told you on the phone, but they didn't well, then it's definitely in your confirmation email
I hope my email on my phone. I have four they sent it four times the confirmation email for some reason and I open it and
Thank Christ because I was waiting for it to be in there and then I had to just eat it
It wasn't in the email. So I'm truly sad. It wasn't in the email. No, no
No, I'm sad it was I would have been furious
But I at myself because I would have been like okay, I guess I should have read the fire would be gleeful right now
I'm reading the smallest of print. I go I go here
I've blown up the small print. I go search this email. It's not in there
She says, Mr. Walsh, I assure you it is I go then please point it out to me. I hate these
Confrontation. Did you call her a thing? I've been in customer service. Did you call her a thing? No, she wasn't
sex with you. Hey, thing. She's scrolling through it and I see her face from chin to forehead like in a cartoon.
Slowly the red rises. She's got one of those rashy splotchy faces and the rash just rises up until her face is all
rash and she goes all right well it's not in this email and I go then you want to check one of the
other three you sent me because they're all the same she goes I get it sir but they definitely
told you on the phone I said well a second ago it was they should have told me on the phone now
as they definitely did I go I'll tell you this if I call it 6 p .m somebody definitely should have
said you need to be here by nine or we're giving your room away sure nobody said that or else I would have
been here at nine. I'm visiting with my fucking mom because I
figure I have a hotel room for the night. Right. So I can
spend a little time with my mom. He went over romantic evening.
You and mom in the hotel. This is what I mean. This is why I
don't want to come to your house later. These are odd hangouts
that you orchestrate. I wasn't with my mother and I are going to
get a hotel room in the casino together. Joe, this was a
hotel room for me. Just for you. My mom's home alone. She'll
leave your loving family to go. Again, it's not any better. No,
because, well, if you want to get into my family dynamics,
they go, Pat, you're welcome to stay here anytime.
Then I go into the room, I'm supposed to be staying in.
It's covered in gift wrap.
Your family actually says that there's a treadmill.
Yeah, there's no room for me to sleep.
That's amazing.
You're welcome.
I know it's amazing.
This is why I am the way I am.
You're welcome to stay here anytime.
It's for Christ's sakes.
They're not, they're not friends in another city.
Well, once they divorce, all bets were off.
And then I go to my dad's house.
I got a giant shelter dog attacking me.
I'm like, this is why I'm not staying here.
I scream over the dog barks as I run for my car. It's a terrible life. It's kind of okay over there
It's my dog okay because he looks dead right now. It's fine. He's fine. How much is he calm down?
Yeah, he's calm down parking up. All right, listen, but that that's that's what I'm saying here folks is the
Emerald star casino in St. Charles, Missouri in a hotel. You have a terrible policy. I wrote a letter to them today
Did you know what they're gonna say? Well, no, oh geez. No, I went back and stayed at my mom's house on the fucking couch
I don't know what you're saying.
almost two months ago folks I go in to see bad Santa too I'm by myself I'm off
it's my first day off of work and I'm getting ready to go do my Thanksgiving
type shit I go up to the cheesecake factory I have a drink I have a little time to
kill I have a second drink I'm not proud of any of this but this is what I did
all right I walk into the movie there's a nice crowd and I I tell you what folks I
I was so excited to see bad Sanito.
I just can't, can I just interject.
It all just came together.
You live like a 68 year old woman from the Midwest.
Look, it's not great.
You're going to Vegas five nights at a clip.
You're drinking alone at the cheesecake factory.
You're getting hotel rooms in St. Louis by yourself
in casinos.
It's not great.
It finally all makes sense.
It all makes sense.
What I also did mention, folks, I didn't go to Vegas
because I have a four year girlfriend
and Joe's going for the AVN awards.
I'm not going for the AVN awards.
I'm going to do a show during the avianno during the avianno that I'm headlining. Okay, well congrats
All right, a little brief backstory bad Santa when I saw it on Thanksgiving day when I had first moved to New York
I was I was Travis bickling it up. I was doing nothing but push -ups
I spoke to no one for months and my two best friends came out to visit and I felt like I was born again
I was so happy to see them and we all got wasted and we saw the first bad Santa and I had never laughed so hard in my life
still when I watch the movie I die laughing I think it's an incredible comedy I
go into bad Sanatoo I'm like if this is half as good as bad Santa I'll be very
happy but I know what's going on I know that the script was co -written by the
fucking guy who did the entourage all right I mean what a step down you got the
Cohen brothers on the first one at the helm and then you get the entourage I
mean uncredited Cohen brothers but yeah they apparently drastically reduced it
which is a huge you know and you go from Terry's Wig off who was a mad genius as
director to this guy, you know, who directs a lot of like kind of fluff, but he's a decent
director, Mark Waters, whatever. So I go into the movie and already I'm like, well, here
we go. The row behind me has about 25 kids in it, little kids, 10 years old, no parent
anywhere. And I watch them all walk into this thing and they're waiting for the usher to
like turn around and sneak past him. So this whole row is full of kids and they are talking
louder than I am talking now from the second the movie begins.
So I'm like, okay, then the flashes begin.
I look back and the kids are taking flash photography of the screen in a movie theater.
So I'm getting angrier and angrier.
We've all been in these situations.
You want to do the Costanza thing where you go insane at them.
I'm just not that kind of a person.
This story unfolds.
It doesn't discredit my 68 year old good Western woman theory.
Yeah, here's what I was doing
A lot of heavy size a lot of looking over my shoulder at them and these kids were just no one in the theater was saying anything to them
They were driving me insane so eventually I walk out I go to the Usher much like a 68 -year -old woman I
Go hey, man. I don't know what's going on in here
But there's 25 kids children in this filthy R rated movie and
and they won't shut up, and it's not whispering.
They're talking, they're running around,
they're punching each other,
and they're taking flash photos of the screen.
Can you please come in and throw them out or talk to them?
Oh, well, they shouldn't be in there, it's all right.
Yeah, I know, you were guarding the door,
but they got past you earlier.
Oh, no, he's telling you that, yeah.
So he goes, yeah, absolutely, I'll be right in there.
Which already I'm like, why don't you walk in with me?
Sure.
So I go in, I sit down, the man never comes in.
Until I never saw him again he never came into the theater. So I'm sitting there
I'm fuming I'm getting anger and anger and to make matters worse folks my very brief review of bad
Santa 2 is that it's one of the worst movies I've ever seen in my entire life and
My buddy Derek Waters who I do the drunk histories with had raved about it
I was hammer texting him when I got out like you you're on the payroll you couldn't have liked this movie
He's the only person I've talked to who enjoyed it
But I had a strong recommendation on top of being excited and this movie is so fucking terrible
So terrible the villains in it you would expect to be in a movie about like a a dog who can talk
It's how bad the villains in this movie are it's terrible nothing works in it. There's no funny jokes
It's a bad movie. I mean there are funny jokes in a trailer though. It's really that bad in addition to those
There's nothing so you wouldn't like it on a plane, you know
So I'm fuming I'm getting angry or an anger and then the kids all stand up together
I'm like, oh, thank God they're going to get out of here and they all walk down and sit in the front row
Together, okay, and resume full volume conversations and start taking photos of the screen flash photos from the front row
So I guess they're like, hey, nobody's yelled at us. Let's take it up a notch
People had already moved to the front to get away from them when these kids moved down to the front
They start moving to the back and something snapped in me folks. I'm like they're terrorizing this audience
No one is saying anything myself included and I walked down my hands were shaking and I lean over the aisle
And I go hey
Shut the fuck up or get the fuck out
Just something I've never done in my life. Okay, right I screamed it and
Folks, I'm not kidding when I say they all turn to me and look so terrified
that I immediately felt terrible and then the theater began applauding everyone in
the theater started applauding and then I felt better and these kids got up and
they were so scared that they all ran out of the theater but as they run out the
one punk kid in the back he goes come at me bro to me I ignored him of course
and then they left but I guess he was challenging me to to a fight which I feel
So pretty confident in saying I would have won.
I don't know.
Now he was a 10 year old.
I mean, you were drunk.
I was I was buzzed.
By walk back, I sit in my seat and this woman behind me goes, thank you so much.
She's like, they shouldn't even be in here.
I said, you know what?
That's right.
They shouldn't even be in here.
And then we sit down and the rest of us for 45 minutes sat in complete silence and
watched the bitter end of bad Santa 2 which is terrible.
Then the movie ends, I walk out and waiting for me in the Americana which is, if you're
We're in LA, it's like the Armenian Grove,
but it's a big outdoor mall, very upscale.
And I walk out and the kid has waited for me
outside of the theater for 45 minutes, the punk kid.
And I'm like, what's gonna happen here?
And he goes, hey, I said yes.
He goes, you can't talk to little kids that way.
You're an adult.
You shouldn't talk to little kids that way.
Did he say it A -D -O -L -T?
Because that would have been my hat's off to the adult now
You can't talk to little kids that way. You're an adult
And I said well, you can't be in our rated movies because you're a kid
I was talking to you like an adult because in the dark
I assumed you must be an adult at an R rated movie. He goes well, it's not fair
You shouldn't talk to kids like that. I said okay, but you also shouldn't be screaming through the movie and then I realize
I'm now in public
I'm outdoors at a mall with Christmas music playing Christmas decorations everywhere with my hands over my head
Catching myself seconds from screaming at a child again in public and I just no round of applause outside
I'll tell right applause. There was mom's galore staring at me
Terrified like what what is going on here? Is this their dad? Is he going to hit this kid?
Is he gonna molest him? He's screaming at a child. Nobody knows what's about that at an outdoor mall at Christmas time
And I stopped myself mid -sense. I took a deep breath and I walked away and then he yelled something after me
I don't know what it was. Oh, I could take a guess. I wouldn't hear it, but I assure you it wasn't nice
But he only had the balls to yell to my back because his balls haven't descended yet because he's 10
He's a ten -year -old pet and folks that's the story and it's been greatly over -hyped but basically the moral
The story is I screamed at a child in public. There you have it folks. Let's do a quick movie recap
I really think we should what we've seen. Yeah
Watching these academy screeners we get I am watching these academy screeners and I think I'm about to become a member of the
Directors Guild okay after having directed my special which by the way people February 3rd comes out
It's not plugged up on comedy central and then February
I believe seventh is when the album
Comes out and you can download the special on can you stop this bouncing update thing from your computer because I know it's
That that drives me insane and I can't focus. I don't know how to stop it right now really. I'm afraid if I click it
It's gonna stop I can't right now turn away from it. You have to turn away from it that Adobe premiere update thing that pops up
It makes me completely insane
I don't, what have I seen, Petty?
You see La La Land?
There was a request for us to discuss that.
No real interest in watching it.
I love La La Land and it's so like sincere.
It seems like something that I would hate.
I loved it so much and I turned my girlfriend afterwards.
She was like, eh, and I couldn't believe
that somebody didn't like it.
And it's gotten really good reviews,
but so many people hate it, especially like friends of mine
and comedy and stuff hate it so much.
I feel I should watch it again because maybe
I was wrong. I don't know but I loved it. I thought it was great. People don't like musicals like that. I like musicals
I just didn't for some reason didn't really have much of an interest in it. The weak link is the songs and the singing is certainly so far
Problem with the mute. You did that's that makes for a bad musical if the singing in the songs are the bad part
Yeah, but I mean, there's not a there's not a tremendous amount of songs and the choreography and shit was all really great
The opening scene is one for the ages. There's a big traffic jam dance number like in fame
Yeah, but I mean if you're gonna be you know like arms folded like oh god
They're singing again. Don't say it. I mean I don't mean you. I mean people in general
Fences I enjoyed it quite a bit. I did too. Just phenomenal fucking acting phenomenal acting from Denzel and Vell of Davis
I almost played is maybe our best actor. He could be honest and and Vell of might be our best actress
And I'm the only reason I'm putting the gender thing on it is so we can fairly represent both people
They were both incredible in a giant pool of actors, but yeah, they're they're both incredible in it
I truly do think they could be the two best people out there. I got it was a film play
You know much like Glen gerry Glen Ross is a film to play it doesn't bother me it bothers some people
It felt a little stagy sure
But the acting was so great. I had no no qualms. You know part. I loved about fences. No, densels character tells a lot of tall tales
It was it was almost like a racially motivated big fish. Yeah, I could see that you know
I enjoyed it. Of course you don't see like witches or anything like that, but I did enjoy that all the stories
He told about meeting the devil and playing him in baseball and stuff like that. Yeah, yeah, and I thought it was a great film
I also saw you mentioned this before but I finally saw Sully and
We talked about the 80s sitcom blow -end thing. Yeah, you talked about the 80s to come ending
Yeah, I would have done it in July and they laughed and it fades out and I said to myself there's no fucking way it ends like that. Yeah, even though you knew that's how it ended and I watched the thing and sure enough that is exactly how the only way it could have been more of a sitcom if it frees frame. I thought it would freeze
friend. Tom Hanks looks back at him and does one of those shaking his head laughs. Yeah,
which is like the dad on Alf kind of just fades out. Yeah. Yeah. Crazy. Crazy.
Uh, last on my list, Patty, uh, is, uh, I finally got, I got a lot of horror movies for Christmas
and we, you know, we can get into them more specifically later on another episode. But the
one I really want to push is I did get the scream factory, uh, special edition Blu -ray
of the Exorcist three. Yes. It does have the fabled directors cut on it. It is a different movie.
It is phenomenal. It is worth seeing. And the original phenomenal phenomenal as well. So I can't
stress to you enough. As a horror fan, particularly if you're an Exorcist fan, you need to go get
that blue ray. It's really, really tremendous. I'm going to get it. Yes. Yeah, I mean, I've seen a
But we've talked too long last night last night because it's fresh my mind I watched hidden figures that comes out today in theaters
So that's a good one to discuss it's supposed to be great. I haven't seen it yet. Yeah, it's about you know three
African -American women who are helping with you know the John Glenn astronauts NASA in the 60s
It was a very straight down the middle like Disney Channel. It's rated PG
It's telling a great story that I had never heard of before but it's these women who were like so amazing at math
And yet still had to face adversity because they're a black and
It's really great in that way like it's sometimes it's great to watch a PG movie like because I never do it
Right, and they're I was like I lame lame stupid whatever it did it with minimal schmaltz
It was a great story very well told Kevin Costner's great in it
as kind of the guy who's a toughy at first becomes a softy and the three
actresses in an Octavia Spencer front who's who's an empire.
Terragi P. Henson is awesome in it and Janelle Monet, who I love as a musician, is great
in both this movie and Moonlight and she's also unbelievably attractive.
Okay.
It's a great story very well told it's a here's what it is. I wish I had told you this before Christmas break
It's a perfect parents movie. Okay. We're not nobody's uncomfortable. Everybody feels good. I would check it out
It's a good move. I don't know if I had the screen to reform Christmas break. Yeah, uh, I
I tried to start
Nocturnal animals. I couldn't do it. It's a bad moment. You you've talked about it. You talked about it a few episodes ago
Yeah, I couldn't do it. It's just the second they did that
And the second they put so much focus on Amy Adams getting a paper cut, I was like,
this is going to be one of these dark indie dramas.
I don't want to do this.
I just got a sense of it.
And then my manager told me in explicit detail what plays out in the movie and I'm glad
I didn't watch it now.
Yeah.
And when you hear about it, it sounds much cooler than it is.
It's not well done.
I didn't think.
It didn't sound cool.
It sounded really depressing.
Yeah.
And really sad.
And I'm glad I didn't watch it.
Let's talk I also saw Dupama you saw that I saw it on theaters. I fucking loved it
For now because I love all of his fucking movies phenomenal. Yeah, body double in the mail looking forward to
Seeing that body double is great real quick new segment, and then we'll get to Rogue One
Scary stuff. This is just a new segment where
Myself or Pat or both of us will discuss I don't even know what this is and item
I told you about it and you don't run the segments by the cohost. No, no, I ran this by you and you said I and this was your exact response. Love it. Let's do it.
That was your exact response. Let's see what it is. It's called scary stuff. Scary stuff. This is this is our related material that is not necessarily a movie. Okay.
So this is where we can discuss your box sets of TV shows or your video games or your toys or whatever. Okay. Today I am choosing to discuss the
Recently released, I mean, I don't know how recently released it was, but it's, you know, it was late 2016
PS4 Xbox One edition of Resident Evil 4
This is a remastered version of Resident Evil 4
in all your HD glory that you could ever want. Resident Evil 4 pat is my favorite video game of all time
Number one slot of all time. This is the greatest video game I've ever played
It is the perfect mixture of action, gore, puzzle solving, there's a level where you get trapped in a cabin and zombies are breaking through the windows and you've got to fight them off. It's just a really really phenomenal scary action adventure game. It's a lot of fun.
This is a re -release of an old game or a new game.
Well, it came out originally for the GameCube initially in the early Aughts, and then eventually
went to the other systems, and now the Resident Evil Capcom has been re -releasing some of the
Resident Evil titles as remastered versions for the new systems.
Okay.
So, this is Resident Evil 4 for your latest system with updated graphics and HD look and everything.
And Game Informer says it's pulse pounding action, IGN says it's an absolute must -have.
game spot says it's an amazing achievement and games radar says one of the best games we've ever played
I totally agree it's my favorite game of all time if you love horror even if you're tired of
zombies this you got to play this game it's so good it's so so good uh fantastic and uh I don't
play video games I have nothing to add but I've seen seven of the movies at this point and there's
another one coming out yeah well so that's scary stuff I got it so next time you come in you go
I played Resident Evil iPhone or whatever, I just downloaded Mario Go, is that scary enough for you?
No, okay. I hear it's fun. I think Mario Go, because our podcast, the umbrella covers fantasy,
horror and sci -fi, yeah, I accept that. There's one of our fans who is very critical.
He said listening to us talk politics made him want to kill himself.
I thought actually when listening back thought it was a very interesting conversation.
I don't think I was a fan. I think he just started listening for the first time and then was like, I want to kill myself.
Yeah, but today he's like, please go back to the old format.
Oh, that's like maybe you could talk about horror again, which felt a little critical to me.
Well, we make it pretty evident at the top of the podcast that we're going to talk about yeah a bunch of stuff
And then we're going to focus on a movie each episode and we always do that we don't ever not do it and
Fangoria encompasses sci -fi fantasy everything else. Yes. So today look
This is just a movie that we couldn't not discuss. Yeah, it's an event film. It's got to be discussed
It falls under the end of the category Star Wars story rogue one
And let's get into it, you know, I'll just say right off the bat, I thought it was phenomenal, I loved it, it is in my top.
I mean, at this point you've got a lot of Star Wars movies, you do, but I put it into my top four, I would say.
Did you like it more than Force Awakens?
I liked the tone of it more than Force Awakens because it was way darker and way less funny.
Yeah, and only had humor in moments to have relief, which there was a lot of robot humor Joe
Well, he was the comic relief, but but in the way that C3PO was used to be they they used him very well
so but but now if it was a Marvel movie that level of humor would have set you off no
I and you have a big allegiance to Star Wars in fact had a Marvel movie
Used humor in the same way. I would say that's how you use humor Marvel movies
by the way, movieweb .com today a movie site that I often check released some
information about the Dr. Strange Blu -ray and it said Thor's roommate to
return in Dr. Strange Blu -ray and it's a picture of Thor eating cereal high
fiving his nerdy this is that come on this is the problem with Marvel look I don't
know Thor's salary but he shouldn't have a roommate so I have a buddy who's Adam
Levine's roommate. It's like, no, Adam Levine has $20 million.
How does he roommate? Well, maybe just gets the long way. I guess so.
I thought this had just the right amount of humor to offset the fact that it was a very
dark film. There will be spoilers as we talk about this. They're unavoidable. I think anybody
less of this is probably seeing it. It's not like, you know, but I like Force Awakens better
because it was in the, it was in the traditional, you know, it's in the, it's in the big trilogy
can in or whatever. And so is this, but this was about different characters and what what have you.
Force Awakens, I mean the applause and the excitement just did not hold a candle to this.
Nobody applauded when the title card went up this time or Lucasfilm went up.
Nobody applauded when I saw this. You kind of strange because the Force Awakens people were going
fucking insane and all the prequels people were going insane. Well, I think that's what kind of
what I'm saying is like I think all of us have a potentially more special
place in our hearts for Forza Wiggins because it's our childhoods up on the
screen whereas this had some elements of that but it was truly just a much it was
almost like the best -case scenario if like Netflix made a Star Wars movie or like
a TV show or something. Yeah it felt to me pretty disconnected from Star Wars
aside from Darth Vader. Somebody asked online which we shouldn't check those
questions. We'll do them at the end. But, uh, you know, somebody asked if we felt that had the
right amount of Darth Vader. I thought Darth Vader was being used a little too sparingly until that
fucking awesome scene at the end where he comes blasting in. I was like, this is awesome.
So, but that for me, you have way more love for Star Wars than I do. I prefer even in Indiana Jones.
I prefer many things to Star Wars. But, uh, for me, this movie was pretty dull. And,
not that involving and I didn't give much of a shit about anybody in it until the last
45 minutes when I was like this is fucking awesome and it was it was an amazing ending
to the movie non -stop action as far as the other stuff I kind of didn't care.
It's a lot of there's a lot of build up through act x1 and 2 right there are a lot of I'd
say if you're a Star Wars fan there are a lot of Easter eggs in there and not even Easter
just nods to things that you would appreciate as a Star Wars fan. The most
important of which to me, and I, man, I did not see this coming from a fucking
mile away, I'd never would have guessed it in a million years. And when I saw
it, I mean, I lit up, I started giggling in the theater. But when they fly to this,
again, major spoilers, guys, when they fly to this lava planet, and I'm like, why
Why are they doing another lava planet?
That's like Mustafar in episode three.
And then you see a black castle and you realize, oh, it is Mustafar and fucking Darth Vader
has a castle on the planet where he was turned into Darth Vader, where he lost his limbs.
And then they go into the castle and it's like this fucking Sith temple and there's a
back to tank where he's just his torso all that remains of him is submerged in water
and then it gets pulled up and placed into the suit.
I was going out of my fucking mind with that.
I didn't see that coming from a while away.
So I love that. And then again, as you already mentioned in a friend of mine, Danielle texted
me today about this. That last scene because you get to the end of the movie and you're
like, this was a lot of fun. And this was very well done.
Everyone's dead. But where the hell is Darth? What the fuck?
You're not giving me any like Vader action because the scene with Vader
before that is is talk is talking and it's cool, but it's just talking.
And it's also no different than when he like choked somebody out back
in the. Yeah. But then the final Vader scene and the finale of the
movie is Vader not only taking out an army of fucking
in republic or rebellion soldiers
in like every forced way you can think of.
It's as he's entering the ship at the beginning
of Star Wars.
It's literally leading, yeah, I might not have caught that,
but yes, that makes sense to me.
It's budding right up against the beginning
of Star Wars, you're like,
this is what he does before he enters
the beginning of the first Star Wars movie.
Yeah, that's cool.
I'm a star, but that's cool.
Yeah, um, I love the I love the surprise of the CG
Grandmuff Tarkin and young Leia. I thought it looked impeccable. I've seen so much criticism of that
And I asked Heather who just watched all those movies a year ago, and she didn't even notice
I thought it looked amazing Carrie Fisher, you know, you could you could tell, but you know, it's it's whatever Carrie Fisher RIP, of course
And I read today that she had finished her work on
force awakens too. I don't know what to call that. Force awakens too. But
apparently she had a massive role in force awakens three. It was like
mostly about her. And now they've had to scrap that entire script. Yeah,
they're talking these might be rumors, but they said they might have to cut her
out of episode eight now, too, because it won't make any sense. Or so they're
setting up. Won't be able to be paid. I hope that's not the case. I'd like to see
one more princess layer run before before it's over but I also I love
Carrie if you if you can check out her writing you should do it I watch postcards
from the edge of the night she's a very she was a great lady wishful drinking
is yeah yeah I watch Larry yeah she's great it's hilarious well look I saw
the I saw Rogue One with Kurt Braun or our friend and comedian and when
and grandma of Tarkin showed up.
He turned to me and he goes, is that the same actor?
And I was like, no, that's some kind of magical rendition
of Peter Cushing who's been dead for at least 25 years.
Yeah, I've seen that done a couple of times.
I mean, the X -Men, when they digitally D age,
Patrick Stewart and them, I thought was done very well
and almost seamlessly.
I thought they did it well in Terminator Genesis.
They did it well in Terminator Genesis.
And they did it pretty well in sopranos,
Which was a crazy usage because I don't want to out. I'm gonna stop because that shows too good to ruin
Well, here's the thing
They didn't just de -age a man in this movie. They brought a man back from the dead. Yeah
And I guess I had an impersonator to the voice is that what that I guess so yeah, but I dude
They're they're really pulling out all the stops because I'm a fan of the TV show Star Wars Star Wars Rebels
Which is on Disney XD and you're a fan. I'm sure you watch it as well
And so this season they just teased that they're finally bringing old Obi -Wan into the mix and so in the mid -season trailer, they show old Obi -Wan and when he talks, I was like, that fucking sounds exactly like Alla Guinness.
Like I don't know how they're pulling this shit off at this point.
Yeah, I work on a few animated things and that there are just people who it's like who do you need and they can do it I worked
I was a page at S &L back in the day and Darryl Hammond they would bring him
10, well VHS tapes if I can age myself of
Of different people that he was gonna do in the show that we key some of them he hadn't heard of and he would go back
Wash the tape and come out and you could not tell the difference. It's amazing. Really it's a gift now
Now let's go to some of these comments about the film because I know he said, let's wait
till the end, but I feel like they might correspond to your criticism.
The movie was a bit slow at the beginning, which I don't disagree with.
I just think it was necessary, and I think it was the slow portions were more enjoyable
from hardcore star wars fans.
given wizard rights can check this person out at the wizard given was it the most was it me or is it one of the dulls blockbusters of all time couldn't care less about anyone. I don't agree with that.
A lot of people have said this criticism of like well you don't care about the characters because you can't remember their names or whatever.
So here's what I have to say to that I didn't care about the characters. I did care about the characters
I really liked and I can't remember their goddamn names either, but I liked all the characters
I thought they were really cool
I really I from the night of the HBO show about John Sotero's foot disease, which is a show I liked quite a bit
She and her so that's the main girl. I thought she was great and girls from theory of everything
Yeah, and he's the guy the main guy is the guy from the night of right?
Yeah, and I thought they were great, but people go I can't remember their names
It's like cuz their fucking names aren't their names aren't frank and Mary. They have these fucking goofy names
They're I can never remember anybody's names in movies and I call them all big eyes or whatever in my mind that helps me
Remember them, but
Yeah, I wasn't that involved with any of the characters either which is probably good because spoiler alert. They all die but
The last 45 minutes as just like an action show piece is pretty hard to fucking argue with
that was pretty awesome.
Yeah, I agree with that.
But for me, I would say it ranks above episode one, episode two, and nothing else.
I mean, I wouldn't put it above any other movies in the series.
I agree that I kind of...
I'm not sure if I like three more than...
I love episode three. I think it's awesome.
Yeah, it's great.
Slow Jen, potentially her biggest fan.
She writes...
Shit that I missed the window again.
Don't hate me, Joe, but I'm not a Star Wars person.
Our wedding is off.
Jen, it is.
What do you mean you're not a Star Wars? Who's talking about it? Who's not a Star Wars person?
But I'd love to take you on a polarizing Lala land. I like your take on the polarizing. We already did it
That's weird Joe hasn't watched it and I will die if I didn't get the bad Santa story. Yeah went Jen. We check got you on both of those
Brian Jepsen at BT Jepsen. Oh, by the way slow Jen at Roberta underscore glass
At BT Jepsen writes, I didn't emotionally connect with most of the new characters, didn't
care about Jin or Cassian, y 'all, question mark.
I like them both very much, I thought they were very cool characters, and I have a feeling
there's going to be a lot more Jin fiction coming out.
I'm sure they'll have books out about how she landed in the Imperial holding cell and all
that stuff.
I thought they were very, very, very cool.
here we go the at the Josh underscore at the underscore Josh underscore brown
rights how would you feel about Leia getting the darkened treatment in episode
nine I think that's what they should do not well they shouldn't do it if she's
the lead character and that's what I'm getting is that she's like the biggest part
of it and that's too much to be digitally doing especially for somebody who isn't
here anymore. It's kind of sick in a way to me. I, you know, I
wonder if they have to get the approval of Peter Cushing's
family for Rogue One or something because it's weird. But, you
know, if Harrison Ford died, they're not doing an Indiana Jones
movie. Well, with a digitally altered, I agree. I agree. I
agree. But I feel like let's say she is the, I don't, first of all,
I don't think she's going to be the lead of episode nine. I feel
like Luke Skywalker is going to be the lead of episode nine.
Yeah. Now what I read was just that she has a, she has a huge role in it.
Okay. So she has a huge role. Yeah. My guess is this couldn't you pull obviously they weren't
doing gigantic action sequences with Carrie Fisher. I would guess.
Probably. And if they were, they're probably using stunt people like they do with Harrison
Ford or, or, or, right. So what I'm saying is her park can still be instrumental. Can
you fill it out by having other people give exposition standards doing some
things and then having the CG. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. Or do
they start episode nine with she's dead now, you know, like that might be what
they have to do. It would just speaking of dead. Again, does the dog not look dead
to you? I think it's just resting. I'm seeing an eye twitch. It's fun. It's fun. Yeah,
he's awake. All right. Here's this comes from Dave Camoric. I don't know how to say that
at K -O -M -O -R -E -K, Camoric. Do you think it was not enough fader or just right? I thought it was
not enough until I saw the last sequence and then I thought it was just right. I agree. It was
almost like JAWS where you're like where's this fucking shark and then the shark delivery was real on point.
Justin Tyler at Dustin or Tyson excuse me at Dustin Tyson 1 2 3 writes can Rogue 1 be the name of your next hour special.
Absolutely not.
No.
How about Rogue farm?
Exclamation point.
How about Joe one.
That's terrible.
But yes.
I want to ask you Joe elephant in the room here.
Did you find Forrest Whitaker to be horrifically terrible in this as well as a rival?
Did you see a rival?
I didn't watch a rival yet because a rival to me wreaks of contact.
And we discussed that arrival.
A rival is pretty dull and I don't quite understand the love for it.
I thought it would be better as a twilight zone or a black mirror, a shorter movie.
But let me just be clear about something.
I don't give a rat's ass about a fascinating open -minded alien
Visitation now if they're not coming and killing us and it's blood not blood. I don't care
Well, I don't have close encounters and I remember kind of liking contact, but a rival left me real cold
The director I love and the director is doing the blade runner reboot the guy who did prisoners
Which you and I are gonna watch for this show this month. That's one of my favorite horror movies. Okay, we will watch prisoners
and we will watch the great Blade Runner sequel.
We'll go see it for sure.
And God damn it, I hate to admit it,
and we should talk about this.
I watched the trailer for Blade Runner 2015,
whatever the fuck it's called,
and it gave me chills.
I got excited because it looks iconic
and it's awesome when Harrison Ford comes out of the shadows
and goes, I used to do your job, I was good at it.
Like, I just got chills now, but God damn it,
I'm gonna hate the movie.
Yeah, the guy Denis Denis Villeneuve or whatever
Going off prisoners and to a lesser extent secario which I liked a lot
I think he's a really fucking great director and I'm excited to see the new Blade Runner
Even though I despise the other one as we discussed on this very show and I've discussed it disgusts me. Yeah, it's disgusting
but
force Whitaker and arrival is
He's doing an accent I can't understand and he's hamming it up so bad force Whitaker used to be a genius
Actor right like even go even like the shield the TV show he's so fucking great on the shield right and
Arrival was the first time I was like what am I looking at here?
He's doing a battlefield earth style performance right in this and Rogue one right Rogue one
I was like get this motherfucker off the screen and apparently he plays a bigger role in upcoming movies. I
No, no farce Whitaker does not play a bigger role enough. That's what I read. I don't know. He plays a bit
He plays a big role in the rebels TV show
Horse Whitaker is is it animated? Yes. Oh, he's voicing the character all right. That's what the upcoming movies he would be
He's like 70 in the goddamn. Yeah, I didn't get the character at all
And I wanted him off the screen see I know I you know
I'm glad you brought this up actually because I really like that character
And this is one of the things I really enjoyed about Rogue One and again this might be for hardcore Star Wars fans only
I don't know
But one of the elements I really, really loved about the film was that they got into the
sort of intricacies of the rebellion.
And I like the fact that there were different factions of the rebellion.
And Faris Whitaker was the part of the rebellion.
It was like the sub -subgroup of the rebellion that were almost functioning like terrorists,
that the regular rebellion was like, these fucking guys are out of control.
And like, they're almost our enemies.
I thought that that was really cool. I thought that that got into some of the
Some of the sort of socio -political
Perspectives that you would have with in a situation like that. I found that interesting come
The
No, you don't agree. No, I don't. I don't know what force workers been doing for the last year
I'm saying his character. It didn't do anything for me. Obviously. I didn't like his character
All right, well, folks, that's Rogue One.
I mean, overall, I give it a B plus.
Yeah, I would feel the same.
If without that last third, you're talking about a C plus,
but I think the last third is some great action movie shit.
The last third, I mean, it's the greatest space battle
I've ever seen in a Star Wars movie.
Yeah, it was awesome.
A phenomenal, oh, oh, and then I can't forget
to talk about this.
Again, just leapt out of my seat
When they're going into the big final space battle and it cuts to the X -wing cockpits and it's red leader, gold leader and it's fucking red leader and gold leader from the original movie and it was stock footage they found from the original movie and touched it up like god damn it. That was just so good. But now where was like porkins.
There's the most offensive name for a fat character in movie history.
There is an argument that porkins is in there somewhere.
I didn't see porkins.
I was only looking for pork.
But I believe porkins doesn't come into return to the Jedi.
Porkins is in Star Wars.
Guaranteed.
Okay.
Well, I don't know.
Look, they had, there's a big fact is the ship.
They had, they had stock footage of red leader and gold leader and they threw it in there
from the original movie and I thought that was fucking awesome.
Yeah.
All right.
Uh, uh, final segment of the show, Patty, before plugs, uh, rotten tomatoes review.
I always like doing this, you know, uh, and we already talked about nocturnal
our animals.
Uh, this review comes to us from Mara Rines Dean or Rinesdine, uh, from you, uh, from us
weekly.
Okay.
Somewhere in a forest, a maple tree wants all its sack back from nocturnal animals.
Yeah.
I think that's a very funny quote, but there's not one funny thing about or there's not one sappy thing. Oh no, I'm sorry
God damn it. Sorry. Sorry. Not nocturnal animals. I fuck I was on collateral beauty
Oh collateral beauty which I can't keep confusing with nocturnal animals. Yeah, yeah, yeah, but we weren't talking nocturnal animal
This is collateral beauty somewhere in a forest of maple tree when so it's sad that I am not seeing people shit on a movie
Like I've seen people really hate that club you and I can't wait to see the thing because it looks so terrible
I didn't get a goddamn screener for it. No, they knew they knew it wasn't in the running
I mean I started seeing the reviews come out when I started reading the reviews
I said let me go back and rewatch the trailers. I know I watched the trailer
I don't remember what it was and then I was like oh, it's this movie where Will Smith is in a diner and Helen Mirren shows up
And she's like I am hope yeah, it's a good emotion. Hope a grieving father
his daughter dies and he writes letters to death, love, and hope, and they respond. So Helen
Miran's like, somebody say you were looking for health. Well, she's death, right? She's
death, yeah. Kirin Knightley's love. Truly embarrassing. It's real. Truly embarrassing. Anything
to plug, Patty? No, no. I'm doing my thing. I'm doing my thing.
If you want to see me do my thing, check out my webcam.
The Patrick Walsh on Twitter and Instagram.
Oh yeah, at the Patrick Walsh Twitter Instagram, you know, that shit.
At Joe DeRosa Comedy on Twitter and Instagram, big comedy special.
That's the big plug right now.
You let me down February 3rd, Comedy Central, hour special.
I directed it and wrote it and I perform it, obviously.
and then it hits the streets sometime later that week for download and whatnot.
Thanks for listening everybody.
I just wanted to add thank you all so much for your feedback on the last four.
It was so much fun being on like Christmas break and every time I logged in the Twitter
seeing all these great comments and things that you're remembered from the episodes
we love reading all that shit.
Absolutely.
coming. Thank you. Keep the five star reviews coming. We really appreciate it. And we are looking into
getting sponsorship as always. Please reach out to us or we will reach out to you. And you might
not even know when that's coming. Be vigilant. Be ready. That's it. Thanks everybody. Happy new year.
You've been listening to Will see you in hell. A presentation of the Fangoria podcast network produced by
Thomas DeFeio, an executive produced by the great Ken Hanley of Fangoria Entertainment.
For press opportunities, advertising inquiries, and information about we'll see you in
hell.
Contact kenatfangoria .com.
You can also tweet me at the Patrick Walsh and Joe at Joderosa Comedy.
Thanks, everybody.
You