I'll see you in hell.
Welcome to We'll see you in hell.
Oh, you're supposed to do the intro now.
Go ahead Pat, take it.
Well, yeah, I mean, this is a whole new intro.
I'm realizing how incredibly dry my mouth is.
I'll probably step aside and grab a glass of water in a minute.
So please disregard hearing each crack of my lips against my teeth.
Right now I just woke up, never had less sleep before a podcast.
And I did last night.
I got home about 4 a .m. or recording at nine.
You got home at four.
Where were you doing?
Joe, I had a wild, wild week in a good way.
No, I reached out to Joe at one point.
I told him that my car had broken down on the desert.
And he gives me the thumbs up emoji back.
You know, probably while in hair and makeup for the taste buds podcast,
he leans over and pushes the thumbs up emoji on a text where I'm telling him I'm suffering
in the desert.
I misread that.
I thought you were saying, yeah, my new car, two years old broke down.
Lot of fun.
And I was like, yeah, fuck any of those.
That's cars for you.
I didn't realize you were like stranded in the desert.
I thought you were like just saying, you know, my car broke down and it sucks.
Right.
Well, we'll get to that.
But welcome folks.
We'll see you in hell today.
We are talking about the new release theatrical release because theaters are back, baby.
They're back.
Buddy in mind told me he made $800 and one day on AMC stock never bought a stock in his life.
So maybe that's a good that maybe it's too late.
I don't know.
But I am seeing movies are back, baby.
What I'm trying to say.
And we are going to do spiral colon saw or is it saw colon spiral?
It's your colon is a spiral.
Yeah.
There's a spiral to your colon.
And I saw your colon.
It's spiral from the book of saw.
Which is a terrible title.
I love that because there has never been a book of saw.
So what the hell are you talking about?
It's this like I've noticed these sort of low rent franchises.
I'm not, I mean, I'm not throwing shade.
Yeah.
You know, you're not going into a saw movie for like intellectual challenge, right?
You're just, you know, but they, these like the lower rent, the franchise, the higher.
They make the franchise sound.
So it's like, yeah, it's like spiral from the book of saw.
I saw the trailer for the new fast and furious.
Yeah.
And it's in the title because of it and it says, F nine, the fast saga.
You know, and then never like that.
You can do the Hobbit saga because just because it's been around for 150 years.
You can't do the fast saga.
Yeah.
And then like when, uh, when, remember, when the second hangover came out, uh,
who, who did that Todd Phillips?
Todd Phillips.
Yeah.
He goes, he goes, I called it the hangover part two because this felt more like a Godfather -esque sequel.
I mean, it's outrageous, outrageous.
Hangover two is, is so bad.
And I, I remember 10 years ago, how crazily transphobic this scene was where they got an actual trans actress,
which I guess is commendable, who turns around to reveal her penis and then men's scream, of course, for five minutes.
I remember that scene very well.
Um, yeah.
By the way, one of the biggest, uh, trans porn stars played that role.
Miss Jasmine Lee.
Okay.
Who, look, I've stumbled upon in my, in my quest around the internet.
Um, beautiful lady.
Uh, and then hangover three was actually significantly worse than two.
And I was like, oh, okay, they, they, they brought on John Goodman and, you know, they're, they're clearly classin' it up.
And this is gonna be a good end to the series.
No, it was terrible.
I thought one was passable.
I mean, I didn't think it was anything spectacular.
And, uh, and then two.
I was out onto the second.
It was like suddenly shot like a Rambo film.
Like, yeah, it was all like grainy and dark.
Everything had like those color filters over it.
I think he, he, it was his sort of audition for Joker down the line.
Like, you know, at some point I'm gonna want to do something serious.
So while they're giving me $100 million to make a three -dude comedy.
Maybe I'll, you know, shoot it and, uh,
and a morphic wide screen for some reason.
Yeah.
And also, too, it's like.
It kind of made sense in oceans 12 when like Soderbergh got a little grittier and grainyer with it.
Yeah.
Because it's still a heist movie.
Funny heist movie, but it's a heist movie.
The, uh, the hangover, too, is about a fucking hangover.
Yeah.
I've always thought outside of maybe a West Anderson where the style is a big part of it.
Uh, a very stylish comedy or a very well shot, well -produced, expensive comedy is not what I'm looking for.
Now, now you can be too shabby.
I'll point to maybe dirty work directed by Bob Sagan.
Now you, you can not even try.
And that's maybe not great, but like I don't like a polished big budget studio comedy.
By the way, dirty work now available in the Sagitt saga box set.
Yeah.
And, uh, it's, it's much like the Marvel has its expanded universe.
You can go into the full house universe.
So you can, you can rent Mary Kate, naturally, Olsen, go to the farm, starring Martin Moll.
Yeah.
You were in that Martin Moll.
Wait, wait, that's, that's not a real thing.
I know you think that you're, uh, Robert De Niro, but, but I know you were in Mary Kate and actually go to the fucking farm.
It's not called Mary Kate, go to the farm, right?
I think it's actually called, oh, like two grandmothers house we go.
Okay.
The cover is like Martin Moll wearing an old lady wig.
Something like, you know, but he's, he's great.
Um, so yeah, we're doing saw from the, the spiral saga.
And, um, I, here, here's briefly what happened is that I went out to the desert for a week to finish a script.
My lovely bride Heather came out for three of the days because it was her three year anniversary.
Doesn't seem like it, but it was.
The universe.
Thank you.
Um, so the Friday before she got out there, I took mushrooms.
And I was planning on just having this really great night.
And at the end of it, driving out to the Integatron and the desert and doing a sound bath.
Now this is an ex.
I mean, it's, it's the expression sound bath that that turns people off.
It's really just every part of that was so L .A.
It was like crazy.
Desert mushroom sound bath.
It wasn't L .A. The way I did it.
I assure you.
All right.
It was a lot of laughing, crying, shitting, drinking.
Right.
But, um, I drove out not even off road.
I have an Audi SUV because years ago, an old boss of mine floored it with somebody at Audi and I fell into getting really great deals on their cars.
And great.
I thought I'd stick with them forever.
I'm out there.
I'm driving back through the desert.
And the sound bath was, was beautiful, by the way.
You said, I'm sure it does more for you on mushrooms, but they just play really loud noises and you sit and relax for an hour and look at the sunset.
It's nice.
Mm hmm.
All right.
I'm coming home.
The cruise control stops working.
Then I realized the AC's blowing hot.
And I'm like, well, you're in the desert.
And I thought, well, a car should be able to withstand heat.
You know, that should be one of the tests they take before they leave the lot, but something's clearly up with the car.
Next morning, I get in.
I'm driving to get breakfast.
Seven notifications pop up.
This system is out.
This is out.
Your AC's out.
You need an oil change.
You need.
I've had this car a year and a half, mostly garage, because we're in a quarantine.
I mean, I call into Audi.
They say, yeah, we can't send a tow truck out to the desert, obviously.
Like, well, why?
It's, it's just outside of LA.
Now, closest to Audi dealerships an hour away, I would just drive it there.
Well, now when this call started, you told me I shouldn't drive it.
So you want me on the highway in it now?
No, well, I wasn't saying don't drive it.
I was just saying, keep the speeds low, keep it, you know, under like 40.
But I have to get on the highway to get to you.
You just stay on the slow lane, you know.
So Heather follows me on the way home on Tuesday.
Follows me to the exit.
I get off and make it there.
Guy looks under the hood.
Looking around for a while.
Then I get a call.
He goes.
I know we're supposed to have a loner for you to drive, but we don't have any loners on site.
This isn't like Beverly Hills.
We don't just have a bunch of loners sitting in the garage.
It's Palm Springs.
I wasn't in, you know, the actually in the desert.
It's Palm Springs at this point.
I just drove an hour to get to the mainland.
And I said, well, that's not acceptable.
I have to have a loner.
I'm sorry.
You can have someone drive it over from another lot.
Well, sir, that would take probably 45 minutes.
Okay.
I'm not doing anything.
He goes, talks to somebody in the back for a little while, comes out.
So we found a loner.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, you found one, even though I saw neither of you look for it.
So they set me up with the loner.
I drive off.
He calls and he goes, Mr. Walsh.
There's a real problem under the hood here.
All your wiring is just destroyed.
The wiring to the AC, the wiring to the engine.
I can't believe you even made it here.
Who told you to drive it from Joshua Tree to here?
An Audi guy.
A guy at Audi.
So he's like, yeah, what happened was rodents.
Eight all of the wiring under your car.
Which for some reason is just exposed to the elements.
So I go, oh, wait, so it wasn't like I was driving off road
and like a rock bounced up since I was in the desert
or something that you would, that would make sense.
No, there's teeth marks all over and they're shit
and rodents ate your wires.
Turns out it was like desert rats.
So I go, is that, is that normal?
After we, after we, you know, declared that it was not rats
in my garage, thankfully.
He goes, it's very normal.
He goes, our wiring is made of soy.
Which smells and tastes delicious to rats.
So I said, now let me stop you right there.
Why are you making your wires out of Swiss fucking cheese?
What are you talking about?
So he goes, we make them out of soy
because the environmentalists had a problem
with what we used to make the wires out of
and didn't have a problem for hundreds of years.
So now we make them out of edible soy.
I said, so this happens a lot.
Happens all the time.
Google it.
There's thousands and thousands of people for, for five years
complaining about this problem.
And I went to pick it up.
It was a very expensive repair folks, especially on a car
that I'm leasing.
Which should have no repair.
How convenient the problem that happens all the time
is because of something stupid they're doing.
And then it costs a lot of money to get it fixed.
How convenient.
I said, is this under warranty?
Since I have a three year warranty and it's a lease,
he laughs, well, no, I can't have a warranty against roads.
That's why they don't fix the wires and not make it soy
because they found a way to get a bunch of money out of the car
that has nothing to do with the warranty.
So it really sucked.
It's a bad situation.
I stayed in Palm Springs for two additional nights.
I was gambling, which explains why I got home at 4 a .m.
Just a disaster.
I was in the desert for ten full days.
Did you make some money gambling?
No.
Yeah, you just flop sweat.
Daddy needs new soy wires.
Come on.
Yeah, I was like, I'll just pay for the repairs here at the casino.
Now, the casinos have all, they're all trying to make the
$100 billion each one of them lost over the last year.
So they turned all the dials down to zero.
You just can't win anything.
But I didn't realize that until far too late into the gambling.
Did you manage to have any fun on this trip?
I did.
I had plenty of fun.
And between us folks, I've started a new, a new therapy
where I talk to a picture of myself as a child.
And if you can get past how incredibly dumb that is,
it's fixing my life.
So I look, I look at the trip as a positive on the whole,
because I had two of these sessions with this dude.
And it's, it's repairing my fragile state.
Who's administering this therapy?
A guy.
Just some guy.
I mean, a therapist.
He was strongly recommended by a friend who has similar issues.
We both have had, you know, we've been to five therapists each
and nothing ever really clicked.
And this guy's been great.
The only weird thing is he asked me to scan him photos of myself as a child.
And I said, no.
And I didn't go, I didn't push it into like, I think that's really weird
and uncomfortable.
I just said now.
And he was like, okay.
But there's nothing odd about that.
No.
He's just the therapy that he does.
What's odd about it?
It's not your, if it was your kids, then I'd be protective.
It's you as a kid who gives a shit.
Who cares what he's doing with it, by the way?
That would be sort of flattered if he was a little off to it.
But no, I don't think, I think if he's administering that specific therapy remotely,
then that makes sense to me.
I showed him the photos and with each one, he would sort of gasp.
He's very, you know, I was empathetic, whatever you want to call it.
But he was like, my, you look so sad even at age two.
In all of these pictures, you look so sad.
I'm like, yeah, yeah, baby.
Well, you're up against.
I'm sorry to hear that about the childhood thing.
I'm happy you're fixing it.
That's good.
Joe just sent me a thumbs up emoji when I told him about my unhappy childhood.
Look, it's brutal.
It's brutal.
You know, we're all, we got a lot of shit coming up right now.
Yeah.
No, I could look, if you, if you want to open your, your mind and heart to it,
I'll give you his contact because you can zoom with him and I, I've been blown away.
If you, five years ago, I wouldn't have been able to do it.
I would have been too like this fucking loser.
I got help.
I like my therapist.
She's great.
Good.
She's not listening.
Joe, you can be, you can be real.
No, she's really great.
She really is.
Okay.
She's, uh, she's exactly with like she talks to me exactly the way I want someone to talk to me.
She's very practical, very down to earth.
Uh, support of the ways, you know, that you need them to be.
You seem better than you were when I met you.
Uh, I am quite happy these days, living life way more on my own terms.
I'll tell you, cutting out the obligation of having to go on the road has been so life changing.
And it has allowed me to pursue things here that I never would have been able to pursue.
It's allowed me to live a more regular life in New York.
And quite frankly, it's allowed me more control over my schedule, where I do whatever the hell I want to do and I get my work done.
And that's it.
So it allows me to have a lot of fun.
And just kind of live a life that I, that I'm enjoying very much.
I love, I love New York and I'm very happy.
So it'll come smashing down in about an hour.
Yeah, what on air it will come smashing down.
Um, and also too, I think all of us are feeling pretty good with the, you know, with the world kind of coming back to some semblance of norm normality or normalcy, whatever the word is.
But, you know, that can't help a boost your spirits, you know, for sure, it's a good feeling.
What does suck is putting the mask back on after vaccinations.
It's like, it's like getting your brace.
When I got my braces off in eighth grade and I was all excited and they were like, now you wear this retainer 24 seven for two years, which I didn't do.
And now my teeth are fucked up.
Folks, where your retainers is the point of the story.
So do you ever look out the wind, the winder and think about the road while Metallic is cover of Bob Sieger's turn the page.
Plus I would do that on the road from the window of the red roof in.
Yeah.
Uh, spokesperson, Mr. Martin Mall.
Is that right?
Yeah, do you don't remember that?
I used to do the red roof in.
I don't.
He did a hotel.
I'm pretty sure it was red roof in.
He did it.
He was the spokesperson for a real.
Yeah, why am I throwing shade at the red roof in for not a high quality hotel chain?
Yeah, don't throw shade of the red roof in throw it at the man.
Throw it at the mall.
The mall.
I've never seen a guy have such a long career on almost absolutely nothing.
Absolutely right.
Like he's almost a household name.
Everybody kind of knows who he is.
He had a couple albums in the seventies.
That's my point exactly.
You find out he had some comedians that you've never heard of.
You find out he was on a show Fernwood tonight that you've never heard of.
Uh, the movies he's been in.
You've never really heard of the ones that you have heard of like clue.
He's not the lead.
Right.
You know, dozens of sitcoms where you know that that came and went supporting roles and things.
Like I don't even think he's been back on the Connor's reboot.
No, he hasn't.
Like, you know, like it's just odd.
It sure is Joey.
It sure is.
You know, the bit players.
There were other bit players in that same sense.
Like Fred Willard's a great example.
But Fred Willard was like in all the Christopher Guest movies.
So you were able to pinpoint like.
Right.
Oh, this guy said a long career and you might not be familiar with all of it,
but he's the guy that does this thing now.
And that's where you know from that solidified him in a lot of people's minds.
He got a late career resurgence.
Yeah.
Levy was like that, you know, you know, he's a sort of a guest star actor.
And he's never been more famous than he is at 75.
He's never looked better somehow, which is inferior.
I mean, his kids are fucking gorgeous.
Yeah.
Jesus Christ.
He really did it.
I mean, he's got like an olive skin.
You know, he's got that that can help.
Yes.
With aging.
His hair was always the weird thing.
Because when he had the real kinky pubro in like vacation.
When he's the used car, which was such a funny fucking scene.
Which has one of my favorite lines.
You think you hate it.
Now, where do you drive it?
But, um, yeah, he all like he used to be an agroner like splash.
Like he was hard to look at almost.
And now he's really a good looking man.
It's crazy.
One of the funniest things.
Jay Oakerson ever said to me.
Because it just painted the immediate picture, you know, exactly what he meant.
Yeah.
And I just laughed so hard.
He was like, Hey, man, we're going to this Italian restaurant on Sunday on Long Island.
Do you want to come with us?
And I go, is it any good?
And he goes, it's great.
Food's really good.
And there's always some guy in there playing piano that has Eugene Levy hair.
I was like, I completely get it.
Because he looks like the guy in Goodfellas.
That Peshie goes to some times.
Yeah.
No, not two times.
The other guy.
His whole family's rats.
Look at him.
You got to probably what I did.
Frankie.
He shoots.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Spider is his nephew.
Yeah, Peshie kills him.
But I got to know.
Nice fucking.
He looks like the guy who smooths his tie and goes, I'm going to get the papers.
You're, I promise you, you're just Chris Christ.
I make these two characters.
I am.
I'm thinking of the guy who comes in with his wife in the fur coat.
That's Eugene Levy.
I believe so.
Yeah.
And actually they, they used his likeness for one of the Simpson's mob guys.
And it looks like Eugene Levy.
He's the guy they find in the freezer truck.
That's correct.
I did briefly mix up two times two times.
Two times looks like the guy who finds the horse and his bed and the godfather.
Yeah.
Two times is in and out.
It's like.
He's almost got like a drag tripper vibe.
And you see him for two seconds and he's gone.
Do you say drag tripper?
Did you just come up with a new pitch where.
It's a clumsy Dracula who people think is gay.
And he has to act like he is up in Transylvania.
I mean, tell me that's not a costume.
You'd see it the worst Halloween party that hosted by a writer slash show runner in LA.
You know, were you supposed to be, oh, I'm drag tripper.
Oh, okay.
All right.
Hey, uh, where's the beer at?
If I'm going to make it through this party.
Yeah.
Do me a favor.
Thanks for the invite.
Now get the fuck out of my way and tell me where the beer is.
Uh, you mentioned Wes Anderson earlier.
I'm glad you did because I've been thinking about this a lot.
How long do you think it is before Wes Anderson's movies are boycotted for being the whitest things
that have ever existed?
He has through, I mean, like royal ten amounts, like a 50 person cast and then Danny Glover at the very edge of frame trying to peek into the movie poster.
Right.
Now he's, I mean, he'll sprinkle in people.
But he's really got up his game, you know, these, well, these casts have a hundred people.
So it looks bad when you have one black person.
I mean, these things give the Woody Allen catalog or run for their money in the white department.
Like Jesus Christ, the subject matter, the fonts, everything.
They feel, they definitely feel wider than Woody Allen movies.
But I don't know that I have ever seen a black person in a Woody Allen movie in any capacity.
He, he ever, there's a black actor.
It's the same guy that was in Red Belt, the David Mammoth movie.
He's been, he would tell Eddie a four.
Yeah, he's in, I think he's in Melinda and Melinda and you're right.
He was in that right after.
I mean, you want to talk transparency.
They were dinner for five.
Remember that show at John Favreau?
Loved it.
Yeah, I loved it too.
So he did an episode where he said, uh, Delroy Lindo was on and Delroy Lindo was, was, was his, what, what pose the question of like,
why do you think Woody Allen never hires black actors?
Yeah.
And then the next movie Woody Allen had come out with Melinda Melinda and it was starting a black actor for the first time.
I'm like, he clearly caught that episode.
But then that was kind of it.
I think.
But get me one of the British ones.
You know, they, they feel more white.
Yeah, it's, uh, it's interesting stuff.
Yeah, I just, uh, yeah, Pat, why don't you take us over?
Oh, oh, you know what, I got a new psycho, an interesting new psycho.
We got a lot we can split between the two, but what do you got by the time this comes out?
I think it's over.
It might not be the vinegar syndrome halfway to black Friday.
They still kicked off today.
Yes.
Uh, everything is basically half off.
If you're, I know this for a fact, if you live near the archive, which is their brick and mortar store in Connecticut or if you can get to it, the sale there on the archive stuff is going all week into the beginning of June.
I think up through Friday, June 4th or whatever.
Um, the vinegar syndrome website sale might end on Monday, the 31st of May.
If you're, if that's the case, it's already passed when you're hearing this.
But give it a check, sniff around, uh, great people doing great things selling great product.
Uh, and it's, and it's big news.
They have a special that I'm so tempted to do.
I've been looking at it. They go to obscure.
I mean, I haven't even heard of them. So it's hard to take a gamble on a buy.
They got a subscription box special.
Okay.
Horror and exploitation only.
There's two versions of it.
There's like a Supreme Collector one and then, and then the, the lower tier is horror and exploitation only.
Because some of the stuff they dabble in is like, you know, weird, like kind of half newty movies, you know, right, like whatever.
So, uh, yeah.
I mean, I, I, we practice what we preach, Joe and I do, but, uh, you got to support these places because I, I'd say we're one year away from Blu -ray is not being produced anymore.
Yeah.
I used to say five.
I think it's about one to two.
And why are brothers is done with, with it. They're one of the bigs.
Shout out to, uh,
Hold on. I got to remember how to spell this.
Also, if you're in the market for vinegar,
bonds has two bottles for $199.
You can get a, a rice or a red wine vinegar.
If you like that, new salads.
So, so, okay, so the, so vinegar syndrome real quick.
They have the subscription sale.
It's usually $1 ,100.
It's on sale for $460.
It's six months of DVD and Blu -ray boxes sent to your house.
They tell you everything that you're getting.
It's, I'd tell you it all up.
It's worth like $800 in some dollars easily.
And the product.
Like box sets and all this kind of shit.
And then also.
You get 50 % off coupons for all of their sister companies and them on top of all this.
It's an amazing value.
It's a little hard for me to justify spending $400 in some dollars right now and something like that.
But yeah, I'm extremely tempted and shots out,
I don't know.
A silo, a silo scope labs.
Here's another company you're going to want to support.
She dropped me an email.
They're located in Brooklyn.
Walsh.
It's that it was the dream email come through.
It's what I've been waiting for.
Joe, I myself have spoken with Michelle and got a lovely package from,
from a silo scope.
They do great movies and great releases of them.
That's good.
She's a fan of the show.
I knew she was reaching out to both of us.
She said, you're right near us.
In New York, you want to come raid the, the, the, the closet.
I was like, are you kidding me?
I was like, this is what I live for.
I've been waiting for this.
So, so this is another.
And I was not familiar with the company until she reached out.
I probably have come across some other stuff and didn't realize it.
But then I went on the website and looked.
They do so much cool shit, man.
They're doing blue rays, DVDs.
They're doing records.
They're doing books, posters, artwork.
Very, very cool stuff.
Another company you should support.
Pat is right.
These places.
This is it.
This is the saving.
Great.
These are the only people are going to be producing physical media anymore.
It's going to be all.
It's kind of like a me, but.
In a sense in L .A.
Where it's like the only place you can buy a physical record now is at.
That's some.
Rogue.
And I know me, but it's an institution at this point.
But at some rogue for all intents and purposes, independent record store.
You know, the Sam goodies, the mass producers, the, you know, the big chains.
They're, they're the ones that are going the way of the dodo.
So support these mom and pops, you know.
Yeah.
oscilloscope is awesome.
I really recommend.
They have one of my favorite documentaries of all time.
Although it's incredibly depressing.
It's called deer Zachary is a recommendation for.
Oh, that's them.
Okay.
Yeah.
But they have a lot of great movies.
Great company.
I wore a t -shirt that, that she sent me out to the post office once.
And this guy grabs my arm mid pandemic like a zombie movie.
I was like, yes.
He goes, where did you get that shirt?
And I said, oh, I said a friend of mine sent it to me.
Just to end the conversation.
And he's like, what friend?
I'm like, I'll see you later, man.
And I just kind of start walking off.
And he's like, well, I used to work there, but they fired me.
And I go, oh, this came from New York.
It's, and he goes, yeah, no, I was fired from the New York office.
I'm like, dude, Christ.
Like I didn't fire you.
Let me drop my mail off.
Jesus.
Yeah.
The.
But let's, let's cruise to the corner.
Let's cruise to the corner.
There's some big news psycho stories.
We'll do next episode.
We've been rambling here.
I'm, you know, you got one off at first.
Yeah, first up is always the catch up if I do.
I'm going to go hard trilogy here to stay in the theme of movie franchises.
I watched, I got, I think I mentioned this on the last episode.
I bought the Warlock trilogy box set from restaurant video.
Okay.
It was $10 for the Blue rays loaded with special features, beautiful transfers.
best on video another great company to support. So I watched let's start with
Warlock 1. Man would have fun awesome late 80s early 90s horror movie that I saw
the box for a million times at the video store. Never rented it for whatever reason
just never rented it never stumbled on to it on cable never found an
on streaming over all these years took a chance and I'm so happy I did it is just an
awesome fun wild 80s horror flick a bit of an adventure there's a little bit of
fantasy elements in it Julian Sands is excellent plays a Warlock that gets
time transferred from the dark ages into modern times and is trying to collect
three parts of the devil's Bible that will bring the un creation it's called the
end of times and a warrior played by I'm blanking on the guy's name who is
Barney wasn't already not a warrior excuse me. Warlock a
magistrate type you know a witch hunter type gets sent also gets sent forward into
modern times to track down this guy and stop him they don't do a lot of dumb I
was worth my biggest worry that it was going to be bugged now with dumb comedy of
like what is this talking box you know like when they see a television right they
don't really do any of that there's one or two very brief moments yeah they play
it pretty straight for the most part it also stars the woman who was the lead
girl in footloose and if her bills no no that's flash oh yeah Lori singer yes
she's in it she's great there's a cool plot line with Lori singer in it where
she gets cursed and she's gonna age 20 years every night so she's got to find
the warlock now too she doesn't want to do it but she has to or she'll die in
four days basically it's just a fun movie man like it's just a really fun
movie some some really really cool practical effects highly recommend never seen it
I used to see all these Julian Sands movies at the video store what there's the
warlocks of course there was boxing Helena which David Lynch's daughter did
where he kept a he cut a woman's arms and legs off and kept her in a box and then
she liked by the end loves him for it yeah yeah but the only thing I've ever
actually seen him in is like Iraq nephobia and I think he was in oceans 13 but all
those all those ladies 13 believes so yeah who's he play I just looked and he's
listed so he must have had a little part he's a great actor very like Shakespearean
type you know yeah good for Julian Sands I saw folks I bet I was excited to
get back into the theaters you know so I'm going to I'm not going to see
everything like I used to because there's so much like true shit out right now but
I have been taking some chances and I took a chance on here today starring Billy
Crystal and Tiffany had a Jesus Christ this thing looks like directed by
crystal written by crystal and another 80 year old white man which I'm only
saying because they're writing all the dialogue for Tiffany Haddish it's it's an
experience you know it's it's way too long it's two hours but it's Billy
Crystal slowly going through Alzheimer's he he's a veteran comedy writer so
there's long scenes of him he works on an SNL type show much like with date
night the Mindy Kaling movie they both have worked in writer's rooms their
entire life and they both put up movies about the writer's room experience that
that look nothing at all like it I don't know how they did it I don't know how
they fucked it up so bad because they know how these shows work but both of
those movies get almost every detail completely wrong here today he works at
SNL and basically everyone is making dick jokes and Billy's always like can't
we do is that the laugh we want so you'd hate him anyway he's the planted as the
hero of it but you're like fuck you Billy Crystal every joke every line
somebody pitches they cut to him like wincing and then when he leaves after
shooting on everybody's pitches the showrunners like look he's a legend we
can't throw a legend that you know like everybody talks about how great he is
this would never happen in modern television it doesn't matter how
they're having a role in writing fucking serious sees are they're not yeah it's
not happening yeah he's like the only reason the shows on the air is because of
him so shut your mouth and you just know that it's Billy Crystal going well nobody
respects me anymore so I'm gonna remind them that they should and make a movie
about it so that's one half of it the other half is him befriending a talented
to the young New York street singer played by Tiffany Hattish.
They formed, Joe, would you believe it was an unlikely yet hilarious friendship, where
I'm going to dare to say they learn a few things about themselves, they do.
It all builds to a scene where at a wedding, Tiffany Hattish sings, Janice Joplin's piece
of my heart with the band and which every little kid at the wedding knows every word to because
they all love the music of Janice Joplin.
These old guys, man, I'm not saying don't let them make movies, but when they're trying
to like keep up with the times, it is rough.
And at the end of this thing, when Billy Crystal is like, I don't know my name anymore.
It's tough him like fake crying, but there's no tears in his eyes because the facelift won't
allow it, you know, and he's like, I don't remember where my keys are.
It's bad.
I'm glad you brought this movie up because I looked it up on Rotten Tomatoes earlier this
week and found two reviews that made me laugh so hard because of how opposite they are and
they're back to back in the top of the section.
The negative one is first, but I'm going to read you the positive one first, meaning in order
on the thing, the negative one comes first, but I'm going to read them out of order, but
they are back to back.
Tim Cogshell of Film Weekly, NPR Los Angeles, KPCC says it can be saccharine, syrupy and silly,
but I got to tell you, I just didn't care.
I love Billy Crystal and Tiffany Haddish and when they mix it up, man, they really mix it
up.
I'm going to say you this last night, I didn't know if it would make sense.
This guy said this between playing riffs on his trumpet, then the editor cut the word
daddy out of the review, you can't call the reader daddy, yeah, yeah, they cut Jack, Jack,
but brother, when these two sizzle, don't get hit by the sparks, Christy Lamire, also a film
week, KPCC and PR Los Angeles, deep bench over the same place, her review is, we need two reviews.
Her review is, this is maybe one of the worst movies I've ever seen, it's just terrible
awkward stiff and never funny.
The two people at the same place, they just couldn't have more opposite polarizing takes.
Yeah, man, it made me laugh really hard.
The truth is actually somewhere between the two, I mean, it's not the worst movie I ever
made it, but it is just kind of schmaltzy and dumb, but it's like, Chris doesn't even know,
he's too lazy to even shoot comedy bits correctly, you know, they do the thing where she orders
shrimp at a diner and she takes one bite of the shrimp, they cut the crystal when they
cut back, she's wearing a giant fake foam face because she's allergic to shellfish.
It's like Billy, you got to have one since this bit's been done a billion times, you could
have watched any other bit where they do it pure luck with Martin Short has a great beast
thing one, but it's like you have a lip pop out first, you know, you don't just cut back
to a face that there's no comedic build to that, it's the only time you could do that
is the three stages.
It's literally got to be that, where, and then you have to do the, whoa, reaction, like that's
the only time that gag could work.
Yeah.
All right.
I watched Warlock 2, Joe, do you feel you can talk about Warlock 2 for one minute as I run
to the bathroom or do you want to pause it?
No, go ahead.
I'm in an emergency.
Go pay.
I watched Warlock 2, another, another very fun, very enjoyable at this point early 90s
horror fantasy film.
Interesting and curious, it's sort of not connected to the first one even though Julian
Sans plays the Warlock again.
And this one has an even cooler beginning than the original movie where they say that
every 1000 years, Satan has an opportunity to bring his child, the antichrist to earth
in order to once again destroy earth.
The problem is is the antichrist needs to assemble these five cosmic stones in order to do it.
But once he's born, if he assembles these stones, he can do it, but he has to do it in a
certain amount of time.
And there are, I guess they're called druids, I think, that are sort of, it's passed down
generation to generation.
They're the gatekeepers.
They're the ones that are there to stop it.
And they keep possession of the stones and by doing that, they're able to prevent the birth
of the devil's son.
Anyway, it opens in some weird, again, you know, sort of dark ages setting and you're witnessing
this ritual happen and you think that all of the weird ominous men surrounding this woman
writhing and pain who's about to give birth are evil and then you realize they're not
evil, they're actually the ones that are stopping the birth of saints, baby.
And they successfully do so, cut to a thousand years later, we're in, by the way, I'm just,
I'm just saying the dark ages, I don't even know if that's the accurate timeline, whatever,
but you get with my point, it's like willow times, whatever willow times is dark ages, right?
I think anyway, cut to modern time, it's a thousand years of past, the devil now has his
chance again to rebirth his offspring.
This time he succeeds and lo and behold, it's Julian Sands now, the Antichrist, which I
believe is a step up from Warlock.
He's gotten a promotion.
They never discussed the events of the first film, the ending of the first film leads you
to believe that they have destroyed this guy for good.
So him coming back in this one, it seems they just created a new storyline for him to come
back.
I was fine with it.
Again, fun movie, not as good as the first one, but some of the gore and practical facts really
make up for that.
And there's just some fun to be had with this one.
If I was going to give the first movie, let's say a B plus, I'd give this one, maybe a C plus,
B minus, somewhere in there, a C plus, which, you know, that's plenty watchable of film
to me.
All right, so far you're two for two in the Warlocks, two for two, babe, okay, we have three
coming up.
Third one will be my last movie today, all right.
Folks, at the theater, I also saw the theme of today's movie corners.
Theaters are back.
Top Gun.
For some reason, Top Gun was playing the atrophy.
I know Top Gun 2 comes out maybe this year.
I think I saw the trailer for it five years ago, but it looked awesome.
I saw the trailer and I'm acts and I thought it looked great.
It's Miles Teller, who's, you know, as far as those young actors go, one of my favorites.
Top Gun, even when I was a kid.
It never, it never reached classic status for me.
I was never that impressed by planes flying around.
A lot of my friends loved it.
Seeing it on the big screen with the Dolby surround sound and everything was pretty sweet.
The movie is fun, you know, Kelly McGillis to me is one of the least charismatic of the eighties
actors.
I don't know how she became so famous.
She does nothing for me.
Did she know?
I mean, I feel like it was Top Gun.
That was it.
What else was she in?
She was in the accused and she was good.
Yes, she had a career.
I don't know.
I just, there, it's a, as Tarantino has often said, he's in that movie sleep with me talking
about it at length.
It's a very homoerotic movie.
There were definitely some people in the audience who I think were there to enjoy it in that
way and sort of a camp way.
But, you know, that, that beach volleyball scene with just, I've never seen it, I've never seen
the movie.
Never seen Top Gun.
No, I never saw it as a kid.
I never had interest in fighter jet movies.
They just never, and then I never saw it, and then I was like, what am I going to watch
it now?
I don't give a shit.
Yeah.
Um, there's a, there's a shirtless oiled up beach volleyball scene that just goes on for
five minutes.
The song in the background is playing with the boys.
And they put these guys in towels coming out of saunas with the bulge hanging and they, and
every scene, everyone is sweating and oiled up and it's very 80s and, and kind of funny
in that way.
Kilmer's a great villain in it.
It's fun.
You know, it's got like Tom scared.
It's got the, the bald guy who played the principal and back the future, you know, and
all these guys that you'll remember, Anthony Edwards, of course, Goose, his girlfriend,
a very minor role as Meg Ryan.
It's a very stacked cast and that's fun to see all these people like essentially as babies.
And then to see Tom Cruise, who of course had been in big movies, but Top Gun was his first
like, hey, this is going to be the number one movie star for like a while, and you totally
get why he does this monologue about how his mom used to listen to sitting on the dock
of the bay.
And he is like, I got so sick of it, I'd have to play it for over and over, but like, now
I'd give anything to hear that song or something like that.
The kind of bullshit they write into these action movies to give their lead, some soul or whatever.
But man, when he does it, you, you're like, I get why this guy became the biggest movie
star.
He, he sells even the dumbest shit, he's just one of those actors who you buy what he's selling,
you know, and it's cool to watch him kind of come and do his own.
The action is cool, but I agree with Joe, I'm not a big, a big plane movie guy.
It's a, it's a fun movie, and I think we're definitely worth going to the theater for it, he never saw it.
Yeah, my friends, my friends late father and well wrote it.
Oh, yeah, just got a, I think he was just awarded a credit on the sequel as well,
because he had written the sequel in like 1989.
That was this huge hit and they were like, we need to seek a weird joke because it came out in 86.
So was there time traveling?
No, no, no, he wrote the sequel in 1989, I'm saying, okay.
So my point is, is this thing was a, I got you, this thing was a huge success and they went to
and they're like, right, a sequel, we're going to make a sequel and you wrote it,
then they never made it.
And it's completely different than what they made, right?
I assume I bet you it's not that different.
Different could it be, you know, I guess they all come back to the flat academy and fly again.
Yeah, the, the, the, the, the unroly student now has to be the teacher.
Yeah, sure, sure.
All right, my last film today is Warlock 3.
I'll keep it brief.
What a startling piece of shit this movie is.
Uh, uh, like reeks of direct to DVD.
All of the quality is gone.
All of the budget is gone.
It bummed me out because Bruce Payne now takes over the role as the Warlock.
He is great in the role, but it is just an awful boring direct to DVD late 90s early.
Oh, it's, you know what I'm talking about.
Ashley Lauren stars in it, who I love and I'm a fan of and I'm always rooting for.
But poor Ashley is always thrown into these terrible fucking movies, man.
Like can somebody let her be in something good?
She was in Hellraiser 1 and 2 and then that was it.
She hadn't been in a good thing since.
She was in that terrible creep show episode this season.
She was in the worst Hellraiser sequel after two.
Uh, she was in this.
I mean, let this lady do something, please.
Um, anyway, I met her once.
She was lovely. She seems very happy.
So maybe, you know, whatever.
But I would not let Warlock 3, the end of Innocence, what an awful title.
I used Don Henley's end of Innocence in the end of the film.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
They, uh,
I almost was just going to say something.
It was going to spoil something we're going to do in the future.
So that's, that's right pause.
Um, anyway, don't let part three stop you from catching in on parts 1 and 2.
And look, you might enjoy part 3 just for Bruce Payne's performance alone.
But 1 and 2 are well worth the money for this Vestron Collection on Amazon.
I suggest you grab it.
We'll do never seen any of them.
Don Henley's the end of the Innocence is hit an album about him bitching about his divorce,
where he was surely at fault. He's a notorious asshole.
My dad used to listen to the end of the Innocence.
All every car ride.
I know every song backwards and forwards of Don Henley's solo album.
I wish I could strip it from my brain and then put in some good memories that I've lost.
I, uh, I've never, uh, I've, I've, I've heard the one song.
Is, is boys a summer on that album?
No, boys a summer's not.
And then, uh, oh, she wants to do his dance, dance, dance.
That's not on that album.
Don Henley sucks dick.
He's so bad.
He sucks.
He had, look, I worked for years at Blockbuster Video.
Shout out to Mike Curry, a hellian back home in St. Louis.
I mean, we used to have these trailer tapes 90 minutes long.
And you just have to restart them when they were over.
They had trailers.
Of course, they had ads for popcorn and shit.
And then they had music videos.
And each month when we put in the new tape,
we'd be like, let one of these songs not make me want to chop my cock off.
And we almost never got it.
And one of the worst that I ever had on that tape was Don Henley's late, late solo hit,
taking you home, which was the, I think it's the laziest song I ever written.
The verse doesn't even really count as having a melody.
And then the chorus is done, Henley going, I'm taking you home.
Also, not a melody.
Like, that's not even a song.
And I remember it to this day, every word also had creeds.
What if from the scream three soundtrack?
This is blockbuster.
Yeah, blockbuster.
I mean, fuck blockbuster enough with this nostalgia that it was a great place at one.
It was never great.
Fuck off.
We put in another video.
You're like, I work at a video store.
I don't want to watch this tape for another eight hour shift.
So you'd put in like the goonies or something.
Something, something G or PG.
We once had our store manager parked across the street when he was not working
and came in and reported someone for watching a movie while on the clock.
Imagine jackering dumb.
You're a 35 year old manager at blockbuster video.
You're off work and you're spending it parked in the pure one imports across the way
to make sure your employees are following orders.
Yeah, I don't have a third movie that I saw at the theater.
So I'm going to go with Italian American,
which I had never seen.
And it is on a fantastic new criterion called Scorsese shorts.
And it is five short films by Martin Scorsese.
And I haven't seen any of them.
The first and not the first, but sort of the best known and most beloved of them
is Italian American.
And it's just for a little less than an hour.
Martin Scorsese interviewing his mom and dad.
You know his mom, whether you know it or not.
She's in good fellows playing Joe Pes.
She's mom.
She's hilarious.
She's also in a lot of his movies.
And his dad, I had not really seen,
but he's a very, very sweet charming old guy who's like a slower older Scorsese.
And it really comes through how much Scorsese loves his parents.
It's fun to see him like, you know, a year before taxi driver,
just kind of hanging out.
He's not the manic, chatty Scorsese.
We all know.
He just turns the camera on and knows he's got gold with his parents.
So he let some talk.
And, you know, there's no like, you know,
it's not going to really compare to the documentaries of today
where there's twists and cliffhangers and everything.
It's just watching an old Italian couple,
you know, talk about the immigrant experience,
talk about how New York is changing,
talk about their lives, talk about how they met,
give each other shit, you know, as old couples do.
I really recommend it.
It was, it was funny.
It was sweet.
And it's a good way to kind of learn
about the backstory of, you know,
everybody's favorite director or one of them.
All right.
There's your movie corner.
That's how you do a movie corner.
And I wanted today's feature spiral from the book of saw
starring Chris Rock, EP by Chris Rock,
co -written, I believe, by Chris Rock.
Didn't get the credit, but apparently at a wedding,
he said, Hey, I got an idea for a new song movie
and that's how this all started.
Wow.
That's pretty cool.
Initial thoughts, well, initial synopsis,
it is a sequel.
People seem to be that haven't seen it or a little confused
as was I, is this a sequel?
Is it a remake?
Is it a reimagining?
No, it's a sequel.
It's, it takes place in the saw universe
and it's about a jigsaw copycat killer.
And that's, you know, so the events of all the
saw films are real in this world
and they're familiar with them.
There will be spoilers.
Saw spiral
is releasing two Amazon and all these places to buy for 20 bucks
on June 1st, I think,
which is like two days from now.
So you'll be able to buy it.
If you're still not comfortable going out to theaters
and as always, if you wait a month,
it'll be on one of the streamers anyway.
Right.
So
it's, it's, it's interesting.
And I believe all the saw movies did this.
It takes place and it's, wait a minute.
Is it an unnamed city or is it Los Angeles?
I think it's an unnamed city because they,
it is an unnamed city because they just keep saying
Metro police.
Yeah.
Right.
It was definitely shot in LA, but I,
right.
Maybe they didn't say, um,
but I think that that's a pretty cool.
I like when movies and TV shows do, do that.
I think that that's cool.
Uh, seven is one of the, the, the, the,
the all -timers.
I still don't really know where seven was shot.
I've been watching Hill Street Blues.
Hill Street Blues.
They never named the city.
Okay.
Pretty cool.
Great show.
I was excited for a movie corner, but I don't have to.
Probably the only city in America that has a Hill Street.
I got to take it off my list now.
Anyway, Chris Rock plays a jaded but very committed and good cop,
who gets entangled in an investigation
for this copycat killer of Jigsaw who was targeting
only police officers and seemingly right off the bat,
only police officers that have done corrupt things.
Uh, he lives in the shadow of his father
who was the most decorated police chief that the unit
or precinct rather ever had or the city ever had.
Um, yeah, but they are strange.
By Sam Jackson.
Yeah, play by Sam Jackson.
They are estranged, um, but he goes to his father for help
because he is very perplexed by this case.
He is working and things unfold from there.
As they do in all saw movies where person after person
gets ensnared in some horrifying dilemma,
trap thing where you're sitting there wondering what you would do.
Yeah, in the situation with both options being awful.
And it unfolds from there.
Do you start to learn what the corruption at the department is?
Why this killer is going after certain cops?
What these cops did, uh, you know, eventually you learn of a
controversy that his father actually helped cover up.
And, uh, you know, it's your typical saw movie.
Lots of misdirections, lots of twists and turns
until you finally get to the end and realize who the actual
man behind the madness is.
Yeah, and it's, uh, it's a very satisfying twist
when it comes the, the theme of it really, you know, it is sort of a,
a saw movie for our times.
It's about corruption on the police force, you know, and I found it,
it threaded that needle really well while being about something,
but not being so preachy that it overtook the horror.
Yeah, you know, it's, uh, yeah, horror movies are always tackle themes,
but, uh, are they do the best ones tackle big themes?
But, you know, it's, it's always nice when they kind of don't jam it
down your throat as this one could have done.
It's Darren Lynn Ballesman who did the original saw, which, you know,
I think most people still consider the best.
I've seen maybe less than half the franchise to be honest with you.
I, I found the traps to be too much for me,
but I've also become a lot more, uh, jaded.
When I rewatched Hellraiser 2, I went, I got through that scene that I had to shut it off with
no problem. So now I just have no, no bottom for what I'll watch.
But, um, yeah, I had to review Saw Five or something and I saw Five.
I saw it at the Magic Johnson Theatre in L .A., which had 10 reserved parking spaces for cops.
And it was just the most fun place to see a movie, just the, the routiest crowds.
And I used to go there for horror and comedy films.
But, uh, that was fun.
The crowd experience may be held, but some, some of these traps were just like,
God, damn, and, and this one was no different, you know, they were,
they, they did a really good job.
I thought about not being
disgusting for disgusting sake, but finding traps that really made you just
uncomfortable. Yeah.
Just feel like, God, damn, that would be miserable.
And this far and the franchise to keep coming up with those is pretty great.
Yeah, I cringed at every trap.
And usually that stuff doesn't get to me.
This one made me cringe.
Every trap, I was like, Jesus Christ.
There's bottles on a conveyor belt near the end.
There's these bottles that keep hitting this, uh, like fan or something, industrial fans.
There's a guy who's like tied up in the hanging position on a stool.
And every time the bottles get released,
then it, they get shattered in the fan.
And then it shoots all the glass bottle fragments into his body.
So like you watched hundreds of little pieces of glass just like,
nail them and it looks so good and real, you know, like the traps really, really work
and are effective. Yeah.
A ton of tongue stuff.
Yeah, the first trap is a guy's got to either rip his own tongue out for lying on the courtroom
stand. Yeah.
Again, and getting people in prison because he lied or getting hit by a subway car.
Those are his two choices.
The one guy's got to rip his own fingers off or he gets electrocuted
in a pool of whatever, uh, they're rough stuff.
It's rough stuff.
Now why the, like when, so he was clearly ripping his fingers off,
he did, that guy just didn't do it at a time.
And you don't know if that's enough.
I mean, can you imagine where you, you do both?
Well, that's, that's what most of them were.
Most of them were, you know, the trap, yeah.
Which is how saw kind of roles.
Like by the time you do the awful thing, you're dead.
Anyway, um, surprisingly, and you know that I'm often a critic of this, uh,
but this movie did it right, surprisingly funny.
And not funny in a gaggy way, not funny because they were going for jokes and punchlines.
Funny because they had well -written characters that were funny.
Like Chris Rock, that scene where he's walking through the subway with his new partner,
and he's just talking about like, your marriage is fucked.
It's never going to last.
Like, yeah, women don't stay married to cops because you're too good at being a cop.
Like, it's like, that monologue was so funny.
And so real is he rewrote a little bit of the dialogue,
especially early on in the movie.
He did one of the jokes on stage.
I saw him in New York and he did one of the jokes from that monologue on.
It's the Pilates.
Yeah, yeah.
Three months to realize Pilates wasn't real, you know, whatever.
But he, uh, he's just, he was really good in this.
When I first heard Chris Rock was starring in a salary make, I rolled my eyes.
I've never been a big fan.
I'm a big fan of Chris as a comic.
I've never been a big fan of him as an actor.
And I thought, this is the last guy I'm going to buy,
playing like a gritty cop on on the hunt.
And I thought he pulled it off in this.
I thought he was great.
And, uh, and I thought allowing him to be basically a darker version of himself
was really what made it work, you know, like letting him be funny.
And Chris Rock, like, was great.
I agree.
I thought monologue was funny at the beginning, you know,
for us gone monologue was great.
That almost, when that, that's almost the first thing you hear in the movie.
And I was like, is this going to be Chris Rock doing stand up?
And then traps, because I guess I'm fine with that.
But what a weird concept, you know, but, uh, him talking about Forrest Gump was great.
You know, like, uh, Jenny didn't want Forrest until she got eight.
Now, now she's ready to hang out with old Forrest.
Yeah, it was, it was funny.
But it felt like things cops would say while trying to relieve tension.
You know, he's not like riffing on jigsaw.
Jigsaw is not in it, but his presence is felt.
There's a, there's a pig mask wearing, uh, killer in this one.
The, and they're very disturbing like a sexual voice that it does.
Yeah.
I want to play a game.
Like it's such a war.
It felt almost like the, uh, that bird lady and kids in the hall kind of voice.
Yeah, yeah, it's a weird voice.
And San Jackson, by the way, coming in with his, uh,
like Jackie Brown style San Jackson.
Like he's doing like swagger.
Like he must be out of fucking mind.
San Jackson, you know, like, it's, it's the exact same Jackson you love.
I bet they shot him out in one week.
I mean, he's very, he's not in it much, but he's, as always, leaves a,
leaves a good impression.
I'm surprised he's never played Chris Rock's father before.
They, they have a great chemistry together.
But I agree with you.
I mean, we're, um, we're talking about Chris Rock for something I'm working on.
And my initial instinct was I just watched the Fargo season or half of it.
And I was like, man, I didn't buy him in that at all.
I got to be honest with you.
And I think it was because he was playing a guy in like the 50s, you know,
it's like he, he has to play a modern man, I think.
Right.
And there's just, he's not the most versatile actor,
but this was a great part for him.
And I think the reason he works as a grizzled cop is he finally is looking
a little older.
He looked 15 for his entire life, you know, right.
Now that he's got some gray in his hair and, and, and he's lived a little bit, you know,
I bought him completely.
I thought he was excellent in it.
And, um, you know, for me out of the sauce I've seen,
I, I'd put it at like number two, but I, I'd have to watch the other ones again.
And I don't know if I had, did you get hours in me?
We don't have to give it away, but did you guess who the killer was?
Because I was, I fell for, I was wrong who I thought it was.
Let's put it that way.
Uh, I thought it was going to be Sam.
I did too.
And they were making it, it was such a blatant misdirection that I was like, I guess
that they're just saying, fuck it.
It's going to be Sam Jackson.
And I was like, man, they're making this real obvious.
But I guess that's what they're doing on purpose for some reason.
And then it's not Sam.
That's all I say.
But, uh, no, it really worked for me.
I mean, it's, it's very well constructed.
It's a, it's a well -written movie.
And I think, you know, definitely when I was getting into the Saw Five region,
it was just kind of like people walk like literally the one I last saw was them like
walking through a haunted house where they encountered each trap.
And I was like, all right, you know, they didn't even really bother with a plot.
This one is very intricately plotted.
And for the most part, it works.
It combines the, uh, cop corruption movie with the gross out horror movie.
And surprisingly, it, it's a good mix.
It felt like a dirty Harry plot, to be honest.
It really did.
That's, that's exactly right.
It felt like a later dirty Harry, for sure.
All eight movies in the Saw Collection on Blu -ray are available now.
On Amazon for 15 bucks, you can get all eight DVDs for 10.
I did a little research.
It seems like the Blu -ray's aren't really a big stretch from the DVDs.
I'm going to cop all eight for 10.
And then I'll buy Spiral eventually when it comes out.
But anyway, hogs are up.
It sounds like for Spiral.
A real nice, refreshing hog up for Spiral.
You know, theatrical horror.
I, we're about to head into a good run, you know,
with Quiet Place and the New Conjuring and some big movies coming out.
But this is the first theatrical horror movie in a while that came out.
And I thought it really popped.
It was a good movie.
I check it out.
I agree.
We'll be back in the next episode with our review of Wrath of Man,
another theatrical only release.
Jotaro's a comedy on Instagram and Twitter.
Taste Bud's pod available on YouTube, audio wherever you get it.
And that's it for me.
The Patrick Walsh, Twitter and Instagram.
Uh, that is it for me as well, folks.
We'll be back Jason Stathman, Guy Ritchie, Jason Statham
in Guy Ritchie's Wrath of Man.
We'll see you next time.
We'll see you in hell.