I'll see you in hell.
And when the sound of your screams becomes a thing of my dreams, you know I'll say.
You know I will.
I'll see you in hell.
Folks, welcome back to We'll See You In Hell.
Today's picture.
Ghostbusters, Frozen Empire.
The best titled ghost.
Strikes back.
Yeah, that's the best titled Ghostbusters that's ever been.
I would say.
What's the competition? Two?
An afterlife?
Okay, alright.
I muted myself by accident. Yeah, two and afterlife would be its comp.
Yeah, we'll get there. We'll talk Frozen Empire.
But what's new with you, Joe?
Pat, I'm starving right now.
I don't have any food in the house. I got to order some food.
The problem is I don't want to show up while we're recording because the thing's going to go off.
It's going to be a disturbance.
But then if I wait till we're done recording, I got to wait another damn hour to get the food.
I don't know what to do here. I'm at a loss.
What are you thinking about? What are you going to get?
I would like to get some kind of turkey sandwich thing.
But I'm also just like, eh, maybe I will just get some shawarma or something.
A little, you know, vegetable. I don't fucking know. I don't know.
Yeah.
One of those things I'm going to get.
Okay. Kind of healthy.
I like the idea of a turkey sandwich.
I feel bad about the bread, but I don't know if I need to feel bad about the bread.
You mean because of the carb content? You work at a sandwich shop.
I know. I try not to eat a lot of, you know.
You're just going to do like a handful of salami?
Yeah. I walk into the kitchen. I reach right into the salami, take a handful.
Wrap it in lettuce?
I eat sandwiches. I just, you know, you can't eat them every day.
And I ate pizza last night, which, you know, now I feel like I shouldn't eat a sandwich today.
Yeah. I do the carb thing so rarely, you know, especially something like pizza or like that or whatever.
It doesn't. It's like when you, when you take it out of your diet for a while,
you realize how it's just not great for you when you bring it back because you're so lethargic, you know?
Yeah.
Like, you know, if you're eating pizza, you know, every third night or something like you do when you're a kid, you don't notice it.
But man, like if I have a couple of slices of pizza now as an adult, it's like heartburn, sleeping bad.
I feel like, you know, as Jim Gaffigan used to say, I feel like I rubbed it all over my face.
My face feels like greasy and puffy. I don't like it.
Well, that's new. I saw Jim Gaffigan last night. What do you think of that?
Yeah. As a friend or in a comedy setting?
Yeah. I went to Todd Barry's birthday party last night.
Todd Barry. It's very funny.
And I saw Todd Barry, obviously. I also saw Jim Gaffigan. I talked to Jim for a while and I spent quite some time.
You're going to like this with a Mr. Dave Foley.
Oh, wow. That's exciting. I just rewatched The Wrong Guy the other day.
I told you like a year or two ago, he followed me back on Instagram and I was like, wow, that's cool.
I wonder if he knows my comedy or something. And when I saw him last night and I said, hey, Dave, he was like, hey, man.
And like it was like a genuine like, yeah, hey, how you doing? Like, I know who you are.
And we talked for a while. We talked for quite some time about AI.
Okay. Where was he? Was he doing standup?
He's at the party.
Oh, party. Okay. Missed that.
Yeah.
No, I love Dave Foley. When he followed me back on Twitter, I was on cloud nine.
And then when I followed him on Instagram and he did not, I was sad because I let things like that affect my mood, which is sick.
I didn't want to bring it up today. I was afraid to bring you down.
And well, no, I'd rather a follow on Twitter. I don't post on Instagram, but still I know I'm not a non -Twitter.
All right. Well, yeah.
I'd rather him like me for my mind than my face. You know what I mean?
I hear you. I, uh, but it was a fun party. There was a lot of friends there.
Uh, I mean, these, I, um, the, the guys I've mentioned, I'm friendly with.
Uh, I don't know if Todd's Todd's a guy where I don't know if I said, you're my friend.
If he would say, yeah. Or if he'd be like, nah, man.
No, I don't really like that.
Or if, yeah. Or if I'd said, you're, we're not really friends. We're just acquaintances.
He'd be like, what the fuck, man? It's a hard guy to read. I'm going to go say we're friends.
I got the invite to his birthday. I'm going to say we're friends. Um, it was a fun time, man.
Had some drinks, uh, blah, blah, blah. You know, not, not really any real story to tell,
but it was fun talking to Dave Foley, uh, a lot about AI.
I got to tell him about when I went to see the kids in the hall and when I was young and I met them after
and I was all excited and all that stuff, you know, it was, it was nice. It was very cool.
It was very cool. But anyway, at this party, Todd ordered about 20 pizzas and everybody ate one of them.
I was like, dude, what are you doing with all this pizza, man?
He's like, I think I ordered too much. I was like, yeah, this is crazy.
So, uh, yeah, that's tough. Anyway, it is. I've never ate dinner.
And then I ate a couple of slices of that and then I felt bad. And here we are, Pat.
I'm trying to figure out what the hell to eat today. God damn it. Um, well, I don't care really.
I cared if you just had a quick answer, but I didn't expect all this. Uh, I apologize.
I know it's not what anybody wanted.
Uh, look, I'm going to actually, we got a lot. I, so I did, I, we talked about some trailers, Joe.
Yes, there's, uh, let's start with Beetlejuice Beetlejuice.
I'm not going to say it a third time. I don't need him here distracting me all day.
I have work to do after we record, but as Joe pointed out, it starts as you, as you might guess,
with a slowed down orchestral cover of day.
Oh, now I will say this, that slowed down haunting version of day.
Oh, does play right before the opening credits start in the original Beetlejuice.
I know this cause I've seen that movie a hundred times.
So they actually kind of did it before the trend, but still you don't need to put it in the trailer.
The trailer, uh, they're at a funeral.
You see Ryder O 'Hara, you know, I, from what I have heard, Jeffrey Jones picture is in it,
but they killed him off and did not bring him back, which I understand.
Why, why do you, why, why did they, why did they kill him off?
And I'm sure Burton would have been like, I don't care. Let's bring him.
I, you know, the fact that they even used the photo means Burton still likes the guy.
Burton had him in sleepy hollow after the shit was going down.
And he was also in Deadwood after the movie.
Yeah.
Deadwood.
Well, see he wasn't, Jones wasn't like Pee -wee Herman.
And I wish that he was.
He wasn't like Paul Rubens where he had this giant collection of kitsch and erotica and nude pictures
and stuff from like the forties, fifties, sixties, seventies, eighties.
And because he got caught at the porno theater, then everybody assumed he was doing fucked up stuff with kids.
And because he was a kid entertainer, he wasn't, he was never accused of that even.
But even my mom and like, you know, I've had exes and stuff.
I'm like, you want to watch Pee -wee's big adventure?
The one with the pervert who like fucked kids.
It's like, no, he didn't do that.
Jeffrey Jones, on the other hand, while I don't know if he's fucked kids,
he was taking naked pictures of a kid in his neighborhood and paying him off.
It is more egregious.
Yeah.
But he tried out for cool kids.
He still auditions.
I mean, that was only five years ago.
He came in and auditioned for cool kids.
I bet he was great.
He was a great actor.
He really was.
Even in like Amadeus, where you're like, how could that guy fit into that world?
He's perfect.
He's just great.
Such a great pompous asshole.
And, you know, Dean Rooney is one of the great characters.
Yeah.
I remember there was a dice.
One of the great comedy villains for sure.
There was a dice clay joke when Pee -wee got in trouble where he's like,
he's like, everybody's mad at Pee -wee because he got caught jerking off.
I didn't even fucking like him until I knew he jerked off.
It's kind of fun.
Anyway, the Beetlejuice trailer, it's a teaser.
It doesn't really show you anything.
The reason I am excited and Joe and I get into this all the time,
usually with Stephen King about how he raves about whatever and he's just,
oh yeah, it's great.
I saw it.
It's amazing.
You know, people lie and they have reason to lie.
Giant financial reason to lie.
But I tend to believe Michael Keaton when he says he wouldn't do it unless they
used practical effects and puppets and he was not going to do any green screen
acting because he hates it.
And he got everybody to agree.
And Tim Burton said, this has reignited my love of filmmaking.
And Keaton saw a cut and said, it's fucking awesome.
And he couldn't believe how great it was and blah, blah, blah.
I'm, I'm choosing to just believe that and hope for the best.
And I can't wait to see it.
The trailer didn't tell me enough good or bad to, to affect my opinion.
Well, I, I agree.
I like how candid Keaton has been throughout the whole process.
I like that he publicly said when Tim came to me and said, I,
I'm going to do this thing where there's going to be a different,
like a newer Beetlejuice backstory.
We're going to revise the characters backstory and he's going to have a wife
and whenever Michael Keaton said his reaction was, yeah, good luck with that.
That's not going to work.
Like people aren't going to cry.
And then he was like, and then I saw what he did and it was great and whatever.
So look, Keaton's excitement about it is exciting.
Okay.
But, but I have more to say about Beetlejuice, but much like today's movie,
Bill Murray, also a guy that doesn't bullshit and there's a lot of quality stuff
that often says, you know, these Ghostbusters scripts,
they were just finally the right scripts and, you know, and whatever.
And I did like Afterlife and we'll get into today's movie.
But my point is, is I've been, I've had a,
I've had a guy I respect and who doesn't pull any punches before,
tell me something was great.
And then you're like, okay.
So you can tell by watching this new one that it's,
that Murray did not think that this was an exceptional script that he had to do.
He's talked glowingly, glowingly about it in interviews.
But anyway, the, but the, with the Beetlejuice thing, you know,
one thing really pissed me off and, you know,
I'm friends with the guys over 800 pound gorilla,
but they post that the trailer has been released, right?
Yeah.
And they, on Instagram, it's like, you know,
because their whole feed is like entertainment news.
And they fucking write in the screenshot, the juice is loose.
Beetlejuice to trailer finally dry.
And then the big line when Keaton comes out of the model at the end of the trailer is he goes,
the juice is loose,
which would have been a really fun line to hear for the first time in the fucking trailer.
I've been waiting five years to see.
And these guys fucking, everybody just fucking pukes everything out.
Now, nothing is sacred.
Everything is fucking riddled with spoilers, right?
It really pisses me off, man.
Anyway, I hear you.
I hear you.
The trailer was reading some article about how when,
how when actors get cast now in these big tent poles,
like the kids who's playing the new Superman,
that they immediately get them into like beach shots with big dicks.
Like they're like, no one knows who you are.
No one knows who you are.
So we're going to get you like in a, in a, in a little pair of swim trunks.
We're going to stuff it.
We'll get you on a beach with some girl and that'll get people talking and it works.
You see it happen all the time.
They're like, like wondering who the new Spider -Man will be.
Check out him playing at the beach in Rio with it keeps happening.
And you're like, what's going on?
This industry plant stuff.
It sounds so ridiculous and I never would have bought it before,
but lately I'm buying it.
I'm buying.
I'm not buying cat Williams.
I think Kevin Hart is very talented,
but there are people in this business where I'm like, what's happening here?
Nobody wants you to be in five movies a year.
Nobody likes you like this.
Nothing is real.
It is all bought and sold.
Your vote doesn't count.
Hollywood is fake.
Everything is evil.
Nothing will change.
It's all fucking owned by corporations.
It is horrible.
It's all hard.
I have, you know, people have told me for the last 20 years of my life that I've
got an apathetic nihilistic view.
And funny how I'm seeing a lot of those people now walking around saying
everything's terrible.
Huh?
Yeah, no shit.
Yeah.
So, you know, sorry.
I didn't need Trump getting elected to fucking realize that fucking nitwits.
Anyway, the sorry, I'm getting angry.
Listen, here's the point.
The Beetlejuice 2 trailer.
I needed to pick me up.
Yeah.
Because I'd watched something very depressing before this and I needed to
pick me up and I saw the Beetlejuice 2 trailer and dropped.
I was so excited.
It does bother me that there's just nothing fun about the trailer whatsoever.
Like I enjoyed seeing what's her face from Wednesday?
O 'Hara Ryder.
Oh, Jenna Wartega.
Like I liked when you saw Jenna Wartega.
Unquestionably perfect casting.
But I liked seeing her go up when she's back in the house and watching her go
up the stairwell.
And I was like, oh, wow, they're like really going back to it.
And then they show the model.
And then I got excited.
I'm like, oh, man, I fucking bet Alec Baldwin and Gina Davis pop up in this
somewhere, or at least Gina Davis does.
Oh, that'd be great.
Is Baldwin out completely?
He's out.
Well, and then they had Justin Theroux at the funeral too.
He's funny, but I don't know if Justin Theroux was playing Winona Ryder's
husband or the new trophy husband of O 'Hara.
It's funnier if it's O 'Hara's new younger husband, but I don't know.
I would be willing to bet it's Ryder because what's it called?
They said, Tim Burton said that a big part of this movie is the coming face to
face with aging and the fact that Winona Ryder's character is dealing with the
fact that she was once the young, cool kid who knew everything, and now she's
there's a reckoning that comes along when you get older.
So I'm guessing it's going to be Ryder's husband.
They're going to have a strained relationship.
Her father dying is going to add further strain and then somehow also bring them
together ultimately to fight Beetlejuice.
Her daughter and her are going to be at odds.
She's not going to she's still going to be she's going to be for Christ sakes.
What's the word?
A strange she's going to be like a strange from her mother and this event of
the dad dying and the dad being because in the movie she does love her dad like
he is the good guy and you know she resents Catherine O 'Hara.
So I think like his death is going to be the catalyst that that forces this
strange and very strange family to band together because the daughter is going
to get potentially sucked into the allure of Beetlejuice as Winona Ryder almost
was.
Right.
And then they're going to make even creepier now that the age difference has
gotten so drastic.
But yeah probably I don't think in a sexual way I just mean like in a way of
like I want to go to the other side and like be a part of your ghost.
But I also am willing to bet 1000 percent that they are going to make Beetlejuice
an antihero now.
Like there will be no he saves the day at the end of the first movie but then
they still fuck him over because he's because he's still trying to marry Winona
Ryder and it's wrong.
Yeah.
Which by the way she's in high school in that movie too.
But no I know.
Yeah.
But so so but but he you know he was 35.
He wasn't 55.
It's not not not not not not any better but some somewhat 55 70 70.
Yeah.
So I think I'm going to I'm going to say just this and I'm going to say I'm
going to say nothing more.
And I asked this for you once in a while to just close your eyes and keep me in
your thoughts.
But Michael Keaton is reading a script of mine this weekend.
OK.
I'm not not I'm not going to say anything negative.
I'm not going to say.
Oh Joe I'm not.
I know you have nothing negative to say about Keaton.
I have nothing to say about him either.
I just love him and I hope he likes my script.
That's I love him too and I hope he likes your script.
Beetlejuice the original which I watched so it's one of the best looking 4Ks
there is.
Neons look incredible in 4K for whatever reason.
I don't have that.
The structure of the movie Beetlejuice is so fucking weird.
It follows no structure books.
No way anyone would ever tell you to write a screenplay.
It gets by on a very thin premise you know like it's a ghost that need to scare
people out of their house.
But my concern is you could do that kind of thing in the 80s when everybody's on
blow and it's like oh Keaton and this new director is funny.
Yeah well go shoot it have some fun.
Now I fear that the Beetlejuice lore they'll try to pack so much on to the lore and
the history that we're going to wind up with some two and a half hour multi sub
plot exhaust version of Beetlejuice where you know it's them you know fighting
in other worlds the sandworm world and all that stuff.
I don't know.
I don't know but I don't feel good about it.
He said so a couple things Keaton has said repeatedly in interviews.
You're going to be surprised at how much heart this has.
That's making me a little nervous.
I have a couple other.
Beetlejuice has no heart.
Yeah.
I have a couple other predictions.
I have a couple other predict.
That's fine.
I'm OK with that.
I have a couple of predictions though.
I think that again they won't just to drive my point.
He will.
Beetlejuice will be redeemed in some way in the end of this movie.
He's not going to remain.
He's going to be very much a hero or an antihero.
I also think that Burn Gorman who you see front and center at the funeral is going to
be the new who was the heavyset guy?
What was that character in the first one who's like her art?
Otho.
Are you doing this?
I feel like he's going to be the new like Otho guy because he always plays a sort of
odd you know ambiguous sort of whatever and the fact that he's right there with them at
the funeral I'm like I bet that's her new Otho.
Willem Dafoe plays a character named Wolf Jackson which I'm all ears.
Yeah I'm into that.
I'm into that.
So what was the other trailer Joe that we talked about?
Oh Christ.
Oh thank you for remembering this.
The Crow starring Bill Skarsgard.
Jesus Christ.
Did you watch it?
I saw it.
I mean look I'm not a Crow obsessive.
It didn't like wound me but yeah I get why people are upset about it.
What is happening in the after he's supposedly dead you see him applying the Crow makeup.
I'm like guys he doesn't have to put the makeup on.
It's what you look like when you come back as the Crow or whatever the hell it is.
You know I'm like what are they doing here?
What is this?
That trailer looks nuts.
If you have not seen it folks.
It opens with Bill Skarsgard with face tattoos and he's a musician and you're like well this is a bad start already.
Didn't we learn from the Jared Leto tragedy do not face tattoo somebody.
By the way I thought it was weird you say a musician but I thought it was a really bad choice to have him do song parodies like Weird Al.
I just you know it's a big swing for such a dark character.
And that's the arc of this movie is the death of the girlfriend is very hard for this zany man to come to terms with.
It's it looks fucking you know what I don't even know if he is a musician.
He's like an ex con or something.
It just looks it looks like they dipped him in hot oil and then ran him through a hot topic.
So it all stick to his body and then said we're going to do the Crow except it's not going to look anything like the Crow.
And we're going to really show Bill Skarsgard's face in this and you're like OK I guess so.
By the way all right is anybody less intimidating than Bill Skarsgard.
There's nothing.
Well now he was it wasn't he.
He was it but he was in tons of makeup and stuff.
I'm saying Bill Skarsgard normal walking down the street like who is this guy.
He needs a sandwich.
Get him out of my way.
He's a blade of grass.
You know I watched Jenny Slate's new standup special which I enjoyed.
But she talks in it about how she was offered the not offered but asked to audition for the role of Pennywise and it.
What.
And it leads to like five minutes of her standup where she talked about she fired her entire team and she was so offended by it and blah blah blah.
And I was kind of like look if I'm an actor and they're like hey do you want to audition for this really cool part they are asking about you.
It could lead to something very lucrative.
I didn't know why she was so upset about it.
They weren't telling her she looks like an ugly clown.
Bill Skarsgard isn't ugly.
No.
Well was she offended because she was like I don't understand it's a man character that you're asking.
She was saying I felt like my reps didn't get me or what I do at all.
And I was kind of like well if my reps didn't show me something I would be pissed.
It's happened before where I find out somebody offered me something they didn't tell me about it.
I hate that.
Yeah I don't know.
I don't know why I was standing up for her agents but I was bothered by it.
I don't think it's a reason to fire.
You're like well they're there.
Now if they're pushing you and you're saying it's not for me that's a different story.
But your agent is supposed to bring you money opportunities.
That would be a giant money opportunity.
Yeah I agree.
What's new with you Pat?
I talked all about my birthday star fuckfest event.
Yeah I haven't had any of those unfortunately.
I'm doing a bunch of things at the moment.
I'm sober.
I'm celibate.
I'm not dating.
I deleted the apps.
And it's all been very good for me.
I'm out.
I'm getting sunshine in the morning.
I'm exercising.
I'm keeping on my shit.
I got a cat which you know at first I got this cat.
Kyle Kanane who you know and his girlfriend Rachel Olson who was a longtime friend of mine.
Were raising this cat and they put a picture of it up and I was like can I take it?
They were just like fostering it.
And they said it's the snuggliest cat.
You're going to love it.
Because when I was going around all these places and it's a little sad going in there.
But they were like what kind of cat do you want?
And I was like I just want a cat that loves me.
That just hugs me and looks in my eyes and pets my face.
I've been saying that to people.
It's tragic.
And then the person at the place immediately went you've quit drinking haven't you?
Yeah that and then the other place they looked at each other and they were like he's going to fuck this cat.
He's definitely going to fuck this cat.
But no.
I was going into these places and feeling judged by like how much I was.
I had to be like look I just want a sweet little cuddly bubbly little bubby chubby.
But Rachel and Kyle were like no this cat's awesome.
And it is.
Although at first they told me about how loving it was.
And this cat was not cool with me at all.
It was like hiding under the bed for long periods of time.
They get overwhelmed.
You're supposed to start them off in a small room.
And gradually open up their world.
And I kind of did that.
But then I just wanted to be close to it.
So I kind of stopped.
And it got a little scared at first.
It was biting me a little bit.
Not breaking the skin but biting me when I would pet it.
And then just a few nights ago you know I'm sitting watching a movie and it like it hops up onto the couch.
And just started headbutting me.
That's its big move is it climbs up on your chest and almost onto your face and headbutts you.
Like please give me love.
It rubs its face against you.
It's just it's crazy.
It it changes your mood.
I mean I hate that I was without a pet for so long.
It's like it's a built in mood improver.
I love petting cats.
I love the purring.
I'd probably love a dog too.
I just don't want all the responsibility.
Yeah I'd like to have a pet of some kind.
But I just travel I move around so damn much.
It's very hard.
Cat would be ideal though.
You leave a cat home for like a week like a feeder and stuff and right.
Yeah.
I think you leave a cat for a week.
They're totally fine.
They do.
They they're they're much like being married though.
They're like kind of ignore you for a couple of days.
They're standoffish and then you got to kind of warm back up to them.
They don't love it but they are totally cool on their own.
What stopped me with the cat was I don't want my furniture all clawed up.
And people are like you're it's going to happen like there's no way around it.
And I was like well I don't want that to happen.
This is my second cat.
This cat is both brand new and traumatized because it had been in like five houses in the past month.
And it has not clawed a single thing doesn't even.
And if I want to cut its nails it won't allow it just yet.
I have to kind of like wear it down some.
But it's not bad.
You put out a scratching post next to the next to the couch and they scratch that.
They get it.
All right.
Well maybe there's still hope.
I never had an issue.
Over at Rachel and Kyle's you know they're putting towels on the on the couches at first because then they just scratch the towel.
There's ways around it.
Now yeah see I don't want to do that.
I've seen cat owners do that where they drape their furniture with things.
I'm like this looks it looks gross to me.
Well you just do that at first.
You know hopefully not doing that for the rest of your life like an old woman.
Now I've seen your scratching post.
Do all cat owners dip their balls over it the way you do.
That's something that I enjoy.
And the great thing about a cat is you get the experience of having your balls scratched but it doesn't draw blood.
It doesn't penetrate the stroke.
Cats know to kind of pull back.
All right.
I'm sorry.
Did I go a little too far with your bit Joe.
No I thought I was going to.
I would have went the opposite.
I like it because it draws blood.
Oh OK.
I would have went the other way.
You like a bleeding balls.
Yeah.
Let's get over to that corner.
Look I'm just going to kick things off with friend of the pod friend of us Mr.
David Krumholz.
He and I had a magical dinner the other night.
We had so much fun.
Super deep conversations.
David is now sober so that kind of led to a lot of discussions about that topic in particular.
But the dude's great.
He's on fire right now and he was in a he's in LA shooting an Indy.
I went and saw his previous Indy called lousy Carter which comes out on Friday.
Very excited to see.
And yeah I believe it'll be one of those you can download for like four ninety nine or whatever on Amazon day and date kind of movies.
It's not a big movie by any means.
But I saw it at video it's which that's where you saw the Scoville special right Joseph video it's video it's yeah the one on the corner out in Eagle Rock.
Yes.
Yeah it's great.
It was a nice little play around.
It was around for a long time back in the day and then it closed down and then they just recently reopened it.
But it's a revival house.
They show old movies all day and then they have a video store there one of the only remaining video stores.
OK.
But it was great.
It was the evening was fun.
The movie is not perfect.
And you know but the movie is basically David Krumholz is a miserable guy.
He is a teacher at college.
He had some success in animation 15 years ago but it never went anywhere.
He's a sad sack loser.
He finds out he's got limited time to live.
So he decides he's going to fuck one of his students because why not and go out happy getting laid.
The premise of the movie basically.
OK.
So the old you've got two weeks to live premise you know we've seen a lot of that throughout the last hundred years of cinema.
But and they don't do much with it to be honest but that's not really what the movie is about.
The movie is just very much a character study about people you don't generally see on screen.
David is actively trying to fuck a 19 year old in this movie and you don't care because he's so good and so lovable.
Women in the audience didn't care.
It's like illegal about fucking a 19 year old.
No there's not.
Yeah.
Let's stop with it.
It's creepy.
You know not you.
Just in general.
Enough of this.
Look I'm just telling you what the world is.
Yeah well the world needs to fucking chill.
People get upset about like a 36 and a 50 age gap.
It's like if she's 36 she's she's probably fine.
You know who's upset about it.
People that can't get laid.
That's who's upset about it.
Anyway sorry.
I'm sorry.
Go ahead.
No you're totally right.
But you know I hear people all the time say things like like if they don't want us to fuck 19 year olds then make the age 21 or whatever.
And it's always shocking.
But then you're kind of like like no that creepy guy has a point.
Like he's allowed to do it.
Then what are we doing here.
And this is.
I say this.
I say this honestly.
I'm someone that wouldn't do it.
I don't have an interest in it.
Same.
Oh same.
Yes.
Anyway go ahead.
Anyway.
So he's also having an affair with his wife with his best friend's wife in it right.
Isn't that in the trailer.
Correct.
So Krumholtz's best friend is played by Martin Starr from Freaks and Geeks and they're really good friends in real life.
His wife is sleeping with David.
David's ex is played by Olivia Thirlby who's an actress I liked a long time and everybody in it is good.
Krumholtz's therapist is played by Steven Root who's doing like a thick Austrian accent.
Right.
So you know it's it's an odd picture.
It's got a tone all its own but and don't expect perfection by the way.
It's it's a bit of a mess but Krumholtz is so fucking good and they did a Q &A after with the entire cast.
And it's just like anytime anybody had the microphone in their hand they talked about how fucking great David Krumholtz is.
So it was a nice night for him.
He really does an amazing job.
He's in every scene of the movie.
And yeah if you're a fan check her out.
It's a it's an interesting little movie.
And then also in the Q &A David talked about how much him and the director didn't get along.
And he talked about it at length and it was deeply uncomfortable.
And that's the beauty of Krumholtz.
He's got a little of that performance art in him.
Like he spent so much time talking about how much he hated this guy and how much they yelled at each other and on stage.
He'll do that.
Yeah.
Everybody's looking uncomfortable.
It was wild but yeah.
I'm a big fan of this Jocelyn de Boer who plays Starz.
She's she's I asked I asked David and she's married.
But yeah but but she's she did Greener Grass which was an awesome movie.
But she's she's really great.
Anyway I'm excited to see it.
I left David a message the other day telling him that it has the trailer has all the feeling of those late 90s in truly indie movies that were being made.
And it feels like one of those you know the last time we saw one of those.
Well we've seen one or two in recent.
I thought I thought American fiction felt like that.
Certainly Napoleon Dynamite was one of that style of movie or whatever.
You know so I'm excited for it.
That was my very heartfelt message from that time Joe.
Well Napoleon Dynamite's like 2006 or something.
Yeah maybe five I was in New York.
Yeah.
So little bit but close enough that it wasn't you know that movie with Owen Wilson were paint or whatever where he played like the Bob Ross guy that felt like one of those movies.
Anyway sure David invited me to a Q &A screening this Saturday but I don't think I'm going to be in New York.
So I don't think I can go but I would have liked to.
Anyway I'm excited to see that my movie corner today will be all nostalgia or things from my childhood starting with since I've said so much negative today about things and always about things.
Kevin Smith my hats off to you at Masters of the Universe Revolution dropped.
It is the follow up season to Masters of the Universe Revelation which was the Masters of the Universe reboot sequel series that Kevin Smith got a shitload of backlash for because he basically undid everything that the original series set up.
He was a non He -Man focused show that there was a lot of controversy around it when he said everybody keeps thinking it's not going to be He -Man focused.
It is he's front and center and then they kill He -Man and it's Tila focused and it was a lot.
There was a lot going on with that.
But aside from who it was focused on or whatever it just was not a good show.
When Revolution was announced I was weary weary weary weary weary about whether I even wanted to see it or cared.
And by God he got things back on track.
Tila is still front and center but you know who else is He -Man on the He -Man show.
They're both awesome characters in it.
It is it feels like He -Man.
It's great.
You luck man.
If you don't you don't like He -Man I'm not going to convince you here.
I don't have anything.
But if you do like He -Man I'd say it's worth a watch.
I don't think you need to have even seen the first series.
This kind of gets you in at a point where you're if you if you know the original TV show from when you were a kid you know enough about the characters that you could just watch this.
Stephen Root also in this playing cringer slash battle cat Mark Hamill.
What's interesting is that I don't have any recollection of liking He -Man.
I don't think I ever saw Master of the Universe the movie or the cartoon.
And yet there are photos of me as Orko on Halloween.
So I must have.
Well maybe it's time you get back into it.
It really shows you about my self -esteem.
Even as a kid I thought I had to be Orko the faceless dwarf and not He -Man himself.
I enjoyed this show very very much.
And I I recommended highly to anybody that was ever a fan of the the old folks over at the Masters of the Universe.
I really liked it.
What is it Netflix?
Yeah and this I don't think there's a coincidence here.
Kevin Smith announced about a year ago that he was done smoking weed and he was like I don't I want to be clear.
This is how I want to live now.
I had no offense to any weed people but I had a good time and I and it's like well what a shock.
The first thing you do after you are not in a fucking weed haze is back to you being good at this like you you were good at this.
You wrote fucking Daredevil.
You know this.
You know how to write this kind of shit.
So like you know it was it was it was cool to see.
So I hope he keeps on track man.
I really do.
Great.
Great to hear.
I I want to shout out as we talked about Terry Gilliam on the Poor Things episode that I watched the brand new Criterion 4K of Orson Welles The Trial which is a movie that I had never seen before.
And God it was awesome.
It is so fucking good.
And the fact that Terry Gilliam and Martin Scorsese maybe they did in interviews at the time were not giving massive credit to the trial is insane.
Brazil in particular steals whole scenes shots feel you know like there's all these it's Anthony Perkins.
There's all these scenes of him walking like through a room with like a thousand desks in it and a thousand losers doing their work.
And that's Brazil man.
There are so many scenes that are just verbatim.
You could hold up the shots next to each other and there is no world in which Terry Gilliam didn't show them stills from the trial and say here's what we're going for.
Which is allowed by the way.
It happens on every project.
Scorsese uses so much of the trial in After Hours.
And I might have noticed that just because I rewatched After Hours the other night.
But those shots of like when he when he sits down next to Bronson Pinchot, Balke in After Hours and the cameras like whipping around the newspaper office where he works and all the cubicles and everything.
That's all this movie.
And you know Wells gets all the credit for inventing all this shit with Citizen Kane and people don't really talk about his entire filmography that much.
It's mostly Kane focused.
But pretty much everything I've ever seen him do is so fucking far ahead of its time.
Like everything we use in movies today for the most part either started or was perfected or was advanced in Citizen Kane.
And to see that in 1962 when he's old and morbidly obese.
He was this inventive.
I mean I'm going to watch every movie the guy made.
It's not like Orson Welles is underrated.
You know everybody knows he's he's one of the greats.
But I just don't think people follow his other films as much.
This was an amazing movie.
It's a Kafka adaptation.
Franz Kafka, Kafka, whatever.
I have not read Kafka.
I have often felt like my life is Kafka -esque.
After Hours is a very Kafka -esque movie where everything just seems to be getting worse.
We've all had nights like this or years like this.
Sure.
And that's what it is.
It's Anthony Perkins wakes up.
Anthony Perkins is fucking great by the way.
He's also speaking of.
He's so much more than psycho.
But he wakes up.
The shot.
Every shot of this movie is so perfect.
And the 4K.
My God.
But he wakes up.
There's cops in his room.
You know they're like hey it's the kind of the Hitchcockian thing.
Like you're in trouble.
We can't tell you why.
He keeps bumping into women.
They're like I want to fuck you.
He kind of doesn't seem to want to.
You're like are they playing with Anthony Perkins being gay here.
It's a weird movie.
Apparently it's a faithful adaptation.
But Orson Welles just rearranged all the chapters.
So the movie kind of flows different.
But it's scary.
It's got very dark sense of humor in it.
I was thrilled to learn that in addition to Orson Welles playing a role.
He dubbed 11 actors performance in their entirety.
And you can't tell.
He also told Perkins that he had overdubbed like 10 of his lines.
And he was like I dare you to pick out the ones I dubbed and Perkins couldn't do it.
Wow.
So knowing that when you watch it you'll hear like it'll be like an old Hungarian woman.
And you're like I think that's Orson Welles.
So it's a fun like game to play while you watch it.
But I highly recommend.
You know it's brand new to 4K so it's easy to find right now.
It's awesome.
I'm sure it's on the Criterion channel.
Check it out.
All right.
I only don't like Joe to make you interested.
It felt like a Twilight Zone.
All right.
I'll check it out.
I'll only do one more.
The new David Tell special is out.
Hot Cross Buns.
Dave is a comic that has meant an immense amount to me since before I even did comedy.
I feel very lucky to have befriended him in this business to have worked with him and
to continue to watch him be the best and funniest working comedian out there.
The special delivers on all fronts.
It's 40 minutes long.
It is so concentrated with jokes.
You're like that was like an hour.
Right.
Like it's got it is so fucking joke heavy.
You can't believe it's only 40 minutes.
And I say that in a good way.
It's the first special I've ever seen that captures what it's like to be at a true David
Tell show.
They got people in the crowd yelling shit out and they just leave it in.
He's turning frequently to a camera on stage and yelling at it.
Like, yeah, he crushes.
It is joke after joke after joke.
I'm just like, Jesus Christ, man.
They're so funny.
They're so well written.
It's fucking awesome.
One of the jokes that made me laugh the hardest is he goes, he goes, I was just in D .C.
And let me tell you, that place has changed since I stormed it.
Yeah, I give him very high praise by saying that I am once I saw that that was out.
I said, I am going to wait to watch this until a day where I need it because I know that I need to laugh sometimes to snap me out of a funk.
And like I know he'll deliver.
So I'm just like waiting for it.
But yeah, he's the best.
He's so fun.
It's one I will watch and rewatch and it'll be, you know, it'll be my favorite.
It'll be one of my favorite things ever to go to for laughs.
I've seen this and I've seen the hour live now twice.
And now I've seen it on this.
I'm still laughing his heart.
So I'm like, oh, this is going to be a keeper like forever for me.
So David Tell Hot Cross Buns, check, check it out.
And I will close with the zone of interest.
The again, multiple Oscar nominee, winner, et cetera.
Jonathan Glazer, the director and all kinds of hot water about his remarks about Israel Hamas.
It seems like there's no way to make a comment about these things without getting in trouble anymore.
But the movie itself, it's a Holocaust movie.
So that tells you right there what you're getting into.
It's not going to be fun.
Spielberg himself calls it the best Holocaust movie since Schindler's List.
Schindler's List is an all time.
It's just an all time.
Great.
I watched it every maybe five years.
It's not one you want to be doing a lot, but I just think it's so perfect.
And that's high praise indeed.
You know, I don't think this movie is anywhere near Schindler's List, but what's fascinating about it,
what's interesting about it, what it did to me, like physically, I have to really admire the movie.
Basically is a Nazi movie shown from the point of the Nazis.
We get a little bit of that in Schindler's List by spending time with Ralph Fiennes,
but we are always led to know that Ralph Fiennes is a monster, a terrible man.
In this movie, we're spending time with the Nazis really to show us how normal their lives were,
how they just kind of went about their day.
And if you didn't know what was going on, they're nice.
They're people just like you and I.
So it's really about the banality of evil.
And it's the kind of stuff that you do not think about really when you think back to those times that these people were also living,
often living within earshot of the Jews that were being tortured and killed.
So the most disturbing scenes of this movie are it's Christian Friedl and Sandra Huler from Anatomy of a Fall,
who play the Nazi couple that we're focused on.
They've got a beautiful garden.
They're out gardening. They're playing with their kids.
They're having fun.
And we're hearing Jews being killed and gassed.
It's wild.
In broad daylight, a beautiful sunny day, and you hear it.
And this is all based in historical fact.
So look, it's not a fun experience, but it changed the way I look at that period of time.
You think of Nazis as all being Indiana Jones.
But a lot of really kind of shitty, I think, short -sighted critiques of the movie were like,
I don't want to sympathize with a Nazi.
I don't want to think a Nazi.
It's like, no, I don't think the director wants you to either.
It's not saying sympathize with these people.
It's saying, think about how easy it can be for this sort of thing to happen.
As Glazer was saying in his speech, he thinks it's happening right now.
So yeah, it's a good, heavy, important, powerful movie.
At the end, it's not a spoiler, but they do the Schindler's List thing of taking us to the modern day.
So really, the ending of this movie is people cleaning.
It's a cleaning crew cleaning one of these camps for tourists to come through and see it in Germany.
And you're like, oh, God.
It does it without any exploitation, really without any violence at all.
I thought this was going to be a lot of like, Schindler's List is an infinitely more violent movie.
There's really nothing in terms of what you're seeing that's terrible.
It's all behind the scenes.
And made me think, man, I really didn't enjoy it, as I said, but it's a very worthwhile movie to see.
And Glazer has put together a real list.
He did Under the Skin with Scarlett Johansson, which is amazing.
He did Birth with Nicole Kidman, which is super underrated.
He did Sexy Beast, which is one of my favorite movies of all time.
He takes like five, six year breaks between each movie and now Zone of Interest.
I mean, he's a great dude.
I've got his music video collection.
He's a bunch of really cool music videos and he's just a guy to watch.
I always love what he does.
It's always interesting.
Joe, speaking of always interesting.
Yeah. Ghostbusters.
Frozen Empire.
Not not always interesting.
No, yeah, it was a bummer because I bought IMAX Saturday AM tickets and I was just I was pumped.
You know, it's like I I really liked Afterlife and most people I know didn't.
Most people on Letterboxd didn't.
And then when this came out, I started hearing people hated it and I was like, OK, well, they hated Afterlife, too.
I love this, but I didn't.
My take my take on this overall.
And this is not a movie that I think we need to try to do a beat for beat breakdown of because the plot is so confusing.
But I will say this.
I don't think the producers of the film could do a beat by beat breakdown of the film.
Well, the three things I will say are Afterlife is a better movie.
Oh, yeah.
Number one, number two, this, though, feels more like a Ghostbusters movie overall than Afterlife did.
And then number three is there is a cohesive good movie in there somewhere.
We did not get it.
It was clearly, clearly cut down from hours of footage.
There are scenes throughout this movie where you see another character, a character is is about to say something and they are cutting.
There's a thing at the end of this thing where Bill Murray runs into Walter Peck.
And and goes, man, you're a bonehead, Peck.
You're just never going to get it, are you?
And then you see him open his mouth to talk and it cuts.
And there's a lot of that in this movie.
There's eighty seven plot lines going on that a very noticeable moment where Patton Oswalt gets dubbed.
Yeah. And they stay on his face, which that always means a very late in the game dub over.
Joe's thought he might have said, fuck.
And they changed it. But like, why are we watching a brand new release that's edited like a USA, you know, Saturday, 2 p .m.
The cuts and edits in this thing are just a jumbled fucking mess.
The guys on a Red Letter Media is one of my favorite YouTube channels.
They're a movie review channel for the most part.
And I watch them frequently. They're very funny.
But they when they reviewed Frozen Empire, they said he said he clearly says it was a something something fuck fest.
And they take out fuck and call it a something something rich fest or something.
Look, this movie has its mo the basic premise.
The very basic premise is there is some sort of ice demon from another dimension that wants to come and freeze all of the earth.
And make it a nice world where everybody's dead except him.
I don't know why they don't ever tell you this.
Just it is what it is. I can. That's fine.
I can live with that.
How this ice demon is captured is very convoluted.
He's inside of this brass ball.
Why how he it starts with this flashback where they're in the firehouse in the 19 in 1912.
And it's not a firehouse yet, but it's a place where this old society of adventurers meets.
And they you that you they open the door and there are it's frozen and and you see that the demons been caught inside the ball.
OK, fine. But they never explain how it got caught inside the ball.
They never explain why when it gets let out of the ball in this one in later in this movie, the ball falls to pieces and doesn't.
It's not a ball anymore. So you're like, I don't understand.
How do they catch him in it to begin with?
You're like the ball is in the firehouse, but then they find it because.
Kamel Nanjiani's character gets introduced and goes to sell it to Ray Stantz at his occult store.
And the PK meter gets a big charge from the ball.
And so Ray buys it and then that inch instead of just having them discovered at the goddamn firehouse where they already are,
then that opens up the doors for Kamel Nanjiani's character, who later is referred to as the wait for it,
because they couldn't even write past Keymaster,
which is another whole not needed, just tacked on other thing and about his family's history,
that they were the demon fighters and and then they have to fight with the Ghostbusters and the Ghostbusters sort of stop the bad guy at the end.
But Kamel kind of does. But then who really does is a ghost who is having a marginal romance with Phoebe.
What's her face? No, Phoebe is the character's name. I forget the actress's name.
Grace McKenna. Grace McKenna. But yeah, I texted Joe.
I go, are we are we about to do a tween lesbian ghost story right now in Ghostbusters?
And Joe said, yeah, but the answer could have really been yes or no, because it is so half assed.
It's like we want to do this. However, we don't want to actually do it because that means parents will get upset.
Kids will be traumatized, whatever, whatever they think happens when two girls kiss.
But it's it's nothing. It's not comedic or dramatic or romantic or fun or anything.
It's this like dreary lesbian love story that involves not even a kiss to my recollection.
And they also never even specifically said this is a love story.
You're supposed to infer that it's like, well, then don't do it.
If you don't have the balls to do it, don't do it. I don't need to see, you know, fingering scenes.
But I'd like a lot now either do it or don't. I wanted a fingering.
So I wanted to say, hey, come get in my trap.
The no, but I mean, the also to it doesn't help matters
that the ghost is like this vocal fry, annoying, like sassy, full of her.
You're like, guys, what the fuck is this, man?
So there's just a million characters they've transported, by the way,
every character that lived in Oklahoma in the last movie to New York without explanation.
Nothing. It's it's insane.
When when Finn Wolfhard walks into that fucking new facility
and sees the girl he had a crush on in the last movie working there
and he's like, what are you doing here?
And she's like, I'm interning for for Dr. Stan.
And you're like, you wouldn't have texted him to say, I'm coming to New York.
Like, and why is she interning? She worked at a roller skate diner.
What do we what is this?
There's a scene at the end of this where they're all like they've all just geared up,
you know, and everybody's getting ready to do the final battle with the ghost.
And they show them all running towards the battle.
And it goes on for like 45 seconds because there's 15 characters.
And I realized, no wonder I don't give a shit.
Ghostbusters was about three Joe lunch pails.
You know, average run of the mill dudes who smoked and drank
and fucked around and tried to get laid.
And they got thrust into this crazy scenario.
That's what everyone loves about the movie.
Now, here we are in the reboot with 15 people of all ages.
They're all running to beat it.
And I'm like, so why couldn't they just easily beat this ghost?
They have so much more power and weapons.
There's no suspense to it.
You know, they're going to win theirs.
And why are they bringing kids along?
You know, I don't necessarily buy that in this death defying thing.
They're like, kids, let's go grab your guns.
I don't buy it. That's one of the children.
That's one of the things they did on Red Letter Media when they reviewed Afterlife.
They were like, remember when Bobby Brown asks Egon to get a proton pack
for his kid brother and Ghostbusters 2?
And then it shows the clip of Egon going proton packs are not toys.
They're not meant for children.
And then it cuts to the footage of Phoebe firing the fucking proton pack.
And you're like, guys, this is just all so unbelievable.
This is how the movie opens.
They're on a wild Ghostbuster run.
By the way, they never explain why the Ghostbusters are allowed to operate again in New York City.
They never explain any redemption, whatever.
All that you see is is they're on a job.
They create all this damage because that's what they do.
And then they're in Walter Peck's office.
And Walter Peck is like, which it's great to see him again.
And that scene's funny. Paul Rudd is funny in it and everything.
And then they go, I'm going to shut you down.
And it's like, OK, then shut them down.
Like, what is the right?
Like, then shut them down.
And then they don't.
Nothing happens.
No drama comes out of it.
Ray Stantz has a very good character arc in this.
I do enjoy the whole I'm aging and I don't want to stop.
It's great. Love that face is lit up.
He looks like he's so excited to be a big part of this and be back on the screen.
And he steals the movie every time you look at him.
He's having a ball. He was great.
I thought Phoebe was great.
I think she's a hell of an actor.
I think she does a great job.
I thought Paul Rudd was funny.
Every other character you're talking about, Phoebe, the main little girl, the main girl.
That's her character's name. Oh, OK.
All right. Grace McKenna is named Phoebe in the movie.
Every other character is an afterthought.
They they sloppily introduced Venkman halfway through.
You're like, wait, is he part of it or is he not part of it or whatever?
That scene sucked.
And it's I'm sorry, Kumail.
Yeah, I'm sorry, guys.
Look, nothing against Kumail.
I've known the guy for 15 fucking years.
I'm happy for him.
I don't want to see.
I'm getting distracted now because I'm seeing a guy I've known.
This is my problem.
I'm getting distracted to see a guy I've known for 15 years with Peter Venkman.
And I'm like, but but anyway, he Bill Murray is funny in the end.
His scene in the firehouse when he comes in at the end, he becomes Venkman
finally for the first time in these two movies.
And you're like, OK, as I told Joe, he has one line that feels like Venkman.
And I guarantee he he improvised it.
Akroyd says, I quit smoking in the 90s.
And Bill Murray goes, proud of you then, proud of you now.
That is Venkman.
But it's also Bill Murray.
And I think that that was probably just made up.
That was the only laugh I had in the whole thing.
And by the way, I like Kumail in this.
I like Patton Oswalt in this.
I just think we're I we got a tonnage of people here.
We've got too many people.
I loved Pat. I loved Patton in it.
I thought Patton had absolute purpose.
I thought he was great.
I bought him in the role.
I did not like Kumail's character.
It was Kumail doing the thing Kumail does all the time in every movie.
I don't need to see smart ass shyster guy Kumail character in this.
It just it served zero purpose.
Zero. I'm not mad that Kumail's in the movie.
I'm mad that they thought because this was not them putting.
This was not them filling a role that needed to be in the movie.
This was them saying, let's get Kumail Nanjiani to do his thing in this.
And those are two different approaches.
I'm sorry. And it's he was he was fine.
He was good. But it's like I've seen it.
Why is this coming into Ghostbusters?
I'm trying to catch up with the kids from the last movie. Right.
And now you're introducing another main character
who also is now like a different form of Ghostbusters.
And I'm supposed to buy that and like whatever.
Like Patton's character had a purpose.
Let's go to the library. It's crazy.
Let's talk to this guy that has, you know, archives and stuff.
You know, it all goes back to TikTok and people's attention spans and all that.
They think we need tons of new characters, tons of new things.
No, the last Ghostbusters introduced tons of new characters.
We're still adjusting to them.
You know, you got Finn Wolfhard, who's probably at this point, tragically,
a bigger star than anyone in the movie to most of people under 20.
And his scenes are like him and Slimer up in a little one bedroom apartment.
I'm like, what could you not get Slimer and him on set on the same day?
Why are these scenes shot in a different location?
Why do they feel so disoriented and detached from the movie?
That's what I'm saying when I say there's clearly a movie there that we're not seeing.
I'm like, Finn Wolfhard's storyline becomes he's going to hunt Slimer in the attic.
They never mention Slimer. He never talks to anybody about it.
He gets slimed and doesn't bring it up.
There's not a lot.
There's not even, to my knowledge, an attempted laugh with Slimer,
who is a comedy character modeled on John Belushi.
It's not supposed to be a scary ghost.
Yeah, it's it's just all of this stuff could have made sense.
It could have been rooted in something there.
And by the way, there are far more implausible things that happen.
By the way, and also for all the shit they talked about,
how they were going to give Ernie Hudson is just do finally.
He's a fucking afterthought in this, which I think sucks.
He's also not not not with them.
He's off in his own little journey, which is like, well, that's not cool.
Why is he suddenly working for the government, the enemy, as we've said,
and all the other are all separated.
You know, they clearly, in my opinion, cut Murray's role way down
because he smelled a lady's pigtail on a fucking movie set two years
or whatever the fuck he did.
And he was clearly cut way down.
He was supposed to, you know, what I heard was supposed to be in this way more.
I don't know. Yeah.
I, you know, poor who's the lady that Paul plays?
Paul Rudd's mom, Carrie Coon or Carrie Coon.
I mean, she's just literally running alongside the group.
Yeah. Same with Annie Potts.
You're going to bring back.
We don't look. I love Annie Potts.
I love seeing her in the other one.
We don't need her in the mix here, guys.
You know, there's too many people in this thing, too many.
By the way, every chance they had like Finn's girlfriend coming from Oklahoma
in the worst writing I've ever seen. Yeah.
Guys, all you had to do, you want her in the movie, have her still be in Oklahoma,
have Finn calling her because he misses her and have Finn wanting to leave the
Ghostbusters because you already have a plot line here where he's talking about
I'm a grown up now. I'm 18. I can do whatever I want.
And he can't leave because of the guilt of his sister having a hard time.
And he's resentful.
And now you've got a fucking character arc.
Instead, you've shuffled him up to a attic.
And the way he's going to prove he's a man is you're going to fan service a
Slimer and he's going to try to catch slime.
It's so by the way.
Holy shit.
Talk about burying the lead.
This whole thing where they've got a secret facility on Staten Island that they
that they've never told the Ghostbusters about where they can contain all the
ghosts and they don't tell them until the ghost containment unit is literally
cracking open and ghosts are getting out of it.
And they never explain that they never explain that this ice demon is sort of
like Gozer.
He can control the ghosts, but the ghosts all got out at the end of the first
movie.
And then that sort of is happening again, but it's not.
They don't explain it.
Then there you're preaching to the choir.
You know, they did one of the hardest things to do, which is reboot a beloved
classic from 30, 35 years ago.
They really did a good job of it and they did it in such a way where we liked
it.
We didn't love the how the Ghostbusters returned the original Ghostbusters for
like one awkwardly shot scene, but we all said, okay, that's pandemic based.
Next time we'll get the boys, you know, we'll have a good time.
And they somehow they blew it again.
You did it.
You had us.
It's just it was really disappointing to me for sure.
And I guess we're going to probably get another one.
It did pretty well.
And they probably won't fix these issues there either.
Murray said in an interview, he goes, he talked about the most painful thing is
wearing the proton packs and he said, he said, you know, we're old now, man.
He goes, so we're, you know, we had to shoot a scene where we walked upstairs
with him this time and we all looked at each other like this is the last one
guys.
And then he immediately goes, not the last movie, just the last take.
I was like, OK, so I guess they're going to and they and there's there's a mid
credit scene that's hinting that the little marshmallow man that they still
haven't explained are going to get an explanation and we're finally going to
get what the fuck that is.
And the director has already said that him and Jason Reitman know that this is
all about eventually centering on Phoebe, which no shit.
We're all aware of that.
So fucking do that through the fucking movie on her without bullshit, like
giving her a ghost to fall in love with or or, you know, getting benched.
Her storyline is she's benched from the Ghostbusters because she's 15 and she's
firing a nuclear weapon around.
It's like, guys, this is the best you could come up with.
This is come on, guys.
This is bat shit right now.
So, yeah, it was a drag.
It was a drag.
I think, you know, Akroyd to me keeps it afloat.
He's got it was it was sweet to see him like eyes lit up, energetic, passionate
again.
And there's, you know, occasionally a good bit or a good line around the
fringes.
But for the most part, it was just sort of an exhausting thing.
And I know that I need more of this franchise.
I said to Pinkstone, it's look, it's definitely worth a watch.
It has its moments, but it is a discombobulated mess and you will never
want to watch it ever again.
That said, I texted Pat Oswald and said, good job.
I did not say this is what I think.
I just said I wasn't lying.
I said your scene was my favorite part.
It was I like that part.
I thought it was it felt like fucking Ghostbusters that part.
They're down in the library.
They're looking at an ancient book.
I was like, this is cool.
Yeah, that and Venkman, you know, at the end.
And that was kind of that.
So they do stuff like like a long close up of the librarian.
Like, remember, this is the same actor from 1984 who played the librarian.
It's like, guys, we don't care at all.
Why is she in there?
Why is the ghost there?
Why?
Yeah, I don't know.
It's so good.
And even the guy on the stairs out front is the same actor from the original.
It's like, OK, all right, guys.
All right.
Well, folks, not great.
Hogs down for Ghostbusters.
Frozen Empire unfrozen hogs because they are down.
We'll be back next time.
Excuse me with who?
Spaceman, Spaceman, Adam Sandler's and movie and probably something else.
Probably Late Night with the Devil.
Yet another possession movie that where a young girl looks up with a
creepy smile and has a voice modulator effect on her voice.
That is the first setting inside of Logic Pro X.
But it's supposed to be good.
OK.
Don't tell me anything.
I'm going to say it.
All right.
You know, the Patrick Walsh Insta.
See when I'll pod our Insta.
Joseph, come see me live.
Joe to Rosa dot com for tickets and show dates and all that stuff.
Joey Roses in NYC, Joey Roses dot com.
All right.
We'll see you next time.
And we'll see you in hell.