I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, and when the sound of your screams becomes
a thing of my dreams, you know I'll say, I'll see you in hell, you know I will, I'll see
you in hell, you know I will.
Folks, it's another episode of We'll See You in Hell, the podcast that's going to talk
about movies, we're going to discuss them, we're going to rate them, we're going to review
them, we're going to trash them more than we love them, it seems, but you know, we're
not here just for the Venom, we're not here just for the dirt, we're here for the good
stuff too.
We're not here just for the Venom, we're here for Venom 2, starring Tom Hardy in a dual
role.
That to me is one of the oddest franchises going.
No one sees them, I saw one, I want to stay on a plane, and it was just fucking bizarre,
they're not good, they're not funny, they're not exciting, the character sucks, and I assume
they're making a third one for 200 million dollars probably.
The character in the comics is very cool, I don't think he should have starred in a
movie.
Well, Venom, meaning the Spider -Man villain, correct?
Yeah, but the thing is, you know, it's this classic fucking thing that they do where they're
like, okay, we're going to make a movie about a villain that everybody loves, so how do
you do that?
Well, we have to make them an anti -hero now, and you're like, alright, so now the symbiote
or whatever it's called, there's this evil alien from another dimension, like cracks
like jokes and shit.
Maybe there's versions of the comic where he does that, I never saw that, Venom was
very sinister and primal, and that's what made it cool.
In fact, when they did it in Spider -Man 3, which sucked, but they did Venom pretty well
with Eddie Brock being a little prick, and he loves the power and all that, that's kind
of what it is.
In this, it's more like, I don't know, Tom Hardy also was playing it, I'm in a Jared
Leto zone with Tom Hardy, where I'm like, is this guy just a, I don't know if I like
what he does anymore.
No, he annoys the hell out of me.
He can't do a role without doing some weird operatic voice, and it's annoying.
You hear a weird, do you hear that?
It might have been my phone vibrating, I turned it off.
No, okay, if you don't hear it, it's fine, there's some kind of noise in my building
happening, I want to make sure you're not hearing it.
I don't hear it.
It's supposed to rain here for like four days, and they're sending in like the most rain
in L .A. history, and there's blizzard warnings, which seems insane to me.
It won't snow here, it'll snow in the mountains around L .A., but it's supposed to be like
a hundred feet of snow, like an hour away from here.
Oh god, yeah, I was on a Zoom yesterday, and one of the people on the Zoom was like, it's
going to snow in L .A., it's crazy, it's so cold here, and then Tim Fenora, who's part
of the project, who's a producer and a great guy from England, he was like, okay, let's
calm down, it's 52 degrees.
Yeah, no, I realized what a pussy I've become living here.
I used to just love when it would be two degrees out, going outside, bundling up, still love
it kind of, but my blood changed, I can't handle it, like it is 55 or so here and it
feels like Arctic, like we're just in the wilderness.
I spoke of this the other day with a friend of mine, it's a trite observation, banging
on pipes, that's good.
That's the thing that they do in New York, is a person will bang on pipes.
Is it to make sure they're good?
What is it?
Who knows?
It's a thing I've only ever seen in New York, the picture, you know, Luigi down there with
a wrench.
Looks good to me, Mario, and he gets sucked into the Mushroom Kingdom.
Anyway, it's a bit of a trite observation, you know, I've heard people make it, but it
is true, you know, when it's winter and you get a 50 degree day, you're out in like sandals
and shorts, and if it's spring and you get a 50 degree day, you're like, this is ridiculous,
it's freezing out here, you know?
That's true, Joe.
You get that from Dave Barry?
Yes, it's from his book, Check My Temperature, and it's musings on weed.
Musings on weed, mostly, but he sneaks a little weather bit in here and there.
Sure.
Check that out.
Who was the other one?
Sniglets, who did Sniglets?
Rich Schneider.
No, Rich, yeah, Rich, right?
I gotta look, I gotta look, Sniglets were like giving a name to something that doesn't
have a name, correct?
Yeah, it was like when somebody -
Rich Hall.
Rich Hall, that's it.
I almost called him Rich Schneider.
I wonder if he got Rich himself off of that, I bet he did.
He did books, and that was when it was a business.
You put a book out back then of that kind of thing, I feel like if you knew how to get
the good deal, you know what I mean?
He probably retired off of that.
Everything's so different now.
I've had a few friends who have written books and they're like, it was the biggest mistake
of my life.
Even not self -published, they get a publisher and the publisher's just like, hey, you gotta
do a bunch more book signings and stuff, we're selling nothing.
And it's like, you know, became a slave to this book.
It's like, I just wrote this because I had some funny stories to share, and now they're
telling me like I'm losing them so much money and I have to go do book signings, but it's
a, not maybe it's a good friend of mine and a great writer, but a nobody in the big world.
So a book signing's gonna do nothing.
Yeah.
Now I hear, can you tilt the mic down?
You're cutting out a little bit on my end.
I wanna make sure that I don't lose you here.
Yeah.
No, no, just tilt it down in front of your mouth a little more.
Thank you.
Um, the, that's funny.
When I wrote a book, co -wrote a book, yes, I remember we had the initial meetings with
Simon and Schuster.
You ever wrote The Talisman, right?
With Stephen King, Peter Straub and you.
No, no, I wrote the Quran.
Right, you know, controversial, but it's definitely still in print, so you can't really complain
about that.
Yes.
Me and Owen King.
You did a translation of Mein Kampf for Florida schools to replace all the books that they're
burning currently.
And folks, be sure to check out Dave Barry's Mein Kampf, a series of musings about trying
to get stuff for free.
Yeah, Mein Kampf, Mein Kampf or maybe Mein Computer, and he's trying to learn the ins
and outs of a computer.
I like Mein Kompt, and it's him, like the free stuff you get.
How about Mein, M -I -N -E, question mark?
Kompt.
Yeah, there you go.
All right, cool.
Um, what I was going to say is, um, damn it, what were we just talking about?
Books, when you co -wrote a book?
When we had meetings with Simon and Schuster about the release, I was like, so we're going
to do like a book tour, right?
Do signings?
They were like, no, like if you want to do that, have at it.
We're not doing that.
And I was like, but wouldn't that help?
They're like, we don't care.
And you do have fans.
It's very, very bizarre how this world works.
Yeah.
Well, that was a long time ago, maybe the industry has changed again.
You make any money off that book?
The advance was not bad, but it's never turned a profit in 10 years.
And, and I believe it hasn't, I don't think it sells well, but if I did, what am I going
to do?
Audit fucking Simon and Schuster and go, I want to see, you know what I mean?
Like, um, but you know, so.
There's a new thing that the, uh, the TV studios and networks are all doing, which is they've
always come in with a somewhat low ball offer.
You know, that's negotiation 101 to start, but they also used to know, well, I don't
want to piss this guy off.
He's been a writer for 20 years or whatever.
We've done business with him before, you know, that's all gone.
I've gotten so many texts lately of friends like, holy shit, have you, have you sold
anything lately?
I just got an offer and I don't know what to do.
So I've got this thing going.
Big people involved, stars, all sides of the camera.
It's popping studios, a lot of interest around town.
I got an offer yesterday.
So the script is written.
It wasn't a pitch.
I wrote the script and I was like, which one of you fuckers wants to rock?
And a lot of people did.
And the place I went with, I was like, okay, great.
And I keep waiting, but they have to buy the script for me at some point
before we take it out.
So, uh, man, good Lord, the offer I got yesterday.
I was like, it's the first time in my life I've considered a different business.
I think advertising might be where it's at for me.
You've said this.
You look at these, you look at these Superbowl commercials, you look at the
billboards in my neighborhood.
I gotta, I gotta make a lot of money in that world.
I have to.
I know.
I don't know, man.
I know the guy that I, that basically created the most interesting man in the
world thing.
And I know another guy that created a very popular Wendy's campaign.
I forget what it was called.
It was when Wendy's was doing the threesomes thing or whatever, where it was
like, you could get three, I forget what it was called, but Wendy's had this
campaign, Dave Thomas blonde and the brunette kind of, yeah, you can get three
items for like three bucks and it was, it had like a very catchy name.
I can't remember, right.
But like those guys didn't have, don't have shit to prove to show for.
I'm not saying they got nothing, but like, I think the advertising industry is
exactly like the entertainment industry now where they're like, well, you created
this under our roof, we own it.
So what the fuck do you think we owe you?
You know, here's your money.
That's my assumption.
I don't know.
Right.
You know that, you know, I have a team.
If you're, if you're a writer, you have a team, you know, whether it's, I have
an agent and a lawyer, some people have a manager, whatever, but so I get on the
phone yesterday with the agent and the lawyer, the agent takes 10%, the lawyer
takes 5 % and the attitude always is kind of throwing their hands up.
They're like, yeah, the business just really sucks right now.
They're like, we'll get you there.
We'll get you, you're, cause writers are supposed to have quotes, meaning a
quote that they have to meet and now they're going below the quotes, which is,
this is why we're going to have a strike and we're all going to be fucked all over
again.
But, um, I was just like, you know, it would be nice if my team didn't call me
every time I, I sell something, which lately is a lot I'm doing well and the
team calls and it's always, boy, I wish we could, uh, wish we had better news
here, that kind of stuff.
And it's like, guys, like you just want them to go fight for you and do it, but
they're like, you got to call this person.
You got to call this person.
Sweet talk.
This guy.
Uh, how close are you with this woman?
Maybe you could call her and I'm like, this should not be my fucking job.
I wrote the script that people like and want to do.
That's my job.
Right.
I, I, I hate my own business, but I get it.
I guarantee people in real estate and all, whatever they're in hate their job too.
That's what I have to remember.
But they, uh, they don't, I talk to them and they, they seem like
they like what they do.
Oh, realtors seem like the happiest, most coked out people of all time.
I feel like they're all fucking each other.
They're all beautiful.
I mean, I, I, I got to tell you, man, for as bad as the airline industry is, these
flight crews, they're walking on air.
These people, they walk on, they're smiling, they're laughing.
Like these people love their work.
Like they, they, you know, because here's the thing.
Here's the thing that the realtor, here's the thing that other industries now, I'm
not saying they don't have it at all, but here's, there's a drastic difference
between the entertainment industry and other industries.
There is not a self -worth like rep as attached to you in certain other
industries, you know what I mean?
Like where your rep starts to affect your self -esteem and all that stuff.
So like they're in reputation, not represented, right?
Right.
So meaning like in, in real estate, you can have a nice reputation, meaning
like you sell well and they say, Hey, this is the person for that job.
But in the entertainment industry, it's like that guy's hot stuff right now.
We all need to pretend to give a shit.
You know what I mean?
Or whatever.
So, and then on top of it all, you know, your realtor, you know, the company,
you know, century 21 or whatever, you know, they might be in cahoots with the
loan officers or the bank or whatever, but like this business, they're all in
cahoots, you know, so the agent is trying to staff your project that you
sold with his clients, uh, you know, your manager is trying to shove you into
these meetings because she knows people over there and she's got another person
there doing this and, and then they underhandedly, a lot of the time come
back and try to push you away from certain things because they want to
service other people that are in their interest.
And I mean, it's just fucking madness, man.
It's just madness.
Yeah.
I used to treat agents as if they knew everything.
And I, you know, I have a tough time with decisions.
So I was like, you tell me, you tell me, but it was so stupid and misguided
because they're always about themselves and everyone in the business is.
So you have a team representing you, but at the end of the day, you die in
your own arms, you know, you got to do it yourself and it kind of sucks.
Um, so in this case, I thought, well, I hate having to write a script while
getting notes from three different entities, especially now when the person
at the top is changing literally once a month, and that's not the small studios.
That's Disney has a new president every month.
Right.
So I'm like, okay, to avoid all that run around, I'm going to write my dream
script, take as long as I need and turn it in a finished product, ready to go.
First time I've ever done that.
So I do that.
They're like, we have zero notes, meaning the entire six month development process,
which costs everyone money and stress and pain and time.
I have taken care of that for you.
I have given you a script that we all feel does not need any work.
That's a gift.
Yeah.
And then you low ball me like.
Fuck off.
We're literally talking about going after the biggest names in Hollywood on the
same call where I'm like, but here's what I'm getting paid guys.
It's fucking shit.
It is shit.
Um, used to, used to make good money.
You know, that's why I live in a nice, nice house.
You know, it's, it's the guys when I, when I started the business were like, I
couldn't believe the money I was making.
Cause I was coming from a, being a temp at state farm, but the old dog is there
in the room where we're like, bro, this business used to be, they'd give you a
Porsche if, if, you know, like the cast of friends all got a Porsche after the
first season, like they had so much money flying around three networks.
Everybody to watch those three networks for the most part.
And, uh, boy, we're fucked.
We really, really fucked at this time.
I'm writing on a show now that hasn't been picked up.
That's what most of my friends are doing.
They're like, we've been writing for, uh, three months and we're going to find
out soon if they're going to produce our scripts.
No, no.
And the more you let them do it, the more they're going to do.
Well, it's, it's all been, it's all part of the great American corporatocracy.
And, uh, the, this has just been reduced, reduced to a content factory, like any
other corporate structure where they have you go into a fucking room for three
months and brainstorm and do all these things and then turn around and go, you
know, guys, we're actually going to go to a different route.
Here's some consultants.
Now we're bringing in, they have the money.
They still have that Porsche money.
They just don't share it anymore.
They now go, oh, what we could do is waste our own money instead of keeping
our employees and talent happy.
What we could do is waste this money on things that we could throw in the
trash if we wanted to, and that's what they do.
Uh, and that's, that's what it is.
I mean, you know, speaking of money, what never occurs to them is maybe we could
save a million a year by cutting one of the 40 useless executives we have
chiming in on this project, but yeah.
Or maybe don't change executives every three months and have to build in all
these like bonuses and, and, you know, uh, clauses that if we, you know, if
we don't renew, you get this much money and, you know, and all this stupid shit.
Uh, Moonves was raping women left and right.
When they finally let him go, he got about a hundred million dollars.
He still has an office in Hollywood.
You know, it's just, it's absurd.
Speaking of money, uh, this is something I've been wanting to talk.
This is a new cycle.
It's something I've wanted to talk about for a while because
it really burns my, uh, britches.
I saw two different articles recently.
Darcy Carden was, uh, one was centered on her and the other was on Kate Hudson.
Both headlines read so -and -so, insert the name, one of the names I just mentioned.
Expresses interest in joining the Marvel cinematic universe.
Okay.
And then you read the thing and it's from a press junket and, and, you know,
some point during the junket, the person's like, and you see this all the time.
Oh God, I would love to be in a Marvel thing.
Just waiting for you to call guys.
And they're just famous enough that they might actually get a gig out of it.
And it's like, it's so sick to me.
It's so sick.
Like what would you really, oh, really?
You want to be part of the fucking billion dollar capitalistic global
conglomerate that will allow your great grandchildren to retire at age six?
Because of the money.
Oh, what a surprise.
It's like, God damn it.
Can a celebrity talk in an interview anymore?
And I'm sure that they do.
But just for the purpose of this rant, can a celebrity talk in an interview
anymore about, you know, I, uh, I'm trying to acquire the rights to this Emily
Dickinson novel, uh, uh, so I can make it into a movie.
It's been a dream of mine.
You know, uh, I always felt they never made American psycho the adaptation
properly, I'm trying to get the rights to do the version that, that the original
adaptation should have been.
Uh, you know, I wrote this script and it's been blood, sweat and tears
to get this thing made, but come hell or high water, I'm going to get,
why is it never that anymore?
Why is it everybody going, Ooh, I'd like to be part of the cool kids thing
that pays a gazillion dollars.
Fuck off, man.
It's also fucking boring.
And because they want a gazillion dollars.
I mean, that, that's, that's all it is.
I do think sometimes they get asked, would you ever do a Marvel movie?
And they go, Oh, absolutely.
Give me a call.
Not thinking.
And then it becomes a headline that happens a lot.
Uh, but yeah, it's just, that's the way to make money now, whether you're an
actor or writer, director, whatever else you can earn a nice living, but if you
want to get rich, that's where you gotta go.
That's where you gotta go.
It's just, it's just, I don't, I won't do it.
Cano's been offered many a Marvel role and they won't do it.
I think he is now though.
I think he's officially finally, but, but, you know, like it's, it's just,
it's just, God damn it is the, is the goal is the, and I love by the way that
people now are finally, Hey, Hey, congrats on catching up America.
I've been down this fucking road six, you know, for years.
I glad I'm glad that I'm being an asshole, but I'm glad that people are finally
going we enough with the jokes, Thor, love and thunder.
It's like, Oh, it took four Thor movies for you to realize this.
Oh, yeah, there's a lot of hate for the new ant man, which I have not seen.
I don't think I even saw the second ant man, but I liked the first.
Okay.
I mean, I don't, I don't mind a lighter tone, especially because Thor and, uh,
ant man present themselves as light comedic fare.
That's why it doesn't bother me as much.
Um, but yeah, the Marvel movies where it's just quip, quip, quip, quip, quip,
and then the audience is just slapping their knees.
Yeah.
It makes you wonder about society.
I said in these, I always think about the taxi driver scene where he's watching
the soap opera and he keeps kicking the TV with his foot while he's watching it
because he can't relate to it.
It's a couple in love and he's like, this means nothing to me.
I don't have this to my life.
I'm a lonely psycho.
And he keeps tapping the TV and then it falls over and breaks, you know, crashes.
He doesn't even really move.
That's how I feel.
That's how I felt with, uh, I don't want to say his name.
I have a meeting with him tomorrow, but, um, these big movies are like,
you looked around at the audience laughing and it's like, then what am I doing?
Well, and here's what am I, what am I trying?
If I, if I'm writing scripts and they're not connecting like they used to,
maybe it's because the executives are sitting in these movies and going,
oh, this is what people want.
It used to be, it used to be, it's one thing if Marvel offers you the thing
and you go, yeah, I'm going to do it.
I'd be stupid not to.
I get that.
But it used to be, you know, I remember when the accidental tourist came out.
I don't know how I remember this, but I do.
Did not expect you to say that, but I remember seeing an interview
with Gina Davis and Gina Davis, Gina Davis was as hot as it could be.
I don't mean physically.
I mean, like she was a go -to.
She was huge at the time.
And I remember supporting actors for that very role.
And she said, I love the book so much.
And when I read that they were making it into a movie, I said,
I have to be a part of this.
That's what it used to be.
There was like some element of the work of giving a shit about the work of
going after the passion or whatever.
Now it's like, you just want to be in front of any camera, any camera.
You know what I mean?
The, uh, you know what it is, Joe, really though is it's hard to blame them
when there used to be a billion movies made and now there aren't like if you're
an actor that unfortunately you kind of have to be this mooch and try to get
these other things because, uh, let's take, I don't want to talk about money
specifics, but like, let's talk about an actor like David Krumholz.
Everybody knows him.
Everybody likes him.
He is unquestionably a very gifted actor.
That's a guy who will get two parts a year, but everyone thinks that if you're
on TV, you are a millionaire, you know, if you're a supporting guy like that,
even if you've been doing it 30 years, you're not making big, big money.
And let, if you, unless you get on a show that goes a long time and those are
rarer and rarer, or unless you do this Marvel thing, I sort of get it, but this
is, I wish people did more passion projects, but this is what I was
referring to earlier, this concept of my worth in this fucking business.
It's like, it's like, I am in the, as, as, as a comedian is concerned financially,
I'm in the actor that like Krumholz I'm in that same kind of wheelhouse in a
comedian's perspective, right?
I make a good living.
I support myself.
Yeah, I do not have millions and millions.
And I mean, I can't speak for David, but I'm just saying like, I'm, my assumption
is, is David is not, if he is, he could pick up a few more fucking checks, but
listen, if he saved his money from numbers with the three as an E, he's got
money, but I don't, I don't ask him these questions.
No, no, I don't either.
And David, if you're listening, we're not to try to talk about your money.
We're just saying, um, but my point is, is I make a good living.
I always say this.
I make a, I make a, uh, an accountant's, uh, living, you know, like, or like a,
if I had like a good corporate job, like that's kind of, but which is what a dream
come true to talk about movies, to go on another thing and talk about food, to go
on the road and do my fucking abrasive comedy and own a hoagie shop, like what a
fucking dream, but in this business, it's like, but yeah, but you don't own a house
in the Hills with an eye scanner that lets you in through the gate and you
don't take private jets and your tickets only cost $25 or $35 and not 150.
Yeah, that's all anybody sees.
It's it's sick.
It's fucking sick.
And I'm guilty of it.
I'm guilty of it too.
By the way, those same, I'm guilty of it too.
And those same people who are taking the private jets and everything else
will turn around and criticize capitalism all the time.
Don't get me.
Walsh don't open this can of worms.
I can't.
Yeah.
No, exactly.
Everybody in Marvel going out and being like, as they cash checks from Disney.
Yeah.
You know, Trump, uh, what, what?
Ruffalo's big on it.
Ruffalo's real big on it.
And you're like, dude, you gave up being a great actor to play the
hulk for 25 years, the hulk.
There's a rumor floating around now that Downey jr is coming back
already as iron man.
And did he die?
Yeah.
Oh, he died in a, what end game?
I don't know which one he died in the last ones.
Anyway, let's go to the movie corner.
I only have two.
That's the thing.
That's, that's honestly, when people ask, it's not, it's not me hating popular
things that I don't like Marvel.
It is exactly that.
I don't want to watch a three hour movie where characters can die and come back.
That's it.
What, what are the stakes in a world where everyone can die and come back and
everyone that I am watching on screen is animated at that point.
I'm a five year old.
I'm watching a three hour animated movie and I'm a 42 year old man.
I don't want to be watching an animated movie.
Have you seen the pictures of Modoc and, uh, ant man, the new
Modoc Google it right now.
I always like Modoc.
It's a cool character.
Wait, wait till you see the, the art design they did on this thing for a
presumably $300 million movie.
It looks like maybe, uh, an investment bankers face in the crank thing.
I'm only seeing, um, I mean, I'm not mad at it.
It doesn't bother me too much.
I mean, they had to make it look a little, I get it.
They changed it a little bit.
If they made it like it is in the comics, it would have looked kind of goofy.
But, uh, you don't think this looks goofy.
Okay.
Well, it's a little alien, uh, man in, you know, like with a giant head,
you know, like, I like, you know, that, but I hear you, that doesn't,
that doesn't bother me.
I'm surprised.
That sucks for, well, I guess it doesn't suck for him, but like
Patton does the voice, Patton Oswald does the voice in a cartoon.
It's like, let him do it in the movie too.
Like Pat, he could have done this.
I'm wondering if you're seeing the same thing I'm seeing.
Well, I'm, there's a million different pictures and the problem is, is you
don't know what one is real.
I'm putting it in the chat.
But yeah, there's the ones of Corey stall where it's just his face.
Oh, is that who it is?
That's the actor from Game of Thrones.
No Corey stall.
I don't know.
Not Game of Thrones, uh, house of cards.
Yeah.
But I can't tell if these things of his face in the thing are real or not.
Then I'm seeing other ones that look really cool.
And I, my assumption was those were the real ones.
No.
And I can't post anything in the chat because who cares?
Who cares?
I only have, let's go to the movie corn.
I only have two, but the first one I'll do.
And it's, um, it's, um, uh, but I want to stay on theme.
I wasn't going to talk about this, but I ended up turning
it off on a fucking airplane.
That's how bad this movie was.
I put on a fantastic beasts.
The secrets of Dumbledore thinking this will just be a fun airplane movie.
Harry Potter world.
You know, I'm in the mood for some trans hate.
Let's go.
I'm kidding.
The, uh, no, but I was like, it'll just be a fun airplane movie.
We'll run around with the wands.
Yeah.
Jude Law is Dumbledore.
Cool.
Mads Mikkelsen, whatever the fuck his name.
I think the fact that that's not the name of a character he plays.
And that's just insane.
He's playing the Johnny Depp part, right?
Yeah.
I was like, I only saw the first fantastic piece and I fucking hated it.
But I guess there's been two or three.
Three.
The first one was passable.
The second one was like, yeah, this one.
It is the most boring.
Who gives a shit?
I mean, it is boring.
It is joyless soul.
It is so fucking boring.
Nothing happened.
And here's my, here's the point I want to get to every fucking scene you're looking
at now, look, I'm going to be guilty of this or some movies that I'm looking
forward to are probably guilty of this, but you know what?
They hide it better.
Every fucking scene you are looking at in this movie.
I'm sitting there going, I none of this means anything anymore.
They can do all of this by putting two people in whatever room they want in
whatever clothing they want at any age they want with whatever lighting they
want and fix all of it digitally to look however they want.
And, and this is a movie where it reeks that they, it reeks of it.
You're like, this is what they did.
Look at how perfectly the light beams are shining through the dust particles.
And, and it's just all of it.
Look, and now we go it.
None of it means anything anymore.
DP.
What does it even mean anymore?
In a movie like this director, what does it even mean anymore?
In a movie like this, they don't shoot scenes in a library anymore.
They have two people on a green screen and they put a bunch of
books in it and post it.
I mean, you get no texture, no sense of place.
Uh, I, I hate it.
It's, it's dominating bigger budget movies at this moment in time.
And you're like, it's just a shame.
Cause you used to watch something and you go, wow, the, the, the fact that
a good, if you look at movies from the eighties and nineties, you know, and
I know George Lucas is, is, is a lot to blame for this, uh, you know, but
at least when he did it, he was like, I'm going to do something wild and new
that I think is the future.
And he was right.
Yeah.
And then also admittedly was like, ah, you get a new technology.
You go a little too far with it.
Maybe I did.
And, you know, we tried to reel it in in the final movie or whatever.
Um, but anyway, um, but you watch a movie like just, just easy example.
Goodfellas it is a fucking masterwork because you're like, cause all anybody
ever says is Scorsese good and that obviously it's a huge part or Nicholas
Pileggi good for obviously he's a huge part, but when you step back from that
compared to now and go, my God, the set designer, the costume designer, the
department, the actor, the writer, the director, the DP, the grip, every single
person hitting that much of a grand slam that it comes together and not just a few
scenes, but an entire, the editor, an entire movie, it's fucking masterful.
And that's gone.
Like that's going away where it's just like, well, it's not gone.
There's plenty of indie stuff out there, but you get, you get, it's pretty gone.
I read the goodfellas book.
I mean, they talked about like just the location scouting for that movie.
Yeah.
It's like, okay, we're in New York in 1990, but we're trying to recreate the fifties.
So it's like, they're looking all around New York for like that perfect
cabana bar, let's say, or whatever it might be.
And you feel that at no point do you question that you're watching a movie
that takes place in the, in the fifties or the seventies or whatever you may be
watching now, if it's a period piece.
There might be one establishing shot of a street with like model T's on it.
And then they go inside and that shot lately I'm learning is often
not even from the production.
Like the, the, uh, they said the very first shot in shit.
What was the movie?
Um, a brand new movie that came out.
They said the very first shot was, uh, stock footage.
Of like a big movie.
And apparently they do it all the time now.
It's like, now Scorsese is like, we got to look all over to find the perfect
location to shoot this literally 30 second scene that'll, that'll make up
one little moment of good fellows.
And here we are.
We're using stock footage in other films, like, because Hey, it's there.
So why not?
Anyway, this is what everybody, this is what everybody.
So desperately wants to be a part of.
This is, you know, because it's about, it's not about the work.
It's about working.
Get in front of any camera you can.
And, and then by the way, when you're coming up the ladder and struggling
apps of fucking Lutely, cut your teeth in any way you can.
You're lucky to even get the work when you're at a point where you're
already a fucking multimillionaire.
Yeah, that's not enough.
Now I got to go do, you know, dude, I love Samuel Jackson.
This guy's fucking hocking cell phones.
Plan.
I'm not sure.
I'm not sure what he's doing.
You know, like look, he did that passion project for apple that the days and
nights of Ptolemy gray or whatever, uh, that no one in the world has ever
or will ever watch, but, um, the bulk of what he just said was problematic.
The passion project for apple.
It's like, it's, it was, yeah, it was all the T's were crossed on that contract.
I'm sure it was fine.
Sorry.
Yeah.
I mean, he, he's given up, you know, like maybe he's not getting offers, but I
find that pretty hard to believe.
I think at this point, he's like at all points.
I always talk about that letter of an interview where he's like, wouldn't
you go to Hawaii if they offered you $5 million?
Sure.
But you don't want to do, you don't want to do nine for them.
One for you maybe.
Well, that's the thing.
And he does do good stuff, but it's like Samuel L Jackson or Mr.
Jackson or Sam, or however I should address him and not a person who doesn't
know him, you, you, yes, fine.
And you did go to Hawaii for 5 million bucks.
So then you don't have to sell Verizon.
Right.
Like, you know, Mark Wahlberg, I've used the example of Mark Wahlberg
shucking fucking AT &T.
It's like, what the fuck is this?
He just sold like a $50 million house and it's like, what are you, are you donating
to charity or what are you, what are you doing with this wealth?
What are you doing?
I'll tell you the one that kills me to say it, it kills me to say it, but I
mean, cringe city, that fucking Danny McBride calling himself Downey McBride
with the detergent commercial where he's riding down the street, throwing
Downey out to people.
Oh, I haven't seen that.
Is that a Superbowl thing?
I think so.
I mean, again, I don't know.
You offer me a Superbowl commercial.
Maybe I'll do it, you know?
And I know plenty of people could go, well, you do ads on taste buds.
It's like, well, yeah, we do do ads.
That's how the show makes money.
Yeah.
Like we do Patreon with this show.
That's how it makes money.
Like it has to, we, you know, I'm not saying don't make money.
I'm just saying like, can't you not make some of it?
Yeah.
Like Christ on the cross, man.
Like I remembered what it was before I do mine.
The first shot of the menu is stock footage.
Now that doesn't piss me off that much, but it led to this bigger
discussion of how much stock footage is used in movies of today.
And it's like, Jesus Christ, man.
That used to be like, you'd find stock footage in like a three
Stooges reel or something, you know?
They put, they put all their money in the wrong things.
Uh, the friends of mine who, who here's a great example.
And I won't say names.
There's a big movie coming out with two big stars, one who has an accident
a while and then another who's, you know, a big star, a buddy of mine has been hired.
Now he loves that this practice because it gets him paid, but this is,
this is why the movies aren't working.
He gets sent a really bad script, an action script.
And they said, Hey, we cast these two people and they are both funny.
And what we'd like to do is add some comedy to the script.
Great.
He adds comedy to the script.
He turns it in.
They're like, great.
We love this.
Got it.
Thanks.
Pay him.
A year passes, they come back.
Hey, they changed, uh, they changed heads here at the studio.
We're thinking we just want to do straight ahead action.
Action comedies aren't really working.
It's a Netflix movie.
And for Netflix, it's just straightforward action.
Okay.
Um, so what do you want me to do?
If you could just sort of scale the comedy that you have in their back, um,
you know, make it more like realistic comedy, but you know, like these vague
notes, he does it, he turns it in.
He gets it a year later again.
Now it's got a ton of comedy in it, but none of it is his.
They go, Hey, the actors hate the comedy in this.
So we want you to do a pass to kind of change the comedy.
He goes, I'm happy to, but this isn't the comedy I added.
And they're like, Oh no, we had somebody else take a crack,
but now they're back to him.
He's like, okay.
He does a pass, adds some comedy.
Then he's like, they're producing it.
And then they call him and they're like, would you want to maybe be on
set to add some more comedy to it?
This is, this is a $200 million movie.
Nobody knows what genre it is and it's, it's in production.
So my buddy is annoyed and we're laughing at this at the diner or whatever, but
he, you know, he's making a lot of money off this.
He's happy with it, but this is why movies.
This is how you end up with Stuber.
Exactly.
You know, like, it just goes, it goes on and on my, my friends, uh, who write
movies are just like, yeah, you know, you write it, um, it, it'll, it'll,
it goes away for three years.
And then all of a sudden it like comes back to you and they're like,
Hey, can you fix this?
So, you know, how many drafts and how much money they blew over that three
years only to come back to you and it happens every time and nobody learns.
All right.
Let me talk about my movie.
Yeah.
In fact, I only, I only have that one that because it highlighted so
well, what we're discussing, I'm going to save my other one.
Fair enough.
I saw a really good new indie movie to give you some positives after
we shit on the movie business.
It is called the civil dead directed by Clay Tatum, uh, and starring
the comedian Whitmer Thomas.
I know Whitmer a teensy bit.
Um, but they're both comedy people and a lot of, uh, sort of up and coming
comedy people are in this, including my friend, Chris Thayer and his
girlfriend, Anna Surigena.
Uh, the gist is this.
It's a great idea.
Uh, it's a guy who's, he's one of these Hollywood hangers is on.
He keeps talking about how he's friends with Andy Samberg, but he's like, you
know, like I'm friends with Andy Samberg.
Like it's like his claim to fame sort of, which a lot of people
out here are like that.
Um, all he wants to do is basically watch TV and drink.
He's a very kind of angry closed off dude.
And into his life comes Whitmer Thomas, who was his old friend from high school.
They start talking and he's like, why are you w w what brought you to me?
Like what's going on?
And he explains that he has a ghost.
He's dead and that nobody can see him.
So he's just kind of been walking around until he finds somebody who can see him.
And now he finds this old high school friend of his who can see him.
So he's like desperate, like you're the only guy on earth who can see me.
I need to be around you at all times, but he's annoying and like needy.
Uh, and it's this great low budget comedy, but it's also a supernatural story,
even though there's zero special effects.
Uh, and I thought it was very well done and charming and funny.
The two lead guys are best friends that chemistry comes through.
Um, it's a really small suite at times.
And I thought pretty darn funny indie movie.
It's new on Amazon.
The director Clay Tatum last night posted the link to watch it for free on
YouTube. So this is exactly the opposite of what we're talking about.
He wants people to see his movie. He'll, he'll share a free YouTube link.
He doesn't care. Um, and that comes through, you know,
you get why they're proud of it. It's a small, original comedy.
That's the kind of things we used to get all the time from independent films.
Uh, and I really liked it. Check it out.
All right.
Uh, Thomas, I do, you know,
yeah, I know him. I don't, we don't like hang out or anything, but yeah.
Same here. I liked his, uh, standup special and I usually don't like singing
comedy, but he had a, he had a good twist on it.
The, uh, yeah, I don't remember where I've spent some time with him,
but it's somewhere, somewhere, a big crazy world.
Anyway, uh, you want to move on to the movie on deck or do you want to do
another, it's up to you.
Uh, well, shit. I mean, I feel like I should do one more for Christ's sake.
Uh, let's talk about scenes from a mall.
Woody Allen and Bette Midler.
This is a VHS box I saw every time I went to the video store.
It's a horrible poster.
Just, uh, and the, the premise of it is scenes from a marriage,
the Ingmar Bergman movie, meaning a couple's marriage falling apart,
but it's all at a mall.
I love this movie when I first saw it.
And then, and I owned the Blu ray of it.
And then Jesse pop made fun of me one day for having it.
And I was like, Oh yeah, I guess you're right.
And I rewatched it and I was like, Oh, I don't like this movie.
I thought I did.
Yeah, he's right to make fun of it.
I actually owned it too on a, on a, one of those double feature DVDs with big
business is that where, uh, Bette Midler and Shelley Long are twins.
No, no, it's not good.
Yeah.
But, um, I finally sat down and watched it.
It's Paul Mazursky.
I at the, over the pandemic watched almost all of Paul Mazursky's movies.
And I find him to be sort of a less consistent, but very
interesting Woody Allen.
His best stuff is like Bob and Carol and Ted and Alice.
Um, and he's made some really good movies.
Don't get me wrong.
Seems from all is kind of, it feels very nineties, but it's not
really satirizing nineties LA.
Like there's, it's Woody Allen with a ponytail and like with the, you know,
with the car, with the giant car phone and everything, but it's not making fun
of them the way that down and out in Beverly Hills with Bette Midler and
Richard Griffiths and Nick Nolte, also a Paul Mazursky film, uh, I really made
fun of them.
That was a very satirical look at capitalism and at people being obsessed
with, uh, material goods and stuff.
And it only came out a few years before this.
Even though it's sent to them, set in a mall, they really don't do anything
in terms of criticizing, uh, the culture.
It's just too annoying people arguing and they both reveal that they've
cheated on each other multiple times.
It's hard to find any sympathy for either one of them.
You do get to see Bette Midler in a sex scene where like, we're, we're
seeing her ass in like see -through panties.
She's got to be 50 when this thing's going on.
Honestly, I didn't mind it.
I didn't mind it.
Um, it's weird to see Bette Midler as like a sexual being, but I liked that.
I liked Woody Allen in this sort of, I mean, he's never relaxed, but I like him
as just an actor, not doing his own thing.
I really did.
I thought he did a good job and their chemistry was pretty good.
It's not a good move.
It's not a good movie by any means, but if you're interested in, in Woody
Allen with a ponytail and Bette Midler arguing in a food court for 90 minutes,
while a mime harasses them in the least funny subplot in American film
history, um, check out scenes from wall.
All right.
Here we are movie at hand, a movie that exemplifies all the right things.
We are saying we wish movies did these days and the opposite of a Marvel film.
It's a picture called tar sweeping the Oscar nomination nominations list, uh,
and sweeping the hearts of lesbian conductors from around the world.
It's actually, I mean, one of my favorite things about it is what a
heartless movie it is really, but yeah, tar is the story of.
You know, a hot con I love when movies try to try to do this.
She's the hottest conductor in town.
You're like, all right, I'll, I'll take your word for it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
No, I know.
That was, there were parts of this where I was like, guys, nobody is
talking about a conductor on tick tock.
And yet, and yet if you are into that world, that world of classical music,
then yes, you are this type of person.
And, um, I think the movie gets that and gets these people very, very well.
The, the premise of it is Lydia tar, uh, perhaps not her real name.
Spoiler alert is a very, very pretentious narcissistic, uh, she's
Kate Blanchett, so she's gorgeous.
Um, but she's at the top of her game.
She's in command.
She's conducting this major orchestra.
She's got a wife and a daughter and an assistant who, and everybody seems to
get along and idolized her and everything's going well, it starts with a
very long New Yorker interview, arguably too long of Kate Blanchett being
interviewed by this guy at the New Yorker.
But it really helps ground you in this world and also realized little by little.
That's why I love that opening scene so much.
And I actually watched tar again, uh, which is rare for a three hour movie
like this or almost, but that scene, as you watch it, you're like, Oh, okay.
This is just a great professional, whatever.
And little by little, she starts dropping things that when I saw it in the theater,
people start laughing at, like, you know, people like this, if you work in the arts,
she's so full of herself.
Um, she's referring to Leonard Bernstein, her mentor as Lenny, you know, that kind
of shit, as the movie goes on, you wonder if she ever even met Leonard Bernstein.
Um, but what happens is she's eventually accused of me too shit, you know, uh, of
seducing and promising job opportunities to young, attractive, uh, musicians based
on their looks, women, and then she fucks them.
She's a lesbian predator.
Yeah.
Um, and you know, for a long time in this movie, she's like denying it and blowing
it off because narcissists like this, like Harvey Weinstein are like, Oh, please.
Like I'm too important to be bothered by any of this.
Well, that comes later in the movie that comes much later.
It's the first turn, a dark turn of events is that this, this student, this
ex, the student who's been excommunicated from this foundation for female composers
because she quote had mental problems is, is harassingly emailing them.
And then they, which is perfect.
Cause a narcissist would brand you as crazy.
Yeah.
And then we find, but also too, this is what a person who was unstable would do.
So they do a nice, the thing I liked about this movie before I go too far is, and
these are spoilers, it takes the approach that doubt took where they never tell
if it definitely happened or not.
Like there's a lot where I was like, Oh, she did this.
And then there was a lot where I was like, I don't know if she did this.
Um, because they just, I think she did it.
I agree with you that it's, that it's vague, but as in, as in doubt, I
felt I left feeling pretty confident that Philip Sumer often had done it.
But in this movie, I left feeling a hundred percent sure she had done it.
Oh, where'd your sound go?
Did you hear me now?
But yeah, couldn't for a second.
Oh, sorry.
Cut out.
I, I'm different.
I in doubt.
I didn't think he did it.
I was like, that's this kid didn't fucking do this or this guy didn't do this.
Uh, especially when, um, if I'm remembering correctly, I might be
misremembering, but when it doesn't matter, we, that I just remember not
thinking that he thinking he didn't do it in this, I was a little more certain
that she had, but I still thought they, it, it, I thought they left it up to,
I feel like it's the kind of thing where if you kept going back and revisiting,
you'd go, oh, but actually they really set it up to make you think that because
they do this over here and then conceivably she might not have done it.
It's just good at that, but they, I'd certainly say they lean harder in this
movie to making you think at least on an initial watch that she's guilty.
Whereas in doubt, it really was the whole time.
I was like, I don't fucking know, man.
Jesus, you know, like, uh, well, I mean, it's a, it's arguably an even darker
story with the places that her character goes to if she didn't do it.
Like when she's a jumping and attacking that other conductor at the end of it.
It's, but I don't think the message of that movie could be beating falsely
accused will drive you insane.
I think the movie wants you to think she did it, but that's my
opinion and opinions are, are your own.
Yeah.
I, I, I saw it as potentially a little more in the other direction,
but it doesn't matter.
It's just, it's, it's whatever your interpretation of the point is, is
the, this person who's harassing her kills herself.
That's the first dark turn of events.
And the way she handles it is so callous where she's like, delete all the
emails that, you know what I mean?
Like, and I'm like, so, so there I am going, God, that's so callous.
And on the other hand, I'm going, well, if a crazy person was harassing you
and they killed themselves and they were going to tie you to this somehow,
and you had a lot to protect, you probably would say, delete the emails.
I have nothing to do with this.
Um, but then things keep unfolding.
There's that whole scene in the beginning where she reprimands the black
student for talking about straight white male composers and she's like, how
would you like to be put in an amazing scene that seems incredible and it's
challenging, it's a challenging scene because you're like, I don't know
where to feel right now, but, um, she gets in trouble for that.
Then the, then the meat or that comes out.
The me too thing, there's a, there's the dominoes fall, but they fall slowly.
Uh, and they're interesting about that.
Now that you're out, now that you kind of got me thinking, maybe she didn't.
Um, is that what she was saying in that encounter with the black
student was so inflammatory, especially in this day and age where the movie is
set, um, and the guy leaves that angry and everything else, but the tick
tock that gets her in trouble is heavily edited to make it worse than it was.
That's it.
That's an interesting aspect of that because you could have just shown
it and had to be just as effective.
If you notice too, she's arguing with him about him labeling
somebody, reducing their label.
Right.
And then when he leaves, he goes, you're a fucking bitch.
Yeah.
So they do a, they do a misogynistic or chauvinistic insult to a woman.
I was like, that's very smart writing.
It makes you, it undercuts that guy's argument.
Now they just do a lot of that in the movie where you're like, fuck,
I don't know how to feel the assistant that eventually betrays her.
Uh, and well, I mean, it hard to say betrays when, when she's
responding to years of betrayal.
And, and I think into that sexual misconduct there too, but that's
what I'm saying she betrays her.
Why does she betray her?
Because she doesn't get the seat for the solo in the orchestra.
Exactly.
She's willing to put up, she's willing to put up with this monster
being an awful to her, um, because she thinks the end game is a better job.
As soon as that job's taken away, it's like, all right, bitch, you're going down.
And is that right?
No, because this woman wouldn't have killed herself if you had come
out and said what you're seeing earlier.
And the hero of the movie, you're like, well, you were kind of fucked up here too.
Um, yeah, I, I, I was fascinated by it when you texted me at the beginning
that you were like, I'm super bored by this, probably during that opening
Kate Blanchett interview, which I get, I was like, knowing the conversations
that Joe and I have had about cancel culture and all that, I really think
this is the definitive movie about it that has been made so far, and I was
hoping you'd come around and like it.
I figured you would.
I did.
Well, and that's the other thing, the other brilliant thing
with the assistant storyline.
The assistant comes in crying in that scene and goes, I just want to be held.
And Kate Blanchett says, now is not, this is not the time or the place.
And so initially you go, she's had a relationship with this woman, but then
you go, no, wait a minute, maybe this woman is someone who comes apart
emotionally at work and she's like, I'm tired of dealing with this.
Stop doing that.
And then on top of it, Kate Blanchett does break her own
rule and comforts her.
Right.
You're like, fuck man, I don't, I don't know.
And then it starts to, it's, it's, it's a, it's a strange commentary on like,
for lack of a better example, the Harvey Weinstein thing where you're going.
Oh, she's such a bad person.
And, and, and you knew all these things.
Why didn't you say anything until you absolutely didn't get what you wanted out
of this, like you, like you pointed out.
So there's a lot of that.
She goes to her wife too.
After that, after that exchange you're talking about, she goes to her wife, who
seems like just a lovely woman and a great spouse, but Blanchett goes home and
is so nonchalant while all these accusations are flying around and her wife
is pissed, but the wife is pissed, at least at first that she didn't tell her
about the allegations, you know, Blanchett's like, this isn't real.
This isn't real.
And she's like, you're a horrible spouse.
You don't communicate with me that you're under investigation.
And it's like, well, true, but what a weird thing to be mad about, you know,
but it also indicates that she doesn't believe that Blanchett did these things
until we see her not letting Cate Blanchett have her daughter.
And then it lets you make the connection.
You don't have to watch all this stuff.
Even in a very long movie, it's very economical with what it shows you, but
that scene where Cate Blanchett goes to pick up her daughter from school and her
wife yanks the daughter away, it's a 10 second scene, but you're like, Oh, their
relationship has really taken a turn here.
So many moments like that.
Also, the only moment in as far as I can remember, the only moment in the entire
movie where they show you that Cate Blanchett definitely is lying is when she
talks about why her face is busted.
Cause she goes into her house, she sees a, what she thinks and is presented to the
viewer as a giant dog moaning.
She runs in fear and trips.
It's a crazy thing to see.
It's a unrealistic thing to see.
It's a supernatural thing to see.
Uh, and so when, so when they make that the one thing that she definitely lies
about, you're like, even there, there's some doubt you're like, well, yeah, she's
lying about that because she doesn't want people to think she's fucking crazy.
What's she going to say?
I saw a giant dog and ran and then fell like, you know, so she goes, I was
attacked and then she goes, don't make a big deal.
I'm fine.
And then I'm like, she's also not soaking up the sympathy of, I got attacked.
She's just being like, keep it moving or whatever.
There's so much in this movie like that.
It's so interesting.
Um, there is, there are several good, no, there are several very convincing theories
online that from a certain point in the movie to throughout the end, like late act
throughout the end of the movie, that it is all a dream sequence because of all of
these things that happen that are not realistic.
There's also, I've seen some very convincing videos about how this is
actually a horror movie, um, and they went through the footage and show in
different scenes, you're like, you see a girl lurking in the background and
you're like, that's the ghost of the woman that killed herself.
Like that's what really freaky, man.
I've read some of that.
That's why I think she did it.
Otherwise you're not getting haunted by ghosts of women.
There are, and I didn't notice it until the second viewing, there are, uh, ghostly
figures and weird women hanging out in the background of a lot of scenes in this movie.
Um, there's also, uh, well, let's talk about the end.
I didn't take that as a dream sequence, but there are dream sequences in the movie.
What did you take of the scene where she's running and she hears really
traumatic women screaming in the park.
She ignores it.
Is that just like a, what is that?
Is it her?
That's another per no, I think it's, she doesn't ignore it.
She runs to try to find it and she can't find it.
But then, you know, winds up leaving.
It's not like she goes to call the police or something.
I, but I think it's, I, well, we don't know.
Right.
But like, and she also, that scene, this is what I mean about like how well this
puts the ambiguity into your head.
She hears a woman screaming and runs to her assistance or at least tries to later.
You see her being callous to a woman who seems to be reaching out for help.
That reinforces the possibility.
This woman has harassed her to the point where she's like, I can't do
anything with a person like this, which is essentially what a therapist
would tell you to do if you're being stalked.
A therapist would say, do not respond in any way to this person.
They're mentally unstable.
They could harm you.
So, and then when her daughter's getting bullied, she goes and, and like passively
threatens the kid that bullies the daughter.
So she's protecting the daughter, but she's also threatening the kid.
Right.
Like it's so, and then you could argue the screams are in her head because she has
guilt and nobody's around when she hears it, you know, and then it's because it's,
it's like the metronome representing time and the clock is ticking and coming
to get her and that's in her head.
Uh, what now let's talk about the neighbor across the hall, the, the woman who
the elderly naked woman we see like screaming and moaning, there's weird
touches in this movie, there's certainly a streamlined two hour version of this
movie, but I'm, I'm really happy with the one we got because there's so much
to chew on and discuss, uh, what it builds to, and this is why I don't think
it's a dream is she goes to an Asian country at the very end of the movie.
I don't think they specified, but I could be wrong.
And we see that after her cancellation, uh, we see her meeting with managers,
like we got to reboot your career and stuff like that.
When we see where she's wound up, which is conducting a gathering of
like a monster hunter group, like almost like a video game type group.
And she just conducting one of those.
It's that it is that it's the,
it's an orchestral rendition of the monster hunter music.
It's a very popular video game franchise.
And that's kind of a wink like monster hunter, get it?
But, but that, that is what it is that they do those all the time.
You know, uh, yeah.
And that, that is her job now, which to somebody like Lydia
tar would be the most embarrassing thing you could ever do.
You also learn when she goes home to lay low for a bit and in a very chilling,
great scene, uh, her brother comes in and goes, Oh, hey, Linda.
Oh, I'm sorry, Lydia.
And we see her, her original certificates that she's received
and her name is Linda tar.
And she added an, uh, an asterisk over the a to make herself look like French.
And like, there's so many little touches.
Um, I saw it in the theater where it was really fun because of
the reactions from the crowd.
Uh, but I watched it last night again at home.
It's on Peacock and I think easily, easily one of the best
movies of last year and Kate Blanchett.
No one's, no one's at that level.
That's, that's a performance for the ages that Kate Blanchett performance.
She's always been great.
Don't get me wrong.
I love her in blue Jasmine, a million different movies.
She is unbelievable in this.
The movie does not work without her or with anyone else.
She's great at playing a waspy, you know, yeah, emotionless, you know, numb woman.
Like she's just, she's very, very good at that.
She's very good at everything, but I think she particularly shines for
whatever reason in a role like that.
She's excellent.
I did.
I loved it.
It's a movie.
I do want to watch a few more times.
I feel like I'll get more out of it every time.
Uh, I'll say you definitely do, especially if you, if you have read
this online shit, when you watch it again, you can kind of like see what people are
talking about, make your own theories.
It's one you want to just read about once you get going, uh, which means
it's a very rich movie.
I mean, the script is amazing.
That, that guy, Todd field who did it did like in the bedroom, I think
was his last movie, which was 2003.
Great movie.
And he did house to sand and fog to bangers.
Like everything he does is huge.
But, but the, the, the time between those two movies and this is over a decade.
And I know he's been attached to things and fallen out, but I just feel
like this guy is a perfectionist.
This script is so interesting.
Like, um, there are scenes that on a first viewing, you're like, okay, in a
three hour movie, do we need that scene?
But when you watch it again, you're like, yeah, like that, that adds to it so much.
My favorite scene is one that really doesn't advance the plot.
I guess you could say, but it's when she goes and meets that old British, uh,
well, he's a British actor.
I don't know if he's, I don't think he's British.
The guy from he's the guy he is.
He's the guy from he's the, he's Donovan from last crusade.
It's the same actor that plays in from, I always get excited
when he pops up and things.
Uh, and he was on Game of Thrones for awhile, but that scene with him.
Where he is sitting and going through, uh, so she sits down and is like, Hey,
did you ever, she's trying to feel them out.
Did you ever have any weird allegations when you were a conductor before the
senses is out of her mouth?
He's like, did somebody say something about me?
It's so clear in that moment that this guy has harassed a lot of
young women in his day.
And then when he starts mentioning the other composers, now, I don't know
anything about classical music.
I Googled each of these composers.
He mentioned where he's like, Oh, it's like what happened with
Rachmaninoff or whatever.
So I looked up each of those people.
He mentioned where he's like, that guy got falsely accused too.
And when you look up the names, the one guy was from like the seventies and he
had raped dozens of men, like 16 year olds, he would bring them in, say, I'm
going to be your, uh, your coach and guide you through and then fuck them.
There's all these reports.
The one guy was like 20 and he goes, I feel really weird about what happened
last time I'm not gay.
Uh, I do want to keep working with you, but not in the same capacity that
we've been doing with this sexual aspect.
And he goes, all right, you're out.
Leave fired him.
The guy went on to become one of the most notable classical musicians alive.
So it is the tar story.
They did their research.
Um, and that, that scene is so fascinating to me.
This guy talking about all these people who also got a bum deal and everybody
he's referencing was a horrific monster, just like him and just like,
in my opinion, Lydia tar.
I didn't, it's funny.
I didn't, I didn't take that.
I mean, he, it might've been, but I didn't take that.
He was guilty.
I took it as he was saying, cause he says being accused is just as
good as being guilty these days.
And I was like, but, but I think he did shit.
His reaction is blowing up reaction when she just mentions it.
I was like, that's all I need to know.
I think, I think as, and here's the thing.
I think if, if, if he is being painted as more guilty than not, I think that
adds even more ambiguity to her.
Because it's like now, now there's a contrast between the two of them.
Yeah.
And she almost too, her reaction to him is almost like, you're not comparing
sexual harassment to Hitler, you know?
And he's like, it's the same thing.
God damn it.
You know, or whatever, you know, like that, by the way, Todd fields, three movies,
Todd field, you may know from eyes wide shut.
He plays the guy that, uh, bartends that Tom Cruise, yeah.
At the orgy.
Yeah.
Or that gives him the, the, uh, the address of the orgy.
Three movies, three feature films in the bedroom.
Grand slam, little children, grand slam, tar grand slam.
The guy, this is what I mean.
2001, did he not do house of sin and fog?
Am I wrong?
No, no.
Okay, sorry.
He did these three 2001, 2006, 2022.
Here's a guy that's like, I am doing what I do and when it is going to happen,
it's going to happen and that's what the fuck it is.
And three of his movies, multiple Oscar nominations for each movie.
He's got, I mean, Scorsese anytime they talk to him these days, he raves
about tar for five minutes.
It's awesome.
Like, um, and I guarantee at some point between 2006 and 2022, Todd field was
like, I'm a failure.
What the fuck am I doing?
I had a great career going on and now it's been 12 years, you know,
this is, this is another way to have a career in this business.
I don't have the stomach for it to, to write, you know, one perfect thing every
10 years and then not worry about not working the rest of the time.
I don't have that, that spirit, but I'm sure thankful for people who do.
I think, um, I think this movie is incredible.
I really do.
I love that.
It reminded me of a lot of great movies like this, like Oleana, David
Manhattan's movie about sexual harassment.
Doubt didn't occur to me until you said it, but that's a perfect comparison.
Um, and you know, I guess my only advice to you would be for like a two hour, 45
minute movie, uh, it, you can't be on your phone, you know, I'm so glad I saw it in
the theater first.
It's one of those where you just have to be looking at it and paying attention.
Or I imagine it would seem kind of boring to you because a lot of it is just in the
way people are acting and reacting, but I realize once I got past it and now it's
these three scenes in the beginning, it's three scenes back to back to back of three
conversation she's having that go like 10 minutes.
And I was just like, Jesus Christ, is this going to be one of these?
Like, like, uh, like jobs where it's just like, or, you know, whatever, not the
Ashton Kutcher one, the other one where it's like, it's just them walking around
and talking about what is transpired.
I'm like, this is, and then once I got past it, now I see like, oh no, that's,
that's showing you how on her own terms, her entire life is at this point.
People sit and entertain every fucking word she's saying.
And sure enough, every one of these people turns on her when the shit goes down.
Uh, so anyway, there's a million great moments of that, you know, like, uh,
luckily I've never had to be an assistant to a monster, but pretty much everyone I
know out here has.
And one of my favorite little moments is when the assistant who does everything
for this woman, everything she comes, a tar comes into her office and she's
like, where's my matcha?
And the girl's like, oh, I'm sorry.
Then Blanchette like goes to the gym.
She comes back and the girl's like, oh, I got you your matcha.
And she's like, I don't want it.
But what she wanted was to assert dominance in that moment.
No, go get me my matcha.
But she didn't even want it.
That's her in a nutshell.
Um, I loved it.
I loved it.
And the reason I think she did it is because she reacts the way all these
people do that, that get caught.
Um, but you can have your own theories and what a great experience at a time
where there's very little movies that, that inspire discussion.
Um, it's the kind of movie where you'll definitely have a discussion afterwards.
I love it.
Hogs are way up for tar folks.
This is good stuff.
When the hogs are up, we'll see you next time for an episode, five movies
that make us cry every time.
Pat's going to do five.
I'm going to do five in the meantime, Jotarosa comedy at Gmail.
I'm sorry, at a Instagram and Twitter and all that stuff.
Uh, I'm on the road.
Of course I got new Orleans, uh, Baton Rouge and Lafayette coming up.
And then South by Southwest all happening in March, go to Jotarosa
info .com for tickets and showtimes.
Also, uh, you'll see any other upcoming shows that are happening.
Uh, I'm a, I'll be back in March 23rd or 22nd at the crane theater with the
new hour, uh, here in New York city.
And there's a ton of other stuff and, uh, come down to Julie roses when you can
open seven days a week, you know, the drill.
I am the Patrick Walsh Twitter and Instagram and frequently the miss Pat
show season three, unquestionably in my opinion, the best and funniest
multi -cam on television, probably the only funny multi -cam on television
unless I've missed something.
Um, this was a genuinely funny show that tackles genuine issues from all sides.
I love working on it.
I love watching it.
I love miss Pat and the new season, season three premieres today, February
23rd on BET plus, uh, you can get the app for, I want to say a dollar 99 for
three months or something like that and catch up, um, because frankly, I
don't know what else the BET plus app has to offer, but, um, check out the
miss Pat show if you can, or if you want to, this is a great season.
Thank you everybody.
We'll be back.
We'll see you next time and we'll see you in hell.