Summer is here, and Bed MDM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer, or check out our
exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz, only available at Bed MDM
Casino.
Spend on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 Fortunes, Mystery of the Lamp, Raken
Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from Anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand.
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action.
Bet MGM game sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 Plus to Waiter, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and West Virginia
only.
Games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as normal, durable site credit slash bonus bets unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
Gambling problem, called 1 -800 -Gamber.
Say hello to the next generation of Zendesk AI agents, built to deliver resolutions for
everyone.
Lulled by over 10 ,000 companies, Zendesk AI agents easily deploy in minutes to resolve 30 %
of interactions instantly.
That's the Zendesk AI effect.
Find out more at Zendesk .com
Hey, hi, how you doing everybody? It's another edition of We'll see you and hell the podcast part of the Fangoria podcast network
You want some info about this network? You want to know about other shows?
You want to know about following this show and finding
in past episodes of our show or all the other shows.
Well, then you go visit fangoria .com.
All right, how many times do I have to tell you?
Very confrontational start to the podcast.
We didn't check our levels, are we okay?
Yeah, I checked them.
I was doing it on the fly.
No, we checked them.
Remember when I said give me a level
and I checked it.
I actually don't remember which is very disturbing to me.
It is disturbing, especially as we sit here
at three to a clock with giant screw drivers in front of us.
We're going to a wedding baby, the great Jamie Lee, the great Dan Black.
Congratulations to you.
I know you're not listening, but congratulations to you.
We do have to drive an hour.
Yeah.
Well, our friend Adam Stein, who's also a writer, will be showing up soon, not to be a guest,
but he's just meeting me and pad at my apartment so we can go to this wedding together.
And I think we're all just kind of banking on Stein, jumping into the driver's seat.
unless, of course, he's been drinking, well, then he shouldn't be driving here.
Shouldn't. That's a good point. That's a good point. Um, Joe, it's good to see
is Joe's dress like one of the mad men today, or dolled up my granddad's
tie clip. Uh, I thought that was your granddad's. I remember it from the war when
the two met. Yeah. Yeah. I was going to get dolled up as well. And then I have a
new cat who has caused me zero problems in like two months and then I left a
black suit sitting on the couch white cat so it was a bit of a stress for
morning but it's fine it's a beautiful cat the other day we got it a cat
nip carrot and it was just like packed with cat nip and it's done that way so it'll
like ease it out over time but the cat immediately is just biting into it and
chewing on it and absorb like it would be like smoking 10 joints to your eye
Right, right, right. This cat was spasming the fuck out. It jumped completely over my couch in a single bound
Oh, I like that. It was crazy. I was just like I watched it for like an hour and a half having the best time of my life
As it twitched like some sort of method. It was great. What is catnip? It's basically weed for cats
No, I know that but I mean what is it the substance? I don't know
Root or spice maybe but they get super high and then just like your eye
They fall into a deep slumber the second it wears off. Oh, it's really great
I wanted to say that's what I was doing on my phone here. Excuse me
Ken Hanley who gets this podcast going up on the air helps us out. He's our executive producer. Great man
He has written a book and I've been wanting to mention this for several weeks. It's called the eye in evil
I ordered mine on Amazon yesterday. It has been out for a while. I'm ashamed of how long it took me to get it
but I urge you to check it out. I'm giving you a preliminary recommendation because he's a hilarious
great dude who knows a shit and I'm sure after I read it I will give you a sincere recommendation.
Ken is great. I highly recommend the book myself. Yeah. It's a nice piece of work. All right,
great. And I'm glad that you're getting a copy of it. Yeah. Sorry, I got distracted. Somebody drove
up into my driveway, not my driveway, the building's driveway here. But Ken is a great
man of fangoria. Ken has blessed me coming very soon. I think I'm allowed to announce this. I'm going to be
I've been writing these short fiction, horror, quirky, whatever stories for quite some
time.
Now Ken's going to start publishing them on the site.
That's awesome.
So, you're also announcing it to me, your dear friend.
Yeah.
So coming soon, the column's going to be called Friction Files and it's going to be fictional
short stories that I've been writing for the last couple of years.
They don't have any sex.
it's a lot of a person dealing with a situation that's otherworldly, if you will.
Sure, it's a lot of one -on -one.
Maybe when I have sex, it's always out of this world.
But I don't know, you know, who knows?
Maybe I'll get, you know, maybe one of these stories will be like an erotic kind of thing.
Sure.
Who knows.
But they'll be coming soon.
So keep your eye out for that.
And by Ken's book, if you haven't bought it.
And on with the show, Pat, for Christ's sakes today, today's sin is pride.
Joe and I have said, this is like the second season of the podcast and we're doing the seven deadly sins.
Pride is one, I know we all suffer with basically just being too proud.
There's no, I don't know what another word to say.
They know what pride means, Pat.
You don't have to, you know, to admit something or to admit default or to admit defeat.
We don't apologize to some myth that you don't really know the definition of the word that will no I do
I don't know why I'm explaining pride to them. I don't know either. We've that's a new thing
This is never been a part of this. No, it is. We explain softly explain wrath
Not in this fashion. We discussed your your singing as if they've never heard of this concept before
But good the end. It's fine. I don't you know, I don't dislike it
I was interested in doing the topic of pride today because I
I want it to just completely bail on our seven sins agreement, yeah, the second season and just go
Right back into phone movie discussion episodes. Yeah, it just hasn't been before we start
Well, this is the seventh one. This is pride
We'll do a little bit about how like I'm too proud and we got to go change the format
No, I want to change it. We can do whatever we want said Joe. This is the fifth sin
We're not on second. Which one have which ones do we miss?
We didn't do lust yet. We did lust didn't we didn't do greed? Oh greed
We didn't do envy.
I think green envy are the two left.
I think so.
Ooh, envy's gonna be a juicy one.
Envy, I might just have to sit out, frankly.
Envy, the Envy episode will just be us playing a podcast
episode of somebody else's podcast
that has way more listeners or something.
And is garbage.
My envy really is inseparable from my anger
and it's not even envy.
It's more discussed I would have to treat I would have to approach it more as like envy like I envy somebody's talent because usually
I'm disgusted that somebody untalented is making it which is not really envy, but in a way it is
I'd like to shoehorn that right into envy. I mean, I that's yeah, let's not get off on the end
No, maybe we should have done anything clearly work chopping at the bit
Let's save that one for last. Okay. We'll have something to look forward to pride
I mean are you a guy who has a problem apologizing to people is one aspect?
Well, you know, I mean, you've seen me in action.
I think one of my most falsely proud moments was a couple years back, we were at some kind
of outdoor summer picnic.
I was on a second date maybe with a girl, beautiful girl, great girl.
She took issue with some joke I made about something and I just wouldn't let that one go.
I just I was I chose to instead of
Engage with her and just squash it and have a nice time to instead spend my time across the yard from her
With Pat and Camille Nangeani
Screaming in their faces about how out of line. I thought the girl was yeah for her for judging one of my jokes
I was sitting with Camille and
You know Camille's like hey, who's the girl Joe broad? I'm like, oh, you know, she's really nice. I just matter seems cool
where are they? And we look over and you're like, now you listen here.
Like over the hot dogs on a beautiful summer afternoon.
We were just like, well, I guess that's over and soon enough it was.
Yeah, we made it one or two more dates after that, believe it or not.
Yeah, but yeah, that didn't last that long.
Yeah, she was a nice girl, though.
I mean, so in your definition, pride is basically not backing down on something.
me because me I'm big on just throwing my hands up and being like whatever the fuck I don't care
anymore about any of that shit. You will not back down on uncertain things and I admire it. Well I'm
better I'm better at I'm better at it now than I was yeah you know a few years out here has
helped quite a bit but you know I have my moments where it gets away from me right put it that way
right but yeah I would say my my my fault with pride is usually something in the ego department that
is making me think, I'm so right, I have to keep going. I have to convince these people
that I am right. Yeah, sure. You know, yesterday, I've been working on my buddy, Moshikashir's
pilot. And we were having a discussion about, what the hell are we talking about? Donahue.
you. The Donahue show. And I said, Donahue establishes would come out and have a discussion
and then he would go into the audience. And Moshe said, no, Donahue, he's in the audience
the whole time. And I said, no, you're wrong. And we watched a video to settle the disagreement.
I was, of course, right. And I stood up. And I mean, I was almost parading around the room.
I felt so good. And Moshe said, I don't like this. And I said, what? And he goes, you being
right I don't like it at all but I couldn't I couldn't it is for some reason really exhilarating
I guess because I'm so frequently wrong when I'm able to just really shove something
in someone's face like like you're dick or no just like what you're saying yeah I know
I know fuck you you'll run into a place just then yeah no I did you went off somewhere
where what what happened there nothing I was thinking back previous times previous
great times I've been writing throughout history. Phil Hartman had an amazing
Phil Donahue that I can't really separate from the real deal at this point.
Phil Hartman's, Phil Donahue was great my favorite Phil Donahue impersonator though
was Darryl Hammond who would do Donahue in different languages which oh yeah
Yeah, yeah, absolutely, yeah, I have seen him do that.
He killed me, yeah, it killed me.
I was thinking the other day, I guess Philharmon would be 65,
something like that.
Like, can you imagine just going to any movie
and maybe he's got 10 lines in it still in the show.
Just hits a brand slam.
Like he's in almost, he'd be in almost every comedy
in some small supporting role.
Yeah, he'd be the guy that shows up
at the end of the Will Farrell movie
in like the great cameo.
Yeah, you think though, but I'll tell you this,
My money would have been on John Love, it's me and that guy too and in love it's sure that guy sure. Yeah, I mean that this
crashing Sean writing for as a very funny line. Just it's imagining John Love, it's it's speculating that he's very unhappy right in his
Life which I'm sure he is but just imagining him up in his
Castle overlooking Burbank where his comedy club is playing the pipe organ which seems like exactly what I would imagine John Love
Then I saw online they had that video where he was allegedly fucking that
Victoria secret model that was like a prank, but I was like why would this
Victoria secret model even know John Lovitz to do this prank he's been out
of the game for so long he's in yeah what was that video it was an April
Fools day prank but I'm like why would they pick love it like the kids who
would be enjoying this prank don't know John Lovitz I guess you're right he's
He's just a joke now.
Well, maybe he did the prank himself.
That could be.
But John Lovitz contacting the Victoria Secret people
and they're like, yeah, we'll send up one of our girls.
Well, I don't think they have exclusive rights, right?
I mean, he could have just found a model, right?
He probably is famous.
Ask David Spade to look through his phone.
Call somebody up.
You know, speaking of Spade,
I think that new Spade and Sandler movie
actually looks pretty funny.
I haven't said that for a long time
about a Sandler movie.
No.
But I love David Spade, and I'm excited to see him in anything and
Loves Bay had love love. It's love. It's was that like in the wedding singer
I thought he was gonna be playing those parts forever like when he comes out from behind that curtain. It's it's magical
What does he say as he's doing ladies night, right? Yeah, and then yeah, but they do that. They do a gimmick where he
floats backwards
Magically it like as he's cackling through the back through the curtain. Yeah, it's really great. It's
It's the funniest part of the movie and I wish I could remember exactly what he says
But it's something like it's all coming together something creepy like that. Yeah, he's like an evil mastermind
Yeah, he's great. He's great in that movie lost and found with David Spade and Arty Wang. Yes, he's great in league of their own
Man, he stole that movie out of from under Tom Hanks almost. I don't agree with that. He's not a cup
He's not a comedic part in me league of their own, is he? You see how that yeah remember that he goes you see how it works is the
train moves, not the station.
He only does his wise crash.
For some reason, I remember him
he's talking to that real homely girl.
And he keeps like breaking her balls.
That's very fun.
Uh, Tom Hanks is, he's amazing.
I mean, no pun intended.
He hits a home run in that film.
I mean, I'd say a grand slam.
It's, it's amazing.
I mean, one of the great lines of all time
is did anybody ever tell you you look like a little penis
with a hat on it?
I mean, he delivers it.
That's the first time he ever played
like a dark character. That was pre -Philodelphia. Yeah. That was like pre -Far's gump. That was
before any of the time. Well, Philadelphia wasn't necessarily a dark character,
drove me because he was gay. No, no. Is that dark? That's not what I'm saying, because he was dying.
A man living his life. A man convicted of dark dying. Huh. Was this what I'm saying? All right.
Dating Antonio Banderas in Philadelphia. Yes. They never even kiss. And I always thought that
that should have been tied into the Desperado franchise somehow maybe that's I always like to watch
Philadelphia as a prequel sure Desperado like that's what sent him on that journey honestly that's
that's a stronger movie by far his lover dies of AIDS and he takes to the three I watched that
anyway have you seen anything I saw a movie that I know that you would love I wish I had seen it
with you called green room. Jesse Popper, dear friend last night was singing its praises.
It's fantastic. It's fantastic. I hope he didn't tell you too much, but I wouldn't even
say anything. It's up in the little field of three. I'll see it. I'll go see it. I want
to see it. I know the plot of the movie from the trailer, but you know, that's all I know.
And I told me one detail that I wish she hadn't told me. Yeah. But it also isn't pivotal.
He just was telling me how like they realized the skinheads are not like the cool kinds of skinheads that they're like the Nazi skinheads
Oh, that's I mean that's immediate. That's not real. Yeah, but just as a fan of punk music
I would have found that that tiny twist very cool. Sure. Oh, that's that's pretty good. Yeah, I mean at at I always like the more
Popier punk shit to be honest and I also love like X and stuff which is actually popier X Ramones
But never the stuff in this movie with like the cookie monster singing and shit like that. I don't like but
You do and you'll probably appreciate it even more than I did. Uh, I got to tell you Pat. I'm almost to the bottom of this class
Pat picked up a
Organic jug I watched her squeeze organic aren't you fresh squeeze? I watched them squeeze it $10
It was $10 I paid for so this is right out of the fucking yeah, this is right out of the fucking fruit
That's what I think of you Joe. Thank you. He shows up with two bottles of vodka fresh
squeeze jug of orange juice. And I'm to the bottom of my glass already. This is delicious. I know.
Or I got a problem. Probably a little, a little of A, little of B, little of A, little of B,
little of C, what do you get? That's D time. That's a song I just made up.
Folks, what are you most proud of? You never said your pride thing. Well most proud of is different.
Well, you know what I mean because that's not a sin pride. Yeah, what's your most pride -ish thing?
That's a word. I
Guess I have a hard time saying I'm sorry as well till after the fact
Sure, I always do but I am the kind of guy who like if I feel I'm right in an issue
It's not changing. It doesn't change for like five years. I don't even know if that's a bad thing
But like there are people, you know, a couple of people out there in the world who I know think that I wronged them in some way or whatever
And I'm always when I look back on it like I don't think so and maybe I should see it a little more from their point of view
And in some cases I have in most cases I don't some of that stubborn some of that's just you don't always have to admit the other person
Is right it took me a while to learn that as well because I always had to like defer to my dad and go
Well, yeah, I guess you are right even though he wasn't and I resented that so much that it made me very prideful
To this day. So sometimes I'm gonna fight with my girlfriend. I'll let it go on for three days and then go
Oh, wait, you're being an idiot and apologize. I wish I could do that immediately
But sometimes I'll let it simmer. I've gotten way better at that over the years. Probably
200 % better since the relationship began but I used to be kind of a simmerer
Where I would just kind of sit and be quiet sure and what's the matter nothing
What's the matter nothing and then I realized I was becoming my dad so I stopped doing that my life changed for the better
That's a real let's like a wife move too a lot of guys wives. They say that yeah, wives do that a lot
Yeah, my girlfriend is a great communicator
And I am not so we had to kind of work it out
But she's always like let's fix it. Let's fix it. Let's fix it. Let's fix it and we do but I'm a big fan of talking annoyed by it
Sure, but admittedly, you know to a fault. I I want to talk it out and
And there's something about when somebody walks out of the room on me.
I can't handle it.
You know, if somebody in the middle of an argument goes, I'm done.
I'm done.
Bye.
Yeah.
It's inferior.
It's the most disrespected I ever feel ever.
Yeah.
No, I agree.
And then generally, I'll follow the person.
But already I can just feel my temper rising and I have to do that.
Oh, you'll walk after the person.
I will walk.
All right, you know, because it's such a
Aggressive move especially in a relationship if someone walks out of the room and you just sit there
Right, it's almost more aggressive than the walk out, but I'm never going in like hey, sorry
It's always like don't walk out before we're done with the discussion. Yeah, it feels shitty doesn't it? Yeah, yeah, yeah
It feels real shitty, but then I'll do it too. I we I tend to have
You know, it's always a once a month thing when you live with somebody. They'll be a little row
But it always tends to be I'm about to go down stairs and something will come up and I'll wind up like
One foot on the stairs one foot up about four different times during the argument
I'll go I throw my hands up and start to walk down the stairs right then show you're just gonna walk away and then up
The stairs I go we resume the discussion something else hits me the wrong way back down. I go right
So I up and down as infuriating as it is when someone does it to me. I do it as well
You know what I you know what I always say Pat may all your ups and downs be between the sheets, you know
Yeah, that's a good way to live your life. I agree with that. I
Don't know I'm I fear that I'm past a point of being able to coexist with another human being. Yeah, I'm 38 at this point
I haven't had a roommate in a
solid ten years
You haven't had any sort of tangible relationship in about ten years me. Yeah, yeah
Nine months was my longest relationship. That's of all time of all time. That's crazy to me. Yeah
Well, it's crazy to me in certain ways, but then some some other people go well that's great because then you'll
When you meet the one it did you'll know right, but who knows that maybe
Do you think like just talking now pride seems like kind of like being a little bitch once in a while
Do you think it deserves to be up there with your murders here?
You're your other sins like why why is pride up there with the seven dead legs? They were talking about mind
I've got confused. I thought you were saying that I've murdered in my other sins and I'm a little bitch
That's that's all I heard. I do think you're a little bitch. Sure. I do know you've murdered
I would never have talked about that on the podcast
I'm just saying I've murdered it's
audience is
It's strange that these are the seven things, you know
That these are the worst thing
And they also I think Shakespeare says pride comes before the fall pride go with pride go okay Joe same thing
But like it I guess that means yeah, you know what there is a lot of truth to that
You know if you're always talking about how fucking great you are you're about to get taken down a
Well, I think the reason pride is in the big seven is because it's like what leads to war sure
You know and things that it leads to in your dick around yeah physical violence and right and murder and
I mean, think about it, crimes of passion, it's, it's, she cheated on me, so now I have
to kill them.
Yeah.
That's pride.
Uh, it's also wrath.
It is.
Maybe a little lust.
Who knows?
Blood lust.
For sure.
So, you know, I don't, I don't feel that pride is a big thing in my life because I, I have
a lot of humility.
I feel like I'm, I'm sort of down on myself, um, I'm confident where I need to be.
but I'll tell you, your friends frequently talk about it.
We'd like you to have a little more pride for yourself.
We find the way you've been conducting yourself
is almost off -putting.
That's fair.
Yeah, no, I hear you.
It is a weird thing where I hear you.
I have that self -esteem shittiness, too,
where you beat yourself up and we're certainly not the guys
that go like, hey, we're going to be the center of attention.
Yeah, so can you still be as faulty when it comes to pride as I don't know?
I have so much hatred for bragging and I'm I'm always so much on the lookout for it
I don't think I could ever really do it myself
I'll tell you where I'm loudmouth is when I'm in a writer's room.
Sure.
Cause I get an idea in my head and I think I just think it's the right idea.
Yeah.
Well we talked about that a little bit earlier.
Yeah, yeah.
No, I know.
But I'm just saying like not to be repetitive.
But like it's it's
As we're talking about this. I'm realizing that really is a place that sets me off
But I have learned to be better about it. Yeah, I used to I used to do that myself. It's just like
You know what I'm learning more and more about these writers rooms is the person in charge wants to do what they want to do and almost anything you say
Can't change their mind right, you know like it's not something that endears you to the other writers if you won't back down on something
Doesn't mean you should always be like,
eh, I don't care what we do,
because that's annoying too.
But if you've said something three times,
like there's always somebody,
and maybe you're this person,
I haven't been in a riser with it.
Who will pitch something?
You get maybe one time, 20 minutes later to go like,
look, I hate to keep pitching this, but blah, blah, blah.
You get one time to do that.
A lot of times it's like, you're right,
that is a good idea.
But you don't get to go a third and fourth time.
No, I try to, if the showrunner says no, it's no.
No, I go to yeah, I go maybe to yeah, you know, and then after two I tap out and then if the person circles back to me
Because they're stumped and goes well, what do you think and I'll go I don't want to be annoying or repetitive
But I'm telling you I think the thing I said is the best idea yeah, you know, I'll say it very passively at that point
Yeah, a lot of times they'll go along with it my my boss is big on you'll pitch on the tome and I'll go no
Oh, like you just mirrored a diaper on his face and used diaper and then he'll take a step away and then turn back and go
What was the exact wording again really which I like and actually you know we've had we've had our differences
But that's a good sign of non -pride, you know
That's a sign of a guy who is a willing he'll never say I'm sorry, or I reconsidered or something, but he'll turn around and go
Yeah, what was it one more time after he's just screamed in your face jokes cometh after the pride
Yeah, that's how you can spend that Shakespeare thing around for that situation. You cut now here's my problem Pat
And this is a problem we've discussed on this podcast before go on we're drinking those delicious screwdrivers
Surely or I'm now have cracked a beer open. Yeah, we're getting we're planning on breezing into this wedding
very drum
Here's my point. I don't want to go to the wedding anymore
Now I just want to sit here and drink with you. Well, that's slow. I don't know what it is with you and me together
But I get one drink in me when I'm around you and I say this is a guy you spend the afternoon with yeah
I don't need the other
world
Maybe
Maybe we make love maybe we don't I'm just talking you mean a plate of nachos at some point maybe like patio
Well, you know and I before when I told you you were that friend for me on this podcast you screened me for several minutes
But I think we are that kind of enabler and a fun way for
and for each other.
What I worry about is that we're always on this podcast
and it'll be like summer on a Tuesday night,
summer on a Sunday morning.
And it's always like we just cracked open a beer,
we're drinking screw drivers, whatever.
Folks, just so you know, Joe does enable my drinking
and I think I his, we don't drink every day of the week.
But when we get together for a podcast,
a little social lubricant helps you out.
The issue is we never can really stop, never have a beer and then I go to the library and Joe goes to the science center we have.
That's not true. I go pissed to the science center quite frequently and the scientists don't like that.
No, they don't. They really don't like it. When I go when I start peeing in the beakers, causing the foam, what is causing this reaction? Like what are you drinking?
Yeah
No, we need friends like that too many people are like I don't know if I want to drink tonight
We're not those people. I just don't understand and again
We've talked about this. We don't understand this actually does kind of tie into pride
I don't if you don't drink I think you're stupid. I
Know I completely stupid idiot. I completely unless you had a problem and you had to stop because you were out of control
Right. Fine. I get that. But if you just don't drink, I just think you're a stupid dumb idiot. Yeah. Here are the reasons to stop you're always fighting with your girlfriend while you're drunk or something. You're always blacking out.
You're angry or there's blood on your dick again. You don't know where it came from. Yeah, there's a sometimes it's your blood which when it comes to the dick is more disturbing.
There's a dead woman in your bed Barton Fink style and you don't know how she got there. Right.
right. Uh, or, you know, other than the night was hot for six months. That's a
throw them from the train writer show. Uh, DUI, you know, uh, I'll go as far as to
say, DUI isn't, I don't have itself. It's not a, I've never had one. Not strong enough
reason to stop. You might have just had it off night. Now, if you have repeat DUIs
that yeah, I absolutely would stop. Now, I have, I have friends because you know, DUI
not something people will admit I've never had one a couple nights perhaps I
should have I'm not proud of but like I got a buddy who if you're like you're at
the corner of of first and Western and you want to go to second and Western
he'll get a cab like he is the most paranoid person in the world and then
eventually I you know you ask him for a friend of a friend and they're like
yeah it's a deal a couple years back I would be the same way I would be so
embarrassed that I think I it would sober me up I would have no shame to
admit to it. I mean, I'd be embarrassed in the moment and, you know, the fact that you're spending $10 ,000
Sure, whatever to I mean, there's no better ad, you know, as far as outside of this is your brain on drugs with the eggs.
There's no better ad than the guy with the breathalyzer in his mouth and it says you just blew $10 ,000. Yeah.
Everyone sees that thing once and you're like, I get it. Yeah. I'm not going to drink and dry. That's up there. That's up there with Wendy's marketing
as far as I'm concerned. And when this does some fine marketing. Yeah. Yeah. I mean, where's the beef?
Who, who, who doesn't remember? Yeah. But yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Who, you just blew $10 ,000. I was never
a big fan of the fried egg one. No. With the drugs. Now you're saying you think it was a great ad.
I did. I mean, because, you know, it was probably a little over the top. But in those days,
the Nancy Reagan days, they're trying to scare you. Like I actually thought that smoking a joint
it would cause my brain to fry.
And it probably kept me off drugs for many years.
Yeah, I think of all those good times you missed out on.
No, I'm glad.
I started at the right time.
I like to think that now that I enjoy some weed here and there,
I like to think that starting drinking and drugs and et cetera
when I was in my 20s made sure that I didn't destroy my brain.
It seems like starting them before your brain is developed
cannot be good.
I agree with that.
I think I started a little later
and that was probably good in certain ways.
There's the other side of me though that goes,
but now you're not gonna have it out of your system
when you're 60.
Sure.
Cause I know people that went batshit
from like 12, 29.
And now they're just like, no, I get up, I go to bed,
I take care of my kid, but they're out of the woods on it.
Right, I feel nowhere near ready to stop any of this.
Yeah, you know, I don't feel ready to stop either,
but I feel like a kid being thrown into the mix
would make me feel completely fine with stopping.
Let me rephrase what I was saying.
I don't want to have a kid so I don't have to stop.
Sure.
Yeah, that makes sense.
You have a child spending, the idea of spending time
with a child versus going out with my buddies,
sickens and depresses me.
I just don't, there's just no part of it
that seems more appealing.
You know, ideally you're in the kind of marriage
where once a week you can go out and get drunk
and she takes care of the kid and once a week
She can go out and get drunk and you take care of the kid. I don't know why that's so complicated for people to understand
Because everybody's an idiot. They really are people will be like, well, you know, I have a kid now
So obviously I don't do anything fun ever
Doesn't have to be like that and if you're married to a woman who's like we have a kid now
So you have to be home every night of the week by my side when the baby goes to bed at what six?
I mean if I if my wife wanted to go out and party I
I put the kid to bed at 6. I got the little baby monitor. I'm watching movies all night
I'm doing nothing different than I would if I didn't have a kid. Yeah, you can do it with ease
But everybody's like, oh, I got to be home at 4 because the baby it's stupid. It's stupid. Everything. It's stupid
Make it work. Make it work for yourself. I don't I don't want it
I want no parts of it
I'd have to be pretty clear if I were to get married that like I don't want to be silently
Resented if once a week I go drink with my friends and you watch the kid because you know the offer goes back
to you as well. I think the mornings are more the issue than the nights. It's like when
we get up tomorrow and I have to be at work and I think that's where the problem comes
in is the different schedules of the husband and wife. And then the guy saying, well tonight's
a good night for me to hang out. And then the wife saying, well, tomorrow morning's not
a good night. Good morning for me. Right. So that's I think where it starts to get tough.
But I would suck it up. You know, like I think a big part of the reason probably I don't get
hangovers is that if you and I go out and tie one on on a Thursday night Friday morning,
I don't have to be at work till 10 30 11. It's fine. You know, I wake up and I feel fine.
However, if I had to wake up at six, that might be different, but if it's my son in the other room,
I'd pull it together and wake up. I've done much more hungover.
My friend Brian does that. He says frequently, if you can't do the time, don't do the crime.
Yeah, he he will we will have nights where we are out to four or five a .m. in New York. Yeah going after it pretty hard
He's up at six seven a .m. with the kids get him ready for school. I love handcakes. Yeah, they're out the door
He takes a little nap. Yeah, you know like he's he gets it done man. I love it. I don't even know if I'd go to bed
The thing that the thing that would change me I think is if my kid was like
Daddy, why does your breath smell like whiskey or you know something like that might make me
changed my life. But hopefully your kid doesn't know what whiskey smells like. I'd be more concerned
that the kid is that close to your mouth. Well, you don't got to kiss your child. Some inappropriate
thing is happening if your kids just hovering around your mouth all lips like that. I think you
kiss a baby on the lips up till like age five. You're not going to kiss your baby. On the lips. Why
wouldn't you? You're going to kiss the baby up till five. You're going to kiss the kid on the lips.
I remember and maybe I'm opening myself up to a lot of ridicule, but I think I kissed both my parents on the lips till about 10 I
Didn't like it and the dad started to feel real weird, but it's just
I think they didn't know how to I think my dad was probably like my dad wasn't affection enough with me
I'm gonna kiss my kid telling my love him so and then he did it once a year and very affectionate
I still hugging kiss both of them. Yeah, but I don't think the lips were ever in strong play
I eventually you know my mom went much later and I eventually was like this is weird
I was old enough to be like mom
That's enough of the lips right she was like you're right. Okay. Oh cool
That's the relief that that's what's her response because any other response would have been upsetting
I think parents just truly don't know what to do and my parents had me when they were in their early 20s
So it's like they were trying to do their best and you know frankly their best wasn't good enough
But here I am and I have a lot of
the needs and problems and what's the other reason I don't want to have a kid and again
maybe this is pride but I think most people's best isn't good enough absolutely who
of us who amongst us is is is qualified to raise a child I can barely keep my shit together
with this goddamn dog I know I know my cat woke me up at 6 o 'clock this morning and I could
would have choked it to death.
I could have thrown it in the trash
because I, once I'm up, I'm up, and it's out there meowing.
Here's what pisses me off.
I say that a lot on dates, by the way,
when I get, when I get an erection.
I'll go, baby, once I'm up, I'm up.
You gotta take care of it.
But you see this little black shadow through the door.
I have those kind of like misty shower type doors in my house
where like you can see the fuzzy outline of something.
Yeah, that's whole house has a very dressed to kill vibe in it very to palm of a
Yeah, yeah, very cocaine. Yeah, soul tree. You might say soul tree
And you see the outline of the cat like put the little ears and everything and it's so cute that the anger goes away
Pretty quickly, but what it does is it sits outside the door and
Well
And it has food, it doesn't need food, it needs nothing.
Then when you open the door, it runs away at lightning speed.
So it just wants to wake you up and then move on with its life.
It wants nothing else from you but to know that you're awake because it's awake.
And that to me is a really dick move and it's infuriating and it's why people don't like cats
and they're not wrong.
I love the cat for the cuddle time when I'm watching a movie is nice and I like it for
when it takes the cat nip as we discussed earlier and goes crazy right but these
things like also did you know this there's they bury their shit in the
litter box you got to get that out and shake it out but did you know that when
they pee on cat litter I had no idea about this and my girlfriend treated me like I
was a complete idiot for not knowing if they pee on litter it forms into a giant
hardened chunk and then you throw that out it's disgusting so I thought the
The litter just had big chunks in it because it's a bunch of like weird rocks and shit.
It was a Campbell's chunky litter.
She's like, no, all of these giant chunks are where the urine bonds the litter together
and then you know to throw that out.
That's pretty brilliant.
It's an amazing invention but I had no idea.
And you know, my girlfriend's giving me a lot of shit about this.
The fact is I've never had a pet in my life.
Never once.
I had a beta fish died
when I was
Maybe 10 years old my family stood on our back porch and watched a large dog mall my sister for several minutes
We all thought they were playing and having fun. So me and my mom and my dad pointed and laughed as a large dog
Just viciously attacked myself instead of vision of your whole family and that scene in the accused
Jesus Christ laughing thinking she's having a good time and then
Being terribly wrong. That's that's essentially what it was
I it was really really traumatic and sad and we never were able to have a pet again and my sister's still and me to some degree if
They dog, you know, your dog kind of is fine. It's a little dog. If a big dog comes up to me
I I seize up my butthole tenses, right and my sister cannot be around a big dog because of this
Well, there's like a trick to do with that with dogs because you know
There's like the shark trick where it's like a shark's ever coming at you a punching in the nose
Right with a dog you their finger are you suck. It's dick and it'll it'll leave you alone. Is that true?
100 % true
100 % I'm working on a book about dog
Trainings and behaviors right now and that's chapter. I think two it comes pretty pretty soon in the book
I mean, this is your basic stuff. I got bit once
I was at a poker game these dogs are at our feet all night
Having a nice time and I went to walk to the door at two o 'clock when I was done with the game and this dog took a big
Chomp out of my thigh and wouldn't I'm sorry my calf would not let go and blood is pouring out of my pants
It ripped through my pants and the owner comes out and he has his hands in the air and he's like I don't know what to do
I don't know what to do to be fair. These aren't house dogs. Pat Pat plays
With some very city russians down downtown. I
Spoker games my issue was, you know, I've seen the paintings. Why are the dogs not playing poker with us?
as I've led to believe but uh he comes in and somebody yells out and he's very serious
he's like shove a finger in its ass and he'll let go shove a finger in his ass and he'll
let go and this guy's preparing to kind of do it and he's like I don't know what to do
I can't do that.
He's the choice is a man faces in life.
Somebody comes out grabs the dog's back legs lifts them off the ground and the dog unleashes
let's me go and I was like thanks good move and the guy's like I'm glad I didn't have to
to shove a finger in his ass.
But it was terrifying and I had done nothing
to provoke it or even looked at it.
And the guy says to me, it's crazy.
It's a show dog.
It's a dog on the mentalist.
It's a dog that's on CBS's.
That's why he was upset.
It's the mentalist.
And he's like, it's never attacked anybody before.
It made me feel terrible.
Like what am I giving off that make this dog attack me?
But anyway, I told him if I was not a nice person,
and you would owe me probably $200 ,000.
And we'd go to court.
Sure, sure.
Yeah, I don't know how anybody has them.
Run mom and dad's dog gets a little feisty sometimes.
I was like, you guys better be careful
because you know, a dog just has to bite the wrong person
and then it's like you got a lawsuit on your hands.
And you win it every time.
Well, yeah, why did you let your wild animal bite me?
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah, it's a valid question, frankly.
Yeah.
I don't know. I was trying to tie it back into pride for some kind of wrap up and I couldn't
think of anything. I would ever. Whatever. Who cares? You know, it's fine. Yeah. That's pride, folks.
I think we did a yeah, we did a nice job. You won a big ending, but I can't, I don't, you know,
it doesn't always work out like that. No. And you know, I'm not going to do a
men's see it and walk off the stage to silence like I'm making a point. He
does that. He did that on his Comedy Central half hour. If you didn't hate
the guy enough, like to silence his the end is him going him going this whole like
soliloquy about 9 -11. Then he goes he goes sometimes it's not what you think.
Sometimes it's not what you expect. Sometimes a comedian is supposed to end his
show with a big left. Sometimes, sometimes he walks off stage. And I believe I got so
mad that I pissed on my television when I saw it. Immediately short circuit who decided
that he was the one at a fucking comedy special leave that he did and then it was quickly
taken away. Let me get standing ovation. I don't it went over. It was before anybody knew
he was. It was like people were like, woo. Yeah. But you know, anyway, sometimes, sometimes
there's no end to the podcast. Right. But the plugs. I tell you, now I'm doing a little
stand up, which I'm going to talk about now next week in New York. I do stand up occasionally.
You are a stand up. You have shows all the time. When you drive down the street here, there's
billboards for all kinds of specials. Yeah. Do most of them make you so angry. You don't know
what to do with yourself. I wouldn't say most of them, but they're the they're the handful
Where I go fuck you there. I think we should say that for jealousy talk. Yeah, you're right
There's one up by my house that makes me so furious
And it's not even a competition who I'm not a competition with this person, but I'm like how dare you yeah
I'll often say oh fuck you out loud to build words of TV shows. Sure
To be honest, I'm out set me off. I've never seen this show. I don't know who's part of it
I might even have friends that work on it
I don't even know, but it was the four like hot housewife types and they were all putting lipstick on and then the one in the middle was eating a french fry
because she's the crazy one.
And I just, it just, I literally would exclaim go fuck yourself at the world word sometimes when I would drive by it.
Well, that's one of those things that thinks it's being feminist and is actually so terrible for women.
To think that if you eat a french fry, you're the crazy one who doesn't have your life together.
I mean, is this it's just what the hell world are we living in? Follow me on Twitter.
Joe DeRosa comedy.
Patty, I am on Twitter,
my Instagram at the Patrick Walsh.
Pick up Ken's book as we discussed and on Sunday,
May the eighth in New York City,
because I'm going out to New York for a week or so.
UCB East, I will be doing standup with some hilarious comedians,
including two of my favorites. Chris Thayer and David Angelo.
Very nice. This coming dollars. This coming Saturday,
May the 8th or 7th. Saturday is the 7th. This coming
Saturday, May the 7th. Can I kick it? Returns to the nerd
melt showroom. Hip hop meets comedy as usual. We play a lot
of videos and making lots of jokes and things. So come out
and see us for that. Didn't hip hop already meet comedy as
good as it's going to get with a little movie called Disorderly
starting the fat boy. Listen, I love disorderly. I won't have you speak ill of it. I'm not. I watched it
30 times and I was a kid. You've been listening to, we'll see you in
how a presentation of the Fingoria podcast network produced by Thomas DeFail
executive produced by Ken Hanley of Fingoria Entertainment for press opportunities
advertising degrees and information about we'll see you in how a contact Ken is
even as Ken at Fingoria .com. See ya. Thanks.
You