Huff, puff, and spin the house down at Golden Nugget Online Casino!
Right now, new players can deposit just 5 bucks and get 500 total spins on Huff and
more puff!
The slot that's blowing players away!
Download the Golden Nugget Online Casino app and use promo code Nugget1.
That's code Nugget1 to enjoy 50 spins a day for your first 10 days!
All on our players favorite game of the summer!
Now's the time to score daily bonuses and spin for all the bacon on the game everyone's
hoffat about.
At Golden Nugget Online Casino, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamberler.
Please play responsibly.
21 and over, physically present in Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania, and West Virginia
only, void in Ontario.
New customers only, nonwithdrawable casino spins issued as 50 spins per day for 10 days valid
for featured game only and expire each day after 24 hours.
C -terms at GoldenNuggetCasino .com slash promos, ends at 11 .59pm, Eastern on August 31, 2025.
The football season is full of guarantees.
And here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October, if your
football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning or winning money back in fan
cash.
Guaranteed
Switch to Fanatic Sportsbook, winning hits different here.
Monthly 21 -plus, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamberler, offer not available in all states,
terms apply, see Fanatic Sportsbook app.
Welcome to your favorite fucking podcast you mother fuckers. Oh my God. We'll see you at hell with talking about the fucking horror movies and the fucking sci -fi movies and
the fucking fantasy movies and what the fuck were you doing watching fantasy movies anyway? Well movie. Is it a peshy?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, no fucking casino or your fucking TV show and what the fuck were you doing on the TV anyway? Yeah
My favorite peshy performance. I think more deserving of the Oscar than good fellows out of control
I just watched a documentary about good fellows the real Henry Hill, okay, and they said
Documentary about Henry Hill. Well, it's about Henry the real good fellows. Excuse me. Oh, okay, Henry Hill said they in fact in the movie
softened peshy's character. Yeah, I'll buy that. He said in real life that guy was like strung out on
Coke. Yeah. And an absolute fucking maniac, like no compromise. Yeah. And I was like, my God,
I don't even, and then they cut the Scorsese, he goes, do I know what the real man was capable of?
I don't want to know what the real man was capable of. Yeah. All right. Welcome to the show folks.
Welcome to the show. I would like to say, before we go any further, that we should just get on
with the show. And at the same time, on with the heat, joe all the way, it feels so right,
it. Be it with Joe tonight. What song is that? The raspberries. I don't know it. It was a
little higher than I expected. I just popped into my head. You don't know, go all the way.
It's in like outside providence and love. Oh, this one from a caddy check two. I'm going
all the way. No. I love somebody. Perent the C's love theme to caddy check two. No, I have
I don't know, that's not her, that's not her, that's not her, that's not her, that's not her, that's not her, that's not her, that's not her, that's not her, that's not her, that's not her, that's not her, that's not her, that's not her, that's not her, that's not her, that's not her, that's not her, that's not her, that's not her, that's not her, that's not her, that's not her, that's not her, that's not her, that's not her, that's not her, that's not her, that's not her, that's not her, that's not her, that's not her, that's not her, that's not her, that's not her, that's not her, that's not her, that's not her, that's not her, that's not her, that's not her, that's not her, that's not her, that's not
if I could just finish my goddamn thought.
Sorry, I'm sorry, I didn't mean to step on you.
Go on.
I just got excited because I was like,
this is a thing we'll bond on.
Yeah.
So you get a power pop.
Do you hear that new Weezer cover of Africa?
I have gone out of my way to avoid hearing it.
It is tremendous.
Isn't it just Africa?
Yeah, but it's, they, it's so Weezery that I was like,
did they get the guy from the rentals back in the band?
Yeah.
It's very keyboard heavy.
It's a true cover of Africa. It's not like they change it up much, but like when it hits that first chorus and
For the first time the weezer guitars come in and he's like and rivers is like it's gonna take a lot to take me away
It's fucking awesome, dude. All right. I'll listen to it. It's awesome
Here when I see them live with the pixie's next week, which I'm moderately excited about. I always love the pixie
Did you offer that to me and I passed off into you three four times?
Is it too late?
No, you can go.
But I can't sit with you at this point, right?
Figure something out.
I could sell mine and get a new one.
I'm going with my buddy, Brett.
Where's it at?
Forum.
Forum, I'd like Brett to stay home.
You might be out of town or something.
I think you said you had something to do.
I'd like Brett to stay home.
All right.
Fine.
I'd like you to stay home.
Give me the tickets, I'll go alone.
Fine.
I mean, weezer and Pixies.
I think sadly weezer are the headliners of that show,
but oh well.
Their cover of Beloria left much to be desired for me
because that's my favorite picking song.
I mean, look, I can't shit on Weezer too much.
Their first two albums are shaped my life
in a lot of ways.
Their goal, the first two.
All right, well, we're talking today about the film Solo,
directed by Mr. Ron Howard.
We'll get there.
I think we've talked about all the,
we've talked about every Star Wars since the fan of
on the show, not the Phantom Menace, the Force Awakens.
Well, we even talked about,
we even did talk about the old ones
because when we did the episode
about the most excited movie experiences
in our mind was Phantom Menace.
Can I tell you, I recently, because I have it in 3D,
and sometimes I like to dust off my old glasses,
and I watched The Force Awakens in 3D,
which was really sweet, I enjoyed it.
But I got to say, and I did not notice
this is the first time around, that John Boyega is very bad in that movie.
He is overacting to an absurd degree.
He screams every line.
He looks so panicked in every scene that it's just kind of unbelievable.
It's a little much.
Maybe he was directed to do that, but man, I really did not like his performance.
I noticed when I watched the second movie, he kind of does like a Denzel thing.
He mimics Denzel, like he'll do like the nod thing and I'm like, oh, he's like a
big Denzel.
Kind of like how Christian Slater you know, Nicholson Christmas later was Nicholson.
Yeah, that's true.
But Christian Slater was not the actor Nicholson was.
No, of course, but he was just doing it on a press.
Yeah.
So I'm saying, like, I'm not saying he's to that extent, but I'm just saying, like, if
you watch him, you're like, I think he loves Denzel Washington and Denzel Washington over
racks, but he does it great.
That's the thing when he does it, it's great.
And he can also under act without without a problem.
Denzel could be our finest living actor.
I think he probably is, but I mean, he's the only guy in a movie I've ever seen.
Slap a Dixie cup off a table at the end of the scene.
That's true. But, but, but I liked it.
Yeah. I want to see equalizer too.
I know. Yeah. I never saw equalizer one.
So equalizer one is fucking awesome.
I got to watch it tonight and then we'll get let's go see equalizer too.
Because brutally violent does movie pass even still like it's such a gif we knew it was too good the last
I did it for years and none of you motherfuckers even batting an eye when it was 40 bucks
But then instead of going from 40 to 20 where they still would have had I bet just as many subscribers
They dropped it to 10 we all knew it was two nuts. They dropped it to three for a month
We all knew in our hearts. It was two nuts the last I gave them as gifts to everyone
everyone I knew, and now it's blowing up.
But no, I heard it doesn't work anymore.
I think over the past couple of days, it's on and off,
but when it's on, what they're planning on doing,
is removing your access to the first week
and second week movies.
So if it's Friday night, Mission Impossible 2 comes out,
you can't see it, you gotta see something else.
And honestly, you can't argue with that.
No, I'm surprised they let you do it to begin with.
Yeah, when you used to get,
free tickets like like as a gift somebody would give you ticket vouchers and you couldn't go to a
fucking first -run movie. I do feel I need to share well now it's two weeks ago fuck but this I
saw that I've still followed the new Beverly which is my favorite theater here in town which has
been remodeling for too long it reopens in December but they said it last week so now it would be two
two weeks ago was the 10 year anniversary of the 20 year anniversary of the release of
Kingpin.
Twenty years.
But wait a minute.
Yeah, I was about 19 when I came out.
But I thought the movie was 96.
I think they were wrong.
So then it's more than 20 years?
Yeah.
22.
I think they're wrong.
But I don't want to call him out. Well, why you looked that up. Yeah, we kind of buried the lead here
And I can't believe we forgot to mention it on the first episode
Pat and I went to the Bruce Willis roast. Yeah, what why why would we not mention that?
I was invited by comedy central. I had a plus one. I said that plus one is only going to be the one. Yes
Mr. Patrick Walsh. I was very excited. Uh, we went down to this thing. We drank
I think copious amounts of alcohol.
I mean, they were just,
it was falling out of the trees in this field.
I drank so many before,
like even Joe made it through the red carpet.
Cause I was like, I'm not doing this red carpet thing,
and then I went inside and instead had eight drinks
and talked to nobody.
We were at a table where at each table,
they gave you and your friends,
who you were sitting with, I mean, bottles,
about four bottles of wine, and we were at a table with my dear friend, Christie Stefano,
funny comic, his buddy that I had just met, my buddy, Scott Moran from Comedy Central,
his lovely wife, my dear, one of my oldest and best friends, Anne Harris, also from Comedy
Central and Rachel Olsen, another dear friend, also from Comedy Mine.
So, and I'll tell you, I know these people, I've hung with these people, I've worked with
these people. We all like to have a couple drinks. Sure. So we went through that crime.
Four bottles of wine. Christ, I think before even Glazer finished her opening roast
set. We had another round. I did cool it a bit on the wine, but you turned it up. I think
what at some point we met in the middle. I turned up on the one. I asked the table next
to see if I could have their wine that they wouldn't seem to be drinking. They gave it
to me. Yeah. And then everybody at our table cheered. I thought I was going to get
chastised. Well, then I'm starving. I had neat and all day and I'm devouring these chips.
And then the guy next to me goes, wait, where are the CBD chips? Every table's supposed to have
CBD chips. So they're marijuana laced. I ate about 400 of them. Luckily, not THC, but I felt like
highly relaxed, like deep muscle relaxer relaxed. Yeah. And I had a great time when over the
after party, Bruce stepped on my foot. Kevin Pollock stole the show. I didn't watch the
roast. Kevin was wonderful. It was great running into him at the after party and getting
to tell him, dude, it was great. I DMed him the next day on Twitter again. I was like,
I can't get the joke out of my head. Joke of the night. Yeah, the joke was Edward Norton's
here, uh, he used to date Courtney love, which is sort of a sweet, romantic way of saying
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, that's not how you say it.
That's not how he said it.
Go on.
He said he would have been about the same.
You think so?
I do.
Go on.
Maybe it's better.
No, he goes Edward Norton's here.
You know, early and Edward's career, he used to run around town with Courtney love.
And he said, let me think of, see if I can think of a better, you know, we're
professional way to say that I'm giving you the punchline. Oh, Edward Norton has a I would say
my setup was better. Well, maybe he did set it up your way. Look, I just said I drank
a fucking bottle of rose in 10 minutes. It was a killer joke. I didn't watch it edited together
because I didn't there was a lot of that. I didn't need to see again. But this thing was I mean,
I mean, it starts off, they got Ving Rames spoof in the Pulp Fiction scene with, like, that's pride, fuckin' with you.
There's sound issues right from the jump.
By the way, was it Ving Rames?
Cause he never turned to face camera.
I confirm with my buddy Ian who works at Comedy Central.
It was his voice.
He said, I'll send you in.
Oh, my voice.
But the tape kind of fucks up.
And then from the, it really set the tone of like a real ram shackle off the rails kind of evening.
As I think all these rows are.
But like you have people up there who aren't well mentally Dennis Rodman
That was one of the I mean he's not a stand -up, but it was one of the worst stand -ups that's I've ever seen
What I was talking about with my buddy Ian and weeping at one point. He did start weeping from inspiration
It didn't seem like he knew Bruce Willis all that well
But he was weeping because of how inspired he was right and he did say every time I talk about you
I get like this. Yes, and everyone including Bruce's closest friends
made, quote, jokes that really didn't seem like jokes about how racist Bruce Willis was.
The first one Kevin Pollock did where he's like, it's probably to see a couple black
guys on the day is because I got to tell you, Bruce Willis does not like the blacks.
It gets a huge laugh and Bruce laughs and you're like, okay, great joke.
But so many people commented on his racism that I think it was true and Bruce laughed at
everyone.
about three quarters of the show Pat leaned over and he goes too many people have made the joke
that he's racist for it to not be kind of course. Uh, I got some big laugh. Again, I drank too much
but I got a real nice laugh from our table. I don't remember what it was. I remember exactly what it was.
Okay, go on. Cause I cherish your moments. I do. It's during Dennis's round minutes thing.
The guy spiraling into a fucking pit on stage. He's not making any sense. Yeah. And then uh,
And we, Dennis had hit about the 17 -minute mark in his spiel, and the audience, I mean,
it was dead silent.
It was very awkward.
And this is coming from a guy that saw the Donald Trump roast and watched the uncut bombing
of the situation at that thing, which I didn't think could be topped until I saw the Dennis
Rodman bombing at the Bruce Willis roast.
And you just, in a very dead, quiet moment, you went, all right, Dennis.
That sounds right, you gave him the rap and all right, Dennis.
Yeah, it was, that was real tough.
Well, it's also like Joseph Gordon Levitt was the host and Edward Norton's up there.
These are like, we're highly respected actors and performers.
And I kept turning to Joe like, what must these guys be thinking?
What did I agree to?
I assumed that they asked me, they had other big names, like how are we going to get out
of this?
and maybe Lil Royal had the sort of the same thing.
But everybody just seemed like,
can you imagine your Edward Norton Academy of War nominee
and you show up and you're sitting next to a man
who meets with Kim Jong -Un and who is notably,
not well.
Ed Norton, surprisingly funny.
Everyone knows what was funny.
Dennis Rahman, I don't know if they show this on the rose
but he looks at the microphone and he says how is opener.
Reminds me of my dick. Oh, really? I missed that. I was outside smoking holy shit Dennis. I was outside smoking you expected more
Holy shit. I was outside smoking when Dennis first went on
I came in about five minutes in and I was like oh, Jesus. I better get to my seat because this is magical
I believe his second line was and if you think you're worried about your age status Edward I
I fucked Madonna raw and the crowd was like, I believe that's when I walked in actually.
It was just like, he, I don't know, it was, he, he was rough.
I think rough for a lot of people, but all in all, a pretty funny evening, a very
funny evening.
Fun event.
Fun night.
Thank you for bringing me.
Right.
I'm sorry.
And I tried to retell the Pollock joke. I feel bad about that. It's fine, Joe.
And I honestly do feel bad about that, which lets you know where I'm at emotionally, right?
You shouldn't feel bad about it. You've ruined a lot of things for me.
Let's talk trailers. Have you seen the new Godzilla trailer?
Yeah, I did. In fact, I posted about it. What did you post?
I post. Does anybody gonna tell the Godzilla people they use the wrong music in that new trailer?
I thought, I mean, the first Godzilla was horseshit in my opinion.
Terrible horseshit.
And of course, the Matthew Broderick one was even worse, but I thought they're very
wise to go in what feels like a different, almost spilled harry in direction.
And I loved the music and I think most people did.
It's like inspirational fucking mute.
It's like, come on, dude.
It's Godzilla.
The Godzilla.
Dan it's a classic piece of classical music. I don't give a fuck what it is
I thought it worked beautiful. They said we have they go we have one hope right godzilla comes out of the water
You're like there. He is the man. He opens his mouth. You're waiting to hear the iconic fucking thing the scream
To get chills to and then they start playing fucking classical music. I'm like come on man. This is stupid
Work for me. I mean if it had at the standard every action movie
with Godzilla. I'd be like, I'm not gonna see that. I hated the first one. This made me feel like
they're doing something different. I think they knew they had to do something pretty different.
I respected it. How about the new predator trail? Wait a minute. I'm not telling my Godzilla. Okay.
I'm getting a little tired of seeing Millie Bobby Brown hyperventilating and scenes about things.
Agreed. I hope she's good in the movie. She's a very good actor, but you know, I was like,
right? You know, they're just blocking from the stranger thing's
tree again. You think we've got enough news stories about her
breaking up with the YouTube star? It's in the news.
Her breaking up. She's 11. Yeah, there's there's news reports
about it. And I'm not only talking about fucking people weekly.
You can have this world, guys. Yeah, I'm out. The also, I got to
say it's a little, the plot is a little video game -ish when Vera Farminga, however you
share your last name, is like, there are seven Titans.
If we don't find all seven, the world will be just like, this sounds like a fucking
video game, man.
Come on.
And it's like, why would you have to find the seven Titans for the world and what?
So we'll see.
We'll see.
I hope it's good, man. I hope it's good, but yeah, I'm excited to see Mothra and you know,
God hear Dre or however the fuck you say it a whole squad on deck. Yeah, they're doing a
sandlot prequel. Couldn't give a shit. Love the sandlot. Me too. A prequel. So what they're all
embryos playing baseball. It's just a guy coming into a baseball mitt. I think my first tweet was
take it easy, Sandlot narrator.
It's kids playing baseball.
We'll figure it out because every moment
of that movie is narrated within an inch of its life.
Yeah.
But it's a great movie, of course.
I remember I saw it in a sneak preview at the Mid River's
Mall six and this was during a time
that when they showed you a sneak preview of something,
meaning you got to see it a week early,
which was always awesome.
them, they would throw in a second feature that had been playing a while because they were
so glad you were doing them the favor of seeing their movie early.
That's nice.
So it was Sandlot and Groundhog Day, a movie I was dying to see again, different time.
I wish they'd bring that back.
It was great.
I still love a double feature, but you got to pay for it or sneak.
I even seen the new Predator trailer.
I saw the first one they released.
I thought the first one they released was bad.
I didn't think it was fun.
The new one looks fun.
I want to see the movie you know the first trailer I was like come on guys
You're not even given a he when you do the predator reveal give him a hero shot. Sure, and it's like a backed
Over the shoulder side angles the first time they should like what are you doing, right?
Toilet when they get to
Good
Kingpin because I have to I was also
Diagnosed with OCD over the hiatus a little confessional for you really
Which was a long time coming. I was not surprised by that news, but I have to close off
conversations. So King Pym was released on July 26th, and they said on this day in 1996.
So we're talking about the 22nd anniversary of a movie I saw on the theater which is disturbing.
Let me take you to an abbreviated Pat's movie corner because we've been shooting the shit.
I soar.
Sicario, day of the solid dad, solid dad.
I really loved the original Sicario and I rewatched it and loved it again, but I think
a big, big part of that is that it was directed by Villeneuve in the same style as prisoners
with Roger Deacons, the greatest cinematographer of all time.
So it held up, but it was because of how amazingly shot it was.
Everything about the new secario is trying to mimic the original, but that's kind of great
because it's like an up and coming cinematographer and an up and coming director who are like
really trying to match those heights and they get off with some really awesome shots.
The story itself, very entertaining, the guy who writes it and he wrote Wind River
and the original Scario Tyler Sheridan and Heller High Water as well.
I like the way the guy writes.
He makes every scene interesting in some way.
It's not all the boredom that I get so often going to the movies now.
He keeps things moving, keeps the twists coming.
Del Toro fucking kills it.
Brolin's fine.
There's no Emily Blunt.
But I gotta recommend it.
It's very entertaining.
Check it out.
I saw the last movie star, starring Bert Reynolds.
OK, how was that?
I wouldn't call it a good movie, but it's enjoyable.
OK.
He is charming enough in it.
And his co -star who was like a 19 year old girl who I've never seen in anything else.
He's not fucking it. No. She's like a sort of like punk rocky like hipster girl.
And she gets stuck driving him like kind of taking him around this town during this film festival.
And he's pissed because he goes down to this film festival thinking it's going to be this big
on her and he gets there and it's like, you know, it's basically like some kids that
were in at the Alamo Draft House.
Yeah.
And they're excited.
He's there.
But he's kind of a prick to them.
And he gets drunk.
And then the next day this, this girl, who's the, her brother is running the festival.
She gets commissioned to pick him up and Bert Reynolds is basically like, you're going
to take me now to relive all my memories.
He's not playing Bert Reynolds.
Two towns over.
No, but it might as well be.
Okay.
It's literally Bert Reynolds, he's like he's like I was a great actor, I made some bad
choices, you know, it's the same story and you know there's some very sweet moments,
there's some very touching moments, it's not good, but that I think a lot of that has to
do with the direction, it could have been directed better, the writings cliche at times.
But, you know, for me, I was just, I was, I enjoyed just seeing Bert Reynolds on screen
again and, and being kind of funny and sure, you know, not doing, I mean, because I, I
kind of check in with Bert Reynolds every couple of years.
We saw him in person.
Yeah.
And I mean, he's made some doosies in the last, I mean, there's that movie with him and Richard
Drifus where they're like the old mafia guys, I've seen it. I mean, it's it's embarrassingly bad. Not
unlike a movie we pitched on this very show. Yeah. Somebody pointed out to me, starred Martin
Moll and Dabney Coleman. Our movie did? Yeah. It was people who like breath, breath smell like coffee.
I remember we had Dabney Coleman, we had Craig T Nelson. Yeah. And Ben Stiller was the young guy.
Yeah, but I never can remember who the other older guys were. I don't think Martin Moll was one of them.
No, that might have been a different bit where we were talking about who's breath smells the most like coffee. Well, that was part of our old man movie, okay, but it was
that was Dabney Coleman. It was all guys that you said you would feel like they were your dad as soon as you met them. It was Cregty Nelson, Dabney Coleman.
Is Keach in the mix? No, Bert Young.
No. Well, anyway, I don't know. People can dig it up. It's, it's an enjoyable enough film.
If you want to see Bert Randle's on screen again doing something sort of comical.
And it's got enough schmaltz in it that it'll, that it'll touch your heart. But, but you know,
if you, if you're on the fence about it, I wouldn't push you to see it. Okay.
I saw Tully, the new Diablo Cody, Jason Reitman collaboration. Joe, what's your thoughts
on Juno? That doesn't seem like a movie you would enjoy.
Two quirky for me. I like Jason Reitman's work quite a bit, but that film is too quirky
for me. First half hour of Juno made me want to rip my balls off and eat them. And then
the last hour I think is actually great and very touching and funny. And I like the Apple
No code is writing, I liked her horror movie, Jennifer's body, I liked young adult, a
great deal.
Yeah.
I liked young adult quite a bit.
Also Jason Rhyma, but I saw the new one, Tully, which is about a woman who's very overwhelmed
by motherhood, and I know that it doesn't sound interesting at all.
That sounds interesting.
But there's like, yeah, it was funny.
There's a twist that I missed, and when I told my staff that I missed the twist, they
made fun of me rightly so for about an hour.
But due to my OCD, I often focus on the wrong things in movies, and I miss the major
things.
There's a great twist that I missed, and when you see it, you'll think that I'm very stupid.
But the movie is amusing.
It is extremely well -acted.
They do have Ron Livingston and Mark Duplos in a lot of scenes together, but they're not
playing brothers.
Yeah.
That's confused.
And you can't tell them apart.
I don't think that was a smart move.
That's a look identical.
But it's certainly worth it.
That seems like something that'll pop on Netflix in the instant pretty quick.
And it's an entertaining movie.
I recommend it.
It's very interesting and I think a lot of people can relate to what we're thinking about
kids and etc.
All right, and close this out with this one. You ready? Yeah, I watched Fletch again. I'd see Fletch a million times. I love Fletch
Never saw Fletch lives
Okay, I watched it. I've seen for the first time and that movie's been trashed to me my entire life. Yeah, it's fine
It's a funny fucking it's Fletch. It's another goddamn Fletch movie. It's not the first one, but I mean, I think it was terrible. I enjoyed it
I've always enjoyed flesh lives. I think some of the characters he does are even funnier,
but it's a much worse movie, but it's better than as we mentioned at the beginning of
the show, Caddy Shack 2, for example.
Yeah, yeah, I thought it was going to be like that level of bad.
No, it's dumb, but I enjoyed it.
It's just nice to see a thing that he was in where he's funny, because I hadn't seen
be funny and so goddamn long. It's been a long time. Clarke Griswald though, one of the best
characters of all time. Absolutely. The guy's one of the funniest actors of all time. It's just
you know, but I'm going to I'm going to forego scary stuff this week in honor of screaming and
what is it, what is it? Deadlines from the Scream and End, 24 -hour news site.
Yeah, very exciting movie news folks. You know what a Star Wars freak I am and we're
doing solo this week. They just made a bunch of, today that we are recording, you know,
when you hear this it'll be a week later but we can have. But today that we are recording
they they started shooting episode nine and they made some really great confirmed announcements
this week leading up to the shooting. Mark Hamill is confirmed to come back as Luke Skywalker.
Is this Ryan Johnson as well? No, JJ Abrams is back. I believe that JJ Abrams is going to take
the good parts of what Ryan Johnson did and also inject a lot of nostalgia into it and really end
this saga. I want to high note. Is this ending this saga? Yeah, this is it. This is the end
of the Skywalker saga nine, nine parts. Anyway, Skywalker's back. They don't know if it's
going to be as a force ghost or if he's still alive, but he's back. They have Leia in it
because they had unused footage from episode seven of Carrie Fisher and they figured out
a way to work Leia into the plot. So she's actually in the movie. That is fantastic, fantastic
stick fucking news.
It depends on what it looks like, but okay, it'll look great.
I mean, it's not going to be like, you know, that, you know, she's like cut into a scene
with like a weird fuzz around her because they edited it.
Also there's a rumor that JJ Abrams will be tying in a lot of references to the prequels
and to the original trilogy to kind of give a cohesiveness to this entire series.
I love that.
I think that's awesome.
I like that Ryan Johnson did that.
There are rumors that they might return to Vader's castle from Rogue One.
There are rumors that there might be an Obi -Wan force ghost.
There are rumors that there might be an Anakin force ghost.
And perhaps the biggest news just behind Carrie Fisher, Carrie Fisher's almost impossible
return is confirmed, Billy D Williams is coming back as Lando.
So I just think he's going to put a really, really nice period on this entire thing and
it's going to be, I'm very excited.
And speaking of solo, which we'll get to in a minute, they're not doing other movies in
the solo verse.
Are they?
They signed them for a trilogy, but I don't think they're going to do it now because the
movie didn't do well.
By Star Wars standards, it didn't do well.
Right.
I mean, Christ almighty, if it was a fucking, you know, if it was Daddy's home three, they
would have been like, we got to make four more of these things.
Did you see the Halloween trailer, one last big horror trailer before we move on to
solo?
I did.
Thoughts.
Underwhelming.
Yeah.
Yeah, it looked to me sort of like a continuation of the Rob Zombie ones, which I don't think anybody
was thrilled with.
And for it to be David Gordon Green and fucking Danny McBride, who have made some of my favorite
things of the last 10 years, I was a little, I guess, underwhelmed as a good word.
I'm not going to write it off, I'm certainly happy Jamie Lee's back, but I don't know.
Well, look, I'm looking forward to seeing it, but my takeaway from that initial trailer
was, this is a remake of H2O.
This is just a variation of H2O.
They already did this.
They already did the storyline where he comes back, she's been waiting, she has to face
him and become the hunter herself.
They've already done this.
So this is a different variation of that, fine.
but that was my first thought. I think it carries much less weight that they are making this a direct
sequel to the first film and negating the fact that their brother and sister. That to me,
that makes it carry much less weight for his return to kill her and her obsession with him at
potentially returning. I just don't buy that. The bloodline thing made sense to me. It's like
like I'm the one that got away in the family.
He has to kill me.
And now it's just like, okay,
so you're pretty sure this dude's gonna come back
to Haddonfield and kill you.
So you've been like doing this like militia training
for the last 30 years or whatever it's been.
Why wouldn't you just leave the town?
Sure.
Why wouldn't you just move away somewhere?
Why wouldn't you try to just put this,
but I don't look.
Maybe they'll answer those questions in it.
I hear it's fucking brutal.
I hear it's super violent and I hear it's scary so I hope that's the case
But the trailer I didn't think it's like the predator. I want to see it
I think the trailer didn't do it justice
You got to hope that they're doing what so few trailers do and saving some for when you see the fucking movie
Yeah, keeping some to the best, but I just feel like their comedy is so
aggressive
so like
different and weird
That I can't imagine they did a straightforward horror movie. I can't imagine that I hope not you think they did like a comedy
Andy Har?
No, no, no.
I mean, I feel like at least it'll be like
memorably weird and fucked up.
Well, I saw it at some horror con.
They had a mask replica from the new movie.
Yeah.
Of a severed head that Michael Myers
had carved on the face into like a jackal lantern.
Yeah.
And it looked awesome and horrifying.
And I was like, okay, well, fuck,
if they're bringing that kind of shit, I'm into it,
You know, sure, but we'll see.
You know, I didn't think H2L looked good when it came out.
And then I saw it on the theater and I fucking loved it.
So, you know, I'll be excited.
We'll do it on opening night and get it out to you, folks.
But let's talk about solo, solo which was at least initially directed by Lord and Miller,
who I think are very creative guys, more in the comedy space, but they've done some really
The Great Things, Lego Movie, Last Man on Earth, et cetera.
And at some point, they didn't like the direction it was going in.
I don't know if that meant too joky or what, or how much input they had, or if they were,
I think, when I heard they were changing the script too much, but was replaced by Ron Howard.
And I will admit that even though I have loved Ron Howard directing across all genres in a way
that I never feel like he got enough respect for.
Parenthood is a fantastic comedy.
Paul Thirteenth is a fantastic drama.
Backdraft is a fantastic action movie.
Like he's kind of done it all.
Willow's a great fantasy movie.
He's kind of a jack of all trades.
Splash a great romantic comedy, et cetera.
But I went in thinking he's old, he's passed his prime.
I was excited about some young hip guys take on this franchise.
and now I think we're going to watch a very boring version and I could not have been more pleasantly
surprised. It was old -fashioned but in like the best way, co -written by Lawrence Cazin, one of
the greatest screenwriters of all time. Yes. Indeed Jones for Christ's sake. Like just the best and him
and his son wrote it together, the love of Star Wars shown through and my only grievance would be the
casting of the lead dude who I loved and how Caesar. I don't think he was there for this part,
but we can discuss him. On the whole, I thought this was just a very entertaining and very well
written, thoughtfully written action movie, which you never see anymore.
Side note. Yes. Lawrence Kesson wrote it with his son. Right. His son just replaced David Kep
and he is now the writer for the last Indiana Jones installment, which I think is quite
poetic because his dad wrote the first one.
Yes. And I think after seeing Solo, Spielberg was probably like, you get, you get like
the cat, you get it. You get why this guy has to because they're similar characters obviously,
but did, did, did kept do a draft it in the like or they just booted them without even.
I don't know. I was, I was never thrilled that nothing against David kept, but, you know,
as far as I can tell, he's written two good movies, you know, Jurassic Park. And I think
I think he wrote Shawshank Redemption.
No, he didn't.
He wrote Stir of Echoes, which I love.
It's fine.
David Keps written some really solid ghost town movies.
Not ghost town, but he's a broken window
with Johnny Depp.
Secret window with a terrible movie.
No, but he's written some good film.
I want to pull this up.
As a part.
Jurassic Park is a perfect action screenplay.
Well, yeah, but as we all know,
there are a lot of cooks with these things.
That's true. And I think Sturov Echoes is an excellent horror screenplay.
It's passable. We've talked about it. He's probably better with adaptations. I mean,
those are both adaptations. Um, I love solo. I love. Okay. David kept. Sorry. He wrote the latest
mummy. All right. I didn't see it. Inferno. The third of the. Yeah. I didn't see that.
DaVinci code movies. He wrote the original Mission Impost. Jack Ryan Shadow recruit.
I didn't see it.
Premium rush is a fun movie.
I never saw it.
It's a fun -ass movie.
Mission Impossible Ghost Protocol.
Okay.
Angels in demons.
Didn't see it.
Ghost town.
Panic rooms good.
Indiana Jones in the Crystal Skull.
Yeah, War of the Worlds.
Carlitos way.
Now, there's a good fucking thing.
Just through death becomes her.
All right.
right? He's, look, he's right up the middle. He created the
television series hack. I can't believe he didn't mention
Mordecai for Christ's sake. I mean, if ever there was a vote for
your side to be Mordecai, um, he also wrote Jurassic World, the
lost world. I like the lost the second one. Yeah. I do. You
like the second one. As a, as a fun time. Yeah. All right.
All right. I mean, I haven't seen that since I was 14 who knows
but, um,
toy soldiers I like.
Anyway, I loved, I loved solo.
Um, I went in, I was very nervous.
I was very nervous about the casting of, uh,
Alden Heidenreich or something.
Yeah, however you say it.
Alden III Reich, I feel like just how they used to change Jewish actors
names when they would become actors.
I'm surprised they don't change a name like Heidenreich.
It doesn't instill warmth when you have that name.
Yeah, but I I was nervous going in. I was like, is this going to be just an over the top slapstick
Thing like what how is it and within?
45 seconds. I was sold I
Loved the way it opened sold though sold. Oh, I love the way it opened and
And with with like a sort of not a tech, not the not the crawl like usual, but like just some sort of text telling you what's going on.
I love the opening sequence with him with solo coming back to his like, you know, orphanage or whatever you want to call it. And then like as soon as that like the fat, the what they call the foul lady whatever that like worm woman. Yeah.
As soon as she popped out of the water, I was like, this is awesome, man, this is like job
of the hutch shit.
And the whole time I was watching it, I was just like, please don't, please don't fuck
this up.
Like, don't let up.
Like, don't take a turn.
And it never did.
I loved every minute of it.
The only thing I didn't like, I thought the, the wookie talk joke was really dumb.
I thought it was unnecessary and a little too silly, but I mean, even those details like, you
you know, when they say we're gonna feed him to the beast,
I didn't see that coming and then it's Chewbacca
and that's how they meet.
I loved, I mean, I was watching that train high scene,
which is the most perfect thing you could ever have
on solo do as a train robbery.
Yeah, great action scene.
I'm watching it.
I'm like, Jesus Christ, this is,
we're not even through the first act of this movie yet.
Yeah.
And they're doing this fucking crazy.
Like, that was one of the better action scenes
of all Star Wars, I would say.
It was awesome.
Yeah.
Woody Harrelson, I loved, and I just like all those Easter eggs.
I like when you see how Han gets his blaster.
I like how you see how he meets Chewie.
I like how you, I like when Woody Harrelson is like, there's a gangster on Tatooine putting
a big job together and you know he's talking about Java and then at the end of the movie,
Han's like, let's go to Tatooine for this job and he's like, trust me, nothing's going
to go wrong.
Right.
And then you realize, no, everything's going to go wrong.
That's why he gets fucking frozen in carbonite and Empire Strikes Back.
It was just awesome. And I actually really thought Alden was great in that role. I thought he nailed
what a younger version of that character would be. A lot of charisma, a lot of swagger,
a lot of confidence. Sure. And but idealistic and not knowing what's what just yet.
Yeah, I mean, for me, it's Harrison Ford, you know, like that I guess for me, the guy
didn't have that star power, a few do, but he was a guy who was really funny in like
a few scenes in a Coenbro's movie to this role.
I don't think he was there yet.
He didn't carry the gravitas for me, although I didn't think he was bad.
And in fact, I liked him, I just, for me, I think, and maybe you can offer your thoughts
on why it didn't do as well.
I think for me, the two reasons are, anytime there's a prequel, you know, the person lives,
the stakes are eliminated by a million percent.
But also, I think it was the casting of that guy.
I think that a lot of people scratched their heads and were like, a lot of people still
need stars. Most people's number one question when they go to see movies who's in it, even
a Broadway play at this point, who's in it is always the big question. I just don't
think that's a name that got anybody excited. But maybe I won't. This is why I disagree.
Harrison Ford was not a star when he played Han Solo. He only got the part because they were
paying him to read with other actors. And then finally they were like, he seems to be reading
it better than anybody else. That was a, that was a different less star obsessed time.
So yeah, but, but so I think it would have been a big mistake to put somebody recognizable
in this role.
I think the reason it didn't do well is because unfortunately Star Wars fans have become
the new Bernie bros, where even though the cause is righteous and pure, there's a, there's
a percentage of these people really, really polluting the pool.
And I think that they're just, a lot of these fans are just fucking miserable.
It didn't matter who they put in this goddamn thing.
they were going to be pissed off. And, and that was it. I mean, they didn't throw a goddamn
fit about Donald Glover playing Orlando. I thought Donald was great. Donald Glover was
the high point of the movie. Um, stole the movie. I thought he was fucking great. Yeah.
You know, um, but, you know, they threw a fit about, about this kid playing Han and, you
know, and it takes place 10 years before Star Wars. So I, I really loved it. Um, I thought
he was fine. I thought Glover, I wished that they had matched the perfection of the casting
of Glover as Lando and found somebody equally that great as Han. And again, not saying
I didn't like him, it just didn't quite, he didn't jazz me up when he was on screen.
But for me, the star of this one is, you know, as we talked about last week with the red
commentary, there are points where it kind of doesn't add up and make sense.
This is like a classic Lauren's cast and style screenplay where you really give a shit
about everything connecting and making perfect sense and you feel that watching it.
It doesn't feel like a movie that's making it up in the fly like a lot of these Marvel movies
do.
It felt like a true story being told and that's what I appreciated about it the most I would
say.
I saw twice in the theater the second time I saw it when they're doing the castle run, which is awesome that you get to see the castle run
You know and initially
the
What's your name from a game of thrones?
Amelia yeah, I didn't even know that it was her but Amelia Clark Amelia Earhart. Yes, Amelia Bidil. Yeah, I believe
She's like co -piloting the ship with Han because they're old friends and
Then like when Chewie says like I can fly whatever
And Han's like you can and then Chewie's like here's how you do this or whatever and she realizes he's more suited to fly
As the copo that she is and she goes Chewie you're up and they're in the fucking castle run and for the first time
In the history of the Star Wars universe
Chihuahua gets debt sits down next to Han Solo in the Millennium Falcon and for the first time in the movie
They play the Star Wars music and I fucking wept like an excited
It just it hit me through the fucking heart, dude. I loved it so much. I tell you there
There's no scenario where I could ever cry at a Star Wars movie. I don't have the nostalgia for that
But I respect that it made you feel that way and then of course the dark mall cameo at the end was
Fucking awesome.
Yeah, I thought maybe I was missing something there
and that was another d 'arth or something
because I was just sort of thrown by that.
I guess if he's gonna appear in the rest of the trilogy
with their, I guess they're not gonna do it.
They can, well, I mean, hopefully they do,
but they completed Darth Maul's story in the cartoons.
Right.
And it's an awesome story.
So he already has come back in that universe.
Okay.
So when they showed him in there, I was like,
holy shit, they're gonna tie this in now.
Yeah, because they're slowly tiling in Star Wars Rebels and Clone Wars and all that all the TV stuff that you want Disney and
That was amazing, but the best part about seeing this movie for me was the day after I saw it Matt McCarthy our dear friend
And I were texting and we were he was like I loved it so much and Christ and he goes man that fucking Darth Maul alien at the end was awesome
I was like, what do you mean alien? And he's like that guy that looked like Darth Maul and I got to be like Matt
That was fucking Darth Maul, didn't you see his robotic legs?
That was, that's all I didn't think it was him either.
I just thought it was another guy.
Well, it gives so much more stakes to the,
it ties the empire now to the entire thing.
You've, the twist at the end is you find out the fuel
that the pirates are trying to steal us for the rebellion.
And then you find out that the people trying to squash
the pirates are connected now to the empire and the Sith.
It gives so much more weight to the movie.
So I don't read the online shit so much anymore.
What are are people liking it that have seen it or were people pissed about it some people like it some people hate it?
Are these the same people that hated last Jedi or different?
Look, let me tell you about these fucking people. They're getting it's getting dark. It's it's hard
They harass that poor girl off the internet. It's fucking horrible. Yeah, and
Here's the thing
These same fucking trolls the same people they complained for a year and a half straight
that all Ryan Johnson was going to do was remake Empire Strikes Back.
Right.
And then Ryan Johnson was like, no, I didn't.
Lately didn't do that.
Yeah, and I did a completely different thing.
And then they get pissed off that he did a completely different thing.
I mean, these are miserable, miserable fucking people that want everything to be exactly
the way they thought it would be in their head.
The first time they see it, they have no ability for growth, they have no ability to watch.
You're closer to them than you might think, Joe.
Stop it.
But but go on. I stopped it. Go on. I saw the last shed. I for fucking time right because I wanted to I wanted to get it right finally got it. Yeah, I
Dug that last Jedi because it was taking chances. Yeah, I like to do. Yeah, I think it was what the middle needed right especially so now
JJ comes back in and does like the here's what you thought it was going to be and here's what you wanted and it's the big payoff
off. And then it's over. But I mean, they're not going to be happy. Anyway, you cut it for
them. I just don't get. I was, look, I was a defender of the prequels. I was never a
person that thought more Star Wars was bad. I was always a person that thought, hey, man,
if there's, if there's more that I don't like or don't care for that much, that's fine. It's
still more. Yeah. You like what you like and whatever. And, uh, and God Almighty, did I fight
with those fucking nerds over fan of menace and all that shit, you know, but I love this
movie. It was a home run, in my opinion. Yeah, I had a really great time with it. I saw
it with a buddy of mine and we were both just like kind of beaming afterwards. It was, and
you know, talk about hype working for a movie because the advance hype and it was like, it's
the bomb nobody gives a shit.
So, and I saw it eight weeks after it came out
and I was just like, wow, this really should have done better
and I think it will find its audience.
But, you know, weirdly, even though it was very tight
into Star Wars lore, it didn't get that bump.
Like people didn't give it shit about it.
It's really weird.
I can't wait to own it.
I can't wait to watch it again.
The only reason I didn't see it a third time in theaters,
I didn't wanna burn it out, but I'm really excited to own it.
I'm very, very excited to show it to people. It became instantly one of my more favorite Star Wars films
and that's it. It was great. You can see that quote on the DVD box. It'll say,
Joderosa, one of my more favorite Star Wars films, because they wanted a quote that was really
Well written always with the Mao folks. And I think that's the first folks of our of our new residency
over here. We're happy to be back. We're thrilled to be back. I am on Twitter and Instagram
at the Patrick Walsh. Watch for the new show I'm running cool kids September 28th on Fox.
and we are doing a live show, October 20th at a place called Omai Ribs here in Los Angeles.
We're doing two shows, one at 731 at 930, $20 for a single show, $30 for both shows.
Ticket link is...
Both shows will be different, by the way.
Both shows are different.
Ticket link is not quite live yet, but it should be coming soon per the venue.
and anyone attending that 930 or returning later after the 730 is welcome to join Joe and I
for a night of heavy drinking at a local bar. Upcoming shows, I think we're going to do mission impossible
for sure. I think we're going to do Castle Rock on Hulu for sure and I know that we're going to
do Gotti probably for the Patreon. Yes. Go to the Hoghouse page on Etsy. We have stickers,
posters, T -shirts, and hats. And you are going to give you a
Patreon this month. Those are my updates and news, Joe.
All right.
Joderos Accomedy, only on Instagram now, no more Twitter and I
will be, maybe be, I guess when this drop, look, I'm going to be at
the DC Drafthouse, the 17th and 18th of August. So yeah, this
comes up before that. And then I'll be at the right clay comedy
Festival in Atlanta in September. I'm also doing some shows in that in and around that region
that following week. So I'll hope to see you then folks. We'll see you we'll see you later
and we'll see you in hell.