I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, and when the sound of your screams becomes
a thing of my dreams, you know I'll say, I'll see you in hell, you know I will, I'll see
you in hell, you know I will.
Folks, it's we'll see you in hell, Pat Walsh and Joe DeRosa are here to review a film called
The Holdovers, not a horror movie, but we're spreading our wings in this new year, 2024.
We don't do a lot of non -horrors.
It's awards season.
Yeah.
No, we don't.
It's awards season, and The Holdovers is a return of podcast fave Paul Giamatti, Alexander
Payne.
We'll see what we thought when we get there.
Joe, you seem, are you hungover or are you, there's a darkness around you today.
Is it the, maybe it's the unshaven, I don't know, but you look like you've just been on
a week long bender with whores.
Not that you look bad, you look like, you look like you're just like Bruce Willis at
the beginning of Die Hard with a Vengeance, they found him at dumpsters, you know.
That's just my aura bleeding through.
No, quite the opposite.
I've been very dry since New Year's Day.
This morning I had to do, oh no, since my birth, sorry.
I had to do blood work, my six month blood work thing that I get this morning, but the
last two days, my show at the Gramercy Theater is tomorrow in New York, and so for the last
two days, three days, two days, three days, whatever it's been, I've been up at the crack
of dawn to be able to get to where I need to get to to start doing press in the morning
throughout the day, and then there's usually other work to tend to at night.
Last night I had a show, blah, blah, blah.
So I'm just, and then I had to get up really early today, go get the blood work done.
I walked home, we're recording now, I'm just, I think I'm just a little underslept at this
point.
And when you say get the blood work done, you mean watch the 2001 Clint Eastwood vehicle
blood work, right?
Yeah, yeah.
It's, I'm in a group.
You ever see that one?
I'm sure it was in 2001, it was a shot in the dark, but have you seen that movie?
No.
What was blood work?
I mean, I vaguely remember, but.
It's awful.
I mean, it was in that period where he was just lost.
Like it was after Absolute Power and, you know, just not a popular movie.
What I do remember about it is that he's a cop.
Wow, 2002.
That was pretty fucking close.
I do remember a scene where he's like a, he's a Dirty Harry style cop, of course, but he
just gets out of his car and just starts opening fire in a crowded street.
That's the scene I remember of it.
I was like, this is a terrible policeman.
You remember?
In the plot here, it says profiler Terry McCaleb returns to service when his own blood analysis
offers clues to the identity of a serial killer.
Not even sure what that would mean.
It sounds like one of these.
His blood work offers clues?
He's trailing himself, or he's been, he's got to prove he's innocent or some shit.
I don't know.
That sounds, oof.
Did you ever see?
I mean, I don't remember nothing about it except him shooting into a street.
The, the sketch from SNL when Darryl Hammond would do Bill Clinton reviewing the movies.
I mean, I must have, but I don't remember it.
I don't know how many times he did it, but the best one was, uh, he reviewed Absolute
Power and he's like, and he's like, he's, he, he opens with just laying out the premise
and he's like, he's like 20 minutes into the movie, the president's wife is murdered.
And then he just pauses and he goes, I love this movie.
I mean, it's, it's an outrageous bit that they're doing considering the Clintons are
friends of the show.
Right.
Like it's, it's so funny.
It's wild.
The bit is wild.
Yeah.
Uh, the problem with one of the million problems with these TikToks or reels is that you can
watch something and think it happened yesterday and then find out it was a 10 year old clip
or something.
So I don't know when this took place, but it was that real thin, um, kind of, what do
you call it?
Like almost like he's, he's, he's turning into dust Bill Clinton that we have now.
He's like old and thin, emaciated, emaciated.
So it must've been a recent clip, but, um, he's like, well, you know, uh, I know a lot
about a lot of things.
And this guy in the audience goes like raping women.
And Bill's like, oh, no, come on, come on.
He's like, he literally goes, no, come on, come on.
It was one of the craziest things I've ever seen.
I was like, no, Bill, you have to deny that or do something other than say, come on.
Like, that's a ridiculous response.
That's wild.
I think, uh, you know, I know a lot of people have conspiracy theories about them and I
don't think she, you know, obviously Hillary Clinton was not doing pizza gate.
I'm not that, that nuts, but I do think country is unaware of like the deaths of
what the Clintons have done.
I think they've had people killed.
I mean, seriously, I think great president for the most part, you know,
comparatively, but yeah, I think he, I don't think they're good people.
Uh, I mean, look, both of their names are prominently featured on that Epstein
list next to Trump.
These are the three that keep kind of coming, keep coming up.
And it makes you just keep thinking of that picture of them all laughing
together at the wedding.
Yeah.
And then, uh, and then the picture from the Giselle, well, it might've been when
she married Epstein where they're both Trump and Hillary are both seen in the,
in the immediate audience at the wedding.
Wild stuff.
Yeah.
And then whenever they're asked about it, they're like, oh, come on, shut up.
You know, they get so, I'm like, no, answer it.
Why doesn't anyone hold these people to a quite, you don't get a follow -up
anymore, probably because you'll be murdered, you'll be murdered.
That is true.
Um, I, this morning woke up and went to CVS.
I started doing, and again, these things you hear your whole life that would
help and you don't do them.
And then when you do them, they help drastically.
That's the story of my life.
It bothers me, but, um, I'm doing this book called the artist's way.
Which has changed my life.
If you're a writer, anything creative, uh, I would recommend it highly, but it
recommends doing these morning pages.
It was written by an ex -wife of Martin Scorsese, but, uh, morning pages
you may have heard of, you just write and three pages every morning, whatever
pops into your head, don't judge it.
Don't reread it.
And you know, it's, it's knocked me out of my writer's block like instantly.
It works so well.
It, cause it puts the connection.
I don't write longhand anymore.
It puts the, it puts the mind hand connection back to it.
You know, like you're just like, it's a better way to get
creativity on the page than typing.
So, which is why Tarantino, you know, does his scripts longhand and stuff.
Um, but it's been working great.
It helps me get the shit out of my head in the morning.
Instead of sitting and stewing in anxiety, I get it out on the paper.
It works beautifully, but I already filled up a notebook.
So I run up to CVS and I've seen all these clips about how insane
inflation is getting with food and stuff.
And I haven't really experienced it.
I use a meal plan, but, um, I went to buy a three ring hundred sheet notebook.
Cause your, your classic college rule that you get in your first day of school
need, you know, like the cheap knockoff old brand that we've had for a hundred
years was 1299 for a spiral notebook.
Yeah.
Weren't they like $4 a week ago?
Nope.
Notebooks have always been a dollar, you know, like our $2.
So I'm like, okay, I guess I'll just get a, you know, legal
pad or some typing paper.
There's nothing under $10 to buy paper.
And it's not like I don't have it, but I'm like, what, what's going on?
So then I went to the grocery store.
There's the classic Mead five subject notebook for 299.
So then what's going on?
These were in the same strip mall.
That has to be a missed price then.
I was going to say it's related to the fact that every, every notebook,
every paper product was that it was 10 and up.
Um, I don't know.
That's odd.
I thought maybe it was related to, uh, you know, it's somebody who is more
schooled in the pricing of lumber than I ever thought I would be after a bar
build out, uh, and then buying a house, uh, the, the, you know, wood lumber
prices are through it's crazy what lumber costs now.
So I thought maybe the paper fallout, you know, was related, but, but if the
grocery store is so, I don't know, that's odd.
That's very odd.
Grocery store is always going to be your best bet though.
Whatever you need, they're going to have the best price when, and usually
so would CVS or a pharmacy.
But, um, well, it was the same all over.
You know, it was, I had to get shampoo, same deal.
I was like, like 9 .99.
What's, you know, it's just crazy shit.
I mean, that's the starting price.
9 .99.
It's like, what, what's happening?
Yeah.
That's you always had the option of like the 99 cents suave, you know, like
that the go -to, yes, that is crazy.
That's all right.
Let's not, we're going to w this will push me down a road of we're crumbling.
Let's not go down that road.
Let's try to keep it sort of light.
I'm in a decent mood today, despite my appearance.
Uh, well, we got a hot screaming and to get to run right off the bat.
Yes.
We discussed, uh, look, I have a deep love for the comedy of David Gordon green.
I think he is an excellent comedy director in his work with, um, Danny McBride.
I love, but he is not a horror guy.
His Halloween series didn't work and way worse in my opinion.
And I believe Joe's was this exorcist reboot.
We didn't, neither of us liked it.
Um, and now after paying $400 million for the rights to the exorcist.
Universal is throwing David Gordon green off the project.
Of course it says he left voluntarily, but come on.
Now, let me ask you, I got a question before you proceed the 400 million.
Was that just for the rights or was that, was it 400 million, meaning the rights,
what the movie costs to make, blah, blah, blah.
Was it just a $400 million bill at the end of the day, or was that
literally just for the rights?
I mean, what the hell, how the fuck could, if it is just for the rights, my
question is, is how the fuck are the exorcist rights worth that much when
it's already been done once perfectly.
And then there's been nothing but let aside from three years.
Let down sequels.
See, okay.
Universal and Blumhouse, you boys bought the exorcist franchise rights for a
trilogy from Morgan Creek back in July, 2021 for an exorbitant 400 million.
Jesus Christ.
Okay.
So we're not even talking price of the movie yet.
I think.
Yeah.
The bid for the package was made by Universal during a time when studios
were in a frenzy to develop a big content for their streamers.
Horror with greens, Halloween sequels proved to be a main driver
of subscribers for Peacock.
So, uh, then this says
Creek, by the way, Morgan Creek.
I remember them from like Prince of thieves and major league that like
91 is the last time I saw Morgan Creek.
I saw, you know, the, the company with the Pegasus horse, uh, tri star.
Yeah.
Right.
Tri star was like my best friend's wedding and a few things like mid
nineties, and then they went away.
Now they're back.
You know, I don't know how these news back doing big shit is Orion.
Orion's back.
Exactly.
It's like, what's going on?
I thought these things were long dead.
It's crazy to me.
Um, let me, I'm going to, it's not much to read here, but, uh, uni and
bloom houses by of exorcist wasn't a plan by which three movies would be
made for 133 million each.
So here's our answer.
The exorcist deal was a broader franchise driver for universal, which
also included a buyout of talent and rights, backends, producer fees,
rights to IP, meaning theme parks, Halloween, horror nights, et cetera.
So that's what they get for their 400 month.
Okay.
Um, now here's an, here's a real interesting, here's two movies
we talked about on the show.
We had heard that there was a push by those involved with five nights at
Freddy's to make that $300 million grossing hit exclusive to cinemas instead
of a day and date release with peacock and instead have exorcist go day and
date on peacock universal did not bite on that option and kept exorcist
primary to theaters and at bomb.
So who were my, my pick, the kids who did talk to me, an excellent
and original possession movie.
Um, who would you put in that spot?
Somebody knew, is there a horror movie you saw where you're like, this
person would be great for the exorcist.
I can't even imagine.
Sure.
Talk to me is as good a pitch as anybody.
Right.
Or, or, or better a pitch than most, I would say.
I would agree with you on that.
I can't think of anyone because it's such a damaged franchise at this point.
I don't even know what the fuck you do with it.
They had a chance to fit, to, to, to make a legacy sequel.
They fuck, they didn't just fuck it up.
They fucked it up royally.
Royally, if, if for nothing else with the unnecessary blinding of
Ellen Burstyn's character, which now I guess they were with the
big Ray Charles glasses.
Oh God.
Yeah.
And then like, I guess they're going, they were, they were, they were setting
up some sort of, you know, uh, she's a seer, you know, the seer with no eyes,
kind of bullshit or whatever.
Um, I mean, the, the stupid, uh, character missteps they made with her were, were,
were easy fixes, but, but you do that, you know, like, okay, now we're in a
position where if you keep using her and you stay on this track, now she's gotta
be blind and it's stupid, uh, because it has no purpose, um, or you gotta reboot
again, now here's the thing with the possession movie and the exorcist.
If you call it the exorcist and you do a full reboot, it's fucking pointless.
The exorcist is Linda Blair, Burstyn and, uh, the two priests.
Now the two priests obviously are not an option anymore, but that, that
is cinematically the exorcist.
So they could make a remake at this point.
They could say, well, we're going to do a, but you're even fucked there
because I read the book, the movie is the, the author of the book wrote the movie.
William Peter Blatty wrote the movie.
It's identical to the book.
There's like one part in the book that's kind of graphic and it's a very fast
scene that's not in the book that's not in the movie.
Yeah.
I read the book ages ago.
And then there's a, there's a B story line that, that explores the, the, but
the housekeeper who's German a little bit more as a potential suspect in
the killing of the director.
but you obviously wouldn't need in the movie.
You're there to see a demon.
You know, it's not the movie director.
Yeah.
It's the storyline that William Peter Blatty was like, that's not necessary for
the movie, right?
So, um, so what are you going to do?
And so it'd be great if you could, you're going to see the exorcist and then in the
home stretch, do they do that whole thing?
The demons like cast out and everything.
But then at the end and into the room walks the movie director and reveals
that he's the one who did it all.
The exorcism was just like unrelated to the murder.
So, yeah, I mean, so at this point, what are they going to do?
They're going to, they're going to make a possession movie.
They're going to call it the exorcist.
Um, so you really think that they're not going to try to save face and continue on
this trilogy because if you've ever seen that happen before, they pulled it from
the schedule.
Okay.
After you was already called deceiver and coming.
Yeah.
It was already called the exorcist deceiver.
After you texted me and said, David Gordon greens off the project.
I looked up the thing and the news, the story after that was it's been
pulled from the release slate.
That's the, they're done.
That means it's, that means it's over.
Like, yeah, well, I mean, it could mean retooling or something like that, but
like it's pretty crazy to announce a trilogy and not do it.
The only times I can remember that happening were maybe like total bombs
that we don't even think about.
Like, you know, like where they adapt a video game and they announce a trilogy
and it doesn't wind up happening or something, but the exorcist is a pretty
huge property to just start again.
They know that's why I think you bring in the talk to me people and I have it
be, and you're not going to like this Joe, but have it be the exorcist junior,
you know, like what a younger, a younger take on it.
I guarantee that's what they're going to do.
They're going to say, we, we want young people in it.
They're going to want Jenna Ortega in it or something, you know, that's
young people, the movie centered around two 11 year old girls.
How much younger are we going to get?
Look, true.
I mean, people that'll get asses in the seats.
95 year old Ellen Burstin isn't putting asses in the seats.
That's what I'm saying.
They want like hot young people that it's going to be the nineties all over again.
The nineties glut of like six pack abs or they could have a, I mean, Leslie
Sodom jr.
I don't, I don't know that he's a big box office draw, but they could have put,
look, that part could have been Michael B.
Jordan date.
They could have put a lot of, uh, uh, box office bait in that role, uh, that played
even that skewed even a little younger than Leslie does, um, even though he's
not old, but that's not the pro to me.
That's not the problem with the movie.
Look, they've ruined, they, they did everything wrong.
They could have done.
They even down to having two possessed girls, one of whom dies.
Where do you go from here?
Now, where do you go?
You going to have three possessed kids in the next one?
Well, look, there's no, there's no conceivable way that David Gordon
Green did not have to go in and pitch the entire trilogy because they gave him
the reins and also he had had huge success, commercial success with the
Halloween franchise, so he went in there and pitched his take and chances are
they liked it, but now that he's off it, they got to be going in a different
direction and not trusting the guy anymore.
I mean, he immediately went into a Ben Stiller comedy.
He's like, okay, I'm going back to comedy.
I'm out of this.
But the reason Hollywood is so disgraceful is that he's going to get
massive paydays for these following exorcist sequels because he's already
a producer on all three.
So you, you take the reins of this $400 million franchise, run it into the
ground and then he will be handsomely compensated for the next several years
off this franchise that he ruined.
That's Hollywood for you.
I mean, it's rated higher.
It rated higher than, uh, it rated higher than, uh, exorcist critics wise,
exorcist two, and it rated higher than, uh, exorcist beginning, the beginning
or whatever, the prequel, um, I still haven't seen Schraders.
It's terrible, you know, obviously excellent to, I'll take over this
exorcist and to be real, I'll take the three David Gordon Green
Halloweens over the DGG exorcist.
I thought that his exorcist was equally as bad as his two Halloweens.
The Halloween ends to me was, was as egregious as a thing you could ever do.
I, the guy, the guy, look, I'm sorry.
Uh, yeah, you know, I'm a fan of the comedies too.
He should not be allowed to do this anymore.
He doesn't deserve to be able to do this anymore.
He won't, unless, unless it's, you know, I hate to blame old, uh, Green when,
when the captain of all assholes is at the helm of this fucking thing, Jason
Blum, the guy makes shit.
I've said it ad nauseam.
He makes money though.
And I just hate that that's, you know, we're talking, we're talking about
the, uh, on the radio yesterday about the difference between Steven A.
Smith's video that he just put out versus the cat Williams video.
Wait, I'm sorry.
Uh, obviously we need to get into that cat Williams video, the highlight of my year.
But, um, what, what does the Steven A.
Smith, I know who that is, but what was his video?
Uh, I forget who the guy is, but a sports slash right wing pundit guy came out and
said a bunch of stuff about Steven A.
Smith, Steven A.
Smith made a retort video calling the guy a fat piece of shit and all this stuff.
And he's like, and the, the, the Steven A.
Smith thing went viral obviously, but we were, we were watching it and dissecting
it and I said, look, I'm not saying what he did didn't work, but there's a
difference between going viral and, and, and becoming like a classic, like a
legendary, whatever.
And I said, cat Williams is thing will be classic.
Why?
Because he's, as my friend, Bonnie McFarland put it, he's so lyrical,
like cat Williams says everything so poetically without breaking a sweat.
Whereas Steven A.
Smith is clearly a man who's perturbed that's trying to act calm.
And that's the thing with this David Gordon green thing.
It's like, well, he made money.
It's like, yeah, I know he made money, man.
You, the Halloween kills or Halloween ends or exorcist believer could have
been a person taking a, all three of the movies could have been a person taking a
shit on screen for two hours straight.
You still would have broken what you, you still would have significantly surpassed
what you paid with the title alone, regardless of what was on the screen.
And I don't know.
I don't think it's a coincidence that these are all Blumhouse movies, but I
also do have to say if David Gordon green was willing to go back to the well with
them as many times as he did, I can't imagine he's not also to blame.
If it was Jason Blum putting his fingers into it and ruining it, I have a feeling
that David Gordon green or whatever would be like, you know, thank you,
dude, we tried this isn't for me.
Yeah.
Or maybe not.
I don't know.
It's just Christ almighty, man.
Like they're destroying art.
We talked about this when, when this believer movie first came out, the scores
for the original exorcist went down because people went back and watched
it retroactively and like, you know what?
Actually, this isn't that good either.
Fuck this movie.
Now we can't do anything out of fear of what the internet will react with.
Yeah, but it's, it's just, my point is, is this has an effect.
Stop like, stop.
This is P other people's art is not a platform for your fucking agenda.
Stop.
It's just fucking sickening.
This new lady who's directing, I'm getting off in a little tear, excuse me, but this
lady who's directing this new star Wars movie, which is a legacy sequel.
It's the Ray movie.
It's a sequel to the sequel trilogy.
This is in the, the absolute most George Lucas can, and you can be in with star Wars.
This is not a side thing.
This is not whatever.
This is an official sequel.
This is episode 10.
And this fucking dimwit director is out there going, I love making men feel
uncomfortable.
It's about time a woman ran shut the fuck up.
Shut up.
Star Wars is not your podium.
Other people's creations are not your podium.
And if you want to put your, your, your takes and perspectives in fine, do it, but
stop doing it while you tie a cape around your neck.
Stop it.
It's obvious and it's desperate.
There's been plenty of diversity and, and, and, and female empowerment, whatever, in
the star Wars franchise, you're not proving anything.
You're not doing anything new.
It's been done by people that didn't pat themselves too much with it.
They'll take the movie away from her, you know, like they, they, they control the
movie.
She's not in charge of what that movie is going to be about.
Well, that's that I would art in, in that particular franchise, I would argue that
no, they won't because they haven't with every other person they've handed these
reins to and let them run wild.
So, you know, with this exorcist shit, it's like, it's the same fucking thing.
It's like, everybody's got this agenda and what they want.
And look, I get it.
That's part of it is just satisfying the investor demands.
And I just, I, you know, what the takeaway is, is we're unfortunately past a point
where the things that we want to see up on that screen are probable, even possible,
let alone probable.
Um, and that's, this is what this business is now.
And unfortunately we're, we're, we're realizing it a little too late because certain
things will be burnt to a crisp and bastardized.
There's no honor.
And how could there be?
You give some 22 year old a fucking executive making decision job.
You know, I'm supposed to be mad at him because he's not schooled on cinema from
the 50s, 60s or 70s.
You know what I mean?
It's so before his fucking time.
I would say yes.
Uh, if you're a film executive, then yes, you should know your film history and they
don't.
And if you're a TV executive, you should know TV history and they don't.
That I can tell you that firsthand, but, um, well, if they're not being taught though,
where do you get it?
You know what I mean?
We have to, somebody should be there.
They're not passing the teachings down or the lake, you know, it's not at all there.
Yeah.
There really is a, you know, and this is what Scorsese people talk about all the
time, the whole film history, film preservation is kind of going away.
And it seemed like it was going to get better when everybody got into criteria
channel and shit over the pandemic, but, um, it's not, it's not there.
And the biggest issue of all with movies going forward is going to be tick tock.
I noticed my own attention span being destroyed after like three nights
watching tick tocks before bed.
Yeah.
And the reason I turned to them is it shuts off my brain immediately.
It's like, ah, some people listen to news in the background to fall asleep or
whatever, but, um, yeah, it was, I woke up and it was, it was making me crazy.
You know, like your attention span is completely shattered.
I found myself having conversations with people and wanting to just walk away.
Cause I was like, what are we going to talk for five minutes here?
I'm done.
And that's not, it's no way to live your life.
You know, I get bored in seconds talking to people and I'm like, I got it.
I had to shut it down, you know, social media.
And this is a, this is a man in his forties.
Like, you know, recognizing there's a problem, a 16 year old girl.
She says she doesn't have the self -awareness, an 11 year old girl
doesn't have the self -awareness to know it's destroying not just her brain, like
it's destroying mine and America's it's destroying her forming brain at 11.
You know, like you're not even like fully formed and you're
shredding your attention span.
So you think these people are going to go see like killers of the
flower moon when they grow up?
Fuck no.
It's, it's scary to me really.
Um, and you know, they get people go before Congress all the time about
TikTok and they're usually talking about the misinformation and the, uh, you
know, all the anti -Israel stuff and et cetera, and those are all problems too,
but they don't do shit and they'll never do shit until people stop making money
off TikTok, then they'll go, Hey, we ought to shut this down.
But it is, it is weird that Congress, I look, I certainly don't want government
involved in, in the making of art outside of potentially grant giving
grants or whatever, which we don't, we don't do in America.
We don't do that.
Right.
I mean, yeah, you see, you know, some of the best movies every year, a few of
the best small movies each year were funded by, uh, Ireland's lotto.
Ireland, they, their lottery funds, small, wonderful film projects.
It's a beautiful thing.
And other countries do that as well.
We don't do shit.
You'd, yeah, you'd think they'd offer some kind of support to cultivate
the arts, uh, when there's things that are inducted frequently
into the library of Congress.
Yeah.
There's podcasts of Jesus Christ.
There's episodes of Mark Maron's podcasts that are in the library of
Congress for being culturally significant.
I think his, I think his Obama one, maybe.
But, but my point is, is like, it, it, it hits all corners of entertainment.
And we, you know, you see, you know, that was the one thing I had a
blast last summer at the 50 years of hip hop in New York.
I mean, it was just, I saw show after show after show and met icon after
icon of rap groups that I grew up listening to and loving, and it was
an amazing, amazing experience.
The one thing that pissed me off was New York did absolutely nothing.
And it does absolutely nothing to continue to cultivate an environment
that allowed something as brilliant as a musical genre to be born.
It doesn't exist.
New York continues to gouge its citizens and not protect, uh, the
people's livelihood here and people are forced to leave and artistic
endeavors are now growing in greater, uh, magnitude in other cities
and other parts of the country.
And it bothers me.
It's like, you know, you're going to do this big anniversary.
Look at this 50 years.
Look what we did.
And it's like, yes, now what are you doing though?
How does this continue?
Well, it can't.
Yeah, can't.
Uh, and I think that's a shame.
I do, you know, you go to a city like Nashville, they've got artist
housing and things like that.
Um, you know, good luck finding that in New York or LA, unless you, you
know, you win some fucking, you know, some, some lottery and you get into
some home where, you know what I mean?
You know, we saw with the sag thing, the, the sag taken, not, not extending
that health insurance for the people that went on strike for them.
Yeah.
Or, or, or minimally extending it.
It's crazy.
Yeah.
I've said we got, uh, Joe and I got sent a video by a friend, Matt, about, you
know, this guy saying they, they basically wouldn't roll all over his insurance.
They had all, they all sacrificed all this time over the pandemic, not the
pandemic, the, the actor strikes where we couldn't work and the writer
strikes where we couldn't work.
And they're not, they're not renewing people's health insurance.
It's like, cause you have to make a certain amount of money in a year
to maintain health insurance, which is one of the most tricky parts
of being a writer or actor.
And a lot of people don't.
So this guy had cancer, if I remember correctly, and he's just like, I'm fucked.
No, he didn't know.
I don't think he, no, no, no.
Well, I don't know.
I don't think he said what his ailment was.
He's no, no, he says it to be it's Greg.
Well, the guy's Greg.
Well, so we had a heart attack.
Yeah.
I sent the video to you and Matt.
Greg had the widow make.
Greg's an old friend of mine in a comic, but, but he acts and as he says
in the video, he goes, look, man, I'm not just some member of the union.
He's like, I, I'm a working actor.
And he is Greg has been acting in things as guest star roles, as long as I've known
him, uh, and he's a great actor and he's a very funny comic too, but yeah, he had
the widow maker heart attack.
He almost fucking died.
Uh, what, what, what is, what is, uh, the widow maker?
That means like he hit all four quadrants of the heart or something.
It's the one that a Kevin Smith had.
It's the one where it's like, you know, if you have it, you're, you're in,
you're, you're in bad shape.
Yeah.
But, um, I never saw K -19, the widow maker, you see that one?
No, no, it's weird too.
Harrison Ford, uh, Liam Neeson.
I never saw it.
I was like, this looks terrible as a Russian, correct?
I believe so.
Yeah.
That's an, I mean, you want to talk about a lost phase.
That's in that Harrison Ford phase of like, yeah, you're not old.
Firewall.
Yes.
Like he had movies you don't even know exists.
They were just swept off the face of the earth.
Firewall, uh, it started with the downside was six days and seven nights.
Which I recall making money, but that movie fucking a sucked.
That was, that was kind of where, and that was that phase of Harrison
Ford where they were like, anyway, check out Greg Wilson's video.
Uh, it's important, but also, um, that's the phase of
Harrison Ford where, um, he, he's like not, he's too old.
He doesn't want to go back and play the legacy characters again, but he's
too young to return to them yet.
Like, and he's in this weird window of like, we want you to be Indiana
Jones, but you don't want to be right now.
So how about we just put you with Anne Hayes on an island.
He's like, all right.
All right, I'll do it.
And then Anne Hayes was revealed to be Ellen's girlfriend.
I remember that.
And they were like, well, what does this mean for the box office
of six days, seven nights?
It was a huge deal.
Oh, wow.
Isn't that funny?
Yeah.
Pat, take us to that corner.
I'll take you to the corner, Joe.
I watched, uh, the new Netflix picture, good grief.
Okay.
Starring written, produced and directed by Dan Levy, the son of Eugene.
Actually, why does, why do people say Dan Levy?
It's Eugene Levy.
Do people say Levy?
Almost exclusively.
Yeah.
There's a comedian also named Dan Levy or Dan Levy, who I know.
Maybe we've been saying Eugene's name wrong this whole time.
No, it's SCTV at the opening.
They would say Eugene Levy.
Yeah.
I mean, I don't think I'm wrong about that.
So anyway, Dan Levy.
So look, I watched every episode of Schitt's Creek over the pandemic.
It was usually something I would have on kind of in the background.
I didn't find it as knee slapping as everyone did.
I was there for O 'Hara and Levy senior, but I was delighted at first by Dan Levy.
I was like, this guy is really funny, but his vibe gets old fast, real fast.
And by the end of the show, I was finding him pretty annoying.
So I was not too excited about a full dramatic feature film from Dan Levy.
When I saw what it was about, I was like, oh, okay.
Now he's going to do the serious thing so he can get some awards attention.
Oh, boy.
This movie sucks so bad.
I knew when Netflix released it on January 5th.
So that basically means if you released it five days earlier,
it would be an awards contention.
And they didn't.
So you know that they were just like, nah, nah, sorry, Dan, this sucks.
And then by the way, making it impossible for him to post
because the insurrection anniversary is the next day.
Exactly, exactly.
It's terrible.
I mean, so here it is.
Dan Levy's husband dies.
And then him and his two best friends go on a soul -searching trip to Paris
that reveals some hard truths they each needed to face.
The movie tries for comedy, but like a light, a very light comedy
for a while and nothing hits and the drama doesn't hit.
It's building to this like big emotional climax where,
look, I'm in, I'm in a phase now where I freely cry with no shame.
I cry all the time.
It's been building up my whole life.
This thing, if this thing had yanked a handful of my nose hairs out,
it wouldn't have made me cry.
It was nothing.
It was just a nothing movie.
And I sent the ending scene to Joe.
This is not a spoiler, but the movie ends
with a close -up of a painting of Dan Levy.
Then it goes from, so it's Dan Levy himself, the man.
Then it goes to a painting of Dan Levy.
Then it goes to directed by Dan Levy, written and produced by Dan Levy.
Those four cards come up one after the other.
It's like, dude, you've gone up your own ass.
This is ridiculous.
Then I saw a clip of him on whatever, whatever that Bravo guy's name is, Andy Cohen.
And he goes, you know what?
He's like, what made you do this movie?
He goes, I just realized, you know, there had never been a movie ever about friendship.
And it cuts over to what's his face.
And he's going like, hmm, nodding.
He doesn't call him out on it.
There had never been a movie about friendship.
Look this clip up.
He says it and no one calls him out.
Madness.
Oh, my God.
I mean, anyway, the movie is an F. It's absolutely terrible.
Joe, what do you think?
By the way, I love in this culture of calling out privilege in every direction.
Enough with this shit.
This is the privilege that offends me.
This kind of privilege offends me.
When a rich person makes a movie about in heavy quotes, real life.
And the plot of the movie is life is so hard.
I need to get away to Paris to collect my thoughts.
Fuck off.
You want to make a real movie?
Make a real movie about life is hard.
And I have to go back to work three days after the death because if I don't,
I will lose the job that cuts my hours short enough that I don't get health insurance.
That's a real fucking struggle movie.
Fuck off.
I got to make a vacation to Paris.
Oh, God, I can't.
Here's the other clip.
My friend sent me.
I'm going to hit play because I forget what exactly he says.
Tell me your biggest pet peeve.
Uh -huh.
He says arrogance, I guess.
There to promote good grief.
The movie that he's directed stars in ends with a painting of him.
Arrogance.
And then so I have the quote correct.
He says, I've just never seen a movie where friendship is the center of the story.
What the fuck is he talking about?
Like, weirdly, what popped into my head immediately was like,
it's because I'm working with Appetel, but like every Appetel movie is about friendship.
Superbad.
I love you, man.
All these, all those movies he produced are about male friendship.
That's, that's one example, you know, Mikey and Nikki, you know, that if I just,
I can name almost any movie and you can say, no, that's about friendship.
And it's the center of the story.
Right.
Superbad.
No, I said Superbad first.
Oh, you did?
That's the first movie I said.
Yes.
I didn't hear you say that.
I said three movies.
Relax, relax.
Booksmart.
Yes.
Yes, Booksmart.
Okay.
I've got, we're not going to do, well, I know we're not going to do,
are we doing Maestro or no?
I'll save it if we're going to do it.
No?
No, we're not going to do it.
Maestro, starring Bradley Cooper.
As Leonard Bernstein or Stein.
And Carey Mulligan as Felicia.
I'm blanking on Felicia's last name.
I was unfamiliar with, you know, Felicia, who does she play?
Oh, for God's sakes.
Where is the IMDB?
Montalegre.
You play the wife of Leonard Bernstein and Leonard Bernstein is a closeted gay man.
Montalegre, I guess is how you say that.
Who was an actress of the time, but I think more of a theater actress.
That's why I was not familiar.
Anyway, look, the movie is very, very well directed by Bradley Cooper.
It is extraordinarily acted by the two stars I have mentioned.
Everybody in the movie is very good.
And overall, I enjoyed it, I guess.
I just didn't understand what the point of it all was.
I didn't really get what my big takeaway was supposed to be.
It's a movie about a man, to contradict Pat, he's not really closeted gay.
He's kind of openly gay at a time when you're not really supposed to be,
but you weren't able to be.
And it's very daring of him, but they don't highlight that.
He's married to a woman who he is attracted to, and who he has many children with,
and who he loves almost unconditionally.
But they don't highlight that.
She says to him, I accept you, whoever you are, and then doesn't.
But they don't get into why or where that turn in her perspective with him is.
He is a man that is single -handedly responsible for modern Broadway musicals,
and the form and sound that they take.
They don't really highlight that.
The thesis of the movie is that the artist is burdened with selfishness.
And in order for the artist to continue to create at his greatest capacity,
he must act only for himself and live only for himself.
But they don't highlight that, meaning if you bat an eye or go get a glass of water
during this movie, you won't even know that he wrote West Side Story.
They make a big deal out of the fact that he is.
That's so weird.
I agree, Joe.
I'm like, okay, so we're doing a biopic, essentially.
When it ended, I said, did I hear a single note or a mention of West Side Story?
And I don't think I did.
It's without question his biggest work.
It's what everyone would know him as.
He did a TV show where he taught music, essentially, on television.
They talk in the movie of the importance of the TV show.
They never show you any of it.
There are clips on YouTube that are like,
this is the most important three minutes you could ever watch about music.
They don't highlight any of this.
My guess is he was like, I'm not going to do a traditional biopic.
I'm going to do an art film.
Fine.
But you have to hit some beats of the story.
We don't know everything about Leonard Bernstein.
If you're doing a story on who's somebody we know every little detail about,
that's different.
We don't know anything about this man.
You can't just paint this esoteric portrait of him because we don't know who he is.
It's an interesting...
It kind of reminds me of the Dahmer movie with...
What's his name?
Jeremy Renner?
Jeremy Renner.
It's not great.
Again, it's well directed.
He's amazing in the performance, but you're like, what's going on here?
The director said, well, I wasn't going to make a movie that exploited the violent aspects.
I wanted to get into the head of who he was.
It's like, okay, this is a much better movie than Dahmer.
But I thought to myself, if you're going to make a movie about the fallout of selfishness
and the burden of the artist acting selfishly in order to create at his best,
you have to then show the apex.
You have to show what came from it.
So then the audience is challenged with,
it's up to me to decide if that was worth it or not.
They just don't really do that.
They make him out overall to seem like a side...
He seems like a decent guy.
Even though he's fucking other people that aren't his wife and whatever,
she says, you can do whatever you want.
But then she's not okay with it and they don't explain why she suddenly isn't okay with it.
There's a really good scene where she's like, the scene they're showing is the Oscar.
She's like, you're going to die a lonely old queen.
Say it again and cut out.
There's the scene they're showing is what?
The scene they're showing is like the Oscar clip is where she's yelling at him
and she's great and she's incredible in the movie.
But she's like, you're going to die a lonely old queen and like screaming about all this stuff.
I hear you totally.
I'm like, so was this an open marriage or not?
Was it that she was okay with it and over time she decided she wasn't?
Fine.
These are all interesting things but pick a lane and tell us the story.
They didn't do that.
And then later she's having an affair and you don't know if it's a result of him
or if they had this agreement all along.
And then she even says when her daughter's like,
Mother, tell us about your boy.
And the mom's like, you hear enough about your father's affairs.
You don't need to hear about mine.
It's just a bit confusing.
I wonder how much of it is accurate and how much of it is hearsay
because it's funny when you watch, again, Cooper is really good
but he does play an actor -y version of Leonard Bernstein.
If you watch videos of Leonard Bernstein in his older years,
he does not talk as if he has no nasal passages.
That may just be how Bradley Cooper could talk with that giant prosthetic schnauzon.
Yeah, it's a good point.
So the movie I would say is worth a watch.
I'm just not saying, oh God, it's a big actor -wise I would say.
They're both in contention for awards.
And even directing -wise, he really did a beautiful job directing this thing.
It's very, very well directed.
I think the script is where there's a little weakness.
There's also this thing, and this is the last I'll say,
they talk in Broadway -speak of the 50s and 60s.
But then they also mumble everything.
I couldn't understand the fucking word anybody was saying.
I had to put the subtitles on.
Then, Pat, you said you had to do the same.
Yeah, there's a lot of the, how dare you?
I never told you where you were going.
And then they're also doing elusive dialogue.
They're mumbling, talking in a weird affectation,
and then doing elusive dialogue where they're not explaining everything.
So it's a little hard at times to be like, wait, what happened?
Hold on.
Oh wait, that's the guy he was fucking, but that guy's got a kid in it?
All right, okay, shit.
All right, so anyway.
And I'll just segue into my next one, which will be Priscilla.
Unless I have to, I don't think I've done it.
But Priscilla is a good example that I could -
You didn't do this?
I did.
If I didn't, then okay.
I don't know.
Sorry.
I'm just going to compare it to Maestro now.
You can do an esoteric,
you the audience know enough about this story that you can fill in the gaps.
We're just going to kind of tell you an artistic impressionistic version of the story.
That's what Sofia Coppola did with Priscilla.
The difference is, we know everything there is to know about Elvis.
And if we don't, we just saw that Elvis movie that told us everything we need to know about Elvis.
So that's a legend.
That's somebody who, there's no one on earth who doesn't know who Elvis is.
You can do that sort of like loosey goosey adaptation of his life,
because we can fill in the gaps.
When it's somebody we don't know, you can't do that.
And this year, I've been watching almost all the Oscar movies twice,
because I'm like, am I just in a bad mood and hating everything?
Because I read these raves,
and I don't know if the publicists are working overtime or what,
but I watch movie after movie and I'm like, look, at best, that's pretty good or average.
So I'm like, is quality diminished or am I just an asshole who hates everything now?
And that's always the question I'm asking myself.
And yet, when I go back to these movies and watch them a second time,
more often than not, I'm like, no, I was right.
That's not great.
I rewatched Terms of Endearment, which Joe, I'll recommend to you again.
Terms of Endearment and Star is Born should be really on your list.
That's why Maestro let me down, is because that rewatch of Star is Born,
I was like, this is a fucking amazing movie.
Terms of Endearment is incredible.
It won best picture, it won best actress for McClane and best supporting for Nicholson.
I used to think of Nicholson as being ancient in this movie.
He's like three years older than me, completely bald, giant gut hanging over his underwear.
You know, it's crazy.
Nicholson is so funny in this.
You're so caught up in the Debra Winger and her mom story, Shirley McClane.
I think you, as somebody with a mom that you sometimes battle, Joe,
you would absolutely love this movie, guaranteed.
Shirley McClane is incredible in it.
It is one of the best character studies of all time.
The opening scene, I can't, and I've read Larry McMurtry's book, which is also excellent,
but James L. Brooks did such a bang up job and talk about a movie like Maestro,
where it starts when Debra Winger's like 16 and then four scenes later or whatever,
she's married to Jeff Daniels and you're like, oh, okay.
He trusts the audience to know that time has passed.
They keep doing that, like time passes, a few years pass, a few months past.
That's an example of kind of trusting the audience to go along with the story.
They give you enough though to follow it, unlike Maestro.
The opening scene, Shirley McClane's daughter Debra Winger is in the crib crying.
You hear Albert Brooks's voice playing the father.
You don't see him, but nice to hear his voice.
And Shirley, the check on the daughter because she's an obsessive smothering mother
and the daughter is sound asleep.
And Albert Brooks is like, honey, she's okay.
She's sleeping.
Please leave her alone.
She gets into the crib with the daughter and keeps like poking her and touching her
until she wakes up and starts sobbing.
Then Shirley McClane goes back to Albert Brooks and she goes, she's okay.
She's better now.
It's like she wanted to wake her up and get a reaction out of her
to know she's okay instead of just letting her at peace.
That little scene sets up the whole movie so beautifully.
It's a mother and daughter as complex a version of that story as we've ever seen.
Winger is incredible.
It's a shame she was such a tyrant in Hollywood because I really love Debra Winger
and have always been very attracted to Debra Winger as well.
It's the best Shirley McClane's ever been ever been.
And I'm a massive fan of the apartment and many of her movies.
She's so great.
Nicholson is so great.
I sent Joe a clip of the movie where Nicholson takes her out on a date
and he's like, you need a lot of drinks.
And she goes to break the ice and he goes to kill the bug that you have up your ass.
Hilarious.
He's just great in the movie.
Got a scene where they like crash the car into the ocean
and as they're trying to get up, he shoves his hand into her bra and grabs her tit.
It's like he's just a monster.
But he's funny and charming and in the end he reveals a hidden sweetness.
It's a perfect movie.
I don't know what else to say.
I absolutely love it.
I got the new 4K which looks spectacular.
And as I told Joe, which she knew I believe,
but Burt Reynolds was offered the Jack Nicholson part
and turned it down for which one of these shitty movies, Joe?
Do you remember?
Well, he might have turned it down for Smokey and the Bandit,
which how dare you say shitty.
It might have been Hooper, which once again, how dare you say shitty.
You know how they'd only say shitty if it was shitty.
And it might have been Sharky's Machine, which again, how dare you say shitty.
But it was one of those three.
It wasn't.
It was one of those three.
Yeah.
No, it wasn't.
I think.
It wasn't?
Shit.
Now when I search my texts, it doesn't bring up stuff.
I just texted you about Burt Reynolds.
So I type in Reynolds and nothing comes up in my phone.
I'm getting tired of it.
Movie he did instead of Terms of Endearment.
Worst Google I've ever done.
Stroker Ace.
NASCAR movie.
Burt Reynolds turned down the role of astronaut Garrett Breedlove to do this film.
Stroker Ace.
Yeah, like not even remembered.
But I've heard the story like about every movie we've mentioned.
The official internet documented is Stroker Ace.
But Reynolds would have been great in it, too, by the way.
But I mean, it's Nicholson's movie and the supporting cast of the thing.
Like I said, Jeff Daniels, Danny DeVito.
Such a strong, strong movie.
Love it.
Joe?
I'm only this will be my last one.
Alice doesn't live here anymore.
I feel like it's connected to the film we're doing today.
Early Scorsese.
You connect Alice doesn't live here anymore to The Holdovers?
It's very much an Alexander Payne type of movie, I would say.
It's OK.
It's fine.
I mean, the performances are great.
It's not really a riveting story.
It's fine.
It's a woman whose husband dies.
The husband is awful.
So it's kind of hard to share her heartache when he dies because he's awful.
You're kind of expecting her to rejoice that she's been freed from this prison.
And she's not, which I guess is kind of part of the point.
She's got a dream to become a singer.
She ends up being a diner waitress after a run in with another awful man played by Harvey Keitel.
He's excellent in it.
Ellen Burstyn is excellent.
Oh, yeah, the exorcist.
There we go.
This is connected to everything today.
Ellen Burstyn is excellent in it.
Chris Christopherson is very good.
The scenes that are in Mel's Diner that the sitcom was based on are,
for me, the most fun scenes in the movie.
It's kind of funny.
The movie almost plays like the Phantom Menace of the Alice sitcom.
It's like if you grew up on Alice like I did, then you go back and watch this.
It's like a prequel to how it all begins.
But it's fine.
It's a fine movie.
I don't quite understand why people love it to the extent that they do,
but I also didn't see it in a timely fashion.
I'm watching it in 2023.
It very much reminds me of a Harold and Maude style film
with a little less of a wild concept, obviously.
But The Holdovers, our film today, opens with the title card, the production slates,
all of that stuff is all throwback to that era of filmmaking.
And then the film itself is shot in a grainy, I don't know what the millimeter is,
but The Holdovers is clearly supposed to be presented like one of these late 60s,
early 70s dramedies that were really driven by characters and dialogue and a very simple story.
And that's what Alice Doesn't Live Here Anymore is.
The kid is great.
I don't know his name, but he's a really funny actor.
Jodie Foster's in it.
She's great.
Everybody's great.
And the movie is entertaining enough that I enjoyed watching it.
It's fine.
It's like the Alice sitcom.
I never saw the Alice sitcom.
I love Alice Doesn't Live Here Anymore.
I don't think it's one of Scorsese's best,
but it's only because he's made so many classics, but I really love the movie.
I'm not saying it to challenge.
I'm really asking, do you love it or do you just like it?
What do you love about it, I guess, is what I'm...
Because people have said my whole...
Not my whole life, but a lot of my adult life.
Oh my God, it's a masterpiece.
But I'm like, okay, why though?
I get that the acting is really good.
It is really good.
But why?
What is the thing that hits your soul about this movie where you're like, oh my Lord?
I mean, I think it comes down to Burson and her son.
I mean, I love a character study.
I don't know if you ever saw Tender Mercies with Robert Duvall, but
I like a little movie with little trues, little...
I don't mind it.
It is Scorsese and I think people probably overrate it and remember the movie more
because Scorsese did it, but I love it.
And I rewatched it over the pandemic.
So I mean, my review is up to date, but I dig it.
I love Christopherson in it too.
I think it's funny and sweet and I dig it.
I love character studies, like The Holdovers to that, which here we go.
Here we go, baby.
The Holdovers.
Take us through it, Pat.
Alexander Payne started out his career and I was like, this guy is my jam.
He's my new favorite.
I thought Citizen Ruth was okay.
And then Election is a modern comedy masterpiece.
About Schmidt is better than Election.
Sideways is roughly as good as About Schmidt.
And then things went awry, in my opinion.
I didn't like The Descendants.
I thought Downsizing is one of the worst movies I've ever seen.
And you know, I know he's made others.
Nebraska was fine, but boring.
I just thought, okay, the guys lost it.
Then I see he's doing The Holdovers and somebody else wrote it.
I'm like, all right, let's see what this is about.
And what it is about, it reunites him with Paul Giamatti.
And what a fucking thrill.
He's the reason for the season, reason for the movie to see him back.
You know, I haven't seen Billions.
I hear it's great, but I don't want Giamatti as a regular in a series.
I like him coming into movies and playing different types of characters.
It's great to have him back in something like this.
The movie is at a prep school up near Boston in the Northeast.
I forget exactly where, but they're at a prep school.
And there are students who are left behind for the Christmas holiday,
who don't have anything to do for the Christmas break, so they stay at school.
These are very small group of kids, including kind of our co -hero,
which is this young man who has an odd relationship with his parents.
We'll find out why later on.
By the way, his only movie ever, this kid.
Yeah, and he's great.
He really is.
Yeah, he's awesome.
And Divine Joy Randolph, who I have loved in everything I've ever seen her in.
I absolutely love this woman.
Those are the three players.
She's the cook at the school.
Giamatti is the teacher who they asked to stay behind and watch the boys.
And we got our main boy.
So at some point, a guy finds out they're stuck at school.
The rich parent flies in with a helicopter to fly these kids out on a Christmas fun time.
And our hero can't contact his parents to get permission,
so he has to stay with Giamatti and Divine.
They're the three left at school.
That's the plot.
They're the holdovers, and more happens from there.
It is very much a character study.
It is about the ways in which these rejects relate to each other, the ways in which they connect.
This is one I watched twice because I was really let down.
I thought Alexander Payne and Paul Giamatti.
I saw the trailer.
I was like, oh, wow, I'm going to fucking love this movie.
My expectations were too high.
It's a very slight movie in a good way, but it's slight.
You know, at the end, and I'm not really going to spoil much here,
but the things that come out at the end of this movie are so minor.
And I guess this was just what Joe was talking about with Alice doesn't live here anymore.
But I wanted something more, really.
I thought when I wasn't crying at the end of this thing, I was like, man, if they had
pushed this a little further, this could have been like a classic Christmas tearjerker.
And they didn't go for it.
Maybe Alexander Payne is like, I don't do schmaltz or whatever.
And I get that.
The ending is, is cute.
You know, I love Giamatti driving off and drinking the stolen brandy and,
you know, his resolution is great.
He stands up for the kid.
They all kind of help each other and get through the holiday.
There's a lot to like, but the opening scene of this movie is Paul Giamatti.
I have talked about this movie on the show.
They cut from a thing of Preparation H to him.
Did we fuck up today?
Maybe, but that's fine.
Because I remember saying this, I think.
But they cut from this thing of Preparation H to him to introduce him, like making him
obviously an asshole.
It's a great little visual gag.
And the first 15 minutes is Giamatti being an asshole to students.
And that's what the trailer mostly was.
That stuff is fantastic.
It's just, I don't know.
It's a B plus to me.
I liked it a lot.
But I think there was an A in here, for sure.
And it just doesn't quite hit for me.
But Giamatti's great.
The three leads are great.
And it's a very enjoyable movie that I certainly didn't mind watching twice.
The music and the scenes of Giamatti, like walking around Boston in the snow
with like folk music playing, they bored me on the first viewing.
And I liked them a lot more on the second.
It really does create a mood.
And I did like the movie.
Yeah, like I said, well, even if you did talk about this, we're able to both talk
about it now.
It is very much a throwback to a Harold and Maude style film.
And that's what he made here.
It's like what Tarantino does.
He used 70s style credits and everything.
Like a full, I'm going to make this a 70s movie.
I'll point out that I said that already, just as you jumped at me.
Because I said super bad after you did.
Anyway, no, but I actually went into this with lower expectations.
Because when I saw the trailer, I had the same high hopes that Pat did.
And then Pat, when you saw it the first time and said, you know, I got a screener.
I was like, all right, I'm going to watch this.
I probably won't like it that much.
And then found myself quite swept into it.
This is one of the few movies where I'm not going to spoil how it ends
or what happens in the end.
Because I do think that one of the most important redeeming qualities of this type of film
is wondering where these characters are going to end up in the end.
I thought first and foremost, this very much was a return to form for Alexander Payne.
I agree with Pat's assessment of his recent works.
I hated The Descendants.
To this day, I don't like
Shailene Woodley.
I can't stand her.
It's not her fault.
She was supposed to be an asshole in the movie and she achieved it.
But I mean, I hated that movie so fucking much.
I hated it.
And this to me, and by the way, that was a movie that tried to be a tear -jerker
and tried to, you know, wring you dry of every emotion you could ever have.
And I don't think it did a good job.
This I felt like was maybe going to move in that direction.
You're not quite sure.
You're waiting to see.
But I thought that this was very relatable.
I thought it was very funny at times.
It's not as funny consistently through as like sideways is, but it's funny.
I thought it was, I loved the characters.
There's nothing better than Giamatti playing a drunk misanthrope.
Like that's what you want.
That is his like when De Niro plays a gangster.
You're like, that is Giamatti's thing.
Can I say the fact that he's always drinking and never appears even slightly drunk
is also perfect because he's an alcoholic.
You're not Arthur stumbling around when you're an alcoholic.
You can drink a bunch and you don't really show.
So he's awesome in it.
And his final dressing down of the headmaster, the penis cancer line is classic.
You did spoil the end.
No, Joe, we've revealed huge secrets on this show of major movies.
I know.
Do you remember?
And that is a minor.
No one's enjoyment of this movie is going to be affected.
No, but I literally just said that he tells the guy he's an ass.
I know.
But I literally just said this is one of the few times I don't want to spoil the movie
That's not spoiling the movie, Joe.
Well, you said the final dressing down of the headmaster.
Now when you watch it, you're going to know when they set up in the immediate beginning,
when he's got tension with the headmaster that he's going to get his strike back.
We have spoiled movies with massive twists, casually.
I know.
Casually.
This is a peacock, almost like a sitcom of a movie.
I'm aware.
You don't want to spoil it?
Fine, I do.
And I don't think that spoiled shit about this movie.
Nobody's going to say this movie was spoiled.
It's like saying Senate of a Woman was great, especially the end when he goes in and sticks
up for the kid.
It's like, all right, well, I guess the whole point of this movie is this isn't the Avengers.
You're not going, oh, and then do they win the fight?
You're going, is this guy going to become a human being throughout this film or not?
Is this kid going to straighten out and do the right thing by the end or not?
Is this woman who's grieving terribly good?
I feel like that's all the investment you can put into this movie is
where do these characters end up?
That's my opinion, which is why.
And we still don't know on several of them.
We know that Paul Giamatti has an exchange with a headmaster
that's been used in the trailers and on TikTok constantly.
The whole scene's playing on TikTok.
The movie has been on Peacock for weeks.
I can't engage this any longer.
We've spoiled so much in this show that the holdover is being spoiler free.
But I understand we've spoiled, which is why I said the exact statement.
This is one of the few times I don't want to spoil something.
All right, I disagree.
And I spoiled one tiny moment.
All right.
I think it's a massive moment in the film and it's one of the funniest scenes.
I apologize from the bottom of my heart for ruining your enjoyment of the holdovers.
I didn't say that.
Listen, also, many, many practically jumped through the Zoom camera
because I dared say super bad after you had mentioned it.
Let's not act like I'm being crazy.
Completely different.
Many people do not watch or listen to this podcast until they watch the movies.
The people who care about spoilers, they all say,
I haven't listened to this one yet because I haven't watched the movie.
How about you say, sorry, dude.
Sorry, didn't think I was spoiling it.
I'm going to apologize to you?
Oh, God.
Why would I apologize to you?
Because I was trying to not spoil whatever.
It doesn't matter.
Do whatever the hell you want.
I'll do whatever I want.
You do whatever you want.
This is two solo podcasts, people.
We just happen to be on the same show together.
I have not spoiled the ending of the holdovers either.
That's just not true.
OK.
My only point is I know that we spoil things.
I'm not saying you've ruined the movie.
I'm just saying when I went out of my way to be like,
hey, this is one thing where I really want to kind of protect the ending of the film.
And then you bring up a key moment from the ending of the film.
I'm like, OK, well, I guess we're you know, I was trying to avoid that.
That's all.
I don't think it's I'm being crazy.
I'm just I'm saying it was it was my goal as we discussed this
to not give anything in that sequence away
because I feel like there's so much mystery as you watch it.
In fact, there's even well, I don't want to say because I was spoiled anymore.
Anyway, that's that's that's my only point.
That's my only.
All right. And I think I wish the movie had been more surprising.
I think it's a very paint by numbers.
Everything you think is going to happen is what happens.
Well, I would disagree.
I think you could say that about about Schmidt.
I think you could say that about sideways.
I think you could say that about election.
I think what makes Alexander Payne films great when they are great
and all three of those are great.
And this one is is potentially great is there is a 10 to.
Not even I would say about a 10 minute coda on each one of those films
where in this one included where you hit a point in the story where you go.
OK, I guess that's it.
And then there is you go a little bit further with the characters and it leads you.
It gives you some resolution while not answering every question I would say.
About Schmidt is the perfect example.
Well, actually sideways to sideways ends, essentially.
When he's drinking the wine in the burger place,
the bottle he has saved for his whole life or whatever the fuck it is.
And then he finds out that this wife that he can't get over this ex -wife is pregnant.
And he finds out at his best friend's wedding
after this trip of self discovery and all these things.
And he's drinking wine in that in that burger place.
And you're like, this is it for this guy.
Like, this is where he ends up.
Like he has nothing.
And then there's the sequence where he drives back to wine country
and knocks on Virginia Madsen's door about Schmidt.
He confronts the daughter final scene of all time.
Yeah, he confronts the daughter.
He you know, it all blows up in his face.
It's a disaster.
He drives off.
You're like, that's it.
And then he gets home and you have that sequence.
I forget what happens at the end of election.
There's like there's like there's a coda.
I don't there's a coda where it shows you that Matthew Broderick has become like
an insane person.
He's like, you know, running through the streets throwing.
I think he throws an ice cream cone at a car or something like that.
And it goes into like Tracy Flicks, you know, what her it's one of those like
we cut forward a few years kind of endings.
So so this this I would say also does that thing.
It felt like classic Alexander Payne to me.
I'm surprised he didn't write it.
I didn't I didn't realize it.
Well, you know, I did know he didn't write it.
I guess I didn't know that he wrote the other ones.
What's weird is that Giamatti when he whenever he's interviewed about it,
he goes, you know, Alexander kept saying, I'm writing something for you.
I'm writing something for you.
And then there's a different screenwriter credit to the movie.
I mean, he might have done a rewrite or something, but.
Were you it's only credited to one writer.
Were you surprised that this was not based on a book?
I would have bet my life that this was based on some old book.
Yes.
And mostly because Alexander Payne always adapts books.
He's been even about Schmidt was a book.
So an election.
So yes.
But yeah, I mean, that's that's the thing to love about it.
It's an original movie at a time when those are in very short supply.
It's a small movie when those are in very short supply.
It's an actor's character's movie when those are in short supply.
So I liked it very much.
And I'm saying this not to bring it back.
But when you post this show.
Yes.
But don't listen to this until you've seen the holdup.
All right.
There we go.
See, we always end up on the same page, people.
That's our Alexander Payne coda to this podcast.
We learn that everything's OK.
Daddy and daddy fight sometimes and we get better.
It wasn't even a fight in the old days.
My two dads.
In the old days, this would have been a non -postable episode.
By the way.
We had two that didn't air.
Just the one.
I'm proud to say.
I feel like one that we started over, though.
One that we're like, OK, let's just start this over.
There have been many start overs.
But but I honestly I don't think because of fights, it's usually we start
talking about something that involves a delicate issue.
And we get to a point where we say this, this can't be.
Yeah.
Here's what's very interesting, Pat.
This guy that wrote the holdovers.
It's the only if you I don't think you said this about it.
It's the only movie he's ever written.
Did you say that?
No, it's the only movie he's ever written.
He's only written television.
But the type of television he's written is interesting.
He he wrote a couple episodes.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
He wrote 67.
He produced 67 episodes of Just Shoot Me.
He wrote 11.
Oh, wow.
He wrote 11 episodes.
Well, when you're when you're a producer, like I'm a producer,
then just every episode you work on it, it says you're a producer.
But yeah, if he's a sitcom guy, that's very inspiring.
He was at the helm.
He created Kitchen Confidential starring Bradley Cooper.
I remember it well.
The Anthony Bourdain Story Fox sitcom.
That's great.
As I am learning, it is so hard to cross over from the sitcom world.
And I loved I love hearing that.
Well, I also love hearing that one of the Sopranos,
the greatest writers started on Sister Sister.
That's always made me very happy.
Which guy?
I'd have to look it up.
He worked on Don't Trust the Bee in Apartment 23.
Interesting.
All right.
The Holdovers, folks.
My hog is up for it.
I would recommend it.
I think it's worth a watch.
Yeah, my hog's up.
I'd say or but maybe after a big meal where I'm not 100 % sure about it
as we head into sex.
But it's a B plus for sure.
I enjoyed it.
We will be back, folks, with a very special episode
where we discuss our 10 favorite sitcom characters of all time.
So get ready for that.
Yeah, if you're listening, which you are,
I'll be at the depending on when this goes up,
it's either tonight or tomorrow night.
Sorry.
It's either tomorrow night or tonight.
Meaning if this goes up on Friday, it's tomorrow.
And if it goes up on Saturday, it's tonight.
I'm at the Gramercy Theater in New York City.
January 13th, one show only 8 p .m.
Please get some tickets.
Come on out.
They're running low.
I'm at the Comedy Mothership next week in Austin, Texas.
Those are close to sold out.
So get your ticket if you're coming.
And then I'm on into many other cities.
February moving forward.
Nashville, Los Angeles, San Diego, elsewhere.
Get your tickets for all of these events at joderosa .com.
And if you're in New York, come to Joey Roses, joeyrosesnyc .com.
Seven days a week, people, serving sandwiches and drinks.
We'll see you next time.
And we'll see you in hell.