I'll see you in hell.
Welcome to We'll See You In Hell.
The only podcast you can turn to when you need to know what's going on with those
genre films you like so much, I'm Joe DeRosa, and I'm Patrick Walsh.
Good morning everybody, I've got shit on my face this morning, I showed up late
to the recording. Usually I'm going off Missouri time because it's where my
parents and my family are, so I deduct two hours, but I instead should have
deducted three, starting it, nine, I thought ten, a huge hub up, an unspeakable
tension creeping into the record this morning. You can't see us, Pat came in
looking like Christopher Lloyd, any Christopher Lloyd character. Yeah I mean it's
not like I do a makeover for myself before these things, but usually I touch
a comb or splash and water on my face. It's fine, we'll get through it.
Today's first episode, oh boy, I'm awake and I can't get it out. We're reviewing
the Creepshow animated holiday special today, but more on that later there's
plenty to get to before it is. And happy Halloween everybody. This is the mid
top in November 15th. We're recording this on November 10th. Gotcha. So we're about
a week out before this actually comes out. So actually Jesus, this comes out on
the eve of almost Thanksgiving. That's yeah, that's true. That's insane. Well,
not Thanksgiving's like the 24th or something, right? I feel like it's early this
year, now the 26th, you're right. Okay, we got a little ways. All right. It's
always the 4th Thursday of November. I'm assuming for December, like December
1st and December 15th, those episodes will sort of be a criss -cross of
Thanksgiving and Christmas episodes. Would you say a criss -cringle cross? Yeah. Yeah.
I would say okay. Criss -cringle makes you want to jump, jump. Yeah, we'll try to
find we're kind of scraping the bottom of the barrel for Christmas movies. Christmas
carry movies we haven't done, but we'll try to find one at least. I mean, I
wouldn't mind just doing some Christmas movies, you know? Sure. Like a straight up,
you know, I mean, it's a shame we didn't do it last year. I really would have
loved to shit all over because it sucked. I might have actually shit on it.
Otherwise, we should have reviewed that Fox Christmas Carol last year. What a
dog show. Oh, yeah, FX one. Yeah, but they're actually doing a live stream
Christmas Carol this year. Like when they do those musicals that they stream
live. Yeah, where it's like Kristen Chenoweth as Scrooge. It's not even Kristen
Chenoweth. It's like, it'll be like AOC. Yeah, exactly. I saw and I sent this to
Joe. I mean, I couldn't believe my eyes. Netflix has an all black Christmas movie,
not a Christmas Carol, coming out starring Forest Whitaker, who everybody associates
with holiday cheer. Right. I've never seen the man smile before. Right. I want to make
sure that I get it 100 % right. The tagline is all about the music, magic, and
melanin for me. I thought to myself, is somebody doing a joke that's going to get
them in trouble? It's the Netflix PR team. It's all about the magic, music, and
melanin for me. Melanon being the pigment that gives your skin its color. Yeah,
Netflix, their PR team at this point is doing a Trump style thing where I'm like, are they
trying to throw this right now? They're really taking some crazy swings, man. Between this
and Cucuties, it's like, what are you guys doing, man? Yeah, I don't know. And I also like,
this is the time where we're normally getting screeners and so forth. You know, the one time
of year that I really, it's like every, every time's like Christmas for me, you open up
the mail and you get those new movies that are coming out. We got nothing this year. I got
nothing. I didn't receive one screener, but not a digital link to anything, nothing, nothing.
Yeah, the person like a link to stream season four of Jack Ryan on laptop, like you usually
get. And then, and then I guess this is a new psycho, but the movie theater chains have
are going to Congress for emergency bailouts now. The nerve. Yeah, I mean, I want to see movie
theater chains stay open to, but guys, maybe emergency bailouts for the middle class of America.
Sure. Not the guys that have been grout gouging us on pretzel bites for the last 30 years. No, I mean,
I'm selfishly rooting for them to come back, of course, but I think a lot of people are very upset
with the way the money has been handled. And I think a lot of the relief money that we're
going to be learning has been going directly into these people's pockets, which is, which sucks.
And obviously, I'd rather the movie theaters get it then. Republican leaders who are already
wealthy, but I mean, yeah, there's, there's a, there's a big problem in this country. It's a little,
it's a little crazy. Before we get to off the subject of terrible like marketing and tag lines and
things. Yeah. I'm a big audible fan. By the way, that movie is called jingled jangle. If you wanted to,
it really is. Go ahead, Joe. Sorry. I am a big audible fan and I went on this morning to see what was
cooking. And they have the rest in peace, Alex Trebek. They had Alex Trebek's autobiography on the
front page. And here's the header. Ready for this? Yeah. What is dot, dot, dot, really sad news.
Question mark. Alex Trebek is Pat. It's like, guys, maybe you don't get clever with the memorial
post. Yeah. I love it. When they think they're being clever. And then there's 900 posts that are the
exact same thing. Well, yeah, that's the thing too. It's not even like any 12 year old would have
thought of that jeopardy joke. But it's just like for Christ's sake, guys, it's just not in good taste.
No, I love Trebek, you know, sad to see him go. The, the people they're already, they're floating
George Stepanopoulos. It's like just fuck off and the show. George, the interview guy from Canada.
No, no, George Stepanopoulos is a very boring political pundit type guy. Okay. I'm thinking around
since I was kid thinking of who's that Greek guy? My friend, I mean, he's a friend of a friend.
I've never met him. He's a Greek guy. He interviews like all the musicians and celebrities and can't.
He's from Canada. Uh, the guy that does the black and white pretentious interviews.
So no, no, he's good. You'd like this guy. It's something like, well, anyway, it's not him.
He'd be good. I saw that the other day. It's like, even though it's probably just a man sitting down
doing a fun interview with somebody. He does them shot like in David Fincher, black and white.
And it makes me so angry to see the people that he's talking to in this format, like with beautiful
cinematography. And the funniest one I've seen is no offense to the man who everyone knows as a friend.
Uh, was Pete Holmes being interviewed in like beautiful black and white. And I was like, this is
absolutely insane. And Pete's like, yeah, so then I, you know, I went up for the first time
in Boston or something. You know, it's the stand -up interviews get this like as if they're talking
to a foreign dictator. You know, it's always like, and what then? It's always the same story that
I went up. Then I started talking about myself doing personal jokes. And then I then I
something caught on. If you could walk us through the inception of the wash, my damn towels bit.
Yeah. And it's like the thing everybody made, they have different people on every night. And you're like,
there's something about the format makes it seem like, oh, shut up because it's black and white.
The worst one of those that I saw was Dak Shepherd, who I was already not a fan of.
Uh, I've said on the show before, if I had to rank most boring people in America, I mean,
Dak Shepherd and Kristen Bell are right swinging up the top of that list for me. Now,
this Dak Shepherd relapsing, do anything for his, uh, excited. It makes me like him better,
but he's one of those guys that like he, that's what made me not like. I mean, he talks about his,
his like, you know, his drug days, whatever. Uh, and he's another one of those, they're one of my
favorite no effects lyrics is they have a song called California drought and it's about him having
to dry out from drugs and alcohol because he's getting too out of control. And he said,
the line is he's talking about AA and he goes, but now I got to listen to a 20 minute story that's
just a rumor. And I'm like, yeah, exactly, man, I hate these stories that these sober people tell
that we're like, there's no way that's true. Yeah. You would be dead. Every person that did that
was dead. And he just had stories like that where it was like, you know, Friday night I had to get
two cases of beer, three bottles of jack, two eight balls, two bottles of diet pills, six cartons of
cigarettes. I go home by myself Monday morning, it's all gone. Uh -huh. You know, you know, like
shut up. So I'm gonna work finishing off the residue of the eight ball as I make an excel sheet.
You know, who claims to have a rough drug past is a gentleman that you and I ran into at the
arc light after Ghostbusters. Are you are we naming him or no? No, no. Yeah, he claims he claims that he's
got that rough drug past, which always makes me laugh. It would explain what his looks have fallen
to, but I'll tell you an interesting one. And John's talked about it on stage, but John Mulaney has
talked about it in his stand -ups that he was like a guy that got sober. So I'm not saying anything out
of school here, but he and I pretty open like, you know, he just I who drank a lot. I could never
picture it. I was like, what? No. Yeah. So we were actually at Pete Holmes's house one night in his
kitchen talking about this. And I go, John, I just can't imagine what you would have been like
that was so bad. Like that you had to stop. Like, what were you like when you got drunk? And he goes,
I was like this. And immediately turned into the most sinister human being I've ever met in my life.
Just showing me what he got like when he was drunk. Like got right in my face. He was like, yeah,
what's up? You think you're fucking better than me? And I was like, holy shit. And there is
something dark lurking around in there. Yeah. No, I sense that in him. You know, he was raised
Irish Catholic. We all have a lot of deep darkness. My favorite thing about John Mulaney was last week
when he hosted us and now and people were offended by his monologue. I'm like, how fucking saccharin do
you have to be to be offended by John Mulaney? You know what I mean? It's like saying this ice cream
flavor is offensive to me or say, you know, it's so crazy. Yeah. It's not a shot at John. That's
just like, that's crazy to me. They were offended three weeks in a row. They were offended by
bird Mulaney and Chappelle. But bird Mulaney makes sense. They're there to push the button.
Brunch of hell makes sense. Yeah. Yeah. Sorry. You said, but okay.
Pat, let me tell you what I've been doing all morning since I got up. And I wasn't up that much
earlier than you. I've been working on a weird out type parody of a Gordon Lightfoot song.
A lot of money in that. Yeah. Ready? Yeah. Oh man, I'm gonna break wind because the beans and guacamole
you're sure at it again. Wow. What do you think? It's got legs. I mean, what's the title is?
Is it you know, you have one line of it? That's all I got. And I couldn't think of two words that
rhymed with sundown that related to farting. I was like, it can be oh man. That's not gonna be a good
parody. Like bad sound, fart sound. I was like, that doesn't make that much sense. I don't know,
that's all I got. I mean, what made you put your pen to paper here with these lyrics? There was no
pen or paper. There was barely any thought. Okay. I was just walking between my kitchen and bedroom
as I do every morning thinking I'll find potentially find meaning somewhere in between the two rooms.
Never do. And I just got the second line got stuck in my head. I'm gonna break wind. And I was like,
and then I just kind of built it all around that to be honest. And it's kind of like when you have
a you think of the twist first and then try to write the script around the twist and that never works.
That's exactly what it's like. Yeah. So I mean, you can do something with Bung.
Because it's sundown. Bung. Bung. No. Bung sounds. I'm breaking wind. Yeah, there you go. Bung sounds.
There you go. Sundown. It did one of my pet peeves, which is sundown is used very effectively in
what is it hateful? No, no, no, no, Django. Then it is used in what's, oh, knives out.
You know, not even 10 years later, like in big scenes. I hate that. It's like there are one
billion songs and so often you hear the same two or three songs in movies. And it's funny.
You say that because Tarantino has talked about when he's putting soundtracks together.
Like when somebody will be like, what about this song? He's like, I can't use that. That was used in,
you know, he's like, he won't do it. He won't use his song if it's been used already.
What's weird though is that he uses a lot of score from other movies. Like he'll use stuff
from black exploitation or stuff from, you know, blood spattered bride or whatever. Kill Bill has
a lot of music cues from other movies, but not songs, I guess. Just score. I'm sure I'm a little
bit different to me. Homecoming season one did that. And I thought they did it very effectively.
And it is a very interesting way to get yourself around having to pay God knows what to a composer
and an orchestra and, you know, the rehearsals and whatever that all costs. But John Williams.
Yeah. Up on the podium. John Williams sells out the Hollywood bowl every year,
playing his little themes. And then they put ET on a screen flying. I don't know which is it.
You wouldn't see that. Not really because I feel like it's like now we're settling into an hour
of John's lesser known themes. Or, you know, it's like, oh, boy, you know, four of them and the rest
are going to be like, just watching classical music. I got to tell you, I bought my dad a double John
Williams disc. He'd be shocked at how many. Okay. It's, dude, it's, it's, first of all, it's all
of the Star Wars movies. That's nine. Four Indiana Jones movies, Close Encounters, ET,
all the Harry Potter movies. Okay. That's a good score. I'm sorry, I shot on John Williams.
Yeah. I would take it back if I were you. All right. Yeah. There's been a fly in my apartment
for, for so long now, I'm convinced it's a friend who was mutated who's tried to get a message to me.
I mean, it just won't, it just won't leave. Have you tried to kill it?
I was trying to not kill it. Why? I don't know. I've gotten softer in my old age with, you know,
you know, the fly. Yeah. Well, there, you can find a million of them swarming around a pile of
shit somewhere. I always love that killing something for no reason. Like, if I find a spider, I try to
pick it up and get it outside. And that's not a drifter. Let it. Well, I've been killing
drifters. So I'm trying to cut back. It's my point. You know, it's like a diet. You say, if you're
going to kill the drifters, something's got to give somewhere else. Do you see Jeff Goldblum's tiny
face as that part of the issue? That's what I was saying. That was the joke. No. It's just I've swatted
it and then I finally broke and did try to kill it the other day and I couldn't, I couldn't get my
hand on it. And then I didn't have a magazine to swat it with. Sure. I just had no way to do it.
It's it's over. It sounds like you've got yourself a friend more than more than a fly. Yeah,
Rumi's, you know, he brings home beer. So I can't complain. Feed something. He replaces it. That's
not bad. Um, Joseph, what's going on in the world? We have a new president since the last time we
recorded, you know, at least until that's contested. But basically, I think, you know, we had 24
hours where it was kind of like, okay, it looks like there might be some semblance of normalcy. And
now I think the fear now is a coup. Now, I, the news keeps reporting that the GOP claims of fraud
and whatever. If they're getting nowhere in the courts, we're covering on without a country this
week. Uh, the like we, we, you know, we cover a take from the left outlets and a take from the right
outlets on the same story. Right. To see how they cover it differently. But we're covering the dead
voters and voter fraud and all that stuff. And the right, the Fox News article that I'm covering
is like, this is all bullshit. Here's the claim. Here's the truth. Like, we have two different stories
covering the topic of fraud and all this stuff and blah, blah, blah, blah, and everything else,
right? Yeah. And both of my takes are from Fox News and both of my takes are, you would think they were
written by like Vox or half power or something. Like that's how hard they're going at the GOP and
being like, this is ridiculous. Yeah. You know, whatever. Uh, there's still a few on there who are
still trying to hang on to their jobs or whatever and, and keep it up. But I have seen a lot of people
just like they didn't even carry speeches anymore. Fox News will cut away and be like, that's not true.
Sorry, we're not going to air it. So that's crazy. I did over the past, you know, there was five days
where everyone I knew was just watching cable news all day, which is something I literally never
give one minute of my time to his cable news. But I kept flipping back between the three and Fox News wound
up getting a third of the time just because it's so unbelievable and entertaining. But the first time I
clicked over there, I believe it was Tucker Carlson. It might have been Hannity and the guests is going
on and on about how elitist Democrats are. And he used the phrase with their, uh, the Democrats with
their bow ties and their foie gras lunches. The first sentence I heard when I flipped over, I was like,
what the fuck is going on? So no wonder everyone's parents hate them now and the world is falling apart.
Yeah, I'm talking to my mom yesterday who will believe anything she just hears on the TV. Sure.
Uh, it's a lot of parents. And she goes, she goes, you know, uh, did you hear this that will
Smith's dead father voted? And I go, mom, there's no way that's true. Uh, where did you hear that? She
goes, I saw it on the news and she's at an age where it's all just the news at this point. She
doesn't remember what fucking channel she even had on. Right. I go, I promise you that was Fox News.
Yeah, and I promise you, it's not true. And she goes, I don't know, they said is dead,
dead, voted. And I go, okay, and so I hang up the phone, I look it up. And what it was was
Giuliani at that press conference they did outside of the furniture store or whatever that was
amazing landscaping. Yeah, uh, said in the same breath that will Smith's dead, dead, voted.
And then also a deceased boxer was still voting in Philadelphia. I mean, just crazy shit. Yeah.
Um, also like, how do you know that's Will Smith's dad is last name is literally Smith.
Yeah. Yeah. Um, it's, uh, it's, it's pretty wild stuff. Now here's the thing. I, I agree. And
you know this about me and I've gotten, I've gotten flak from our own fans about this. I hate the
left. I make fun of them all the time. I hate the fucking phony liberal class and all that,
I make fun of it all the time. It doesn't mean, though, that I don't have reason or rationale,
or I just don't like bullshit. So I hate Trump. And I hate the other bullshit too. I'm just so tired
of this finger pointing of like, well, they suck too. And it's like, okay, but what are you doing
that's better? Can you do a better thing right now? Yeah. I just relieved to have a, uh, and hopefully
fully sworn in president, who knows, you know, as you said, how it's gonna go. I just relieved to have
a president again, not because I love politics or really believe in America or any of that stupid
shit. I'm just relieved to be able to turn on the TV and hear a news clip where he doesn't sound like
the asshole friend of mine that I'm constantly worried about getting too drunk at the bar because
he's gonna start something. You know what I mean? Like, it's just nice to have a president again going,
we need unity. It's nice to hear the word unity come out of the president's mouth. It's very nice. I
just, I worry that we're too far gone. I think it's very encouraging that the, there's not violence
in the streets right now, but I do think that once this is official, because I think his people are
just like, he'll pull through. Donald pull through. He's not going to unless there's some sort of
weird thing. But then you gotta, there's so many people that have to go along with what he's doing.
The only issue is, I don't know if you saw these policemen, grown men, crying in the streets when
he lost, but that is a concern. The police are definitely on his side, you know? I don't think,
I don't think it's all police. I think, look, I think this, I think the state of things,
and we'll get off of this, guys, I know you don't like when we go too far down a non -entertainment road.
But let's face it, folks, the greatest show on earth, out there to American politics.
I don't think, I think it's like anything out. It's like when people say, like, well, you know,
they say it about all groups in this country at this point. There, there's more voices crying out
about this at this point. And it's like, yeah, because every voice now is the ability to be amplified
and the most sensational of all will be exploited. So they're going to find that the story is a cop
that's crying in the street about Trump. The story is not the however many other cops that aren't
crying in the street or relieved whatever. So that doesn't worry me too much. And maybe I'm naive,
we're optimistic or whatever in that sense, but what I mean, I don't think there's going to be,
I think this is going to be very, just, this is just going to fade. I feel like now that Trump
is not the guy in the hot seat anymore in the in the big chair anymore, rather. I feel like this
is going to be like Brian Callan, dude. Is it going to be like, okay, go do a Patreon only podcasts
and yeah, we're not getting behind you on this one. I really think that's what it's going to be.
Nobody is going to be beholden to this guy once he has no authority. Right. He could be old until
him when he does have authority. Yeah, it could just be that he wants, he doesn't want to go down
as the loser. He wants to go down as the person who is wronged by society, but he always is and
puts himself in that role. But it could all just be some act. And then he goes, you know,
golfs and shits himself until he dies. But I will and I will say this for the Trump fans in our
audience because I know we have some. I think my takeaway from this last four years will always be this.
I think it's a terrible shame that we saw a guy who clearly in the very end here in the very end
when he got COVID and started saying some sensible things online. When you see his optimism about
the vaccine, when you see when they instated a mute button at the debates, how his demeanor completely
changed and he was very nice and everything, I think it's a terrible shame that he didn't display
that behavior for the last four years because I think then at this point, the positive things that he
did do would have actually gotten a little bit of traction and a little bit of gratitude. And he could
have left some sort of potential legacy. And I think because he went so far in the other direction
with being so exploitative and loud and brash and borish, there's just no, he undermined it
everything. I know liberals that will go, I look, he did X, Y and Z. And I think that those were good
things that he did. But it's like, it's like a Nixon thing. It's like Nixon did some good shit,
but then Watergate. And it's like, wow, it's all ruined now, man. That's all anybody's going to
remember. You know, it's the, it's the stain. Yeah, I mean, I'll just remember how he made me feel
every day, which was vaguely nauseous and scared. That's what I mean. It's like, it's like, I wish,
I wish at some point he would have just acted like a guy in that position instead of a celebrity being
sensational. And you know, and or whatever the better word is for it. But anyway, that's
all I'll say. Sure. I mean, the worst of it is the hate that he has stoked and that I think is
is going to be, we're going to be dealing with for a very long time. I'm curious. See, I have a,
I have a foggy sort of lens with that because I live in New York. Sure. And I'm in California. We don't
see everybody honking their horns and celebrating. And you go, all right, people are in a good mood.
Yeah. And it gives you the illusion at least that it's the majority of people feel that way. And then
also to that Biden won the popular and the the electoral college. Yeah, that everybody was,
the majority of people were fed up. And the majority of people did want to move in a more enlightened
and unified direction. And that the idea that we were outnumbered, if you had that mindset in
this country, it was false. I don't know. But, but that's, you know, whatever, we'll see what happens.
We'll see what happens. So it's out web to say on that every day for the last decade. Yeah.
Let's go to the movie court. Yes. Okay. I've been watching quite a bit less because I was watching
Sean Hannity and things like that. By the way, they're all so annoying.
Rachel Maddow is so smug. Yes, she really is. And just like, there's people I like on these
networks, but it's like, God, why do you have to the Chris Hayes? Why do you have to talk like that?
He seems like everybody that's talking, he's about to go wrong. It's stupid. Like, God, it drives me nuts.
Why is that personality like reward? Why do you? Why do people want to spend their entire day with
somebody who's like a smug? No, it all. I don't get it. Yeah. Here we go. Joe, I don't know why I'm
starting with this, but I dusted off. Look who's talking. Basically, I found myself intrigued by the
career of Amy Heckerling, who was one of the only female directors working in Hollywood in the
80s. And in the comedy world, it was basically her and Penny Marshall, Penny Marshall to much greater
success. But Amy Heckerling directed Fast Times at Richmont High. She then went on to European
vacation. Yep. Later, she would have much greater success writing and directing Clueless, which
is a fantastic movie. So look who's talking is kind of in the middle. It's probably her biggest hit.
And it seems completely unlike anything else she did. She wrote it. And I was just like, I got
to watch this thing again. I saw it at the dollar show when I was nine. My mom took me on my sister.
And I remember on the big screen, it starts with a bunch of sperm going to the egg. Yeah. And my mom
just absolutely flipping out. She had not had to talk with us. We were both like, maybe
sister like, what is even going on here? Right. But that's really all I remembered about the movie.
Sure enough, it's it's Kristie Alley, gorgeous. Interprime. Johnny Travolta passed his prime,
but very likable. This was this was the first Travolta come back. This was like, right. You know what
I mean, before the pre pulp fiction come back, right. And he was coming off like the experts,
like really like movies that just were complete bombs. Then you got Abe Vagoda and a key supporting
role. Baby grabs his eyebrows at one point. But the movie is horrible. I mean, I remember it being
I loved it when I was a kid. I've never seen it. I did too. I really did. I mean, I think the reason
you love it is like it's a baby's day out type adventure near the end. The kid drives around and
you know, I forgot that the kid grow in the second half of the movie is like three. He's not a baby
anymore. But these Bruce Willis voice overs. I mean, he's they're the most shitty, obvious jokes
every time. The one that I remember in the in the trailer, people laughed into the next trailer was
he's talking to a woman with big tits. Yeah. And then Travolta goes, are you thinking what I'm
thinking? And Bruce Willis goes, yeah, lunch. Yeah. That was the that was the that was big. I remember
that that laughter just blasting off the walls of the theater. But it's it's not a very good movie.
The one liners for the baby are just so shitty. And it really winds up feeling just like
those e -trade commercials that Pete did again. Right now, like they're just and Pete had fun
of your material. He was kind of improv and riffing whatever it seems like Willis. The first thing the
baby says when it's in the womb is it looks down at its dick and he goes, how am I going to get that in my
mouth? Wow. It's like Jesus Christ. Because he thinks it's his thumb. I guess, but it's still a baby
trying to get its dick and its mouth. They're watching one midded into a movie. I don't remember
that line at all. Jesus, that's wild. I mean, they got they at some point they have Travolta dancing.
They're kind of a charming couple. Kirstie Ellie claims in her autobiography that she fell in love
with John Travolta and almost left her husband during this time. I don't know. They did two more of these
movies. They did the ones where the dogs talk and the other one. So then also at the end of
Likus talking, they they had the baby sister and it's Joan Rivers and she goes, can we talk?
Yeah, but then in the second movie, it's Rosanne. It's Rosanne, which I'm sure Joan Rivers was like,
what the fuck? Yeah, I don't know, man. It's I always felt bad in for Rosanne in the movies. God,
I felt like she deserved at least one decent one, but she had a rough go. She made two two movies.
She devil and this one and it's like at least she double had a statement to it. Yeah, but Christ on
the cross, I every watch she devil not that long ago. It's it's not I mean, look who's talking is
worse than she devil. For example, yeah. And what were her other movies even? I remember watching her do
a TV movie where she was a mom who joined her son's football team at school called Backfield in
Motion. I mean, she didn't have the best agent outside of the Rosanne show. I think that's it. I
think those were the only movies. I don't remember. I mean, she was in night. Oh, God, she's in
Freddie's dead, the final nightmare. That's right. Just the stain of the series. Yeah.
Yeah, like Tom Arnold had a better movie career than Rosanne did. It makes no sense.
True. All right. I watched I'm way behind on some of these. I've had some of these on my list
forever, but I watched the second season of afterlife. The Ricky Gervais show. Yeah, I did too.
I mean, this thing is I love Ricky Gervais. I'm a fan. Were there moments that I laughed sure where
there are moments where I guess I felt a bit moved for the guy's struggle. Sure, maybe.
It's just a bad show. I mean, it's just tonally all over the map. He doesn't. He's trying to do
crimes and misdemeanors. He's trying to bump morbidly dark drama right up against
like quirky snappy comedy. And it just he just doesn't know how to do it. Ricky Gervais is very good
at something. And he doesn't do it anymore, which is starting something absurd and then allowing it
to gradually become more real and resonate more with the viewer. For some reason, he stopped doing
that. And now what he does is he swings this hard pendulum between like dick jokes and utter
schmaltz. So it's like it's like you got you got Robin Williams and like by Centennial Man in one
corner. And then you got Robin Williams from Mork and Mindy in the other corner. And it's just it just
doesn't work at all. This thing goes from him literally on the couch watching videos of his dead
I mean, every fucking episode every episode ends with him watching his dead wives at their wedding
and crying every episode. By the way, ends the 10 polls of every episode opens middle segment ending.
It's just throughout every episode. Yeah. And and then and then in between those, it's like
he's in like a yoga class and the teachers farting and burping. Yeah. You know, and he's like
it's disgusting. I can't I can't fucking down. I can't fucking you know, and it's like a scene that
would have been in like extras, right? So like I don't know what he was quite going for with this.
He's clearly at a place where he can just kind of do whatever he wants. And Netflix or whoever
else will just allow him to do it. There is no editor. Nobody is saying this is bad. And if there
is, they're being overridden. Yeah. And the show goes well too. But it's just not it's just not
good, man. And both seasons had about four moments total throughout the all the episodes
where I was like holy shit, that's really funny. And both seasons had about two or three moments
where I was like, oh, wow, that's very touching. And then outside of that, it was either
small central jokes that fell flat, premises that weren't being followed through with
or him being such a heinous human being that you didn't even want to watch the show anymore.
Right. You know, none of it gets followed up on. There's a thing at the end of the first season where like
he, you know, he gives that that drug addict money to basically kill himself with heroin.
And then like his brother -in -law finds out that he did that and like none of that ever comes to
fruition. There's never the moment where like maybe the cops come around and ask a few questions
and it's tense for a little while and whatever or he has a breakdown in the following season where
he goes, I was trying to help him but I don't know if I did the right thing. There's no payoff,
there's no follow -through. He just does it. And then all these lessons that he supposedly has learned
about himself at the end of the first season where he's like, I'm going to use my powers for good
not evil. Instead of being really shitty to anybody that annoys me, I'm only going to be really
shitty to the people that deserve it. And you get excited for season two because you think it's
going to be this like free for all like dexter style comedy where he's just really rude to awful
people. He doesn't do any of it. And the second season is just a replay of the first season.
He just wants to kill himself again. He moaps around about his wife. Yeah. And then he almost kills
himself at the end and then the dog comes in and saves him and stops him from doing it. Just like
at the beginning of the first season, you're like, oh, for Christ fucking sakes. Give me, I mean,
it's just it's just bad. I imagine they'll do the same thing in the in the third season. I mean,
it's I don't think they'll do a third season. He does too when he gets out. That's all he ever got.
I thought I got picked up. Oh, maybe maybe he did. I don't know. Grief and depression are two of
the least interesting things to watch in a movie or television. They made so many movies about
20 -year -old dudes with depression when I was growing up. And it's just very, very hard to make
compelling and it's depressing. I mean, you can make it funny depression like in an office space
is very funny, but it's as drama watching somebody grieve or watching somebody be sad is usually
pretty rough stuff. I like the first season though of afterlife. I saw I was going to propose we do
this for the show, Joe, but I wouldn't put you through that. I watched both versions of the witches
on Halloween night. It was the saddest Halloween I've ever had. And I've had some sad Halloween.
But the the first witches with Angelica Houston is done by Nicholas Rogue, who was like a great director
to don't look now, you know, one of the great horror movies. And the witches is a lot of fun.
You know, it adapts the book very well. Angelica Houston is really going for it. There's some really
cool makeup. There's some really cool Jim Henson's creatures effects and work. I like the witches
when I was a kid. I probably liked it even more now because it didn't scare the shit out of me like the
witches used to. The witches part two, they're the remake, I should say, is directed by Robert Zemeckis,
who if they haven't shut him down, it's coming. You know, he he's reached that point where it's like
that's enough. Spielberg never got there, but he dabbles. When Spielberg was doing the BFG and
stuff, you're kind of like, all right, Steve, like, you know, this might be the end. People just get
too old to do the shit. Right. Zemeckis is too old. The witches is A, you know, it starts, they do
they do a black version of the witches, which more power to them. But why not have a great black actress
play the witch instead they give the boring straight characters to a black family. So instead of
the little boy from the first one, it's it's it's like if it's not in the 50th, it's hard to even tell
what period it was in. It's a Octavia Spencer and she's taken care of her of this kid and there's this
whole new subplot that adds nothing to the movie. And halfway is going into like the stratosphere of
overacting. She's really bad. That's kind of the worst that she is is when she's like unhinged
like that. I it's hard to watch. She's not funny and she's trying to be an Octavia Spencer from
what I've seen in the film. I watched some clips and some trailers. Yeah. I'm like, they they got her
right back in the position of playing like the 1950s black lady. I was like, couldn't believe it.
Yeah, what we complained about in shape of water. It's what we said was cool about Ma that they
did that they took her in a different direction. Yeah. It's what they did in, you know, it's it's it's
the same thing. They they just it's I feel bad for her like it's shitty. She's essentially I mean,
she's doing a voice like I mean, it's it's real like, you know, made in a 50s movie kind of vibe.
And it was depressing. I don't know what they thought it would add. What I would have enjoyed
was seeing Octavia Spencer as the headwitch, you know, like it's what we always talk about with
diversity. It's not fun for these people to throw them a part that has no juice to it, no fun
of any kind. And you're you're checking your box, but they're getting nothing good to do. It was
it was a bummer all around. I mean, that the racial aspect of it, I thought I'm surprised nobody
jumped all over it because it was just depressing to watch. Can I say this? Again, I haven't seen
the movie, but what I got in the trailers was enough. Yeah. Stop letting Chris rock narrate things.
What the hell? It doesn't work. His voice is distracting. It's too distinct. Yeah. He's not good
enough of an actor to do it. He's not I'm it's I said this last time when this came up.
Chappelle could have pulled it off in my opinion. You want to name and maybe they went after him. I
don't know. There are plenty of if you're hellbent on getting a black stand up comic to to fulfill
that type of role in your film. There are plenty of guys that are more capable in the acting
department. Cat Williams would have been better by by a long shot. He's not good at this. Stop
having him do it. It ruins the fucking thing. It like you can't get past it. He it starts and the
the narrator is the kid as an adult. You you gathered, but basically it starts with it. Okay, I'm in
this rolled doll world of like magical witches and it's starting up and the first thing you hear is Chris
Rock going, you ever seen a funky ass witch? You know, like that's what it is. We both about fell
off the couch. It was like, what is this? The tone is just all over the place. And I think what it is
is these guys have no idea how to tackle diversity. So it winds up looking awkward and uncomfortable.
But Chris Rock talking it in his very very distinguishable. I'm you know, you know, you're listening to
Chris Rock's voice more than almost anybody else coming across this movie, but which it's it's so
weird. None of it works. The effects look way worse than they did in 1990 with the original wishes.
The effects look terrible. That's I couldn't get over the mouse effects. I was like, what is this?
This looks just like sci -fi channel CGI. Really rough. And then it ends with
Octavia Spencer, the kid and the mice. The kid is a mouse now. And they're dancing to
what is it? He doesn't get changed back at the end. No, they're dancing to we are family
which is what's been used in every trailer. But like the 80s. That's what Zamekis is like trapped in
the 80s. So they're all dancing to this. There's a scene early on where Octavia Spencer has to she sings
and dances to like a temptation song that is so awkward I had to look away. And I'm not exaggerating.
It's a really really really really bad movie. The original which is is a lot of fun.
All right, I watched. I'll go with another series. I'll stick with series today.
TV series. I watched. This is a fast one and also tying it to yours a sort of remake. I watched
Dracula Netflix the three episode. I guess BBC production that was done by the same guys that did
Sherlock Holmes. For Sherlock rather. For Sherlock to me was one of the greatest shows that's come out
the last 10 20 years. I thought it was amazing. Never saw. I thought they nailed it all.
You never saw the Cumberbatch. Oh my treat yourself, dude. It's fucking great.
Really amazing. But so I was excited for this. You know,
get another retelling of Dracula. Do we need it? Do we not? I don't know. Let's see what they're
going to do with it. I mean, you could say the same thing about Sherlock Holmes. There's been plenty.
The first episode of this is essentially tackling the Bram Stoker novel from a sort of different
direction. It was great. It was a great execution of that novel in that story. I was like, oh my god,
I am 100 % in. Where is this going? This is amazing. And then episodes two and three were so
forgettably bad that I didn't give a shit. And I don't even know if I finished episode three.
But you know, typical thing where they hit the ground running in the first one, give you everything
you want. And then in the second two episodes, they're like, now we're going to go off in our
own direction and explore some carrot. And it's like, oh, forget it guys. I don't care.
Yeah. I'm going home with Renfield to see what is thing.
Yeah. But I would say this. This is my review for you to take with you. I would watch the first
episode just and look at it as a new Dracula movie. And you'll have a great time. And then
leave it there. Walk away at that point. Yeah.
I've been going through the early movies of Paul Mazersky who would later do down and out in
Beverly Hills, which for whatever reason is a movie I loved when I was a kid. It was always on
the local channel. I would have to see it. My mom said it was too dirty. It's dirty. Yeah. But
they added edited so I could see it. But I bet Midler fucks homeless Nick Naltier, something like
that. Yeah. And she's married to Dick Dreyfus. But I have a big even more so than 70s Dick Dreyfus.
I love 80s like asshole Richard Dreyfus, which really builds and then peaks in what about Bob.
But I love him with a very short fuse exploding at people. It just always made me laugh.
Anyway, Paul Mazersky is a great director's very similar to Woody Allen. He would later direct
Woody Allen in one of his worst movies scenes from a mall. I thoroughly enjoy the film. I've
never seen no excuse. I've never seen it. But it is it is usually hailed as a low point for everyone
involved. Anyway, in watching some of his early movies, they had them kind of spread out across the
the streaming services. And I actually rented this movie called Bloom in Love with George Siegel.
And the reason I wanted to discuss it is because the last time I talked about George Siegel on
here, we were talking about Where's Papa, which featured the horrific comedic gang rap scene.
Right. So Bloom in Love, which came out a couple years after Where's Papa, it kicks off. It is
it is a guy who's in Venice. This is clearly how he had the whole idea for the movies in Venice,
Italy. And then it keeps cutting back to Venice, California, which you're like, okay, this isn't clever
enough to build a movie around. But this is a lawyer. His wife comes home while he's
fucking another woman. And the entire movie is him obsessing over his ex wife still in love with her.
He doesn't understand why she's so upset that he fucks somebody else. He's like, it's the 70s. I don't
love her. But you know, I was talking with the Juvez thing about how depression is really
tough to pull off. This whole movie, this guy is depressed and pining for a woman. And it is miserable.
I like all 70s movies. I just like the feel. I like the coats. I like the beards and the musk
stashes and guys drinking coffee and so forth. There's something about a 70s vibe that I always like.
So I'll give it that. But I'm watching it. It's kind of dull. It's just this guy pining
until about the 90 minute mark where Seagal goes over to this woman's house. She is marrying
Chris Christofferson at this point. She's completely moved on. Christofferson is arguably a thousand
times better looking than George Seagal. He plays a singer in the movie. You're like, okay, this woman's
going to be happy. Seagal comes in, tries to convince her to get back with him. She's like, I've
moved on. I don't love you anymore. I love this other guy. Leave me alone. At which point Seagal throws
her to the ground and rapes her. God almighty. What's with Seagal? I'm like, Lex. George, why are you
picking these movies? What is going on? So he rapes her. She tries to fight him. It's one of those things
where she's like, fuck you. Fuck you while he's going. You know, it's not like it's graphic,
but it does go on. You see him pin her arms and et cetera. And then in the very next scene,
you learn that the rape softened her. It proved to her how much he loved her. And it patches up their
marriage. Fix his things. That is the end of the movie. And here's another movie I've almost never
heard of. Like these movies should be notorious. Where's Papa in this movie? But that's it. For the
last half hour, you watch them sort of be like, you know, she's like, I didn't know you felt this
way about me. It is the worst rape message I think I've ever seen. What would be the best rape
message you've ever seen? Don't do it. Rape is bad would be the best message. Okay. Fair enough.
I think rape will fix it. If you have a woman who doesn't like you, you should rape her because
then she will is probably the worst take I've ever seen on rape. I will close out with an anthology
series that will tie nicely into our main feature for today. Yes. I've watched the new season of
amazing stories. I also went back and purchased the original two seasons from the, I guess,
the late 80s or early 90s. Yeah. Of amazing stories. One of which, both of which, actually, I bought
foreign copies of because I actually, my PlayStation and my Blu -ray, Sony Blu -ray player are apparently
region free. I didn't know that. Somebody sent me dark room before to watch and I tried to watch
it. It wouldn't play. So I thought they were region locked. One of the kind fans sent it to me and
I couldn't watch it. And now I can watch. I don't know. Now it's not region. I don't know. I
apologize to that person. Thank you again for that. Sorry. It didn't work out. Anyway.
But anyway, I rewatched the first two seasons. I hadn't seen them in quite some time.
Amazing stories was never a home run type of show. It was an anthology series that tried to be
basically the Twilight Zone, but it leaned much more heavily into the sort of spirited
and heartwarming aspects of the Twilight Zone, the sort of magical and mischievous, if you will,
aspects of the Twilight Zone and far less into the darker sides of it.
When you do that kind of show, I mean if you watch Twilight's in the movie, the Spielberg's episode
has kicked the can. Kick the can could have been a pilot for amazing stories. Now the average episode
of amazing stories is far better than the Kick the Can story in Twilight's in the movie. They're usually
not that mushy, but a lot of them have that sort of vibe. So it was never a great show to me. It was very
well executed. It just wasn't my speed. That said, there were about six seven episodes every season.
I truly liked or loved and thought it was worth owning, and I was correct on that. The new series came
out was much shorter season, instead of like 15 episodes or whatever, it's like six.
And I can say that they missed the mark in just about every episode. The only passable one was Robert
Forster in an episode about a grandfather that gets superpowers that actually started really fun
and really cool. And then by the end of it, they just didn't stick the landing at all. And
in my opinion, at least. But I mean, if you're going to watch one of these apps,
that's the one to watch. Is it on Apple? It's on Apple, yeah. The pilot app, I mean dig this folks
it's about a guy that gets transported to another time period and falls in love with a woman
from that. I mean, this is just like as generic as you can get with these kinds of story lines.
There's an episode about like a World War Two fighter lands mysteriously in present day. And it's
like Jesus Christ, guys. This is like shit coming out of like the Rod Sirling idea generator on
Google. You know what I mean? Like this is it's such lazy stuff. Did Shyamalan do it?
No, Shyamalan has a different movie on Apple. I can't remember the name of it. Yeah, I haven't
seen that yet. No, this was I think Spielberg was back. Okay. And I get excited. I got excited
because it starts up and it plays the original. Oh, and again, John Williams theme, great theme.
And as soon as it starts, you're excited. You're like, this feels like the old show. I'm in. Let's
do it. And then it just got on mighty. The episodes are just not good. It's just not good. I
watched some of it when I was a kid was family dog. I spent off of amazing stories. That was a cartoon
and that I think also served as a pilot for a show. Yeah. That sucked. That one sucked. But there's
a great one with Jeff Cohen who played chunk in Goonies. There's a great episode with him. There's
an awesome one called Mirror Mirror with the guy from Law and Order Sam Waterson who plays a horror
author. And every time he looks in a mirror, he sees this like deformed monster trying to kill him.
Which is really fucking great. There's some great ones. There's some great ones. These new ones
pretty much sucked front to back. And in a world in climate where we're losing bite in everything by
the second to take the bite out of amazing stories. You're dealing with some really benign milk
toast stuff. And that's what this came across as. And that's what it was. And it's unfortunate. But
which takes us into our featured film this week, which is, that's not really a film. It's two
shorts, I guess, but a 45 minute creep show shutter Halloween special. And the first one up is
Survivor Type, which so I'm also watching at a very slow pace. The Tales from the Crypt Show. Didn't
they do Survivor Type on Tales from the Cryptor? Was it just a rip off? I mean, it's very, very similar.
He doesn't eat him. He doesn't eat himself. But it's the one with calm McLaughlin.
It's somewhat similar. I mean, yeah, it's too different. No, so Survivor Type is a Stephen King
story from the 80s. Right. From Scott and crew. Yeah. McLaughlin carrying death. Well, I carry
death actually a story from the 50s because that's from one of the old comics. Yeah, I think there's
probably you could draw some parallels. I don't think they're painfully similar. But I understand,
I see what you're saying. Both are about a guy sort of trapped, desperately trying to
get himself out of a situation that he stuck in. And as he tries to survive his, he becomes the,
he becomes the, his own undoing. Man, both have birds in them that play a big role and so forth.
Yeah, I thought they were pretty similar. But so yes, Survivor Type, the, the, the gist, the plot is a guy
is a drug dealer, you know, he's, he's trying to haul cocaine. The sir, he was a surgeon
who on the side is selling heroin. You think the surgeon would be enough money for you, but he
something he's in a position where he's got to get him. I think he's like gotten in trouble. I think
there's something at the beginning that he needs a lot of money to get himself back into the medical
game. Yeah, because he got into some, so he's going to do it by selling a shitload of heroin or
something like that. Yeah, it's very strange because they, they tell you all this stuff about him and
you see all this past. But really, it's like, what, what do we need to know about this guy? It certainly
doesn't make you care about him anymore. But it's just like watching, I guess what bothered me about
the whole endeavor is shudder. We got to have a talk. What, why? Yeah, everyone I know subscribes
to you. When are we going to start seeing some of this money on the screen? The creep show,
the animation in this thing was sub -South Park. They, they were panning over just, I guess it was
the comic book, you know, that they're trying to do, they didn't even have mouths move. Okay, so, yeah,
so, okay, so here's what they did. And this is upsetting. There are these things called motion
comics that you can get on the internet, which basically they're graphic novels or comic books
that they add some motion to in the panels. And it's a very, if you're familiar with the program after
effects, after effects is an editing program for graphics that allows you to take layers of a picture
and move them and create depth and all this other stuff. So it's basically you take a program
like that, you take a comic book panel, you separate all the images and you're able to give, you know,
you're able to make the car move across the frame or whatever. But that's about it. You can't bring
life to the images themselves. You could just move the images around. Right. And it's also become a way
to sort of cheaply do animation or affordably, I should say, do animation because animation is
incredibly expensive. It's a way to do affordably do animation. So what, where you see it now, a lot of
the time is in music videos, bands since music videos have no budget anymore and there's no real
place for them to live except for YouTube, bands will create music videos like this. So as soon as
shutter announced, creep show is doing a two story animated special story by Stephen King,
story by Jill Hill, one is survivor type. I was excited because survivor type was supposed to be
one of the live action episodes and they never did it in the first season on shutter. And then they
said it's going to be animated and I thought, oh no, this is going to be that motion comp. If I've
seen the live action thing and what they can afford, they can't afford to do real animation.
Yeah, they just can't. By the way, there are places that do animation real cheap. I mean,
they might not look amazing, but they're better than panning over a picture. So I wish they would have
now that said, I thought that the stories were well executed. I enjoyed hearing key for Southern
England in the first story. I thought it was Adam Corolla till I looked it up, which is nuts.
I thought the Joe Hill story was pretty good. I enjoyed it. I didn't not enjoy watching this,
but you got to advertise what you're giving people, man. You can't say we're doing an animated
special and this is what it is. You've got to be a little more straightforward. And then of course,
as soon as the first trailer came out and I saw it, I was like, yeah, it's exactly what
is afraid it was going to be. And they're also doing this thing with the creep himself,
where they have like this, they'll put a, it's terrible. They'll put a guy in a suit
to get the motion shots. This is live action to get the motion shots of the creep, the guy that's
supposed to bring you the stories where. So he's like sort of waddling around the room,
like with a zombie walk, which doesn't make any sense. And it like, it's, it doesn't work.
And then he sits down and then as soon as he sits down, it cuts to instead of a guy in a suit,
an animatronic that literally looks like they got it at like home depot for sale for your yard,
for Halloween. Yeah. It's just painfully not well put together. You know, I respect the hell
out of Greg Nikotaro. I really do. But guys, well, look, it's not even his fault as a director.
It's, I don't know who's fault it is. It's somebody, somebody has to step in with the art department
and say, this doesn't work. Yeah, we need to take a new approach. This isn't, it's good enough,
isn't good enough. We have to figure out like a better way to do this. And nobody seems to be doing
that. I thought they would have learned a bit from some of the mistakes of the first season and potentially
hearing feedback. And they didn't, they didn't change anything. Shutter has big problems in this regard.
It made me feel sort of betrayed, which is how a lot of their original movies make me feel when I look
at what, what people are doing with no money, what kids can do with their iPhones, etc. Like we're
seeing stuff that's below that. And people are paying for this service. So, you know, the, the most
recent Joe Bob was a massive letdown. And part of that was just personality. They all seemed very
depressed and tired and, and sad. Well, I also don't know why on the Joe Bob, it's like they, they
suddenly tried to do a scripted thing. And I was like, what are you guys doing, man? Like this isn't
a scripted, like it's scripted in the sense that he delivers monologues that have opinions in them
in a, in a podcast or standup sort of way. Why are you now writing scenes between him and Darcy
where they hate each other? This is what are you guys doing? And then some, I think it reached a point
where they were trying to like improv and riff in that mindset. And eventually you're like guys
watching you to put neither one of you who can act hate each other is miserable. Like we're trying
to have a Friday night fun time. It seemed like they despise each other as opposed to the fun.
Now, maybe there was some tension off screen. I don't know, but it felt real at certain points. I mean,
from what I know, they're good. I've looked up Darcy's like YouTube videos. They're like friends.
Like she's got videos where they go. They're like, we're going to take a trip together. We're going
down to see the cabin that was in this or whatever. And they seem like they're really good friends. So,
I'm like, why are you playing up this angle of them not liking one another? And then like the way
you're playing it up is by making Joe Bob sound incredibly like sexist and like, don't make Joe
Bob unlikable. You know what I mean? Like, like, I don't know, man, it just didn't, it just didn't work.
It didn't land. It is a thing. This creep show special at best. Again, it worked as a motion,
it worked great as a motion comic. That's what it should have been. It should have been a motion
comic that was released online. It should not have been tatted as a animated special for Halloween
and thrown up on to shutter. It was just not, come on guys. It's an online thing at best. And what
it seemed like to me is if a friend of mine was making an animated movie or show and they were like,
check out these animatics. I have friends who'd work an animation and they'll show you an animatic
where they, it's like a story board. They can kind of scroll through and give you an idea. And it's
like, oh, cool. Yeah. I see what that's going to look like. But this was, they put the
basically animation to come up on screen. So what you're saying about this being a, you know, a known
format, I didn't even know. I just thought it was cost -cutting. But like, I'm sure anyone who
turned this on was like, Jesus Christ. Survivor type, I think the fun of it would have been the gore.
I imagine that's why they never adapted it because watching a man eat himself was probably too much
for some to take. But you're on a shudder. You have no content restrictions. You put cannibal
holocaust up there. I think they didn't, I think they didn't adapt it because they couldn't do it
with a live, they couldn't afford to do it. I think they were like, we can't, we can't get an island.
Yeah. You know what I mean? Like, I feel like they had no way to shoot that properly. Right.
There is an animated above ground pool somewhere shooting it. Now that said,
uh, twittering from the circus to the dead, which was a Joe Hill story about a family that
ends up at a circus where, where the attraction is zombies and they're luring people in to eat them
basically. Yeah. Would have been a fantastic episode of the show. And in fact, they did a similar
take on that with the, with the awful Dave and Arquette episode, which was about a town letting zombies
out to eat people. Yeah. That were obstructors. You could have just done the Joe Hill story. Yeah.
And it would have been great. And you could have also not done the other awful Joe Hill story you did
about like nessie coming out of the water and befriending the children or whatever the fuck was going
on in that one. Awful. Yeah. I don't know anything about Joe Hill's writing. Um, I haven't ever read any
of his stuff, but I thought the second episode sucked. And I think the reason is they had just Joey
King, um, do the whole thing in this sort of like OMG hashtag Twitter voice, uh, and she narrates the
whole thing in such a way that I didn't want to hear her speak anymore. I hated listening to her. And
that's the other thing. They pay one voice actor per story like shutter. That had to have come
down from the top. Oh, you can only pay one actor to be in that. What are you doing? Like yeah,
this project should have been canceled or you needed to give them another $250 ,000 to make a
production. This is not a show. Um, and while the second story goryer than the first, like,
entering from the circus of the dead, the original story is told through a series of tweets,
which if you read it, I think would probably be really a really cool format for a short story
and a really interesting new thing. Yeah. And, uh, so taking it out of that format and turning it
into story, you're already stepping away a little bit. That said, I thought it was a really cool idea.
And it could have been an awesome live action episode. And it would not have cost them an incredible
amount. It would not have cost any more than what they spent on the other episodes. And instead,
it kind of gets reduced to this halfway, half baked in between, you know, not really one, not really
the other. And it's just, it was okay. And you're right. I mean, nobody, I mean, if you're going to have
one character driving the ship, the least, you don't want it to be a Gen Z, like, you know, I rolling,
you know, like kind of bratty kid. It's like, forget it, man, like that's if we're hearing from one
person right now, that's the worst person we could be hearing from right in this kind of annoying
teenage girl voice. Yeah. And then if it was like valley, a valley girl for the 80s, you know,
it's like, come on guys. At the end, then the, the creep or whatever, the first is zombie. And then
it switches, but the zombie grabs her phone and then tweets details to, I guess, lure more bait into
the things that we're going to tour around, come see us so they can get more zombies. And we watch as
the zombie types eight tweets into her phone. Yeah. He's like, you know, we'll be touring the following
locations. And then it's like, we'll be touring through the fall. And then it's like, we're talking
about the refreshment options. Like your stories over, like stop doing this. He just keeps tweeting and
tweeting and tweeting. I was completely let down by both. I mean, if I had to, I can't say I enjoyed
either one really, but I just feel like there's a vibe that shuttered lately. And I know everybody's
hurting with the pandemic, but I feel like they need an influx of cash because everything is looking
too chinsy for me. Everybody has to get the fuck over this. There's a pandemic so everything needs
to be done remotely. Yeah. There are ways to work around this. There are safety precautions you can
take. Start taking them. There are affordable precautions. If a nightclub in Manhattan,
yeah, where Miami can do rapid testing at the door for a 25 % capacity, whatever, you can figure out
making decent content with a few people. It's possible. It's possible. It doesn't have to cost you.
It doesn't have to be gross. Okay. I think it's gross. The Jurassic World 3 used 40 ,000 rapid tests
to get the production done as people are having a hard time leaving the house and this sort of thing.
But guys, everybody get a fucking grip and figure out ways to make things work. It's possible. If
in a multi -cam sitcom live audience scenario, there is a way to do this. Figure it the fuck out.
Jesus Christ, man. Like you're producing stories for the special that feature one character.
Yeah. I mean, come on. It's stupid, man. It's stupid. You're animated Halloween specials should not
look significantly worse than a Garfield Halloween that I used to watch on CBS when I was eight years
old. Anyway, that's your creep show. I got big plugs, people. Do it. By the time you hear this,
we'll have already have opened. But Joey Roses, my sandwich shop pop up, eight sandwiches for eight
bucks a piece, old school classic stuff to the brim sandwiches. Delicious. You can follow us at
Joey Roses, hard eight on Twitter and Instagram. We are open at the stand in New York City. If you're in
New York, please combine, have yourself a sandwich. Again, eight sandwiches, eight bucks a piece.
We will not let you down. I promise 12 to 4 p .m. every Wednesday through Friday.
And that's what's happening. Come on through. All right. Also, my special, you let me down as
available on YouTube or free on Comedy Central's YouTube channel. Go give it a watch. Enjoy yourself.
Take it in and watch for free. And I hope you laugh.
Okay. So my, you know, Twitter, Instagram handles at the Patrick Walsh.
You can follow us on C you and help pod at Instagram. Thank you, Emily for running that. Thank
you, Emily for everything. Thank you, Emily. Thank you to all for joining us on the Patreon.
And our new four episode a month plan. It's been a great success. We were very happy with
to keep bringing you the content. And our next episode will be focusing on the evil dead one,
the evil dead two and the evil dead remake because we have already done army of darkness. You can
put the episodes together. That's it. We will see you next time. We will see you in hell.