Summer is here, and Bed MDM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer.
Or check out our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz, only available
at Bed MDM Casino.
Spin on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 Fortunes, Mystery of the Lamp, Raken
Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand.
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action.
Bet MGM in Game Sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 Plus to Waiter, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania, and West Virginia
only, games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as normal -durable site credit slash bonus best unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
The football season is full of guarantees, and here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October, if
your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning or winning money back in fan
cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
Winning hits different here.
Monthly 21 Plus, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamberler, offer not available in all states
Welcome to another episode of we'll see you in hell. I'm just fell down. We'll see you in
hell. This is the podcast brought to you by the Fangoria podcast network. If you want
info on us and the other shows on network go to Fangoria .com. And here we are. And I did
almost fall. I tripped on the mic cord walking across the living room. It's okay. We pat
Matt and I are here, Pat Walsh and I are here.
We are staring at my new beautiful Sony 4K television.
How many inches, Joe?
55.
Now, I meant your cock.
56.
See what I did?
It is a nice TV.
Congratulations.
We're in the hazy glow of Black Friday.
I've got a lot of packages coming to my home.
What's showing up these days? What's fun? What, you know, what blu -rays I got?
Yeah, I just bought a bunch of stuff that was like four bucks, you know. I got this new Oliver Stone book I'd really wanted to have my eye on.
I got, is it the book, is it the book about the movie W?
you. It's all about W. Yeah, it's about 650 pages on W. No, it's kind of Matt Zoller
sites who is one of my favorite film writers. He did a great book on Wes Anderson. A lot
of interviews, amazing pictures. And he did the same thing basically with Oliver Stone
and it looks awesome. I got it today. Okay. Pat, you look very comfortable. Pat's laying
sort of on his side. He's wearing a north face. Some sort of a, I wouldn't call that a fleece.
What do you call that thing it's it's a place I think it's your standard North it's it's freezing cold out for LA
Which means it's like 60 degrees
It's the holiday season
Right, you know, and I'm glad it's finally cold because you know fucking thanks giving 80 degrees
I want to kill myself honestly
Yeah, I don't like when it's hot for the holidays
I don't think we're out of the woods. I feel like it's gonna get hot again. It will it always does I'd prefer for it to get hot
to never have to see where that North Face thing again.
What the hell?
I don't like it.
Why not?
It's very dead.
I don't know.
In the way you're sitting, you look like a college professor
that's gonna try to bang me during the office hours.
I don't care if we're...
Well, not after the things you just said to me, no.
I don't like the way it looks.
You know, North Face is a very popular brand of clothing
and it's warm and comfortable.
Again, Pat.
You frequently use this argument popular.
Doesn't mean it's good.
They couldn't be more comfortable, and they're warm.
Not shitting on North Face.
I like a lot of their jackets.
I don't like what you're wearing right now.
I don't see now I want to return it.
Well, then that's your problem,
and I would talk to your therapist about it.
Oh, I mean, you know,
you gotta be able to take these criticisms.
If somebody says, hey, your North Face sweater
is fucking revolting lehittiest,
you have to go, it's just a standard
Zip up just get off my back. It's a very basic bland zip up jacket. I'm a confident man
I can take it when somebody says it looks like a dog puked all over your sweater and then you
Told you again to the whole thing. I don't think there's much shittier
You can do than criticize someone's clothing because then they're like well, I guess I'll never wear this again
Well, like it's just a shitty thing to do. I don't talk shit about your clothes. There's much I could say
I'm wearing a t -shirt and jeans.
I'm wearing a fucking jacket and pants.
You know, many times you come out like,
do I look all right in this and I lie and say yes?
Well, that's terrible.
You don't do that, you don't lie.
Because who wants to have something in their closet
that you're just like, I'll never wear this again.
I'm just busted.
One guy said it wasn't nice.
Bust in your shoes a little bit terrible.
I haven't seen you in a month
right away you're getting fucking fresh with me.
I'm breaking your balls a little bit.
The truth is I got this from my dad, and it's going to him for Christmas.
Are you joking? No, I came in the mail today from Nordstrom. I put it on because I was fucking cold
But I don't think it's nice to rip on a man sweatshirt. You cheap prick. Why am I cheap? You're wearing somebody's gift right now?
It was cool. I wanted to make sure it was nice. I hope your dad hears this. He won't. He won't support anything. I do ever
In fact, if he does see anything I do, he'll openly criticize it, as he has been 35 years.
He has your own ugly sweaters to wear.
Why are you having to dip into your...
Folks, I could see this sweatshirt, which is like the most basic sweatshirt of all time.
Why?
Roughly the exact same color as your T -shirt.
My T -shirt is a solid gray.
That is a speckle brown.
This isn't brown, Joe.
Oh boy.
Patties is Christ. I just don't like hearing that you got to swipe into the polyanna gifts to get yourself warm
You don't have a jacket you can throw on I wanted to make sure it was a nice jacket and I don't give a shit
Well my dad gets for Christmas. Oh boy. All right. This this got too deep. I'm sorry. This got too deep
All right, he's gonna fucking love it. Well, he should he's an old man
This is why I'm saying you shouldn't be wearing it folks
it's such a just a general nondescript sweatshirt. This is what I have to deal
with. Patty, come on, I'm pushing your hump a little bit. Don't ridiculous. Look,
you look really sad right now. No, I'm starting to feel bad. Yeah, I want to take
my jacket off. I'm trying to make myself feel bad and I don't. But you know what I
mean? Right? No, I'm hurt. Welcome to, we'll see you in hell. We already did that
part. It's time for pets trying to block it out. Pat's movie corner. Yeah, there we go. Yeah,
that's what we're supposed to be talking about. What have you seen? And don't tell the Silent Night
Deadly Night story. Save that for the Silent Night Deadly Night podcast. Well, I'm going to be talking
about bad sand, too, when it's thankfully out of theaters. That's what I meant. Bad sand at
delivering dog shit. Don't tell the bad sand a two story till we do the Silent Night Deadly. That's
another tease. We tease them the last. Definitely won't remember, but okay. I'll remember.
I saw bleed for this boxing movie Miles Teller. You know it suffered from
comparison to Whiplash which I thought was fucking awesome. It's another guy
who's very very driven. He's a very cocky boxer. He's a gambler. Some great
gambling scenes in it. Womanizer gets in a car accident. It's completely paralyzed
But he's got a box again. It's a true story. I've hung out with a guy. Was he a nice guy? The real guy
He was very nice. All right. We drank together
Where why and how did you hang out with him? I met him through my friend comedian Bill Burr
Okay, he came out to see Bill and then he came backstage and I was opening for Bill at the time and we all went out after the show
All right, and he did get a little punchy with me when he had a few drinks in him
Yeah, which was frightening, but he was a very playful, lovable guy
All right. I mean, I like Miles Teller. I like the movie. You got, uh, what's the guy's name?
Too face. Aaron Eckhart. Aaron Eckhart. He, I mean, he's just doing, uh, please give me an
Oscar performance. They both are. Eckhart's like bald and fat, using an accent. I mean, this
stuff starts to get really old to me after a while when people are like, please give me an award.
And I don't think it's coming for either one of them, but it's pretty good. It's, it's,
very similar to the fighter. Uh, it's not anywhere near as good as Creed or even the fighter
really, but it's a fine movie. Okay. Uh, you know, B B plus entertaining. I kind of want
to say it. I don't know. Raging Bull kind of was the be all and all boxing movies for me, but
but maybe I'll see another one one day and maybe it'll be that you've seen many others, right?
You've seen all the Rockies. Oh, wait, no, I'm sorry. I take it. I love which I said three seconds ago.
I love all the Rocky movies yeah, and so okay, so all
seven Rocky movies and
Raging bull, and then that's it for me for boxing. All right, so that's fun. How about digs town?
Digs town's pretty good
There's like if you want oh, man, that's a great reference if you're like listening to this and you're like I've seen everything and
And digs towns are really good underrated movie James Woods who's now insane and Lou
Gossad Jr. who's probably close to it.
It's really a fun movie.
How about play it to the bone?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
Jail, but they're gonna undisputed or something. Oh, yeah, that was kind of cool actually box for the prison
That was kind of cool to whatever who was in play to the bone again. Woody Harrelson and
Antonio Bendabas. Yeah, those were the dark Harrelson years. I went to a
Halloween party in New Orleans of Miss Jennifer Coolidge, one of the funniest women in the world star of the Christopher Guest films and
Legally blonde and shit, American pie stuff was mom
And I went to a party. She has like a mansion down there. It was so incredible. Very spooky vibe and who walks through the door
But mr. Woody Harrelson dressed as I think a scarecrow, but I don't really know what the costume was
with a
Middle -aged Asian lady that he was tongue -kissing and grinding upon
and just holding and drinking openly from a full bottle of vodka blowing up
what is spot dude I loved it I mean he's not a married man why can't he go to
a party and grind on a lady and drink vodka right did I criticize well how
am I blowing up his spot I was just choking which with you tonight it's the same
night as the previous episode how am I blowing up a spot don't say that because then
it ruins the illusion yeah I tell you what folks use your illusion as that's
Rose taught us. I saw Moonlight, the critically acclaimed indie movie that is being talked
about for Oscars and folks, it should be. It's an amazing movie. It's basically like
Boyhood in that it tells, you know, it cuts in at three different periods in this guy's
life, but it's not the same actor or anything like that. It's a young black kid in kind of
a very dangerous neighborhood who is gay, struggling with that. He's about maybe 10 when
the movie starts, then they cut to him in high school, and they cut to him as an adult.
It's a very powerful, and then they do it. It's like boyhood where they do it. I just said
it wasn't like boyhood.
It was an amazing looking movie, powerful stuff, great acting from all three age groups.
And I really, it was something I had not seen before.
I loved it.
All right.
Why don't you do one, Joe?
Well, I have three.
Go ahead.
I saw Ouija.
Ouija, too.
Two.
Return of Ouija?
Yeah.
Which I believe.
If you've episodes back, you refer to it as Ouija the early years or something like that.
Yeah.
You called it something really wrong, I remember.
It was very funny.
Oh, yeah, I don't remember what that was.
But it's called Ouija, the origin of evil.
Yeah.
Pretty phenomenal harm movie.
I've heard nothing but great things.
I didn't see either Ouija.
I wanted to and never did.
It was sort of what I really enjoyed it.
It was creepy in the right ways.
It was almost like a scarier poltergeist and it almost put an apoltergeist vibe like a sort of mysterious
Mystical vibe that turned much much much much more sinister than poltergeist ever did and I love the board
Huh we jee board origins. I think that's yeah, it becomes
100 % less scary to say we jee board. Yeah, or and then to say origins
But it was a creepy movie, the little girl that's, you know, that gets possessed or whatever,
she did a great job.
Okay.
I enjoyed Henry Thomas back on the big screen as a priest.
Everybody in the movie was great.
It was shot beautifully.
It's a period piece.
It takes place in the 60s.
They did the titles and everything like it was an old 60s horror movie.
It was very, very well done. I really, really enjoyed it and I suggest it or highly
I recommend it. I also saw Baskin finally. What the hell is that? Baskin is a
Turkish horror film whose trailers looked reminiscent of the thing, the carpenter
version of the thing. I didn't find the movie to be at all reminiscent of that
once I saw it, but it's creepy. It's sort of like a weird fever dream. You know, the
The fact that it's subtitled made it a little more fever dream -ish to me because I'm
sure there's stuff I was missing because I'd look away for a second and miss something
somebody said because I wasn't reading.
But overall, great visuals, some pretty tense scenes.
I don't want to ruin anything.
There's a few twists and turns in there.
But when you finally get to quote the place where the shit goes down and quote, it's a pretty it's a pretty wild ride for that 25 minutes or whatever.
And I like the ending quite a bit.
You can watch it on Netflix, you can stream it.
You can bask in it tonight.
night. Last but not least, I saw ab fab, absolutely fabulous. You and your girls have a night
of the town. I was on a plane once again, and it was sitting there for free, and I said
I want to see this day of movie. Have you ever seen the show? I've never seen the show.
Is it funny? Yeah, it's two middle aged women running around drinking literally as soon
as they wake up doing coke like just out in the open in the fashion industry, the movie
was exactly that. I mean, they just came in hard with the, you know, just no regard
for PC with the humor. Okay. They made a transsexual joke within five minutes of the movie
starting. All right. It was a very funny joke actually. They go, she's talking to her ex -husband
is paying for her house and he's remarried and his new wife goes he can't make your house payments
anymore because he now identifies as a woman and he's going to do the change and then his ex -wife
goes oh you finally managed to cut his fucking balls off which I thought was a very funny joke
It was funny. The plot of the movie is they accidentally kill a supermodel. I can't
remember her name. She's a real supermodel. Was it a hit and Britain? Like, do people
still care about that? I don't know what it did review. I think it did pretty well. I
think it got some backlash for not being, you know, PC or whatever, but the show wasn't
PC so if they, you know, it'd be like if in 20 years from now they made it it's always
studying Philadelphia movie and it wasn't a reverent. Like, right. It's got to be a reverent
and that means going to places that, that, you know, there, and it wasn't like, none of
it felt like punching down because they were making fun of everybody evenly. Like, they made
transactional jokes, they made racial jokes, they made jokes about gender, they made jokes
about children. It was, it was all very fairly dulled out. So I liked it. I thought I was
It's really funny.
All right.
Yeah.
One last one from me, and I'll be brief.
So this horror movie that just came out on DVD
called The Whaling, which I had heard great things about.
It's close to three hours and I don't want to get
its country of origin incorrect, so let me look.
It is a South Korean horror thriller.
The wailing, the wailing, it got amazing reviews this year and I just rented it and it was pretty fucking awesome
I think it would have been just as awesome at two hours, I will say, but I was pretty riveted by it. It's like
Kind of like a ghost possession type thing in a small Korean village
It's sort of funny at parts. The characters are great. You really give a shit about everybody in it and
and it's got some really cool scary shit in it.
I liked it a lot.
Now, let me ask you this.
One element of Asian horror that I'm not really a fan of
is that the ghosts are always,
not always, but a lot of the time,
a young girl with black hair and black smoke.
No, it's not that.
It's not like you want or whatever.
Yeah, okay.
It felt completely unlike any of those, well, those are Japanese movies also, but yeah.
It felt very different and cool and it looked them incredible.
I would strongly recommend the wailing.
Add fab at a 60 % on run to make it, wailing had like a 99 % or so.
For a comedy that's not too bad, that's not too bad.
Let's get into what we came here to talk about Pat.
The task at hand.
The task at hand, this is a film that my very first conversation with Ken Hanley, our producer,
and the reason we're here on this wonderful network.
work. The very first conversation I ever had for him was when he was writing for a subsidiary
website of Fangoria, and he interviewed me about horror movies, and he said, what horror
movie franchise do you hate? And I immediately said, Jeepers Creepers. Wow. And I have talked
shit, I talked shit immensely about the film series before that, and I've continued to talk
eventually since then. I think it's a terrible, terrible, terrible franchise, but I know
that you like the movie, so we're going to discuss Jeepers, Creepers, and I feel like
maybe a few fireworks. Well, the issue is, I saw it when it had come out, 2003 or something.
I think when I first moved to New York, I thought it was super fun, liked it a lot, and I remember
even enjoying the sequel, which I have not seen in a very long time. I've never seen
the sequel. I've only I've seen the first one I've seen parts of the sequel and what I saw
the sequel. And yet you shit on an entire franchise of the movie you've seen. Well, there's been two
of them, Pat. And the first one is an abomination. And the second one, the parts I saw were terrible.
It wasn't getting any better. So I was like, I'm not going to sit here through the whole thing.
Well, you know, I don't know why you'd even call that a franchise two movies because there's supposed
to be a third one coming or maybe it came out. There is, but it's been straight to video. It's been
hit up with a lot of problems due to the director being a convicted child
velocity. Right. Which I really want to talk about this time out. Okay. Well,
let's let's let's in this is as Ken pointed out when I told him we'd be
talking about this. An old recurring theme comes back to the podcast. That is
true. Pat Afele. It's been a long time. But so so everybody out there know that
is Pat supports the movie Jeepers creepers. He's in a roundabout way. Oh,
You don't even know if I'm supporting it you're supporting a you like the movie so when I saw it and whenever I saw it
I liked it and now I'm saying I watched it again two hours ago. Did you like it?
Here's what I think
I think it is
Unquestionably a well -made
Movie it's just already. It's just unquestionably just a
Just this is schmuck talk and again much like the the North Face company
It's a very popular movie. There's a lot of people anglin for this third one
Uh, it was like I looked it up like the biggest labor day opening of all time or so that it made a ton of money on no budget
Um, yeah, well there were you know
Because there's never been such thing as bad horrors equals, but sure we're talking about the original
No, no, I know, but you said a lot of people are angling for this third one
Oh sure, no, but people really want it
But for me what was hanging over this new viewing and hanging over in a very big way
was the balls of a man that blessed children was the fact that and if you look
this guy up he is smiling in his mug shot. His name is Victor Salva. Yes. Imagine
a pedophile. There he is and his mug shot he's got a big grin in his face. It'll
be the first thing that comes up when you Google it. And what he did folks was
in 1988 on the set of this movie clown house which I believe Sam Rockwell was
in yeah yeah he filmed himself and it says forced oral copulation which I
don't know if that meant the kid blew him or he blew the kid but they're both
terrible options he filmed himself either blowing or being blown by a 12
year old kid who was acting in the movie and under his care he had tons of
child pornography lying around his house he was convicted of these crimes went
into jail for what was supposed to be three years,
served 15 months of it.
Okay.
Then was released on good behavior.
So this guy is a monster.
But he's not struck against since.
As far as we know.
That we know of, yes.
Okay.
Then he comes out, he does powder,
which is basically, you know,
a very creepy movie about a shirtless boy
who lives in the house with the family.
Yeah, let's let this boy live at our basement. So I
Forg I knew and I forgot that Francis Ford Coppola produced
Cloudhouse the movie which he got arrested on right blowing a child
Or forcing his penis into the mouth of a child
Francis Ford Coppola comes back to produce the Jeepers Creepers movies and this blew my fucking mind
Because there's no way Coppola doesn't know about that. So wait Coppola comes back to produce
But was that before he was convicted or after he was convicted?
He was convicted in 1988. Oh, okay. So then then couple that now now I've read
up I've read up on this stuff about Salva. Yeah, okay
Last year. So I've read up on you know the latest doing so I'm gonna take the pro pedophilia stance
I'm not taking a pro pedophilia stance. I do
You sympathize in some ways with the argument that has been made by certain people on his
behalf of he did something terrible.
He served his time.
He redeemed himself and that doesn't mean that he should never be allowed to work ever
again.
Now I can't speak.
That's why I asked as far as I know, he is not offended again.
If he has, that's terrible and that sucks and no one knows, I mean no one knows.
But you see what I'm saying.
I do.
I'm saying like if the argument is he should have served a greater sentence. I'm all ears. If the
argument is that type of punishment doesn't redeem a child molester. I am all ears, but I'm just
saying the one side of the opposition that I would not opposition. You know what I mean? That I
would sympathize with is the idea that okay, but the whole point of going to jail is to serve your time
and be redeemed and then put back into society
so you can work again.
I agree and when I was,
I mean, the comments on this deadline article about,
because recently,
Jeepers Creepers 3 Cathedral is going to be released,
but I mean, then he's bringing the church into it.
I mean, this is just, you know,
it very briefly fell apart
because people in Canada were like,
this guy's got a casting notice up,
do not work on this movie
and they kind of shut down production. That's when I read that and then I read a statement from
him or his camp saying, look, I made a mistake and I learned my lesson. Yes. They are going
to do it. I would say not, not have three force of these comments on deadline are like,
fuck you for like they're going further than where you're going with this where it's like he
served his time. Who cares? But they say things like, I'm going to read one here. You hypocrites commenting
hatred towards Silva would be crying bloody murder if you had a conviction served your
sentence and were then continually pilloried.
You are all far more disgusting than he and the very next comment goes, I never ate a
child so which I love.
Then the very next comment, a lot of pedophile apologists out today like it gets heated if
you want to look up the deadline article it came out pretty recently.
I mean, my issue here is, you know, once a pedophile always a pedophile, I'm not saying they
should all have their dicks cut off, but the urges are there.
When I watched Jeepers Creepers this time, I still found it a well -made and effective
horror movie while not being an amazing movie.
But this movie is about pedophilia, Jeepers Creepers, right?
right? You think it's about pedophilia? I really do. And maybe it's just watching it
through those lenses. But the the character's name is the creeper, a standard name for
a pedophile. Right. But he sniffs and licks his prey. He's trying to find out what and
they're like, he'll keep eating and eating until the hurt goes away is how he's described
at one point. You think the entire time he's going to kill the hot young girl, you think
he's out to like seek her. But at the last minute, the twist is that he's been trying to
get to Justin Long along. So he sniffs and licks the girl and he's like, no, I want the
boy. Sniffs and licks Justin Long. There's a scene in a dinosaur.
Well, that's not pedophilia. That's him being gay. Yeah. Well, there's the very first scene
in the movie is there, there's playing like spot the license plate. Right. And Justin
long goes gay gay forever or something like that right uh this one says gay for it the first
line of the movie is gay forever right right and she goes no that means six a like sex a forever
that's what they mean okay that's a discussion I'm like that's a weird first line for your movie you know
right but I'm watching it through this lens and keep in mind I'm I am never and would never suggest
that gaming's pedophile at all that's not what I'm saying but no that's not really the subtext is so
thick in this movie that I couldn't deny it. There's a scene where they're in a
diner and they keep talking about Justin Long's dirty underwear that he's
gonna bring home the underwear to his mom to wash because their brother and
sister. The whole opening scene after Gay Forever is about his dirty underwear and
his sisters like they stink, they smell bad. The creeper pulls his suitcase out of
his car and has been sniffing his clothes and his underwear. He's sniffing a
boy's underwear. This is a guy who's trying to say, hey, I'm directing a horror
movie now. Let me try to take the attention off my pedophile past and he
has a character named the creeper smelling a young boy's underpants. All right,
well, he's not a... All right, that's gross and strange. I'm just tipping the
The underwear sniffing is just weird and strange to me regardless, male or female.
But he's not a young boy just as long as like 22 in the movie or something, right?
Fair.
Now, I do remember in Jeepers Creepers 2, there's 30 shots of shirtless 17 -year -old boys.
I'm sure they were 18.
Okay.
Peeing on the side of the road, lingering on their ass cracks.
Right.
Well, there's a...
I got you.
You say maybe where there's smoke, there might be some fire.
I'm saying, if I were accused of that crime, I mean, there wouldn't be a child within
a hundred miles of the set.
I would be going in a different direction than a character named the creeper smelling
a boy's underpants.
Sure.
I did notice there's a diner scene with a hundred extras in it, and all of them are adults.
And that kind of made me laugh because I was like, oh, he just can't have kids on the movie
set.
Well, probably not.
I'd imagine there's some sort of...
But when there is an extra, it's an oiled up beef cake like an 18 -ish year old.
That's fine. Look, look, it's, you know, that it isn't it isn't because I think this movie was
him confessing in a way. And there's, I have much more to say on this, having just watched it.
I know you do. I evidently. Here's my point. You know, I can't apologize for what the guy did.
It's terrible what he did it's into many people obviously an unforgivable offense
But I also can't criticize a dude that's into dudes
Like in a bunch of fucking 19 -year -old hard bodies around you like you know, that's that's the same thing most men do that are into chicks
Like it's like all right like I mean that movie Tyler Perry directed that we saw had a bunch of like
questionably young girls and you know bras and falling out of their shirts right so it's like it's I'm not saying that's a crime of course. I'm saying
Think about what you're doing
That's when when we're already giving you a big pass. I understand that you're saying it doesn't send the right message perhaps have some
30 year old beef cakes with their shirts off. I understand and Woody Allen does the same shit and of course
We've discussed him on the show. He's a he's a legend at this point of course, but
To just always have his love interest be 19 to have that be the plot of movies
Well, he didn't he hasn't done that since the whole Suni thing that hasn't the youngest he went since that Suni business was
I think Helen Hunt which was still a ridiculous age drop, but he was in her 30 you know like he's it's like now
It's my least Cyrus and he's 80. I know he's not romantically linked to them in the movies
It's just he's always got these young female co -stars, and it's like
There's something to it like if I were accused of rape, which I will never be
Or you might guess you never know when to be accused of something. I'll never do it. Right. I would be if I'm a director
Hey pet, you know me neither for the record. Yeah, I know. I know. I would be directing Glen Gary Glen Ross as my next project
All right, but now I it's it's it's I get your theory you're it's not a theory
If you're accused of molesting a young girl and then you keep getting progressively younger and younger girls in your movies
There's something to look at. I don't think that that's what Woody Allen did
I don't I think you're off the mark with that argument. I think he's using
He's using he gets hot women 80 years his junior to be a movies with him every time
But I know they're legal. I guess but he's making movies with Hollywood starlet
He's not seeking out. I mean, he's you know, it's like that's true. It's it's it's it perverted to have scarlet
Johansson in your movie like she's very popular. Is it's perverted to have
the the what's her face?
Miley Cyrus. Yeah, what's her name flama awareness to me?
I
I you're more on the mark with the victor salva one that I think I'll ask you raped a 13 year old girl in the
Yes, yes, um, he doesn't do movies about raping girls in the ass and he's laid low and yeah
But would you do movies about dating your girlfriend's daughter? No, I know I know
But I'm saying they they just don't have any awareness and it's a strange thing
I'm just making a comparison
Polansky is hailed as a fucking hero and I still think Chinatown's a masterpiece, but
People really look past that and maybe that's
Why the fuck does that guy get off the hook?
I don't know.
Your salva doesn't.
I don't.
Well, I don't know.
That's true.
And I don't know.
So, and I'm not saying either of them should be off the hook, but I should in my special
I should on Polanski.
Right.
It's like that fucking guy.
And look, he did his time.
I know or I think he didn't I think the stories he did his time and then he had to leave because
they wanted to do more.
I don't remember.
It's very convoluted.
The point is is like he, you know, like one guy gets this pass in the other guy.
I doesn't and it's like, I'm not saying any of them deserve a pass.
No, no, I'm not saying.
Chinatown is anything but a masterpiece,
and I'm not comparing Chinatown to fucking Jeepers Creepers.
But Jeepers Creepers is a pile of shit.
I'm not saying Jeepers Creepers is a pile of shit.
I think it's a very entertaining horror movie that's that's better than most movies of its kind
So you think it's cool that this
mythological whatever you want to call it supernatural flying
Flying creature the creature can fly. Well, I actually love that at the at the half -way marker
Whatever when they run him over with the car or whatever and then the giant wing pops up
It's a really cool moment. Yeah. Yeah, no, he can fly yet. He drives a pickup truck
Why is he driving the pickup truck?
I guess that was your issue the last time this came up
because I was trying to avoid your issue.
You guys have a pickup truck
that I believe has vanity plates on it.
Well, Joe, because he can't fly around
because then everyone's gonna know what he's doing.
So he can roll up to the Poe Dunk Backwoods gas station
and get out with a monster space
and just he pumps gas.
The creeper has to go pump gas.
This is what he has to do.
He's got to go shit the money again. I got to go pump gas and he obviously can just fly every
year. That was your that really was your issue the last time we discussed you can hang up on something
and it ruins the entire thing because it's bad to make it into a horrible movie. It's just it's an
effective horror movie. It's not an effective horror movie. It's not scary. A monster driving a truck
It's not scary. He wears a trench coat and a top and a fucking Fedora, which fuck off for ripping off the Fedora from crew
The Fedora is Freddy Krueger. You don't rip. That's like having a monster in a hockey mask. You do not do it
You do not do it. Jason is the hockey mask. Freddy is the Fedora
But whatever. I will say I'm always
Surprised by the reasons you don't like something. They're always baffling to me. The monster can fly and he drives a truck around that
Then let's look past that. I don't want to look past that explain it to me that is so stupid and he's got vanity plates
I think he's just trying to pass himself off as a normal person
The wing doesn't make an appearance till halfway through and I think the reason even on this news now second viewing
I was like I didn't audibly gas, but I was like oh, that's really cool. This wing is popping out
I didn't know he could fly because he was driving a pickup truck
There's a little bit of bait and switch there, of course, but it can't be flying around town, right?
Because he's got his underground layer of truck says jeepers creepers on the front of it
So the so the monster not only drives a truck fine. We will look past that pet. He's also got a sense of irony
This is a monster with a sense of I just watched it. I didn't notice his driver's line said jeepers creepers
I guess you're reading on the front of the fucking truck. Is that a poster you're looking at?
Look at Google Jeepers Creepers truck because I remembered some sort of vanity plate situation
There's oh, there's a lot of vanity plates in the but doesn't his truck say like creeper on it or something something like on the back
So that so that so the so the so I'm looking past the truck the monster
Ordered he's got a registered vehicle. This is a vehicle
That a flying monster has registered with the state and has ordered
I mean, the things that you will look past and the things that you won't are so wildly infuriating to me.
Wash, explain that to me.
I think that this is a...
That means he's got a mailing address.
That means the monster at a home gets mail in his cave thing that he lives in
with tons of bodies strewn about the old awesome like the cysteine chapel or whatever.
Yeah, and it's just laying low on this cave where his very mailman delivers vanity plates.
to the creeper's house.
I mean, and he doesn't go.
He goes, hey guys, just a weird thing.
Delivered vanity plates today to a guy's house.
I don't know what they said.
We might want to run a check on it
because the whole house smelled like rotting flesh.
Well, what is the history of the creeper?
We maybe we'll find out in Cathedral.
Maybe he was a man at one point.
Why couldn't he have been a man at one point?
He wasn't a man at one point.
And they can make up whatever shit they want.
Fine, and I will also look past the things
Things that you won't look past are mind -boggling and frustrating to me.
But I'll look past both of your things.
They commit the cardinal sin in all of horror and jeepers creepers.
Is this going to be that woman that comes in?
Yeah.
The black mystical island lady that comes in and just explains everything in two seconds.
It's ludicrous.
And then when they ask her when they try to poke holes in it, she's like, it's not like
watching a movie child.
Yeah.
I certain things don't get to me say they leave out sir and guess what she doesn't say
Guess what she doesn't say all of her knowledge about the monster and all this shit. Guess what she never says
What he he he be a man once child, but Joe. She doesn't she doesn't see everything
It's not like watching a movie. I don't know how you don't get that. Oh my god. I mean
To sit here and watch just alone just watch a movie called jeepers creepers and to and to pick away at these things
These movies are just, they're little scare machines. They're supposed to be fun and scary.
Pat, why do you do this to yourself?
Pat, because there's good and there's bad. It's that simple. There are good things and there are bad things.
I'm not saying every harm movie has to be the exorcist.
I'm not saying every harm movie has to be this sweeping masterpiece of a character study in the cinematography and a bad, I'm not saying any of that.
You're saying for Christ's sakes, don't make it absurd.
Don't make me have to picture a goddamn flying snake monster filling out the form for vanity plates. It's ridiculous
I mean
Is it a plater? Is it like a sign that he puts on his car because he seems very human
It's I don't know. It's just I'm gonna say he was a man at one point and I think we're gonna find that out in Cathedral
Come and get it made. Well, I think it's been me because there's a poster of it. Can it is not letting it happen. I thought it already been me
Now here's my question, this goes back to your thing about the commentary of the film
or the subtext rather.
Do you think there's a chance?
Not even a subtext upon watching it again, not even a subtext.
Do you think there's a chance, and I'm not, this isn't me playing devil's advocate anymore,
I'm just literally just asking this out of curiosity.
Do you think there's a chance that Salva is absolutely going for the message that you think
that he's going for?
I think so.
an anti way. Maybe he's saying this was me and I'm ashamed of it and it's monstrous. Maybe. I mean,
Salva had an abusive stepfather and he came out to his parents when he was 18 and they shunned
him and whatever. So a line like he's going to eat and eat until the hurt goes away is a little
shocking and
A what what I mean if you want to talk about ridiculous what is the creeper hurting from
You know like that that's not even explained at all. So that's already a little ridiculous
Well, he has to it's like it's like return of a living dead
They they need to feed on humans or or because they're in pain if they don't and they get you know
He he's if he eats your eyes and he can see you whatever now
I'm gonna cut to the end of the movie because he has just a long
Uh, skin hanging up in his place basically. Yeah. And this could be the worst part of the whole movie. His eyes are out. Yep. And then the creeper's eye
pops up in just a longsie. Now
I thought it was kind of a fun ending when I first saw it. Now I'm thinking to myself
The boy he molested can only see the world now
from the creeper's point of view
Well, that's very interesting and he's been also literally inside the boy. He's inside the boy and now the boy will forever have to see the world from the point of view of a victim.
Because he's been molested and you know what song starts the second it not super scraper's Joe.
I thought that's the song that play the creepers play throughout the whole movie which is I think what led to the trend of like every horror movie having an old song.
No, that's Sam Raimi did that way before they say when they deadly night did that way before they they the closing credits
I just watched it today the closing credits of that are
He did a Christmas song he didn't start that trust me. He far from started
He brought it back because you know and reading about it. I think horror was was on the outs essentially when Jeepers creepers came out
a lot of people how hold it in higher regard than they should but
His eye pops up in this
This kid, he's 21, but it pops up in his face and it's kind of a cool little ending.
And then the song that starts immediately goes, children, watch out.
Those are the first words that come out.
Children watch out the boogie man's coming.
And then it's a whole song about how children need to get away because the boogie man is coming.
This movie isn't about children unless it is.
And I think it is about child molestation.
I think I don't think you're wrong.
I think it you've convinced me that it's probably about child
Maloney either subconsciously or he's saying like this was me I do think it's
About child molestation and I think he's raw it sounds like he was trying to do
Something to say this is this was me and it's not good look at least I hope that's
What he was trying to do you know it made it like a I don't want to say I don't
want to say deep and get carried away but it made it a deeper viewing and it made
it just disturbing I never want to see it again because it felt like a guy like
well I can't make a movie about child most Asian so I'll just do it through a
horror movie which is sort of interesting until you find out that the man is
a pedophile. Beat and goo is the vanity plate. Beat and goo. B -E -A -T -N -G -U. Beat and
you. I don't even know what that means. Well, I would think it means beat and go. That's
what I thought it meant. Like, like, I'll beat you. Well, at one point, Justin Long
goes, what beat and go? And the lady goes, no, think about it a little harder. What else
could it mean? But I don't remember what else it does, man. Well, he's got whatever his
secret word is on his license plate. And it's, I mean, it's dumb. They start the movie
looking at trying to, they're playing a game of trying to decipher life. That is dumb.
I'm not going to argue with leave and fucking clues all over the place
No, he's saying a movie is fun and good doesn't mean I think everything about it is perfect. I
Don't have a problem with the word fun. I run the word good
It's not a good movie. I think it's a it's a well -made movie with several cool moments
Like when he cuts this cops head off while he's driving and then he like holds it up in the moonlight and it's sucking his tongue out of his head
I'm like, it's cool
It doesn't bother you that the whole thing is kind of built around a pun of Jeepers creepers. Where'd you get those peepers?
I don't think it's an eye movie is based around a pun tonight pun tonight pun
It's an eye pun. That's not what the whole movie is. It's one. Did you just said this wrong place for the entire movie
It ends on an eye gag. They're not trying to make you chuckle through the use of jeepers creepers. Yeah, I don't know
I don't know I don't know Pat
I don't understand some of these things that you like it. It's it's crazy to me
ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
People are like okay, the creeper's not your Michael Myers not your Freddie Krueger, but he's up there
I don't agree
But I think trying to create a new kind of villain like that with a with a story comes around every 23 years on the 23rd night
Or whatever they're trying to he's this pedophile is trying to do something kind of fun and bring back that old
80s fun horror movie and I think it succeeds in that regard now
I watch it as an adult in a very different way and I think it's interesting in its own way there too
Well, they wondered did he say did Francis Ford Coppola say he say to him, I want to make
a movie about pedophilia and I want to get my demons out through this horror movie.
And then Coppola said, sure, but then he couldn't tell anyone in the press that.
Well, of course he couldn't tell anyone in the press.
I find it hard to believe that that Francis Ford Coppola would turn a blind eye to a man
in that position if he did not think that he had redeemed himself.
Sure.
But I mean, he produced the movie where he molested the kid, you know, that's what I don't get
Well, you wouldn't distance yourself from that guy if you're producing of course you would
But you're also talking about 10 years later, and maybe maybe this was Copa's way of saying
Hey, man, you've did a really terrible thing on something I was involved with and now this is going to be the way that we make it better
I don't know. I'm just that's a very Italian thing
I just I it's strange to me because there was boycotts on powder and all powder was put out by Disney was their issue
But there's there's a rough there was boycotts of all of his stuff and the kid who was molested as an adult is now trying to boycott
Shit, well look. It's it's a very very very complicated thing and I feel terrible for that kid and
You know who the hell knows with this stuff, you know, it's well, you know that he did it
No, I know. It's terror. Now there were people on this
LN thing saying, it's a shame what they did to him. He
should be getting bigger budgets. The guy is the next
del Toro. Which is quickly shut down. That's an
insane sentence to make. The guy is not good. Well, I
think the horror genre is largely comprised of junk. I
think things good things get through. But your
average horror movie is junk. Right. It just is. I'm not trying to ghettoize an entire genre.
Right. But there's a lot of shit horror movies all through the years. Oh, there are tons
of shit horror movies. And this is one of them, which is why I can't believe that you're saying
it's good. I think this one is a damn sight better than your average horror movie.
Look, if you, if you, here's what, here's why I disagree with you. If you're talking about the
surface skimming horror that you get in your average run -of -the -mill
strip -mall movie theater yeah probably but that stuff is like the worst of
the fucking worst if you really delved if you went into my horror collection and
you watched every fucking movie I had up there which is a lot of movies I'd be
hard press for you to find many that you thought were better than Jeepers
Creepers. I think you'd think it was far worse than most of those films and those films are not
Award -type films. I mean, it's no I know they're fun and I like many of them
But I think the guys got something and there's cool shit in it and it's clearly made on a low -budget
But the effects are cool. I think the character is cool
All right, you heard it here folks and I think movie folks if you're gonna watch it again about a monster that drives a truck
And I bought the fucking scream factory thing with all the
Extras on it and I'm sure there'll be not one mention of pedophilia on it
There's a huge documentary about the making of the movie. I don't I don't I bet you they don't stray from it
Every Woody Allen documentary even the ones that he like gives you some approval to they talk about all that shit
They didn't do it. I bet they'll stay away from it
But I think it is the most interesting aspect of the movie and if you watch it with
my theory, which I don't know if it's only my theory for other people view it this way,
I think the movie is about an undeniable urge to do terrible things made by a pedophile
and it's a fascinating horror movie.
It's a cool, entertaining, fun horror movie made way more disturbing and sinister 15 years
later, now that I know the backstory of the guy.
you want to you want to wrap this up with bad movie reviews? Go for it. I always
enjoy this. Go for it. You'd never look like you enjoy it. But I enjoy it. Well I
never think to look up a bad story. This one's really easy. This is about this
one is for almost Christmas. Okay. Almost Christmas. Very quick one. This comes
from Jane Harwitz at the Washington Post. Is it a good movie? Not particularly.
like that's it yeah I just that's why like the Rod Tomatoes bad reviews because they're short
and they take the funniest part of the review yeah and you're like that's all I needed to know I
guess like that's I don't even look at Rod Tomatoes anymore I think it's a jockey side anyway
let's plug it away my short horror fiction column some severe situations can be found at
fangoria .com new story once a month for at least a few more months and it's
going pretty well. Thank you to the readers and follow me please on Instagram
particularly at Joe DeRosa Comedy. I am at Twitter and Instagram at the
Patrick Walsh. You can also for what might just be a couple more weeks watch my
classic vines on Vine at the Patrick Walsh because they're shutting that side
down. I had a real nice run there. I thought it was a fun app. I met some cool
people from it, did some fun things. I got nothing folks, the holidays I want to go home.
That's it.
All right.
This has been an episode of We'll See You In Hell. It's produced by Tom, exactly produced
by Tom, Mr. Fail, and produced by Ken Hanley of Finguria Entertainment. It's brought to you
by the podcast network, Fangoria, podcast network,
advertising inquiries, press opportunities,
information about, we'll see you in hell.
You can contact Ken as emails Ken at Fangoria .com.
Thank you to everybody for listening and downloading
and pushing us further and further up the charts.
Thank you for all your tweets.
Please keep them coming.
We've been doing very well.
We appreciate it greatly.
And then again, to just stress, Joe and I are at a point now
where we can start looking for advertising.
and we don't really know where to begin.
If you have a little business, you have an app,
you have a website, you wanna get a pretty,
I don't know if we can discuss our downloads,
but it's a very, very good amount,
and you can get a lot of eyes on it for a bargain
because we don't know what we're doing,
so you can take advantage of us.
Hit us up at the Patrick Walsh,
at Joderos Accomedy or head up Ken Hanley at Fangoria
and ask about advertising with us
because we'd love to get a little money for doing this.
Thanks guys.
Bye -bye.