I'm here for Bet Rivers Online Casino and Sportsbook with poker icon Phil Hellmuth.
And now, thanks to the excitement of Bet Rivers, I'm also a slots icon.
That's great.
And a same game parlay icon.
Cool, cool.
A blackjack icon, a money line icon, a roulette icon.
Take it from Phil Hellmuth.
If you love games, Bet Rivers is the place to play and bet.
Bet Rivers.
Games on.
Must be 21 plus and present in West Virginia.
Void were prohibited.
Terms and conditions apply.
Gambling problem, call 1 -800 -GAMBLER.
Hattaday presents, in the red corner, the undisputed, undefeated, weed -whacker guy.
Champion of hurling grass and pollen everywhere.
And in the blue corner, the challenger, extra strength, Hattaday.
Eye drops that work all day to prevent the release of histamines that cause itchy, allergy eyes.
And the winner by knockout is Hattaday.
Hattaday, bring it on.
I'll see you in hell.
And when the sound of your screams becomes a thing of my dreams, you know I'll say.
We're back.
We'll see you in hell.
Episode two.
Number two.
This is a big one tonight.
Nightmare on Elm Street.
Nightmare on Elm Street one.
Episode two.
Directed by Wes Craven.
The movie, not the episode.
He also directed the podcast tonight.
He's not happy with our performance thus far.
Get out of here.
Come on.
We're thrilled to be here doing this with the Fangoria podcast network.
Newly launched Fangoria podcast network.
A proud moment for both of us.
I'm Joe DeRosa.
I'm Pat Walsh.
Thrilled is extreme for me.
I'm I'm having a nice time, but I wouldn't say thrilled.
Fair enough.
I mean, you want to bite the hand that feeds.
No, absolutely not.
Listen, so we're jumping right in, I feel like.
You know, we open the series with Children of the Corn.
And now the second episode, we're going right to Nightmare on Elm Street.
I don't think it gets any more classic horror than this.
It doesn't.
We discussed doing Leprechaun.
Pat made the point of he didn't want people to think it was a thing where we were just
making fun of movies because I don't think anybody thinks Leprechaun's a great horror movie.
No, no, but we wanted it to be.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, we wanted it to be.
I wanted that remake, that new one that came out to be awesome.
The new Leprechaun.
Leprechaun Origins.
That happened.
Oh, yeah, I didn't know about that.
I met Ricky Gervais once on a radio show and I said,
why of all the things you made fun of on Life's Too Short, did you never make fun of Leprechaun?
Yeah.
And he was like, oh, man, I'm sure we did.
It was just probably got cut.
OK, fair enough.
Anyway, I cackled like a madman and told you he didn't believe in God.
Yeah.
Well, let's fire it up.
I actually get tense when we're talking and you haven't started it.
I don't know why.
Because this goddamn Apple TV, you know, it does this on and off thing.
Yeah.
All right, so we'll count to three and then say search.
And that's your cue to pause the podcast.
Search for Nightmare on Elm Street on whatever your device for streaming is.
These are all movies that are on Netflix instead.
You can go ahead and search for it now.
You don't need a countdown to search.
Well, let's just wipe your ass for you.
You know, let's give them I'm on Elm Street.
We'll say play.
You do a play and then immediate pause.
We're all on the pause screen.
And then we go one, two, three, play.
Yeah, but they need time to do that and it might not be fast enough.
So they're doing it now.
But what if they weren't?
Let's just give them a countdown.
Let's just count down everything you do.
All right.
Here's the countdown for you to go find.
When you hear me say search, you pause it, you go, you find it, whatever.
What are they pausing?
The podcast so they can go find the fucking movie.
They're listening to it.
Just let them go do it.
One, two, three, search.
Like a like a dog.
Joe in the morning when he wakes up, before he brushes his teeth,
I have to come over and go one, two, three, brush.
And then he brushes his teeth.
Now, just in case you got confused because Pat talked
through the part where we're supposed to say we're back.
We're going to give you another chance.
One, two, three, search.
We're back.
OK, here we go.
You've unpaused.
Now, this is how we do this.
You hit play.
And when it gets to the first frame of the screen of the movie,
you hit pause again.
And the reason we do that is because load times vary, right?
Am I over explaining this?
I feel like it couldn't be less complicated,
but being made more complicated.
OK, well, I'm trying my best.
What do you want for me?
I just feel like people are going to get confused.
I worry about that, too.
All you're doing, everybody, and I think we might have to adapt
this for a future one, is you're going to hit play and then hit pause.
So now we're all on a screen that has like one second or two seconds on it.
Right.
Because everybody's load time is different.
That's where we do that.
Everybody's load time, everybody's Wi -Fi is different.
You have time warning.
You're going to be waiting 30, 40 minutes.
Oh, as you would say.
You're going to do when we count down, one, two, three, play.
We all hit play and now we're going to watch.
OK, so now you've got it paused, hopefully at this point.
I hope so.
Or else, I mean, if you don't, I don't know.
I don't know how you hit play on this.
OK, OK, so here we go on play one, two, three play and it's playing.
There we go.
We got new from New Line Cinema.
New Line Cinema is on your screen.
All right.
Hopefully we're all on the same page.
And the thing I think you're missing, Joe, is that
that they don't need to pause the pocket.
They can look for this stuff while listening to it.
What if it takes them a while?
What if you're dealing with a slow man?
I mean, I think that's all I'm saying with the slow man.
He he's always got to quit.
Now, I'd like to start with something completely unrelated.
In the last episode, we talked about how much of a disappointment
the Poltergeist remake was.
Right.
And we both speculated that perhaps the new vacation would not be up to par.
It's got, I believe, a twenty six percent on Rotten Tomatoes.
Terrible reviews.
And Joe and friends, I'm here to tell you, I just came from seeing it.
And it is extremely funny.
The vacation remake.
There are a lot of big laughs in it here.
Get the fuck out of here.
Now, whenever they go for a huge like a set piece, a huge over the top scene,
those don't really work, but everything else works.
And now I'm going to confuse it even further by telling you
I didn't love Ed Helms or Christina Applegate in it.
But I thought the movie was really funny.
I thought you were going to go into a thing about the Nightmare on Elm Street.
We're going to get there.
OK.
But I thought it was very funny.
And the kids in this remake are so fucking funny.
The little kid.
Basically, the one gimmick is that it's a younger brother bullying his older brother.
I I.
Funny.
I thought those parts in the trailer were funny.
That's how you sound.
That kid cracked me up.
The little kid in that movie.
Both of them were great.
And the movie gave me a lot of laughs.
And I'm sorry I spoke ill of it and nobody's telling me to say that.
I promise.
Then why is it getting such bad reviews?
I think critics just kind of generally hate comedy.
I'd love to sit next to these people and see if they truly didn't laugh
throughout the movie.
I can't believe that you're telling me this movie is all right.
I'm going to believe it.
Listen, here's where I'm going to believe it.
Terminator Genesis, as we talked about in the last episode, terrible reviews.
Yeah, terrible rating.
I loved every minute of it.
I might just start going with the opposite.
And Rotten Tomatoes is usually if you really read the reviews, it's like, oh,
this is a good review and they're putting it as a bad or vice versa.
OK, fair enough.
But I'm telling you right now, it's very funny.
I usually go by what Richard Roper says.
I'm a big Richard Roper fan.
Sure.
Well, he's a very incisive film critic.
If you're watching the film along with us, which you know you don't have to do.
I guess we should have mentioned that at the top.
I forgot to.
But, you know, you don't have to watch the movie along with us.
You can just kind of listen to this.
Just walking through some pipes.
But if you are watching, she's walking through some pipes.
Now I'm having anxiety.
Film editor Rick Shane just just went off.
I'm having anxiety about the fact that we didn't tell them at the beginning
they didn't have to watch the movie.
Well, no, they know.
Do they?
Yeah, we have a we have a whole description of remember.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
OK, good enough.
Good enough.
I worry about everything.
Here we go.
I wish we had slammed Peter Travers because he's a far worse critic than Richard Roper.
No, I really meant what I said.
I like Richard Roper.
I like him, too.
He's a he's a very like man of the people type guy.
I loved Ebert.
Ebert's my favorite of all time.
There's there's no better film critic.
I don't know if I'd be doing what I'm doing without Roger.
Here's my favorite Ebert review.
You ready?
Yeah.
He said Indiana Jones in the Kingdom of the Crystal Skull loved it.
And he said, was it as good as the first one or the second one or the third one?
I don't know.
That's like asking me if I eat four pounds of sausage, which pound was the most delicious?
Oh, well.
I'll tell you that fourth pound was not the most delicious.
You should have a little better memory than that.
It was a great analogy.
My favorite Ebert review is of a horror movie.
M. Night Shyamalan's The Village.
And it's such a funny, perfectly written review.
And I urge you to look it up online because I won't do it justice.
But the final paragraph of it is such perfect, funny, trash in the movie comedy writing.
I loved it.
What did he say?
Uh, we'll see.
I just said if you should probably look it up because I'm going to botch it.
But the gist of it was, uh, it's the kind of twist that I'm going to botch it.
It's the kind of twist that makes you want to.
I'm going to botch it.
Look, are you saying you're going to botch it as if it was smooth sailing up until this point?
You forced me to say it when I said, God damn it, Joe.
Now, here's a part that I'm glad you asked that question.
This is a thing I was always slightly confused about in the original Nightmare on Elm Street.
Is she, are these children dancing and singing really there?
Or is she dreaming this right now?
Because look, this is reality.
And they shot that in a very ghostly way.
Are they supposed to be the girls that Freddie molested?
Well, they never say molested in this, in this original.
That's something they more clarified in the remake, which I enjoyed.
Uh, I know people say it sucked, but it did suck to those people.
You didn't see parts four, five, and six in the theater like I did.
I mean, it was just nice to have a scary Freddie back again.
I was happy about that.
New Nightmare was good.
Do you like Freddie versus Jason?
I like it now.
I had to watch an interview with the director who said he wanted to make like a classic
monster fight movie, like a Godzilla versus King Kong, like over the top, crazy, whatever.
Once I saw that and understood where he was coming from with it, I was like, okay,
now I like it.
Right.
But I had to see that because I went into the theater again, opening day.
And from the minute in the opening monologue where Freddie goes,
then they forgot about me and that's a bitch.
I was just like, what is he going to surfboard right now?
I never liked his wisecracks.
I went into Freddie versus Jason thinking it was a legal thriller along the lines of
Kramer versus Kramer and they would each have attorneys and maybe it was a divorce case.
For custody of the kids.
Custody of the kids that they would molest or murder.
Yeah, who gives to molest and murder these children?
Going back to Vacation for no reason, since this isn't a vacation podcast,
but when you watch the new movie, note that there's a bizarre obsession with pedophilia
jokes.
Like there's 80 of them and they're not all great.
No wonder why they wouldn't take some out.
It's a little weird.
Who's making the pedophilia jokes?
They're everyone.
Everyone in the movie is basically hinted at as being kind of a pedophile.
Want to make note again, second episode in a row, strong pedophilia theme.
I'm telling you once again, it's on the brain vacation.
And we're watching a movie about a pedophile.
One of the most famous pedophiles ever.
He's not quite a pedophile in this one.
What are you talking about?
He's a child murderer in this one.
They don't ever say the pedophile thing.
Sure they do, don't they?
No, they make a point to say it in the remake.
And if you watch any behind the scenes stuff with the remake, they say like,
we wanted to make him even more unlikable.
So we brought out the pedophile undertones.
I thought for sure they did.
I mean, I guess the assumption is in this that he is, I mean.
How old is Johnny Depp here, 17?
I think his age is gorgeous.
He's just beautiful.
Now he looks kind of like Steven Tyler floated up on the beach, but still beautiful.
He looks like Steven Tyler got raped by Stevie Ray Vaughan's scarf collection.
Or Steven Tyler scarf collection.
Both Stevens big on scarves.
Yeah, that's true.
Now, which of these two were you more attracted to?
Heather Langenkamp or I don't remember Tina's real name, but the blonde.
I think I'd go with the blonde.
I think she turns me on a little bit more.
It's a little of a pixie vibe.
No, I always loved Langenkamp.
I liked her on a ABC TGIF sitcom called Just the Ten of Us.
Yeah.
About like a family of basketball players.
Yeah, that was a coach.
That sitcom was shot about eight years after this and she played a character two years younger.
Yeah, that's true.
Which always confused me, but I did like a spin off for Growing Pains.
That's true.
It was a good show.
Yeah, yeah.
And then now Scream, which we also took bandaid about viewing and talking about tonight and
maybe will in the future.
Of course we will.
But Scream, I guess clearly owes a lot to this movie directed by the same guy.
And they found the exact same person, Skeet Ulrich, to play the Johnny Depp role.
Like you wouldn't know they were different men at that time.
What happened, Skeet Ulrich?
Where are you?
I don't know.
I guess maybe because his name was Skeet and then when it hit the rap world,
his name basically represented coming on something.
It's one of my favorite Hollywood Minute jokes by David Spade.
It was when he was big and they put up a picture, Skeet Ulrich, and he went,
Hey, Skeet, Johnny Depp called.
He wants his DNA back.
Yeah, I love the balls of David Spade.
Like really not having any sort of film career at that point,
just taking on the hugest people in Hollywood.
Got in trouble for it.
I know I got in trouble for it.
Yeah, Murphy.
Yeah, but it's great stuff.
It's great stuff.
It's the good stuff.
It's the old stuff, as they say.
Now, your favorite nightmare on Elm Street is this one?
Yeah, I mean, without question, number one in my book is the best.
I think number three is the second best, and I think seven is the third best.
I own them all.
I've only seen one, two, three, and New Nightmare,
and I've seen all the modern day ones that I thought were all kind of trash.
Two's got some fun moments, but it's not a great movie,
but I put it above five and six without question.
There's a great documentary about the whole franchise that discusses the
intense homosexual overtones in Nightmare on Elm Street 2.
Yes.
And I got to tell you, they weren't far off.
It's like there's a really interesting thing going on there,
and it's like not that subtly dumb either.
No, no, it's written or directed by a gay guy.
I think a gay guy wrote it, and there's a tremendous documentary
called Never Sleep Again.
That's what I'm talking about, yeah.
On Netflix, where he's laughing like,
yeah, I just thought it was fun to put a lot of gay undertones through the whole thing.
Oh, it made the movie a blast to watch.
I like it.
Wow, they're really going for it.
You got that fucking gym teacher that's like,
I'm going to make you do laps at midnight because you caught me in a gay bar.
Now hit the showers.
And then Freddy chooses to whip him.
Yeah, yeah.
Freddy like whips him while masturbating or something like that.
The one part I didn't agree with was when they go in that documentary,
they're like, it's clearly a gay metaphor when he could run.
He's with the woman that he loves, and he leaves her to run and retreat to his friend's bedroom.
And I was like, well, he runs away because he's going to turn into Freddy and kill her,
and he's terrified.
And he goes to his boy's house.
That's what any guy that age would do.
I think he also, though, has a pretty lengthy choreographed dance in his bedroom.
Yeah, that ends with him popping a cork as his dick.
There it is.
Yeah, it's an enjoyable film, though.
The part with the bird bursting into flames is pretty crazy.
Yeah, I remember that.
And then the end is the standard house party.
Actually, horror movies don't give you a lot of house party getting attacked by a killer.
Wes Craven says in that documentary that was the part where he realized
he was like, they blow it.
It's off the rails.
Why is Freddy appearing in real life?
Yeah, there's something like if there's that many people around,
you're not that scared because it's kind of like, well, at least you're there in it with people.
And then watching it, you're like, well, they're not going to kill everybody.
By the way, if you're watching along with us, Rick just came inside of Tina.
I mean, he might have pulled out.
We don't know.
He might have had a rubber in those days.
You're wondering who Rick is.
He's the guy that you can't tell if he's Italian or Puerto Rican.
He's just kind of right up the middle there.
Maybe a black Irish.
Nobody knows.
Sure.
Is there some there's a little nudity in this, I think.
We were bemoaning last night the lack of nudity in the horror genre,
which I think is a real shame because you could always count on teen movies
and you could always count on horror movies.
And now neither, neither.
And usually they're PG -13 in both cases.
I watched Mirrors this afternoon starting The Great Key for Sutherland.
And you see Amy Smart from the back naked.
I remember that.
You see her butt.
I mean, it's just a tremendous shot.
And I was out.
I was by myself.
It was three o 'clock in the afternoon.
And when they showed her ass, I went, oh, nice.
Which should mean that I missed that.
Yeah, I should be never allowed to be to date ever again.
It's a really real creep.
Oh, nice.
Don't say that in real life.
When you see when I see Amy Smart naked.
When you're making love to Amy Smart,
who would not be doing anything particularly smart that night.
I'll tell you that much.
Look at this hospital blanket they have on the bed.
This bright blue hospital blanket.
I want to say last night I said I made some remark that I didn't know
if any girls would be listening to this podcast.
And I want to retract that.
It was a very sexist and stupid thing to say.
And I know many girls who watch horror movies.
I don't know why I said it.
Can't believe that's the thing you're worried about.
Well, I have to saying that the happiness is a tremendous film.
A lot of people think happiness is a great film.
The films can be good about difficult subjects.
I just want to mark two episodes in a row.
Lots of pedophilia talk and talks of the gay undertones in a horror movie.
Because last night we got into the molester that made powder and fun house.
Or fun.
It was a fun house or was it?
It was called the fun house.
I believe so.
Oh, no.
What's the movie Sam Rockwell?
Sam Rockwell is very it has a very early film.
That's a horror movie.
It's not fun house though that I do not know.
I can't remember this one of my favorite parts of the movie when Freddie
comes through the rubbery with that.
He makes the wall into like a latex.
Just really great, cheap, well done special effects that don't look cheap
as compared to our last one, The Children of the Corn.
Look at that.
That looks perfect.
And you know this movie had no budget.
Yeah, and it looks real as shit.
And Children of the Corn decided to put like a sticker over the screen
to represent a man turning to flame.
By the way, this whiskey I picked up today is
delectable.
What's the name of it?
Let's give him a shout out.
I can't remember.
I left it in the other room.
Papa Bourbon's Drink Hutch.
Something like that.
I think Whiskey Dicks O 'Hallahan.
Yeah, I've met him once or twice.
Good guy.
Great whiskey.
Any you think they're maybe doing a little Christ symbolism
with Freddie coming out of the wall in front of that crucifix?
I don't know what it would be and I'm not smart enough to speak further on that,
but maybe they are.
Well.
Is that Ernie?
Cookie jar is Ernie, right?
Yes, that's an Ernie cookie jar from the back.
I never noticed that good.
I absolutely good.
I think the I don't think that's Christ symbolism.
I think it's supposed to be the symbolism is he knocks Jesus off the wall like
God can't protect you.
Sure, sure.
When he comes out of the rubber wall.
Is this a look you like the lady in a dress shirt and no slack?
Does anybody not like it?
Just fantastic.
Is anybody complaining about this look?
I gotta say, it doesn't happen much in my day to day life,
but it happens in movies all the damn time.
Now, if you're watching along with us and if you're not to worry, it'll be described.
We're about to see a shot and it's the scariest Freddie has ever been and will ever be.
They will never make Freddie scarier than this moment.
Tina is now in the alleyway.
They stole that shot from Paperboy, the video game.
Yeah.
Of a trash can.
Well, it's like the part coming up where the guy in the boombox
makes a car crash happen.
Yeah, exactly.
That is the scariest thing ever.
The long arm Freddie and he's just pretty laughing like a witch.
It's so fucking scary and it's something that would happen in a dream where you'd be like.
This is God puts the claw over his face.
There's that look at the way he's running.
Yeah.
Oh, it's so scary.
And he's just toying with her.
That's what the great part is.
There he goes.
He disappears, reappears in front of her.
He can catch her if he wants, but he's going to have some fun with her.
Now, going back to Paperboy, the video game, I.
But can we just can we point out this part?
This is the second scariest thing.
Are we doing a paper for the video game podcast?
Are we doing a nightmare on Elm Street?
Cuts the fingers off and green slime jizzes out of the.
Yeah, it's pretty gross.
Fingers should have been thicker and pussier.
Well, sorry, Pat, that it didn't more closely resemble actual come.
I apologize.
I do come green.
Well, did you ever see the watch Vince Vaughn movie?
I sure did.
I think you like that quite a bit more than I did.
I loved it.
But my favorite joke is when the Indian guy is rubbing the green slime between his fingers
and he says it does feel like come the taste, the color, the texture, and it's bright green.
Yeah.
And then you find out later is an alien.
You're like, oh, yeah, right.
Alien come.
That's a good.
I remember that joke.
Great joke.
This is amazing.
Special effects right here.
It is similar to the Joe Beth Williams and Poltergeist being thrown around the road.
Very similar.
Anything hotter, anything hotter than Joe Beth Williams and Poltergeist.
We didn't touch on that last episode.
I used to really I would like I would be like this is going to be my wife.
I would like her to be Joe Beth Williams and Poltergeist.
And any more any more of a dad than Craig T. Nelson.
I know.
And what I also love is that that movie's PG and the parents are getting high up in their bedroom.
They're getting just sitting in bed getting high.
I love that about Poltergeist.
I'll tell you what my dream is.
You know, Sam Rockwell was in the Poltergeist remake.
I do.
Oh, and in that one, they drink a half a glass of whiskey instead of getting high, by the way,
which tells you everything you know about the remake.
Yeah.
Here's my dream.
I want to make a coach remake starring Sam Rockwell now.
OK, well, it's coming back to TV.
I know.
Let's get the success.
Let's get Sam Rockwell in there.
Now, who's playing Daubert or Dwayne the Rock Johnson?
I put Dwayne the Rock Johnson in the Daubert role.
I put a tanning Chatham in the Daubert role.
Tanning Chatham.
I think you're done drinking.
We're 20 minutes in.
You just said tanning Chatham.
Oh, Channing Tatum.
Sorry.
That's great casting, though.
You know, it's good cast.
I'll see if Tanning's available.
There's Michael Jackson from the Beat It video just hanging out in the.
My take on Channing Tatum has always been that both of his names sound like things
you'd call your taint.
Yeah, I can see that.
We did that as I wrote that as a joke for the Pete Holmes show.
I said, did they deliver it?
Yeah.
Oh, baby.
Lick my Channing or lick my.
And then again, then she goes, what do you mean?
He goes, you know what I mean, my Tatum.
Classic dirty stuff.
So ladies out there, if you ever consider having sex with Joe,
just know he might say things like lick my Channing, referring to his taint.
And he also, upon seeing your butt, might go, oh, nice.
So Nancy is now on the police station with her parents played by Home Over Jones,
John Saxton, John Saxton from Enter the Dragon fame and barely clinging to his hair.
And a woman who is the most melodramatic actor of all time.
I've only ever seen her in.
I mean, this is just.
Yeah.
Look at the just weepy eyes.
She looks like Petunia Pig from the Looney Tunes or something.
Who's Petunia Pig?
Porky's girlfriend.
Who's girlfriend?
Porky's like the Minnie Mouse, Daisy Duck.
You're blending all kinds of cartoon worlds right now.
I'm saying they all had their girlfriend and Petunia Pig was the girl.
OK.
They're all boring, bland characters, unfortunately.
This guy should take some of his eyebrows and put it on top of his head.
I love John Saxton.
Did you ever see Enter the Dragon?
Of course.
And he's in Rambo, right?
No, you're thinking of Richard Crenna.
No, I'm not.
I think John, I know who Richard Crenna is, but I think I think he might be in Rambo,
but maybe he's not.
He's in Rambo.
I thought he was.
Look, I don't know.
Well, I love John Saxton first blood same old.
I can't remember the line that he says to to Black Belt Jones in Enter the Dragon,
but it's great.
Look at this lady hitting the vodka at seven a .m.
There's something me and this lady have in common.
Anyway, back to Paperboy.
The obstacles in Paperboy, it's like a trash can lid guy with a boom box,
you know, rabid dog.
Then don't forget, rabid dog and rabid, just a dog.
Yeah.
And then within seconds, you're face to face with the grim reaper.
That's quite an escalation of obstacles, Paperboy.
I don't know.
Is this a bit?
I don't know if it is.
Sounds like a bit to me.
I send this to Jerry Seinfeld, which I believe he watches.
Have you played this paperboy game?
You seen this thing?
Then shows up the grim reaper.
I remember encountering this guy many times in my paper route.
I said five minutes ago, I'm dealing with a can of Sprite.
Now I'm face to face with grim death.
I like I don't know if any video game has and you don't know who that guy is
against the tree.
Is he real?
Is he not real?
Is it in her head?
Is it not?
And I've seen this 10 times.
He's just a dude watching her, man.
Like in Dining Dark.
But now he's gone.
Orange outfit.
I bet they got that from this.
Well, out jumps the Italian and or Puerto Rican kid.
He's got her in the bushes now.
Because his shirt and a leather jacket.
Here's what happens if you're not watching with us.
Tina, my favorite girl, is now dead because Freddie killed her with his long arms.
And her boyfriend that jizzed inside of her just before that happened.
Right.
A boyfriend here played by a young Liza Minnelli.
They think that he killed her.
So he's on the he's on the lamb, if you will.
Yeah.
From the cops.
So now he's trying to tell Nancy he didn't do it.
But of course, the cops show up because her dad's a cop.
And they're going to some for some reason, barefoot.
He's wearing old Navy jeans, no shirt, barefoot and a leather jacket.
He's dressed exactly like Stanley Tucci was in that Levi's commercial.
He did all those years ago.
I know that's a deep cut, people, but trust me, it exists.
Tucci in this.
There's a Stanley Tucci Levi's commercial.
It was one of his first acting jobs.
It's out there.
Guys got a body like a rock.
OK, I wouldn't doubt that.
Now, this is what I was going to ask was.
Wait a minute.
Oh, paperboy.
It wasn't a question was what I was going to say about paperboy.
Yeah.
I don't know that any video game.
Look, oh, by the way, that's the lady from something about Mary.
It's none of Mary and now insidious.
And now she got this role and the insidious role because her brother,
Bob Shea, is the head of New Line Cinema.
But I think she's a great actress in her own right.
I love her to pieces and she's fantastic.
I love her to pieces.
And I plan to have sex with a young lynn shea here.
Really?
I would absolutely go on that far, but I think she's a handsome woman.
I'd like to.
I would enjoy that.
Mousy.
I like it.
OK, great.
Now, by the way, third recurring theme.
Kingpin to two episodes in a row.
I well, you figure a movie is at least 90 minutes.
I'll never go 90 minutes without talking about.
Look at this shirt that this kid's wearing.
Yeah, it looks like a stained glass window.
He's a look.
He's a guy that likes a party.
Right.
He's the guy that has a donkey at his party in the 80s.
Do you remember here?
Now, this should be a segment on the podcast.
When when was the first time you saw this movie?
Do you remember?
Oh, yeah, man, I was I was 11 years old and I was obsessed with it.
OK, it was the greatest thing I'd ever seen.
I mean, this was my godfather at 11 years.
Oh, OK.
Oh, that's disturbing.
Nancy's friend Tina just showed up in a body bag.
And I think if I'm not mistaken, a worm is going to come out of her mouth in a minute.
I think so.
Or a snake of some kind.
Now, see, because of my fear of VHS,
horror boxes and the fact that I was not allowed to see already movies until I was
actually 17 years old, which really don't care for my parents doing that to me,
especially since I was obsessed with movies my whole life.
Sure.
I don't think I saw Nightmare on Elm Street till I was about 17 years old.
And I thought this is pretty scary.
But I had it built up my mind as though it was going to ruin my life.
It is a scary movie.
For sure.
Well, the thing I like about 80s horror movies is you get to notice what have
the clothing styles were back then.
It's crazy how much things change in so little amount of time.
Nancy's dressed like my aunt Rita.
Well, some of these outfits, you know, are going to are kind of big in hipster circles,
like where we live here.
Nobody's wearing a pink sleeveless sweater.
You can see it out there with a collared shirt and khakis, baggy khakis.
This lady shows up in the documentary.
Where's your past lady?
She's not great.
She's great right here when she turns into Freddie.
Yeah, I take it back.
She's pretty good.
Yeah, she's awesome.
And there's leaves in the hallway when Nancy starts dreaming.
This is this is this is what makes this movie so great.
He adds these West Craven was so good at adding these elements to the set.
The different sets that really made it feel like a nightmare.
Like in the beginning, you see loose cattle running for no reason.
Yeah.
Through a watery like boiler room hallway.
She's in her.
She's running through her high school.
Now the hallways are all dark.
There's leaves blowing around.
Freddie has the extended arms.
These are these are very specific qualities of nightmares.
And I think that's really what gave this movie.
Yeah, I mean, I've seen it a bunch and it's always feels kind of fresh to me, too.
Why do you think because this movie, I think, cost something like
five million and made fifty or something like that.
You know, horror movies usually make good money.
We can look it up.
Why aren't more horror movies good?
You know, it's do they feel like they'll just make anything now
and they're all kind of the same.
And why can't like everyone's scared of stuff?
Why can't you put your own personal take on a horror movie and make it good?
It's my philosophy that horror most of the time gets the porn treatment.
And they say, well, as long as you have your money shot, it's who cares.
Yeah, true.
And the money shot in a horror movie is a kill.
Uh, and I think that just like with porn,
you know, there are the Burt Reynolds guys from Boogie Nights being like,
I want to make a film.
Oh, look, he had maggots coming out of his bra.
There are those Burt Reynolds type saying, I want to make a film
and I want to make something truly erotic.
And then there are other guys saying, it doesn't matter.
Yeah, have people fuck on camera for as cheap as possible.
And that's all that that's all anybody cares about.
Now, probably the best example of like a porny type horror movie
is like the Final Destination series where it's just kill, kill, kill.
But those are really fun.
Like, yeah, put the time in to have a clever kill, you know, at the very least.
I like that series.
All of those have really good kills.
Well, this is why I can't believe that you're a fan of the Jeepers Creepers franchise.
Look, maybe I'll rewatch it.
I really enjoy Jeepers Creepers.
Please don't rewatch it till we can rewatch it on here.
Yeah, I just I'm dumbfounded that you thought that movie was good.
I don't know.
Sometimes I just happen to be out of the house, you know,
when I go to a movie, I'm like, yeah, I like that.
But it came out when we were like 17 or so.
No, it came out when I was living in New York.
So I was 23 years old.
Really? I liked it.
I don't know what to tell you.
I had a nice time.
Freddie also in these in these original films had a much more pervy sexual vibe to him.
Yeah. Does he not later?
No, later he's putting on sunglasses and eating pizzas and shit.
And he kind of lost like what made him a creep.
Isn't Roseanne in like the fifth one?
She's in the sixth one.
OK, they play crazy people in the town.
All right.
Yeah, it's it's Freddie's Dead is is an abomination.
I mean, it's you know, I still watch it.
Yeah, because it's just, you know, it's it's bad fun.
But like and you also own and I guess must enjoy the Freddie TV show, right?
I own every episode.
OK, it's a shit show.
Congrats, Joe.
Do you like the show?
No. Why do you want fucking terrible?
A friend of mine.
I'm a completist.
Yeah, I enjoy the fact that I own it.
Yeah.
And I enjoy watching it with people to be like, look at this.
Right.
But it's you know, so for camp fact value, I enjoy it.
But no, it's I can't stand by it in any way.
Is it he's haunting a new person each week or is there a cast that we follow or what goes on?
Well, you know how everybody who is a fan of Nightmare on Elm Street thinks,
you know, if they only would do this without Freddie,
that's who that that's who the show is for.
He's in like two episodes.
The other ones are just like about people living in nightmares.
And that's it.
And he's an England in the other ones.
He's he hosts all of them.
But it's literally he's like the crypt keeper.
Yeah.
And then there's two episodes that the Freddie character is actually in.
You think and even those aren't that great.
Huh?
What what kind of house you think England's living in?
Like, is he doing all right?
He's got to be, man.
I mean, it's it's the money he must have made off of this.
People are often wrong, you know, like he probably made 50 ,000 for this.
And then by the end, at the very most, he's getting a million,
you know, and that that money is twenty five years old at this point.
Well, look, let's I mean, here's the thing.
They couldn't do this series without him.
So there's no way that by the third movie, he wasn't like, go fuck yourselves.
If you want to do this, this is how shitty contracts.
We're like here.
You're only going to get X amount of dollars no matter how many times we do.
Well, let's let's look up Robert England.
All right.
Celebrity Net Worth.
Is there any reliance on this?
How do they know it on Celebrity Net Worth?
That's why I'm asking.
Is this any any way reliable or is this just a shit show?
I think people would be a lot more upset if everyone knew exactly what they 14 million.
All right.
I'm getting 14 million.
I'll buy that.
How much do you think he made for the Adventures of Ford Fairlane starring
I mean, look, even if you make scale on a movie like that,
the unions make sure that you get your residuals and stuff.
That movie made money even though it was wasn't as big as it was supposed to be.
Yeah, you know, that's true.
So, I mean, you know, I I'd imagine it was pretty decent.
I'd imagine.
Yeah.
What I love when you go back and watch documentaries about old movies,
which I always do if they're available on the DVD.
I love that shit.
Yeah.
The make like the making of.
Right.
It was a good name.
It'll be like it'll be like it'll be like Ford Fairlane, the Adventures of creating a movie.
Yeah, exactly.
Who framed Roger Rabbit?
I'll tell you who framed the movie Roger Rabbit, the the people who shot and directed it.
Like, wow, that's the title you went with anyway.
I love how especially like in this like I watched a lot of this
Nightmare on Elm Street documentary.
It's about eight hours long.
It's so long, but everybody in it seems hurt that their character,
what they think, I don't know how they went ahead and made Nightmare on Elm Street four
without janitor number two is like janitor number two's opinion.
Right.
You know, everybody in it is like I was shocked that I wasn't asked back.
As though people are wondering what happened to like the guy
who died at the end of Nightmare on Elm Street eight.
Right.
I mean, this is such a great shot.
Nancy's in the bathtub.
I mean, that's a poster right there.
That's a clock coming out.
They did this in the remake.
I was very happy that they paid tribute to the scene in the remake
and they didn't really change it.
Okay.
Maybe I do want to have sex with Nancy as she lays there.
Sprawl spread eagle in a bathtub.
Oh, nice.
Tasty.
I'm kidding.
Come on.
Bath pillow.
Who has that bath pillow in the tub with them?
Well, although let me ask you this.
Look at the towel.
Look at the bathtub.
Look at the sheet.
They're all that same color of blue.
Is that telling me anything?
I mean, I don't know.
Does blue signify evil or something signifies?
Maybe it signifies Friday's coming because so far every time we've seen blue,
Freddy shows up.
Well, let's look that up.
All right.
I like this scene a lot.
Yes, it's a great, great, great scene.
Look at the little nudity right there.
Once again, getting pulled under water in a bathtub and it's an endless bottomless sea.
I mean, it's just good.
It's good nightmare stuff.
I agree.
They know how to do this.
What I and I know a good nightmare because I wake up nearly every night,
nearly screaming because I have night terrors.
You do about me.
I do.
I'm every night like I'm in a horror movie and go.
I'm not looking forward to that when we're like the odd couple and live together.
You mean like in three months?
When my house is foreclosed.
Well, join the club on that one.
I was I have it happen a whole lot and it's not it's no way to live.
I don't know what it says about me, but I have a real problem with them.
With the night terrors.
Yep.
You're about the third or fourth friend of it.
Look, there's another towel and the bathrobe is blue and the hand towel is blue.
All right.
This is what I found big on that color coatings movies.
This is what I found.
Ready?
Let's see if we can make any link here.
Blue symbolizes trust, loyalty, wisdom, confidence, intelligence, faith.
You just looked up what does blue represent in general?
Not in this movie.
Yeah, but I'm saying let's.
I'm sure Wes Craven didn't go.
The door is blue to the house.
The front door is the same color blue.
I think I really made a big discovery here.
Blue symbolizes trust, loyalty, wisdom, confidence, intelligence, faith, truth and heaven.
Yeah.
Heaven.
Yeah, baby.
Blue is considered beneficial to the mind and body.
It slows human metabolism and produces a calming effect.
Dreams.
Sleep.
Blue is strongly associated with tranquility and calmness.
That is it has a meaning.
The people it's it's it's featured every time the people are having nightmares
being killed by Freddy because it's calming, it's soothing, it makes them go to sleep.
That's that's very interesting.
I think that's what it is.
Yeah.
Very excited about that.
Now, here, Skeet O 'Rourke comes in this exact same way and scream.
Does he really?
Yeah.
Through the window.
Johnny Depp's coming through the window of Heather Lang and Caps bedroom.
Yeah.
He's climbed the thorny rose bush vine outside of the house.
Now, when I was a kid, the only way I could watch R -rated movies was if they were on channel 11.
He's got blue sweatpants on now.
Look, I've made a really great discovery here.
This is nuts.
It's all over the fucking place.
Look at that tush.
Who?
On John or Heather?
Let's pretend I'm talking about Heather.
Heather also has like a giant mosquito bite on her forehead or a zit or something.
She does.
But I like that they left it there.
That's like in The Witches of Eastwick.
There's a scene where Michelle Pfeiffer is a huge cold sore in her lip.
Really?
And it's real.
And the director was like, no, leave it because you're sickly in this scene
and that makes you more human.
And she went with it.
You know who that director was?
George Miller, director of Mad Max.
He did Witches of Eastwick?
He sure did.
I mean, which babe and babe pig in the city?
Yeah, only the second one.
Yeah, I had a tweet once.
I'm looking for a babe in the streets and a babe pig in the city in the sheets.
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, I still think that's funny.
I mean, I mean, I would have went like this.
I'm looking for a babe.
And by that, I mean a pig in the city.
I would have went like that.
All right.
Probably less fun.
I think it's tighter and that's how you get to it.
Well, you know, it had somewhere in the 178 faves range.
So I guess America thought differently.
All right.
Sorry.
George Miller.
Now, Witches of Eastwick.
Yeah.
What bothers me is, was Witches of East dead in the TV show in any way linked to it?
No, not linked at all.
They just ripped it off like that?
Yeah.
It's embarrassing.
Uh, I was just about to say, and now she's gone, but Langenkamp looks exact again.
Not it looks exactly like, but it gives me a very similar vibe to Jennifer Jason Lee
in like fast times, which came out the same year.
I mean, Jennifer Jason Lee, there's another one just just smoking 80s hot.
You know, Joe, these these women have lives and personalities.
It's not just, you know, pieces of meat.
All right.
Fair enough.
But I do love her.
You'll be apologizing for that next week.
I apologize for my I mean, it's a very apologizing, heavy time in American culture.
I don't think Jennifer Jason Lee would be upset if she heard me say smoking hot.
Probably not.
Yeah, not.
Yeah, I love JJL.
She's been great in so many things.
There's a great movie called Georgia where she plays an alcoholic.
And she does like a 10 minute like terror.
She thinks she's a great singer and her sister actually is a really good singer.
So then like she does this 10 minute Van Morrison song and it sounds so terrible
and she's so wasted that it's one of the hardest things I've ever had to watch.
Check that out, Georgia.
I'm sure it's not on DVD.
It's a VHS maybe only.
I don't know how you're going to watch.
How do people watch movies that aren't on DVD?
Netflix streaming like we are right now.
Well, this is on DVD in blue, right?
Sure.
I have a huge VHS collection, but nobody has a VCR anymore.
I had a tremendous VHS collection.
I had a basement wall covered.
The prized possession or the centerpiece of it was the film Fatso starring Dom DeLuise.
Sure.
I remember with Anne Baccaron.
Can't get the fucking thing on DVD.
It's $150 on DVD.
Met Peter.
I'm sorry.
Met not Peter DeLuise, the other DeLuise kid.
Michael DeLuise.
Yeah.
In a diner recently.
Okay.
Told him how much I love Fatso.
He said, I have an original poster.
I'll give it to you.
That's awesome.
Never heard from him again.
Was Dom DeLuise a clausda gay man?
We got to go find Michael DeLuise right now.
I don't think it's going to be that hard.
I don't know him.
Is he on Twitter?
I don't know.
My friend knew him.
I got to find him.
I had always heard tell that Dom DeLuise was a clausda gay man.
I don't know if that's true.
I had heard that too.
I don't think so, though.
I think he just was a mildly effeminate guy.
Michael DeLuise, great guy.
One of the nicest, like the gentlest eyes I've ever seen in a man.
Okay.
Seriously.
And was thrilled.
I was apologetically saying to him, I love the movie Fatso.
And I'm sure you get this all the time.
Yeah.
He was so clearly touched.
Well, it's not here.
This is what I always say when we live in here in Los Angeles.
We see a lot of celebrities of all of all.
Sure.
Ranges.
Yeah.
A list down to your Z list.
And the good rule of thumb is like, if you go up to Tom Cruise,
you're like, Tommy, I love Top Gun.
He might humor you, but he doesn't care.
He doesn't want to talk to you.
If you go up to like, I saw Richard Reel in a diner the other day.
Who the hell is that?
Richard Reel was in office space.
He was the guy who goes, it's a jump to conclusions man.
I love that guy.
And he was on Cheers.
And he was also, you're going to love this connection.
Remember last night I brought up mysterious skin about the pedophile?
Yeah.
He played a John, like a John who picked up a street kid to like have sex with him.
So in the movie, he has sex with Joseph Gordon Leavitt.
He's like a disgusting hotel pervert.
And how old is Leavitt in the movie?
18.
But like, is he playing a kid though?
Yeah.
You know, he's, well, you know, he's playing like a teenager.
He's supposed to be like 15 in it.
He got molested and now he's like a hustler.
Okay.
I got you.
But, uh, so Richard Reel sitting there and I was,
I was saying to the person I was with, I was like,
Richard Reel is the kind of guy who you go up to him in a diner and you're like,
Hey man, you're just the best character actor.
And I always love seeing you and stuff.
So funny in office space and blah, blah, blah.
And he would talk to you for an hour and be so flattered and go home and tell his wife.
Sure.
Some, some kid came out to him in a diner and I didn't do it,
but like those are the people who love.
Why didn't you do it?
Because he left while I was talking about how these people love being approached.
He left.
This is another great nightmare detail when Nancy's trying to run up the steps
and she's stepping in marshmallow.
The steps are turning into marshmallow.
Great point.
This just is a dream.
It's not real.
This is just a dream.
That's what she keeps saying.
And then boom through the mirror, Freddy.
What a great shot.
Good scare.
What a great shot, man.
Um, let me, I want to tweet out right now that we're watching this
and that people should be sending us questions.
So if you could talk for a moment.
Well, now do I need to say one, two, three tweet before you?
No, I'm just going to, I know you're like a countdown show.
A lot of smart mouth coming from you tonight.
Uh, why don't you just say, by the way, you're you have off tomorrow?
Uh, I do have off tomorrow.
Yes, I'm off on script.
I mean, do we take this party on the town after this podcast?
Yeah, let's go get drunk.
We're sitting here sipping whiskies.
That sounds fantastic.
I got a late morning tomorrow.
Tomorrow's my non -workout day.
Yeah, you're exactly like me, Joe, and that if a drop of alcohol touches your lips,
you want to go drink until two in the morning.
Yeah, it's a, it's a problem.
It's a sad, pathetic quote.
Yeah, you're never going to be like, yeah, I'll have a beer.
You have the beer and then you have 17 beers.
But I should say this isn't a drunk podcast and we're not drunk.
We're not drunk, but I mean, we've had, I had two wines before this and then
I'm sipping this delicious whiskey and I didn't know about the wine and I'm
watching my, uh, one of my favorite movies with one of my best pals.
I mean, you know, I don't, uh, keep talking because I got to tweet this.
Okay.
Yeah.
Going back to VHS, I had this huge collection and it's like
everybody who bought Beanie Babies and thought they're going to be rich or like,
I have all these baseball cards.
I thought I was going to retire at age 21 from my baseball card collection.
They're all worth nothing at this point.
So my VHS, I get on Amazon.
I'm like, yeah, I can get some money for these.
They're classics.
You can't get one penny for a VHS unless it's not available on DVD or it's going
out of print.
So I sold a VHS copy of rad, the BMX biking movie.
I remember you telling me this.
$500 and it was in not, I put on there, not good condition.
The box was completely beaten up.
I had stole it from Blockbuster video that I worked at and I got $500 off of them.
What'd you pay for it?
I stole it.
I worked at Blockbuster.
I sold it to myself for like $2.
No, I didn't steal it.
God almighty.
Are we passed the statute of limitations on a hard crime?
Well, they fired me for other things.
So I don't really care.
That's a terrible company and they're out of business.
So they can't do anything.
I think maybe you should go down to Barbados until things blow over.
Blockbuster fired me because I was making too much money.
My friend said that 825 an hour at the time.
My friend Mike Bello said that to me once back in high school.
I was, I had a job and, and, uh, or I'm sorry, it wasn't my job.
It was a place where my buddy worked and he gave me free food or something.
Yeah.
I was panicking.
I was panicking that we were going to get in trouble and then moral people, Joe.
And I was, I was just, I was going on and on to Mike about like, am I okay?
Do you think I'm going to go to jail?
And he said, I think you need to go to Barbados until things blow over.
I mean, it's, it was, it was such a sharp comment for a 17 year old kid.
Uh, the other movie I had, which made me some money was somebody gave me as a Christmas
white elephant, uh, you know, gag gift thing, a VHS copy of a movie called Gator Bait.
And essentially it was like kind of a deliverance knockoff, but it had like a
playboy playmate on the cover.
Sure.
And it was an exploitation movie where she gets sexually assaulted in the bayou.
And then she goes to kill everybody who wronged her.
So I was like, how funny gag gift.
I never opened it cut to 10 years later.
Gator Bait is only available on VHS and I have a new sealed copy of it.
And I sold it on Amazon for like two 50.
Jesus Christ.
That's what you gotta do.
You gotta, you gotta watch the market.
Speaking of Gator Bait, I almost bought, I'll spit on your grave recently.
I was out in the ridge up in Toronto.
Uh, I almost bought the remake.
I never, I'd never seen the remake.
I've seen the original and that remake was so miserable and I didn't buy it.
I was like, I don't need to see this.
It's, it's just too depressing.
Yeah, it was too much depressing.
Just, I don't, it's, it has tapered off considerably, but there was about a three year window
in about maybe the mid two thousands where rape was an element of every horror movie.
And it bothered me so much.
There's a lot of these like, like weird glass house on the left, that kind of stuff.
Yeah.
And which was also a Wes Craven remake.
Now, but there was that one in the woods with like Stallone's son.
Right.
That one was like, I don't know.
It's just like where every scare is like watching a woman get raped for 25 minutes.
I'm glad that era of movies is over.
Let me look it up.
Uh, well, Pat looks that up.
Uh, we are now at the funeral scene of Rick, the guy that killed Tina.
Yeah.
You know, this is, since it's a horror movie podcast, probably 45 dudes just went,
yelled the name of the movie after the podcast.
Uh, I'm usually that guy by the way, but I don't remember those.
If you're watching along with us, you would have just seen that Rick had the saddest
funeral on planet earth.
Apparently had no parents or family.
It was just Nancy and her folks.
And a couple loose friends and old ladies.
Sure.
Uh, John Saxon now coming in.
Nobody believes you, Nancy.
Nobody believes you that a supernatural burn man is killing your friends.
Nobody wants to hear it.
This is one of the things I hate about horror movies is they always have to have this part
where the person's like, don't you get it?
The clowns are doing it and everybody's like, yeah, you, why don't you get some
sleep, sweetheart?
You know, well, look, if I came over here tonight and you were like, Pat, don't you
see the birds are going to kill us all.
I'd be like, Joe, what the hell's wrong with you?
You never believe that person.
But why does nobody ever say you've been perfectly sane until this point?
This is the first, I'm going to go ahead and give you the benefit of the crazy thing
you've ever said.
Let's spend five minutes exploring this as a real possibility.
Yeah.
Nobody ever goes, nobody ever goes, you know, Nancy, if it weren't for you painting
your name on the wall with your own shit, we believe you.
Yeah.
Nobody ever says that.
Everyone's like, well, you're a sound of sound mind, but fuck it.
I don't know what you're nuts now.
Yeah.
Well, you're my daughter and I love you more than anyone in the world.
But Charles Fleischer, by the way, the voice of Roger.
Exactly.
And we said, who framed Roger Rabbit?
By the way, I thought of the perfect name for a documentary about who framed Roger
Rabbit, who framed who framed Roger Rabbit.
Beautiful.
That'd be about the shooting of the movie.
Yeah, exactly.
Charles Fleischer was also amazingly good and creepy in Zodiac, which is one of my
favorite movies of all time.
He's wonderful in Zodiac.
Charles Fleischer.
He's so good in Zodiac.
Everybody and there's 800 speaking roles in Zodiac and everybody in it is perfect.
A bit of a horror movie veteran, Charles Fleischer.
Also, one of the one of the cast members of Demon Knight, which is one of my favorite
horror movies of all time.
Never saw it.
I only saw Bordello of Blood, which I was watching.
Bordello of Blood outside of the Dennis Miller scenes where he's just being like funny.
Yeah.
Is not good.
Being allegedly funny.
He is funny in that.
OK.
He is funny that when she.
He probably wrote his own dialogue.
He's funny in Joe Dirt.
Yeah.
When she when she's looking.
My favorite line in Bordello of Blood is when she's looking for.
She's a PI and she's looking for her brother who's missing.
Played by Corey Feldman.
Yeah.
And she goes, my brother's been missing.
I need your help.
And she shows him the picture of Corey Feldman and he starts laughing at the picture and
he goes, oh, I got to put this in a locket.
All right.
Yeah, I should check that out.
Now, again, now back to Zodiac.
The scene where the Zodiac killer kills those two teenagers at the lake.
Yeah.
And Zodiac's not really a horror movie, but that is by far one of the scariest scenes
in movie history.
Dude, that part's scary.
That part's scary when he goes to the guy's house and he thinks like he might have found
the Zodiac and he's not sure.
Yeah.
Zodiac.
I mean, it's probably three hours long.
I could.
There was a summer not long ago where I watched that movie every night for like two weeks.
I was obsessed with it.
Yeah, it was a great flick.
Robert.
That was the first movie where I was like, oh, my God, Robert Downey Jr.
is an amazing actor.
Yeah.
And that was his comeback.
Oh, yeah.
But that was Downey Jr.'s comeback.
That was the first movie I think that he did after he got off the drugs and everything.
Yeah.
And it was like, holy shit, this guy's like, no joke, man.
He killed it.
He was like really, it was really, really funny, which, you know, he kind of brought
that to the part.
It wasn't really on the page.
This movie that I'm talking about was 2005 called Chaos.
Right in the heart of like rape horror movies.
2005, four sadistic thieves, including Sage Stallone,
Sylvester Stallone's son, who died recently.
Did he commit suicide or did he just die?
I think he had an overdose.
That's a shame.
They brutalized two teenagers looking for drugs in the woods.
So there you go.
And it's so bad.
Is Sage one of the bad guys or good guys?
He's one of the torturers.
But you know what I remember the most, and I shut the movie off at this point,
but they cut off the girl's nipple.
Oh, come on.
Like, what are we doing?
I like a horror movie to be a little fun.
And I realize a lot of people like depraved shit.
I don't know what nipples are fun, but not when they get cut off.
No, I like a nipple attached.
I always have.
Let's get back to call me old fashioned.
Good old fashioned nipple show.
I don't like the nipple being cut off.
If you're watching along with us, we're in the hospital scene now where they're
trying to monitor Nancy's dreams.
And they just had one of those machines where.
Which I never buy like those machines with all the pens where the ink lines are going.
Yeah.
I mean, who who was able to read that?
The doctors was looking at it.
They go, no, no movement.
They might not even use them.
An actual movement.
It might only be like a movie only construct.
I don't believe it's a real machine.
Yeah, it might be.
It's like the lie detector.
I don't believe it exists.
I do not believe it exists.
I pointed out the blue door.
But the final scare of this, I'm not mistaken, is Freddie coming out that blue door, right?
He grabs her like at the end of Carrot.
Yes, yes.
And you can't.
And Wes Craven did not like that ending originally.
Come on, Wes.
It's a great ending.
It's OK.
It's kind of defeats what it is, which is she defeats Freddie.
I'm not scared of you anymore.
He disappears.
Yeah.
Then he just magically comes back in what is supposed to be real life.
OK.
So it's a good horror movie ending.
But I remember Wes Craven saying like, you know, it was merely just a setup for a sequel.
And he didn't think that that was the point of making the movie.
Nice buns, Nancy.
Remember when Wes Craven directed like one non -horror movie called Music of the Heart
with Meryl Streep and then never did a non -horror movie again?
I refuse to watch it.
I saw it.
That was during a time where I saw every movie and then gave it a letter grade in a spiral notebook.
Oh, God.
That was my life, people.
Now, here's.
I think I gave Music of the Heart a C plus.
What was it about Meryl Streep's maybe teaching poor kids or deaf kids or poor deaf kids or
something about the kids never live under stairs or turn evil or anything like that?
No, no, no, no, no.
OK, I don't have no interest.
Now, I'll tell you a Wes Craven movie I remember watching in maybe junior high that is so bad.
It's called Shocker.
Well, it's Pat.
I swear to God, I was just about to bring up Shocker.
Bring it up, Joe.
I also think Shocker sucks.
Here's the thing.
Wes Craven said he thought it was a commentary on the media, right?
Well, I believe that is true.
But he also said that he never got his what he thought was fair royalties for the franchise
of Nightmare on Elm Street.
So he said, I decided I was going to create another franchise and not make the same mistakes
I did contractually like I did with Nightmare on Elm Street.
And he made Shocker.
He thought that was going to be it.
And it was terrible.
I felt bad for I have such respect for the man, but I felt bad for him that that didn't
work out.
But then he came back with Scream and I was like, OK, now he got it with Scream.
He nailed it with Scream.
And Scream's great.
But Wes Craven, now you do have to ask yourself, how do you write and direct this thing?
And then he made so many bad movies.
How does it all happen?
You know, like how he made he made bad ones and good ones.
It seems to be the how do people make movies that are so bad and then so good?
And music is the same way.
It's just sure scary.
You know, it really is scary because you and I are both in the creative fields.
The biggest fear I have in my entire life beyond death and anything else is losing my
ability to be funny or good at what I do.
Well, as you know, look, you know, I used to be real hard on guys.
You know, I'd be like, I'd be like, you know, why did John Carpenter make this many good
ones and then these other ones that kind of sucked or whatever?
The perfect movie.
And then so many bad movies.
But you know what it is, I finally realized, like, well, everybody doesn't have the advantage
I do of being a standup where it's like, no, this is what it is.
Put it out or don't.
And nine times out of 10, they will.
And it's fine.
But, you know, as a writer, I have staff written, you know, things get picked apart,
things get changed around.
People get last minute doubts and everybody has a hand on it.
And then by the end of it, sometimes the final product isn't what you want it to be,
especially with a horror movie.
That's if you're dealing with the story and Carpenter kind of had, I think they pretty
much had free rein in the 80s and early 90s.
But if you look, if you look, there's a clear line that gets drawn with Kraven's a great
example in the jump from a young new line cinema, which was not a big boy studio.
It was a very indie studio.
It was very grassroots.
They call it the studio that Freddie built, the house that Freddie built.
Right.
I mean, and who doesn't?
I mean, I hear it every day in the coffee shop.
But there's a clear there's a clear line in quality that gets drawn when it jumps to
the major studio stuff.
Yeah.
Now, I think they let him dance a little more to his own rhythm with the screen movies.
Well, scream is written by Kevin Williamson.
So that's a different thing, too.
It was.
And I also think for some reason they give more slack with slasher movies.
You know, they said this with the when the last moves are.
Anything without a supernatural element is a little more legit, I think, because it could
really happen.
And they let they let horrific things go a little a little more with like the opening
of scream.
It's it's it's disturbing.
Oh, for sure.
They cut that.
He cuts Drew Barrymore's throat.
She's gargling on her own blood.
It's it's very disturbing.
I was terrified by scream when I saw it.
And now it's more of comedy.
It works as more comedy, but it's a really good movie.
They all are.
But, you know, when they did the Nightmare on Elm Street remake, they said one thing
we want to do is we want to make them look truly like a burn victim.
Right.
And then they said, well, we had to reel it back because we didn't want people to like
turn away from the screen every time they saw him because it was disturbing.
I'm like, no, make it disturbing.
Yeah.
I want a monster that sticks in my head and gives me nightmares.
That's why the exorcist freaks me out so much.
She's so scary looking.
You rarely get that.
And who played Freddie in the new one?
Jackie Earl Haley.
Oh, yeah, that was a good call.
He's great at playing a creep.
He's great at everything.
He plays mostly pedophiles now.
Again, little children.
It's my girlfriend.
When that movie at the time, my girlfriend at the time,
when that movie came out, gave it to me on DVD.
And I remember talking to a comedian named Julian McCall about it.
And I said, I love Julian McCall.
Yeah.
I said, my girlfriend just gave me a copy of Little Children.
And he said, you should examine your relationship.
Yeah, that's a little weird.
It's a good movie and a good book.
Tom Brown.
The movie is, I mean, there's the literally the most disturbing
scene I've ever seen in a movie is when he's jerking off
in front of the school on his date and the woman starts crying.
Yeah, it's terrible.
It's once again, pedophilia rears its head on me.
We'll see you in hell podcast.
Yeah, we need to stop.
Look at this lady.
She's got a very busy.
She looks like Virginia Madsen is melting.
The lady from sideways.
She's being so mean to this woman.
What's wrong?
She's so dramatic.
I love I find her sexy in a strange way.
Yeah, I mean, it all liquored up.
By the way, what's in the back of Nancy's sweatshirt?
All liquored up.
Nancy's pajamas all day.
Bathroom all liquored up.
A nice vodka drunk.
Sure.
Why is it?
Why is an alcoholic mother always a vodka drunk?
Well, because that's that's that is true to life, I think.
And now there's so many delicious flavors of vodka.
It's a great time to be an alcoholic mother or aunt.
You got toasted marshmallow vodka.
I'd go my own way.
I'd be doing Jaeger bombs the whole time.
I get that.
That's it.
Just straight Jaeger bombs.
You know, the next what's interesting.
We talked about her, you know, her having a zit and now she has kind of a red nose and etc.
Like the 80s were talking about Anthony Michael Hall earlier because of vacation.
Like all the teenagers had zits.
They were real.
This is in the studio movies, the indie movies.
The teenagers were real.
Now you can't find a teenager on screen who doesn't look like she's been airbrushed
and it's not real.
Everyone's ugly and awkward and weird when they're teenagers.
Now you're absolutely right.
And if I may point out the scene we're in now, Johnny Depp.
Johnny Depp is wearing a he's wearing a belly shirt.
Yeah.
Which I like, but he's also in his bedroom poster on the wall.
Rush grace under pressure.
Never realized that was the poster.
Never saw that either.
Uh, love rush, one of my favorite bands and the poster predominantly blues and purples.
It's the only Russian album.
Actually counterparts also has a blue album cover, but it wasn't out yet.
Up until this point, that was the bluest of the.
Yeah, I love the phone.
Blue phone.
Johnny Depp on a tan phone.
She probably blew Johnny Depp earlier.
Oh, you guys, I'm just trying to have fun.
And he said, don't rush it.
Have some grace under pressure.
Look at this, folks.
This is why we write the TV show.
Sure.
I just watched.
I never like rush.
I just watched a rush documentary that I loved also on Netflix.
Oh, it's beyond the lighted stage.
It's tremendous.
Great.
It's fucking tremendous.
I might go see them next week.
Actually, this weekend.
Where they're playing the forum or the staples?
Uh, I think the forum.
I can't go.
It's my buddy's party.
I never saw them.
They were never my bag.
But whatever, I saw them once.
I respect them.
I saw them once and I was so drunk that I weeped during Spirit of Radio.
You know, that's where I'm at in my life at this point.
That was three years ago, but whatever.
Uh, here's the famous line.
Don't fall asleep.
She just told you, Johnny, don't fall asleep.
She's not fucking around here.
Even you don't believe her.
Look, nobody believes her that this guy's coming into their nightmares.
Nobody believes her.
Here's why there aren't more great horror movies or great comedies or great whatever.
Blue Blanket on Johnny Depp's Bed.
True.
Sorry to cut you off.
That's all right.
The reason is, I think, that kind of one -line premise, if you fall asleep, you're dead,
is obviously such a perfect...
You walk into any studio and you go, hey, I got a movie where if you fall asleep, you die.
They'll hand you an oversized novelty check.
Right.
Uh, and the, those premises just don't come along that often
because if they did, somebody would have thought of it.
Sure.
And comedy's the same way.
Like, the 40 -year -old version.
I would imagine somebody walked in, Judd Apatow, I guess, walked into a studio and said,
the 40 -year -old version.
And they said, here's money.
Right.
Because it's perfect.
Like, and those things are, they seem so easy to come up with, but they're not.
Right.
A simple one -line premise.
And that's why whenever I ask somebody, somebody's like, hey, can you read a script of mine?
I'm like, yeah, what's it about?
And they go, okay, so there's this guy, right?
And he's like an air traffic controller, but he never really, and I'm like, okay,
this movie is not going to happen.
Right.
You need to, for better or worse, be able to say, here's the movie in one sentence.
I agree.
Especially for comedy, especially for horror.
If you want, if you want any sort of success, if you want somebody to give you some money,
you want to do a weird indie, you know, you can't explain David Lynch's movies in one sentence.
Sure.
But, you know, those aren't the big hits.
Well, I would agree with you.
I fucking love David Lynch, by the way.
I love David Lynch.
I would agree.
My favorite types of horror movies are horror movies that establish very simply,
there's no escape.
You have to face the fear.
Yeah.
So, that's why when people go to the movies, they poke holes in them.
I used to only go to the Magic Johnson Theater to see.
I thought you were going to say to Magic Johnson's movies.
I was like, I didn't know he made films.
I would only go to the Magic Johnson Theater in Compton here in LA because for horror movies,
I loved people shouting out of the screen.
And I would have so much fun and laugh and yell out myself at times and stuff.
But if people are watching your movie and they can be like, don't do that, you idiot.
What do you do?
That means nobody's buying your shit.
Right.
What you're saying is they can't have an out and then that's truly scary.
They don't have an out.
It's truly scary.
All the best horror movies, there's no out.
Nightmare on Elm Street, you fall asleep, you die.
Texas Chainsaw Massacre.
All the hillbilly inbreds are running the town.
You can't get away from them.
The Exorcist.
Your daughter is possessed by the devil.
You have to stay here with her.
Look at that mask on the wall, by the way.
Look at this bod on Nancy taking it off.
We're only getting it from the back, but it is delish.
You know, when I was a kid, because it's all I saw something about a rear side bottom boob
is almost sexier than the whole thing.
I love it still to this day, but that little small of a back right there,
you could really grasp that waist.
All right.
Take it easy.
I'm getting worked up here.
But I was watching Mirrors today and I thought once again, brilliant premise for a horror movie.
What's everywhere and you can't get away from them.
But isn't that kind of what Poltergeist 3 was?
Mirrors, water, puddles.
Ah, yeah, but Mirrors did it way better, I guess.
All right.
Do you like Mirrors?
I don't remember.
I enjoyed it very much.
I remember Poltergeist 3 was terrible.
Poltergeist 3 is to me unwatchably bad.
As much as I love Tom Skerritt.
Sure.
I saw Poltergeist 2 the day I got braces and then the scene where the kid's braces attack him.
I mean, when I was a kid, I loved Poltergeist 2.
Now that I'm older, I don't like it as much.
No, but it's not a bad movie.
That preacher guy is still a lot of fun.
From Phantasm, right? Same guy?
No, not the same guy.
Are we sure?
Positive.
Angus Scrim?
Okay.
Not Angus Scrim.
All right.
Phantasm 5, eagerly awaiting that.
It's made, it's done.
Still hasn't come out yet.
Theatrical release or you think it'll go straight to?
No, it'll go straight to Vid.
But I mean, you know, the guy that did Phantasm did.
John dies at the end.
He did Bubba Ho Tep.
Right.
He does a lot of great stuff.
Don Coscarelli?
Yes.
Never saw John dies at the end.
I liked Bubba Ho Tep a lot.
But he's got Phantasm 5 as I believe.
This lady get it together for Christ's sake.
I mean, she's stashing bottles all over the house, this lady.
I don't think, and I've been a big advocate of drinking for about 10 years.
I don't think I've ever drank out of a bottle of liquor.
I did once recently, my friends and I went out for a big party night and we were starting
at a girl's apartment and I finally did this.
I always wanted to do this, but one of those little glass pint bottles of whiskey.
I've done that.
Just drank the whole thing at her house.
It was a lot of fun smoking cigarettes.
I felt like a real like I was on the case.
But you never picked up like the 10 pound bottle of Jack to your lips.
Yeah, no, I don't stash like Nancy's mom does a three liter
vodka in the linen closet.
Along with the one in the kitchen that I hide behind my back.
There's Johnny Depp's dad.
He's not a good actor.
That guy looks like he gave birth to Johnny Depp, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, that's viable.
I had a friend tonight.
I had that phone when I was a kid.
I had to answer talk about horror.
I had to answer every phone call until I was 17 until I left that got out of the house.
I had to answer every phone call.
Hello, Walsh residence, Patrick speaking.
Who made you do that?
My dad was a Nazi.
Well, no comment.
Hello, Walsh residence, Patrick speak.
And my friends would be like, Pat, it's Ryan.
Like, what's wrong with you?
Who the hell?
Yeah.
What is that bullshit?
And then even like my dad's friends would be like, why do you have to say that?
Can I just talk to your dad?
I'm like, I'm sorry.
Now, if you noticed it, we passed it, but they just showed exterior shots of the houses
a moment ago, both houses draped in blue light.
She's wearing a blue members only jacket with a blue phone
and a blue bedspread.
Patty, you really cracked into something here with the blue road, baby.
You really cracked into something here.
I'm proud of you, man.
Thank you.
Blue towels in the closet, blue towels in the linen closet.
Oh, blue phone is now ringing blue tissues on the on the shelf.
Flew my mind is what it did.
Blue phone is now raised in the back.
That's the police.
That's the police and her dad's a cop.
What do you think of that?
Blue painting on the wall.
And they really did their work here.
I this is the part where the tongue comes out.
Hold on here.
I'm your boyfriend now, Nancy.
That was always gross.
What do you think Freddie's breath smells like when he licks her face like that?
That's not good, man.
No, I went to film school and I took a class where this professor would talk.
He would make every movie into a game movie.
All had a gay subtext and it was fascinating how he did it like some like he would talk
about Rebecca, the old Hitchcock movie, where clearly the maid is like has a lesbian interest
in her and you watch and you're like, oh, shoot, you're right.
I never saw Rebecca.
Is it good?
It's it's a great movie, especially with that bit of information.
But then like he'd watch Die Hard and he'd be like, well, clearly John McClane is gay
and the room would kind of laugh.
And then by the end of the class and it wasn't the class wasn't like finding gay subtext
in movies.
He just did it.
So like you'd be like, maybe John McClane is gay.
He was a fascinating man.
By the way, Johnny Depp asleep on the bed now.
Blue sweatpants, blue number 10 on the belly shirt.
And now he's dead.
And there's another blue blanket on the bed.
He just got pulled in the bed by Freddie and now a blood fountain shoots out,
which I enjoy quite a bit.
Yeah, it's a good shot.
You only get one take of a blood fountain shooting out of the bed.
Yeah, this is it.
What do you think?
I guess they must have poured it in there.
How do they do that?
It looks like it's shot.
It's going in reverse.
Maybe that's an upside down room.
Okay.
Yes.
I can't believe I have to explain that to you, but I do.
I love the magic of cinema, Joe.
I like to let it wash over me and confuse me and dazzle me.
Yeah, that's clearly an upside down room.
Now I bought the special edition of the Nightmare on Elm Street VHS tape.
My friend Jim and I split split it.
We found it one night at Sam Goody or something, one of those old record stores.
Warehouse music?
Yeah, something like that.
Where you could listen on headphones like what we're doing now.
Yeah, it was pre -DVD.
We found the double VHS and we bought it because the second tape had a bunch of bonus features on it,
which at that time was pretty unheard of on anything.
But the bonus tape had deleted scenes.
Okay.
One of the fast forward through to find the next scene.
The ones that you cared about, yeah.
But one was Johnny Depp's bloody corpse coming up out of the hole in the bed
and then plopping down before anybody discovered what was happening.
It looked like he had just been murdered and it was a great shot.
I have the Blu -ray box set.
I'm sure it's on there somewhere.
I'm sure it is too.
I don't know why though they would have cut it out of the film.
The dad now is very upset.
He's throwing up because his son's blood is dripping through the ceiling.
That's upsetting.
Yeah, I would guess so.
I'd guess so.
Now, do you like the Friday the 13th series or do you find it a lesser?
Uh, yeah, I like it.
I don't like it as much as Nightmare on Elm Street, but I've only seen Friday the 13th.
They're great.
I mean, I think the ratio of good ones to bad ones is equal.
Friday the 13th might actually have a better batting average than Nightmare on Elm Street
simply because there's more so they have more chances to make better ones.
But they don't have a classic like the first Friday the 13th is not a classic.
It's just kind of an okay slasher movie.
I don't like the first one.
I think what the remake did was best,
which was establishing the events of the first one in the opening credits basically.
Two is to me where Friday the 13th really kicks in.
Two's great. Three's great. Four's great.
Oh, okay. I gotta watch all those.
Five sucks. Six and seven are great.
After that, they all kind of suck.
Takes Manhattan.
That's a waste of time in my opinion.
Isn't that six or seven?
Jason takes Manhattan is eight.
Okay. Then there's Jason X in space.
Yeah, Jason Goes to Hell is number nine.
Jason X is in space.
Is Jason Goes to Hell set in hell?
No, it's just the idea that he goes to hell at the end of it.
Okay, and they thought some fucking horseshit thing about like, you know,
he's it's an ancient demon.
You know, anytime they do that, it's like, get the fuck out of here.
They try to do that with Michael Myers and the curse of Michael Myers.
Yeah, it's stupid.
But Friday the 13th, part six is my favorite of all of them.
And I'm interested.
What's the premise?
It's called Jason Lives.
Okay.
And the opening of the movie is fantastic.
It's the guy that plays Horse Shack in Welcome Back Cotter.
Ron Polillo, I believe.
Yeah, and then the grownup, like a different actor,
but it's the grownup version of Corey Feldman's character from part four.
He wants to make sure that Jason is actually dead.
So they go to a cemetery to dig up his corpse.
They dig up his corpse.
It's there.
Kid pulls out an iron pole from the fence,
starts stabbing Jason repeatedly out of rage.
Right.
Lightning strikes the pole, reanimates Jason.
Okay.
Jason punches Horse Shack through the chest,
hand comes out the other side holding his heart.
It's a great fucking flick, man.
All right.
And we talked about Darabont on the last one.
Darabont directed or he wrote the third Nightmare on Elm Street.
Correct.
Dream Warriors.
Did he?
Yeah, I think he wrote it.
I thought Craven wrote that one.
Let's look it up.
Darabont wrote four then maybe.
By the way, Friday the 13th reboot, I didn't even realize.
I knew they were working on one.
It comes out in like November.
A Friday the 13th reboot?
Yeah.
Now, didn't they already do a Friday the 13th reboot?
They did.
And I thought it was solid and it didn't for some reason get any traction.
But it was one of the scariest kills ever.
He takes a girl and puts her in a sleeping bag.
Yeah, I remember when I saw that.
And then ties the sleeping on the tree over the fire.
That's so scary, man.
Hold on.
Nightmare on Elm Street three.
Let's see here.
This woman's an attractive woman.
Why was I so mean?
I don't know.
I mean, the strange part is she's six years younger than we are right here.
People just looked older back then.
That sure is true.
Let's see.
Nightmare on Elm Street part three.
Seventy four percent of Rotten Tomatoes.
Deservedly so.
Patricia in the bed during this makeup scene.
Patricia Arquette's screen debut, if you will.
Screenplay.
Wes Craven, Bruce Wagner, Frank Darabout and Chuck Russell.
Chuck Russell, I think, didn't like the mask or something.
I want to see what else Darabout wrote in his early career.
He was a he's primarily a screenwriter.
Nightmare on Street three.
Love it.
The blob.
The fly to love it.
Fly to is good.
I love fly one.
I mean, the original.
Well, it's not the original.
It's still a remake.
But the fly with Jeff Goldblum to me could be my second favorite horror movie ever.
Yeah.
It's one of the most disturbing things I've ever seen in my life.
But I love the fly, too.
It got a bad rap.
I think it's great.
All right, I'll say it.
I don't know.
I never saw a lot of those bad sequels.
Like I never saw Predator two, but I love Predator one.
I never saw Predator two either.
You see in Danny Glover.
And you're right.
Chuck Russell did write the mask he wrote.
He wrote, co -wrote the blog.
He wrote a racer.
Oh, that was a rough one.
He also wrote when he shoots that alligator and he goes, your luggage.
Yes, I do.
That was in the trailer.
But he also wrote Collateral, one of my favorite Michael Mann movies.
Oh, Collateral's a fantastic movie.
Yeah.
You adapt.
Good for you, Chuck Russell.
Way to come back, baby.
Oh, was a producer on Back to School.
Love Back to School.
Who doesn't?
That's always very inspiring to me when somebody's got a couple hits in the 80s.
And then you're like, oh, I guess they tapered off.
And you see they wrote some big hit in the 90s.
I love it.
Like it's a cool movie or the 2000s.
Co -wrote Dreamscape.
Love that.
I don't know Dreamscape.
Dennis Quaid?
Yes.
I do know Dreamscape.
Did I tell you I saw Dennis Quaid at a party the other night?
Whose party?
When I was at the Montreal Comedy Festival.
Oh, yeah, you told me.
Yeah, Quaid was there.
I'm walking out of the.
Who's funnier than Dennis Quaid?
Well, he was doing a reading that Jason Reitman was doing of The Big Lebowski.
What was he playing?
The Nihilist?
He was playing.
Jackie Treehorn?
I think he was playing The Big Lebowski.
No, Michael Fassbender was playing.
No, Fassbender was playing The Dude.
The Dude, right?
I think Quaid played The Big Lebowski.
Oh, well, that seems wrong.
I can't remember.
But it was a fat old creed.
It doesn't matter.
But the point is, is I got off the elevator in the hotel.
Everybody was saying and there was like 10 people on the elevator
and we're walking to these glass doors to go outside.
And you threw the glass doors.
There's a set of stairs and there's this guy on the set of stairs.
And I just turned to everybody on the elevator that was on the elevator.
I go, is that Dennis Quaid?
Yeah.
And we all started laughing because it was Dennis Quaid.
It was like the most random play.
What the fuck is he doing here?
We didn't know that he had done the reading.
Looks amazing.
Of course.
Have two brothers ever looked less similar than Dennis and Randy Quaid?
Dennis Quaid.
I stand by this should be Indiana Jones next.
We could get four or five good movies out of him as Indiana Jones.
He's perfect for it.
All right.
Looks great.
He's got that indignant like, come on.
You know, he's like Dennis Quaid.
I love him.
What's your favorite Dennis Quaid movie?
I was just on the tip of my tongue.
I was going to say how much I love interspace.
That probably is the best one, right?
Yeah.
I mean, it's just a great, great movie.
Joe Dante.
I love a Joe Dante.
Yeah, a man is a great underrated movie.
You know, I had a Twilight Zone, the movie poster signed by Joe Dante.
And fucking when I moved, he seemed to disappear with all my other valuable paintings.
What can you say?
I'm not accusing anybody.
No, but right.
Yeah, we're in the climax of the film at this point.
Nancy is Nancy has purposefully gone to sleep.
She set up booby traps around the house.
She's now in the boiler room alone.
Home alone.
Yes.
Nightmare on the street gets very home alone at the end.
Yeah, as does that great James Bond movie.
Actually, the not so great one quantum of solace ends it like an abandoned house.
And James Bond sets a bunch of traps.
That movie is also home alone.
You know what I always wanted to do was do a short with Macaulay Culkin about the kid
from Home Alone getting out of an insane asylum in his 30s because he horrifically mutilated
two men that came into his home.
I mean, that was my favorite movie for years when I was a kid.
I was Macaulay Culkin's age when that came out.
It was like a dream come true.
And I love John Hughes and remain a huge fan.
But I watched some I guess it was probably on the DVD, like a DVD extra.
And Chris Columbus, the director, was talking about how Joe Pesci like basically came from
the set of Goodfellas to do Home Alone as like an afterthought.
And he's like, we have days of footage of Joe Pesci like screaming in Macaulay Culkin's face.
I'm going to fucking kill you.
And he's like, no, Joe, Joe, he's a 10 year old boy.
And this is a PG rated comedy.
It's like he's an improv guy and he'd get real into it.
And they'd be like, you're not at Goodfellas anymore, Joe.
Oh, that's beautiful.
You can say like you want to like break his nose or something fun like that.
But you can't say you want to murder him and bury him in the desert.
Is there anything funnier than Daniel Stern getting the tarantula put on his face?
It's the best scream in movie history.
I would say it's you know what?
Another great one is Bruce Willis in Death Becomes Her.
I like a man with a high pitched scream.
It's always funny.
I never saw Death Becomes Her.
Believe it or not, I was in rushing to get to the new Goldie Hawn vehicle.
Look, fine.
But it's really good.
Robert Zemeckis.
It's it's a very funny Bobby Z.
Very funny movie.
Great special effects.
And it has a lot to say about aging and Hollywood and culture and it's a great movie.
Nancy just found Glenn's headphones in Freddie's boiler room.
Glenn was Johnny Depp.
Right.
And in case you were mistaken, they did have a label on them that said Glenn.
Uh, you know, I thought the other label that said headphones was a bit much.
I felt like Wes wasn't really giving us credit there.
Why does Nancy currently have blood all over her fingers?
I don't know.
What was the?
Yeah.
How did she get?
Oh, because she picked up Glenn's headphones.
What did she land in that?
She's fine.
She's dreaming.
Oh, yeah.
Have you not?
Have you lost the premise of the movie already?
So she landed in some rose bushes.
Freddie's going to jump out.
She's going to wake herself up in a minute.
And this is the whole thing.
She figures out halfway through the movie.
I can bring Freddie into real life.
Yes, of course.
All right.
Now she's about to wake up.
There he is.
But he doesn't know what she can do.
She tackles him.
He thinks easy kill.
Boom.
Wakes up.
And who hasn't had that feeling?
What do you mean?
Well, I have this feeling every night.
You're about to be brutally murdered in your dream.
And then you are like, wake up, please wake up.
And you jolt yourself away.
I have that feeling every time I go into a pitch meeting.
I didn't know you had night terrors.
I'd love to sleep over one night and hear those things.
No, you wouldn't.
Oh, God, I would.
I should probably double down on the therapy.
It's like whenever you talk about something in public,
it's like, oh, wait, this isn't normal that I jolt awake nearly
being murdered in my sleep every night.
And you scream.
Uh, no, I usually go like.
Now, here's what bothered.
Here's what always bothered me about Freddie.
Freddie coming into the real world.
Yeah, because they do this in Freddie versus Jason, too.
Comes into the real world.
Freddie versus Jason.
Also, we are.
Yeah.
Horror movies.
You'd think the first thing he would do is start going.
My fucking skin hurts.
No, it's fine.
Burn to a crisp.
Yeah.
Doesn't it doesn't seem to faze him at all.
That always bothered me.
Things like that bother me.
All right.
You know, she just broke through a window with an umbrella.
You know, sure, why not?
You could break a window with an umbrella.
Now, here comes Freddie.
Look, I mean, it's that is home alone.
He gets a sledgehammer in his stomach.
That is home alone.
There he goes.
The only thing the scene is missing is a kick to his nuts.
Yeah.
Or paint cans being thrown in.
Uh, this gets a little paint canny right here.
He runs through the.
He runs right through the trip trip wire and sets off the lamp bomb.
Yeah.
And just kind of gives like an ouch like it.
Ah, yeah.
Yeah, maybe.
I love it.
Nancy screaming out the window for help.
That was a weird choice of takes.
There's a cop across the street and he goes, maybe I should go tell the lieutenant.
Did you just see on the stairs there appeared?
Yeah, that's like a giant bottle of bourbon.
Oh, she's going to grab.
No, no, this is one of her booby traps.
Okay.
I was going to say, did the mob just leave a bottle out?
Which she throws it out, but it just shatters on his chest.
She's reburning him now.
But now she's burning them on this side.
And there's a man in a Freddie Halloween costume now getting who's on fire.
That literally looks like the Halloween costume of Freddie I bought.
At Rite Aid when I was a child.
There he goes.
He is making sort of Schwarzenegger noises, right?
How to get to the chopper.
Come on, you're better than that pet.
That's his big line, right?
You're better than that.
What is that an old?
That's like a Kevin Pollock routine.
All right.
Well, I'm not saying that's not a diss of Kevin Pollock.
I'm just saying he's been saying that for a long time.
Well, I don't know Kevin Pollock.
I don't follow his career.
I do.
I liked him in Grumpy Old Men and Diner.
Was he wasn't in Diner?
No, I love him in Grumpy Old Men.
He's in a lot of movies that seem like Diner.
You know, Pop.
That's my Kevin Pollock impression.
Sure.
Hey, Pop, what do you get a doofy did a pop?
He's got that Queens, New York thing to him.
The cops are now in the house.
They're here to help Nancy.
And she's leading him downstairs because there's smoke coming up from the basement
where she set Freddie on fire.
How?
By throwing a bottle of bourbon into his chest.
But what's this?
Fiery footprints up the stairs.
Fiery footprints.
Again, this is what starts to bug me is I love the movie.
I'm not knocking it, but this is now a real man that has been burnt on top of burnt skin.
Yeah.
And he's still somehow running around the house to kill people.
We're into like 12th and 13th degree burns.
Yeah, he's on top of the mother trying to burn her right now.
Yeah.
And now the mother is look blue again.
The mother's corpse burnt to a crisp sinks into a blue abyss.
Look, isn't that Saxon's wife?
Yeah.
He seems oddly nonplussed.
They're divorced.
Oh, okay.
Well, then she was a bitch.
Yeah.
Well, there's an extra $7 .50 a month.
I don't got to spend.
That's what he's thinking right now.
You know what?
Saxon should have yelled there.
Now you deal with her bullshit Krueger.
He should have yelled that as she sunk into the bed.
She's your problem now, Kruegs.
By the way, watch your credit cards.
You know, it's another way the movie could have gone.
Once again, the whole room is blue, which makes you question, is Nancy?
Did you ever think about that until I laid that truth bomb on you?
No, it's killing me though.
It's killing me.
Shyamalan did it like Unbreakable is an extremely color coded movie.
If you watch it purple and you know, he's talking about making part two.
Man, that'd be great.
Unbreakable is such a fucking classic.
I love it.
And I'm pissed that he's I'm like, why did it take this long for these guys
even talk about making it?
Yeah.
Such an awesome movie.
Like make the second one.
Everyone talks about it like it's a cult favorite and it made like 150 million dollars.
Yeah.
He was still the man.
It's like make the next unbreakable.
Unbreakable.
Another great effect shot here.
Freddy comes up through the sheet.
And again, it's like a late sexy kind of a condom, kind of a dick going into a condom vibe.
So my theory here is now Freddy's back.
He's still alive.
He magically comes out of the bed.
My theory is, is she's actually dreaming here and doesn't realize she is.
However, she still defeats him because she realizes I don't I'm not scared of you.
Yeah.
Which is how she felt through the whole booby traps in the area.
Can I blow your mind again real quick?
Yeah.
Home Alone, the big turning point in Home Alone, like the act two when he's like,
I'm going to defend everything.
He yells, I'm not afraid anymore.
Yeah.
Like three times in a row.
I'm not afraid anymore.
So movies, the same movie.
Let's let's change the statement I made earlier.
Home Alone gets very Nightmare on Elm Street.
Yeah.
Not the other way around.
Get that furnace in the basement causing trouble.
That was scary.
The neighbor.
How much?
Okay.
That was kind of a children of the corner thing.
Freddy just turned into television snow.
She's not scared anymore.
She opens the door.
Here's the daylight.
Look at those blue eyes, blue, blue earrings, blue eyes.
I don't think she had blue eyes in the whole rest of the movie, did she?
No.
And I believe a blue outfit.
They do color contacts on it.
Yeah.
See, I think that whole end is supposed to be she's still dreaming.
The whole thing is she's still dreaming.
She thinks she's awake.
She thinks she's defeated him.
She hasn't.
She's still dreaming.
Her mom's wearing a smock painting with giant buttons on it.
Let me tell you something about what the mom looks like right now.
Two words.
I likey.
Again, ladies and gentlemen, please don't have sex with Joe DeRosa.
You're just going to hear.
I love this access buttons down the front.
Yeah.
Purple and blue.
Well, I guess everything's happy from here on out.
I guess we're going to hit stop.
It looks never mind this smoke that's everywhere.
It looks like smoke just billowing all around them everywhere.
Nobody seems to notice it.
They're dreaming.
Wait a minute.
I thought this was the end and everything was going to be fine.
She's still dreaming.
The car is Freddy stripes.
The mother doesn't notice that something's wrong.
That the car looks like a Freddy car suddenly.
Yeah.
And here we go.
Mother in front of the blue door.
What's going to happen?
Oh, there's the little girls from the beginning.
Right.
And here's Freddy's arm.
And he pulls the blow up down through the window.
Yeah, that's kind of a weird effect.
Well, I mean, you know, very.
How else did you make that like the end of Carrie as well?
One final like when the arm jolts out of the grave, it's a very final shock.
Carrie.
But that's only in the remake.
Does that happen in the original?
They don't do it in the remake.
They do do it in the original.
And her arm comes out of the grave beautifully done in the original.
They keep zooming in on these rocks and it's that beautiful woman,
whatever her name is, Amy something.
And she's at the grave and the hand comes out and grabs.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
Terrifying.
I forgot about that.
OK, you're right.
Amy Irving.
Sorry, Steven Spielberg's ex.
That's it.
This song.
We're at the closing credits.
What's the song playing?
Yeah.
Did they do like is this song like what they used to do
or like there had to be a song about the movie?
Like it's a nightmare on Elm Street.
Talk about a nightmare.
Let me see if I can wear it before we sign on.
I'm down the street.
Nightmare on Elm Street.
Like the song in Who's Harry Crumb by The Temptations.
And it's they say who's Harry Crumb.
They go.
It's called Big Fun parentheses.
Harry Crumb.
Oh, God.
Big Fun.
Harry Crumb.
This is the according to YouTube, the Everly Brothers.
Oh, no.
This can't be the Everly Brothers.
No, it's not the I mean, the Isley Brothers.
It says the Everly Brothers.
All I have to do is dream.
No, that's whenever I want you.
All I have to do.
That's in the remake.
Oh, yeah, you're right.
You're absolutely right.
Is your backdrop on your phone Greece, the movie?
Yeah, I think that's funny.
OK.
It's from the scene.
It's from the You're the one that I want scene.
It makes me laugh.
All right.
I can't find.
Laughter is important.
Changing the.
Hey, as we're wrapping up here so you don't have to listen to Joe Google on this podcast,
send us movie suggestions, thoughts, ways to improve things you love, whatever,
because we're starting out.
This is new to us as well.
Any suggestions you got?
Did you tweet out earlier?
I did.
I forgot to look at it.
Oh, my God.
Look, there's nothing saying we got to end.
If there's any questions right now, I'm going to look at Twitter.
We're going to ask.
OK, can I read you the one comment under the video?
Yeah, please do.
On YouTube of the ending song.
There's no information on the guys that did this song.
It's actually a really great song.
Good drumming, awesome sense.
Why is there no info on this band?
They're called two one three.
That was posted six years ago.
Not when the movie came out.
Six years ago when YouTube came out, that that was posted.
We have any questions?
We do.
I'm going to read through them.
Do you think Freddy Krueger served in Nam?
Do you think he's seen some shit?
I think it's a great question.
The timeline adds up to me.
I would not be surprised if he served in Nam,
but I bet they would have mentioned it at some point during the series,
because why not?
Yes, and yes.
And actually, if you're going into pitch a Nightmare on Elm Street sequel
and like the 80s or whatever, you really should have done a Nam,
Nam themed.
That would have been perfect.
Great question.
And our man, Ken Hanley, our point man over at Fangoria
and the Fangoria podcast network and all that stuff,
he sent us a bunch of questions.
I say this is a good way to end is just answer Ken's questions.
He says, has Joe checked into a health care facility
after admitting he liked Johnny Depp and Tusk?
What a beautiful question,
because it's one of the worst performances in recent movie history.
And you know who else didn't like it from everything I've heard?
Kevin Smith.
He was like, I hate that I have this guy
and it's such a great get, but he's ruining my movie.
What are you talking about?
That's what I've heard through the great plan.
Oh, I don't believe it.
I think that's bullshit.
In all seriousness, though, Funny Freddy or Scary Freddy?
For me, Scary Freddy.
Funny Freddy is annoying.
Of course.
Is New Nightmare the best sequel for me?
Yes.
No, three is the best sequel.
New Nightmare is the second best sequel.
OK.
And then would you recruit in small towns?
I don't understand what that means, but no.
I don't know what that means.
Yeah, I'm just going to say no.
Thanks for listening, everybody.
I'm at Joe DeRosa Comedy on Twitter.
I'm at ThePatrickWalsh on Twitter, Vine, Instagram.
And guys, we'd love your feedback.
I hope you're enjoying the podcast.
Yeah.
Give us some feedback.
It hasn't aired yet.
So when it does, we'd like to know.
We'd love it.
All right, guys.
Thanks a lot for listening.
Take care, and we'll see you in hell next time.