I'll see you in hell.
And we are back to, back with vengeance, back with fury to review and back to the wasteland to review the wasteland.
Furious. Oh, Furious. That's right. It takes place in the wasteland. It's called which is, you know, the new
Mad Max was going to be called, which will never be made now because this is, this is tank. They said it's the worst
Memorial Bay weekend in 20 years or something like that. Well, this weekend's, yes, supposed to be even worse and
they were like a Garfield predicted to win by a call is the headline I saw. Imagine George Miller, an 85 year old wild genius, given
one last shot at, at glory. And he's losing to Garfield voiced by Chris Pratt. Well, it goes that America. Who, what studio put out Garfield?
I'm looking no, not business. Imaginarium imagination. I want to say one Warner Brothers, but that's Furiosa, I think. Yeah. Well, my point is, I'll look it up, but my point is, whatever that studio is, Sony, they had dear God, dude, it's
Furiosa was at 68 million Garfields at 102. Not even close, not even by a call. You could almost say Garfield is making litter of Furiosa.
Sony's got some kind of inside scoop because the balls to put out a fucking Garfield movie on Memorial Day weekend. They had inside it. That's like insider trading shit.
They knew, yeah, that they were going to take it somehow. I mean, you know, I knew things were getting bad again movie was when my mom, hey, I called my mom today. And it's always just complete shock. My, my mother and father do not call me neither one of them. They, they will not. This is why I'm bad on the phone, Joe. This is why I don't want to talk in the phone. My parents don't call me. And then when I call my mom's like, what's going on. There's like four questions. Why, why are you calling? What's is someone is everything OK?
Mm hmm. Anyway, I'm like, I'm shooting the shit with her about movies. And she was, have you seen Garfield yet?
I'm a 43 year old single man. I've not seen Garfield. She was, we can't find anything to see. She was, we like the fall guy, but every week they like to go every Thursday or every Tuesday because it's half off in Missouri. And she's like, we can't find anything that we just turned around and came back home the other day.
Two retired people driving 15 minutes to the theater, get out of their cars. Look at the 18 plex and say, no, there's nothing for me here. Stuff.
Pat, I'm not exaggerating the movie tavern, which is one of these, you know, Alamo Draftow style places. Yeah.
Which by the way, I'm done going to places like that because you're trying to watch a goddamn movie and the waiter comes up and has to go to everybody.
Yeah, top of the lungs. Just hate it. You gang, you guys going to need anything else? You good to die? Come. It's like guys.
Aside from you're in my horror festival, which was a nightmare. The worst movies I've ever put scene put together 60 bucks down the drain.
I went with my ex to see the night and gale on a Sunday morning, which is a very disturbing movie about sexual assault.
And the guy next to me is like just shit housing, a giant breakfast burrito.
And like I mean, there's a there's a rape going on in this guy's like knowing on this thing with sour cream and his beard.
And I was like, no, yeah. To me, the Alamo Drafthouse seems more corporate than the local AMC. I don't know why, but they do.
Yeah, well, it's not a mom and pop anymore. No, no, no. Yeah. And movie tavern.
You know, when that came to my hometown before I moved to the big city with my dreams of my one suitcase.
I'm sorry to interrupt you again, but his movie tavern just a chain of restaurants slash theaters. It's exactly the trend.
No, they were they as far as I know they were established after Alamo Drafthouse, but it's exactly the same thing except not is not as hipstery, but when that opened, I was so excited.
I was like, oh, man, you got a movie. That's awesome. You can like eat in it. And because there was a time for the young listeners where eating at the theater was like maddened.
He was like, what? Like drinking in a theater? Forget it. You had to like sneak it in like a hobo.
Yeah, I mean, the first thing was the first time I heard about like being able to drink in a movie theater. It seemed very foreign to me.
Yeah, this thing now where you can just get a regal, you know, go get a jack and cocoa. It's that's new. So anyway, the the movie tavern is exactly like Alamo, except more a little more milk toast.
But it's I don't know. I just and then I get annoyed. I get annoyed when I'm trying to watch the movie and the waiter's like, hey, sir, do you I'm like, get out of get out of my face.
I have a button. I'll ring for you if I need you.
Which I know I'll go even further. I find that should annoying at a comedy club, you know, like when I go see a friend over at the improv.
Like when they come around and are like, so anyway, it's just the two drinks and then you see I took away the tater tots or whatever.
Like I'm there to enjoy the comedy and the movie isn't even further step I think away from it. I don't know. I don't know how I would continue telling jokes either.
With all that shit going on, but I guess you just get used to it like everything else.
There's good. Well, there's a good version of it in a bad version of it. You know, like a well oiled machine.
The weight staff knows the volume to speak to not be distracting how to be efficient move through the world. That's a common thing a comedy clubs.
There's a there's a there's a there's a stock line that comics used to say some of them still do. I'm sure where they'd be like, God damn, where'd y 'all learn to order food in the helicopter.
You know, because like yeah, yeah, out of where anywhere. Speaking of comics, Seinfeld's really going on a tear this week every time I see him in the news, I'm like, oh, he's just going off. He's just done.
Yeah, he came up and said he misses like a man's man. I was like, okay, but why are you saying this now? He's always been sort of pushing up against kind of almost wanting to be canceled or something.
I think he'd almost like it for the real of it or for the material he gets from it because he's really pushing at it lately in a way he does not have to when he's out touring the pop tart movie.
I think when you I always I always said I'm a big Seinfeld fan. I'd love to meet him. I'd love to talk to him. I'm not taking a shot at anybody in particular here when I say this, but I think I always said I don't trust a clean comic.
Yeah, I see how stage squeaky clean. I'm like, that guy's hiding something. He's got a dark side. I think that's what you're seeing now. This guy for so long.
Like on the sitcom, the the remember that episode. Yo, well, hello, we pretend my girlfriend's belly button talks. The real story was the guy said he was his girlfriend and he pretended her ass talks.
And then Jerry was like, that's too dirty. And then in the special features, he's like, you know what hindsight asks his way, Funny Air, we should have just done it. Yeah.
And but my point is is you got a guy that that's cookie cutter clean cut right not cookie cutter or clean cut. It's going to come out eventually. He's he's letting it fly now, man. Well, I mean, he had a big scandal right out of the gate. I mean, he was dating high school or when he was 40. So that is true. I forgot about that. Yeah.
And I mean, it was a it was a different time question.
To each his own. Um, I, two and a step to an extent, to an extent, and to each her own, by the way, and to each their own as well. Yes.
Um, I was going to say, Joe.
Oh, I know I haven't had a drink in two weeks. Okay. Spiked me just forget what I was going to say there.
Um, and I'm saying it. I don't think I don't think I want to do it. Just Christ almighty.
I don't think I want to do it anymore. Pat, just let it go. Just just enjoy that you're doing it right now. Don't jinx it. Just leave it alone.
I've been doing it for a year and I hadn't done it in a while. Um, and I had no feelings of like hunger, no feelings of like, oh, you know, I got to eat food again or whatever else. What I had was a complete mental breakdown.
I have never, my anxiety has never been so through the roof. I was like at one point banging my head on my wall. Right.
I was in misery and I was like, no, Pat, you're going to do the five day water fast. You committed to even though it's doing something very bad to you and it's not fun.
So then day five noon hits. I had my first meal, which was like some probiotic juice was the best tasting thing I've ever had.
And just kind of since then I wake up with no shit.
But you know, I was waking up in big piles of shit every day. And now I wake up with no shit. It was that combination of that fast. And I'll say it again, ashwagandha and magnesium.
Change my life. All right.
Now I'm not saying I'll never do anything again. I'm saying right now. I couldn't even fathom it. That's it right now. That's an even fathom it.
That's all that exists is the now. You could not have said more LA or shit things in a row than you just did magnesium.
What the fuck was the other thing you said? Agnaganda ashwagandha and magnesium. And I go past all these idiots on TikTok with all their stupid theories. But this guy was a meathead and an idiot. And he was like, look, I'm dumb, but I always had a real anxiety problem.
Somebody told me to take this and I don't have an anxiety problem anymore. And I believed him because he was so dumb and not trying to sell me anything and magnesium in this ashwagandha or cheap as hell.
So I got him and I feel like that constant thing that anxiety sufferers have, that feeling that like you're not right in your body, you're not at home, you're not comfortable that I've had my entire life.
Was quickly gone. Do you take capsules or I'll give this shit a try? Do you take capsules or powder? I take capsules. And it's very easy. You just look it up online. You know, you can get them at Costco or the grocery store or wherever else.
Look, maybe it's stopping drinking that did it and that magnesium has nothing to do with it. I don't know. I'm no expert myself. I'm saying that I feel good for the first time in ten years probably.
Yes, no, I remember a good thing. I remember a month and a half ago when you said this.
No, not true.
You'll never hear me on this podcast talking about how good I feel. Maybe I'm feeling okay a week, but like this is sustained several weeks.
I saw the Queen of the Stone Age and didn't drink. I was like, I'm having a great time. He was on enough Molly for both of us.
But I was. Yeah. He, he goes after that guy. What would now now let me ask you about Queen. Look, I wish you the best with this. I've cut by drinking back to one day a week.
But that one day, I will tell you as I think that's a great idea. If you can do that, that would be my ideal as my as our old friend Trevor Moore said to me once. I only drink two nights a week.
But boy, do I swing for the fences? Yeah, sure. That's kind of how I'm looking at it. So I got pinkstone coming in on Sunday, today's Friday.
And get the crew together and we're going to have have a day. I'm supposed to be in New York right now. I called out of my two spots tonight because I got held over with family stuff.
I don't want to get into it. But since I was held over and I didn't go to New York tonight, I did start playing my Mad Max video game that I've been playing. And thank God we're recording this right now because I really felt like a loser. I was like, I'm not, I'm just sitting here playing Mad Max.
You're doing you're doing the furio said diet just water and minerals. That's right. What do you think one of the characters in that movie would say if you said to them? No, no, I have food.
I just choose not to eat it. Look, people in glass houses shouldn't be throwing stones. Everybody in that wasteland has their issues. All right.
Maybe you talk to me after you get the 45 boils, lanced off your back.
I'm playing the game. I'll get into the game. Well, it's a scary stuff. Actually, the game is awesome. Are you Max? Yes. Okay.
The game came out in 2015. It came out right after Fury Road came out. It is not based on one of the movies, but it takes place in the Mad Max universe. It's its own story.
George Miller has said it's not canon. However, I'm going to talk about the game a lot more when we talk about the movie today. But the game itself, which George Miller has also said it did not turn out very well is, I don't know what he's talking about. It's critically acclaimed every video game person online reviewing it is like this game is amazing.
It is. It is an awesome game. Like you get it. It's car combat. You have to infiltrate these fortresses and you just beat the shit out of people and steal their fuel. And it's fucking awesome, man. And it's just your upgrading. You're trying to build a car called the Magnum Opus.
So you can get out of the wasteland finally. And it's an amazing game. So if you like a grand theft auto open world style game that's far more combat focused. It's almost like Arkham City is probably a better parallel.
So check out Mad Max. Man is is it awesome. And it's made me the game has made me now appreciate the movies more and the lore of it all more because when you're in it for that long in the game.
Because a video game is like a modern day video game is like at least 10 hours, most of the times, yeah, 30 to finish, sometimes 60 like you're in it for so long, like you just, I don't know. I found a new appreciation for the lore of of Mad Max.
I saw in a violent nature yesterday, which we're going to review next time next week on this show.
But it sort of made me want to play a good video game again, which is not usually my thing, but you are it's like a first person shooter about your Jason Voorhees.
Is that what the Friday the 13th game is? Are you Jason and that you can you can be the Friday the 13th game is you can play it alone, but it's really designed to play online with other people or against other people and the idea is, is you can be one of the counselors who's part of a team of counselors trying to thwart or hide from Jason or you can be Jason and hunt the counselors.
I would say that's probably as close as you could get to an in a violent nature experience. There's a Texas chainsaw one.
I think as well, where your leather face maybe I don't know video game video game for everything now. It's kind of wild. Excuse me.
Let me take you down to that movie corn.
I'd like to, well, I'll start with what I saw yesterday. I saw babes.
Oh, directed by babes directed by Pamela Adlon, who her effects show better things was excellent. And she was the main creative force behind that.
This picture is written by Atlanta Glazer from broad city.
The less said about her stand up the better, but I really loved broad city.
And her writing partner Josh Rebenowitz, it is a sort of warts and all fluids and all look at having babies.
And it stars Michelle Beto, who I know as a friend of Joe.
I met lovely gal and Elana Glazer.
They have the kind of chemistry that I presume comes from a great friendship in real life. If not kudos to them for making it seem so natural.
And that's really the appeal of the movie is their chemistry. I would say script wise it leaves a lot to be desired at a certain point.
You know, in a movie that's an hour 50 when the story hasn't kicked in. You're like, what, what am I watching here? You know, it can't just be kind of a string of little funny dialogue bits.
And they try to kind of add one in in the 11th hour and it's too little too late. You don't really care. That said.
So let me ask you though, isn't the plot that she gets pregnant on a one night stand and that's the movie. She gets pregnant off this guy and he dies.
Oh, okay.
And she's just like raising it alone, but Bhutto has kids of her own Hassan Manage place her husband. And yeah, it's just like best friends who are going through pregnancy together.
And that to me, if you're just kind of hanging together a bunch of funny scenes, keep it 90 guys for a comedy.
This got exhausting by the end to me. Unfortunately, this is funny people in it. It was great to see Oliver Platt. I always love Oliver Platt.
John Carol Lynch, the character actor who played Marge Gunderson's husband in Fargo. And he's been in, you know, zodiac and things like that.
He's very funny because at the beginning he has this terrible comb over and every time they see him, he's their fertility doctor, he's trying something new with the hair.
So he's shaved the comb over and puts it down and he has like this disgusting lumpy head.
And I like seeing those kind of big visual gags. And you know, there's funny stuff in it. And it's likeable enough to make you wish it was a little better because I think a polish on that script.
But we could have had a real solid comedy as opposed to another kind of pretty good one. But babes, not quite for me. Boutot and Glazer are the reason to see it.
All right. I watched the beta test.
Jim Cummings. Is it coming or coming?
Yeah, the beta test was his latest film. It's about a Hollywood, a Hollywood agent played by him, who receives a mysterious invitation to go to a fancy hotel and have a sexual encounter with an anonymous person.
No strings attached. No questions asked identity concealed. He is becoming more and more jaded with the Hollywood lifestyle, the, you know, just the routine.
I mean, his marriage or soon to be marriage is becoming stagnant sexually. He goes to the encounter and has the greatest sexual experience of his life. He can't stop thinking about it. And then he goes on this mission to try to figure out who the woman is. And as he tries to figure out who the woman is, he starts to become aware that perhaps something more sinister is going on.
The original film, very, it's wild into places. It's it's shocking and it's wild and it's very, very funny.
It's dark. It's very, it feels a lot like what's his name, your friends and neighbors, Neil, a beaut. Yeah, it feels like a Neil, a beaut type of thing. Not quite as rough, but it's, it's in that world.
But it's very funny. And I mean, you want to talk about a scathing scathing commentary on Hollywood. And, you know, there's a monologue towards the end where he's like, because they talk about, I've noticed this is a recurring thing with Jim Cummings.
It's a lot about it, but they did this in Wolf of Snowhuller, like the new climate we're all living in. What you can't say what you can't say. Yeah. And that's referenced throughout the movie. And Harvey Weinstein is referenced throughout the movie. Well, since Harvey went away, things are different or whatever, at the end, I won't tell you exactly what happens or what unfolds.
This is a little bit of a spoiler. He has a sort of breakdown and does this amazing monologue where he's like, Harvey's gone, but everybody just wants to be Harvey, like, and he talks about how like everybody is acting so virtuous. And it's all bullshit. And he's like, none of us have any money. We're all pretending that we have money. We have these cars. We can't afford. We tell people we own them. We're just leasing them.
A lot of insight, quite frankly, shit that I didn't know about agents where I was like, oh, that is why they're all driving fancy cars because I was thought they were just running off with all the money, which they are a lot of the time. But, oh, yeah, agents always do better than the talent. Yeah, but I was like 10 % of 50 people.
Of course, I never, never thought of it that way. No, this is a look. You have to do this. If you don't, it looks like you're a failure.
I just really enjoyed the movie. It was challenging and interesting. And I think he does the male gaze thing well. I think he does it without apology, but he exposes it for its flaws at the same time.
And I think that that's a nice line to walk. It's an honest line to walk. And it seems like he's a genuine guy that's that cares about gender overall and is aware of the flaws of his own.
And we'll exploit them and make fun of them and expose them. But at the same time, we'll not also grovel and apologize to the point of not utilizing his, you know, his own masculinity and his own art or whatever.
However, you want to say it. But I think he walks a fine line. I think it's pretty interesting. And I enjoy his work quite a bit. He should be in more, he should be starring more stuff.
So, yeah, he's great. I mean, he mostly just writes so he can act in his own stuff. But I'm sure people catch on to him soon. Yeah, he was when I was on Twitter, he was following everyone, he would follow everybody in Hollywood.
Like, this is after right after Thunder Road, but I was like, the guy's hustling. I mean, I never had the patience for that kind of stuff. But yeah, he's made a nice little body of work already. I saw
your phone ringing spam risk all day or day. I saw the idea of you, the new Amazon Prime original movie.
Um, huge. Apparently it's one of the most streamed movies in the history of Amazon and it didn't go to theaters at a time where, as I said, my mom, who will, who doesn't know how to operate Amazon Prime, can't find something to see at the theaters. The business is broken.
But the movie would have done a hundred million dollars. If that fucking anyone, but you could bring in that much money. Why not keep the hits coming.
But then again, I think had I seen this in the theater, I probably would have thrown my popcorn at the screen. It was not very good. It is the, just the most basic of plots. I guess it's based on, you know, what they derogatory called chic lit.
A book that was sort of like fan fiction about a woman who meets Harry Styles in a one direction concert, an older woman, and they fall in love.
And that's basically what it is. It's Anne Hathaway, who's 40, who spends the whole movie being like, I'm so old and unattractive. And I guess I better push my breasts up so that somebody, you're one of the most stunning human beings on earth.
You know, like, and what I always think of is all the women who watch that and go, oh, God, if she's insecure about herself.
Yikes. Sure. I don't know. It bothers me because I, of course, feel that now as well. It's become everyone has the perfect body.
But Anne Hathaway, she's 40, she's insecure, she's divorced. Her ex has moved on, she's cheating with a younger woman, whatever.
So she goes to Coachella, not very convincing, stand in for Coachella. By the way, can I, can I just interject? Yes, the entire reason I didn't want to see this movie.
Yeah, it is now maybe I'm wrong, but I'm like, we're now making movies based. It started with with brands like Uber. Yes, stuff. Now we're doing like it's like, of course it's Coachella, the biggest music festival.
It's a huge brand thing. I'm sure Coachella will put money into this. It's just God damn it, man. It just makes me sick. Yeah. Well anyway, go ahead. Sorry. What are you going to do? And it's on Amazon Prime. So, you know, here, here we are.
But Anne Hathaway lives in Silver Lake, which is where I live, you know, and that was, that's kind of fun when you want to move these shoots in your neighborhood. You go, I've eaten there. You know, that's kind of fun.
But she goes to Coachella. She meets this guy. He's British or whatever. His name's Nicholas Goldstein. He's, you know, a stand in for one direction and all that. He's very hunky.
Very boring, very dull. No personality. I guess that's the fantasy nowadays is just a man who looks good and barely speaks and just wants you and nobody else and has no edge or personality of any kind.
Or body hair or, you know, just just a twink man who loves only you. And she falls for him. But she says this can't be because it's so forbidden. What with me being 40 and you being 24 years old.
And then we juggle that non -situation for the remainder of the movie.
It's like, you know, the obstacles are Anne Hathaway has a 16 year old daughter and that's a little awkward.
But, you know, it's just a very simple premise for a movie. It seems very similar to that marry me, which came out with the, didn't you see that one Joe with Owen Wilson?
Yeah, that is a terrible film. But is that this premise too?
When I saw the trailer for this, I was like, this is just marry me, isn't it? And I was shocked too. I almost texted you about it because I was like, I can't believe Anne Hathaway is doing these kinds of move.
Like, this is people are just hard up, Jack. Yeah, it's, it's super generic. And then, you know, not only that.
I check the credits. This thing was not only directed by the great Michael show Walter from the state. And then it was has directed numerous great movies and projects and television.
But written by Michael show Walter and Jennifer Westfeld, who is an excellent writer of smart adult romantic comedies.
So those two together, I don't know how you find a movie this devoid of humor. And this just kind of frictionless.
You know, it's like, they won't, you know, nudities gone. So you have these sex scenes that look like you're watching a hallmark commercial where you see like, you know, they kiss and then like a pair of panties being thrown in slow motion across the floor.
Sorry, that's not hot to me. I guess, you know, it definitely seems like it's for the, I don't know what to say.
The, the, the less discerning rom -com fan because there's no common this at all. It's just a romantic drama. And it's played very kind of annoyingly straight and boring and right down the middle.
And to have show Walter, who is so weird and has such an insane sense of humor. This involved in a project so generic is also kind of a bummer.
But, you know, it sounds this all sounds terrible. It's not great. It just felt like I was being marketed something.
All right. There you go. Where's the passion people?
There ain't none. Ain't none. I watched another independent feature by another independent feature maker. One Mr. Jim Jarmush is the dead don't die.
I remember reviewing this five years ago on this very podcast and talking about how much I hated it, particularly the ending.
I'm glad that you finally cut up to it. It's a terrible fucking movie. Yeah, it really is. It's just a nothing.
It's just a nothing, nothing movie. It's for God's sakes. There's just nothing to it. It's lousy. It sucks. It's boring. I wrote to you.
As I was watching it about how boring I thought it was, and you said, yeah, it's really a slog. It sucks. And I also said to you, and I stand by this Jim Jarmush has been making boring fucking movies for decades.
And he just continued. Jim Jarmush is the prototype for criterion collection. Like the title is in that collection. I'll tell you that.
He's the prototype of like, yeah, there ain't really much here to dig your teeth into. But boy, boy, it's art. And you're like, I guess I don't know. It's fucking boring.
Yeah, no. I mean, he was considered a God in my film school experience as well. And I would always fall asleep when they would screen his movies. But you never really, I'd never come out and say, I don't like this guy's work. But the older I get, like what Joe was texting me about at the other night. And I was like, yeah, I'm not seeing anything to disagree with here.
Like he makes the, you know, the thing the most pretentious annoying guy in your film class would make. But he's been able to do it at a pretty solid one to $5 million budget for 40 years. And I don't know how.
That's not these are smash hits. He's not Wes Anderson. No, he is not. No, he is not.
He is the, he is, he is like a gym drama. I said to you, I go, he's Kevin Smith without the dick jokes. Like it's just like, yeah, at least Kevin Smith, like in the good movies, there's like gags to laugh at. And there's characters that you have fun watching.
Like there's nothing interesting about any of these characters. It's Bill Murray moping the fuck around being monotone and somber. Yeah, it's Adam driver.
You know, just being, I don't know, I don't even know.
It's Chloe Zevenier. Like, again, just I don't even get the point of the character. Like I can't even give you a trait.
Selena Gomez. These are all good actors. Selena Gomez. Just nothing. There's just nothing happening. Selena Gomez's whole purpose is to wear short shorts. Right.
And walk around while guys like ogle her or whatever. The only character character with any discernible features or traits rather.
And it's my least favorite character in the movie is till the Swinton for no reason doing this fucking Scottish accent just so she can show off.
And it's a rip off of kill Bill. She's just doing kill. It's she look. They do her up to look like Uma Thurman. She carries a sword around and she cuts zombies heads off.
Yeah. And it's kill Bill. Yeah.
The movie sucks. It's pretentious. The end, what you talked about on here.
When Adam driver throughout the movie keep saying, this isn't going to end well. And then Bill Murray finally at the end says, well, why do you keep saying that? He goes, because I read the script.
Yeah. What is the point of that? What is the point of that now?
I'm a big at the Losfield is three. It got a big like one of those laughs. One guy in the back like, but spills is honored Arnold Palmer into his lap.
Boy, it's hard to say Arnold Palmer when you're angry. Yeah, it's in there.
Now I'll say this.
I'm willing to give Jar much a little slack here because this is sort of in the COVID zone. I think, or was it pre -COVID? I think it was pretty.
You know, it's like, all right, everybody kind of was a little off their game during COVID.
Yeah. That one, that one to me is where I was kind of like, this guy's a joke. He's a scam. You know?
No, 2019. So it's right. Yeah, it's, I mean, it was written before COVID.
I mean, but also to the fucking like at the beginning when the song The Dead Dog die plays and driver does the thing of the game.
Come on, get into it. It's the theme song.
Yeah. What is the point of that? What is the point of that aspect of the film? Like, what is the commentary there?
What is the point of the of the, it's two 10 second bits that throw off the entire realism of your movie, which I know is a movie where fantastical things happen.
Zombies happen, but still like, you're getting nothing from those two tiny jokes.
Well, but it's also, and it makes me feel like fuck you, honestly. Yes. Fuck you for taking this seriously. Fuck you.
If it was a movie about making a movie. Yeah. And then the joke at the end is the main character goes, I read the script. This isn't going to end well.
Cause it's a disastrous production or whatever. I'd be like, oh, that's really surreal and funny and clearly a commentary on whatever.
Like, there's this is that's, it's just jammed in there. By the way, Jarmus is one of these guys sunglasses on 24 seven.
Yep. Like, you know, man, I don't know. I don't, I don't have time for it, man. It's cool kid shit.
Uh, you know, Wes Anderson gets on my nerves sometimes, but he's cranked out some bangers. I mean, Wes Anderson has cranked out that.
Sophia Coppola has cranked out some bangers. They're allowed to miss the mark here or there. This guy holy shit.
And now by law is unlimited access to Bill Murray as well.
Do you see down by law? I've seen down by law. I mean, I recently watched night on earth, which was supposed to be another one of his masterpieces. I'm like, well, you got a lot of great actors here saying things that aren't funny in a cab.
That's the movie. The biggest atrocity was coffee and cigarettes.
Oh, I remember, maybe I just pretended I like these at the time. I remember kind of liking ghost dog. I remember kind of liking dead man.
Yeah, I like ghost dog. You know why there's a fucking plot. Yeah, right. Exactly.
There's a plot. And then like, and there's absurdity in it. And like it is kind of weird and offbeat when like the Italian mobster is wrapping all the flavor. Flavestuff.
Yeah, like that's funny and weird and you're like, that's odd.
Okay, I'll go with you that far, Jarmish.
But dead man, I refuse. I'm like, I'm not watching Johnny Depp not talk for 90 minutes. I'm not doing this 90 minutes.
I think that's 220 if it's if it's a minute.
I saw sperm world, which we also could have called the idea of you folks.
sperm world.
Yes, sperm world.
This is currently on Hulu.
And I watched it because I am a huge fan of this director's first and probably not as first made a bunch of shorts, whatever.
But he got put on my radar by directing this documentary called some kind of heaven, which followed people in a retirement community.
And is one of my favorite documentaries of all time, like a five star movie, it blew me away.
The way it was shot, the people he focused on.
He focused on this guy who decided that he was going to be out of his mind high on drugs for the last 20 years of his life.
But he's married to a woman who doesn't approve.
And that story, I mean all the stories in it are great, but that it to me is one of the darkest human stories I've ever seen.
And I just was like, I got to watch what this guy does.
He gets these really amazing stories out of people.
Premiering on Sunday, he's got a new thing called Renfair on HBO Max that I'm very excited about, which is like a three hour behind the scenes look at a Renaissance fair and the power struggle who takes over as king.
I'm excited to watch that sperm world, maybe a bit of a rush job in between the two projects.
I loved it, but to me, it didn't go deep enough.
What it is is people who get online and say I will either fuck you or I will give you my sperm.
And it's for people who can't afford the sperm bank.
So it's a lot of lower income people.
This documentary starts with a very chatty, like almost coked up level chatty, a kind of weird guy opening a door to a motel room.
This strange woman he's never met comes in.
And he's like, yeah, so basically I'm going to, you know, bend you over off the side of the bed and I'll fuck you like this.
And then, you know, we'll keep your legs up here like this sort of.
And she's like, I just need a minute to kind of get my bearings if that's okay.
John the floor awkward uncomfortable shit throughout.
And these men all seem, I'm not judging, but they seem to be fairly damaged people.
And they don't get the intimacy required.
There is an old guy 65 who's impregnated several women, but he falls in love with all of them.
And he falls in love with this girl who's like 22.
And she says she's a lesbian to get him off her back.
And then he invites her over to watch Mulholland Drive.
And he's like looking at her out of the corner of his eye during the lesbian scene.
It's, it's a wild movie.
And this guy, if I didn't say his name, it is Lance Oppenheim.
He's on the best show with Tom Sharp in this week.
They have an interview with him.
But he's a guy who after that first one, some kind of heaven, I will watch every thing this guy does.
I really do love him.
Spurmworld, not my favorite, but it's on Hulu right now.
If you just want to watch something that will make you cringe a lot, it's, it's that kind of vibe.
But for me, I wanted to know like, what's the damage of a guy who has impregnated 150 women?
And they don't ask the questions that you want asked.
They're instead just kind of observing all these strange and awkward little moments.
But I came away from it like, I want to know what was going on with these people.
Because what a life.
Anyway, check it out.
My third, my third was going to be the crow.
But I actually think we should do it in honor of this new, new, new and old when it comes out, right?
Pat, you will not get me into the theater to see the new crow.
I'll tell you who really doesn't seem to like the new crow is the star of the new crow.
I read an interview with him and he was like, yeah, I don't like the way it ends and I didn't like this and I didn't like that.
It looks absurd.
Yeah.
They played the trail.
Let's do the original one.
Yeah.
I got it in 4K.
I'm excited to rewatch.
There's an easy way to watch the new one.
I'll watch it.
But I'm not driving to a theater to watch it.
The, the, it looks ridiculous.
Yeah.
Ridiculous.
Like there's, they, they take all the, now, maybe I never read the comic, but they take all the supernatural part out of it.
It seems like, like in the, in the movie or in the trailer, I mean, he's just like walking up to people.
Like, like, and the guy's like, I killed you and he's like, yeah, you did.
Here I am now.
You know, like, no, it's like kind of creepy when he's like ghostly and they don't know what's going on.
And like, I don't remember the crow.
And that, that's why I'm excited to revisit it.
I also don't remember being obsessed with it.
I like the soundtrack for sure.
Still some bangers on there.
The cure still plays that song from, from that soundtrack, which is great.
Yeah.
One of the great helmet songs on that milk toast.
Yes.
Anyway.
So that's all I got.
I was going to do that was my third one, but I'm going to save it.
Okay.
Great.
Then let's get down to it.
Mad Max.
Is it just Furiosa or is it a mad Max saga or what's the colon?
Do we know?
Furiosa colon.
A mad Max saga.
Okay.
I thought a saga.
I guess a saga can just be a story.
All right.
Yeah.
Furiosa.
The.
It's basically a prequel to Fury Road.
Fury Road.
I've seen three times since the theater, but I remember being at the Vista, the original Vista,
seeing that movie.
I remember that moment.
About halfway through where like the sky goes blue and all the sound drops out after you've
been watching nothing but action for an hour and the entire audience started applauding the
only time since I was like a kid where that felt like real and genuine to me where everybody
was just like this movie fucking rocks.
And I love it on rewatches.
I love it.
I also love how simple it is.
They're driving one way.
Then they got to drive the other way.
There's not much more to it.
This one, when they start doubling and tripling and quadrupling down on plot, I was getting
a little nervous.
And when I saw the chapter headings come up, I'm like, oh boy.
But basically you're getting the story of Furiosa, who was on Nutella Joy.
She was on the big rig with all the other kind of child bride types in Fury Road.
I don't know.
She wasn't.
Furiosa is Charlie's throat.
What?
What is the matter with you?
No.
You're joking, right?
Are you joking?
I'm already wrong.
No.
Yeah, Charlize Theron is pure.
So this is a prequel.
It's the story of how she comes to be.
I thought on Nutella Joy was one of those girls on the she might have been.
She might have been he loves doing that.
He loves taking one person, putting them in a different role.
He did it in Fury Road, the bad guy, Joe, Imogen, Joe, whatever the hell the guy's name is, Morton, Joe.
That's the same actor from the first Mad Max movie.
He loves recasting people in New World.
Unfortunately, I'm completely wrong and embarrassed.
She wasn't even in it.
Oh boy.
So all right.
Well, I thought she just became one of the maids on that because at the end she joins the other maids.
No, that's her putting them on.
She's putting them on to the truck because she smuggles them out in Fury Road.
That's the thing.
Okay.
We had Rosie Huntington Whiteley, Riley Keo.
It was a lot of hot blondes, you know, like in their underwear.
And I guess I just thought she was there, but she was probably only 10 years old back then.
It was unnecessary.
I thought it was unnecessary to recast the role.
I thought that with all the deaging that you can do.
And also the fact that I think really has had a miserable time on that movie though.
Well, maybe that's what it was.
That's what it was then.
But but my point is, let's say, well, okay, if she didn't want to go back, she didn't want to go back.
But if she did want to go back, the amount of time she's got like black shit all over her face and her face is covered.
And would just make it Charlize.
Like this is like, like, but in any case, also, by the way,
Furiosa doesn't enter the picture till a third of the way in, you know, as Annie Taylor joy.
Yeah, yeah, we see her as a little girl.
That okay.
So you should definitely summarize the plot if I'm that wrong because clearly I missed something.
But I watched these for the spectacle.
And this one was more plot than spectacle or more plot than action, I would say.
But not that that was necessarily a negative by the end of it.
Walk us through, Joe.
It opens with, well, first I want to say that there are a lot of tethers to other Mad Max things throughout this movie, which I really appreciate it.
It opens in a sort of Edenistic garden, which to me is very much a nod to it's not the same place as Thunderdome.
I don't think it might be.
I don't know, but it's very similar to where the children all live in Thunderdome.
I thought that was cool.
The place is being potentially, it's secret.
It's a Valhalla amidst this wasteland of nothing.
So they need to keep it secret.
And they furious as a young girl spots that there are intruders.
And she goes to try to thwart the intruders, the intruders spot her.
They chase her as they're chasing her.
She pulls out a whistle and starts blowing it.
It's the same whistle that Mad Max blows in Thunderdome when he's fighting master blaster.
Little things like that, I thought are kind of cool.
Anyway, they abduct her.
They bring her back to their camp.
Their camp is run by.
Dementus played by Chris Hemsworth.
And, you know, I will say odd to call them Dementus in a world where Harry Potter had the Dementors so famously.
I was like, guys, I thought with the Australian accent, I thought they were saying Dementors.
I was like, that's dumb.
Well, what's funny, too, is he's mislabeled online as Doctor Dementus, because people think Doctor Dementus.
Oh, really?
Which he's not.
It's just Dementus.
He, you know, and he's one of the warlords of the wasteland.
They end up killing her mother who tries to rescue her.
Furiosa quietly swears vengeance.
And she wants to get back to the green place where she is from.
She tattoos a map to it on her arm so she'll never forget how to get home.
And then the movie unfolds from there.
It's about her journey in trying to get back to this place.
Eventually, not too far in.
Dementus attempts to overthrow a Morton Joe at the Citadel from Fury Road.
He gets swatted down, but eventually takes over Gastown, which sends all its fuel to the Citadel.
And Morton Joe agrees to make a pact with Dementus.
You can run Gastown.
I'll accept the wager or the pact.
And we run the Citadel and we trade.
And that's how all the Mad Max movies kind of go.
There's a group that needs something from another group.
Will it be war?
Will it not be blah, blah, blah.
Amidst all this, Furiosa grows up.
She proves her worth on the Fury Road run between Gastown and the Citadel.
She ends up being taken under the wing of something Jack.
I can't remember his name, Pretorian Jack.
I think it is.
They sort of fall in love.
They make a pact that she's going to bring him back to this place, the green place.
But Amidst all this, they are undermined by Dementus.
And she still wants to kill him because he killed her mother.
And ultimately, it becomes her mission to avenge her mother and kill Dementus above all other things.
That's basically the plot.
I don't want to go through every single little beat, but that's basically the plot.
That's basically it with, of course, driving scenes and battles and people flying through the air and things blowing up and so forth.
From me, I thought it was the best Chris Ham's worth has been.
I loved him as the villain.
And I like him way better when he's being his authentic Australian self.
Otherwise, I don't even know if I've ever liked him and anything.
He was awesome.
They were both.
He was.
He and Anna Taylor joy.
They were both great in different ways.
Absolutely.
He got to chew the scenery and be the Wild Mad Max villain and he's great at it.
And she has three lines in the entire movie and conveys so much with her eyes.
It's insane.
And she also had a miserable time on the movie, like a traumatic time.
Like I think people don't want to go out to the desert and do this.
I think they really earn their money in these movies.
They're so physical.
And you're just standing in the sand.
You know, Dune is kind of the same thing.
But to me, everyone raves about the world building in Dune.
World building is the new Hollywood term for, you know, what like George Lucas did or whatever creating a world building the world.
And the world building of barter town or wasteland or gas town or whatever.
To me is so much more exciting to look at and beautiful and effective and just my style, I guess, way over a Dune.
You know, like the world building of Dune is they're in a big pit of sand.
You know, I know there's more to it.
You nerds.
But to me, Dune bites.
Dune bites.
And that's why even as I started kind of being like, all right.
I wish there was more action in this Mad Max movie.
Eventually, what kind of won me over about it was just I saw it in I max.
And it was just looking back and forth across the screen at all the cool shit I was saying.
That's what eventually won me over.
And that's what made me not even really noticed the 220 thing.
I think we could have cut 20.
I always think we could have cut 20.
But I really liked it.
And then this morning when I woke up, I liked it even more because I kept thinking about cool shit from it.
I think George Miller is a true artist and a visionary.
And I'll take his crazy visions over the muted drab brown visions of Dune.
I liked I liked the movie.
When I first saw it, I was like, it was okay.
There were parts I liked.
There were parts I was kind of bored, whatever.
The more I thought about it, the more I fell in love with it.
The more I appreciated the performances, it's very well directed by Miller.
There is my one gripe aside from the length.
It does not need to be as long as it is.
No.
But my one gripe is there is some very painfully obvious CGI stuff in it.
Now let me pause you there because I went in having heard that from you and others.
And I'm usually very critical about that.
I love the old school practical effects.
I noticed a couple of times maybe people rolling off a bike where I was like,
oh, wow, that could have been done better.
But only a couple.
I didn't see big swings that didn't land.
So what about this?
There were just things like where a truck was like,
there's the part where Chris Hemsworth is like ramming the gate over and over.
And it's backing up and driving into camera backing up.
Yeah.
He's not sitting in that truck right now.
It's like obvious.
Right.
It was stuff like that where I was like, he clearly after two people died on the last
movie.
Yeah.
It was like, we have to be a lot safer.
And I think that's the only reason for that stuff.
It just shows because every other Mad Max has been so insanely real.
Yeah.
And I it just showed in this.
That's all which I get it.
That's what I missed from this or at first.
Like last night when I was talking with my friend on the way out to the car,
I was like, I just missed the wall to wall two hours of insanity.
Just the craziness.
That's what I missed.
That's what kind of let me down because that's why I come to these movies.
But because it got less crazy, I don't know if that's because he's 85 or what,
but or that two people died last time.
But since we're not focusing as much on the action, the car chases,
the story really did shine by the end of it.
I really did care.
And I really loved both of their performances in a way that makes it such a bummer
that unless somebody wants to do maybe a half budget version of it,
which could be cool too.
I'd want more of that story.
I really dug the Furiosa prequel.
I'm not even a prequel guy because I figure who gives a shit.
You know how it ends.
But I hope is it was cool.
My hope is that because everybody saying we're never going to get this,
because the next thing was supposed to be Tom Hardy,
Mad Max, the wasteland, where it was the year before Fury Road.
And everybody say, now we're not going to get it because this didn't do well.
My hope, it hardly can't open a movie.
I don't think.
No.
So my hope is that this will now lead to us getting one last Mel Gibson,
Mad Max, because that is the stunt he needs to pull to get a Mad Max movie made again.
And I think there would be nothing cooler than seeing Mad Max in his 70s
in this fucking like, it would be awesome.
Anyway, he's already got the beard.
I mean, it would be amazing.
That would be amazing.
And he doesn't have to talk.
We can just beat him up.
It would be fucking awesome.
Anyway, those are my only gripes in the movie.
I actually, the thing I really like most about two things I like most about it,
I really like that it leaned into the legend of Furiosa,
because they talk about that in the Mad Max movies.
There's a man named Max.
They speak of him.
He's got all these nicknames.
Like, you know, and he becomes like this sort of legend, like a ghost.
And I like that this was, they played it very much with like an unreliable narrator,
especially the thing at the end, where it's like, this is the story of this woman that gets told.
And is it true or not?
Who knows?
And blah, blah, blah.
It's like a little prologue.
It definitely feels like it's own little contained thing in a very cool way.
So I thought that that was cool.
And I thought that that did as apprehensive as I was at the beginning with the chapter headings,
as you said, and also starting with her as a little girl and everything.
By the end, I was like, oh, I get why he did that now.
So that all really worked.
I also loved, you know, the guy said the video game is not canon,
but he took tons of shit from the video game and put it in this movie.
There were characters from the game in the movie.
There were two characters from the game in the movie, Scrodus,
who's the main villain in the video game is in the movie.
Scrodus and Rexus.
Rexus.
No, yeah, there is a guy named Rexus.
Right there next to Scrodus.
I assume that was intentional.
I got a big laugh.
Yes.
Chuck Bucket is in the movie who is this mechanic that you work,
you're with him through the entire video game.
There was also devices from the game that were in the movie.
A big part of the game, a huge part of the game is sniping.
There's so many sniper things in this movie.
A huge part of the game is ramming, like ramming through gates and shit.
That was a big part of this movie.
A huge part of the game is a harpoon and pulling things down with the harb.
That was part of this movie.
There was so much stuff from the game that it's made the game much more enjoyable.
But yeah, it's a really, really, really solid piece of work.
And then the best part, and this is a major spoiler,
and talking about the legend of Furiosa and all that stuff,
she's tied, she's captured at one point by Dementus.
And he kills her boyfriend, Jack, he kills him.
And he keeps her chained with her.
She's got a damaged arm at this point.
She's chained up with her damaged arm up in the air.
And he's doing it to fuck with her even more.
And then he gets off the, Dementus gets off his like throne or whatever
and goes around to see where she's been chained up to confront her.
And she's gone.
And she's gone because she cut her own arm off.
Yeah.
And it's the arm with the map to her home.
So she sacrifices everything in the end.
So she can escape and plot her and plot how to kill this fucking guy.
Like it's, I got chills at that part.
I was like, holy shit, this is nuts.
So that was awesome.
That was awesome.
It's a good.
It's a really, it winds up being a really cool story.
Like at first, I was like, this is a drag.
I don't want this.
I don't want more exposition.
And by the end, I was very into it.
Reminding me kind of of solo where it just works like really, really well, you know,
as its own little contained thing.
And another look at a beloved franchise.
So I'd love to get more.
I'm sure they'll be talk of a series or something at some point.
It'll be rebooted in five years if they don't do it now.
So why not do it?
Uh, yeah.
My hog is plenty up.
Mindy up fully engorged.
Fully engorged with water and fuel.
From the wasteland for Furiosa.
By the way, my favorite character in this one was the baby man who sits in a world of vegetables in a tank.
Well that, that kid is 13 years old.
That's the kid that went viral because he.
He was the video of him went viral because the kids were teasing him at school.
And he was crying and saying, I want to rope to kill myself and the mom.
Oh my god.
The mom video.
I mean, I'm happy that we learned more about how cruel people can be and that bullying is terrible.
I do think it's weird that a mom videotapes her son in that state and puts it up publicly.
That I didn't see it.
And I'm glad he passed on the new Mad Max.
Yeah, that said he George Miller saw it and put him in the movie, which is awesome.
But honestly, he was my favorite part when he died.
Sorry again, spoiler.
I was like, man, I love that kid.
Yeah, that kid was awesome.
Yeah, the characters, the characters are I, my favorite character was the guy with the.
I mean, not main character, but the character, the guy that had like that bird nose.
Like he had like that goal.
Yeah, yeah.
That guy was awesome.
Yeah.
It was a great movie.
And Morton Joe was played by a different actor.
The original actor sadly died in 2020.
But, but the other actor looks the part.
I thought it was the same guy for a minute.
I did.
But please, I hope we get more Mad Max.
I'm sure we will.
George Miller wants to do another video game and, and you know, I'm sure we'll get comic books.
I think there have been comic books.
But it's worth the IMAX.
I want to go back and watch all of them again.
And I just watched all of them.
And I didn't like Fury Road on the we rewatch because I was like without the theater and everything.
But I also watched the black and chrome one.
I think I just got to rewatch it and call it.
Yeah.
And apparently that's not the one to watch.
All right.
Well, folks, we'll be back with in a violent nature, a title that is nearly impossible to remember.
Sometimes they'll just be a title that's just slippery.
That movie much like what was that called late night with the devil.
It's a shutter original, which I didn't realize till I was seated in the theater.
So that should be on shutter by the end of the month.
If you don't get the theaters to see it.
But it is a cool experience in a theater.
And maybe I'm not committing us.
But maybe we'll finally do Pearl.
That's on streamers now.
And Maxine is about to come out.
So.
Sure.
All right, folks.
I got.
Well, it's official.
We announced today my special is taping September 14th, where Phoenixville, Pennsylvania at the colonial theater.
My hometown.
Kind of wild to be doing a special home town.
Well, I'm from collegeville, but it's same thing.
Anyway, we're shooting September 14th.
Two shows only very, very, very limited tickets.
It's a very small room.
But it's going to be a great time.
This is I never promised to a rose garden.
Been working hard on it for about two and a half years.
There are going to be one or two warm -up shows leading into the taping.
But that's it.
The tour is done.
And now it will be the taping.
So I'm excited.
You can also catch me out there doing some other things this summer.
Like the Burke Chrysler tour in June.
A fully loaded.
I'll be with Steve Byrne and some other fun people in Pittsburgh on July 20th for a charity event.
I'm out there.
But please come and get your tickets for the special Joe de Rosa dot com.
And if you're in New York, come on by the Joey roses.
We're open seven days a week.
Joey roses dot com.
Miss Pat show season four just dropped on BET plus is doing extremely well.
Please check it out to eight episodes.
Get the free trial if you don't want to pay.
I'm at.
Oh, no, no, no, go ahead.
I'm sorry.
I'm at the Patrick Walsh.
We are at CU and help pod on Instagram.
I do one more plug.
Sorry.
Please realize it was announced.
I'll be October 11th and 12th.
Rosemond Illinois Zanies in Rosemond doing a bunch of clubs again.
Starting in the fall with brand new material.
That's that's the first announced show of the run of new material.
So come on out to that too.
All right, folks.
We'll see you next time and we'll see you in hell.