I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, and when the sound of your screams becomes
a thing of my dreams, you know I'll say, I'll see you in hell, you know I will.
I'll see you in hell, you know I will.
Folks, it's Will, see you in hell, apologize about the echo, I'm in an empty
house, but we're back, and here we go with some talk on Insidious.
Aye, aye, aye, part five, they just keep going with this fucking franchise.
Now Patrick Wilson is directing them.
Yeah, we'll get to it, I'm done with this franchise.
There's always a point where you got to tap out and I'm there for those.
Mandy Moore is going to save it with the sidequel that they're going to do now.
So what's that, Mandy Moore and Kumail, they're not the couple, the demon goes to them, what is it?
You got me, it's one of these, it's one of these title calling a story of insidious,
or an insidious tale, they all do this now with these franchises.
The weirdest one I've seen, is you remember that movie Wonder with Owen Wilson?
Oh yeah.
About the kid who was, what was the kid?
Jacob Tremblay, he had the facial deformity.
Oh yeah, yeah okay.
So there is a movie coming out, set in World War II,
and it is called White Bird colon a wonder story.
What, what, what does that mean?
It's in the same universe.
How can it be in the same universe as a movie where Owen Wilson has a son with a weird face?
A movie from Nazi times.
Facial deformity, let's not say the kid's got a weird face.
You know, a facial deformity, yes.
Yeah, but I mean, but what a, I'm assuming,
I'm assuming they, in some way in this film,
talk inspirationally about like a grandfather or something,
or you meet a grandfather who fought in World,
well no, Christ, the guy would be a hundred now, or whatever.
I don't know, some shit like that.
It's gonna be like, remember they talk about the grandfather,
or the great grandfather, they're going to show his story now.
Wait a minute, was Wonder set in the past?
It might take place in the eighties or something.
No, it's not like in the forties.
So White Bird says after the events of Wonder, meaning it's a sequel,
Julian has left Beecher Prep for good.
He is visited by his grandmother from Paris.
Oh, here we go.
Who tells him stories of her childhood as a young Jewish girl in Nazi occupied France.
Why do you need, why do you need to connect this to Wonder?
It's a, it's both a spin -off and prequel.
No, sequel.
I'm reading it from Wikipedia, a spin -off and prequel to Wonder.
That doesn't make sense.
You're saying after the events.
No, no, prequel, prequel is my confusion.
The flashbacks are the prequel part.
Yes, but it also says a spin -off.
But it's the kid.
It's the kid's bully.
Oh, they couldn't get Tremblay.
The kid's bully is expelled from school in Wonder for bullying the kid with the facial disorder.
And then the sequel is him after he's been expelled talks.
I guess he's talking to his grandma and she's like, you know, who was some other bullies?
The Nazis, but like why in God's name does this need to be a Wonder spin -off or prequel?
I don't get it.
Did Wonder do well?
Give me some numbers on Wonder.
I don't remember it doing great.
It was written by the great Stephen Conrad, apparently with a gun to his head,
because he is an amazing writer and Wonder was not very good.
Julia Roberts and Owen Wilson.
What was your question about it?
Did Wonder make money?
Holy shit.
306 million worldwide on a 20 million budget.
So yeah, then that's there.
That answers your question.
And sometimes I'm just shocked by what a movie made.
I would have thought this lost tons of cash.
That answers your damn question.
Yeah, it does.
All right.
We've probably spent enough time talking about a Wonder story.
We're going to get too insidious.
Joe, what's new with you on our break between recording?
I looked up the weather in New York and I was devastated
to learn that it will be 70 degrees there, just like it's 75 degrees here.
What devastates you about that?
You want it colder weather, you mean?
When I go to New York, I want it to be arctic.
When I go to Missouri, I want there to be snow and it never happens anymore
because I'm so sick of every day being the same in LA.
I know no one wants to hear you complain about perfect weather every day,
but it's boring.
Yeah, it sucks that the few days I'm going to be in New York,
it's going to be exactly like it is here.
But I like New York.
I won't say it'll be exactly.
I think 70 in New York will still have times throughout the day
when it feels crisp and fall -ish.
I would imagine that by the time that sun goes down,
you're going to get some of that chillier weather you'd like to have.
Are we both going to have seen killers of the flower moon
by the time I see you next?
I think I'm going today.
No.
Okay.
We should do that.
I got to tell you, I don't think I got it in me.
Four and a half hours.
I mean, Jesus Christ, guys.
It's three and a half, but you're going to have 30 of trailers for sure.
I don't know if there's an intermission.
It's weird.
Dances with Wolves would have been the first three hour I saw at the theater
and I saw it at the Dollar Show with my dad and I fucking loved it,
but there was an intermission and I loved that too.
Because it was the first time as a kid of the eighties,
I was able to like experience that kind of old school thing.
I don't know that any movie released in my lifetime since
has had an intermission that I'm aware of.
Joe, do you?
Hateful Eight had an intermission.
That's correct.
That's the only thing I've ever seen that had one.
Irishmen didn't.
I mean, what's the fear?
I guess they want to have as many showings in a day as possible.
I don't know.
I mean, in an industry where the movie houses are planning screenings around
the goddamn Taylor Swift thing.
I mean, it's like they can't put a fucking intermission in for something.
By the way, Taylor Swift, I randomly, somebody was like,
oh, it was my friend back in Missouri.
It was like this album is a great album.
You should listen to this album whenever.
And I'm pretty open minded.
I've liked her singles.
I know she's talented.
I just wouldn't drive around listening to it.
But I put on this album.
I think it was evermore or one of those ones she did with the national guy.
And it was great.
It really was.
And I was like, I'm going to go see what this girl's all about.
And I realized she has done something pretty ingenious.
Christopher Nolan has been praising her all week.
He's like, she's done as much as I have to save the movie coming experience.
She is not allowing any of these plans.
Like I'm AMCA list.
So I'm supposed to see three movies for free a week.
She's not allowing you to do that.
You have to pay the full amount for it.
And then she's saying, I'm not having any screenings Monday through Wednesday
because I want my fans to be focused on their school work
on those first three days of the week.
And you're like, okay.
But then when you look into it a bit, you realize
Tuesday is when AMC offers their $5 tickets.
Yeah, this is she's not doing shit for the industry.
She's doing what she always does, which is
greedily sucking up every fucking dime she possibly can.
But she's showing in a business ruled by greed, whether we like it or not,
the entertainment industry runs on money.
She is showing them how they can make that money by doing things.
She's smarter than them or her team is smarter than them.
I guess, you know, it is a business making operation.
Also, I have read and I'm not standing up.
I don't know anything about her, but all I've read about her
is that she gives giant cash bonuses to her truck drivers,
everybody on her team and blah, blah, blah.
I think she's about as good as you can be for being a billion, billion, billion.
Possibly.
She's somebody that demanded a higher amount in her streaming revenues that,
which there's always like an inkling of nobleness in what she's doing.
But then there's also a part that's very selfish.
So it's like there's always the thing where it's like she's demanding more
streaming revenue.
That's a good thing.
Artists should get more.
But then it's at the expense of other artists, arguably,
because they have to pay her so much more.
So it's, you know, this kind of thing where it's like
Taylor is doing this for the movie industry.
It's like, wow, that's really noble.
But then you go, yeah, but it's also fucking the other people with movies,
like because now their movies have to be the screening times have to be set around.
Like Taylor and I'm not complaining about this one.
Taylor Swift's movie is the reason the exorcist believer was.
That was the last nail in the coffin.
Right.
Second weekend of that's run of its run when it could have in theory bounce back.
Yeah.
Taylor Swift dropped.
So I will be forever grateful to Taylor for that.
But I don't know.
The jury's out for me on her.
You know, there's a lot of theories that she stunted the vinyl manufacturing industry
with the thing where she made it the clock.
You know, she not she had that clock that you could make out of her records.
Oh, yeah.
And what she's she's also, you know, in her mind, trying to make up for the billions
she lost when that asshole sold all her rights out from under that scooter brawn character.
Making it.
I mean, they're charging 25 grand for premium tickets, whatever the hell it is.
You know, she's doing just fine.
She's doing just fine.
Anyway, she could be a doll for him.
Yeah.
I mean, as far as billionaires go, I don't have many issues with her.
And I think she's extremely talented.
She's like a Bill Gates where I'm like, you could say bad things, but you could probably
also say good things and they haven't done anything as far as I can tell.
That's completely heinous.
Yeah.
Which in this day and age is something.
Well, you know, last night I saw this anatomy of a fall at seven thirty with my buddy Brett.
And we left, we discussed it.
We went our separate ways and I was like, you know what?
I'm still amped up.
I'm not ready to go home.
I'd love to see another picture tonight.
And I go up to the box office and I'm like, oh wow.
Like I could, so I could see killers of the flower moon, but it was starting at ten thirty.
So that gets out at two thirty in the morning or something.
Now I had just seen anatomy of a fall, which was a two hour movie stretched to two forty.
So I'm like, well, I can't do that.
Let me see it.
I'm going to see the Taylor Swift movie.
That sounds like a fun cap to the night.
And if I get tired and want to go, it's not the end of the world.
If I miss the end of the concert, I look that up.
It's two forty five.
Yeah.
And then when you add in Nicole Kidman in the trailers, it's three.
Everything is over a three hour experience.
Stop it.
Well, at least with Taylor, it's the concert.
Yeah, the fans want to see the concert.
I don't know.
I get that.
At least the fact that there's the three movies I was talking about seeing were all over two
thirty is like, come on, guys.
Yeah, this killers in the flower moon.
I mean, it looks I mean, people are saying it's a masterpiece.
I love these reviews that are like Scorsese's most riveting film in years.
It's like his last movie was nominated for like five Oscars.
Yeah.
What I saw something, maybe the only was like, don't call it a comeback Scorsese.
I'm like a comeback.
Where did he go?
What are you talking about?
What did he do before Irishman?
Before I mean.
Well, I don't know what was the one right before.
Look, he hasn't been enough.
Whatever he did before Irishman was huge.
There was Hugo, you know, which wasn't great, but that was a while back.
Let me look.
I tend to like everything the man makes, whether it's his best or not.
I really do.
He did.
See, this is man.
I hate IMDb.
What does it bring up?
It shows you a huge list of what he's done as a producer.
Yeah, it puts producer first.
I don't know why.
Why are you doing this?
Although also, when are they releasing an afternoon with SCTV?
Scorsese directed Conan O 'Brien interviewing the cast of SCTV like five years ago and it
was never released.
Where is it?
I don't give a shit.
I do.
Joe, and that therefore you should give a shit.
Those interviews always suck.
It's always way more dry than you want it to be and they're telling inside stories
and you're like, who cares?
And then by the way, Conan's going to be cat crawling all over the stage
because God forbid anybody gets any attention.
All right.
Now, now you're beyond the pill.
We don't, we do not need to be going after SCTV and Conan.
I'm not going after SCTV.
I am going after Conan's interview style.
It's just, you know,
Well, interview style is the same as Jimmy Fallon.
It's a lot of look at me.
The difference is Conan is doing it because he is always funnier
and more entertaining than the guest.
I'm not there for you, Conan.
I'm there for the guest.
But here's the thing.
Fair enough.
Fallon does the opposite.
Fallon just sits there and all of the guests, like, you know, it'll be,
it'll be like Angela Lansbury describing the final weeks of shooting murder.
She wrote, and he's like, he's like, oh my God, that's so amazing.
That's great.
Oh my God, the best show I've ever seen.
Honestly, it's the best show I've ever seen.
So here's, here's Scorsese from, so the part it was 2006.
Then we got from 2010 on not counting shorts and shit like that
pilots.
He did shutter Island, which I fucking love.
Pass from it for me on that one.
I love that movie.
He did Hugo, which I liked in 3d, but I've not wanted to watch again.
He did the Wolf of Wall Street, which I think is one of his best.
That was before that was right before Irishman, right?
It was Wolf of Wall Street.
2013 was Wolf of Wall Street.
Again, nominated for Oscar.
It's hitting grand slam.
It's like, what is he talking about?
Well, silence, which also was very critically acclaimed, but a very
difficult movie to watch.
I know it was personal for him, but it bored the fuck out of me.
I guess they're referring to silence, but then came the Irishman
and then came flower moment.
It's so sad and also interesting and sweet to hear him saying like,
I don't have much time left.
You know, like I'm just trying to make the best pot.
Like I maybe got one more movie left and you're like, God, that's sad.
And it must be sad knowing that whatever your next project is,
you could just die in the middle of.
And that's that.
I would like to see him at this age do like what, like a Woody Allen
style thing where it's like, Marty, don't be afraid to go small.
It doesn't all have to be a hundred million dollar budget, you know,
four hour epic, whatever, like go make a little indie drama over in
Paris or something with a cast of five people, like just, just make some small
stuff, like enjoy yourself, you know, I would love him returning to that
indie period where he was essentially not bankable and he made after hours,
which is awesome.
And he made king of comedy, which is awesome.
And it is what you say about Woody Allen is true because Woody Allen
can't do this anymore, but Martin Scorsese can at any time get any
actor in the world that he wants to do anything he wants them to do.
So why not, you know, get the say I'm looking for the best three character
indie script and cast it with the best people on earth also.
And by the way, I was saying this about De Niro back in the 90s and then the 2000s.
Obviously we love the two of you together.
I don't need another Scorsese DiCaprio picture.
I don't need another Scorsese De Niro picture.
I want to know what other combinations produce and we're not going to find out.
I think he knows now he loves Leo.
They have a great working relationship and no one's going to pass on a Leo movie.
Although two years into the writing of this movie, DeCaprio said,
where's the heart of the story?
I don't know why we're following all the white guys and they completely
rewrote it and overhauled it and told it more from the point of view of the indigenous people.
Now, of course, the indigenous people are saying it wasn't enough.
And you know, they don't, who knows?
I haven't seen the movie, but yeah, just avoid that.
Just avoid stepping into all this controversy and make something little.
I agree.
I would like, I wish these guys would go out.
I say the opposite.
I wish they would go out on the train they rode in on.
I'd like to see De Niro and Scorsese ride off into the sunset together with smaller
intimate pictures about a different age group than the ones they tackled in the 70s.
I've said it for many Irishmen.
That was the Irish.
Well, that was a huge movie though, is what I'm saying.
I'm saying like, don't, you know, go shoot a small movie with De Niro and Ben Pesci.
I mean, where they play two old brothers aging in the Italian countryside or something.
I don't know.
You know, I mean, how great would it be to do a Banshees of Inna Sheeran type thing
in Italy or something?
I don't get why Keaton is still a staunch supporter of Woody Allen.
Like, I don't get why.
Like Woody, go do a movie with Diane.
Like do a small little movie with Tony Roberts and Diane Keaton as older characters.
That would be interesting though.
This thing he's doing in Paris is getting like rave fucking review.
People are saying it's his best movie ever.
Well, whenever he goes away from comedy, it gets good reviews because he's like 90 -year -old
people don't have their finger on the pulse of comedy anymore.
Yes, that's true.
The Killers of the Flower Moon, and I don't know if you saw this, Joe.
I'm sure this, you did not care for this, but Scorsese said his biggest influence
on Flower Moon and its pacing is Mr. Ari Aster.
Oh, come on, Scorsese.
He goes, look, I looked at some of the truly great horror movies of the last couple years,
and he said, Midsommar, Hereditary, and Bo Is Afraid, the three movies made by Ari Aster.
Bo Is Afraid is not really a horror movie, in spots, certainly.
But is this a horror movie?
I wouldn't consider that, Scorsese did.
It's a horror movie for people with anxiety.
It's definitely showing you its anxiety taken to a horrific extreme.
The Flower Moon, I'm saying.
Why is he saying he was looking for horror movies?
I think, weirdly, he's referring to the pacing,
which I guess means he's just slowing things way down.
So we'll see.
Maybe he means Goodfellas is a movie on 100 shots of espresso and cocaine,
and he just realized that you can still make a successful movie and slow down the pace.
How I took it, but he clearly admires the guy a great deal.
If I was a free Aster and Scorsese was talking about how his biggest influences
were the three movies I've made, I would probably retire and just be like, I'm done.
I'm good.
Anyway, I'm excited to see it.
I have read the first page of Killers of the Flower Moon 900 times.
I think I started trying to read it during the deep pandemic,
and I have never made it past the first page.
Nothing to do with the writing.
I just have no attention span.
So there we are.
Let's go down to that movie corner.
Speaking of comedy, here we are, folks.
It's out.
The new Frasier.
Oh, yeah.
Hit us with it, Joe.
I haven't seen it.
I've watched the first three episodes.
That's all that's available.
The reviews, I think, that are most spot on
are the ones saying Kelsey Grammar is great.
The supporting cast needs some work.
I don't disagree with that.
I don't agree with the reviews that are criticizing it because it's not Frasier.
It doesn't have the farcical nature of the other show,
and it doesn't have the supporting cast.
Well, Frasier also was...
This is essentially a spinoff of a spinoff,
and that's clearly what they're doing.
Just like Frasier was a spinoff of Cheers,
where there were ties to that original story,
and eventually those characters showed up in some capacity,
but it was limited.
It's clearly what they're doing with this.
It's the character in a new setting with a new tone,
and that other cast that we all love is going to sort of drift in here or there
and get mentioned and whatever, but it's a new show.
Kelsey Grammar is amazing in it.
It does feel like Frasier,
but it is true that the supporting cast is where things are lacking.
I went back and rewatched the first season of the original show,
and in that original season, there are underdeveloped characters.
Particularly Daphne and Roz and John Mahoney's character are written very like...
They're very surface -level characters,
and they're given jokes that are just jokes for the sake of jokes
versus things that are really coming out of the characters themselves.
You're seeing a lot of that in this version
with particularly the son character and the nephew character.
I think that the best and most well -developed character
is the guy playing his best friend,
and I think that these characters could become more developed.
I think they're a little miscast.
Scratching my head as to why they cast somebody
to play the son of Niles and Daphne
that's clearly supposed to have that pratfall physicality that David Hyde Pierce has,
who has it but doesn't have it as effortlessly as David Hyde Pierce does.
I just don't get decisions like that.
You know, it's like, get somebody in there where it's undeniably good.
And the reason for that is because the industry now has been destroyed by too many cooks,
and God knows what agency had their fingers in this,
who from the studio has their fingers in it, the nepotism, whatever the fuck it is,
everybody's got a finger in something now,
and the days of just, you got the role because you deserve it most are gone.
So I'm not saying the kid doesn't deserve the role.
I'm just saying I'm confused as to,
he just doesn't have the undeniability that David Hyde Pierce has.
The kid playing the son is fine.
He's serviceable.
I don't think they're giving him a lot to do yet,
but another thing I'm sort of scratching my head over,
which is just such a simple little choice,
is like, he's modeled after John Mahoney's character,
and that's where the conflict comes in with him and Frasier.
It's like, give the guy Mahoneyisms.
Like Mahoney's, it wasn't a catchphrase, but Mahoney would always go,
ah, geez, that was always the thing he said when Frasier would be to Frasier.
It's like, have the kid say that.
Have the kid say that phrase in his own way,
and it just starts to create this connective tissue
that should be there.
I don't think it's impossible that that will come into the fray.
Again, I will cite the Frasier.
Yeah, and I will also say Picard, where I talked about that before,
where, you know, Picard season one and two were like,
people were like, what is this?
It's not, and then in season three, they were like, holy shit,
this is like some of the best Star Trek ever.
I think the show has the potential to get there,
and it does have some laugh out loud moments.
I will say this.
It's better than any other multicam currently on television.
It's better than Call Me Cat or any of those shows.
Low bar.
It is a low bar, but unfortunately, that's the bar these days.
So, you know, you can't help but realize
whatever multicam you put on TV is going to be a byproduct of that.
It just is.
It's not must -see TV anymore.
It's just not.
So, you're not going to have the pool of competition
creating the stuff that you used to,
but I think that this show could rise to the occasion.
I am enjoying it.
You know, so we'll see where it goes, but more than anything,
it's just great seeing Kelsey Grammer back again.
It's really lovely.
And he slipped right back into it.
He's great.
There's no part where I'm like, ah, he's trying to do it,
but it's not hitting.
Like, he really falls.
This is his Indiana Jones.
Like, this is his character.
Yeah.
I mean, he's been playing this character for literally 40 years,
so he should have it down.
Or 20, you know, but yeah.
No, no, no.
Frasier was on Cheers, Joe.
Yeah, yeah.
It was 20 years at the end of the Frasier run,
and so this is now 21.
Oh, yeah, I see.
He took some time off.
I see what you're saying.
Yeah, yeah.
But he's better at this than any...
Like I said, this is his Indiana Jones.
Like, he knows how to play this guy.
Yeah, it's amazing how, I mean, I'm a huge Sideshow Bob fan as well.
He's just a guy who has impeccable timing.
He really is.
And he seems like a blowhard.
It's very rare for a blowhard to have amazing comedic timing,
but he's got it.
They're saying...
Now, I know that it's the behind the scenes for the show
and it's promo for the show,
so they're obviously not going to say anything negative about him,
but the cast gushes about him in a way where I'm like,
this is beyond, like, good P...
Like, he must be just lovely to fucking deal with.
Like, they're like...
I knew some people who had worked on the Alec Baldwin,
Kelsey Grammer Multicam pilot that didn't go to series,
like, two, three years ago.
So imagine what that would have been.
But what I heard from everyone was that Kelsey was lovely
and Baldwin was a nut.
And that every day, Kelsey Grammer was sitting on that set
waiting for Alec Baldwin to come to set for like an hour.
And everybody was like, these men are of equal status.
What is going on here?
Well, I'll tell you something.
In Hollywood, for a Republican to get...
For people to go, he's wonderful, you gotta be truly wonderful.
I also heard on this show, and I want to specify,
because it could be looked up,
that I did not hear this from the wardrobe person
or the prop person.
I heard this from somebody else.
But that, you know, when your character is married,
let's say the prop person will come over
and let you pick out a wedding ring out of a few rings
or whatever, you know, that's costuming and props.
Baldwin is like, I feel like my character would have a watch.
Aren't I extremely wealthy?
Why don't I have a watch?
They go and wardrobe brings him out three options,
you know, like three Rolexes or whatever.
And he knocks them out of her hands and onto the floor.
He goes, on a movie set, they'd bring me a hundred watches.
What an asshole.
Are you to choose from?
Did you ever think we'd see the day discussing Baldwin's
where we'd be longing for Stephen to come back?
Look, I still love Alec Baldwin, I can't deny it.
But did you ever think that Alec would be arguably
the most unlikable of all the Baldwins?
No, absolutely not.
That man has been circling a heart attack for like 40 years.
I'm always glad when I see him and he's not like sweating,
but he just keeps having those kids, you know, he's got,
we're going to have more Baldwins to contend with soon.
I saw a movie that I had not seen since I was a kid.
It's, it's just a strange little movie, Mad Dog and Glory,
directed by John McNaughton, who did Wild Things.
He's had a pretty fun little B movie career and written by the great Richard Price,
who did his work with Spike Lee many times as a great author as well.
I got to tell you, I don't think this movie is very good.
It is De Niro and Bill Murray.
It was a big deal at the time that they were switching parts.
De Niro was playing a very shy, mild -mannered New York City cop
and Bill Murray is playing an aggressive, hot -tempered mobster.
Have you seen this movie, Joe?
No, I remember seeing the trailer as a kid and I was so confused by it.
Yeah.
I just didn't understand what the hell was going on.
I just never had an interest in it.
I would always mix it up with like Bonfire of the Vanities
and The Grifter.
There were some movies at that time where comedy actors were suddenly doing these sort of drama
things. I didn't know what the fuck was going on.
Yeah, this would fall into line with those movies.
Mad Dog and Glory does not really decide on a tone.
It's kind of a romantic comedy, but it's fucked up
because the movie is basically De Niro is a cop.
He rescues Bill Murray from a convenience store robbery.
Bill Murray, to repay him, gives him Uma Thurman.
Basically like a Honeymoon in Vegas type scenario, like here, take this woman for a week
as payback, but lo and behold, De Niro falls in love with her,
even though she's less than half his age and they have no chemistry.
Um, it's weird.
It's a weird movie produced by Scorsese.
It never hits a laugh out loud moment because Murray is so obviously trying to play it straight
that there's no comedy getting out.
De Niro is playing it shy and quiet, which reads as boring.
He's just not making many choices here.
So the novelty wears off immediately.
You're just watching two guys who are not really shining in these roles,
and it just feels the whole time like they're in the wrong parts.
Apparently they massively reshot the ending because it's a street fight.
And originally Bill Murray beat the shit out of De Niro
and the entire, uh, test audience was like, no, De Niro would beat the shit out of Bill Murray,
even though De Niro is a foot and a half shorter than him.
So like you can just tell the movie had problems from the jump just because
you just don't buy it.
And that's the problem with it.
You know, um, De Niro is this nerd who needs a woman.
You need, you know, he needs to be set up with a woman.
Just, you don't buy that.
You don't buy Murray.
You don't buy any of it.
And it's not as good as it should have been.
I can't recommend Mad Dog.
Uh, all right.
I'm going to stick on the television theme.
I mentioned on taste buds.
We talked about, did I tell you the kid from The Sopranos was on the show?
I saw that.
But so did you tell him you've watched three episodes of the show?
I didn't bring that up, but, uh, he's never seen the show either.
Really?
Yeah.
I guess it would have been too young at the time.
Yeah, he was very, very cool.
He was a great guy, but we talked about Nickelodeon.
We started talking about Alanis Morissette and Dave Coulier.
And one thing led to another.
And I brought up the show.
You can't do that on television.
Yeah.
That I grew up watching and I loved it so much.
And it was so crass and off color and great.
And it was back when kid stuff was gross.
And I said, I, you know, I've searched high and low.
I can't find it.
And people started messaging me saying, hey, actually the first season's on Paramount Plus.
And I looked and it was, and my God, does it still deliver
with every bit of bad taste?
You know, sketch after, it's, it's basically plays like Rowan and Martin's laugh.
And it's very fast sketches all based around how bad kids have it in these situations.
And it's like, it's like a kid that's about to be executed by a firing squad
with like a Nazi style general, a kid that's trapped in a dungeon
being tortured by a different Nazi style guy, whatever.
Kids eating snot and puke at the burger place because barf,
barf puts gross stuff in the burgers.
Kids being neglected by their alcoholic parents.
It's wild.
It is fucking wild.
And I love that it was on TV.
I love that it sort of cemented Nickelodeon.
I watched a documentary about it as well called, you can't do that on film
where they talked about how like it went to this fledgling little network called Nickelodeon.
And it exploded.
It became this phenomenon in the United States.
Yeah.
Produced in Canada.
And it was just great, man.
It's just a great show.
It's fun.
And it's back when kid humor was wild and dangerous and a little bit wrong.
And also something that adults could also enjoy.
So if you haven't seen it, man, do I recommend checking out.
You can't do that on television.
It's also the thing where the green slime was invented.
That's the show where the Nickelodeon, the famous iconic Nickelodeon slime.
That was the show that did it.
I mean, it's still like a PG show, isn't it?
Yeah, it's not R rated.
Yeah.
At least by the standards of the 80s.
But, you know, like the kid never gets killed at the firing squad.
He always tricks the executioner into getting shot.
Yeah.
The kid in the dungeon, you know, the gag is he's always just trying to get out of
the dungeon and he can't get out or whatever, you know?
The people eat the barf burgers and it's gross, but nobody dies or anything, you know?
Like the alcoholic parents are neglectful and out of touch or aloof,
but they're not abusive to the, you know?
And one of the things that I guess it was one of the producers or writers said was
or creators, he was like, he was like, our whole goal with this show was to make
kids at home feel better because they were watching kids that had it worse than them.
And being a kid sucks, but we wanted to give kids other kids that were in such terrible
situations, they'd feel great about their lives.
That's awesome.
Yeah.
Fucking great.
So you can't do that on television.
Very overdue for a box set.
That really needs a big box set release, but I'm surprised Shout Factory hasn't done it.
Well, now there's no money in it.
If it was going to happen, it would have happened probably.
I saw anything else, speaking of Woody Allen.
Love it.
I know a favorite of Joe's and an all -time favorite film of Quentin Tarantino.
I felt about it how I felt when I saw it.
I remember being so pumped to see this because I had just moved to New York and it was the
first Woody Allen movie to come out as I was a cool New Yorker.
I was like, oh, I guess I'll go see the new Woody Allen today.
I said to my non -existent friends, but it's a good, cute, romantic comedy.
I, Ricci is being like rediscovered now with his yellow jackets and I do think she steals
the show in yellow jackets.
I only saw the first season and I heard it fell to shit, but she's been great forever.
I really loved her.
Well, her kid acting was amazing.
I mean, her Wednesday is the template for Wednesday Adams, but that black snake moan,
her performance really blew me away.
Her and Sam Jackson in that movie have really stayed with me.
I just think she's great.
She's very funny in this.
It's this weird Woody Allen thing where her character is a massive overeater.
She's always talking about how much she's eaten and she looks like every other actress,
like she weighs 90 pounds.
So that's kind of an odd thing, but it's bigs and Ricci and they're both perfectly charming.
There's almost no plot to the film,
but I liked it.
It's pleasant.
It's fun.
It's not primo Woody, but I dig the movie and I do feel that when he
uses younger actors as his mouthpieces, it's always better.
It's best case scenario for an older version of him because he's got the younger version to do
the romantic shit and then he gets to just be there and be the Woody Allen part that you need
to see, like the jokey, bigs doesn't have a ton of funny stuff in it.
He's like kind of a straight man.
Woody as his mentor, you know, it's a good relationship.
It's a believable relationship that it's this weird thing in terms of comedians and comedy
writers where your friend group scans like 50 years just because so many different ages are
in the game that you're in.
So it works.
It works a lot better than when it's Woody Allen walking around with Selena Gomez through
the streets of Paris or you don't buy that.
But yeah, I really liked anything else while still being baffled as to why Tarantino would
consider it one of his favorite films, but I do like the movie a lot.
I think it's one of Woody Allen's best and yeah, some of the funniest stuff, you know,
the gag alone of his paranoid about how paranoid he is about everybody else being anti -Semitic.
Yes.
When they're walking out of that restaurant and he's like, did you hear what he said?
He said, Jews start all wars.
And he's like, he said it to his friend, but it was meant for our benefit.
Like those sequences are really, really funny.
But anyway, I agree.
And DeVito in there too.
DeVito's fantastic as the charlatan manager.
Everybody's first manager in the business.
That is Danny DeVito in that movie.
Harvey Wexler, clearly a little Harvey Weinstein influence.
But yeah, I was a little thrown by how similar that character was to Broadway Danny Rose.
But I love DeVito in that part.
Jimmy Fallon in the mix, speaking of.
Remember when he acted.
Anyway, I liked it.
Joe?
Last one is, and I've only watched two episodes, but god damn it.
Creep show is back, folks.
Season four.
And speaking of jumping ship, I will never, I vowed it and I went back,
I think last time against my will, but I'll never watch another creep show TV.
First episode I'll review.
Starts.
I'm like, okay, this is intriguing enough.
First thing they did right.
Pat, you'll be happy to hear is they cut all the creep.
Creep segments.
Okay.
I was like, okay, guys, you're learning like you don't need those.
They're not really working, right?
At least in the way you're doing them.
So the first, that was the first thing I noticed.
And then the episode starts, the story starts.
I had thought it was a sci fi story.
I had even texted Walsh about it, but I was accidentally watching an old episode
that was so bad I had blocked it out as if I had been molested
by the episode.
Speaking of Woody Allen.
So the first episode is called, I think it's called 20 minutes with
Michelle or something like that.
It's about a young or about a woman who comes home and then a younger woman comes to her
door in a panic and said, there's a monster out here.
You have to let me in.
And she's clearly traumatized and the woman lets her in.
And I'm like, okay, this is kind of a cool concept.
When you first see the monster, it looks really cool,
which is another step in the right direction for creep show.
And I'm like, holy shit, I think they fixed.
I think they listened and they learned and they're fixing the problems.
And then there's a plot twist where the monster starts having
regular old candid conversations with the woman he's trying to kill.
And it is fucking absurd.
It is stupid.
It's supposed to be funny and it's not.
It's terrible.
It's fucking terrible.
This was followed up by a story about a war photographer who has regrets about
something that transpired when he was in the war.
Oh, wow.
We've never seen that plot a million fucking times in every horror anthology show.
So this was the first episode.
I was very disappointed.
I was very aggravated.
The highs and the corrections were not enough to make up for the bullshit.
The second episode isn't bad.
You just don't give a shit at all.
Or the second story, rather.
Now, I started another episode where the first story is called The Hat.
And it's about a writer with writer's block who gets a hat
that his favorite writer used to wear.
And there are dire consequences.
The Hat lets him write and lets him write better than he ever has.
But again, this is a premise that's been reworked through
horror anthologies many times in different ways.
That episode was actually kind of entertaining.
Or that story was.
And I'm going to watch the rest of the season slowly but surely to see if
there's anything worthwhile in it.
But I just don't get.
There are things they are missing in the scripts,
and the directors are missing as directors.
And there are obvious things that these guys should be catching.
And it's just very obvious this is a crew of people
who have not directed a lot of stuff,
who have not written, I guess, written a lot of stuff.
I don't know what the fuck is going on.
Well, to me, the weirdest aspect of this program is that
the showrunner is Nicotero, a makeup artist.
I'm so confused by that.
And he's got no business running a show,
and he's got no business directing episodes.
He just doesn't.
I'm sorry.
The guy's a great makeup guy.
But look, Tom Savini, the god of all makeup artists next to Rick Baker,
has directed a couple things.
He's not, okay, fine.
He's not running a fucking TV show.
So I just don't get it.
There's things in this where you're like,
just for example, the episode The Hat that I'm talking about.
The guy's got writer's block.
He's obsessed with this writer named Bachman,
which is a very lazy Stephen King knob, obviously.
But he's obsessed with this writer to the point where his fiance or girlfriend,
whatever, is like, please stop talking about this guy.
You're not him.
You're a different, you're your own person, whatever.
There's a scene where he's sitting in his agent's office,
and his agent is like, oh, you got writer's block, honey.
Let me show you something.
And she literally takes him to the adjacent wall in the office
where there is a display, museum -like display of all these objects, items.
And she's like, this is Richard Bachman's hat.
He used to wear this when he wrote a book.
It brought him good luck.
And you're like, guys, just from a writing standpoint,
your agent would have pointed this out to you already.
You would have asked the question, whose stuff is all this over here?
It's like, just little shit like that.
You're like, it's just amateurish, guys.
I'm sorry.
These might seem like frivolous details.
They're not.
This is where the devil is, in these fucking details.
And this is what makes somebody step back and say,
this is a real professional work that's being done,
or this feels like a student film right now.
And Creepshow feels like a goddamn student film,
or a fan film, or whatever you want to call it.
I just don't get it.
Do you keep going back to it because of your love of the Creepshow movies?
No, I'm a sucker for anthology horror.
I actually don't know why I'm going back to it.
In fact, I was going to tweet the other night when I was watching it.
I was going to say, why are we even calling this Creepshow anymore?
The Creep segments, although they didn't work, are gone.
Like, it's not Creepshow.
It doesn't feel like Creepshow.
None of the original people are connected to it anymore.
And I realize that's how a lot of this stuff goes.
But I'm looking up Nick Katara right now.
He's directed, okay, well, I'm wrong.
He directed 37 episodes of The Walking Dead.
Oh, wow.
Okay.
So I guess he has directed.
I mean, but to me, you know, this thing's got a 7 .0 out of 10 on IMDB.
I don't understand.
What the fuck is everybody watching?
Anyway, I think people support Shudder as an underdog.
And I relate to that.
I often, no matter what I cancel, I always leave Shudder
because they do feel to me like an old friend.
But it's also cheap.
It's like five bucks a month.
So I can't, you know, I can't speak.
I can't lie about some of their shit though.
You know, I love the Joe Bob.
I love how much they care.
I love the movies that they have in there most of the time.
But their originals on the TV side and on the film side are always pretty damn rough.
Sometimes when they acquire something, it works out if they buy something.
But anything they do in -house tends to be bad.
I hate to say it.
I almost feel like they'd do better if they just stopped their original programming
because it's not working for me, but maybe other people like it.
Well, shit, I might as well go ahead and do Creepshow.
I did the 4K.
I have heard many people discuss how amazing it is.
And I was very excited to see it because as I've said, colors pop so much on 4K.
And since this is kind of doing that Dick Tracy style thing of bringing comic book to life,
it does look really beautiful.
The transfer is great.
Creepshow is just a movie that I'm never going to love as much as Joe here.
Or some people do.
I like anthology horror as well.
But I do think this is kind of the primo example.
I, you know, I'd give it a B plus as a movie.
I like it a lot.
But the stories as they are, and I kind of feel this way about
the whole Tales from the Crypt and EC Comics kind of genre.
And they're not scary enough and they're not funny enough.
So I'm left in this little thing of like, that was fun.
And I like that the stories are short, but the movie itself is two hours and it drags a bit.
I think one of the stories could have popped out, but I love it.
I love the gross outness.
I love the effects, the practical effects.
I love the cockroaches blasting out at the end.
It's a lot of fun.
It's, it's nonstop fun.
I just wish individually on their own, the stories hit a little harder.
I always find myself struggling to remember what the stories are.
And they don't stick with you in the way a great Twilight Zone does to me.
But in terms of bringing this kind of style of horror comic to life,
it does a beautiful job of that.
I love the cast and it's really fun.
It's a great Halloween movie for sure.
All right.
We are reviewing.
Oh God, the task at hand is burdensome.
Insidious, The Red Door.
I saw this a month ago.
And what I, what I remember about it is that I had sex with my date afterwards.
I have zero recollection of this film.
I read the Wikipedia page this morning and it seemed.
You know, it, it triggered a memory or two, but I was not fucked up when I watched it.
I think if we had done it two days after, I would still struggle to remember
what is even going on in this movie.
But I leave it to you, Joe, if you want to summarize.
It starts in the right place.
Yeah.
It picks up with the funeral of Barbara Hershey's character.
Um, by the by to start off insidious five and give us no real bearings as to where we are,
just assuming that we remember the insidious saga.
I mean, I, I had no clue what was happening.
Well, I don't think that that's that crazy.
It's, it's a pretty famous and successful franchise at this point.
I remembered that I remember.
All right.
You know, I was like, Oh, I guess his mother died.
Um, and she was a pretty pivotal character in the first two.
So like, I was like, okay, Barbara Hershey's character is dead.
There's a strain between Patrick Wilson's character and the eldest son,
who's the kid that was in the coma in the first movie.
Uh, and then they show you the flashback that they were hypnotized to erase all the
memories of the events of the, the haunting or whatever it was called in the first two films.
I was like, okay, that's pretty cool.
This is a good setup and Patrick Wilson gets into his car.
He's texting with the son.
It's awkward.
They can't, they, they don't have a good dynamic.
And as he's texting, he leans down at one point and behind him and very
blurry in the bat through the back window of the car is you see an ominous figure
approaching and you realize, okay, this thing is going to start terrorizing them again.
They have no recollection that any of it ever happened to begin with.
This is going to be, I was like, I was, I was in, I was like, okay, here we go.
Uh, and then we jumped to Patrick Wilson taking his son to college, uh, for the first time.
And from here on out, the movie just gets inherently shittier and shittier and shittier
and shittier.
It's, it's the dialogue is terrible.
My first, we meet Patrick Wilson, son's roommate.
I mean, that part was absurd.
It was just absurd.
A young 18 year old male is sharing a dorm room at a major college in 2023 with a woman.
And, oh, they must've mixed up my name.
And then she, by the way, she goes to the, she goes to the bursar's office and said,
and to, to, to get it fixed.
And she comes back and she goes, I guess I'm stuck with you tonight.
We can't, they can't fix it.
You're like a university would jump through flaming hoops to assure that you guys were
dying in the same room.
Sexual happened between the two of you.
They would be liable and there's no, there's not a community college in America
that would allow this to go on.
And by the way, Pat, if I could just not to step on you, but if I can interject again,
write a decent script and put a line in where she just goes,
it's fine.
I told them, I identify as a guy.
Put anything in to make it make sense.
Anything you have to explain what's going on.
Yes.
So then I'm sitting there watching it with my date and I'm like, are we going to have to,
I go, I'm going, I just flashed forward to this roommate character making wise cracks
to a demon in the back half of the film.
And she was like, oh, that's definitely going to be happening.
And sure enough, sure enough, you know, it's like
those two have zero chemistry, zero.
Weirdly, Patrick Wilson and Rose Byrne don't have chemistry
and they've been playing this couple for a decade.
Byrne's there because Byrne's clearly there because she's like,
guys, I'll do it if you give me this much.
I don't want to do this.
I'll do it as a favor to Patrick.
She's never been worse.
I like her.
She's awful.
Patrick Wilson is not a good actor.
I've always kind of thought he isn't and I'll tell you what,
he ain't a great director either because this movie is terribly directed
and he's not a great singer because he sings the closing song.
Also, you are too rich to have those hair plugs.
You're too rich.
They look too bad.
So Patrick is not a good actor.
The kid that plays the son is not a good actor.
My friend pointed out to me after she saw it, she was like,
go fuck yourself with the brooding artist thing because she's an artist.
And she's like, I'm so fucking sick of this in horror movies.
Like the troubled art, like fuck off the angsty.
That sucks.
There's really no sense to why this kid starts seeing spirits and dead people
sixth sense style.
The purpose of him seeing them in the movie is they're trying to warn him.
And Patrick Wilson is now seeing spirits of his dead father
because his dead father is trying to warn him of what of this demon
that's going to come back and try to hurt them.
None of it really makes any sense.
I'm sure if I went back and combed through the first two movies,
I'd figure out some sort of connective tissue or reasoning behind all of it.
I'm not doing that.
Um, it's, it, it all becomes far too convoluted.
This isn't nightmare on Elm Street.
It's not a simple device.
It's not just a, you go to sleep.
You're the kid of a person who killed me.
So I'm Freddie.
I'm going to appear in your dreams.
And that's how this works.
That's a pretty one, two, three.
All right, let's go.
This is not that this is you're dealing with another realm called the further,
which I always thought was a stupid fucking name.
But anyway, you're dealing with another realm called the further.
You're dealing with different types of spirits from that realm.
You're dealing with different reasons as to why these two can see those spirits.
You used to have Lynn Shea in there to explain everything to you.
Now she's gone because her character is dead, I guess, or whatever.
Oh, but she pops up.
She pops up as, as a ghost Barbie style.
I never thought I'd be comparing Insidious Five to Barbie.
Yeah, but yeah, and it's, it's really just becomes about the father and son reconnecting
through saving one another by going into the further to stave off this demon,
which by the way, they don't even really bring that demon.
Just bring back the guy that looks like Darth Maul from the first two movies and just
have him wreak havoc and we're going to have a good time.
They don't even do that.
Most of the ghosts in this thing are quote, good ghosts.
Yeah.
Like fuck off.
Who cares about any of this?
They also look so bad and Patrick Wilson holds the shots of each ghost eight seconds too long.
Like he holds them until you like see how bad the makeup is and then goes on to the next shot.
There are zero scares in the movie.
The story does not work and Joe, I hate, I hate to do this, but let me read you
the four credits of Scott teams, the screenwriter of this film.
Okay.
Halloween kills the third movie in the franchise where they introduced the other Michael Myers
fire starter with Zac Efron.
No, no, no.
Halloween.
Hold on.
Halloween kills is the second one.
Oh, the second one.
Okay.
Sorry.
It's okay.
Fire starter with Zac Efron, which we reviewed on this show and it's probably the worst of
all these that we've discussed and city is the red door and then he graduated to
the exorcist believer.
Well, what a surprise that a guy out of the Blumhouse camp sucks at fucking horror.
What a fucking surprise.
God, I love how right I am about Blumhouse.
I love it.
I'm reveling in it.
The, by the way, Blumhouse Walsh stepped away from insidious five.
Did they?
Didn't put their name on it.
No, this isn't screen gems and Sony pictures picked it up.
Now here's the, here's the real bad news.
16 million dollar budget made a hundred eighty eight million dollars.
Oh no.
So Wilson's out there thinking he killed it.
Oh, Wilson.
So then he's going to direct again because all they care about is that BO.
You'd better off.
You're better off having the volleyball.
Wilson direct the next.
I mean, this thing.
Yeah, it's damn it.
It sucked.
It felt like a made for TV sequel.
Yeah, 20 years later.
It was a lot of these later sequels and, and, and I'm about to go back through the saws
because I've only seen the first two saws and then the jigsaw.
I'm about to go through and watch them all.
Not jigsaw, the spiral, which I liked, but I drop out and then at some point I'm always
like, ah, it's Halloween.
It'd be fun to watch like eight movies this weekend.
And the Friday the 13th marathon was a blast.
Sometimes it works out, but what we're getting now is like this movie would have been a direct
to VHS back in the day.
Your vast majority of people would never have seen it to just pretend and release it.
This is some sort of big theatrical outing or that it's up to par is ridiculous.
And by the way, I feel the exact same way about pet cemetery bloodlines, a prequel to
a remake of an adaptation of a book.
Arguably insidious is worse than bloodlines, but now the direct to DVD junk market I think
is becoming this streaming horror market.
Like the Hulu Hellraiser, Hulu Razor felt very direct to DVD.
It's just things under a different name now, you know?
Well, that Hellraiser made this makes that Hellraiser look like, you know, Citizen Kane
or something.
It's like, I hate to use your cliche response.
The bar just keeps going lower and lower.
It's true.
This was, this was, I would say this was a Halloween five.
Mm hmm.
I'm not counting the David Gordon Green Halloweens.
Yeah.
I would say I'm saying like just the feel of like sequels that went a little too far
eventually.
This feels like Halloween five, Halloween six territory.
Paul Rudd Halloween, like where you're like, guys, yeah, it's over.
Just let it just let this go.
Christ almighty, you know?
It's Easter.
Why are you still doing Halloween, you know?
We've moved on.
You think this Thanksgiving movie will be any good?
This Eli Roth?
Any good?
I don't know, but I, I like Eli Roth in horror mode.
I always have.
I think he's got a pretty decent track record and why not?
A slasher movie set on Thanksgiving coming out of Thanksgiving.
Like it's a simple idea.
We don't get this shit anymore.
So I'm, I'm at least happy to see it.
Yeah, I'm going to see it.
And it's one of the trailers from Grindhouse, you know?
So, uh, I'm going to see it.
You know, it looks kind of wild.
I mean, they, they really give away a lot in the trailer.
So, you know, well, they got that weirdo back from, uh, the guy who's on suits,
which I've never seen, but, um, and he was in the hostel one, two Rick Hoffman.
The first one.
Yeah, boy.
I mean, that guy is a very excellent and unsettling character actor.
And I always love seeing him.
I'm pumped.
You know, I, I, I'm pumped.
I like Eli Roth and I think Tarantino is producing it.
Isn't it?
Maybe not.
I, he, he, he must be.
Hold on.
Let's look it up.
Yeah.
That guy in a hostel is, is my favorite.
I fucked with her all the other night.
I don't remember what her pets look like.
He's such like a psycho.
He's so good.
Thanksgiving movie.
That's well, they're going to have a tough time when people are trying to Google this thing.
I always think that when I just don't think they think it through.
Patrick Dempsey is in this.
All right.
I'm listening.
Oh, Tim Dillon's in this.
You love Patrick Dempsey, Joe?
I like Patrick Dempsey.
Patrick McDreamy.
Patrick Dempsey is in one of my favorite eighties movies of all time.
Lover Boy.
Oh, I like Lover Boy.
I used to dream of being the Lover Boy taking pizzas to middle -aged women
piping them down.
What a dream.
And then you have sex with the woman after.
Dempsey and Tim Dillon is all my buddies got a little part as a war or a bailiff in Joker 2.
And he said that Tim Dillon is one of the, one of his co bailiffs.
I guess he's got a little acting career brewing.
Yeah.
I'm going to ask Tim about Thanksgiving.
See if we can get us some insider info.
All right, folks.
We'll be back in November with some more stuff.
Eventually that live show we're doing is coming out on the 28th.
We'll release the audio of that.
We'll probably do Killers of the Flower Moon, even though I'm dreading the runtime.
We'll do, I think we're going to do Where Evil Lurks, When Evil Lurks,
whatever the hell it's called.
But we'll be back with some stuff, folks.
Come see me live if you could, joderosa .com.
Of course, if you're in New York City, come to Joey Roses, joeyrosesnyc .com.
And we'll see you on the 28th.
And don't forget after the festivities over at Arlene's Grocery at 11 PM,
the party goes over to Joey Roses for the after party.
It's going to be a lot of fun.
Dress up, get busy, come have fun with us.
I will see you there as well.
Let's get the COVID -19 virus together.
We will see you next time, folks.
And we will see you in hell.