Summer is here, and Bed MDM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer.
Or check out our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz.
Only available at Bed MDM Casino.
Spin on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 fortunes, Mystery of the Lamp,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand!
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action!
Bet MGM in game sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 plus to Wager, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and West Virginia
only.
Games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as normal throwable site credit slash bonus best unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
Gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamber.
This episode is brought to you by KPMG.
Making an impact is how KPMG helps make the difference.
KPMG applies advanced tools and strategic thinking
to convert data into actionable knowledge
and deliver value by improving performance through transformation,
modernizing processes with technology,
harnessing the power of data,
navigating complex M &A transactions
and enhancing trust among stakeholders.
Go to kpmg .us slash advisory to learn more.
or KPMG, make the difference.
This is a headgun podcast.
Welcome to another fine fine edition of we'll see you in hell the podcast about horror sci -fi and
fantasy films we review we commentate we bitch
To my left
Is my dear friend and co -host mr. Patrick Walsh
Hello folks. Welcome to we'll see you in hell today. We'll be talking about the season two premiere of
of perhaps the hottest thing in horror sci -fi fantasy right now, Stranger Things, and now on with the show, and also on
That was a good one. You got up there. There's a little more than a feeling key change on that one. Yes!
Yes.
Close my eyes and she slipped away.
Right?
Dad, do you ever feel that I'm slipping through your fingers?
No, I feel like I've pretty much got you.
Joe, today I proposed that we hang out basically from 9 a .m. till 2 a .m.
I said, Joe, I got other things to do, but we're having a nice hang.
I did. I kept adding things to the hang. I said, let's, let's, well, here's where it all started
because we went to a wedding yesterday and we were supposed to, we originally were going to stay
over at the wedding and then come home this morning, today's Sunday. And I said, you know, why don't we
record the podcast during the week because, you know, Sunday, we're not going to really feel like
recording. We're going to be probably hungover and stuff from the wedding. And Pat said, now let's
record on Sunday, keep the party popping.
So we were originally supposed to have this full 48 hour
experience together.
But then we ended up not staying at the wedding,
going to our separate homes last night.
We got it today, I still wanted to have the party pop.
Sure, in some way.
So I said, let's record and then go,
maybe do a bar or something and I said,
you know, why don't we also get lunch beforehand
and go then I just had to do fair.
maybe you win me a stuffed animal. I had to eventually just admit to Pat that I was lonely.
Yeah, that's the kind of thing like 10 years ago when I, when I,
I cried me to girl that I liked at a bar or whatever. And then she'd go,
hey, we should hang out sometime. Maybe we kiss at make out at the end of the night or something,
give me your number. And then the next day I'd wake up and be like, hey, I'm up, nothing to do today.
I was thinking maybe we grab breakfast and then we could go over and see a movie and then I actually have a six flag season pass if
That interests you and then perhaps a second movie. I have concert tickets at eight. And then of course
I would never see the girl again, right called coming on too strong, but folks. I ask you
Who doesn't want someone to like talk to you make out a little bit on the next day?
You're like, let's hang out all day
It's got it's being branded as clingy or scary. I was just a lonely man who wanted some some friendship right
Well, the fact that you'd be proposing it to her as she walked home and you were following her.
Right. That's what would freak her out. Dick in hand. But I mean, in a relationship like this,
there is no scaring away. We're deep in. That's no, that's very true. So yeah, deep in some would say.
Yeah. This is a marriage of sorts. Yeah. A love affair, if you will, I will. And you can't, you know,
with your better half. Joe was driving me in my better half home last night, 10 pm, massive traffic
jam on the highway. I think we've hit it even even more so the normal hit a real low point of
love and respect for the Los Angeles area. Would you agree? Yeah, yeah, we, I don't think we said one
positive thing all day yesterday, driving around this town, these people that we live around,
the traffic, the heat, the goddamn weather, everything. It's just 90 degrees in sunny,
we're three days out from Halloween. Yeah, there's like, maybe we watch a scary movie tonight.
I'm like, who even gives a shit? Yeah. It's not Halloween. It's just goddamn, you know,
Fletcher weather. Yeah, exactly. This isn't this isn't Greg Remlin's weather. It's it's it's just there's no spirit anything. No. This is dead people. We live. Oh, God. I don't know that the world's much better. I think we're hitting just a real low point. I or my eyes are more open than they ever will. And it's always been this bad, but I don't think so. I can see clearly now.
Brands gone I've pinpointed it. It's not here. Here's what it is the world is
terrible yeah sure sure the United States one of the probably more terrible
places in the world he's sure getting worse all the time the entertainment
business the rottenest business in the world outside of politics yeah and it's
close. We live in Hollywood. We are the we're the tiniest of the Russian dolls. We are in the
eye of the storm right now. There is we are at the epicenter of evil. That's true. So that's why
it's so miserable. That's why I can't I can't go on. I'm going to have to move somewhere at some
point, but until I make it in this business, which could be never. You were trying to explain to me
where before we started recording, but why did you push Harvey Weinstein to do what he did?
You know, and to keep doing it. Quite frankly, I didn't like, I didn't like he was having a nice
run, and I was jealous, and I thought I got to take this guy down a peg somehow. So I said Harvey,
I got two words for you, potted, plant, and I ran with it and so did he quite frankly.
Yeah.
So that was it.
That was it.
I got to tell you, and I know he wouldn't mind because it's so funny it needs to be shared.
But Harvey Weinstein, our friend David Crumholz, yes, actor, you know him, if you don't know
the name, you know, you look him up and you know, he's in my television program.
and I text, we text each other, I text him the other night.
It was the exact same question.
Why did you encourage Harvey Weinstein
to do what he did, walk me through the steps?
Right. He wrote back immediately,
like as if he had this text ready to go.
And this is fake folks, obviously.
Met him in 90s, this was so funny to me,
I kept reading it and laughing and laughing.
Met him in 96 while shooting angst, the ice storm.
He was shy, but he took up plenty of space, both literally and figuratively.
He was a presence, booming bassy voice, the face of a lower east side horse manure collector,
hiding a brilliant so readily apparent to anyone with a soul.
He was sad, lost.
I spoke with him at length.
All I said was, fuck everything that moves, wasn't sure if he even heard me.
I regret having any part in hurting those women, but I've been hurt too.
I lost my friend, my pupil, my obvious successor.
Where do I turn now?
I can't stress enough that that text came back within about 30 seconds.
Wow, that's very funny.
And folks, I know there's nothing funny about Harvey Weinstein or what happened, but
as I always have, you got to laugh so that you may not cry.
Well, also too, we're not making fun of what he did, we're making fun of a guy making
up a ridiculous scenario, which he's going to be his successor, that's funny.
That's true.
Put anybody's name in there, it would have been funny.
What do you think's going to happen with the company, just fold it up, because Bob's hands
aren't clean.
I'll tell you that much right now.
There's Bob's hands, they're coming for Bob.
Nobody's hands are clean.
And I keep saying this, and I'll fucking say it again, and this will be a nice moment for
everybody that ever got mad at our trump bashing on this podcast yeah for
everybody that that crucifies at any right wings politician who took money from
the NRA at some point in their campaigning lives you know why don't you go
crucify miss sweet Hillary and Obama right now for taking money from a fucking
set at the very least sexual assaultist and at the worst potentially a rapist
It's like everybody, all the articles are out now.
Tom Hanks being one of the biggest voices.
Everybody has said the same thing.
They all knew, they all knew.
And you should be really disappointed in Hillary
because talk about a woman who twice now in her life
has benefited from the success and power
of a man close to her that has a costed women.
twice now she's done it and she's supposed to be the feminist icon. She's supposed to be the
wave of the future and all this stuff. She is twice now kept her goddamn mouth shut and turned
her head while men she needed to benefit from did disgusting and despicable things. So that's the
truth. There is no discussion. There is no argument and I just want you to see that we have a fair
and balanced podcast. You think she's the kind of the the Karmelos soprano here? I almost thought you
She said the crumholz, the crum, yeah, she's 100%, it's funny you say that because the
analogy in my head is always good fellows.
She's caring when the FBI is going, don't give me the baby to watch routine caring.
Your voice is on those tapes.
We heard you on those wiretaps.
It's that.
It's like, I'm so tired of it, man.
Everybody is so full of shit.
So let's just start calling everybody on their bullshit.
Let's stop picking and choosing who gets called on their bullshit. How about that?
Tarantino comes out, you know, a week later. I don't know. To me, it's odd that everyone needs
to release an official statement about everything that happens. It's psychotic.
Like, I didn't tweet for about three weeks. I know you're off Twitter, but I didn't do it.
And every time something new and horrible would happen, I would be like, if I don't say that I hate
women being sexually assaulted right now,
am I the problem?
Because people will say, if you remain silent,
it's as bad as sexually assaulting someone.
A, it isn't, but, and it isn't by about a billion percent.
But what am I supposed to do?
Tweet, tweet, hey, I also don't like sexual assault,
but they're mad about Tarantino
because they're best friends or good friends.
Then Tarantino says, I never do anything about it.
Then two days later he says, you know what I knew about it.
Yeah, like what's going on there? You don't have a publicist?
Clearly he put it out and then he was like, you know what fuck someone's gonna find out that I tag team to woman with Harvey Weinstein once
I look like it looks so much more guilty than if he hadn't said a word. I love Tarantino's films as much as the next guy
But let's not pretend for a minute like he's a he's a stable individual. No, I mean you
Then I saw Joe and this out of his fucking mind this churn my stomach to this this actress puts up and everyone starts retweeting this thing
like it's an amazing story about how Tarantino she's an actress who I don't know her name
and she hadn't been anything that I know I'm speaking nothing ill about her as a person
I don't know her I don't even know her name but she tweets this story they got a ton of traction
you know about five years ago I was walking down Beverly and Quentin Tarantino pulled up
alongside me in a car he asked me to get into the car this is a woman just walking down
He asked me to get into the car and discussed an upcoming role with me right there on the
side of the road.
I feel I need to say that he did nothing inappropriate to me.
He didn't make any sexual advances on me.
I'm like, what?
Why are you coming to his defense because he's not being accused of anything.
Right.
B, yeah, moving director pulling over the side of the road and asking you to end of your
car.
I'm thrilled and glad and relieved that nothing happened to you, but
They don't get into that car and be Tarantino's hands aren't clean there either. That's a creepy fucking thing to do
You can say hey
Because clearly it's about her looks. He didn't know who she was he could say hey, you're very beautiful
Would you like to go to a coffee shop and discuss the thing?
I don't want to make you uncomfortable. You know like you got to say get into my car on the side of the road
Maybe he did say that. I don't know. Maybe he did
but i'm not look i'm not just this thing to say like hey before you all jumped
down tarantino's throat he didn't rate me once and i was in his car for five
minutes and this is why i say it's not this is why this is why this is why i say
these public this this this culture of public statements is is out of control
and it's become psychotic yeah everybody is everybody is not doing it for the
right reasons obviously no that fucking uh thing where that girl or that woman
excuse me, tweeted about David Cross making like the racial joke, no, look, 10 years ago.
If he did that, yeah, okay, that sucks, like, be offended by it, like, nobody's saying
you shouldn't be, but the fact that she has to do it on Twitter, okay, because God forbid
anything is not a fucking public, you know, you know, public consumption trial these days.
Not only she does it on Twitter, then everybody starts attacking him on Twitter and she goes,
well, I don't support or condone anybody publicly attacking Mr. Cross right now for, it's
like, well, then why did you do this on Twitter?
Yeah.
By the way, who wanted to be attacked more was his wife, Amber Tamlin, who was a very, very
outspoken against all this, why is she supposed to be?
And it was like, hey, you're going to stick with your husband now that you've heard this.
She had a thousand at things until finally Amber Tamplin who I know nothing about Amber Tamplin
I'm just telling you a story of what I saw all happened online. She now has to get on Twitter and
say
Charlene ye I
Believe your story about what my husband said I believe you
Please stop holding women accountable for their partner's actions. I believe that my husband did this
I am staying with him
Here's why I'm staying with him. I do I believe this happened. It's a terrible thing that happened
I'm like what why why do all of you need to make statements here, right? What's happening?
Well then and even in David Crosse don't make racist jokes to people don't get me wrong
Right, but like what what's going on here? And then even in David Crosse's apology
Yeah, he's not not a good apology
Well, but because here's why it wasn't good because you will get crucified for anything you say that's out of script
Yes, the perfect script so he's his first thing is I can't believe I have to do is I don't remember doing that
I don't the sounds way out of character now look whether he did it or not I can't speak to right
I'm speaking to the intent of what that first apology was for me
Yeah, and the and the intent clearly was the way I've long heard the man as an asshole, you know
I don't know him at all he may well be I don't fucking know the guy
But my point is is the clearly the point of his first apology was I don't think I did this I don't remember doing this
And even when he's trying to say that, he has to say,
I'm not saying you're lying.
It's like you can't just goddamn talk anymore.
You just can't, I mean, Jesus fucking Christ, man.
You know, and everything is at the hands of children.
It's either literal children or mental children.
But anybody that wants to, you know,
that thinks that we all should just be part of this pile on.
And on social media and 140 characters and everything,
it's childish.
Yeah, stop it, stop it.
Well, this is a group of comedians, by the way.
And I can imagine, especially with alcohol,
a situation where cross who's used
to pushing the envelope and his comedy
makes an off -color racist joke
that there's fake racist jokes
that happen in writers room stuff all the time.
I'm not saying they're great either,
but they happen in everyone's last
because you're sort of making fun of racism.
Maybe that was happening here, I don't know.
Maybe he was being a racist asshole.
I've heard he's an asshole, I just said that.
I don't know him.
But, what I'm saying is,
I would imagine David Cross is not a racist.
I would imagine he's not as well.
Yeah.
But who knows?
When they start saying,
hey, Amber Tamplin,
I can't believe I'm talking about these people this much
because I don't know how.
You have to,
because it's in the news every day.
Hey, Amber Tamplin,
I know you've spoken out against rape and sexual assault.
What are you going to do about your husband now? So suddenly in the same breath
These things are made the same it's too much a racist joke is unquestionably horrible
We don't know the context or what happened or if it was something taken the wrong way or we don't know
We weren't there, but in the same breath to be like, oh, you don't like rape
You're gonna divorce your husband because he made a
a racist joke to someone?
Are they both bad?
Yes, are they both equal?
Absolutely not.
Yeah, and just for anybody listening
that might think we're going down some sort
of put up or shut up or victim shaming thing
or whatever the fuck it is, you wanna call it?
We're not.
What we're saying is, is the people
that have been raped and assaulted,
this is incredibly fucking insulting to them.
I agree.
People that have gone through true, true,
the harshest tragedy, it's all tragic.
But people have gone through the harshest tragedies.
Okay, and I am a person that believes rape is worse than murder
because you have to live with it if you're victimized by it.
It's fucking horrible.
Okay, sexual assault is horrible.
Being manipulated because of your gender is horrible.
All right, so can we not start putting every single thing
in that same category?
because it fucking sucks for the people that's just disrespectful to the people that you know
I the the the the the equivalent thing I keep saying is like I've got club I've had many club
bookers tell me you're you're white you're another white guy uh -huh sorry yeah is that racist by
definition yeah of course it is however am I gonna go up to a black person and be like dude I get it
your grandfather was a slave. I get it. Great grandfather. I totally get it. Yeah. Yeah.
You got called slurs today when you want. I get it. Right. I'm not going to do that. It's
disrespectful to to a much more tragic situation. And I don't think because as you said, you can't
talk anymore. I don't think that Charlene Yee even said. I know for a fact she didn't suggest
them in one breath equal and I find it really fucked up.
My only gripe with Charlene was not that she was upset about this, was not that she had
a problem with it.
It was not that she wanted to mention it.
My only problem with her was that she did it publicly and turned it into this public shit
show.
Okay, fine.
If that's the way you want to handle it, then at least commit to it.
But then to start to back pedal and go, well, I don't condone.
It's like bullshit.
You fucking knew this was going to happen.
This is what you wanted to happen.
and you wanted people to cast stones at him.
That's why you did this public.
Own it.
I'm so tired of people not owning their shit.
Just own your shit.
Be like, yeah, this is what I fucking wanted.
And maybe now it's going a little farther than I thought.
Maybe I feel a little weird shit.
Maybe I need to say, cross, sorry about that.
That's my bad.
I don't know, but like just own, at the very least,
own your shit.
And that's my only beef with her.
If that happened, I feel bad for it, sucks.
the, you know, the initial thing I mean. Sure. Anyway, you know, Pat, this is what happens
when we do this without drinking.
folks how about we take a little trip to Pat's movie. Now you don't want to if I poured
your drink you wouldn't drink it right now. I'm not in the mood now. Will you get in
the mood today at some point. Yeah, probably. All right. I mean, I'm not in the mood either,
but I just I feel dead inside. Well, that's that's a problem. If you feel dead inside
without alcohol, that's a problem. No, I just I'm saying I feel dead inside right now. Yeah,
this conversation. Yeah, let's let's let's lighten it up. I mean, I feel dead inside always,
but I hope it's not because I'm drinking because of it, but drinking does help it. It certainly
helps you. Folks, I saw a great documentary I was just telling Joe about called Too Funny
to Fail, the story of the Dana Carvy show. It's on Hulu. This is a show that in my very
formative comedy years, I could not have been more excited about. I loved Mr. Carvy and
And it was a very, very weird show.
The writing staff was Louis CK, Steve Carell, Stephen Colbert, Dino, Stemmetopoulos, Robert
Smigel, Charlie Kaufman, Brody, Charles Lachon, and Spotlessmont, and being John Malkovich.
I have heard it said always that Dave Chappelle was on the writing staff, but I did not see him
anywhere on this special, so maybe he didn't feel comfortable, I don't know.
But I'm sure they would have mentioned his name, yes, it was a dark weird show it opened with
They all just kept saying if Carvey had just done the church lady done his impressions
It would have been the biggest show of its time. He was a massive star. They thought he was gonna take over for Letterman
but his first sketch he played Bill Clinton
breastfeeding a litter of puppies
with eight
very realistic fake nipples on his chest. Why?
Very strange and I don't know but that was the first sketch they had they talked to like the head of ABC at the time
Because it came on after home improvement and he talked about how they did like the minute -to -minute ratings
And how every minute was a drop -off of like
600 ,000 people and it kept getting worse and worse
They did this show called granny clown which was an old woman in a clown full -clown makeup
And she comes out on a walker and starts lecturing the kids about how death is coming and then eventually
they set a cream pie in front of her and this actual 80 year old woman in sad wrinkled
clown makeup lowers her face into the cream pie slowly and then slowly pulls her face
out of the cream with it all over and the kids look traumatized.
This was on at 7 .30 pm when I was kid and I loved it and you know, to say it was a huge
It was on for six weeks, so it's hard to say that.
But it was one of my first tastes of like real weird comedy
because it was on ABC.
Sure.
I was like holy shit.
It was way beyond SNL in my opinion.
Yeah, that's how the Ben Stiller show and the Kid's War were for me.
Similar thing, yes.
The documentary is great.
There's a lot of funny stories.
Some of the people you want to talk are not in it,
but they got Karel and Colbert.
And the funniest part as I was telling Joe is they show an actual promo
For the show and Dana Carvey insisted every week on having a sponsor and calling it like the Mountain Dew Dana Carvey show
And they make fun of the sponsor brutally, right and sponsors of course we're pulling out and furious
So they showed this
Preview for Wednesday's episode and it goes
Home improvement and it's Jonathan Taylor Thomas and he goes because sometimes I want to die dad. I just want to die
And the promo says on a very special home improvement, uh, you know, we talk about teen suicides and it says followed by
The diet mug root here Dana Carvy show and they show this to Colbert and he has tears streaming down his face laughing and
They all admit even smigal who is a very cold dark man very funny man, but he was like I had never seen home improvement so five weeks in
I'm like I might as well watch what our leading is and then he said he felt so bad
for all the families that had to watch the his show
and he was like ashamed of it.
That's great.
It's a great documentary.
Good.
I also watched the first four episodes
of David Fincher's Mind Hunters.
It's not right to call it that
because he only directed a couple episodes
and it has a writer and et cetera.
But it feels finchery.
It felt a lot like Zodiac.
It's about like the early days of tracking serial killers,
70s.
And not enough is finchery these days.
That's true.
You know, I love finchery.
Yeah.
He did a hell of a job.
It's a beautiful looking show. It's kind of a cast of unknowns. It had a Zodiac feel. Zodiac is one of my favorite movies of all time. Absolutely.
There was a period where I watched it once a week for a year.
Psychotic check it out again. I've seen it check it out again. Three -hour slog. I
Absolutely drop it down a junior die slowly. It's a movie. It's a good movie about obsession
Obsession, you know, we all have our obsession. We all have a poster set. Yes. That's true. Yeah
Good. I love it. I know it's one of the few shows and ages where I actually said I'm gonna take a step back and wait a few days
because I want to make this last.
I really enjoyed it.
And it's about the early days of serial killing.
The guy who steals the show is not Jonathan Groff,
the guy from looking who's the star of the show.
It's his partner and I wish I knew his name
but it's like this 50 year old,
size more type dude who is so good on the show.
And this six foot five, 350 pound serial killer
that they keep interviewing,
who's done all this fucked up shit.
And he's like really charming and...
No, that's cool.
I love the show.
I really do and I think I saw in the face with page some of you are watching it
Maybe we'll do an episode on it
But that's it. I think that's all I saw Joe. I got two
Well three, but when I'm gonna hold my comments on I saw these snowman
Which we're not gonna talk about yet because I want Pat to see it so we can do an episode better move fast because I think it can open in like
14th place you gotta get in there quick
If for nothing else, the Val Kilmer performance, all right, which is
I don't know what the fuck what is he playing?
An Icelandic to alcoholic detective. Okay. Have you ever seen Val Kilmer in at first sight?
Blind man. I remember the movie. I never watched it though. That's a performance you need to see as well. All right. Fair enough.
Kilmer, by the way, is speaking of all these accusations,
Accused this week of a woman who was auditioning for a role in the doors in 1990.
He punched her in the face during the audition and they have video.
He paid her some million dollar non -disclosure, she's like, I'm breaking it.
Yeah, that's the, he did the, you know, he was doing that whole like, I am Morrison.
Yeah.
What would Morrison have done?
That new documentary is about to come out about where it's all the behind -the -scenes footage
from Man on the Moon.
Wanna see it?
with Jim Carrey playing Coffman. Jim Carrey is such a fuck anymore. The fucking thing, the whole thing is about how
They didn't want this footage to come out at the time of the movie because everybody was gonna think he was an asshole
Right, because he got so deep into the character and he was doing all this Andy Coffman shit to people, right?
And obviously pissing a lot of people off, but he felt like he had to live it or whatever. So fine, whatever
And he's like
Andy, Andy, Andy, Andy, Andy, Andy, Andy, Andy, Andy, Andy, you know, all through the
trailer and the preview and it was Andy and I wanted to spirit and all this stuff.
Yeah.
It cuts the title and the movie's called Not Andy and Jim, but Jim and Andy.
You know, it's like even you put it alphabetically, Andy and Jim, make, put it appropriately, Andy
and Jim.
This is not Andy Kaufman, not Jim Carrey.
Yeah.
Anyway.
He's so is it is it's like footage of him on set like screaming at people?
Yeah, some of it in the trailer is pretty crazy. I want to see it. I
I'd like to rewatch man on the moon. I liked it. I wasn't blown away by it. I own it. I enjoy the film. Yeah, it's a good film anyway
So but so what did I see that I can't talk about? I saw American made Tom Cruise's new picture loved it
Cruise charismatic and charming as always
It's a story we've heard a million times, you know, the government hired me to do a thing.
It's kind of illegal, but it's the government.
So, hey, that's fine, right?
They won't fuck me.
Then they fuck me.
And then, you know, it goes crazy.
And, you know, you've seen it in Lord of War, war dogs, all that shit.
But this was a movie I expected to just be a sort of beat for beat, retelling of a story
I've heard many times.
And I actually found it very interesting and very funny.
It's it's really funny. Uh, it's really, really fucking funny. Uh, why is it so slept on? I guess
America's dumb with cruise. No, it got it's it's very well reviewed. It's got like an 85 %
bomb. Just a complete bomb. It's a small move overseas. It makes money. It's a small movie. I mean,
it's not a big flashy movie. Most of the actors in it, I have never seen in anything except for
The lady that plays his wife, I've never seen her ever, the people that play, oh, the
only other person I recognize in it, the kid from once again, the kid from Get Out that
plays the brother and he's a show kid in Twin Peaks.
He shows up once again, playing like a fucking spastic, like scumbags that can't be trusted.
He's so good at that kind of role.
And clearly, he's just like, look, they're giving them to me.
I'm going to keep taking a bunch of this watch, get out again.
Best movie of the year outside.
Yeah, he's, he's great.
Better on the second viewing.
I got to see it again.
I love it, though.
Anyway, so I saw that in the only other thing I've really seen.
I got to tell him about six seasons deep into perfect strangers.
It's on Hulu.
Every night at dinner, I put on a couple of episodes.
Can I ask, are you laughing out loud at it?
Oh, a lot of it makes people laugh out loud.
It's, when I, in those formative years, the shit I was watching before a day in a car
every show opened my mind, was, my favorite show was Perfect Strangers and Alph.
Couldn't get enough of either.
And Mama's family.
I was never a huge off guy.
I did like Mama's family as a kid and just watching them, they're showing it now on 13 or something.
I went and looked at the DVDs after we discussed it, the other right in the bar.
It was $90 for this fucking thing.
It's like, it's Mama's family.
That should have brought us.
Well, no, you can see it on channel 13.
Bird Cage with a parrot telling them clues
about how to find gold was the plot of the episode I saw.
Yeah, the perfect straight,
every episode of burgers, except for season one,
they're kind of just finding the footing of like,
here are these two guys forging this weird new relationship.
And then after that, every episode is literally,
like Balky gets an opportunity. Larry's like Balky, Balky, Balky. Here's how things
work in America. And then from that point on, it's Marklin Baker just destroying everything.
Like they have so many episodes where by the end of the episode, the apartment is just littered
with holes in the wall and everything because they're looking for like a lost poem or something
and the walls like from some of our poet that live there.
It's a fucking, it's ridiculous, but it's great.
It's very fun.
Did Baker still show?
Yeah.
And it's very much, I never noticed this as a kid.
It's very much a throwback to old, you know, that sort of,
it's very three stooges.
It's very like Mark's brothers.
Oh, and Hardy.
Honeymooners, it's like, you know, it's them scheming,
but it's a lot of physical humor.
You could tell the writers were like,
This will be a great visual gag if we do this.
There's one where they're like trying
to change the sheets on this 350 pound man
in a hospital as he's asleep because he's been sedated.
And they just tie in this thing where it's like
bulky volunteers at the hospital so he knows this guy
and he's like, he can play Simon Says while he's asleep.
And you're like what?
And then it's just a gag so they can like,
like as they're trying to change the seats,
about you can keep going like Simon says
and he like sits up sleeping.
That's really stupid.
That's very stupid.
Yeah, it's ridiculous.
Yeah, it's funny and it works.
So that's all I saw.
On to the scary stuff real quick,
I saw one more picture.
It's coming up this holiday season.
Downsizing the new Alexander Payne.
Oh yeah, how was that?
Bad.
So you had said you thought it looked bad.
It was I thought the trailer looked terrible. It's it's Matt Damon and Kristen Wage decided they're going to miniaturize themselves
To save money and help save the environment and
Move to one of these mini communities. That's a great idea. I would have made a great twilight zone or something, right?
Alexander Payne man has lost his touch and it was a bad movie and it was for my Oscar
consideration. So clearly they have high hopes for it. But I sure hope not. It was a bad movie.
And there is a, a Vietnamese woman in it, which is for my money, the most offensive character
I've seen in five years. You know, like she literally comes on the scene and she's folks, I'm doing
this voice because it is her voice. But I'm going to make it less offensive. And I'm telling you the
truth. Okay. Uh, like Matt Damon does something and she's that she says it's like five times him.
I thought you were just stupid, but you crazy. You crazy man. And this audience of all white people
going to see an Alexander Payne movie at an Academy Awards screening. Um, dying laughing at this
woman's broken English. I was so uncomfortable shifting in my fucking seat and they're pushing this
woman for best supporting actress. These are all people by the way. This is an advanced screen. There's
Progressive entertainment business. These are all the open -minded people telling you that
That they that they know the way and the way to live and and the moral code we should all adhere to when I say that this woman
Sound sounded exactly like the short -round character from Indiana Jones the Temple of Doom right same voice and mannerism except
And this is a 1984 movie we're talking about Temple of Doom
room. That was a more nuanced portrayal of an Asian American character short round.
Never a good sign. The kid that played data in Goonies gave a more nuanced performance.
Well, then what's extra, here's a couple of things that are extra gross about this. This
woman is like a shrill, obnoxious, mean character. Here's a few things I'm going to just step
back and look at. Alexander Payne was married for a long time to Sandra O.
Things ended very badly I believe with like infidelity and problems. Then his
next movie he's got this real screaming Asian -American woman character. That
added a whole different layer for me. And then what made it gross is to me is that
the character's redeeming quality is that she loves helping people and she's
while doing so, she's like a bitch.
She's like, come on, carry my stuff, carry my stuff.
And I just kept thinking like,
somebody got wind of the script and they're like,
if you're gonna have an Asian woman play this role,
if I'm even gonna send this out to people,
you need to make her a really good person or something.
Right.
So it made it feel like it was okay to laugh
because she was helping people,
but I gotta tell ya, I didn't smile.
And I think they could be in some trouble.
Now is it the film?
is there a lesson they learn that trying to save the environment by making
themselves small means you also lose your emotions get small too and a
smaller world is not necessarily a better world is it one of those things yeah
well it's trying to have that kind of cap or a feel -goody thing at the end and
you're just not feeling it all Damon is oh Damon sucks in it like it just
This is not a good movie.
All right.
How's Wig?
I can't say too much about Wig about the movie to be honest.
She was fine.
You can't say too much there's not much to say or you're like hiding details.
I'm hiding details.
If a case anyone cares about the movie but she was fine.
All right.
Also it's two hours and 15 minutes and you feel every minute of it.
You guys got to stop with these goddamn films.
You got to stop with these goddamn films.
Stop every fucking director.
Go hang a painting at the fucking Met.
All right, go get something and put it up in the getty,
or it's like, stop.
That's one thing I'll say now about the snowman.
It's, you know, the guy, the director's defense
of the film was, you know, we just ran out of time and money.
And you just realized we just couldn't,
we couldn't get everything done.
we needed to. It's like, well, maybe you shouldn't have spent two days on the shot of the license plate.
Right. You know what I mean? Like, there are so many masturbatory shots in this film that do nothing,
nothing to advance the story, nothing. How did Scorsese come on as a producer of this thing?
Look, they look visually appealing. That's it. And it's like, yeah, you didn't,
because you were so busy jerking yourself off, you didn't get your goddamn movie done.
And now it sucks. It probably would have sucked anyway to be honest. It's a dumb storyline. But
Did they replace the heads with snowman heads or pack the heads in snow? You'll have to wait and see, Pat. All right.
But anything to recommend about it?
Yeah, Val Kilmer's performance. It's worth seeing the movie. Yeah, you got to see it because we're gonna have a goddamn trash fest on this thing over.
Sure, I'll say it, but it won the one positive for me was it's the same guy that did tanker tail or soldier spy, which was another
Bucking scruciatingly boring movie excruciating boring mess of a film anybody that was like oh, I followed it
No, you didn't it didn't make sense. I felt so hard asleep in that movie. It was so fucking boring
Yeah, it's this is it's the same thing except this time around people are like yeah, this is bullshit, dude
Right. This is unnecessarily confusing. It's stupid.
Right. Anyway, Joe's scary stuff.
You know, I don't have anything this week for it really.
Wow.
I'm trying to think, oh no, I do.
This is, you know, as always, a product that is horror or sci -fi
or fantasy related that is not a review of a film,
but a review of the product itself.
And for this week, I will pick the thing that everybody's going crazy about Super Mario Odyssey.
The game's everybody's good as people thought it was going to be the anticipation was worth it.
It was well worth the wait.
The game is fantastic.
It's getting perfect 10 reviews almost everywhere.
People are saying that Nintendo will be competing against itself this year for Game of the Year,
having released both Legend of Zelda Breath of the Wild and Super Mario Odyssey just months apart.
it's really great. If you have a switch, go and get it. If you don't have a switch, you're
fucked. You'll never get to play it because they'll never port it over to the other systems
as they never do. But if you have a switch, check it out. And I would say, I would go as far
as they, it's probably worth getting a switch for the game. If you're a Mario fan, if you're
not, then you're not going to like it. Anyway, we're at minute 43. There's a long one today.
Let's get into the movie review
The show review is and there will be no spoilers here
We're only talking about the pilot there are the not the pilot but this episode
One season two of stranger things the by the way the boys are back by the way Pat
Yeah, if you're worried about spoiler reviews. I was googling the show today season two. Yeah, because there were a couple of things
I wanted that couldn't remember from season one. Yeah already
Season two ending explained all over the place. I met a kid Friday. I met a kid Friday night at a party who had already watched the entire thing
Get a job
Jesus Christ
Get a job. I wish won this morning. I
Felt exactly how I felt about the first season in that I enjoyed it. I was left a little wanting
thing. I didn't feel an immediate desire to watch the second one. Now, I thought, let's
just hop right into it. This is, I mean, you're going to watch the first episode. Watch
it, you know, 11. No, you said the first episode. Oh, didn't, didn't we know that 11 was
alive at the end of season one. Yeah. They left a little clue. Yeah. Yeah. The wall
forward. I didn't knew she was alive. So then why was it treated as some big reveal at the
end of the pilot? Well, I think it was you knew she was alive. She hadn't been found.
It was unconfirmed. Okay. So the fact that at the end of the pilot, you see that she's living with
the sheriff. That was, you know, that was a core reveal. That actually made me smile. I thought
but that was very cool.
Cause I also thought they set it up really well.
We're like, he comes in the whole episode.
He's clearly pissed off that he's not getting
to fuck Winona Ryder's character.
Like he's really just sulking through the whole thing.
And then he goes home and he grabs the beer.
And you're like, oh, this guy's life sucks.
And then you see there's two dinners.
And you're like, oh, that's weird.
What's that?
And then she comes out and I'm like,
oh, that's pretty fucking cool.
And then you realize that he's dating 11 now.
Yep, and he calls this in very poor taste
What's he would frequently say hey 11 you want to meet 12 referring to the size of his member
Which I I thought they didn't need to go that far away. I agree. I could not agree more
Now here's what I'll say about
This this first episode it looks great. Yeah, it looked great and not only did it look great
But it did a great job of kind of capturing the 80s
like, you know, that arcade being in like that aluminum
siding barn type building, that's very Missouri to me.
I don't even remember where the show set, but I was.
Show is set in, oh god damn it.
Hawkins Illinois, I think.
They shot it.
They actually shot it in Atlanta.
Yeah, but I think it's Illinois.
I think that very much felt to me.
I used to go to great skate roller rink,
which was in like an aluminum -siding barn in Missouri.
Like, I was like, oh, okay, they did a little research and stuff.
And at the same time, even though it was shock -rate, it looked great.
And they have, in theory, this attention to detail.
I'm watching this thing. They're playing a video game that,
and it's not hard to recreate the graphics if you need to make them a video game.
They were watching an animated movie.
No, that's a real video game. That's dragons there.
That's a real video game, and that's how it looks.
Yeah, yeah, that was why I was that's why everybody was so nuts about it. That's that was actually a pretty great
It didn't even look like you could play it. Okay. We were just watching it happen
It's it was a it was a game of cut scenes essentially where a scene you'd watch the animated scene play out and
And they would move very quickly
Yeah, and a and a spot on the screen would illuminate
Which meant you have to hit your joystick in that direction and if you hit it correctly and on time
It would play the next scene very quickly and if you missed it you would die and it was very fucking hard and
It was it was I believe it was the first video game never cost 50 cents. Okay, which is why
That the teeth kid was being like this piece of shit, right expensive piece of shit
Okay, well, I'm completely wrong. Yeah, it was the uneven better example of details of the period
Yeah, no, that was actually a really great pat they put that they put that even in the trailer to because that that was a huge 80s
Not like that was I was like oh, they they really nailed it like that is the game. They should be playing
Then I'm wrong that looked to me to be very stupid my only other real issue was
And this you know the kind of thing happened in all kinds of movies back in the day
When the guys like act they I don't want you giving your rash to my sister acne's not a rash
Could we put one fake zit on this guy's face?
That was crazy.
If we're gonna talk to him about having acne,
what?
That was crazy.
Give him a zit.
As a guy who was covered in zits for my formative years,
it just really pisses me off.
By the way, I guess I don't hang out with a lot of 12 -year -old kids,
which is good.
but do kids not get acne anymore?
Or is it just an L .I.?
I have not seen a kid with acne in LA
since I moved here 10 years ago.
I never even thought about it.
I think it's not so much an issue.
I and all my friends had so many zits on their face.
Yeah, it's less of an issue.
There's a lot of medications and things for it now.
So I think they're able to treat it better.
But here's the other thing too,
that guy in the arcade.
Yeah, who's like, I want to date with your sister.
He's like a 30 -year -old actually.
30 -year -old, yeah.
He was in a lemony snicket. He's been in a bunch of shit. I see him at the Trader Joe's, by the way, sometimes shopping with his wife
It's like, yeah, no, he's way too way. It's like yeah, they got this like man. Yeah
So get a kid in the throw a kid into that role, maybe. Yeah
I will, I like, I only have one criticism of the show, which I will save.
I really enjoyed the pilot.
I enjoyed it much more than I thought it was going to.
I was kind of getting fatigue from all the advertising and just seeing these kids everywhere
and all that, you know, it just, it just cut,
it got a little tiresome.
So I did.
I feel bad for the kids, definitely.
I didn't think I was gonna enjoy it that much,
but I really did enjoy it.
I did too.
I thought they captured the spirit once again very well.
I really like that they took it now beyond.
It just looks like the 80s and there are 80s references
to them making fun of tropes from the 80s,
which I thought was very funny.
It was self -effacing at times.
Like I thought it was really funny
when the new kid pulls up and like the fucking muscle car and he gets and it's playing rock
me like a hurricane.
He gets out with the cigarette and then it shows does the the tracking shot past the
three girls.
They're like, who is that?
You know, I was like, that's really funny.
Like when they, I did like when I said, look at it, check out his ass and they cut to like
the most average flat generic male ass.
Whatever.
I was, I was thinking it's a bad.
It was a bad ass.
It wasn't even a good ass.
Bad to very average ass.
So anyway, I really, really liked it.
It was, I really liked seeing a well -known
a writer back in action.
I was as enthusiastic about that this time around
as there was the first and around.
Was happy to see Sean Aston in the show.
Same here.
Haven't seen him in a while.
He apparently has been at the old country buffet
for the last.
Sean Aston for seconds.
Either that or he's he's drinking a 12 pack of beer every day. Like it was a giant
stomach. Yes. Just a head like a goddamn watermelon. Yeah. But I love Sean asked and it was
fun. I did too. I got a big kick out of Paul Reiser. Of course. I always love Paul. You know
what I love Reiser and Whiplash. Whiplash. He's great in Whiplash. You know what I love
I love Ryzeran as well, speaking of shows that I love Red Oaks on Amazon, the best comedy
they have.
You know what I love Ryzeran?
Ryzeran, have you seen Red Oaks?
You'd love Red Oaks.
Red Oaks is some of it.
It's strange or things, but for 80s comedies.
I tried to jump in in the second season and like the main kid was living in like France
or something.
And to watch the whole thing.
Alright, let's go back.
I didn't know.
The first season is like Caddy Shack, tons of nudity, etc.
Yeah, second season's a bit more of an art film
But but still funny and good and this third season has been great. I love it
You know what I like rising the thing about my folks have been Peter Falk on the rock which I believe is a Zach Braff film
No, it's not it's not so many directed that the directed so wait. You're talking about a recent movie
Yeah, the thing about my folks. I did not see a thing about my folks because riser was in some one who's in buy by love
love, of course, with Randy Quaid in my mode.
My favorite daily show joke from the Craig Killborn error ever is, he said, Helen Hunt
is leaving Matt about you because she, she wants to focus more on her film career after
her Oscar win as good as it gets.
Paul Reiser said he wants to do the same, focus on his film career, which means making VHS
copies of Bye Bye Love in his house.
it's so mean it's such a funny thing about my folks was oh five there that
couldn't have been a breath couldn't
the web oh no i'm sorry the guy directed city island directed at the
thing about my folks i love city island okay written by Paul rise or the
thing about my i fucking love city island i the city islands one of my favorite
movies of the last few years that's that's weird i thought it was fine
I thought it was hilarious, but I related to the family.
I was like, this reminds me of my family.
It's loud.
Everybody was always eating pasta.
But anyway, the only thing I didn't like,
my only criticism of this episode,
and it's clearly gonna be a plot point,
and if I'm wrong, correct me on this,
because this is why I started googling the show.
The goddamn building they go to
to get Will, the son that disappeared in the first season,
to eat it, it's the fucking evil building from the first one.
Like, Paul Reiser even says at one point,
those people were gone.
It's the laboratory building from the first season.
So they just went back to the same place.
Thinking, well, they're all good people now.
Right.
And they're not, of course,
there's Paul Reiser's lying and he's setting them up for something.
Riser was so clearly lying from the jump and like right off the bat
He's like we're the good guys, right? You know, he's not and since this movie is so obsessed with everything 80s
Riser did this in aliens
Oh, that's interesting, which I know you hate, but that's interesting
That's great. Riser was one of the all -time great kind of like two -faced weasels in aliens
so clearly that's why he was cast here, but I
I guess now coming in for season two, for some reason,
I'm way more open -hearted to the show.
I think I'm gonna enjoy it a lot more.
Last year, the hype had gotten so great,
I just kind of, I could not get on board with it.
I'm gonna enjoy it too.
And please, let me know if I'm wrong
about if it's a different building,
but I don't think it is.
When they show the building, it does like a dun dun dun.
Yeah.
It's like this is the evil building,
They're going back so and then and then it is the building because he riser goes down to the basement and they have the fucking portal still, right I'm like
Why would you do what I don't know yeah, I like the show
I wish I always find myself wishing that the kids dialogue was a little funnier
And I know that people I thought the same thing in it. I know people find the kids hilarious. I really don't I
Think they're they're adequate and toothless is funny, but
I he made me laugh a lot like good actor when he kept doing that thing where he's like look at these choppers
Like like yeah, that was very funny that kids really good. He's really funny too when she's like how presumptuous and he's like
Yeah, presumptuous like because he doesn't know what the word me right and I I greatly appreciated
That they had the guts because it was a funny thing with the kids as ghost busters
when the black kid is dressed up as as
Venkman and he was like, oh, I was supposed to be Winston
because I'm the black guy.
I thought that was funny.
I was like, you know, and he's like, I didn't say that.
And he's like, well, you were thinking it, you know what I mean?
It's like, it was just funny.
I thought it was a very funny scene.
That might be in two because I watched it and don't remember that.
Oh, shit, that is an episode.
I was gonna say, surely I didn't forget that from the small.
Sorry, an episode two.
I was gonna check myself into a hospital.
In episode two, they dress up as the shoppers thing in episode two.
No, that's one.
In episode two, on Halloween, they go to school dressed up as the ghost busters and it's
four of them.
I like them.
And the main kid, Mike, I think Mike and the black kid, they have, they both are dressed in,
they both have, say, vankemen.
Okay.
And nobody's winced.
No.
That seems realistic.
And he's like, and the main kid is like, you were supposed to be Winston, you know, the
like, nobody wants to be Winston, Winston stinks.
He's not even a scientist.
Actually, it makes you feel bad for any Hudson,
because they really shit on Winston.
But then the other kids, like, no, he's awesome.
And then the kids, like, oh, I'm supposed to be Winston.
Why?
Because you're not black.
And he's like, no, that's not what I said.
And he's like, you were thinking it, you know,
there's just a funny argument.
And I'm like, it's a believable,
it's one of the things I like about the show.
I'm like, they do portray the kids as believable 80s kids.
I agree, you know, like they're all obsessed
with this new girl in school who rides a skateboard and they just stand and stare at her.
You know what I mean? And there is no part where they're like, I mean, they allude to
the, you know, it's kind of creepy. But it's very innocent. It's like these kids are just kids.
Like, this is kind of how you acted back then, you know? Yeah. I like where this new one's
heading. I do. Yeah. All right. And I hope it lasts a while. It's fun to have this every Halloween
way and to kind of look forward to.
And we'll revisit this after the finale
and do a basic season recap.
Well, I went once we get to it.
I mean, but my point is we'll come back to this
and do a season recap episode of Stranger Things 2.
Yeah.
But for now, that's where we're at.
And that is our show.
Folks, I am at Twitter and Instagram at the Patrick Walsh.
Doing as I got to do putting it on your radar,
this January living biblically coming to CBS might not be January, but that's what the vibe
I'm starting to get. And I think promos are going to be filmed this week so start looking for them.
Come follow me on Instagram. Jota Rosa Comedy.
And what else? We have our Patreon. Oh yeah, shit. The patreon .com slash WSYIH.
Yes, the new episode WS why I H pod pod
Thank you so much to all of you have donated can't say it enough
I'm floored. I'm thrilled. I'm teary. I'm touched. It's it's been a very very generous
Uppouring from the fans. We appreciate it this episode
As of this episode posting the patreon secret or extra app should be up
We said we're 30th and we said we're doing it Halloween. We do it the day before it's the new one. Yeah, it should drop tomorrow or Halloween day.
And that's it.
Thank you, folks.
We'll see you next time and we'll see you.
No.
So fast, Patty.
I don't mean to cut you off.
We didn't forget your patrons.
We promise you shout outs. You're getting some goddamn shout outs. Shout outs. Excuse me.
Shout outs. Fuck it. That's how we do it around here. You can hear ice clinking in the background.
That's because our dear friend Vince has arrived during the podcast and it's beer 30, as we say
around here. Thank you, Derek Clark, hitting us with a big donation. Very sweet of you. Thank you,
sir. Timmy Kaye, Sean, and you're all special by the way. We're not making anybody more special
than anybody else. So let's start over. Derek Clark, Timmy Kay, Sean Florin, Dolores Martinez,
Will Foley, Megan Lybrand, Scott Blickens Dürfer, Alec Walker, Brett Werner, Tristan Carlson,
Laura Sexton, Anthony Guajardo, Maxwell Ashcroft, Brett Klingker. That's a good one.
And Alex Lowe, Ethan, with it, with it, Weston Thomas, oh boy, why don't you take it
from here, Weston, my apologies, but I mean, I'm looking at a deep Scandinavian last
name here or something, Weston Thomas, Havid Hild, I'm doing my best, Havid Hild, thank
you, Weston, Jared Blair. Thank you, buddy. Josh Smallridge, Richie Verdugo, Chris Hopper,
Emily Rosenbaum, Emily Florence, who runs our fantastic Facebook page. Thank you, Emily,
for both, for both your contribution and for running a hell of a community. Sean L. Jordan
Martin Parker, Dave Camorek, Abbey Manuel, hi, Abbey, Kim D 'Angelo, Michael Whitsett,
Jonathan Jolotte, Michael McBurnett, Carla O, Mike Willis, wheels, I believe, excuse
me, Stephanie Power, Hunter McDonald, Sterling Abrigo, Giron Sanderson, Diego Campos, Jake
Ferrati, Stefan Musso, Zoe Blaschkevich, it seemed right when I said it. Edmund Dillon,
Asli Kuvinsland, Dan McLeod, Brandon Gash, Lorenz Bunganiers, Alejandro Salgado, we're
laughing at your names. Some of you guys have great names. Oh, this one's real funny. Papa Spoosh.
Hey, excuse me. I got to go into the bathroom in Papa Spoosh.
Tegan McLeod. There's two McLeod's on here. I wonder if they're related. Matthew Little,
Tracy Reddington, Sean Thomas, Amanda, Alzumara, Jason Wyble, Michael Curry, Drew Spindler.
That's a dear friend, a special love, Pat's Andrew Koval, Sam Mitchell, Aaron Milinowski,
Scott Nolan, Jack Gertz, Greg Sarnson, Benjamin Tahia, Misty Zavar, Brandon Nock, Brandon
in web. Don Don Jay. Dojne. Excuse me. Dojne Wilford. Johnny Ferg. Mathias Pagui. Pagow.
Superfan Giovanni. Michael Gold. Danielle Deur, Eric Lamora. Michael Magigal. My dear
friend who owns Mr. Suit Records in Lancaster, Pennsylvania. Go check it out. It's a wonderful
in the shop. Stephen Rez, Walter Keegan. I'm going to pass the mic back to Pat in a second. Kevin
Marison Eck, Erica Branding, Lawrence Anderson, Jared Smallridge, Zach Shondorf, Will Potter,
Natalie Craig, Nathan Baskett, Edmund Agaball, Anthony, just Anthony, Kyle Kinslin,
Brook Adams I'm not saying his name but folks the best name there is on a baba duke
Scott Patton
We mean we've already done everyone else excellent. Thanks everybody. Thank you folks. We'll see you in hell