Summer is here, and Bed MGM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer.
Or check out our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz.
Only available at Bed MGM Casino.
Spend on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 Fortunes, Mystery of the Land,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand.
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action.
Bet MGM in Game Sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 Plus to Wager, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania, and West Virginia
only, games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as normal, durable site credit slash bonus bets unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
The football season is full of guarantees, and here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October, if
your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning, or winning money back in fan
cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
Winning hits different here.
Monthly 21 -plus, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gampler, offer not available in all states,
term -supply, see Fanatic Sportsbook app.
This is a head gum podcast.
Hello everybody and welcome to another episode of We'll See You in Hell.
This is a podcast where we discuss a new or old horror sci -fi fantasy picture or television
show each week.
For this week we're discussing Darren Arenofsky's mother.
And now, without further ado, on with the show and on.
Who with the j -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -o -
in. Yes. It hasn't my girlfriend had not seen it. Does not like scary shit. Our good friend
Laura Kightlinger, a hilarious comic if you're in the Los Angeles area. I saw her the other
night at a show and introduced myself and did you mention my name? I think I did. I was
quite drunk and I feel that I've made a talk to her for too long. I feel like I might have
hit that dead zone where she's like this guy really needs to stop talking to me now. I'm sure
you were fine. I love Laura and she is hilarious. But she wrote me last night, and I didn't,
I should have known at the time, but I got a text, hey, do you want to go see it tomorrow
with me and my boyfriend? I said, you sure? Heather, you want to go? She said, sure. Then
I got about 14 texts confirming and three additional emails confirming. And then today I realized,
she might have been a little drunk folks. But we were all excited to see it. We went over
to the E rustic we had their bloody Mary brunch, you know, eggs, you ever been over there?
To the E rustic?
Well you get breakfast and you're gonna talk to me, what am I, a schmuck?
I've been there with my dude, but what did I just get off, uh, uh, uh, uh, what's the old
saying?
I look at your truck?
I look at it, I just got off a boat, you know, turn, I think turn up truck.
Well that, that too.
No, I mean if you've been there for the bloody Mary brunch, no, you get breakfast in a bloody
Mary for $11.
It's nice.
What did, what was your breakfast?
I had eggs and fruit and hash brown all right. Well, give me the good stuff, baby. Don't leave out the deets
Well, we had a great time. We'll go over to it and I was saying on the way up
Look, I've already seen it
If you read the book, you're not gonna like it get her boyfriend Garrett was like oh
Fuck I love the book. Okay, you might enjoy it
But I wanted to go in with new expectations
Not that this is gonna be the book expectation, right?
And not since we've started doing this podcast if I received more tweets face books, etc
Of people being like you guys are fucking idiots, but we also got a ton agreeing with it
That's true agreeing with our take on the full saying thank you for being the only people saying it's not great on the Facebook page
However, there was a lot of people like these guys are crazy the movies great whatever and I really did go
in like a real head space of like I know I didn't like it the first time so I you
know let me go in with an open mind and folks I know I said that it was not
good on last week's podcast but I was wrong it's actually terrible it's
fucking terrible and to go without the benefit of the eight nine drinks Joe and I
I had to just go in cold and watch this thing.
I mean, it's awful and Pennywise in particular
is a fucking embarrassment.
And I've had so many people be like,
but wasn't he amazing in the row?
No, actually he wasn't.
We might have even eventually,
by the end of last week's podcast said,
yeah, the performances were good, scars were good,
he's not good, he's terrible.
I'm very happy to hear you saying this
because I was thinking about seeing it again
literally the same approach. Okay, let me go in and see it now. Yeah, this is a regular movie.
And I'm happy to hear you saying that I was hoping this would be the misdirection
that you were setting it up to be to say no, it's actually worse.
But yeah, I mean, it's cheap jolt scares and they turned a really wonderful story into the goonies.
Not even. And yeah, well, the goonies are classic. I'm not shitting on the goonies,
but I'm saying, like, those two worlds don't need to mix.
I watched it with my girlfriend who's not do well
with horror and tends to cover her eyes
and ask me what's happening.
So we just don't usually watch scary movies.
I'm just like, watch the fucking movie.
It's a little heated.
But you push her around the kitchen.
I shove her around, you know?
Grapefruit in the face.
But she's watching this, doesn't cover her face at all.
She's watching it.
And then at about the two -hour mark,
she turns to me and she goes,
this is pretty fucking boring.
Yeah, and that's something that we did not really touch on last week because
I guess I was drunk and having a you know it's excited to see the movie whatever. It's really boring
Yeah, and especially seeing it a second time. It's a boring fucking movie. And there's no there's no
Wait to it. There's no soul. There's no substance. So you it is just a fucking cheap scare fest
And it and it's trying to be the conjuring and all these you know, it's like it's it's so it's
I'm tired of everything being the same.
Like everything is the same.
Anyway, sure.
And they should have ended after the first monster house scene
where they go in there and they do all that.
There's another half hour after that.
With no really, like the scares aren't up.
The drama isn't up.
It never has that moment.
You can tell they're going for it
when the kid with the glasses goes,
well now I'm gonna kill this fucking clown.
You can tell they're going for the cheer moment,
but nobody's cheering.
No.
Like it's there there's nothing exciting about any of it. There's nothing triumphant. They took the they took the guts out of that
Character yeah, and I believe I did say this last week. We we're not doing it again
Yeah, but I you know they took the guts so then when he does say that you don't have any reason to cheer
Yeah, because they took out a pivotal fucking scene that makes that makes you realize why that kid is taking it seriously now
so it's it's
It's a it's a bad movie. I'm glad to hear this that I'm that we weren't just being
Don't sit again, but here's something of Penny was dying
That kid goes I know what I'm writing my how I spent my summer vacation paper about really oh
God really. Oh, God. This is a this is your nightmare fuel
Yeah, fuck so so here's an interesting fact
act. As we mentioned last week, but I did not know this little piece of information. On
the last episode, when we reviewed this film, we mentioned our confusion that not only
Stephen King, but his son renowned fantasy horror author, Joe Hill, gave the movie accolades.
Joe Hill said it was one of the five scariest films ever made up there with Texas Chainsaw
massacre and jaws ludicrous uh so I was like what am I missing here like what I'm missing some
well turns out they're making a lock -in -key movie and the director of it is directing the lock -in -key
and I was like there we go oh oh now oh now I get it now I get it there we go that was a real
disappointment I was very business as just people lying and lying and lying lying lying lying in
the hopes that they do something for you in the future or lying as a favor to you doing
something for them in the present or the past yeah it's it's all bullshit and
everyone just falls for it and says yes that's right that's true I love this
it's it's the sickest business in the history of America
entertainment history it's sick sick and then the church well it might not be
sicker than some aspects of the church but yes I think it's probably has the same
aspects according to Corey Feldman it has the same aspect analyze a wood apparently
there's a big ring of high -profile petafiles, and Elijah Wood is not one of them, he's exposing them.
Yes, yes.
What would you say would be without a discussion of petafiles?
Let's do a Pat's movie corner, because Pat, I'll tell you, I feel terrible.
I was in Vegas last night. We did emotional hangs live, Kurt Bronnellar and myself for the very first time.
Beautiful, beautiful time at the Scoops Fest. Thank you guys for having us.
It was just wonderful, the crowd was electric, it was packed, we had a blast.
But then I decided to get unreasonably shit faced.
So at 8 a .m. when I was looking at the cold, hard light of day in the bathroom window and
I was like, I haven't slept yet, I should probably go to bed.
It was a rough night, but it was fun, and you came over with some beers, and I'm having
a sort of a patchum up whiskey, but I'll tell you, I'm too sips into this thing.
I feel like I'm drinking night quill.
It tastes terrible.
And the frightening thing is, as the buzz slowly creeps back, my head immediately goes,
Well, I mean, we I get we could go out for a few beers. It's only five o 'clock
So who knows where the night leads us when alcoholism comes into play. That's true. I'm open
Anyway, let's do a Pat's movie corner. What have you seen? Where was where was that going? It seemed like you're building to a tale or something
About what about Vegas. Yeah
No, I'm saying let's get to the goddamn show because that's like I'm gonna fall over in my chair right now. Yeah
Oh, a past movie. Yeah, that's what I guess that's what I was wondering is how it connected to Pat's movie corner
No, I was saying like you're gonna say I watched a movie on the plane or something. Well, no, I well I did watch movies
Okay on the plane, but I but I would give you the honor of starting your own segment sure
I have only seen one movie in the past week to my knowledge and it was a picture called girl's trip
And I thought it was a funny movie
I am probably not the target audience for Girl Strip,
but I enjoyed it.
Would you say it was a good movie or just a funny movie?
Like, it strikes me as, and I'm friends with Tiffany,
I'm very happy for this issue she's having
with this picture, but it doesn't change the fact
that to me it looks very much in the vein of like,
the hangover and stuff like that where I go,
well I guess there's some funny parts,
but like I wouldn't call it a good movie.
It is an unquestionably bad movie, but to me I don't think bad and good factors into comedy at all to me
What the hell are you talking about?
What I am talking about is is for me if a comedy is funny, it is a good comedy
Okay, if you want to talk about what's a what's a good move? Okay, like toots. He's a good movie and a good comedy
Okay, I got you. You know what I'm saying? Yeah, I got dirty work as a terrible movie
But a great comedy. Okay, that's I got you half baked terrible movie great comedy
Okay, I got you see before another one of the favorites the dog shit movie. Yes, but I love it and girls trip
You know, I mean this thing starts with narration where it's like hi, I'm Regina. I'm the business woman
But I also like to have fun
And then it's like here's my friend Betty. She likes to have fun
But she also knows when it's time for business, you know like
They they the narrow you don't need narration in a comedy ever in my opinion. All right, fair enough. We understand the plot
You could have just shown us these four girls they
You know, it's entertaining and Tiffany
Hattish, Hattish, Hattish, yeah, off -air pat called her Tiffany Hadish
I thought it was a D which was up there with Tobay Hooper. Yes, and these these you take these regular names and turn them into these like a wrist
I've never heard had it, it's not a regular name, but I'm saying it's a normal name and then you take it, you make it sound like some kind of French emperor or something.
I wouldn't be surprised if she gets a nomination, much like Melissa McCarthy back in the day.
She's so funny that the others look a little lazy in comparison.
And yeah, it's, it's, look, it's, I think Jada Pinkett is a great actor.
She's not a comic.
She's not funny.
No, the, the other three are like really not keeping up with, with, with
Hattish because what Queen Latif as they went, I love Queen Latif.
I've loved her since I was 11 because I liked her music and I was a big rap kid.
And I think she's a good actor.
I don't think she's funny though.
Like I'm not everybody has to do everything.
It's like, you know, you stuck in amazing and like stuff like Chicago and stuff like that.
It's like, you know, it's like I don't want to see Harrison Ford in a comedy.
I love Harrison Ford.
Yeah, sure, you know, but you know, it's a it's a very likable movie.
Uh, I'm glad I saw it.
I'll take it over badmoms any day of the week.
Uh, and you're going to get a badmoms Christmas this year, I believe.
I don't think I'm going to see a badmoms Christmas.
But yeah, we were two billion dollars.
We were talking recently, Joe, about how guys have the most of the big
10 pull movies are marketed towards guys. Right. And the movies that women have marketed towards them
are maybe not the best movies. No, it makes me I feel I honestly I feel bad for women because I know
they want more to choose from. I know they want. They're getting pitch perfect three were back pitches.
They're getting bad moms Christmas and they're getting 50 shades of part three. Right. Like these aren't
good movies. Yeah, you know what? I was mad they didn't title those movies with like a number
corresponding like 53 shades of gray. You don't even need to write. But anyway, but look it's
you know it's it's my thing is it's what sucks for so many women that really like the cinema
at least for American made movies. You know guys get marketed the same kind of like whatever
never shit too. Like, like, you know, we talked about the hangover and stuff. Again, not
great movies. But then like, guys also get like the Irishman with De Niro and Peshie
and sure. And, you know, you get like, and I'm not saying that many women may love those
movies too, but I'm saying like, there should be shit like that for the ladies as well.
Like, I feel like they don't get a big payoff. Like, where's the Emma Thompson and Julia
Roberts and you know you know it was good actually oh sage county August oh sage
County that was yeah predominantly female cast and that was a great flick that was a
great flick yeah I just we're like you know Woody Allen when he did like when he
would do the off hand in her sisters in my favorite movie of all time but his
other female movie like interiors sure it's like it's like they're literally the
Woody Allen movies you never want to watch yeah this is a story about four
assist us that are in a living room and you're like,
what?
Well, I mean, man, the man in our sister's is great.
Yeah, that's great.
But, you know, these are movie by man.
Yes.
You want, I'm trying, I want to be as open -minded as woke
as I can be.
I wish that the movies marketed towards me were better.
I wish the movies marketed towards women were better.
I wish everything was just better.
I don't want to tell you.
Now, I'll give a half -court, nothing but net swish shot to a movie I saw, which was
Wonder Woman.
I finally watched Wonder Woman.
I have not seen it yet.
It's a fantastic superhero movie.
They walk the line, the deep look, we're not going to go down the DC Marvel road.
Thank you.
But DC is doing it very, they're finding a great balance with their films.
They're very much in the vein of like the Star Wars movies and stuff like that.
There's charm and there's humor, but they're not joke machines, they're not comedies.
So Wonder Woman was great, it was an amazing commentary on feminism, especially since it
took place during World War I, it was just a really great movie.
That being said I'm I'm losing my flavor for these movies now like I don't enjoy I don't I haven't enjoyed a superhero movie
And so long and I'm starting to realize it's because I don't like superhero movies anymore
Yeah, but I you can if you like superhero movies you will fucking love Wonder Woman
It was great like I'm not even that excited for Justice League and I'm like I should be really excited for that and I'm not
And I'm just terrified that one day I won't be excited for Star Wars anymore and I hope that doesn't happen but
but Wonder Woman was great.
I also saw going in style.
I saw Michael Cain, Morgan Freeman, Alan Arkin,
gonna rob a bank, not a great film.
I loved it.
Okay.
All right.
Again, I wouldn't say it's a great movie,
but it's a perfect, go watch it with your mom kind of movie.
Sure.
very charming everybody loves to see the old guys that don't take shit from the
young guys I thought I thought was his face from S &L was really funny in it
Keenan yeah cool Keenan's the best Keenan was really funny yeah that scene
where it's like Morgan he's looking at the footage with the cops of Morgan
Freeman with the whole pork loin in his pants yeah and he goes had to be the
brother had to be the brother yeah there it was real you know there he was
really funny as you as you told me many times your favorite working director
is that breath yes yeah yes yeah and my favorite working actor is Alan
Arkin right right so you know not that I'm comparing
to have you speaking of Alan Arkin have you watched cross -point blank yet I did
watch it did you like him I liked it it was a charming film but I saw it too
It is so 90s. It's not crazy. I really thought you would like it more than. No, I liked it, but it is so 90s
It's crazy. It's like he comes into town
The girl that got away is the DJ and the local radio station. Yeah
She makes them hash it out with her on air. I mean it had Kevin Smith like stinklines coming off
You know, so it's pretty great, but it was it's a great flick and how about how about a pre -enterosh pivvon bringing the heat
pre -enterage Piven was great. I love that he's track. I love that he's Jack Hammer
in the joint and then he has to go show the real estate to people. Ackroyd was
great. Ackroyd. Maybe at his best. Yeah. I really enjoyed it. Kusek is always
Joan Kusek, Grand Slam as always Sergeant Pepper, Jack. In fact, we did an
episode of when I was saying earlier, we went to Vegas to do emotional hangs
live and our guests were the hosts of Hey Scoop's podcast. And Matt was Matt was one
of the guys and he was telling us about how he was stage managed a show in Vegas. Okay.
And I was like, I just picture you. Tell me if it's like this, I just picture a Joan Kusak
type with a clipboard running around. Right. You had a pencil behind your ear back there.
But that's exact. I love when she plays that kind of role
I love when she plays like the person that's got a wrangle everything
Yeah, you know, and you get to see her screaming at people and to me her funniest ever is in and out
Yeah, she's great, man. Well, I'm gonna give my funniest Joan Kusak to my blue heaven
Sure, I'll give you that my blue heaven did not benefit from a rewatch a recent rewatch as we've discussed on this show
Um, so, but I, but I did like Gross Point Plank, uh, I just saw it too late.
All right.
Uh, lastly I saw, I saw one other movie.
I saw all those two and I saw, um, oh, how to be a Latin lover go on.
Much funnier than I expected it to be.
All right.
Uh, it's very much a Ken Marino movie.
he directed it and it's very obviously like very Ken Marino -ish. Is it a you know like
how like every week they'll be a movie that's like in the top 10 that's a Latino movie?
Like there were they speak Spanish most of the time. No there's a little Spanish but it's
mostly English. Okay all right and it's it was funny it was about like a guy that wants to be like
Like you know, it starts with him as like a 10 year old boy and he and his sister and
their mother live in the car and he's like got this magazine with this like rich guy with
this trophy wife on the back cover advertising scotch or something and he's like, I want this
is what I want to be when I grow up and his sister's like, that man has a job.
He's not just like, you know, he's not just rich and then he goes, no, I don't want his job.
I want hers.
So and then it cuts them. He's a jiggle. Oh, right falls in love with this like 80 year old lady Caesar across the pool
He's like, oh, she's perfect
You know, and he obviously mirrors her for the money and then she throws him out to start fucking Michael Sarah
Who really hits the nice home run in this Michael Sarah's and how to be a Latin lover Michael Sarah's in about three scenes
And he is fucking tremendous in it. All right. All right. He plays a scumbag anytime Michael Sarah plays a scumbag
it's great right anytime plays anything it's great the best the best performances of scumbags are from
people who have studied scumbags and been the recipient of scumbags. yeah like a Michael
Sarah I'm sure so so I enjoyed the film I thought it was very funny all right I'll see and again like
this whole discussion. Is it a good movie? Yeah, it's not bad. It's not you know
but I mean here's the other thing too. I think we're very jaded and this is what
I was having when I was watching Wonder Woman. This is when I watch all these
movies. Kind of said the same thing about all of them. I enjoy them but when you
watch enough movies you can just see the twists and turns coming. You're like okay
obviously this is the character that's gonna redeem himself and there's this is
going to be when they think the guy died, but he didn't. And this is going to be the
guy they actually do kill off. You know, like, it just starts to become, you know, a little
wrote, but, um, sure. So I don't know. Maybe that affects maybe, maybe these movies are better
than we think they are. I don't know. I also, uh, it's, it's about time for the return of
Nathan for you, probably the funniest show on television. I've seen it many times. I met Nathan
and once at a party.
They just did, they had a special, an hour long special
on Comedy Central the other night, I was scream laughing.
And it's just like the special.
It wasn't even the premiere.
It was like an update on previous episodes.
I just, I love it.
If you don't watch it, you should.
That one where he is marketing the fitness jacket.
And the whole thing is like we do not like the Holocaust.
That's the whole marketing campaign that he's got back to that in the special. Yeah, I mean that is
That was insanity. I was like this kids out of his fucking mind. I can't believe like I don't know how he does this shit with a straight face
He's yeah, he's got kind of like a death wish that I really respond to right
I like it a lot. Sorry. I had to turn in poor to another splash
I'm happy to see you buddy because I'll tell you I'm in a state today where I'm ready to end it. We'll be fine. And I need it to see a loved one, quite frankly.
Well, let's get to mother or you want to do scary stuff scary stuff
By the way, I can't tell you how many people and this was true
I was not making a joke when Joe put on Instagram the other day
Something about our Instagram account. I was not aware that we'll see you and hell had an instant
We don't have one, but you I was feeding it that to Twitter. So I put the Twitter handle on it
because I'm not going to do Twitter anymore.
Now what happened there?
I haven't talked to you about this.
I can't get into it.
It's a whole thing with the other podcast.
It's, I pissed off a bunch of cyclists
on the emotional hands.
Yeah.
And what did you say about cyclists?
I told a story about opening my door
and this guy on a bicycle.
I didn't see him.
He almost hit my door.
And by almost, I mean, trust me when I'm not being,
I'm not being a shitty here.
He had plenty of time to stop.
He had enough time to completely circumvent my door, 100%.
And was going slow enough to yell fuck you at me repeatedly.
So it's like, it wasn't like I almost hit the guy.
It was a guy being super precious about the bike.
And I was like, look, I went on a rant.
I said fuck you.
You want to ride in the street with everybody else.
Take your chances.
And I know that a lot of people did not agree with that.
but I ended the entire rant by saying the point is
I went into my show that night,
which was at UCB on Sunset, and this is where it happened.
And I said to the audience, this just happened,
am I wrong?
And the audience said, yeah.
And I went, oh, okay, I'm wrong then.
And I said, I was just mad that the guy acted
so shittily about it.
It wasn't like, hey dude, watch it.
It was literally like venomous fuck use repeatedly.
as if he's not even a part of this equation.
So anyway, a lot of cyclists.
Why were you in the wrong for opening your door?
Because apparently the doring is a thing
and Bikers flip over and I know that
because I used to bike when I lived in Manhattan.
But that movie with Joseph Gordon Levin
was about your life in Manhattan, right?
Yes, what was that called premium rush?
Third rock from the sun.
Did you see premium rush?
No, no.
But I remember.
I could get anywhere in this city in five minutes. Yeah, yeah, Michael Shanna by the way folks
That's a B plus movie it ain't bad at all. It ain't bad at all. I couldn't be less interested the only way
I'd be less interested if he was with DJ. Yeah, no, sure if he was playing a DJ
I'd be a little less interested. We're your friends. Yeah, so anyway
Some guy decided to take a portion of the
discussion, transcribe it, and then put it online. I had many people start coming
after me and like bikes .com. No, on Twitter. Okay. Nobody was, nobody was
talking about what I said at the end or anything. Everybody was focused on this
one part of a fucking rant on a podcast that's supposed to be funny, right? So
everybody started coming after me. Then I start realizing these people who
actually work in the industry, like the entertainment industry.
The producer of one mad money, the low point.
One of the first movies I reviewed as a film critic.
Low point in Diane Keaton's career as we've just got.
Yeah.
And Katie Holmes.
The guy that a producer of mad money was like, I will see
to it, you never work.
Oh my god.
Like, I know everybody.
And then I looked up his work.
I was like, what does this guy do?
So he's okay with a runner in a film about statutory rape.
That's a runner in the movie waiting.
So he's fine with that, but my bike rant was off base.
And your bike rant was basically, why can't I open my door without fear of a bike
or running into it?
Was that the gist?
Basically.
And I was just blowing off steam.
And at the end of it, I was like -
And he's going to see to it that you never work again for this, at a time where people
People are literally returning to Nazism.
Yeah.
Okay.
So, and then, so he came after me, he blocked me eventually, because I said, let me, he told
me to explain myself and I go, let me explain how comedy works.
It seems Robert O 'Greene.
I go, let me explain how comedy works.
I don't explain myself, especially to bookers.
See if you can understand this, fuck you, you whiny pig.
Then in another tweet, I said, I hope you flip over your handlebars on your way to the entitlement
meeting and he goes he goes that's a that's a threat of violence I go no it's
not a threat it's a wish at the hope that you yeah and I go have fun I go
keep comparing cycling in some crazy way to the struggle right you white
privilege twat yeah and then he and then he blocked me so another guy was coming
after me I found out this guy I go to his Twitter feed he's got a goddamn thing
on the moth, I'm like, this guy's a fucking performer.
Another guy who's written several popular
cycling books started coming after me.
And I was like, you know what?
Once I started doing the explanation thing,
where was it posted though?
Twitter, everything was Twitter.
But who was the account that all these cyclists are following?
Oh, it's like a community.
I didn't even know that.
So they were all like, it got traction
because of this one guy and these other cyclists chimed in.
I don't know if they know.
So I sent out like five because it got to a point where it was like this is not me arguing with trolls
This is me
Telling people that I work in an industry with in some way that I didn't say what this guy is saying
I said and he's he's leaving pieces of this out and
I sent like a couple tweets to one of them explaining it and then I was like, you know what?
I'm done. I've officially now been trolled on Twitter
by the extreme left and the extreme right.
Everybody acted the same.
Everybody threatened to try to affect my work
and my well -being.
Everybody acted unreasonably.
Everybody was demeaning in one way or another
and I was like, I'm fucking done.
I just don't react well to that.
I'm not the guy that can go on Twitter and go,
I'll ignore it.
I can't do it.
So I will post to it through my Instagram.
For some reason, shit doesn't get like that on Instagram.
I don't really know why but it just doesn't and that's it. It's like you know, you'll you'll get updates that way from me
But I'm done. I'm not doing personal interaction anymore with anybody. I just can't do it and I apologize to the people that were actually sad
The two people that cared but you know like there were some fans that were like the joy of Joderos on Twitter
Thank you. There were fans. There were a couple fans are like do that sucks man. I think you're funny
I like your feed and whatever and I'm like, so you know, but it's like yeah the fucking
Crazy people are just so much louder of course than the rational people and I just I don't like being in that environment
It doesn't make me feel good. I hear you so
So that was the but wait, why did I tell that whole story?
Because I got true. Oh you yes, why was off Instagram? Yeah, we're going to scary stuff. Oh
Joe scary stuff. Yes
And you said you you said oh, oh the now I oh Jesus Christ wow wow
Uh, Joe Skiers, another video game this week, uh, for you Nintendo Switch players out there, or the people on Steam, I think you can give this on your PC and I think you can get on PS4 and stuff.
Shovel Knight.
Treasure Trove.
I love the name Shovel Knight.
Treasure trope.
Fantastic.
Fantastic game.
Uh, as, as true a, a, a homage to the eight -bit side -scrolling classics of Nintendo.
as you will ever get. It plays like it. It sounds like it. It looks like it.
It's a fucking blast. It's great getting the different
magics that you can use. And the treasure trove edition has different
versions of the quest with different characters that you defeat through the game.
So you get a ton of content for like 30 bucks. Go buy it.
It's download only on the Switch. I don't know if hard copies exist for the other
consoles, but it is a wonderful fantasy video game.
What's some I guess there's some higher elements. There's a
You fight monsters and shit, but anyway check it out. You'll like it
All right, I
I don't really have anything
That's fun. We're sorry 38 minutes in we haven't even talked about the movie yet, so all right
Well, I did see Darren Aaronovsky's mother. I
Want to say briefly here at the beginning Darren Aaronovsky's a one of the ultimate hit hit or
Mr. Rectors. I fucking love Black Swan, one of my favorite movies of that year.
Wrestler was my favorite movie of its year and it's one of my favorite films.
Recommend for a dream, I don't see myself ever watching it again but it's certainly a
technically fantastic movie. Yeah. But we're talking about a guy who clearly has some major
issues with women. I would say. You think you think he's got issues with women or do you think he's
treatment of Alan Burston in particular and recommend for a dream and then also Jennifer Connolly
asked to ask Dildos saying for example just tormenting these women. Black Swan really torments Nally
Porman. Here's my question though and this will apply to mother but you see that as you see that as
a woman issue or you see that because I took the poor treatment of the female character
and mother as his coming to woman's defense and saying this is what we do to mother earth
and win out to some extent, but when he in that five minute scene where we're watching everyone
kick the shit out of Jennifer Lawrence, I was like this cross is over into some sort of
say it a masochism. Okay, mother and it is just girlfriend. If you're going out with Jennifer
Lawrence. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Oh, Christ. She's, I mean, something's going on. She's David O 'Russell
as well, uses her all the time and there's like a 30 -year -age difference. There's a lot of, I have a
mother if there's even a point of doing so is Jennifer Lawrence is living with
Javier Bardem. He's a writer who's got writer's block. He seems impotent. Javier
Bardem is 30 years older than Jennifer Lawrence never mentioned. No, they
mentioned it. Okay. Yeah. Michelle Fyfer when they when they come in GCC go
she got she's so much older than you. I recounted the entire plot of mother to
both my girlfriend and the writers room that I work in and nobody could believe that
was the whole movie, but it is.
Sure.
Basically it's, they live together at Harris and then eventually Michelle Fyfer kind
of treat it like a halfway house and move in, they start treating it like it's their own
and then eventually lots of people start treating this house like it's their own and things get
more and more surreal from there.
I've seen it mostly compared to Rosemary's baby and repulsion to amazing horror movies
both by Roman Polansky, which is obviously another issue, but to compare this movie to
those two to me is absolute heresy.
They are classics of horror and I thought this movie was embarrassing, frankly.
Okay. So I will tell you this. I went into the movie not expecting to like it.
Yeah. I did read Jennifer Lawrence's explanation of the film before I went in
and it was a great help. It let me know beforehand this is not going to be a
horror movie. I will say this it's the most mis -market in movie I've ever seen.
It actually makes me mad at Darren Arunovsky that they like it because he is a guy
that gets say in things and Warner Brothers is very behind the picture. It's
Like, don't market it to people this way,
because it's not what I saw it today.
I finally saw the trailer for Mother
and it was like, get ready in this theater,
in a Kitchcock style marketing.
Like in two weeks, the movie that'll fuck you up forever.
Yeah.
It is not that.
No.
So I thought her explanation was very insightful.
And she said, look, it's about the world.
It's about mankind.
It's about the way we treat Mother Nature.
So knowing that little bit when I went in and then learning after the fact made me look at it through a different lens.
It made it make sense to I was like, okay, this isn't a movie that this isn't this is an absurdist play basically right on film about the way we the way people the way we act the way we conquer things and steal things and and claim it to be our own and show no respect for it.
and then she's mother nature.
She's being oddly patient
throughout the entire movie with these people
decimating her house,
which when you're watching it is strange
and then you realize, oh wait,
no, that's actually a pretty brilliant commentary.
Like, that's mother nature.
Like, mother nature is like, can you please stop
until she freaks out and snaps
and causes like a fucking earthquake to happen,
which does happen in the movie when she freaks out.
It seemed to me like a off, off, off, off, broadway play.
I would have seen by a girl I was dating when I was 22 years old, just moved to New York.
I thought it was embarrassing and stupid, and so the next day, you know, people were like,
oh, it's supposed to be a mother nature.
I also heard it's supposed to be about religion, because he just said no.
and I like Noah, way more than most people.
I like Darren Aronofsky's Noah.
But it was just not, okay, if it is about Mother Nature,
if it is about religion, whatever, fine.
You have to look at it as a movie.
Is it entertaining?
Is it, do I care about what happens from scene to scene?
and the answer to all these questions is the biggest no of all time. I saw it opening night
there was 30 people in the audience, 10 left immediately, 10 left around the midpoint
and then everyone else left by the time they stopped Jennifer Lawrence for five minutes.
I will say this. And Ripter closed off and ate her baby, then everybody else left. And I was like,
you know, I wish I'd fucking left with them. But if people are gonna leave two hours into a movie
We like this where you're still thinking,
well, maybe I'll find out what's happening at the end,
even though you really don't.
No, you do though.
I say, I don't agree that you don't find it.
Here's what I, let me say something.
All right.
I think, look, for as much as we complain
about the quality of films on this podcast
and people doing things by rote and whatever,
I've got to take my hand off to Warner Brothers
being a studio that big, getting behind a movie that feels so much like a surrealist French film from 1965 or something like that.
You know, so it's like, I am shocked that this is a studio film, I'm shocked.
If this was a little indie film, it would be wonderful.
I mean, for me, I was actually kind of enjoying it for the first half.
through my own reading of it.
I saw it the Thursday before it opened.
I was not, I hadn't read anything about it.
I was looking at it as a interpretation
of dating a narcissist or being married to a narcissist
who everyone tells him he's so great, et cetera.
And then you're nothing in his eyes.
And I thought that was kind of interesting.
Then when everybody starts kind of moving into their house
and then Kristen Wigg is an agent,
Yeah, I guess in it. Yeah, and all these people keep coming in. Then I was like, okay, well, this is a very niche movie
About how when you're dating somebody famous or in the entertainment industry all these people just start showing up at your house
Right, and suddenly you have to like
Be friends with these people that you hate which is how I really take the entertainment industry
I have to engage on a daily basis and be friendly with people that I hate and wish
harm upon.
And then I was kind of into it at that point, but I thought, this isn't a movie for America.
This is a movie for like a very small portion of the entertainment.
It's not, yeah, it's look, it's not, it's, it's, but I don't even think that's what he was
intending.
Well, my interpretation of it.
No, I think that that is a commentary in it, but I think, well, he, so he dated Rachel
Vice he was married to Rachel right but so that's how I started to read it was like now I dated this
Or I was married to this very famous woman and I lost myself
I
Think the fame is a comment was a commentary in it about God
I think Harvey Harvey are Bardam. I don't know if I'm saying you're right. Harvey are bradam. Yeah, I felt like his character was
was both God and
man kind. Okay. And I took that as God saying, I love you, but worship me. I love you, but worship me.
I have to, I love you, but I have to turn my back on you. I love you, but I have to tend to all
these other people. Right. You know, and you're sitting there going, God, why are you doing this to me?
Like you're supposed to be, you're supposed to be dead. But then when Jennifer Lawrence is like you
At the very end when he rips her heart out,
Temple of Doom style, she goes,
you don't love me, you love that I love you.
Right.
How does that factor into a view of religion or mother earth?
Well, I think that's an interesting comment here.
Well, again, I think he's duly God and mankind.
And what I took from that was,
that's an interesting commentary on God to me.
You know?
You just love that everybody worships you.
You don't love us. Look at all the tragedy in the world. Look how terrible the world is.
You don't do anything nice for us. You just love that we worship you. So that's the God side of it.
So this was like the Al Pacino says in devil's advocate. Yeah, it's absolutely landlord. Yeah, exactly.
Okay. And then the mankind side of that to me was was was was nature was like this bullshit about like
how people say they love the planet and we say we love people and we say we love beauty and nature
or whatever, and then we destroy it constantly.
And to me, it's Mother Nature saying,
like, you just love that I'd give you whatever you need
whenever you need it.
You don't really love me.
You don't really respect me.
If you did, you wouldn't be building these fucking malls
and bombing places and doing all these other things.
So that's how I took that.
There's also a really, Natasha Legero turned me
on to one of the interpretations of the Ed Harris
and Michelle Pfeiffer characters,
which was that they represented Adam and Eve.
So they were the first two people led into the Garden of Eden.
She takes the forbidden fruit.
She takes the glass thing off the shelf.
It breaks.
Right.
He shuts them out, literally out of the Garden of Eden.
He boards it up.
He's like, you'll never get in here ever again.
Right.
There are two sons show up.
One slays the other one, can't enable.
Right?
Yeah.
And then the descendants and ancestors of Adam and Eve start becoming greater
and greater and greater and greater, until finally you end up with a very sort of, you
know, even the house, like even the whole thing with the house, like he lost everything
in the fire, like to me, that was a commentary on, again, nature, like we take these beautiful
settings, he goes at the beginning, he goes, she goes, I can't get a cell signal and he
goes, yeah, we like it that way. And it's like, so here's this guy that's like, yeah,
we've like gone so far out of our way to live in this beautiful, secluded little piece
of paradise, yet I'm going to let these people come in because they like me and literally
kill my baby, you know what I mean?
So but here's the thing, you know, like get out is an amazing commentary on racism, but
it's also a fucking funny and exciting and suspenseful horror movie.
You know, like Magic Mike is an amazing movie about capitalism and how we use people to
make money.
Right.
And then it's also extremely entertaining.
Even to me.
A heterosexual man.
Well, that's how I feel about hostile.
I think hostile is a tremendous hard movie and also a fantastic commentary on how different
people use each other in one another in different ways.
I couldn't agree more.
Yeah, this to me felt like one of the most miserable viewing experiences I've ever had
So that at the end I could go oh, okay. I guess it was about religion or I guess it was about
Mother Nature fine and if if people if critics feel smart
Picking that out great. I still can't imagine you enjoyed that two hours watching the movie because I sure sell did
I look it was a bumpy ride it was certainly something that that there were moments where I was like
I want to stick this out. I don't know then there were moments where I was very invested
Then there were moments where I was like I got to see how this ends because I think I might know where
This is going right and then leaving and driving home and and thinking about it the more I thought about the more
I was like wow I really think that was a brilliant
Metaphor that was a really great piece of work, but
But, it's not a goddamn popcorn movie.
Look, I saw it, I saw it, it was my first movie pass.
Movie that I saw, by the way.
You know, it's like, I might have been a little more pissed
or a little bit pissed.
Had you spent 16, 50 or whatever.
Well, yeah, 17 bucks and then another 10 on candy
and so it and whatever, I would have been like,
I just spent 30 bucks, like what the fuck?
It's, so you know, it's like, look,
I get the goddamn
Cassavetes and Warner Herzog box sets over there. It's like are those movies that I want to watch over and over and over again
Not really right movies that I really enjoy and respect the hell out of absolutely. So yeah, you know, it's like
It's not a glad a challenging movie is getting made
Well, that's the biggest takeaway to me is that
It's not just that a challenging movie got made Warner Brothers
Let Darren and look Darren Aaronowski is a popular guy. He's not fucking Scorsese. No, he's not, you know, you know
He's in that sort of Alexander Payne camp where it's like it could all go away if he fucks up royally and they still got behind him
By the way, I don't know if it's in a preview for Alexander Payne's new movie. Yes, downsizing. Yeah, looks interesting
I think it looks terrible, but maybe it'll be great. I mean it looks terrible. Well, I hate he lost me with the last
I hated the descendant and sentence sucks and I did I couldn't get through Nebraska
Yeah, and I wanted to because I really love Will forte and I really love Bruce Dern
It's fine. I couldn't get through the goddamn movie. I was so bored and I was like what happened?
Downsizing look like it might have some of that bite that like election and about Schmidt had again with some very funny
Parts, you know, but those were very real movies and downsizing looks like a fucking
and you know, parody of a Twilight Zone episode.
I think, I have a feeling there's more to meet the,
that meets the eye with that trailer, you know what I mean?
But we'll see.
But my point is, you know, I was reading a thing
about the guy that, I can't remember his name,
the director, the director, the original Dracula,
the Belle of the Ghosty one, Todd Browning.
Yeah, yeah, his follow up to that,
because they were like, we love you, you're a genius.
What do you wanna do?
He's like freaks, makes freaks,
gets banned and just literally ends his career.
Yeah, so I like that we live in a time now where even if people don't understand the
film, a major studio is behind a guy like Aaron asked him being like, your career is not
going to end over this.
So don't worry about it.
I got you back.
However, nobody was behind Noah, which to me is a superior movement.
Noah didn't look good to me.
It just looked like gods of Egypt or one of those like kind of shitty like Moses goes in a real kind of weird interesting direction
But I think like those rock monsters in it. They're very like dark crystal Jim Henson. Yeah, the rock monsters coming out
I don't know where but
For me two of the best movies of the last 20 years are black swan and the rustler and those were also
Extremely profitable movies on a very low budget, right, so they'll always hope
that happens again but yeah you only get two or three mothers before you're out
of the business entirely. Yeah I'm not saying he's got a huge bomb and
everyone walked out of the theater. I'm not I'm not saying he's got free reign
to do whatever that's what it's not like he's he's not Scorsese he's not one of
these guys where it's like what do we need to do to get it done you know but
he's a respected guy obviously and he's he's had some Oscar nods and stuff like
like that, so it's like, I really like the film.
Now, that all being said, do I ever want to watch it again?
No, but not because I don't think it's good
or entertaining in any way.
I found it to be a horribly accurate commentary
on humankind and it made me terribly depressed.
Yeah, I left it because the day that I did the thing
where I was like, I'm not doing Twitter anymore guys,
sorry, like I can't take these people anymore.
They're fascists on all sides. I can't do it.
That day was when I went from that right into mother. Yeah. And then you're sitting there and you're like,
this is what people do. People are terrible. They would eat a baby.
You know, so it was it was very fucking depressing. So I don't know emotionally. I could see them.
It was kind of like a like watching a radio hit album. I was just like, when am I gonna?
When am I gonna be the right kind of sad for this?
Yeah, I didn't need the reminder that everyone in the world is dog shit
I guess, but I'll also say this I saw the trailer for American horror story the new season which is
So stupid looking and so on the nose. It is a terrible fucking show. It has never been good
It was pretty good for most of the first season. I like the first is it has sucked after that
But the ending of the first season was literally a beetle juice rip off, which is problematic
for many reasons.
It has never been good since then.
It tries way too hard to shock.
It tries way too hard to be sexy.
It tries way too hard to get in your bones, and it fails on all fronts, and I hate the fucking
show.
And you want the trailer for the new season and it's like
It's literally just them being like Trump got elected and then one guy being like the revolution begins
I can now lead the sheep and then another lady having a nervous breakdown because she can't deal with it whenever and it's like
Guys, I don't need my commentaries to be that spot on. Yeah, I don't need like the trailer of the season to
You literally have a news thing in it that goes, Donald Trump is the president, and
it's like, get a little more creative.
So again, this is why I like mother.
I thought he did a good job of creating a strange scenario that gave a very interesting
commentary, because it could have been way more on the nose, and it would have been very
stupid.
The other Adam and Eve thing is the rib when he's over the toilet, his ribs exposed.
It got the very rare F rating from CinemaScore, the audience polling system.
Like very few movies in the history of time got an F and it received an F.
Yeah, you can't.
This is not for...
No.
This is not, you know what I mean?
This is like when...
But I like this shit and it wasn't for me either.
You know?
If you took that Sting ukulele album that he did, whatever the fuck that thing was where
You did all like the Baroque music and you yeah, and you put it out and we were like it's the new police record
Sure people would be like this is the war. It's nice. It was not marketed properly. I agree
Joe wrap this up for us. I have to pay and
the show and
Folks, I'm signing off you can find me at the Patrick Walsh
Twitter and Instagram. I'm still on Twitter. I'm putting up with the people
have a good week. Folks, come follow me on Instagram. Like I said, I'll post to Twitter
through Instagram, but Instagram is where the action's at. And quite frankly, I'm
going to get my damn Instagram numbers up. So come follow me over there. What else is
going on? This comes out tomorrow, which means I will be... Well, you know what? Not a lot
happening right now for the next month or so. I'm just kind of in LA. So go read the Penn
House column. If you do, I hope you like it. If you like it, great. That's great. I hope
I hope you do. It's called you let me down every month in Penthouse and that's it. We'll
see you again in hell.
That was a HitGum Podcast.