Do you know where!
Folks,
Brooks, it's we'll see you with the two who do the review on the moon.
Woo.
How you doing, everybody?
Good to see you.
Good to see you, Joe, and welcome back to we'll see you in hell today on the show.
We're going to hell.
We're going right into the mouth of hell.
We're raising hell with the new hell razor.
I don't love this new thing of like hey, we're making an entirely new scream.
And we're just going to call it screams and now you have two movies called scream.
Yeah, I don't like calling a movie hell razor when it is not in any way a remake of the original hell razor.
But that's what it's called hell razor.
It makes the original hell razor 1987 and it makes the new one hell razor 2022.
And the original doesn't deserve to be changed like that at this point.
See what I'm saying?
I see exactly what you're saying.
We will get into it deeper, but I will say before we get to the review,
just to hint foreshadow, if you will, yeah.
This movie continues in another ever going or evolving rather confusing trend ongoing ongoing.
That's the word where they've now made a product that's even farther away from the source material.
Then the original hell razor was, which was fairly close in areas, but very far off in other areas,
even though Clyde Barker himself adapted it from his book.
But this now it gets to a point where it's like you're like it's like the it's like multiplicity.
It's like this is now the copy of the copy of the copy and you're like, yeah, guys, like there's obviously like connective tissue here.
But this is way like like it's just it's odd to me.
It's a strange strange thing that we that that that they do with these legacies and franchises.
By the end it felt like there was more of a home alone influence than anything else.
It's setting traps.
This by the way, I mean,
well, have you noticed that's a trend this home alone up.
Yeah, like grow.
They did it in a Rambo.
Yeah, the last Rambo.
They did it in a pocket.
Lipto becomes home alone at some point.
The last James Bond or one of the last Quantum of solace.
I believe becomes home alone at some point.
They literally go to an abandoned house and set up traps.
James Bond sets up traps.
It's the end of equalizer too.
So is he lures everybody back to the coastal beach town.
Right.
Because it's been evacuated because of the hurricane and he sets wild like death traps for everybody.
That's how it takes down Pedro Pascal's team.
Yeah, it's just become a big screenwriting crutch like.
And then so then at the end, we do the home alone ending.
It's just an option now.
God, everything sucks.
Jesus, God, everything is terrible.
And then to me, what really starts to fuck with me is if everybody was in agreement that everything's terrible, great.
And when you talk to people in person, that's generally what you get.
But when you hop on Twitter.
And you see all these glowing reviews of something that you know in your heart is garbage.
And everyone knows is garbage, which is a lot of what Twitter is.
It starts to make you feel like you're being gaslit for Christ's sake.
I'm like, do I just not like anything anymore, but you realize, no, it's just not good.
No, because that's the, that's the real bummer is.
It's the algorithm is now such a part of our lives that so much of what you see on social media.
That gives accolades to something and also so much what you see of what gives criticism and hatred at something.
It's not even real.
It's designed to keep you in the algorithm and to make you a part of this.
It's so insane.
Like, God, it's just a terrible fate.
I just keep saving my money.
So I could, like, I just keep saving, saving, saving.
So eventually I can buy the biggest house with the most land as a full cash buy.
Yeah.
And then just go work at whatever local came art, Walmart equivalent they have at the door.
And, and to pay for my health insurance every month and my property tax, which trust me where I move will be six dollars a month.
I just got, I got mine two weeks ago and I have not been able to open it because it goes up so much every year.
And it is a terrifying amount of money every time.
Yeah, it's brutal, dude.
It's at a point where I'm like, there was a time where I dreamed of buying something in New York.
And I'm like, I would never purchase anything here because of the property tax.
The, dude, it's property tax.
It's HOA stuff.
It's every building now is a co -op where there's like a community board fee.
And the fee is like two grand a month.
Right.
For the rest of your life.
Like, fuck off, man.
Well, your friend there at the bar was telling me when I was in New York about that finders fee they have in New York.
If like if they show you a place that you wind up taking you owe them some thousand dollar fee years, that's crazy to me.
Jesus Christ.
That's your whole job.
Buy the buy.
Joe, I don't know.
I don't know if you saw this on my, and I just put it on my Instagram stories.
I rarely even look at Instagram anymore.
But because they don't show you your friends.
Yeah.
You get on there.
I scroll for 10 minutes.
I haven't seen a post from a single person.
I follow.
What are you doing?
Blair Saki, who's a good friend of mine.
A very funny comic.
You should.
It was so cheap.
So I say Saki.
Is it so cheap?
Oh, I don't know.
No, I just always assumed it was so cheap because she's Italian.
She's great.
Watch Blair if you can.
Her standards.
She's very funny.
But she.
She told me she unfollowed everybody on Instagram because she wanted to have Instagram.
And she did.
But the feed was like, it was too much.
And she was like, yeah, dude, when you do that, like they fuck with you.
They're like, they're like, oh, you're not following anybody.
So your post isn't going to really get seen.
Like.
It's the manipulation is insane.
It's insane.
Anyway, sorry.
Go ahead.
Okay.
So every day.
I get.
You know, two or three realtor flyers in my mailbox.
I famously told the story of the Glenn Schellhammer.
Realty when the psychotic neighbor I have.
Was screaming Glenn Schellhammer.
I'm going to rape your mother because he thought that I was Glenn Schellhammer.
Because he had a flyer in his mailbox that he thought I looked like this guy.
Glenn Schellhammer.
Glenn Schellhammer is a great name.
It is, especially for a realtor.
Glenn Schellhammer.
I'm a realty.
How you doing?
I was surprised.
Realty.
All back to the last episode.
I get.
In my.
And I'll be able to show you here over zoom, Joe.
But hopefully you caught it on my Instagram, folks.
In my mailbox.
Not wrapped.
Not sealed.
This.
I'm just going to show it to you.
The.
Picture of a fully nude man in the in the in the burnt, rentalled style.
Hand covering his genitals, of course.
It's says not your daddy's realtor.
And the back.
Just a standard realtor flyer.
Just as if the,
as if the front didn't happen.
This man.
And I'm just going to give you his first name is Todd.
works at at Shell Hammer. So part of the Shell Hammer real estate group and I got to tell you if this
awakens the the demon and the psycho that lives below me the stalker I'll be very upset because I
got to imagine him opening this and being like I need to fix this neighborhood go to town taxi driver style.
It blew my mind not your daddy's realtor it's sexual. I was going with my friend my friend
were like so is it like a like you don't live in West Hollywood is it a gay it's not a gay thing I said
daddy is very much a a goes both way term now you know I I've been called daddy just and start
joining the dating pool again I think daddy is troubling but I like it I think daddy has become
more of a gay term at this point though perhaps I think I have a friend who has a son and he said his
son was talking about there there was a group of boys at the school who were straight boys but
they have a gay boyfriend yeah and the gay boyfriend it keeps calling all of them daddy I mean I can't
base the entire culture on this one circumstance but yeah I was laughing very hard at this kid I was
like that's really funny that that kid does that yeah anyway I I was called daddy by a 33 -year -old
woman the other night I was like well so what that I have you when I was seven is this one you had sex
with to the Jenga yes okay but yeah it's like you know daddy is kind of cool and fun but then there's
also a part of me because I'm going through a midlife crisis that wants to go hey I don't know if I'm
at a daddy level you know it hurts a little bit I can't imagine calling a woman mommy mommy no you
flip it it does not work that you're suddenly Dennis Hopper and Blue Velvet if you start calling
her mommy unless if if like the Hispanic version of it like mommy with the eye or poppy like
if we got culturally appropriate you got to say it like that yeah and I got to tell you the brown
face I put on doesn't have did you see I've never watched the Great British Bake Off
but everyone loves it and helps calming it is whatever did you see the photos of their Mexican
week that they did yeah they're they're wearing the Clint Eastwood few dollars more to thing they're
wearing giant purple sombreros England is England's wild they really talk down to us but they got
their own shit going on I tweeted the other day I just found a wig and a rant and a book of
Randy jokes where should I start my sitcom Canada or England England you go through those sitcoms
I mean you take the office and peep show out of the mix it's like a now in partridge it's like every
sitcom yeah every sitcom is a guy with a wig yeah well you are dick jokes it's like in extra season two
when he gets on that show with the little curly perm wig that he's wearing it's but I mean guy in a
wig playing like a old woman it's a guy playing an old woman and then it's like every joke is like
I'm watching I'm watching it's called like Mrs. Bakers boys yesterday yeah and the show was it
before a red dwarf came on it would yeah well these things they used to come on PBS these
show are you being served remember that one yes well faulty towers was a great one I looked forward
to faulty towers but they had some shit on there this this one of the jokes this thing the lady goes the
the neighbor comes in an all black and the and the man and the woman's dress and wig goes
did did somebody die was it your husband and she goes it wasn't my husband but my husband lost his
willy that's the joke and then the the other lady goes the man lady goes he goes oh he's he's
dying piece by piece isn't he and then the other way he goes not his willy his brother named willy
like this is the joke in a renowned British sitcom yeah they do it's always like well I wish we could
have as sophisticated comedy as the brits but you're you're really talking about maybe four projects
and Americans have four great projects too yes doing that well I saw Patrice O 'Neal once who
was a friend and Brendan Burns who was also a friend Brendan Burns is an Australian comic but he
lived in England at the time yeah Brendan I witnessed Brendan Burns in a green room at the just
for last rest will tell Patrice O 'Neal that English comedy was superior and I watched Patrice O 'Neal
scream shut the fuck up with with a vehement I've never I mean it was it was like a protester yeah
and then he started going he said y 'all's comedy sucks dick and then he said coming to the stage
in Eagle Puss shut the fuck up it was yeah it was the most life ago he really reduced it to just
exactly what it was yeah I think what it is and and I'm a guy who's a big fan of a very certain strain
of mortifying embarrassment British comedy which is your partridge in the office and all that kind of
stuff they do that cringe comedy better than almost anybody absolutely beyond that I have very
little interest in it but I think what people fall for is the same reason that a woman with a British
accent is immediately very sexy women are very attracted to men with British accents it's just
something different so like they're giving you the same old willy jokes but the British accent makes
it seem sophisticated and I think a lot of people fall for that well there's the the one funny sketch
ever on Jimmy Glick the sketches on Jimmy Glick are terrible oh man when Joe was out here I had this
best a click DVD and and we had to shut it off because I was like oh no so this this guy only only
thrives in the interview format where he is the best that's it yeah but the one funny sketch
they did was the thing where they spoof the English sitcom and they're the plastic surgeons who are
also drunks it's like ad fab except it's plastic surgeon yeah and then they'll it's doing the
critic spiel so and so says this so says this and then one of them says so and so says it's English
so it must be smart and funny it's like that's a real fucking like jab I thought those are very funny
jab but um is absolutely fabulous funny yeah it is it's very yeah it's very depraved I like
ad fab quite a bit I look I should give that a go it's funny Craig Ferguson said to me why I said if
you could only I was a radio show and I said if you could only see American television or English
television for the rest of your life what would you pick and he said American and I said you're crazy
and I started naming like all the great English comedy shows and he goes yeah yeah but you that's
you only see the good ones right see all the other way and when I was in Ireland doing a festival a lot
of English comics told me that they prefer the American office to the English office which I thought
was bad shit yeah well it's the same thing as I was saying about how we're kind of smitten by
British people the they the appeal of something different when I went over to I guess well
was Greece was my honeymoon we we wound up spending like a day with this couple that was really cool
and nice and they were from the UK and they were speaking very they were they had great taste but they
were speaking really reverently about sitcoms here that are generally considered shit and by the way
I would lump two broke frozen with that category but they were talking about big bang theory like it
was the best and everything and and good for them but I think it's the same thing they watched the big
bang theory and it has a different level of entertainment to them because it's it they feel like
they're learning about America right whereas when we watch a British show you can't help but also feel
like you're a little more intelligent and you're learning about another culture even though you're not
really sure sure yeah I will say this about they're less snobby the the British weirdly are less
snobby they like dumb American shit yeah that's it they like it but yeah yeah that is true that is true
they British shit comes to also they they go into weird I mean this is a compliment they go into weird
places way more than American sitcoms do and I'm talking back like you look at like the young ones
yeah that would have never been a show on the US you look at I think they tried to do an American
version didn't really work peep show but with the leaky actually yeah they tried to do it right but also
too um you know like like the like the like like Ian McLean wait who Ian McKellen that's
Magneto yeah yeah Ian McKellen did a sitcom like recently and I'm talking like an on video multi -cam sitcom
where he watched the first season it was kind of good it was funny were they're like the gay couple
only live in the big dark house or yeah yeah even that was like a daring thing and like and I was
like man it's just different over there like Ian that'd be like if if if like here if like Christopher
Plummer was suddenly starring on a sitcom you know right very odd here you know right who I think
was English originally but was he Plummer Plummer I think I think we just think of him as English because
like he had always planned those parts I don't know he got cancelled he got me too no he didn't
you're thinking of frankly angel I'm thinking of Franklin jelly you're right yeah Langella out at the
yeah yeah you know so we were I'm I'm trying to assemble a creative endeavor and we've been talking
about people that have been very exciting to me and I feel comfortable mentioning this now but we've
been we were we're getting close to talking to Bill Murray wow and I was so excited about this
and then they literally literally released an article yesterday that was like Bill Murray is over
here's why and he's cancelled he's cancelled he's fine they all got settled he paid the woman the
hundred thousand dollars apparently it's all fine well I know he when I read what it was it said he
straddled a younger woman and kissed her while wearing the mask while wearing the protective mask
now oh boy in the grand scheme of things I know you're not supposed to compare it's like okay and Bill
Murray is a notorious jokester on set but yeah the woman was uncomfortable I understand why
he paid her the money okay and apparently the shoot resume same day Gina Davis talked about him being
really awful to her on the set a quick change he had some massage device that he insisted on using
honor when he first met her and she demanded repeatedly that he not do it and then yelled at her in
front of the crew Lucy Liu has a big issue with him on the set of Charlie's Angels so they're just saying
like nobody's gonna risk it anymore apparently he's in and I I wish you hadn't told him to do all this
stuff Joe apparently he's also in the world's greatest beer run with Zac Efron which looks terrible it
got like a 14 % or so yeah so bad but I was talking to my buddy about how I was kind of bummed out
because like we were getting ready to make the like call Bill Murray and my friend was like yeah he's
in this movie like five scenes as a British bartender doing a very bizarre bad British accent and I'm
like if they're not using Bill Murray and the trailer for this thing like he must be on the outs
there are some things about to come out well I mean it sounds like most of these even the straddle
kissing I realized that's I understand why that's wrong obviously fully these these sound more like
he's obnoxious in an asshole versus like he's like assaulting people I guess the straddle is
considered an assault but yeah so I don't know maybe he's look he he did apologize for that thing
and it's like but I don't know I don't know anymore I don't want to you know I'm afraid to
say one way or the other well yeah he said I did something I thought was funny and she didn't
think it was funny and you know his thing is like walking into a group of people and being like oh that's
a pretty necklace and he bites it and then you know like he's just that guy like Rodney Dangerfield
and Katty Shepherd you walk in you're taking people's hats off and putting them on your head and blah
blah blah and I think we've just hit a point where all that stuff is not cool anymore you're kind of
just supposed to stay on your lane and go through your day and you know it's gonna it never should have
gone to this point obviously it's never okay to straddle a woman who doesn't want you to straddle
of course yeah it's it's just a shame I think a lot of these old guys and I am not excusing it in
any way because obviously they could easily educate themselves I think they grew up in a world
without intimacy coordinators and all this and it was like if you got a boner on the actresses leg
you laughed about it and blah blah blah and they try to carry that into today's society and
immediately their 50 -year career is shut down like Langella had a problem with the intimacy coordinators
he was like if I want to reach up and grab the actresses butt I should be allowed to I'm supposed
to be mimicking sexuality and everybody was like no fraction well but look that's a tough that's
a tough call and I'm not saying it was right grew up that way he's a method actor and actors think
they exist in a whole nother plane so yeah I mean I get it but even but even beyond that it's like
if you're saying I did a I did a we shot a short film years ago called cheat and I had to have a
second it was a comedic sexy but I have a sexy unit well actually no that was all very choreographed
we were like okay now we have to make it look like we're doing it this way so like you tell me like
is this okay and yeah but so so that was my one experience so I can't speak with real experience here
you know the part of it the the only part of it that drives me nuts and with like the
Langella thing for instance this is a David O 'Russell movie correct no no it's Mike no it's Mike
I'm wrong I'm very wrong what's the it's not it's the TV show he was on the Mike what's his
face it's the new Mike what's his name show the guy that did all the fucking horror things on Netflix
midnight mask my planet yes I think it was it was a house of usher remake with Langalla as as
that's right yeah so yeah so I mean look there's there's just so many cooks in the kitchen with
something like this I'm not saying Frank Langella was right or okay by the way Joe have you seen too
many cooks the internet video when it came out yeah yeah okay just making sure it's all time class
yeah it's very good but but it's like sometimes these directors go like okay guys just just like okay
so here's an example Oliver Stone if you watch the bonus features on the doors right yeah
they show Meg Ryan talking about like being in the movie and Oliver's approach and all this stuff
and they show the clip where she her tit falls out then she covers it in the it's in the actual movie
and then it cuts to Oliver Stone he's like yeah that's that was a bummer that she did that because
you know it's like we were she just wasn't embracing the spirit of what we were trying to do which
was free and so my point is is I'm not saying that's he was saying it was a bummer that she just took one
to doubt no no that she that when her breasts came out naturally and it was unplanned yeah she had
covered it oh I got he was saying you know we were all trying to go for this let's just be here and
be in this and whatever yeah I'm not saying Oliver Stone is correct what I'm saying though is
is these concepts are coming from all angles during a production and I don't know Mike Flanagan but if
he says to the actors go for it have a passionate scene get into it make it real and Frank Langella
jellic grabs a woman's butt that's very different to me then if it's a very choreographed safe space
thing and then he does that I'm not saying either is right I'm just saying that it bothers me that
we don't hear from all these other surrounding entities that are part of the production
when this sort of thing happens why am I only hearing from Frank Langella about this
well yeah you you heard from the actress and then you heard from Langella and Langella did not
apologize really he was like sorry you know that you know that's what I do and that's I'm an actor
and I'm not gonna step down but you know I wonder I haven't dealt really with an intimacy coordinator
I've shot a couple sex scenes in my day but they were all relatively tame and everyone was
respectful and cool but like you work in them you mean no no no no no oh oh when I was at
always sunny we did some behind the scenes stuff and with there was a sex scene with Dennis and a
few different things that we did can't loosely directed kind of stuff but they were always it was
just a girl in a broad everybody was nice it is the most awkward fuck being in it is the most awkward
fucking thing and like I said the one I did was comedic but the girl you know she was like I was in
my underwear and she was in like a under underpants and she wore like pasties on her nipples and it is
so not erotic in any way and awkward and fucking weird and like you know the whole time you're like
because I was like yeah I would really love and I don't know why none of these big magazines
has maybe they haven't I missed it but I want an lengthy in -depth interview with an intimacy
coordinator I want to know what goes on and I want to know if they do things like if I was an intimacy
coordinator I would probably be like tell the guy to jack off before the scene you know like I
wonder if that stuff gets discussed like you can't be walking in with a loaded gun and then grinding
margo roby old I well you you but you could never say that as an intimacy coordinator now because
somebody could turn that around on you and go correct I believe I was told to masturbate yeah
and then the and then why wasn't the woman told that right aren't her feelings valid and it's
just it's just such a fucking gauntlet to run what if she were to leak all her my leg it's such a gauntlet
when I was in the college you want to talk about something I would never do now in a million years
with a fucking gun to my head when I was in college we had to do scene showcases in theater in my theater
class I was in a scene I did a scene with my partner her name was Kate she was very sweet
she played it was an old play one of these old Czech Kovian fucking things where I was the father
that was molesting his daughter or so she played the daughter not molesting she was grown I don't
know what that term is at that point yeah I don't know whatever it's still probably molesting the point
is though as we did this scene where I'm like coming on to my daughter uh -huh and she's like you
know the character is like sort of this this sort of buxom you know whatever and and the scene is that
the daughter does not care for you know but she feels pressured and whatever I forget what the
what how it ends but we would not care for her father coming on to her no she doesn't like him
okay but it's that's part of the the idea of the scene is that because of the time period she's
unable to refute his advances or else she'll be banished or I some shit like that I don't remember okay
me and Kate used to rehearse the god damn scene in my fucking
a bedroom at my apartment because it was like you needed privacy to do it just not because of
the nature of it because you had a rehearse the scene and there was no rehearse it and I remember
she would say to me like when we was just me and her working on it she'd be like you can go farther
with this like don't feel weird like you know like it's okay yeah and and I never did I felt awkward
the entire time but my point is is can you imagine a scenario in this day and age where you would
feel comfortable saying to somebody let's go into my private bedroom and rehearse the scene where
I play the dad who's trying to fuck you my daughter and no no that was a prank those whole thing
he was he was going in for scene studies and then fucking the girl it's it's and it was very
professional nothing bad happened or anything you know but my point is it's like it's fucking wild man
like like you know it's just wild when I think back to like so anyway I don't know it's just it's
just a wild memory to have amidst all this yeah yeah yeah yeah anyway she's suing me
folks let's get to the movie corner I love I'd love it if this recording was subpoenaed by a
court and they do play the entire thing from the start to the courtroom and everyone's just shocked
and then but then the upset in the courtroom is your honor we'd love to play you that audio
but it's behind a paywall yeah can we pull the jurors to get the $7 to listen to the podcast please
that's what gets I get off because of the paywall and then they come and burn me alive like
they're ready I saw I haven't seen much I I can't really focus I don't know if I talked about
this on the sole of movie corner I'm sorry if I did but I rewatched the quick and the dead
Sam Raimi's quick and the dead story about pets penis preuy agra
well couldn't be dead and quick it could be one or the other um there it is I think Sharon Stone is
very bad in this film I hate to say it but I think she's good in a sex pot role and beyond that
not check you know casino she's great yeah she's great at playing uh uh there's only
wrong with saying she's great at playing a disaster yeah some people are playing a bigger great you know
great to play in a mess but what can the day where she's the hero she doesn't really work for me um
it's it's fun to see de caprio and russell crow early early early in their stardom
you're getting a pre gladiator crow a pre titanic de caprio uh as like the kid
and it's a pretty fun western and the appeal of it really is Sam Raimi showing off with his
camera tricks gene hackman's basically doing a riff on his unforgiven character he's got some great
dialogue he's braiding it of course uh the supporting cast is pretty stacked and it's fun
to me what makes this stand out really is uh the crazy way Sam Raimi shoots all the action by the
end you're basically watching mic tycent's punch out it's just gunfight after gunfight various fun
matchups between two people and that's fun um the story's kind of cool too it all works but really at
the end when you got him like everyone who gets shot it puts like a giant circle through their head or
it blows their brains out or so you know he does all sorts of his cool evil dead type stuff a little
more controlled than it was in the evil dead of course but um yeah it's it's a fun movie you know a lot
of people call it their favorite Sam Raimi i've been seeing online a lot lately i don't get that
but uh i enjoyed it okay i don't understand the circle thing can you explain that
there's all these shots have you seen him quick in the dead no so like at the end let's say
Jean Hackman whips has gone out you know you do the the take three steps turn and shoot thing
when he shoots it'll take a complete circle out of the center of the man's head it's like from behind
you're looking at you're looking through the guy's head you know what i mean so it blows out the back of
his head it's got a clean head exactly oh hole right here yeah there's a lot of that like
somebody will put his hand out in a bullet hole will go through the hand and then there's a circle in it
you know it's a little Raimi shooting through it right zooming in on it and yeah okay uh i i love
when Raimi does that shit uh especially when he brings it to a big budget thing i don't know if he did
that to the new doctor strange i hope so but um i know a lot of people who hated that movie and a lot
of people who thought it was kind of cool i haven't seen it yet i i i've heard that it's just
it's like four marvel freaks yeah yeah like you know but like i'm which i'm not so no i'm only going to
do two because i haven't seen much either and i got to ration these out because i'm traveling and i
don't know how much more i'm going to see outside of stuff we need to review but uh i will both do two
i saw uh i saw the uh well yeah let me just now do these are a little fresher so a movie called the
children uh this is a horror movie actually presented by sam ramie ghost house pictures um
it's an english horror movie from i guess it's probably from about two thousand somewhere in there
uh not a bad little horror movie it's about a um christmas holiday gathering of two sisters
the sister the one sister goes with her husband and daughter who the husband is the stepdad to
and uh the daughter and then their child the what am i trying to say jesus christ there's there are two
sisters one of the sisters is married with two kids one of the kids is hers from a previous marriage
and one of the kids the younger one is hers from the current marriage she's in with this with the older
child stepdad they go to visit her sister for the holiday um her sister also is married and also has
her own kids and they're going to have this big three day sleepover for christmas or whatever it is
the visiting family the older kid the teenage daughter doesn't want to be there
there's a lot of contention between her and her stepdad there's also some weird
like undefined sexual energy between her and her uncle who's not her uncle by blood it's her
it's her her aunt is the one by blood it's her aunt's husband um there's just some general tension
all around through the family and some one of the kids becomes infected with something
some unknown substance or whatever and the children go crazy and start to do horrible things to the grown -ups
and that's your movie i mean that's basically what it is it's all right pretty suspenseful
there's some pretty cool kills uh there's some stuff that'll make your blood run
cold and overall it's a good little small budget horror movie that flew under the radar
um i recommend it it's a one location picture uh and it's a nice little study in a one -location
horror movie if you're interested in such a thing what does the name one more time the children
okay no wonder i didn't remember it bad title that's not it i don't think it's a bad title it's just
that a generic generic that a killer title it's not a killer time uh that's children yeah it's worth
it's worth a watch folks i really really looking here i really haven't seen much i saw i want to
shout out a couple stand -up specials i saw and really enjoyed the funniest of them i got to say
and i'm not going to shouldn't any stand -up yeah knickroll special little big boy uh very
became such a gifted sketch performer and of course i saw uh oh hello four times you know between
Broadway and la i loved it so much and i forgot really about his stand -up i had seen his first
special when i first moved to la i used to do them do sets around town and i always thought
they were funny but he's really good in this one the first 10 -15 minutes it's kind of like
you're waiting for it to start almost it's not nothing's really hidden for me but then it just really
took off i mean i i was laughing really hard at a lot of this stuff he has funny material and it
is performed in a very funny physical way he's a guy who utilizes his voice talents uh to help his
jokes at times but doesn't overdo it he's a great storyteller i enjoyed it very much him talking
about getting dumped and realizing that the breakup has been focused group with all of her friends
and you're the last one to find out about it that was obviously hitting me uh it was very
gang Wang was a comedian i was unfamiliar with uh he seemed to be a friend oh okay so you can do
in a mitch head berg impression didn't mind it clearly he's an influence but he's just got this
laid back i don't know if he is a stoner in real life or if that's just his vibe but his deliveries very
laid back stonerie and funny his material is funny he does a bit in this about how uh i think he's
reading to a kid or something and it sounds it sounds like e 40 lyrics and that bit had me laugh
and really hard as a big fan of e 40 i liked the show those are the two i've seen that really stood
out and i enjoyed uh i watched Sam morals which i thought was solid Tim Dylan's which was solid
and Pat Naswell's which was solid but those are the two that i thought were really kind of special lately
yeah those are all uh those are all good specials uh i didn't finish patents yet
um i liked Nick's quite quite a bit uh the mommy joke was so funny about how mean you are to
your mom yeah yeah uh you know the line that really made me laugh the hardest in Nick's special was
the the thing about steroids where he's like you know like he takes steroids in the weakest way
possible which it's like for his skin or whatever right and he's like i take steroids so my skin
doesn't whatever and he's like are you enjoying the date so far like he that that voice he does
is really funny yeah yeah um but i liked it quite a bit i didn't see Tim's yet
Tim's a buddy i should have watched that by now and i didn't but i really liked Sam's quite a bit
um i preferred him in like a unuh unhinged riffing setting than a formal stand -up setting i mean he's
they're off the cuff he's fewer funnier but his stand -up set good too i like that yeah yeah i like uh
sam's is i've always sam's a good as a very good friend of mine and i've always admired Sam for
how uh he just writes tight jokes man he just does a thing that that i don't know how to do
as a comic and i envy it i'm just like i don't know how to do that like to write jokes that are
just super tight super succinct that aren't one -liners they're jokes you know not that one -liners aren't
jokes but you know what i mean right um i enjoyed that special uh very very much um yeah these are
good specials go check them out um now i'll say you know let's let's go to the movie let's talk about
let's talk hell razor um i got to by the way just real quick i got a quick scary stuff i'll
slip in how about that all right great two audiobooks that i'm just enjoying the shit out of
paperbacks from hell and the horror of it all um you can get them both on audible paperbacks from hell
is a book dedicated to the horror novels of the late 70s into the late 80s
that are just wild exploitative horror novels um used to see these left and right back then you
don't really see much of them anymore the covers alone to a lot of these which that the ones they
talk about in the book they've started reprinting them a lot a lot of them under the label paperbacks
from hell um but the cover alone on these old horror novels makes you want to buy them i actually
went and bought some of the old books that he talks about in this thing i it's hard to find affordable
ones i found a couple affordable ones most of them are terribly expensive now because they're out of
print um but it's just a super fun book that tackles all of those wild horror movie novels that
used to come out left and right um it's it's it's you know and it's it's done by category it starts
with like a you know a thing about demons and the devil and then it gets into a thing about killer
kids then gets to know a thing about aliens and it's just awesome uh the horror of it all is also a great
audio book that's basically honestly the whole thing is kind of in defense of horror movies
and the crux of it is the author combating very harshly combating cisco and ebert's critiques of
horror movies in the 80s and how incorrect they were and like they they really made some mistakes on horror
for sure yeah and like the guy starts with this big disclaimer when he starts talking about them
about like what an inspiring man ebert was in the way he dealt with his health condition and
how sad it was to see a man die like that and but the bravery is to be commended and he has such admiration
for him as a human being yeah and then the biggest but in the world but his take on horror movies is
shit yeah and then uh and then it kind of goes from there and um by the way he uh cisco was way
way worse he was like a puritan yeah he gets into cisco too uh but the book is just a love letter to
horror movies and and a defensive horror movies and slasher movies the guy that wrote it
actually let me look this up to be sure but i believe from remembering correctly
he did he remake of ice spit on your grave uh but uh well here's the
which was called i shit on your grave correct no what's even worse than spit
yeah i think um oh second steven arm and row
you know you'd think i'd look these things up or be able to remember anything
that i ever do but i can't i can't remember shit at i can't commit anything to memory anymore
you're not alone i think the the brain fog has swept the nation enveloped the nation
when i say the book was called the horror
horror i believe so i had it written down that i had written down
um anyway i i i think he worked in some way on the uh remake of ice spit on your grave
which is interesting because i'm getting this terribly wrong and i can't look it up right now
anyway the point is is the guy staunchly defends these movies and what they are and why they deserve
to be reviewed properly however he will say but i in never in a million years could defend a movie
like the original i spit on your grave it's a hard fill play yeah it's got no redeeming quality
so his stance on all this is really balanced but he's like but that doesn't mean you don't
you make a bullshit about it when you're reviewing it like it's it's just a really interesting book
uh yeah it's uh it's uh it's Scott Weinberg my buddy talks about that all the time is like
just say i hate horror movies and then don't review them you know you can't you can't review
something where you hate every thing that i mean we i've proven that wrong by reviewing every
Marvel movie on the show but i'm doing that to entertain i'm not doing that to like you know be a
voice of criticism against the film it's like if you hate horror across the board and you don't like
being scared by the way that's 50 % of America our buddy Vince Abel can't watch horror movies and he's
a he's a you know strapping young man um it's young people don't like really not neither of those
things but he's sure he's a tall strapping man he you know but uh he's he won't watch him he's scared
him and that's a lot of people so if that's you why would you review them you're obviously going to
hate every horror movie that you watch it's not fair so this the author's name is Adam Rackoff and he
wrote the remake of i spit on your grave yeah which is so interesting because he does not seem to
like the original but but he's it's just a very nuanced interesting book the bulk of what this guy's
done which is hilarious because he's such a huge uh like grind house horror kind of thing
is like homework and like like made for lifetime movies you know he wrote all the he wrote the wrong
fiance the wrong real estate agent the wrong prince charming i guess this is against series
on the lifetime uh so you know but you know his newest movie is a Merry Christmas Wish
okay okay so i love that i whatever you got to do to keep to keep a float in this business i have
all respect for it yeah me too he does a lot with Vivica a Fox he wrote most of the episodes of her
show keeping up with the Joneses i don't know if he created it but she's she's been in some of the
movies he's written okay um love that the Fox yeah she's great in fact she's been I think a lot of the
movies i think she's in all of the wrong person movies jesus christ there's eight of these things
i think the last time no i'm not gonna say that nevermind let's move on yeah she's uh i guess
vivica plays the bad guy in all these and she she and she's the oh she's the detective i see
so she works all the cases of these wrong you know the wrong cheerleader coach is one of them oh wow
all right oh no i'm wrong fox pretends to be people and infiltrates people's lives in these films
okay okay heavy man that's a big mythology there i was trying to just
yeah anyway all right let's get let's let's focus how are we
um directed by david brokner uh written by his uh his guys so these guys did super dark times
which we reviewed on the show uh and i absolutely love super dark times it was great he did the nighthouse
which we reviewed on this show when we were kind of split on i think we both agreed it was solid
and scary in parts and stupid and slow in parts i liked it more than joe he did a couple creep shows
so you know obviously those well he did what he did the man in the suitcase one of the one of my
least favorite episode yeah uh and then the ritual which was his Netflix horror movie that was pretty
good um he's a solid horror director don't get me wrong i get why he was given the reins of
hellraiser the film itself you know we're dealing with a new pinhead um and of course we'll discuss
what we thought of of the new pinhead the story joe can you walk us through because i really thought
i was gonna be watching a remake i knew there would be changes but this movie from opening shot to last
has almost nothing to do with the original hellraiser there's well i'll tell you this and this is
what drives me a little crazy about what hollywood does now the story it's not a remake i thought it was
gonna be a new adaptation of the hellbound heart which is the original novella right in a little more
true to form it's not that either it's a whole new story uh it's about a girl who is a recovering
alcoholic and drug addict who is barely skating by living with her brother trying to stay sober
and she gets out of desperation uh she decides to tartake in a small heist with a guy she is seeing who
she met in the program which you're not supposed to do at the stage she's adding the program um quick pause
uh this very funny joke writer chase Mitchell who i am friendly with and follow on uh letterbox pointed out
something that i didn't even notice that when he asked her to go in on the heist when the boyfriend asked
her to go in on the he says give me a hand i'll give you a cut didn't even notice but uh i went okay
all right that's clever i like that there's clever movie involves 500 hands getting cut by 500 sewing
needles this joke pointed out um no it's not so the box that cuts you as the blade comes out of the
box right every centabyte when we'll get to it has sewing needles incorporated into their costume
with like pearl heads on them that that's not scary looking anyway um anyway she partakes in this small
heist she uh uh what they end up stealing from this freight yard is a bot is the box
and then you start to learn that the box has different configurations and every time it is
it is the puzzle is solved it moves to a new configuration however when the puzzle is solved it cuts
somebody and takes blood from that person that person becomes the victim of the centabytes who will
then appear and take you to hell um and the box ultimately wants to be sent through all the
configurations so it i don't know it tries to i don't know it's a bit convoluted in that aspect but
she gets wound up with the box is the point um and her brother gets killed she is Odessa
Odessa Azeon who is Pamela Adlon's daughter and looks a lot like her i thought she was she was
good in the part i guess i liked her in this movie i thought the entire cast was was very solid
i thought it was very well directed yeah um it looked cool but overall as a movie
it's just this is what i let's start with what i said are at the top of the show i don't understand
why they start to do copies of copies so for instance they said we're gonna do a new hellraiser movie
and we're gonna have a female play uh uh pinhead yeah or you know whatever and i thought well that's
interesting especially since they're they have it's a trans woman playing pinhead and especially since
hellraiser in and of itself and the hellbound heart it deals with sexuality and like
blurring lines of everything so i thought who better could be a centabyte than a trans woman you know
what i mean like right i think that's perfect um but why is she pinhead in the book
the lead centabyte is referred to as the female in the first hellraiser movie pinhead is not the center
of attention the centabytes are even and the female centabyte if you rewatch the first movie does seem
to take a little bit more of a leadership position it's just pinhead was so visually stunning and
interesting that he got the poster and all the press and blah blah blah blah and then all the sudden
pinhead is the guy that that becomes a star of the show right if you're rebooting why and you
and you're recasting pinhead and then you're recasting with a woman why not make the woman
centabyte like in the original book the lead centabyte especially when you have a variation of that
centabyte in this movie who has nothing to do whatsoever yeah um that irks me you know in fact
if i'm not mistaken in the original novella pinhead isn't even it's not even pinned it's pieces of glass
i might be wrong i might be getting confused with stuff from the scarlet gospels but that's the
either here nor there that that i don't understand the second thing i didn't understand is you've got
a set up here for a very simple story that can all take place under one roof which the original
hellbound heart does so does the original hellraiser you've got a drug addict girl who needs to be
watched over by her family because she can't be trusted to not relapse right this was the exact
plot of evil dead remake well i thought the exact same thing the second i was like boy it's so
weird when a brother is like this obsessed with his sister and then i was like wait a minute where
i seen this dynamic before addict sister brother is unhealthily obsessed it's the evil dead remake
the exact same dynamic and it's like and in both movies used addiction as a metaphor you know it's
exact same way right and it worked they used it really the addiction element was used very well
in the evil dead remake because number one it gave you the reason they were all at the cab and cut off
right number because she had to kick she had to dry out right number two when crazy shit started
happening nobody believed her because they they were like you're fucking using again
it's a great it's a great device for that movie i thought they were just gonna rip it off in this and
do it again which at first i was like oh man they're just stealing this and then by the end of this
thing i'm like i wish you would have just stolen the evil dead plot line because you went in
directions with this that this didn't need to go there didn't need to be let's start with this
collector character who yeah you're talking about goren viznik right yeah they've added this when
they added this new dimension to the box which is it whoever it cuts is who they come for which
allows it to be a device used for manipulation we we put you can put the box in the hands of somebody
else that person can solve it for you um they can get cut and claimed by the centa bites and then
you can witness all the sites without being sacrificed yourself okay i'm willing to go that far with
you but then they take it a step farther than that in this it's not just that the centa bites
can't be seen by you if you're not the one who solves the box because when they show up only you the
person that solved the box could see them right but now they create this whole other element that's a very
very weak variation of a thing they did in hellraiser for bloodline where he devises a way to trap the
centa bites with golden gates it makes no fucking sense it's stupid these these that one point when
the when the metal bars are keeping the centa bites out i'm like yeah i texted joe is this a
because i haven't seen all the hellraisers is this a new development that centa bites are scared of
metal because i don't recall that being part of their lore it's not tell your mic down just a little
bit so it's it's a little just tilt it down toward your mouth a little bit it just got a little
above your mouth so you go you went a little quiet um the uh but yeah like that's the thing it's like
so in hellraiser bloodline which is a pretty good hellraiser movie
the way he traps the centa bites at the end is in the distant distant future he's the this guy who's
who's who's a distant ancestor of the guy that created the lament configuration the box yeah figures
out a way to turn this and it's a space station which is weird to see the centa bites in space but it
is what it is to turn this space station he's created into a giant box and that's how he traps them
and destroys them he literally traps them inside of a literal box right and it kind of makes sense
like they take you through it to to an extent throughout the movie of why this is happening everything
and you're like okay i buy it in this there's no explanation these things can open ground and walls
and whatever the fuck they want whenever they feel like it they can appear and disappear out of reality
whenever they feel like it why are they trapped by these bar it's stupid it's stupid that
only the person that solves the box can see them but then other people can see them depending on
the circumstance that's confusing it's convoluted and and and greater than any other criticism i could
have is the reason the original hellraiser franchise got off base was one simple thing
they tried to turn pinhead into Freddy Krueger and that's not what he is the centa bites are judges
of hell these people that toy with pleasure and temptation and their greed and all the things that
this collector character signifies in this movie they get punished for their lust of trying to find
these greater pleasures and and for the people they are in the original two hellraisers when when they come
and it's not a it's an innocent person they don't take them they're like this isn't what this is
that makes the characters of the centa bites so cool and so interesting and so nuanced and by the way
the way that the heaven and hell mythology works that's the whole point yeah and
this thing just this thing goes they go they go to they go to hellraiser three in this thing with the
centa bites being on earth hellraiser three sucks they go to hellraiser they go to them do you think that
they were trying to make this movie part of the hellraiser franchise as a whole or they just borrowed some
stuff pet who the hell can tell anymore yeah because you're sitting there going none of these characters
are in the original hellraiser none of the centa bites look the same they look different right
right they're being portrayed slightly different the rules of this are different but they're playing
the same music yeah like it's fucking confusing man like it's the same font it's the same on the
title it's like there's so many similarities where you're like I just make a fucking sequel man
like that's what I don't get make a goddamn sequel make a sequel with some new centabytes and make and
and have have uh uh uh uh uh blackened in the actresses name but you know the cursed
later the place cursed in the first yeah two movies have her show up you know and put do the
trope where she's in a mental hospital and they got to go get information out of her whatever the
fucking is you know like yeah it feels really like and then when I read about the long uh troubled
journey to the screen this movie took you can see all the different drafts that went in and
basically for ten years anyone who got a draft of the script said no we want to make this more like
new new user friendly teenager friendly we want like a hot young cast that kind of thing so they were
trying to go the the scream route with it and this I guess sort of splits the difference it is young
hot people um they're all fine although none of the characters are particularly interesting you don't
really care if they live or die uh for me just from a uh mapping out standpoint they kind of
reminded me of cabin in the woods to them driving away from the place forever in a van you know that
just it was the exact same scene yeah yeah when they're driving away uh and then they crash their
little van that they're in and then they have to go back to get the car to try to drive away again
I was like guys this is just boring you know like you can't that that's not great plotting
crap they crash the van so they have to go back to get the car it's like you know
if there's no forward momentum after a certain point once they get into this mansion then it does
become home alone it's probably a victim of covid where they had to stay in one location for a long
period of time but it takes away really everything special about the hellraiser franchise to me it
it just puts these crazy wild characters into a very generic environment and it's not that cool
there's zero sexuality in the film and the original hellraiser even though you're not seeing
that much fucking there's some but it's about sexuality and how you can go too far into your uh
kinks and depravity and so forth it's so that element is gone because they think nobody can handle
watching sex anymore even though everybody in america watches porn every day of their lives it's very
strange it's very strange and that that bothered me about it too it's very strange they they
immediately immediately they introduce you to the star of the film yeah fucking none of the
and and and she's going like from the back hard or hard you know like right and you're like
oh like this like sexuality of hers is gonna like get her in trouble with when because she's
gonna get tempted by these things and some yeah they don't play up any of that like never mentioned again
you know and like that's one of the best one of the greatest elements of the original hellraiser is
frank the main dad's the main dad's brother fox julia the dad's wife julia is played by a famous
i forget her name but she you know she's a pretty renowned actress in england um she's been in tons of
shit i met her once she was very nice i met her and kirstie they were and duck Bradley duck Bradley
was okay but they were very they were all nice doesn't matter and now i need her name you've been talking
about her for too long to not say her name her name is Ashley Lawrence Ashley Lawrence
wanted to say Aubrey Plaza now she's great too i can't believe i blanked on
Ashley Lawrence anyway um
what was they saying oh frank in the first movie fucking julia julia is a plenty attractive woman
but the way they establish frank and the type of guy frank is it's like she's certainly not
gonna turn this guy's head right yeah but the reason he does it is because it's his brother's wife
yeah like that is so they don't say it but that's what it is and like that that carries so much weight
in the original movie like this this these people that have uncontrollable fucking lust and like and
like they had to the point where they have to hurt others with it uh you can tell with
this with this goren visionate character what's his name like leaf or something i don't know
i don't know if it gives a shit but he is um you can tell they decided to go the capitalist route
because every horror movie has to criticize trump and capitalism now as well um his whole thing
yeah sex is part of his brew of of of things that he does too much but like when they go to a party
at his house there's people fucking in the dimest light imaginable at his house so you're supposed to
say like oh this guy must be really depraved but you know that's sort of the it really is the fascinating
part of the original and what people can relate to is sex is a thing where if you go too far down
exploring your kinks eventually regular sex vanilla sex is not enough for you anymore that's really
the relatable beautiful part of hellraiser and it's just like you said that first scene harder deeper
or hit it from the back whatever to start that and then ignore it um it's just not what this
franchise is about this franchise used to be about excess there's one moment of excess which is
when from inside the woman's throat you see the sewing needle go through incredible i was like whoa
you know gross shocking but those moments are i won't even say a few in far between there's
only one of those moments in the movie then but then the other thing with the main character with
the sex stuff is when she's in trouble when her brother disappears and everybody's mad at her
yeah and her life is at its lowest point she goes to the guy she's seeing who eventually turns out to
be in league with this collector and and setting her up she goes to this guy she's seeing he answers
the door he's surprised to see her because she's very guarded and keeps her distance and she goes kiss me
and they fuck and you're like she's also a sex you're like here we go she's also a sex addict like
this is going to she she's a drug addict she's an alcoholic she's a sex addict she's got an indulgence
issue that's going to get her in trouble with the centabytes and nothing yeah absolutely fucking
nothing in fact the only thing she's tempted to get from the centabytes is potentially resurrecting
her brother from the dead right that's it that's it they go they they do hell razor two in this thing
where where the bad guy who's obsessed with the spectator being a spectator of the box becomes
the centabyte at the end which is what they do with the doctor and hell razor two they cherry picked
excuse me they cherry picked the first four they cherry picked this fucking hell razor franchise to
the point I can't believe there wasn't a cop story line about a cop because that's where all the
sequels eventually went everyone was about like a cop on a case it was a tracking pin huh yeah no no
like a dirty cop who was paying for his sins right now but now how did you take the ending I
thought the ending was sort of cool and it's just sort of that guy becoming a centabyte correct
because there was everyone online had confusion about what happened at the end but I think I got it
he just became a centabyte yeah I don't know what anybody was confused I don't believe anybody was
confused I think now that that there's now a market for we're going to explain the ending of every
single movie and make it sound like it's something people are confused by so you click on the site
to see sure yeah but I mean I don't know dude I don't know it's too long you know it's two hours
it's not fun it's a joyless slog although hell razor always was kind of a joyless franchise don't
get me wrong but yeah it's just kind of lies there and in reading about the backstory of this I learned
that the nighthouse which you and I both saw Joe started as the hell razor sequel
the script when it went in for the nighthouse was intended to be a hell razor sequel now I'm sure
there was a lot of differences but it was in development hell for so long that they eventually
had to go a different route which I guess is what we wound up seeing and made that movie into the
nighthouse you wonder what that project would it look like or what that would have been who knows
it's it's it's the nighthouse the nighthouse is a painfully boring in my opinion painfully
boring horror movie that plays like a lot of the later hell razor sequel okay here's a woman alone
in a house whose husband is dead and she misses him yeah and she probably gets the box and wants to
read you know right right right right I mean Jesus Christ guys this I'm sorry I'm not even saying oh I
could do a great job at it but this just isn't fucking rocket science like the the amount of
bad sequels they've made in this for I mean Frank look hell razor is a bad fucking franchise at this
point I mean it's not even at this point before this but there are three solid hell razor films that
vary between pretty solid and great and then there are all the sequels plus now this fucking thing
there's a slew of comic books I've read a lot of them some of them are cool some of them really suck
it's a bad franchise at this point you know my one on my other you know the new pinhead is fine
she's very serviceable she does a good job yeah you're gonna have the Freddy Krueger problem with
pinhead for the rest of time it's not Doug Bradley it's not Robert England it's never gonna it's
just never gonna be the same without them period it's not Jason Voorhees it's not Michael Myers it's
not a maskless person there's a very specific personality and voice and look that made the character
popular it's like when Brad Derr of dies Chuck E is well they'll take his voice and put it into that
fucking computer that they can now yeah yeah yeah but you get my point like it's just it's just you know
she's fine the thing that bothers me is they do with her voice in this what they do with every
fucking horror thing they put it through that same generic voice modulator thing what's like
it just sounds like cheap distortion like it doesn't yeah it's not a cool they they worked on the
Doug Bradley voice they worked on the Robert England voice they take the voice and they texture it and
they drop it in octave and like they do all this really cool stuff to it so you're like god damn it does
he sound like that that's weird like well it's like ET you learn like just ET's voice was Deborah
Winger was in there and then they also use like animals and they use like all these different elements
mixed it all up tested it until they found the perfect voice yeah this is the lady talking and they
put a little filter on her like she's singing lead for the strokes or something and it's not particularly
scary you know no it's not her fault but it's not really scary no her performance is good all of the
centabyte performances I are good I mean everybody else is just kind of walking around but I didn't like
that there was like a running centabyte I thought I was stupid why would it ever have to run if it
can get you it can get you their supernatural beings I hated that that guy was inexplicably living in
the walls of his own mansion with like a clock in his chest or whatever the fuck that was just stupid
yeah that felt more like saw to me when he's got that device twisting his nerve endings I was like well
that's a saw trap isn't it it just wasn't needed it just none of it was needed uh like
yeah and so anyway I don't know I guess might take away ultimately was this was better than a lot of
the hellraiser sequels were but that is saying absolutely nothing yeah that's like saying you know
Robocop 2 is better than the Robocop TV movies like yeah no shit but who cares you know like I've
only seen hellraiser one and two this felt like a tremendous drop off to me uh it lacked all of the
flavor vibes sexuality danger menace excitement disturbingness of the hellraiser one and two that I saw
and my hog is down you know I feel like this is gonna start another franchise of these and and they're
all gonna be roughly like this or lesser versions of this and the problem with these franchises now is
don't start with the classic and then get progressively worse you start with shit and get progressively
worse so these franchises are not worth and then all lining up for it I just don't understand
what the issue with these studios is every single legacy thing they take over they do one of two things
and both are wrong they either give you almost nothing because they're saving it for some big payday
for god knows when and where yeah that never comes or they give you absolutely everything all at once
and it leaves nowhere to go the sequel to this should have been a guy going I'm a famous collector
and I'm obsessed with the box and I figured out a way to trap the centabytes yeah that's the sequel
yeah I agree why is that in the first movie along with the drug addict storyline along with the dead
brother storyline along with you know it's it's so fucking much it's like yeah you know to really
to tell you about where we are as a culture and and this could not be helped I understand
but when I clicked I turned every light in my house off I grabbed a pillow I'm all curled up ready
to be scared watch the new hellraiser and I hit play and the first thing that comes on my screen is
Hulu presents a Hulu original hellraiser it's like all right already I've never been less scared in my
entire life you know it's just a different time in America yeah folks my hogs down me too
and I you know I don't know what else to say we're gonna be back we got to obviously with it being
October we've got a lot of big titles backed up we plan to do barbarian we plan to do pearl we plan
to do Halloween kills and to do oh smile we got smiles definitely one of the next two yeah we'll be
doing smiles so check that one out if you haven't seen it it's you know that's the horror movie about
to make a hundred million dollars essentially a profit while Amsterdam which I discussed on my movie
corner is losing a hundred million dollars so all that means is we're gonna get more bare bones budget
horror and less movies about adults behaving like I mean this Amsterdam is such a disaster it looks
terrible it lost somehow a hundred million dollars I mean every actor in America is in this thing and
it's a complete mess it looks terrible it looks like a bunch of actors jerking off going yeah it is
go have fun together it looks fucking terrible and it will be outdone I predict by this Babylon movie coming
out so when the trailer for that one up I said that movie is going to lose that's going to break a
studio that movie it looks so shitty and they have huge stars throughout you can't tell in a five -minute
trailer what it's about it's it's it's it's 40s Hollywood I guess and and Marga Roby's a co -head I'm
like okay yeah no one's gonna go see that no one's gonna go see that sorry yeah Brad Pitt is some
studio head or something right it's Brad Pitt yep what is this it's so it's a weird time and and the
lessons they take is like well if this hundred million dollar movie about complete nonsense starring
Brad Pitt and Marga Roby didn't work I guess we'll see I guess we'll stop making those two and we're
just gonna start getting only superheroes because now people have been trained by the business you
did it to yourself you idiots to only leave the house for superheroes and to stay home for comedy
for drama for every other genre yeah yeah it's gonna destroy our country so keep writing is it
it already is yeah keep writing think pieces calling Martin Scorsese an idiot and a hack for
criticizing this this this superhero yeah gluttony yeah oh god some fucking idiot and get
god bless Guillermo del Toro I read both pieces I mean del Toro man he should write about film he wrote
he he stood up for Scorsese he so eloquently it was it was wonderful the balls on that moron that
wrote that piece just for clicks it's all for clicks they don't even mean it all right thanks we'll see
you next time and we'll see you and hell