I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell
And when the sound of your screams becomes a thing of my dreams
You know I'll say
I'll see you in hell, you know I will
Folks, it's we'll see you in hell back up in that bitch
Your boys Pat and Joe here to review yet another carpenter classic
Escape from New York over here
Yeah, we're going through all the classic carpenters
I mean many of these have been requested many times
I hope somebody out there is still listening and appreciating that we got to your request four years later
People, I live in New York, this thing was a fantasy when it came out
Looks like a fucking documentary these days
Uh huh, uh huh
Anyway
You mean because you walk through the city with an iPad shooting innocent people?
Well, I don't do that, but I do call myself Snake
Call me Snake
Which confuses people
I love, I mean Russell doing such an Eastward impression in this thing
I mean the call me Snake, I laughed out loud
Call me Snake
We'll get to it of course, but uh
Yeah
Russell performing, I love Kurt Russell, it's a questionable performance
Yeah, no I love Kurt Russell too
In this picture, but he gets it done where it counts, but it's a little, I can't tell if it's supposed to be funny or not
Like it's a weird, I don't think it is
I've been trying to cast, I'm trying to cast my father in something that you'll hopefully see on television eight years from now
And you know, a lot of choices that we discussed were like, oh yeah, he'd be good, but all kind of expected
And then one day I just shot out of bed in the morning and I was like, Kurt Russell
Because we need him to be sort of charming at times, but also horrifying and a monster
And like Kurt Russell, he doesn't, when he does those roles, like in Death Proof, he's awesome
He rarely does, but he's awesome
He's got a menace in him for sure
He's like that in Hateful Eight
Like he's charming as hell, but he's horrible at the same time
He's great
Anyway, we're here to, we'll get to that picture
I'm enjoying going through these Carpenter classics, I would actually like to, and I'm not putting you on the spot
But maybe next month we hit, we do a revisit of Prince of Darkness
Because it's right in the row of these, like I'm just curious
Yeah, well weirdly, probably because they're big sellers, all of his movies are on 4K
Like there's huge, massive, you know, like Rosemary's Baby and like giant hits that have not come out on 4K
Major movies, but all of his are out probably because they just, people buy them again and again
But I'll watch Prince of Darkness
You told me the 4K is supposed to be amazing
The 4K on Escape from New York was awesome
The Fog was really awesome
I mean, they do a great job on his shit, because it's 80s and it's filmed on film
I've got New York on VHS, which is a perfect VHS movie to own
Sure
But I am going to buy that dual steelbook Fog and Escape that's on Amazon
And I don't think it's a steelbook, but they're on, it's a two disc set, it's like 45 bucks
I'm going to get that for sure
I'm not going to buy Prince of Darkness until I re -watch my DVD
And then if I think it's great, I'll upgrade
But I'm ready to do an upgrade on both of those movies
Do you think the band P .O .D., remember P .O .D.?
Do you think that they were called that because of Prince of Darkness?
That's a great question
I feel like P .O .D. is Christian
That could be, so maybe they're fighting the Prince of Darkness
Weren't they, Here Comes the Boom, isn't that P .O .D.?
You mean, which one was click, click, boom, ready or not?
Oh, Saliva
Saliva
Click, boom
P .O .D. did We Are, We Are, you're right, Boom
Yeah, the movie is named after that song
I actually do kind of like that song, but yeah, they're like a Christian rock
Payable on Death is what it stands for
They're Christian metal
I mean, Christian metal, it flies under the radar
You could be a metal band and be Christian and you could still play the cool stuff
For some reason it doesn't come across as obviously as it does with Christian rock
Yeah, it's like you could either be singing about God or a girl you want to have sex with, really
I mean, technically DMX is a Christian rapper
He would do a prayer on every album and all that stuff
I guess you can have a duality, right?
P .O .D.'s other hit was Youth of the Nation, remember that terrible song?
We are, we are
The youth of the nation
No
That was a
We shouldn't talk shit
You know who listens to this podcast randomly is a lot of like bassists for death metal bands
Like there'll be somebody on Twitter with like a million followers who's like, dude, I love the show about whatever
And I'm like, who is this?
And you look and they're like, I play harpsichord in, you know, Cannibal Corpse or whatever
Yeah, yeah, exactly
Yeah, follow, have you ever seen my band Drag Tooth?
I don't know
Well, there's big bands too
We got a guy from Doves, which is a British band I used to like
The lead singer of Slipknot, I know at least one point used to be a fan of our show
I don't know if he's out there
He was? Old Cory?
No shit
I think his name's Cory, right?
I guess the metal and horror community's kind of synced
I'm a fan of that guy
He's one of my favorite talking heads on the like In Search of Darkness things
He knows his shit, man, that guy
He does
I got stopped by a hellion yesterday at the grocery store
Made me feel like a hot celeb
Gelson? Was that a Gelson spotting?
It was Vons, but I was wearing deeply stained shorts
Not stained by anything I provided, but you know, like work shorts for being out in the yard and stuff
Deeply stained shorts, no underwear, a sweatshirt, a jacket that didn't match any of it
And then tennis shoes with no socks
Also hadn't combed my hair
And of course, everywhere I went yesterday I ran into people who knew me and people I know
You ran into the head of the modeling committee that you submitted to
Oh, no, not today
Hey, we just wanted to offer you this million -dollar contract
Now you said dirty from being out in the yard
You don't have a yard as far as I can remember
I don't have a yard, but I have an extensive plant, potted plant and, you know, garden collage
I get out there with the hoe, you know, the hose
What about the gardening tools?
Folks, I said, what did I say one day?
I said the only kink shaming I'd ever do is when my garden hose acts up
That was an old weed I had
Didn't do well
But I hate the hose
Still to this day they have not solved the problem of you walk four feet with a hose, it kinks up and you can't spray it
It's wild, hose technology is wild
It hasn't made any advancements in a hundred years
It's wild how stunted it is
When they came out with that a few years back
You'd see like a commercial for it during like Judge Joe Brown
Like at one in the afternoon for that like retractable hose
I was like, finally they've done something with hose technology
There is no product that has ever worked worse than that Judge Joe Brown retractable hose
I get that you were excited that they might have fixed it, but they didn't fix shit
That thing didn't work
Speaking of shaming, I've got two new psychos here
The first is a little less along the brand that we do, but it fits in well enough
Katy Perry just got back last from an American Idol contestant
Who came on the show, they thought she was like 16
The lady was like, no, I'm actually an adult, I have three children
And Katy Perry stood up and grabbed her chest like, what?
And I guess Katy Perry does a thing on the show where she faints onto the desk as a gag or something
She's very funny, that makes sense
And the contestant goes, if Katy Perry lays on the table, I'm going to be all faint or something
And then Katy Perry said, girl, it sounds like you've been laying on the table too much
Meaning you're having too much sex, you have three kids
It's funny
The woman makes a public statement that Katy Perry has mom -shamed her
Oh no
What?
White girl?
Don't know
They couldn't even look it up
She's a white girl
Let's just say it
I can't remember her last name
I was going to try to guess by last name, but I can't remember it
I'm just, dear lord with this shit
So that was the first thing
The second thing we'll be able to see
Mom -shaming
The lady's like, mommies love your...
In her statement, she's like, mommies love your babies no matter what
It's like, what are you talking about? You cretin
Nobody is saying to not love your children
She made a joke that you...
She thought you were a child and you're an adult and you already have three kids
She just made a joke
You have a lot of sex
That's all
You don't want the host of an entertainment program to make an innocent joke
Steve Harvey's tearing people's lives apart over on Family Feud and they laugh
They love it
God bless, my hat's off to Lizzo
Lizzo apparently came out very recently and said
At this point, cancel culture is cultural appropriation
You've taken a thing away from people that needed it
To try to level some form of justice
And applied it to every little selfish thing you want
I was like, dang, alright, right on Lizzo
I appreciate it
Good point, Lizzo
Yeah, I've never heard it put like that, but it's totally true
It's just like...
You know, Burr talked about that
Someone has a notorious SNL monologue
And Chappelle talks about that as well
It's like...
You don't have to hop on
You don't have to insert yourself into every social issue
You don't have to make everything about you
Yeah, it's wild
But you do, don't you?
It's wild
Well, you want to talk about making everything about you
The good people at PETA, they're doing such fine work over at PETA
PETA?
Yeah
PETA
PETA Pocket
Strange to name your organization after a thing you stuff with meat
I never realized that until right now
That's true
PETA, they have made a formal request, meaning public
That...
I sent you a voice memo about this
I don't think it went through
And I'm glad it didn't
Because I get to break it to you here
PETA has made a public request
That Good Burger 2
feature vegan burgers
Oh, fuck off
Just fuck off
Jesus Christ
You imagine
Go back to bed, you fucking losers
Give me a break
The level of privilege you are functioning from
When that's your cause
We're going to go after Good Burger 2
The sequel nobody is talking about
To a movie nobody remembers
About a sketch we can barely...
What? That we barely laughed at
And I'm not trying to shit on Kenan and Kel
God, good for them
Go do your thing
I'm sure there is a portion of the population out there
That's excited about a Kenan and Kel reunion
But for the love of God, people
Good Burger 2
You mean Good Impossible Burger
I hope
This is PETA's
This is what PETA is striking after
They don't...
What's that?
Pricks against the ethical treatment of animals
Is that what it's called?
What's the P?
Parents?
People?
Just people
Okay
Are you excited about Good Burger?
Suddenly, as my friend pointed out to me
And I'm not going to name his name
Because he is a professional writer in television
So I don't want to blow up his spot
But if he does hear this, I want you to know
Brother, I am recognizing this was not me saying this
You texted this to me
But I get a text from a very funny comedian slash writer
Two nights ago
And he just said
So now we're going to pretend Good Burger is a classic?
Yeah, that's a great point, dude
The movie got like a...
Nobody talked about Good Burger
You know, right?
A couple of weird things that I have noticed
Over the last 10 plus years
Is that the generation behind us
You know, maybe not a full generation
But people 10 years younger than us or so
I did grow up with Keenan and Kel on all that
I've never seen all that
I had never really seen Keenan until SNL
Where he has been the funniest person on the show for 10 years
He gets laughs every week out of nothing
Yes
He's amazing
Kel, I don't really know other than he was in Mystery Men
But...
He did stand up after that
I don't think...
Yeah
I think he kind of went a different route
Good Burger, I must have seen when I was like too old for it
16 and I thought it was kind of dumb
I mean, it's basically the trailers like
Welcome to Good Burger, can I take your order?
It's like that's not particularly funny to me
But it's like a teenage clerks sort of
And if they're doing a clerks too
Where now they're old and sad and still working at Good Burger
I'm into that
I don't know that I'll watch it or not
But that movie and the Goofy movie
Have developed like huge followings of people
And I've never seen the Goofy movie either
But those are two movies I've noticed that have big cult followings weirdly
And maybe people will go see it
I don't know
This is like Good Burger to me is like
And I say this as a friend of the man who wrote and starred in the movie
Yeah
This would be like people clamoring about like
They're making Half Baked 2
It's like, alright guys
If OE, that is right
They are without any original people, right?
Yeah, it's like a Crackle Original or something
I forgot about that
And I think I have friends in Half Baked 2 as well
Yeah
Sure
But here's my point
It's like if you like the movie
There are movies I love
That are not critically lauded and whatever
I love the movie CB4
I love it
It makes me laugh really hard
Charlie Murphy and Chris Rock made me laugh at it
If they were like they're making CB4 too
I wouldn't be running around saying suddenly CB4 is a classic
It's not a classic
It's a movie that some people really liked
I was one of them
That's how I feel about Good Burger
I feel like it was like a stoner comedy
That wasn't allowed to be a stoner comedy
Because they were like 14
But you know
It's got a 33 % on Rotten Tomatoes
It's got a 5 .5 or 5 .7 on IMDB
It
What was it?
It made $23 million on an $8 .5 million budget
That's pretty good
I don't know
I just
It's just
This retroactive
Sheen that we put on things
Like
You know I'm happy for Kel Mitchell
He's kind of the Mark Hamill of the Good Burger
Yeah
I'm sure he's quite excited about Good Burger too
You know good for him
Keenan's very funny
But you know it's like
Like I'm assuming Dan Schneider won't be back
As the owner and manager of Good Burger
Nope
That's probably gonna be the plot right
As they buy the Good Burger
Or they run it
Keenan runs it now
Because he's the responsible one
And Kel still works there
Because he can't get
His character can't get his shit together
I bet that's
Probably he's the family man
And then Kel's like
Takes him on a big adventure
Yeah
I don't even know what they did in the movie
Like
I don't remember them having adventures
I just remember them sitting in a store
Taking orders really
Let me ask you a question Pat
Yeah
Do you think Robert
Wool will be returning as angry customer
Wow
That was
That must have been the last gasp for Wool
Imagine like
He was on the poster
Like Tommy Lee Jones and Robert Wool in Cobb
A few years prior
And now he's angry customer in Good Burger
Three years later
Wow
Okay
Linda Cardellini was in the original
As a demented Hills patient
So there's a place called demented Hills in it
They're not going to be allowed to do that joke again
That's for sure
No
Shaquille O 'Neal as himself
Carmen Electra
Do you think she'll be back as Ron Roxanne
The henchwoman of Kurt
There's a henchwoman involved
Kurt
Are they trying to get the recipe
What's the plot
Kurt was played by Jans Schweitzer mind
Of Warlock 3 fame
Okay
What's the good burger plot
Let's see
I'm just pushing it
The summary is too long
I can't
It's very long
It's something about burgers
There's a burger place
The thing
Do with
Burger place opening
It's a classic you know
I
Classic burger caper
Have a date tonight
With a sober woman
A third date
Not a big deal for me
But
It definitely limits what you do
Generally
The early dates are like
Let's go get a drink
Helps with the nervousness
You know
That's your standard early date
So when you take that off the table
It's like dinner
Or what do you do
Bowl or something
So I'm looking today at movies
And I'm like
Well I always love a classic dinner and a movie date
Friday night
But here's where we're at
She told me I don't like scary movies
That rules out scream 6
But
It would also be ruled out
For anyone who hadn't seen the previous movie
It's
It's very
Heavily tied to the previous movie
Creed 3
So if she hasn't seen the other two
Why would we see Creed 3
Shazam 2
Which
Neither of us want to see
And you'd also have to see
100 Marvel movies to understand
No Shazam's DC
Whatever it is
Shazam's DC
And you could get away with Shazam
With just seeing the original Shazam
Well it's not a date movie
No
It's also supposedly terrible
Yeah
John Wick Chapter 4
Which is 3 hours long
Now granted I'll see it
But I can't say
Hey you want to go see a 3 hour movie
Where people get shot
For you know
For a third date
I got a thing about John Wick 4 to tell you
But go ahead
I got Adam Driver
And the Dinosaur movie
That's lost 100 million dollars in a week
This fucking thing
Dude
I got a Jesus movie
Tom Cruise
And Will Smith
Made that fucking movie
Did Adam Driver
That one
No
I'm saying like
Will Smith did After Earth
With his son
Which is
It's this
It's this fucking thing
The kid and you crash landed on the plane
And then Tom Cruise did that sci -fi thing
That nobody fucking remembered
It was like the one bomb Tom Cruise has ever made
I don't understand Driver doing this
It seems like this is what he thought
Would be the one for them
And they're like
No we don't like you and this stuff
Like nobody saw this movie
It's
There's Jesus Revolution
A Jesus movie
Literally a Christian movie
Kelsey Grammer though
At least
Ant -Man
Quantumania
So another movie you have to see
100 movies to understand
Cocaine Bear
Which I saw
And it's one of the worst movies
I've seen in years
Really?
Wasn't fun?
No it wasn't fun at all
Then you got Avatar
Still hanging in there
And Puss in Boots
Jesus Christ
How is there no movie
A man and a woman can go on a date to?
No wonder the business is failing
Well this is why
And I got friends with kids who are like
Yeah we saw Puss in Boots two months ago
And then there hasn't been a kids movie since
So we're going crazy
We got our kid hooked on movies
They went to see Puss in Boots
And they're like
I love movies
And now there's no movies for them to see
It's outrageous
They're all giant budget sequels
It sucks
This is why I drink Pat
Why stop drinking
Then you gotta go to the movies
Mike Lawrence
Friend of mine
Funny comic
He told me that he saw John Wick 4
At South by Southwest
So he got to see it a little early
Yeah
And I said how was it
He said it was awesome
I said
He said it is three hours
So be ready for that
And I said
Well Mike
I just hope it's not another three
Another three hours of
Hey here's a coin that gets you a pass yet again
You know what I mean
And he goes
I'd
I'd be prepared for a lot of that
And I was like
Damn it
How many times are you gonna get his exit ticket
His get out of jail ticket
And then he gets to keep going
And then another thing happens
That's the more unforgivable thing
Then he gets another ticket
These were
This was a movie
The first and second movie
It was perfect
That was it
And it just has to keep going
And going
And now there's a TV series coming out
It's like
I don't want to see a TV show
About the fucking hotel
And now the guy is dead
The guy that played the
Awesome concierge
Whatever
The hotel is dead
Or the tailor I mean
It sucks
And R .I .P. to the great Lance Reddick
Great actor
But
John Wick is just like this perfect little thing
You know
It's like
It's Death Wish
It's all these classic 70s movies
Updated perfectly
A great starring role for Keanu
And a very relatable small story
They killed my adorable dog
And now I'm going to kill them
Got it
Love it
As they keep doubling
And tripling
And now quadrupling down
On the mythology
And that
Like you said
The hotel and the coins
And Laurence Fishburne
And all that
Maybe there's somebody out there
Who cares about it
I have never heard anyone
Discussing John Wick
Who wasn't like
That kill
Where he threw him
Through the glass
Thing was so fucking awesome
No one is talking about this stuff
So why would you add
Presumably in a three hour movie
My guess is it's 90 minute action
90 minute
Mythology
No one wants this
What are you doing?
Yeah it's just
It's because of Marvel
You know
Everyone thinks they got to start a world
And Keanu
Keanu of all people
Yeah
Should know better
Because this is exactly what happened with The Matrix
Keanu
You gave us a perfect
Under two hour
Bulletproof
No pun intended
Comedy
In the
I mean action movie
In The Matrix
And then the second
You went to your little
Unplug their heads
City
Where everybody is going to dance
To bongo drums and shit
Everybody was like
What the fuck is this?
Who cares?
Um
Mike also said
He's a big Marvel fan
He said
About Ant -Man
Marvel movies now
Actually are comic books
Where it's like
If you're not following everything
You don't know what the fuck
Is going on
In the movies
Yeah
Well like Ant -Man
Is supposed to be like
The light funny one
And I think
Even though I don't care
I think it's very smart
For them to have
Here's a wacky one
Here's one for the kids
Here's one for
Women
You know whatever
Because the true fans
Will go see everything
No matter what
But what I heard about this
Quantumania
Is that there's so much
Mythology discussion in that
That any sort of lightness
And comedy
Is just sort of
Beaten to death out of it
Because they have to
You know
Service all this shit
Um
I don't know
Before we
Before we go to the movie corner
One last thing
I want to say about the sheen
This retroactive sheen
We put on everything
Here's the one I'm most sick of
Pat
Yeah
This fucking
Blockbuster nonsense
Guys
Blockbuster was a scumbag
Corporate chain
That put mom and pop video stores
Out of fucking business
They were bad for the business
They destroyed the video
The at home video business
They
The only good thing
That came out of blockbuster
Was the affordability
For the consumer
To be able to buy
Uh
Their own home videos
That was the only good thing
That came out of it
Which
Yeah
You could argue is huge
And Pat and I are huge collectors
So sure
Uh
And that
I would argue that
It's all I have
Yeah it would have become a
Possibility either way
But
Yeah
Blockbuster certainly hit fast
For
The fast forward button on that
But this thing
Where everybody now is like
You know they just
I just saw a new story today
Uh
Internet discovers the original
Blockbuster
Uh
Website
Prepare to be
Nostalgic
It's like
That's
That's like being like
Hey gang
We just
We just unearthed the old
GE website
Let's get nostalgic
It's like
What the fuck
Is everybody talking about
Anymore
Now this is it
Now
It's not enough
That we accept
The corporate bullshit
And the corporatocracy
And the big box stores
And the chains
We accept it
We use them
We don't have to
Crucify Target and Walmart
Whatever
I get it
They're part of life now
We all accept it
That's not enough though
Now I gotta be nostalgic
I gotta walk around
Like
Remember the good old days
Of Walmart
Oh boy
We're getting
Childhood
What the fuck
Are you all talking about
We're getting
Now
Uh
The movies that aren't
Equals
The original movies
And this
Was it you telling me
About this the other day
Joe
It's just like
Everything
We're getting the history
Of corporations
As movies
So like Air
The Nike movie
You're getting
How Air Jordans came to be
As a film
You're getting
The story of how
Tetris came to be
Now we all made fun
Of Tetris
I was like
What is this gonna be
Blocks falling from the sky
Or something
But you come to find out
It's about the making
Of the game
Tetris
These are
These are movies about products
As a video game fan
I am excited to see that
Because
Because it is a crazy story
But
I don't know if the movie
Will be good
But
You know
Look
I know
I'm not
I almost don't want to say this
Because I know you're friends
With the guys
I'm not knocking the guys
I think the original
Idea is very cool
And I really enjoyed the show
But
I'm watching clips
Of Cobra Kai the other night
On YouTube
They got
Machio
Fighting
In a
Somewhere
It looked like a dance club
I don't know what it was
Fighting the bad guy
From Karate Kid 3
It's like guys
The reason Cobra Kai was cool
Was because the sequels
Weren't good
It like
Brought us
It got us back on track
With what made the original story cool
Now we're so
We're mining so much
Here that
That we're into
Like the worst of the sequels
And repeating
The corny set pieces
From those sequels
I got to watch a
60 -year -old
Italian from Long Island
Do karate
With a
70 -year -old man
With a ponytail
This is
Come on guys
It's not the Space Odyssey
If they were
Aliens and magic
I'd be like
They're not
These are regular guys
I will say
In talking to
My friends
Who are comedy guys
At heart
They have a big
Sense of humor
About all that stuff
They know that it's
That it's kind of ridiculous
That's good to know
I haven't seen
The latest couple seasons
But I really like that show
For me
I was just like
Oh okay
It's more of a
Teen -focused show
Like A Stranger Things
Or something
Than I realized
But a lot of
Grown -ups
Love the show
I think more than their kids
I haven't seen it in a while
But I like it
Yeah
I respect the show
I'm just saying
But I'm not picking on them
These legacy things
All do that
Like Star Wars does it
Where it's like
Guys
You're now mining stuff
That everybody didn't like
The first time around
Why are you doing it again?
Yeah
And if you're doing it again
Do it fucking better
You're gonna make a show
Called Obi Wan
About a younger Obi Wan
Played by Ewan McGregor
A character from a
Trilogy of movies
That most people
Were not happy with
I like them
But whatever
Don't go back
And make Obi Wan
As not
Miss the mark
As much as
Half the fucking prequel movies did
Make it better
And it's like
Nope
We're just gonna
Kind of do this again
I just don't understand
I don't get
It's like
Star Wars is gonna come out
With a Jar Jar Binks
Series sooner or later
Yeah
You'll be like
Remember this?
And it's like
Yeah, no, I remember it
We hated it
Baby Jar Jar
Creed 3
I loved
I think Creed 1 is the best
And actually on a rewatch
I think Creed 1
Can kind of hang
With the Rocky franchise
As an equal or better
To a lot of them
I agree
Creed 2
Creed 2 a step down
But on a rewatch
I liked it a lot more
Just because it wasn't
A let down
It was just kind of
I knew were my expectations
A lot
But the problem
Creed 2 makes
Is
We'll have
Drago back
And his son
But
They wound up making
Drago so sympathetic
That you actually
Care about him
And his son's
Kind of nice
And
You know
It's like
You can't bring back
The villains
If they're not going to be
Villains anymore
That's kind of why
Creed 2 didn't work for me
But it was going
The exact same route
As the first one
We're going to do
Basically Rocky babies
And have all their sons fight
Now
I was worried
They were going to
Continue doing that
Like where 3
Was going to be
Mr. T's grandson
Or something like that
Fighting Michael B. Jordan
But instead
They came up
With a very
Cool
Very
Well acted
By Jonathan Majors
And very
Interesting
Troubled character
From Michael B. Jordan's
Past
Who is buff
And hungry
And ready to start boxing
But they have all this
Bad blood between them
Now that's not
An original story
In terms of boxing movies
They've been doing those
Movies since the 30s
But
It breathed a whole
Lot of new life
Into the Creed franchise
Because
Their
Failure so far
Has been villains
Yeah
One and two
I don't think had good
Villains at all
Even Creed
It's not like you care
That much about the
Bad guy
It's the Creed story
But
Yeah
I think this
Needing to tie everything
Together
And have like
Everything be an
Endless
Saga
Is going to just
Destroy movies
It's like
At some point
Nobody's going to
Want to go see
The 12th movie
In a franchise
Because you can't
Start fresh
You know
You shouldn't have to do
A week of homework
To go see a movie
My boycotting of
Creed 3
Is based more on
Stallone's
Unhappiness with it
You know
His being cut out of it
Is that why he wasn't in it?
He's like
I'll never see that movie
He's got a real
Problem with the studio
There's talks of doing
A Drago spin -off
He's like
This producer is a leech
He's bleeding everything
Out of the thing I created
Yeah
Like
Is that Erwin Winkler still?
No idea
Yeah
Because I mean
But Stallone
You
I'll say this
They must have known
What a big
Help
To those Creed movies
1 and 2
Stallone was
Because like
It's a great story
But like
You know
1 and 2
Would have both worked
Without him
I guess
But having him there
In the old lady glasses
Yeah
Being like
Being like the
The Yoda
Or the
Obi -Wan
Whatever
Was perfect
So now that you're missing him
I was like
Oh man
I'm not gonna be into this
I don't think
Until
I think they realized
They had to really beef up
Majors
And get somebody amazing
And they did
And to me
I didn't think about
Rocky after that point
But it sucks that
He's unhappy
About a franchise
That he created
That sucks
I might check it out
At some point
It's really good
And in IMAX
It was awesome
I think
You know
Michael B. Jordan
A significantly better
Director than
Whoever did Creed 2
He's a really good
Director
Of action
In particular
Let's go to the
He also
And now I'm just
Reviewing Creed 2
So this will be my first
Movie I guess
For the movie
Okay
But Creed 2
B. Jordan
I realize I've never
Seen the kid smile
And I just thought
He was like
Mr. Serious
Or he got some bad
Advice from somebody
Or was like
You know
People like you serious
Or something
Or don't show your
Light side
So what's interesting
Is that in this movie
The first time
He's in charge
He's lighter
He's smiling
He's happy
He's funny
He's flirting
With his wife
He's interacting
With his daughter
Which is really sweet
And I bet that was him
I bet like sometimes
These actors are like
Could we give me
A little something
To play
Something fun
Where I'm not just
Scowling and pissed
All the time
And it made all the
Difference
It felt like a new
Franchise sort of
The one thing I saw
About the Creed franchise
That shocked me
Is that
They are planning
A spinoff about Creed's
Daughter
Who is
Four and deaf
So
What is that gonna be
I think this is why
Stallone's not happy
You know they had to go
To Stallone to get
The first one made
He had to like
Green light it
And I think he's
Sitting there now like
I fucking said okay
To this guys
I didn't say okay
To a movie about
The daughter and
Drago's son
Right
Like you know
Anyway
I'll go to
To stay on theme here
A classic film
That was also
The franchise was tarnished
By the far inferior sequels
Silence of the Lambs
I just rewatched
On an airplane
Tough one to watch
Especially when
Jodie Foster has come
Through an interface
I forgot they showed that
By a man named
Mung isn't it
Mink sorry
Miggs is his name
Miggs
Yeah
Miggs thought the same
I was always impressed
By how quickly
He was able to
Produce a load of cum
Unless he had been
Saving a jar or something
The man's been
In a stone cell
So it was just
It was probably your smell
You see a woman
Immediately
Here you go
Anyway
I rewatched Silence of the Lambs
What a fucking masterpiece
I had bought the
Criterion
Blu -ray
A little while back
But I hadn't watched it
I just
I just bought it
And then I was on a plane
And I was like
You know what
I'm gonna watch this now
It's awesome
It's perfectly acted
I think it's the best
Of Jodie Foster
And the best
Of Anthony Hopkins
Of the guy
That plays Buffalo Bill
There's the three
Best performances
I think I've seen
Them do
And they're all
Stellar actors
It's just an awesome movie
I mean there's not much
To say about it
Other than
When you start to read
About what they did
In the sequels
You're like
What?
And you know
Jodie Foster wouldn't do
Hannibal
Because she's like
I don't believe that
She falls in love
She was right
With Hannibal Lecter
At the end of it
I watched Hannibal again
Recently
And I was like
This thing is a
Goddamn mess
I mean it's Ridley Scott
It held my interest
Because
I remember
My dad was a huge
Huge Silence of the Lambs fan
I went to see it
Because it was rated R
And he came home
And was really
Troubled by the
Brain scene
Yeah
My dad has never
Watched a horror movie
He doesn't
He doesn't do
Horror or anything
And he was like
Everyone on the way out
Was talking about
How that was just too much
It was too much
You watch it now
It looks a little
Ridiculous
But it's kind of
Disturbing
When they're eating
Leota's brain in that thing
I
Well, Leota's eating it
He's feeding him
His own brain
Which is a cool idea
But
Lector becomes
A little too
Super villainy
In the second one
Right
Also
The Oldman's character
Is so disturbing
It's
Disgusting
It's just really tough
It's really tough
And I
I don't mean that to
I feel
I will say
One positive
Of social media
For me has been
The enlightenment
To people
Dealing with
Awful things
That I could never
Imagine
People having to
Deal with
I saw a girl
On Instagram
Who was dog
Sitting to make
Extra money
And her face
Got eaten
By the two
Of the dogs
And she's had
To have her face
Rebuilt
And her boyfriend
Stuck with her
Through the whole thing
It's a beautiful
Fucking story
Yeah
So
I feel bad
Saying like
The Oldman
Character is
Disturbing
Because his face
Is all ripped off
You know
Justifying
All over the place
Just to say
I don't mean to say
That callously
It's disturbing though
It's upsetting
And then
But then on top of it
Really what's disturbing
Is it's not just
That he's got his face
Ripped off
It's that
He's also a pedophile
There's a lot
To that character
Where you're like
I don't know man
This is one of our leads
In the film
Yeah
Anyway
The original
Is just airtight
It's a brilliant premise
And then you go
And watch
Red Dragon
Or even
Manhunter
By the great Michael Mann
And you're just like
Yeah this is the same
Fucking story
It's just
You know
And he did write
Manhunter first
The novelist
And then
You know
So
Silence of the Lambs
Is the one
If you haven't seen it
In a while
Check it out
No
Silence of the Lambs
Is the ultimate
I just got the 4K
On Kina Lorber
To put it out
Which I'm
Saving for a special occasion
I'm so fucking
I went on the Criterion
Sale
And it's like
Eight of the fucking movies
That I just bought
And still in the wrapping
Are on there now
For 4K
It's like
Come on man
Yeah
That is why I now
Wait a good six months
Or if it's something
I know
That they'll probably
Put out on 4K
But they're
Look they're a business too
Criterion I think
Laid off
Ten percent of their staff
Or some
They're doing what
They gotta do
Although it sucks
But
Yeah you know
I go see old movies
In the theater
Fairly often
There's all kinds of
Reparatory places around here
But Silence of the Lambs
Is one of the few
That I went to see
That played like
It was opening night
Just like people
Screaming and fucking
Freaking out
And everybody had seen it
It just works like
Gangbusters
Did I tell you
About the William Goldman
Story about
Silence of the Lambs Joe?
No
It's brief
But Jonathan Demme
Who had never done a
Thriller at that point
By the way
And then just casually
Made the best
Thriller ever
He
Did a screening of the movie
For like Spielberg
And all these big people
And it was like a month
Before it came out
And William Goldman
Was there
Because he's considered
The best note giver
In Hollywood
He apparently fixed
Good Will Hunting
And he's a screenplay doctor
So
They go see it
Jonathan Demme and his
Producer
Are like
So fucking excited
Afterwards
Because it played like
Exactly how they
Wanted it to play
Gangbusters
All these huge
Spielberg
All these huge people
Coming up like
Oh my god
You got a hit here
This movie is amazing
And then like
A week later
He told the editor
Like go ahead
And lock picture
We're ready to go
A week later
He gets a call
At home from
William Goldman
The great screenwriter
Of Misery
And Princess Bride
And all these movies
And he goes
Jonathan
I didn't get to
Talk to you
The other night
I just wanted to
Tell you how much
I loved your movie
And he's like
Well thank you
He goes
You're going to hate me
Here though
I got a big cut
That I think is
Going to take it
From an A to an A plus
And he's like
Bill don't even
Tell me man
We locked picture
We're done
And he's like
No I think you're
Going to want to hear it
I think you're going to
Hear it
So he's like
What is it
And apparently
There was a huge scene
Right before
Jodie Foster goes to
The house
You know the greatest
Scene maybe in
Thriller history
When you realize
She's at the wrong house
Yeah
Or when you realize
The FBI's at the wrong
House
They do this amazing
Fake out
That just works
Beautifully
And you're like
Oh fuck
Jodie Foster's
Going to die
And your heart sinks
One of the best
Moments of the movie
And he's like
That's
It's a great scene
But he goes
You got a ten minute
Dialogue scene
Before it
Where Scott Glenn
And Jodie Foster
Like meet up on a
Staircase
And he's like
You don't need to go
Down there
Don't go down there
You're playing too
Risky with the rules
Or whatever
Right
And it was this big
Really well acted scene
And Demi was like
It was Scott Glenn's
Best moment as an actor
In the movie
And he's telling me
You cut that
Ten minute chunk
I'm telling you
The movie's going to
Work so much better
So he goes to his editor
And he's like
Look I would tell him
To fuck off
But it's William Goldman
Can we just run it
And watch it
Without that
Ten minutes
And they do
And then Jodie Foster
Just appears at the house
And they both
Having watched every scene
Of this movie
A million times
Felt like sick
Because they were like
A you're terrified for Jodie
Even though we know
What's going to happen to her
But also this movie
Is a million times better
Without that scene
All right
So they cut it
Pretty incredible
That is incredible
That's interesting
Because I always found it
Confusing when Scott Glenn
Knew when he's like
When he knows
She's in danger
I was like
Wait how does he
I guess they talked
Or whatever
That's why
It was a big conversation
Anyway
That's interesting
What do you got
I got
I watched
And Justice for All
The Pacino film
Talk about waiting
For three fucking minutes
What's that
I said talk about
Waiting for three minutes
That movie
You're just waiting
For the big scene
At the end
And that's it
Yeah
It's Norman Jewison
Who did like
Moonstruck
And all these amazing
Movies
You know Pacino
And his prime
In the 70s
And I was just like
How did I never see this
But
Jack Warden
Right
Who was my favorite
Probably my favorite
Supporting actor
In all of 70s movies
There's two Pacinos
There's three Pacinos
I haven't seen
I think I've seen
Everything else
I never saw
Revolution
Which is supposed to be
A disaster
And actually kind of
Killed his career
For a little bit
In the 80s
There's Author Author
Which is like a
Pacino romantic comedy
That I've never seen
I've seen it
Many times
How's that?
It's like
It's like a
Light hearted Kramer
Versus Kramer
That's always what
It reminded me of
The author is
Kind of going through
A divorce
He's a playwright
It's comedic
It's not heavy
I remember there was
A scene
Where
He goes
The check bounced
And he goes
Oh the check bounced
The check bounced
Hey let me show you
How it bounces
I'll bounce it
Off of you
And he starts throwing
The check at people
Or his producers
Or whatever
But yeah
It's not
Author Author's
Not bad
It's just
Nothing you'd be like
Oh I gotta own it
Right
I'll probably check her out
Although
And Justice For All
Did not really
Win me over
It's not a terrible movie
All 70s movies
Have a vibe
You know
And the supporting cast
Always helps a lot
In these movies
I just love 70s movies
I love the feel
The vibe
But the movie itself
Is very bizarre
It's a
Dark comedy
A lot of the time
Jeffrey Tambor plays
A fellow lawyer
Who is having a complete
Mental breakdown
And that's interesting
I also think that
It was probably
The inspiration
For the Tom Wilkinson
Character in Michael Clayton
Michael Clayton
The ultimate
Legal thriller
It's just a masterpiece
But you got a guy
Who's like
Slowly losing his mind
And it's in the law world
And whatever else
But they don't
Treat anything
Seriously enough
It's all this kind of
Zany comedy
Like Jack Warden
At one point
He's suicidal
He's a judge
Who's suicidal
And he takes Pacino
Out on a helicopter ride
Around the city
Yeah
And Pacino's like
Freaking out and screaming
And it's sort of fun
I guess
But you're like
What am I watching?
This is a courtroom drama
Why is Jack Warden
Flying around Pacino
In a helicopter?
And that's how I felt
About the whole movie
Then it builds
To the scene
You've seen a million times
Where he goes
I'm out of order
This whole courtroom
Is out of order
Yeah, you're waiting for it
And that's a good
Courtroom scene
And that's where Pacino
Finally says he's fed up
With a corruption
And he's fed up
With everything
It's about a judge
Who is accused of rape
And he hires Pacino
As his lawyer
Because everyone knows
Pacino hates him so much
That if he is able
To defend him
He must be innocent
Right
At some point
Pacino learns the guy
Did rape him
Rape the woman
And that's when he
Decides to fight back
Not a bad story
I just can't
For the life of me
Figure out why half of it
Is like a slapstick comedy
And the other half
Is dog day afternoon
It just winds up
A completely schizophrenic
Movie that doesn't work
I got one more
And it'll stay on theme here
How is it?
Oh
Oh no
That's weird
It stays on theme
Accidentally
I was going to initially
Say it stays on theme
Because it's an older movie
That I rewatched
It's a Pacino movie
It's Scent of a Woman
That's so weird
I love Scent of a Woman
It's schmaltzy of course
Sure
The critic had the best
The cartoon the critic
Had the best joke about it
Where he's like
I'm a blind man
That's got magical powers
Because like
Throughout the movie
Chris O'Donnell
Will do some gesture
Without making noise
And Pacino will be like
Don't do that
Don't you do that
In my presence
But anyway
It's like when Ray Charles
Shoots the kid
Who's trying to steal
The guitar in Blues Brothers
So
But again
I watched this on an airplane
I tend to watch stuff
I haven't
I've seen already on an airplane
I find it comforting
And helps me lull into the area
Where I can sleep eventually
So
But I love Scent of a Woman
I will cry
Every time
In the big finale
When Pacino comes to save
Chris O'Donnell's ass
It's just awesome
You know it's a movie
Really about the
Coming of age
Of Chris O'Donnell's character
Through his weekend
With this hard boiled
Ex -military
Monster
Played by Pacino
And Pacino's
Pacino's character
Finding his humanity again
And it's
Fun
It's funny
It's dramatic
And upsetting at times
Pacino's plan in the movie
Is to go have this big final
Elastora weekend
In New York City
And then kill himself
He lost his sight
Because he's an alcoholic
And he was juggling
Hand grenades
And one went off
Near him
When he was drunk
It's just a great movie
I just
Really, really like it
And
I mean you couldn't
Make it now
Also too
You know
People make fun of
Scent of a Woman
People talk about it
Like Bicentennial Man
Or some kind of
Robin Williams
Schmaltzfest
And it's like
It's got the Schmaltz
It's also about a character
That talks
Non -stop
About pussy
Through the entire movie
Yeah
Like you couldn't
Make the fucking movie
Now
Honestly
When I re -watched it
A few years back
The title takes on
A disgusting kind of
Even the title
You're like
He's talking about pussy
Well no
The title means
The perfume
Is the fragrance
Yes
You know what he's talking about
But it's a great
It's a great movie
But I was at
I was
I was in
Austin, Texas
It's one of these movies
And this is what
I love about it
I was in Austin, Texas
And I went over to
The comedy Mothership
To do a set
Which is
Rogan's Club
And my buddy
Chris O 'Connor was there
Who's a really good dude
And a funny comic
And we were
We had had a few
At this point
At the bar
And I brought up
Scent of a Woman
And he was like
Yes
And we were screaming
Scent of a Woman quotes
Back and forth
At each other
It's that kind of movie
You could quote it
If you like it
For like three days
You know
Sure
So
You know
It's worth a watch
It's funny
It's like
I would say like
Oh it's a good watch
With your parents
But it's kind of
A little too crass
I would feel uncomfortable
Watching it with my mom
Sure
To be honest
But
Scent of a Woman
I watched
A horror movie
That I stumbled upon
Called Swallowed
Oh yeah
Which is brand new
It's new to rent
On Amazon
For five bucks
Or something
But
I actually came to it
In kind of an odd way
I
Was wondering
I loved the movie
The Ruins
And
I think it's a very
Underrated
Gross
Intense horror movie
And
I was like
Why did that director
Never make a movie again
Because generally
If you make
Any horror movie
They let you make five
And
I looked him up
That was kind of
It for him
I don't know
If it was difficult
Behind the scenes
But he certainly
Never got any
Sort of respectable
Budget again
And the movie's
You know
15 years old
At this point
The name's
Carter Smith
And I looked him up
And I was like
Oh he's got a movie
Out right now
And I just went
And bought it
It's unfortunately
Not very good
But
What works about it
Is the stuff
That worked for
The Ruins
Which is like
A very
It works for me
A very comfortable
Attitude towards
Sex
Nudity
Roast stuff
Violence
I like movies like that
Where there's just
Kind of anything goes
The plot of this is nuts
It's two best friends
One gay
One straight
But you get the feel
And the straight guy
Would probably blow him
If he asked
And the gay dude
Is going to
Hollywood
To become a
Gay porn actor
Before he leaves
His friend is like
Why don't
I make
I want to make you
A bunch of money
Because you're a good friend
And we've been
Best friends forever
And I want to
Get you some money
So you can have
A good time in LA
When you get out there
So he decides
He is going to run
Drugs for
Jenna Malone
And the drugs
And here's the
Most interesting part
Of the movie
The drugs are
Like bugs
And Jenna Malone explains
It in a monologue
That's perfect
It totally works
To explain this
Crazy premise
You know how
There's those toads
That you lick
And they get you
Crazy high
These are bugs
And you're like
Oh got it
Perfect
And there's these
Little balls
And inside of them
Are bugs that
Hatch out
And they're
They're really great
Drugs
So they shove
A bunch of these balls
Which contain the
Bugs into
The ass
Of the straight man
He's going to take
Them across
The border
They stop at a bathroom
There's a redneck
Who starts a fight
With him
For being gay
Punches him
As hard as he can
In the stomach
And the bugs
Shatter with
Inside of him
That's a really
Really good premise
For a great horror movie
It just doesn't
Quite get there
Unfortunately
It's super low budget
So the script's
Not quite there
But there are
Fisting scenes
In this thing
I mean it's intense
It's kind of funny
At spots
And the villain
Really is
Mark Patton
The gay guy
From Nightmare on Elm Street
Part 2
Oh
Who made that
Whole documentary
About how he feels
You know, taken advantage
Of by that movie
Or whatever
Somebody clearly saw it
And gave him another shot
And he acts the hell
Out of the part
He's really menacing
And really good
It's a movie
With a ton of dick in it
Be ready for that
A lot of flop and dong
A lot of nudity
A lot of graphic ass stuff
You know
Sort of a good
Like
This is the kind of movie
That you'd think
Cronenberg's son
Would make
And you'd be like
All right, nice try
Junior
But Cronenberg's son's
Actually really good
This one just kind of
It's a deep
Decent
Body horror
Low budget effort
All right
Swallowed
Not to be
Swallow
Which is another horror movie
A great horror movie
You ever watch that?
No, I gotta see it
That's really good
I love that movie
Swallow
All right
We're talking
Escape from New York
John Carpenter
Movie number
I think this was
Third or fourth
In his
Repertoire
Somewhere in there
Anyway
Simple enough plot
To folks
It's the future
Crime is outrageous
New York has been walled off
To become a
City prison
The island of Manhattan
There's a 50 foot wall around it
There are no guards
You get dropped in
And you never get out
That's the only rule
Obviously you can imagine
It's a hellscape
Inside of those walls
The president gets
Shot down
Or there's an attempt to
Hijack
Well, somebody does hijack
Air Force One
The attempt is to kill
The president
And everybody on board
The president escapes
From the plane
In an escape pod
Lands in the city prison
And Snake Plissken
Played by Kurt Russell
Who is somebody
Who has just been apprehended
Black ops soldier
Who got caught
Robbing a bank
And is on his way
To be sent in as a prisoner
Is suddenly then
Taken aside
By the powers that be
And say
If you do this suicide mission
And save the president
We will give you amnesty
They up the ante of that bargain
By implanting explosives in his neck
Where if he betrays them
Or doesn't get the job done
He will die
When they trigger the explosives
There's a lot of stuff in this movie
That you can see in other movies
And other things
It's very comic book -y
I don't know which came first
This or these other things
But the bomb in the neck thing
Is Suicide Squad obviously
The suicide mission
Is Suicide Squad
I believe Suicide Squad
The comics existed before this
But I don't know if the bomb device
In the neck thing did
The city prison is Arkham City
Which they did in Batman
It also kind of reminded me of Crank
The whole idea that like
Something within you could blow up
You know
Yeah, yeah
Crank's obviously way after Escape
And then of course Snake Plissken
He's Nick Fury
He's got the eye patch
He's amazing with guns
He's superhuman
But he's not actually
He's just human
And that's the movie
You know
I always say about Escape from New York
Escape from New York is sort of
The quintessential 80s
It is this thing
Like when you went into a video store
In the 80s
Every cover of every movie
Looked like it was going to be
This movie or Terminator 1
Those were the two movies in the 80s
You thought anything you rented
Was going to look like this
The Exterminator
They had like a million things
That even sounded like those movies
Yeah
It is
From a
I think it's an extraordinarily
Directed film
And I would say this about it
From a visual standpoint
This is the movie where you see
Why things went wrong with John Carpenter
John Carpenter still made this kind of movie
With
For instance, Ghosts of Mars
But Ghosts of Mars was made on much higher definition film
With very different textures
And lighting and colors
And clarity and all that stuff
And when you put this kind of movie
By the way, so was Escape from LA
Yeah
And when you put this kind of movie on film like that
It looks fucking ridiculous
When you got it on grainy dark footage like this
It looks fucking amazing
You know
So
And the movie itself is well done
Sorry
It's incredibly well done
No, no, no
It's
For me, I ask Joe
Are you ever confused by the beginning of this movie?
I've seen Escape from New York five times in my 40 years
And I am always confused by the beginning
And I was here again
So when Joe explains what happens
I'm like
Yeah, that's exactly what happens
But it happens so fast
Like it's almost like they could have just put it in a little
One of those computer screen things
Where they tell you what happened
Because to me it's so fast
So many things happen in that opening five minutes
That I'm not caught up
I admire it
I love that he doesn't like explain everything to you
You get that little piece of information
That Manhattan is now a war zone
And it's a prison and blah, blah, blah
And then it's off to the races
You got Donald Pleasance as the president
Yep
You got
You know, once that's in motion
You know, Pleasance is basically
It's basically just a rescue mission for him
But also Kurt Russell doesn't give a shit about the president
Carpenter's themes and what's important to him
Are always very obvious
You know, like the fact that Plissken, our hero
Was caught robbing a bank
That's because Carpenter hates capitalism
Which you can see come out even more
And they live in other movies of the 80s
But I think what happened to him was not just that
These movies started looking too good for what they are
I think Carpenter seems like a guy who more than anybody
Was burnt out by studio notes and everything
And just kind of gave up and stopped trying
He talks about that experience with Chevy Chase on memoirs
As kind of his end of the road
Like he was just like, I can't do this
Why am I doing this?
And it's sad
I mean, the guy has been lost for a while
But talk about a rediscovery
Everybody loves Carpenter now
As well they should
We talked about his amazing run last time
This movie uses like matte paintings and stuff
In a brilliant way
You can see the low budget
You know at times you're looking at a painting
Or you're looking at something a little like
All kinds of camera trickery
And yet you never for a second doubt
That you're watching exactly what the movie is
And they do it on a shoestring
It's really impressive
But those tricks
Like somebody driving into a painting that's in the distance
Again, movies look too good now
That could never work
There's something beautiful about it
Especially on the 4K
Because it really makes you see how much work went into these backgrounds
I don't know, the movie
Vibe wise I love
Action wise I love
Plot wise I love
And I love Kurt Russell
But it's another one that's always left me a little cold
I think it's just because the thing is so amazing
But I love two or three Carpenters
And I put the rest in kind of a B plus A minus range
And that's where I put Escape as well
It's a hell of a lot better than Escape from LA
Well there are arguments that Escape from LA
Is a further commentary on everything
And that it's
It is, I mean they got the plastic surgery world and everything
And they say themselves
It's making fun of these big Hollywood movies
I don't know if that's true
And Carpenter's the kind of guy that would never tell you anything
He's big on that whole let them think whatever
It's better for the movie
By the way, you can get this
The 4K set available now on Amazon
I was wrong
Now there are no special features
But for 50 bucks
You get Escape from New York
They Live, The Fog, and Prince of Darkness
In 4K?
In 4K
No special features but in full 4K
I'm gonna get that
That seems very worth the money
That's great
Anyway
What I liked most about Escape from New York
Is kind of like what I was saying earlier about
I forget
Well I said it on the last episode about The Fog
I think it's an airtight story
I think from point A to point B gets you there
Doesn't complicate anything
I like that it's the classic
You know Carpenter said about The Fog
He's like oh classic
The ghosts come back for revenge
That's a classic trope and I think it works
And this is a classic trope
The anti -hero has to go in to save the president
It doesn't get any more exploitation film than that
That sounds like it would be the plot of Machete
Yeah
Or whatever
And I think it is the plot of Machete
Right
I think
And I think budget wise it probably wouldn't have allowed for it
But I would have liked to have actually learned
A little more about the inter workings of the prison
And you get a little bit of that
You get a little insight of the politics of this prison world
With the Duke being played by Isaac Hayes who's great
Yeah
The brain who's being played by
What's his face?
Harry Dean Stanton
And the Duke is sort of the kingpin of everything in there
The brain is the guy that's figured out how to potentially escape
And he lives in the library and he's diagramming all this stuff about
Because all the escape routes out of the city are loaded with land mines and stuff
You've got Barbeau in there kicking ass
I always love seeing her
Yeah
Married to Carpenter at that time
And then you got Russell of course
I love Russell even in his corniest moments in this I still love him
And again I think it might be tongue in cheek
I think it's supposed to be kind of funny
Oh for sure
I have heard
I've only watched one of them but I have heard that the Carpenter Russell commentaries are the funniest commentaries available
I've only listened to the one on The Thing but apparently this one has a great commentary as well
And they do just crack up the whole time like they think these movies are hilarious
I love like Russell tells the main you know the general whatever it is
The guy that the head of secret service or whatever who sends him in on the mission
Like when he secretly implants Russell with the explosives Russell goes when I get back I'm gonna kill you
And then at the end when he oh and then Donald Pleasant says the president
He's awesome
I mentioned sorry
He when he gets back from saving the president the guy goes you're gonna kill me now snake and he goes I'm too tired
Which is a great moment
And the end is awesome
The plot of the movie is he has to save the president
Why not just because it's the president but because the president has on him an audio cassette
I always love that too when they do a movie about the future
But they don't realize they're not gonna have cassettes anymore. It'll be right different
He's got to take five minutes to explain what the future version of an audio cassette is who gives a shit
Yeah, he's the president is flying to a conference a NATO conference to make peace
Yeah, where World War three happens and in order to do that
He's got a cassette tape for whatever reason where these where the peace plan has been recorded
Right play for the heads of Russia and China and hope no backup. They didn't write it down. It's all just on the tape
Yeah
So when they realized you can make a dub of a tape in about 45 minutes a complete dub
It costs one dollar the cost of an extra tape. Yeah, that should be in the opening scroll. There are no more tape recorders
Prime is the year is 1997. No one can duplicate tapes
They they when they realize the Air Force one is going to get hijacked and they're gonna die and the president has to escape
They give him the only copy of the tape
So they tell snake you have to get in you have to get a copy of this tape or you have to get this tape with the president
Because without this tape World War three is going to happen. Yeah, so he saves the president
the
He has the tape on him
The president when he goes to talk to him about
What transpired and all the people that died in a way to save his life Donald Pleasants suddenly is no longer a great guy
He's just like well snake. I don't know what to tell you. We all make sacrifices and then snake
Well, fuck you. He goes to the general the generals like do you have my tape? Yes, he gives it to him snake saves the world as
To queue it up for this thing
And oh it that's right. It's being televised the president's going on air to play this thing this speech or whatever that's on the tape
They play the tape and it's the music that was playing in a cassette player in the Duke's
Chambers or some shit. I can't remember and
You realize snake swapped the tapes and as snake pluskin is walking away after you're disappointed that he didn't kill the general
He takes the tape from his pocket and rips all the tape that he realized that he's out of spite now
I'm gonna cause World War three
Which is awesome. Yes, and that's the moment when I realized the mistake they made in my opinion
They made with snake pluskin snake pluskin should not have been an escape from LA
Snake pluskin should have been in big trouble in little China
He should have been Indiana Jones
It should have been like snake pluskin and the and the pit of dimensions or whatever
They should have sent him to do all crazy adventures and that this should have been how it all started. I
Agree. I mean you could you could essentially make
Big trouble in little China with him playing that role and not change any dialogue other than what people refer to him as yeah
The thing you couldn't I mean the thing you need a another guy, but yeah, you I would have loved that
Yeah, snake pluskin franchise
Anyway, thumbs my hogs up for escape from New York my hogs up as well. I think it's
Upper mid carpenter. I think I would say upper mid, but I love it
a lot of people been asking us and asking Emily apparently a
Lot of people asking what is up with me and Joe. We did not even have a particularly stressful month
So I guess we just kind of need to re -explain we're if you're subscribing and you want four episodes and why wouldn't you?
Will give you four episodes a month between the first and the 30th or between the first and the 31st
There's no set time. They're supposed to drop
There's a time that we've kind of established that they are probably gonna drop
But all you've got to know and trust is that we'll get you your four episodes each month
And that will get you your movie corner once a month
And the one time I didn't make it you got to the next month. So
We'll always get you there. We'll never screw you over
No, and you might have to wait a little bit
But the waiting is the hardest part as Tom Petty once sang and yet absence makes the heart grow fonder as I said
I even met to that expression. We will get you there people. We appreciate the support as always
Which is why we are explaining ourselves and we appreciate you being out there if you're in the Chicago
Michigan Illinois area that you know, whatever, you know what I mean that whole area Midwest
I'm doing a bunch of shows this coming week. I
Get out there. I think hamtrank. I think that's how you say it right hamtrank
Is apologies if I miss said that I'm stupid and I don't know geography
anyway
I get out there this
Coming Thursday for one show
I'm just pulling up my shows. Sorry guys plugs. Hey, yeah ham tramp tramp
Michigan independent comedy club this
Wednesday Thursday March 30th. We added a second show. Thanks for selling out the first show
Second show has been added Grand Rapids, Michigan
Midtown Grand Rapids
Is the name of the venue to show no one show that night the April 1st is Chicago, Illinois Reggie's rock bar
Added a second show there. Thank you very much, Chicago for selling out the first show and then Batavia, Illinois comedy vault April 2nd
And then April 6th here in this East Coast Stanford, Connecticut at New York Comedy Club Stanford
Come on out doing the new hour at all of them
I hope to see you there and come to Joey roses in in NYC if you are in NYC Joey roses and wise
Joey wrote for Christ sakes
Come on out people you get it
I got a bar and sandwich shop here and come to the shows Joe DeRosa info comm for tickets to the shows by the way
the Patrick Walsh at Instagram and Twitter just did my buddy Ben Rogers brand new podcast the
Garage tapes, which I don't think I told you the first time but now I can tell you is a
Movie discussion show
About movies that don't exist. So I did the first episode we discussed an erotic thriller for an hour
But it was all improv. There is no real movie. I think it's a great idea for a pop cast
I had a lot of fun doing it. You can check that out
And that's it the Miss Pat show
Season two and three are currently airing one on BET plus one on BET as always if you're gonna watch the show
I recommend BET plus the episodes are ten minutes longer and full of all kinds of dirty jokes and r -rated material
And that's it. We will be back with a review of
knock at the cabin
we have also been made aware that the next episode is our 300th episode and
We'd like to at least
Acknowledge that but me me and Joni to talk and see what we're gonna do there
Thank you all for your support. You love your patreon magic
As always I see people getting double -charged
Reach out to Emily reach out to me whatever and just trust that we'll get your money back and we're not doing it intentionally
Patreon is a very glitchy website. Apparently. Thank you all. We will see you next time and we will see you in hell