I see you on the drain, I'm gonna say n ee ee ee
I see you on my drain, you know I say n ee ee
Hi folks, Helians. Welcome to the first ever. We'll see you in
Hell bonus episode. Things are going to go a little differently on
these apps. They're for you. Patreon subscribers that gave ten
sweet dollars or more to what we hope is your favorite or one of
your favorite podcasts. We thank you and this episode is just for
you folks. Nobody else gets it. You're exclusively in the
exclusive zone. And I'll tell you, it's where it's pet. It's where
it's pat. What does that mean? It's where it's at. Oh, it's where
it's pat. You know, I don't think it's going to catch on. I don't
think it will either, but you don't have a name that's it's I mean,
a good name, but it's hard to put it into a thing like there's no
like phrase I could think of. I've hated my name since the it's
Pat character hit the airwaves right as I was entering puberty.
How about this? Congrats, you're getting the bonus episode
because you gave to the highest donation tier time to patch
yourself on the back time to pat yourself. Yeah, how about
compacts? That's worse than either of them. Nothing's great.
Folks, we're having a lot of fun here tonight. But I think it's
time for us to get on with the show. And and in the process
on who with the gym. Now I should have said this before we
started recording, I don't think you should do that in these
episodes. I think people would riot if I didn't. I think these
should be like like how Star Wars puts out like Rogue One. There
is no opening crawl in these episodes. These are different.
These are special. No, I think I think the people want the
show with the Joe. I don't think anybody's going to take
your side on this. Hope we could start a new thing where I on
these episodes, I say a pat thing. Well, I mean, I'm telling you,
none of those are catching on. It might be something for the for
week two. Okay. But it was none of those. I'll try it next week
again or next month. Month two, these are once a month.
Folks, I want to tell you about the day I had. I'm getting
very down on our society. Well, I wouldn't you. Now,
obviously, everything that's happening in the news is a
disaster. And I'm not going to get political. I'm talking, but
I'm talking about everything. I'm talking about Harvey Weinstein.
I'm talking about everything. It's also like everyone's kind of
been joking about Harvey Weinstein sexually assaulting people
for decades. And it was kind of like a weird joke. And then
now I'm called him out for raping her. Like a couple of years
ago, and everyone was like, all right, Rose, I found out yesterday
she was she was banned from Twitter for it. She got banned from
Twitter. Twitter brought her back. Man, Twitter, what a bunch of
fucks. They're real fucks over there. Twitter is as bad as it
gets. I was taking the lengthy walk from your gate to your
apartment door. I decided to check in with Twitter. And I had
been been been away from it for a bit. And what I saw was I
forget the exact name. Let me bring it up. But it was a new breed
of guy who is so homophobic that he will not wipe his ass. There
was a Buzzfeed article about this that is being shared. So
who walk around with a shitty asshole because he thinks
touching his ass is gay to avoid putting his his hand and his
ass man's missing out on one of the greatest joys in life by
the way. You consider wiping your ass a joy. One of the only
high points of my day is really getting in there. Oh my God.
And getting it clean. I enjoy that. Oh boy. It feels good. It's
a man's G spot. Ladies. It's called septic masculinity. When
homophobia presents, prevents men from literally wiping
their own asses septic masculinity. I had to look at my Twitter
likes and in doing so I want to I want to call attention to a great
follow Mr. David Angela one of my favorite comedians. I like
David quite a bit. And here's this tweet. Dr. Phil's guests are all
crisis actors, right? I mean, this family can't get their son to
stop using drugs, but it'll hop on a plane to talk to Phil. The
next one is a little play sobbing. He's violent. He's abusing
drugs. He won't listen to us. Where is he now? Drinking
LaCroix in the green room?
hilarious. Follow David Angela. He's a great man and a very
funny man. That's very funny stuff. Um, folks, I called a
lift. And how many occasions I've been frustrated with a lift on
my way over here. And yes, I'm responsible enough to know that if
I hang out with Joe, there'll be drinks and I need to lift this
woman. I'm hearing that more frequently for more friends and that's
all right. Don't worry. You want a friend who encourages you to
drink and you're that friend. That's good. You kind of rolled in
here. We're ready to do it today. I needed to do it. Yeah. That's
got the shirt wide open speaking of Weinstein rolls in. He's got
chest hair out on this button down. Wearing an open robe and
nothing underneath. Yeah. I call, I have to call the lift and the
Uber to a different address than my own. Because if I simply type in
my address, they go to the street below mine. So already, it's
like, yeah, guys, we have the technology. So I enter the
address. I enter the address across the street. This and everyone
can find it that way. It's worked a million times. This
girl tonight, she's nowhere to be found. I get a text. She's
here. I walk outside. She's not there. This happens very, very
often. I'm like, okay, what's going on? She calls. Hi, um, and I'm
hearing the way's voice talking louder than her in my ear. Yeah.
Her radio is full volume. And she opts to add a phone call into
the mix without turning anything down. So I answer the phone and
it's like, hang on, hang on, hang on. Just three people screaming in
my ear. So I said, ma 'am, I can't hear a word that you're saying.
What do you need for me? She goes, where are you? That's how she
starts it. This is a woman who is supposed to be providing me a
service. You're getting me. You're getting me all wound up. I
said, ma 'am, I am at my address. I'm at my address that I enter.
I don't know what to tell you. She goes, well, can you look on the
app, but with disgust in her voice? Can you look on the app and see
where I am and tell me where I need to go? This is how she's starting
the conversation. Not not. And by the way, there's a million ways to
start it where I'm not mad at you at all. I understand GPS can
fuck up. What I've been there. She's disgusted with me. She goes,
well, then can you find me on on the map and tell me where to go?
I look at the thing. I would have said, no, I would have said
bye. Yeah, exactly. Seriously, I look at the thing. I'm like,
all right, you're on my street, but you're, you know, two minutes
away, just turn around and come back down the street. She goes,
well, I'm looking at this thing and it says I'm at your house.
I said, but you know where I am and you know that you're there and you
called me to know, you knew I wasn't there, right? Right. She
goes, sir, sir. And then finally I had to say, can you please turn
off either the ways or the radio, ma 'am? I can't hear what you're
saying. She goes, okay, well, what I need you to do. And now she's
practically yelling, is tell me how to get to your house? I said,
okay. Drive down my street. You're on it. And she goes, but sir,
there is a fork in the road. Oh my god. So when I was coming
down the street, I made a left. Are you saying I need to take a
right? And this is the voice she's using. I said, there is no
fork in my road. So I don't know what to tell you. Hold on.
Sorry. I didn't know my ring. Sorry. That was an accident. That
was an accident. Sorry. Sorry. Sorry. About the bonus episodes
that disaster. I said, there's no fork in my road. So I don't know
what to tell you. But just drive your face in the wrong way
drive down to me. So now I'm guiding her while on speaker phone
watching her little toy car on the lift app, make its way down to
my house. She says, I don't see you. I don't see you. I said, right,
you're still a minute away. Oh my god. She's driving. She goes,
sir, I don't see. And I said, look, I put my address in. So you
have it, right? Right. I'm telling you, you're on my street.
Look for my number. Right. She says, okay. And hangs up on me.
Why did you not cancel this right? I don't understand. I'm waiting.
I'm waiting. I'm hovering over a cancel because if I if I do
that, then I get here 20 minutes light. I'm waiting. I'm waiting.
I'm waiting. She does not come. I call her back. I said, I don't
I don't understand how you're not here by now. She goes, well,
you told me there wasn't a fork. And I'm here at the fork.
So I said, can you just put your car in park? And I will walk to you.
She goes, okay, okay. This is the level of customer service we're at.
So I walk because it's because it's your fault, Pat, that she,
yeah, she because she should make money for not knowing how to do
anything. Right. I don't everybody's attitude now. I should just make
money because it's a do a thing to want the one thing you're supposed to do.
Do it. Okay. Fucking a. This is coming on the heels of Heather and I went
out the other night. And the girl is practically screaming at us because of
how narrow my street is. Yeah. I got into a lift. The other night.
Now here's why can't call a lift. And I'll say this flat out. I know
Uber's got a lot of evil under its belt. As far as far as ride share goes,
evil is the is the most devilish. Uber is the most devil. Uber is, excuse me,
is the most devilish. Uber is the wall. Is your first drink of the night?
Yeah. Why? What did I just say? You're saying words in the place of other words?
What did I say? You said like evil instead of Uber. Oh, well,
they're similar words to me. Okay. Evil Uber. Yeah. No, that's why I'm dealing
with it. Yeah. No, I was not. Okay. I wasn't, you know, not in that bad estate.
Uber is the most devilish of all of all the apps. Uber is the Walmart
of ride share services. Yeah. However, lift is the Walmart of ride share services.
Lift is terrible. And do you get what I'm saying? I do. It's like you're, you're not,
you're not going into a Walmart for customer service. No. It's like you're on your own.
Find the shit wherever it is. Yeah. They're terrible. And I don't want to support Uber.
And I'm not saying I've had a great experience with them either, but this was nuts.
I will say I know at the top of the Uber chain, there's some really nasty shit.
It's mostly at the top. And I know some of the drivers have done some nasty shit.
But I will say this, I had an incident recently with Uber and they really came through for me
customer service. Why? I had a driver who said it's flat out said to me, I'm crazy.
Okay. And then went on and made up all these like bullshit stories about me being an
unruly customer. And Uber called me and I just went through the whole thing with them.
And they were just like, we believe you, we know you're telling me truth.
Like, and they were very helpful. They gave me like bonus money and all the shit.
Right. So I appreciated that, you know, I don't think you're going to, like, I work on the
Warner Brothers lot. You get a parking ticket on the, on the Warner Brothers lot. It's a, it's a
joke. Yeah. Obviously, it's a joke. I would hope so. So when Uber will try, like, I'll get a ride,
I got a ride canceled on me leaving the bowl the other night. The Hollywood bowl. After petty.
That's exactly right. I wanted to meet you guys at the roast. Did we talk about seeing petty
two days before? We did. We must have. Okay. Sorry. But I wanted to meet you guys out of the bar.
And I left, I was walking out while I was playing American girl. I beat the rush. Yeah. That's
what we did, too. I'm out there. I'm waiting. I'm waiting. I'm waiting. This girl calls me.
Honestly, it was a similar ride. She was like, I'm not seeing you. And I said, well, where are you?
She was among Kahwanga. I said, I'm on Highland. I said, that's what I've entered here. Highland and
Odin. You have that information. There's no way they don't know where you're at. Right. So she's like,
well, how far is that from Kahwanga?
It's nuts, dude. I got into a lift last night because Uber,
I don't remember why, but I picked a lift for whatever reason. Yeah. You know, my mood determines
which one I'm going to go with. Pink. It stands out. Oh, I remember why. I took a lift last night
because I couldn't remember the address of where I was going. Okay. And I didn't feel like
searching through the dark part here, folks, as it was his home. It was, I didn't feel like doing
the thing where you got to dig through a million emails to find the, and I was like, you know what?
Lift doesn't require the address. I know how to get there. I'll just tell the guy. Right.
Says, when I book the ride, do you care to enter the address? I say no. It says fine. Right.
Guy shows up. This is the first thing that bug me. It's at three minutes. I'm waiting. I'm waiting.
I'm waiting. It's like five minutes. I look at the app. It says we found you have even better driver.
Yeah. It's like, no, you didn't. The driver canceled. Don't rub my balls. Just tell me what happened.
Yeah. But whatever. So now the other driver comes. It's taken twice as long as it was supposed to,
but whatever. I get into the car. The guy goes, where are we going? I said, I'm going to direct you.
He goes, he turns me. He goes, you didn't put the address in the thing. No, I didn't.
And as a driver for this service, you should be aware that that's an option of mine. Yeah.
I don't have to do that. I will direct you. Right. And he goes, and I didn't say that part.
But I go, I go, so I'll just tell you where to go. And he goes, okay. And immediately it's like,
it's like this, this, this, now this, this, this, there's this energy like we're defusing a bomb or
something danger it. Like you can't even wrap his head around that you were probably going to
pee. It's right. Five minutes. Yeah. Yeah. And I go, five minutes away. I go, go back out to
Losfields Boulevard and head towards Losfields. Yeah. Didn't know how to do that. I had to tell him
which direction Losfields was in, which is where he just came from. How are you a driver and don't
know the basic streets? It's like so, so he didn't know that Losfields was to the right and Glendale
was to the left. Right. Fine. I jump. We're on Losfields Boulevard. There's, there's bumper to
bumper traffic. As always, I say, listen, I'm on the phone, by the way, with my friend Jerry,
who's my buddy of mine since high school, who's telling me about how his mom died three weeks ago.
Okay. And we're trying to have like a heart to heart. And we had already been talking for a while.
And he's like, dude, if you got to go, don't worry about it. You're in the car now. And I was like,
Jerry, it's fine. We can still talk. Like I want to talk to you about this shit.
And I say to the driver, I said, Jerry, hold on one second.
Sir, so we're going to be on Losfields for a bit. Listen, you're going to make a left on Hill Hurst.
Right. That should be the end of that exchange. I go back to my phone.
Guy turns around and goes, well, where is that? Is that the next light? And I go, no,
it's not the next light. It's coming up like you, and I start getting attitude because it's like,
dude, fuck you. It's not my job to make you a decent driver. If you can't fucking, it's the base,
it's basic shit. It's basic shit. If you can't even be responsible enough to say, I'm going to keep my
eye out for the street we need to turn on to. And and had he said, okay, cool. Is that a ways down
or whatever? Like, yeah, fine. I got you. I would have said it's half of mine. What was that the
next light? It's just, I can't stand this shit. I can't fucking stand it, man. Everybody went, you
know what? And I do think it's appropriate. We're talking about this on the first ever bonus app.
How long we do this podcast? Two years before we even put a Patreon page up. Yeah. And said,
like, hey, if you want to donate, it'd be nice. Thank you. We would like to try to make some cash off
of this thing. Sure. Two fucking years before we even dared say, like, yeah, if you want to donate,
please do. If you feel like it. Yeah. And like, everything has flipped to the customer is an annoyance.
Yeah. Like, I was just trying to drive, but now I got this loser in the back seat. No, no, no,
that's not, that's not the way this works. And my hats off to my hats off to booze, cheese sticks.
One of my favorite spots. They are not a sponsor. I just love the place. And silver lake.
Great. I went there today for lunch. It's an awesome cheese steak. And if you live in LA.
And great customer service. I'm sure. I tell the lady at the counter what I want. She flips the
little screen around. She goes, is that correct? Yeah. I go, that is correct. I order my food to go.
I go sit outside on one of the picnic tables to get some sun. Yeah.
Guy comes out, yells, my name gives it right to me. Sure. So it's like, yeah. And you know what?
I tip 15 % at the counter for that. Sure. You know, it's not a way. It's not a waiter coming out.
I tip. Yeah. It's time to get it to go. I'm still tipping. And it's good customer service.
Now ask for tips as well. And I'll do it when, when warranted this lady tonight, after all that,
then she starts driving forward. And I'm watching her ways because she has a GPS. And it says,
turn left on Claremont. And she is making a right. And I said, ma 'am, it's a left. And she was,
oh, thanks for letting me know. You have a GPS. The lady the other night who can't find Highland,
arguably the biggest street in Los Angeles. So now I've beaten the rush. I missed Tom Petty's second
to last performance of American girl to beat the rush. And she's nowhere to be found. So then
I get the we're sending somebody else to come get you. This girl calls me. She's furious.
She's like, where are you? And I said, well, I'm down at the best Western because the other girl
who was lost, I said, I'll meet you halfway. You're on Cojanga. I'm on Highland. Let me meet you down
here at the best Western. That's the halfway point. She goes, great. During the interim, she cancels
the ride on me. Right. So now I'm at the best Western. Then they send somebody else to get me,
but they send them to the old address. So this girl's like, where are you? And I said, I'm at the best
Western. Why are you there? It says you're at this intersection. I said, I know, but I spoke to the
previous driver. She was lost. So I agreed to be here because previous driver. I'm the only driver.
Oh my god. She didn't even know about the other thing. She hangs up on me and I'm on on driver three.
I didn't go out, as you well know, because I was furious. Right. Now today, I wake up. Recently,
I judged an aspiring TV writer forum sponsored by PlayStation. Right. A bunch of kids, you know,
well, you know, freshman in college basically pitched some TV showrunners, including myself,
their idea for a show and the best five out of 10 who were out of like 10 ,000 got to produce a pilot
that it's going to air on PlayStation. Great. So some of the kids had really great ideas. It was very
fun. And then as a nice little bonus treat shows up at my house last night, PlayStation four,
VR headset, all kinds of accessories and ship. Beautiful. So I wake up.
I'm kind of hungover from last night. We had our dear friend Pete's bachelor party. Not hungover,
but I was high. So it just felt dumb. Right. Joe proposes a diner hang. We go. It's great.
I come home and Heather, my girlfriend had just watched Broad City this week. And on Broad City,
they had mushrooms. This way, the episode was about them being on mushroom. Right. Heather's like,
what are mushrooms like? I've never done. I go, well, I have like a chocolate bar of mushrooms in
the fridge. So she goes, well, could we do it sometime? I of course. Right.
They're that we get them out. I'm making sure we have them whatever it. But in my stupidness this
morning, when I come back, I see a piece of chocolate and I throw it at my mouth. It's a very minor
dose of mushrooms. But it's how I started my day. Jesus Christ. Honestly, it felt like a few hits
a week. Okay. It was pretty minor. But I was like, okay. And then I'm feeling good. I had a very
stressful week as I always do. And I'm like, I'd love to just play this PlayStation and not have to
set it up. I want to just play the thing. So I'm sitting there. I'm looking at home audio people
online and reading reviews and everything. And I'm like, fuck this. I can hook up a PlayStation.
I'm a grown man. I go to hook it up. Not only do I not successfully set up the PlayStation,
one cable to an HDMI to your TV. Well, I also ruined my cable viewing, my turn table viewing. So
now I can't listen to music. I ruined everything. How? Because the setup in my home is in a closet
that is rooms away from the television. And I just didn't think it through. I've been plugging
things into the wrong thing. So I go, fuck this. I'm calling a professional. I call a guy. This guy comes
in my house. He shows up. He goes, what do you want to do, Armadian guy? I go, I'm just trying to set
up a place. This guy's job is setting up home theater systems. I told him on the phone, I want to set
up a PlayStation. And I got too many chords. I got all these chords. It looks like a god damn,
you know, like Christmas vacation in there. I go, you just want to clean down so that I can
as ludicrous said once, open his trunk so many wives, it looks like a bowl of spaghetti. That's correct.
Yeah. I said, I just want to look in there and not be intimidated and know that if I want to plug
A into B, it's not going to fuck up my whole system. I go, the guy that set it up did, he's trying
to do too much. So he's looking at it, he goes, okay, okay, gets in there. He's looking at it.
You can, I'm starting to realize almost immediately he doesn't know what a PlayStation is. He's like a
55 row guy. Oh boy. So he's looking at it. He's looking at it. Then he comes in. My TV is mounted on
the wall, you know, and it was a very professional job and not a cheap job either. That's where this is,
this is exactly where I'm against the wall mount is because you can't get to anything. But it was all
set up that you can do it in this back closet. But this guy's I guess old school. But he's also a guy
who all he does, it's like when they, when they, anyone like who's coming to repair a toilet or something
comes to your house and they start asking you questions about, it's like, I don't know anything about
toilets. You're a plumber. Like I just, I hate it so much. So he comes in and they make you feel stupid.
But he's looking at it and he goes, well, how do I get to the wires on the back of the TV? How do I get
to the wires? But I said, well, they're in this back room. I said, sir, with all due respect.
It's exactly what I said to him. I said, with all due respect. If all you do is home theater setups,
have you never seen a TV that's mounted on a wall? Right. And he stares at me. There's a bit of a
language barrier. But he goes, no, so the plugins are behind the TV. I said, well, maybe, and while I'm
answering his question, I should also point out that below my TV, on my, on my little
cabinet is a pricey high -end turntable because I really get into my vinyl and my music.
You like your records. I like my records. And it's a nice system. Speaking of which, I got some gems
today that I'd like to talk about. I loved, I'd love to hear it. But, you know, of course, it's the glass
top, the glass top, to the turntable. And it's right under the TV. And this guy, and I am not exaggerating,
who is a, let me just say it a third time, a home theater installation expert, grabs with both hands
the side of my flat screen TV on my wall and yanks seemingly as hard as he can, the left side of
the television. I'm not kidding. Did it rip out of the world? A piece of plastic from the back
goes shatters and goes flying out the right side of the television. I jump off the couch because
that's where I should be on the couch, letting the professional fix it. Right. Because I called him to
do so, I jump up and in the nick of time, grab the TV, a 55 inch television, as it falls off the wall.
And into my hands, because if I hadn't jumped up, it would have landed on my expensive turntable
that was below it. And both would have broken. Both would have broken. Yeah. And I said, you know,
to be honest, I lost it. I caught myself pretty quickly, but I was like, what are you doing?
What are you doing? He's like, well, sorry, he's like, it should be hooked up better. It should be
hooked up better. I said, you're yanked. It's wall mounted. I haven't had a problem in three years,
then you yanked it off the wall. So he goes, you have it. Do you have it? I said, no, I don't have it.
You need to help me. So I start trying to move my turntable. And I'm unplugging something
that is very carefully wired and hooked up, trying to protect it. So then I get it down.
We get the TV re -hooked up on the wall. So it looks okay on the wall again.
Looks okay on the wall. He's like, sorry, sorry. He goes out to his truck, puts on one of those like
coal miner helmets with the light. How was he neat that for? Looks behind it. And he goes, oh,
here it is. Moves the TV a quarter of an inch and finds the hook in that he needed. Plugs it,
there was no tech. He was going to just yank the fucking thing off. I don't know what he thought he was
doing. Jesus Christ. And honestly, once I started talking to him at the end of the night,
I'm at the end of the transaction. I was smelling alcohol and I had had nothing to drink.
Well, you were on mushrooms. I had had nothing to drink. I know, but I'm saying you were
on mushrooms. You sure you were smelling alcohol. The lowest of doses. I mean, I wasn't like
spiraling or something. Right now, right there. But talk about an experience you don't want to have
when you're on any dose of mushrooms. The guy finds it plugs it in. He sets up the PlayStation.
We kind of basically I wind up setting it up in the end because he doesn't understand what
this cost you. I'll tell you, we get the PlayStation set up. Then he goes, okay, you're good to go.
He's going to write a leave my home. There's shards of the TV connecting device on the floor of my
living room. There are cords dangling out the back of my television. And the PlayStation is sitting
on my coffee table. Well, so I'm worried about you. You're real. You're real. This is high tension
right now. I'm serious. You're having a stressful week. And then this is your Saturday. By the
way, this place has five stars on Yelp. Those are probably fake reviews. So I said, sir, you can't
leave here. He goes, what's the problem? I go, so for starters, I go, do I need any of this
shit that's sitting on the floor that fell out of the back of my television? He goes, no, you can throw
away. Okay. I'll do that. But obviously, I don't want my PlayStation on my coffee table. I want it
set up in my closet that I have for my Blu -ray player and et cetera. Well, you can't do that. He did
it. And it works. Oh, we did. Okay. So you have it. So the PlayStation is accessible, but in the closet.
We set it up, you know, it's close enough that the sensors pick up and everything. So he takes it back
and he's like, all right, we good. And he starts to leave. And I go, but sir, the other reason I
called, there were two reasons is that none of my stuff works. And he goes, well, I fix it so it all
works. I go, can you please let me check and make sure I check my direct TV, nothing, no signal.
I put on a record, no sound. So I said, you see, so you gotta, he's looking, he's looking, he's
antenna box back here is for this remote. And the remote doesn't work because something's wrong
with the box. Can you check the box? He goes, yeah, yeah, yeah, he goes out. He yanks. I have this,
this nice cabinet. I'm actually yanking the cabinet is full of, you know, a bunch of books and stuff,
but you know, you can move the cabinet with two people. And I tell him he's, he's yanking on the
cabinet and he can't move it. And I hear a, I'm not gonna say how much this fucking cabinet was,
but I had a decorator do my house. I wanted to at least, I have no taste in any other aspect of my
life. I wanted to have a nice looking house. This guy is yanking on this cabinet underneath the
thing. And I go, sir, please stop doing that. And I hear, I hear a snap of wood on this like
crafted cabinet that I got like an antique shop. I go, sir, why are you yanking on that? He goes,
well, I need to get to this thing back here. I said, sir, you need to ask me if you're going to do
that. What you were trying to get to because there's a box back here. I'm trying to get to. I go,
sir, that is not a box. That is the part of, it's part of my turntable. And it's the subwoofer thing.
Just before or after the diner, it's like 4 p .m. It's 4 p .m. Yeah, I go, that's for my subwoofer.
He goes, you sure that's not the remote? Yeah, I'm sure. What, what you need to look at is what I've
told you three times to look at. Right. He goes back there. He's like, I can't figure it out. That's
how we're about to end the transactions with him saying I can't figure out as a home audio engineer.
I can't figure out how, how you can watch TV, how you can listen to music. And he's getting ready to
leave my home saying I can't figure it out. Right. I get up there. I'm on a ladder. I'm tweaking
things around. And I go, here we go. I turn the thing. I push it up against the wall. And then suddenly
the sensor's working and everything's fine. And I go, all right, man, I think we got it working.
Thanks. He was, okay, good, good, good. Can I get some water?
Hmm, that's sure. I give him a glass of water. He drinks it. And I am not, thankfully it was water,
but I'm not kidding you, Joe. I give him a, a solo cup of water. He drinks it and, and you know,
takes a big swig of it. He hands it to me. And he goes, good, I get another glass.
Fine. Okay. Pour him a glass of water. I hand it to him. He takes a tiny sip off this glass.
Sets it on the edge of my coffee table in a way I will describe as criminally insane,
where he's got a fourth of the cup on the table. Right. Right. And three force off. Right. And of
course, the cup falls, maybe this guy was drunk, splashes to the ground. And then I put together that
the man is drunk at four p .m. And I said driving around, driving around, doing cup. So I said,
you know, what man? There's no real apology to that. I'm like, it's water. Don't worry about it. It's
fine. I go, what do I owe you? It was, I don't know. You want the invoice? I said, I'm just asking
me this, yeah. I want to hear it. I want to hear this number. 100 bucks with a question mark.
I said, is that like a usual rate? Is that the rate for what happened? He goes,
that's sort of his calls, you know, about a hundred bucks.
It's okay. About a hundred. I write the man a check. I get him out of my high. I just couldn't,
I sat down. I played a little bit of a game. I was rattled by the encounter. I was rattled by the
encounter. Well, yeah. Yeah. That's a, and this is your, you got to, Pat and I, as you mentioned earlier,
we hit the diner first thing this morning about 90 amp. He orders a plate of what looked to be
nothing more than nachos to me with, with, with a substitution of eggs for a little lettuce. Joe
stick. Well, Joe, what nachos do you know have lettuce? Well, nachos usually have like lettuce tomato
and onion on them and melted cheese. This was melted cheese beans, a meat, and then eggs all over
chip. It's, it's a, it's a Mexican breakfast. It's on, it's on every menu and call what you want. It's
God damn nachos in the morning. It was a special. It was 995. I said, I'll try it. I got people
at a joining table saying, are those those chilaquilas? They look good. Can I try some? Now,
I had half of it at most. Joe's over there eating pancakes and shit as well. Why is that? I'm,
I'm not saying it's an unreasonable breakfast. Why is it a, a more reasonable breakfast? I'm just
breaking your balls, but I'm saying you go home with a belly full of breakfast nachos. Yes. You eat,
just a piece of candy laying out in the open, which is, it's not a choice in my opinion.
Even in your own house, certainly couldn't question that. Do you see candy just laying around on
around? Certainly couldn't question that, that that was a strange move. But, but, but I, that, that, now you're
on mushrooms. Now you've got a guy coming in with this one. On mushrooms is a heavy exaggeration. I
want to stress that. I want to stress that. I'm saying this to support you. Yeah. We're not in a
state that you could, you, you'd like to be in to deal with something like this. I'm just saying like,
and, and, and the last one on this is 30 seconds. When I walk up to your gate tonight,
there are three ladies sitting out there. Ladies. And I buzz, and you buzz me in. And these
ladies are sitting out there silently. And I open the gate. And I turn to them. And I say,
are you guys trying to get in? It's three very innocent look ladies. I, it looked as though
they were waiting for somebody to open the gate. Right. I could not have been nicer with this. Are you
guys trying to get in? Two of them say nothing. The third looks at me with like a, a heavy sigh and
an eye roll. And she goes, no. I got to get out of this town. What are we doing? I got a society. It's
this town. It's this town. I got a, I had two encounters with drivers. The one I'll talk about,
pull up to a red light today. On my way back from a Meba, where I picked up. And I'm not going to
go into a great detail. By the way, this, this show is going to be in a few minutes here. We'll get
to the topic, which is Pat and my favorite number one horror movie. Yeah. I go to Meba today.
First two jets to Brazil albums have been re -released on vinyl finally. Never heard of the band.
Just the Brazil was Blake from Jawbreaker. It was his band following Jawbreaker. So they only had
three albums. I really like the first two quite a bit. So I grabbed those. That was a nice surprise.
I grabbed Elvis's first album on vinyl. Found an original fantastic. Pressing great. Got
Buck Owens record. Love Buck Owens. What brought you to Buck Owens? I heard him on, I've been listening
to Willie Nelson's Roadhouse a lot on serious. And Buck Owens does a great song with my favorite
country artist. Dwight Yoke. Yeah. Great figure. Oh, that's on the one I got. Well, probably the original
version. And Dwight has an album of like 25 Buck Owens covers. That is a masterpiece.
And I got an album by The Sloths who were a garage rock band in the 60s that put out a couple
singles then broke up after two years. Never released an album. Get together like two years ago.
Get back together like two years ago. After 1964 to 2015 or whatever it was,
60 and record the album. They never recorded it. And it's so where do you hear about The Sloths?
I saw it in the oldies section. And I was like, this looks new. Why is it in the oldies section?
And I previewed it on iTunes and then listen and then read the story. And I was like,
this not only sounds awesome, but that's a great story. Yeah. So I bought that record.
And I also got, I think that's it actually. So anyway, I'm on my way back from Amoeba.
Guy in front of me, light turns red where I see it. And there's a guy in front of me almost blows
through the red light. He almost blows through it. Fine. Not in my business. No. He's not in the crosswalk.
His car is two thirds out of the crosswalk on the other side because that's how far into the
fucking crosswalk he got before he hit the brakes and stopped. Out of the kindness of my heart,
I back up significantly to give him room to reverse. Go on. He does. Light turns green.
He then sits there for a solid 10 seconds, 12 seconds, as the light is green. I don't lay on
the horn, but I give him a bump. Like, come on, buddy. Let's go. He turns around like, what?
Then sticks his hand out the window and does like this waving like, what's your problem? And I
driving full speed behind him, reach around my windshield and plaster my middle finger to the
windshield and start screaming, fuck you at him. It's like, dude, not only did you almost run a red light,
not only did I accommodate you and your dumb fucking mistake. Now you can't even admit to the fact
that you're seeing there's a fucking green light and it's time to go and now you're dead,
stopped at a green light. Everybody in this city, it's accommodate them 100%. Not partway, not
meet me some of the way on this. Not can you give me a break here? It is this is what I am doing and if
you don't accommodate me 100%, you're shaming me or you're being derogatory or you're being rude.
But some people are not born here. So does it, does you become that through living here?
What happens? Because everybody that comes to the city thinks that they deserve to be a movie star.
That's the problem. Everybody comes here from wherever going. And some people come here because
they just want to do good work and they know that there's industry here and we know a lot of people
like that. So obviously, I'm speaking in generalities. But most people come here because they're like,
well, I want to be Tom Cruise. And they're completely entitled and then they get here and they start
drinking the cool late. I can't take it anymore. Dude, I was like, I got to get out of this fucking city.
I have to get out of this city. I can't do it anymore. I'm filled with rage whenever I go into public.
Filled with it. Filled with it. Guy the other day turns in front of me, makes not just a right hand turn.
But a right hand turn as slow as humanly possible with no turn signal. So I almost rear end him
because he and I fucking honk at him. And he's like, what the fuck man? It's like, this is your fault.
You asshole. You know, everyone makes mistakes driving. If somebody honks at me,
you get it. You know, like, yeah, yeah, you're right there. Unless they're honking for no reason.
My, what I get a lot in LA is I'm waiting for a family of four to cross and a crosswalk. I want to make
a right turn. Right. And the person behind me starts laying on the horn to, to what? Plow down a family?
It's disgusting. It's disgusting. The city's filled with disgusting people. No etiquette. There's no manners.
This business is disgusting. Everything's a pig fuck. Terrible. And onto our topic for today.
You know, we're about 42 minutes in and in typical. That's good.
In typical, we'll see you in how fashion. We have not even graced the topic at all yet.
Well, just so you know, folks, we're recording two tonight. We're also doing Blade Runner,
which is our standard episode. And, you know, I came in with a head of steam about this Uber thing,
etc. I said, you know what? I'm giving it to the Patreon people. We're launching this thing.
We want you guys to feel like your money's going to good place. And we need, we set it a little bit
up top. We really do appreciate like how quickly this, this money added up for this Patreon. It's a beautiful
thing. The Facebook page is off the charts. Joe's still not on Facebook, but I'm on there every day.
I love it. As always, please keep the transcriptions coming. They're very funny. I always
screen -grad them and send them to Joe. It's a very positive community. Also, I'd like to address
we were informed the other day that someone on the Facebook page
was was fake trolling us for being racist. But it was a quote joke.
Right. And they've been shut down. So whatever that was, the gentleman has said it was a joke.
I don't know what's funny about that joke or who he was, but it seems kind of stupid to me.
Joe and I love people of all racist colors and creeds.
I'm going to say discriminate against certain creeds. But races and colors, I'm fine with.
Yes. What is creed? I never knew what creed was. Is that religion? Apollo,
Scott Staps band. Yes. The only ones I wrote. I think creed is...
And the Clearwater Revival. There's enough creed in there.
Creed might mean religion. I think it does. I think it does too.
I was just joking anyway. I'm sorry. We're here to talk about our two favorite movies.
Is that what we're getting to? I mean, look, Pat, I think this title, the title of the
episode might be retitled, Pat's therapy session. Please help this man. You're having a hard time.
So let's talk about something like this. This was my relaxing day off and I felt like I was going to
pop a fucking blood vessel. We're going to talk about our favorite horror movies, meaning each of our
number ones of all time. Of all time. We've said before these episodes will be lists. There'll be
surprise. We'll be our surprise. I believe I've mentioned mine on the podcast before because I think...
No, we never covered this movie. So I'll tell you now. We haven't covered mine either.
The Exorcist is my number one hard to argue. I think it's...
Yeah, I think it's an inarguable choice. It's a film. Now you mean dominion.
You mean Leslie Nielsen's repossessed. Where's my order? Yeah. Repossessed number one. Exorcist is fun.
Exorcist to the heretic number two. Yes. Pazuzu. Exorcist the beginning. Number three. Dominion. Number four.
Go on. I don't count Exorcist three and then Exorcist one comes in. Yes, absolutely right. I think that's
the right order. No, Exorcist the original and even the director's cut that added. Some people were
mad about the shit they added in the in the I guess it was the late 90s early. I love the spider walk.
I love the quick I love the quick shots of the demons and everything. Yeah, I think it adds to it.
I did. When I saw that new version of the theater, I really fucking loved it. I don't know why it
gets that ramp. I was scared shitless when I'm resold in the theater and they'd seen it many times
already and it's still terrified me. I remember I went with my dear friends Scott and Dan and Jamie
from back home. You've met all of them and we came home. They were all living together at the time.
We came home and we were downstairs in the living room talking about the movie and we were really freaked
out and like man that was really scary and then I remember this Scott goes where's Dan by the way?
Where did he go? We're like I don't know where is he and Dan came spider walking to the best of
his ability. Down the stairs. At us almost broke his neck because he couldn't do it. Was it a reverse
crab walk down? He tried to do it but really very really was just sliding backwards down the stairs
and almost killed himself and we laughed like we were doubled. It was one of the funniest things I've
ever seen. But I took a core. I always liked the film The Exorcist from the very first time I
saw it as a kid. It was one of two movies my mother refused me to allow me to see when I was very young
meaning 12 -ish you know. Scarface was the other one. Okay interesting. She said those movies are
too graphic. You can't see them. Right. So when I finally did see The Exorcist what is the
graphic scene in Scarface is the like the the chainsaw bed. I think it was the chainsaw and I think
it was just the utter the utter lack of respect for the word fuck in the film. I mean it's just left
and right. Yeah. So in the drugs and all that I guess you know put anyway. I finally saw The
Exorcist when I was probably 14 years old. There's a scared the living shit out of me. Couldn't watch
the movie by myself until I was in my 30s. Yeah. And I took a course. I took like a music and film
like summer camp thing when I was in high school and there was one of the classes in the film
side of it that we took was a dissection of the movie The Exorcist and all the class was it was a one
time thing and the guy showed us The Exorcist and then broke down why the movie is so effective.
And yes and it was a fascinating course and so aside from the movie being extremely well written
I've also read the book. It's one of the best adaptations of a book you will ever read or ever see
excuse me. The superbly acted it's superbly directed every part of this movie is just perfect.
For me second only to eat prey love in terms of adaptations. So but then on top of it there's
all this technical stuff that you don't really I guess maybe initially realize. Well freaking I mean
freaking was an easy contemporary of your scores Azy to Palm and etc. And they just kind of lost
his way but he'll bubble up on the right one he does yeah he never quite got the notoriety of
those guys but he's still doing this thing and he's still great in fact I just found out I think
October 26th I think it is he's signing Adamiva record he's signing the double vinyl soundtrack release
of The Exorcist that just came out or is it about the tubular bells over and over probably it's a
spooky soundtrack it's not something I'd ever put on in the house right I don't see how you
could ever feel good to it it's weird that he would be signing the soundtrack why he had nothing
to do with the soundtrack. Well he's the one guy probably from the movie that's yeah I mean any
Omar Akone he's not going to come in from Italy to sign it right and William Peter Blattie I believe
is dead. So The Exorcist what is weird about you saying that it was one that you could not watch
is that it was the only already movie my father would let me watch what and it's I don't know who
would get an R rating release today with the crucifixion masturbation and all that shit I don't know
how it would be yeah it's and my dad was like I was probably 10. Jesus Christ and you know I would beg
and beg to see PG -13 movies but he was like cool of the excess and I watched it and then I was like
why could I watch that and I also it made me think that that's what all R rated movies were that
level of intensity. So he said well you know I wanted you to learn about Catholicism which my
lord really shows you how how fun that religion is and then he took me down to downtown St. Louis
the night after we watched it we had dinner and he said you see this staircase here and I said yeah
and he said according to legend in many news reports that is the very staircase where the
priest was thrown down the flight of stairs because the extra story happened in St. Louis wow
it's what he told a 10 year old boy so I'm already fully traumatized by it and then he let me know
that it happened here in my hometown that's upsetting yeah that's upsetting yeah when I when I first saw
that the the whole movie disturbed me and I loved it it has a level of evil that every horror movie
has tried to get and can't get it can't even come close. There's something and these exorcism movies
that come out now that are completely about the movie yeah these movies come out of their PG -13
exorcism movies it's like get out of my face and even the R rated ones don't go that far there's
only one scene in the book dealing like in the graphic there's only one graphic scene in the book
that they did not put into the movie yeah but the fact that they kept that crossing is pretty
unbelievable and you know what this was 1972 yeah when you could which makes no sense because it's
that classic argument of you could do more than then you could do now yeah it doesn't make any sense
well midnight cowboy in 1969 yeah it was rated X right you watch midnight cowboy now it's the
tamest of ours there's like some tits yeah and you know he's a male prostitute there's literally no
gay sex nothing nothing happens there's no profanity hardly uh three years later the exorcist gets an
R rating and they have a 12 year old girl masturbating with a crucifix yeah saying f may Jesus she says
may Jesus fuck you yeah and her vagina is bleeding because she's stabbing the cross into it so hard
and Linda Blair is the massive box office hit they asked Linda Blair Blair much later in life like how
did you shoot that scene and she was like I didn't really know what we were doing she goes they just
put a like a box between my legs that have like a sponge in it that put out red stuff oh my god and
they were like just just stab that box with this cross and she was like okay so she did it and then
she's also not in some of those scenes it's like another actor portraying the but she's in a lot of it
and yeah you know it's it's pretty it's pretty heavy stuff it's like in Gerald's game yeah
the scene where spoiler alert the scene where uh uh the ET kid Henry Thomas plays the dead he's
masturbating to his daughter who's sitting on his lap yeah and I wondered like does that kid know
what this scene is how it is or do they like super impose her in somehow yeah where she's sitting
there and they're just like okay so now he's just gonna like rock the bench and say just keep watching
and right you don't need to know you know it's very strange but like I guess but um but anyway um
the uh you know they talked about when they that Dakota fanning movie came out where there's like oh
she gets raped and they said they were like look she's not we didn't shoot the scene as a rapeseen
we shot close -ups of her crying and then we we cut in the other shit right so um you know I don't
really know how they did all the stuff in the exercise I kind of don't want to know to be honest I
don't want to ruin uh it it feels like watching a documentary yeah exactly it's crazy I mean just
crazily well -acted by everybody so some of the things and then we can move on to your movie some of the
things that I learned in this class yeah he said he said look in 1972 73 whatever it was the
teacher said huge fear of Islam okay and it was like sort of the initial the initial Islam
ophobia was was that was the first time was happening that to me much like close encounters the boring
uh desert opening of both those movies I'm like I don't need this so this movie start he goes first
thing you hear in the film Islamic chance right he goes so that's already it's 72 people are already
set off yeah you know uh he's like he he played us a bunch of scenes and he goes you hear that noise in
these scenes that's the sound of bees yeah because they recorded the audio of beehives and they
were like it's just a thing where it was tested that this sound makes people very uncomfortable so it
appears here here here here here in the movie uh he's like if you notice like they they show this
shot of these wild dogs fighting uh maybe they're coyotes I don't know and he goes later in the movie
you you hear the sound of of the dogs come back but there's no attention called to it and we're not
looking for it you're not going to notice it he was pausing it like if you see here the demons face
is found in the flame of the candle that that blows up when she's in the attic for like a frame
right it was shit like that uh he said uh this part here he's like that's the sound of people
fornicating and you again you don't know what it is because it's the sound that your hearing does not
match the vision right visual excuse me it's just a superbly made film it's to this day
in a good way the most disturbing movie I've ever seen yeah uh the most disturbing movie I've ever
seen in a bad way still is antichrist sure and I still kind of want to own antichrist for that reason
I do own antichrist but uh but antichrist is you know that hits points where I'm like do I need to see
this right now yeah I don't know that there's as much purpose to the upsetting uh nature of that
film in my opinion as there is to the exercise yeah to me the exercise is spot on you're going to
make a movie about the devil this is how low the devil sinks to quote Richard prior devil's low
motherfucker jack uh you know so it's like it just hits it it hits it in a way that no movie ever ever
has including the hell razor franchise and I love the hell razor movies no nothing's come close so
anyway that's my pick patty what do you got uh my pick is a is a much lighter film um but
it's not even close for me my favorite horror movie is poltergeist okay
um and part of that may be it's one of the very few horror movies that was rated PG and I could
only watch PG movies until I was 13 so when I saw poltergeist to me that was as every bit as scary
as the exercise and it remains a pretty terrifying movie um one quick side note this week on my show
I was able to cast Miss Joe Beth Williams the mother and poltergeist to play the mother of a
character on my show which I am very excited about I always really loved her and she looks
exactly like my mom did when I was a kid which I think also adds to my enjoyment of it
Craig T Nelson is like a I don't even really like Craig T Nelson but he is just a classic 80s dad
and poltergeist to me blows ET and all that shit out of the water I've just always liked it more
it's a cooler story it's better and I never really understood how ET became this all -time classic and
poltergeist is kind of you know it uh cool almost a cult thing you know it made $60 million
where ET made a thousand you know I love I love Craig T Nelson by the way I just want to go on
record saying that he's a guy that I hope to meet one day because you know I didn't know that
big gun dude but you know if you met him you'd feel like you were just with your dad
yes he's got a Harrison Harrison Ford's like that yeah uh
Dabney Coleman who we've discussed you know who you know smells like coffee yeah there are just
those guys who go if I met him I'd just would start calling him dad immediately but poltergeist uh you
know when Joe Beth Williams and Craig T Nelson are in their bedroom and the kids are asleep and they're
going to smoke a joint yeah this is a PG movie as well like I for for me this movie was a big
I would say even more than like seeing tits for the first time there was a lot of stuff in it
where I was just kind of like do my parents smoke pop like I didn't even know what that was when I was
a kid I don't know that I did either I didn't know I didn't know weird and forbidden to me I bought the
DVD of poltergeist poltergeist poltergeist yeah uh probably at this point 10 years ago but uh
but when I got that DVD I hadn't seen it in years and I remember when that scene came on I was like
oh yeah smoking weed right I was such you was just rolling a cigarette when I was a kid you know
I never realized that and then they'd never even let you do this now like and they you know
they didn't in the remake of poltergeist which is an abomination but with Craig T Nelson like devils
work that film and I love Sam Rockwell I fell into a bit of a depression I fell into at least a
week of depression after I saw it but Craig T Nelson then in a parapagymapant stands in front of the
mirror and does tricks with his belly fat because he's got this big beer gut right like in the
mirror like there's just these little touches to it where you're like they wouldn't let the male
lead of a movie do that now they you know he'd be standing in front of the mirror like actually a great
example is like that Amityville thing where it's Ryan Reynolds with a 24 pack that's your dad now
right that's your dad there's just something so much more I don't know I those two are like a real
family those two are real family those two reminded me so much of my parents the kid is so ugly
the boy was so fucking ugly I was just going to say the kids don't look like six -year -old models
yes in waiting like they're they look like normal kids the boy is hideous he's got those fucked up teeth
which is why even though two is obviously a lesser movie they did a perfect scarcity by having his
braces attack him because obviously the kid needed braces did you know this by the way there was
supposed to be there was an idea never got out of development but there was a script floating around
to do a pastor creed or whatever the fuck his name is from the two they were going to scream right
past yeah they were going to do a pastor movie wait is he the same guy from Phantasm this is always
trouble no angus scrim is the tall man in Phantasm okay but this other guy and the other two different
actors the second one the movie the guy that plays him in the second one died and then they
get a different actor the third one they're both equally creepy yeah yeah but they were going to do
a prequel to poltergeist about just that preacher would love and how it all started right that would
have been very cool anyway sorry go ahead no I just I mean for me even though it terrified me I remember
I threw up when I was a kid because I watched that scene where the guys face falls off that scared
the living shit out of me as a child it's scared believe it like shit out of me really pure like film
school effects which I love about it but right after that and this will sound like a joke but my mom
called me in for lunch and it was spaghettios and they looked exactly like that guys melting face and
I threw up because I was I was such a pussy when I was a kid that poltergeist played like the exorcist
for you as opposed to this big brooding yes broad chested man that sits before me yes yeah all right but I
really uh to this day I watch it at least once a year both of these movies the exorcist and poltergeist
you have to see in a theater because the the sound design in both these movies is unbelievable
and at the very least watch it in your home with a good sound system and the lights off because they do
those strobing effects in poltergeist yeah that really make you feel like your house is I it's a it's
the best movie for me in my opinion to watch like in the dark around Halloween and there's never been
anybody better like when you when it comes to the horror movie trope of we're gonna have an older
person come in who's the expert yeah all this stuff there's nobody better than Zelda Rubenstein who
or Stein however you pronounce it Stan yeah her sheet you're her coming in and then in the second movie
when this shit starts up again and Craig T Nelson is like tell the magical midget we said hello
week we're we're out I remember my mom thought that that was like the funniest yeah call back to the first
one like you know do you like to uh you seem to like it more than most I like it I like it I don't
three is not a good film but I mean I enjoy it Tom scared anytime you're gonna talk about
he's another guy soon as I met him I just start calling him dad yeah for me the the perfect level
of horror comedy outside of like outside of misery which is always discuss in this podcast is them
checking into the hotel and pushing that TV add on yeah that is such a beautiful perfect ending
this movie great and they're all exhausted whatever but and the guy by the way yeah the guy where it's
like yeah you move the headstones but you didn't move the bodies you son of a bitch the bad guy the old
guy yeah or the older guy so there was a local supermarket chain on the east coast where I lived called
pathmark sure I'm there and he was the spokesperson for really so like yeah you'd have these like small
budget like local commercials and that guy would come on your TV be like come down to path mark
the apples are 39 cents a bundle he seems to still act I don't know if he's still alive but I feel like
I see him all the time he pops up and shit don't pop up on like you'll see him on like the golden girls
like Blanche will be like so Rose you really like this new man you've been seeing right and it'll
be that guy my other favorite thing about poltergeist in terms of structure as a as a as a writer myself
is that it has a structure that goes again I would say goes against the rules of screenwriting
as much as anything from like the you know the French new wave and all that shit that everybody
raves about breaking the mold and it's a huge right down the middle Steven Spielberg a picture
I'm Toby Hooper let's not leave tobes out of this as we know I know I know but Toby still I think
it feels as we discussed on this when Toby died and I'm calling him Toby now I admit my mistake
and here's the beauty of him being the stand in for Spielberg yeah it let it be a movie where you
saw women smoking a joint you weren't going to see that you weren't going to see that in ET that's right
it it got it got Spielberg more edgy which he needs to be and it got Toby less fucked up which you
know that is why that's my favorite movies I saw it at an age right that's what I could handle
but uh basically poltergeist ends and climaxes and it's done and you're like holy shit that was crazy
and scary and really exciting and they're packing shit up and it's daylight and the movie is over
and then she goes upstairs and takes the bath and you're like why am I watching joe bath
Williams take a bath right what's going on here and still I forget now and I've seen it 55 times
she gets in the bath and I'm like oh right we got another 20 minutes of even better they they
they climaxed the movie yeah they get the kid out of the the further whatever it's called in poltergeist
and then it gets better and scarier and more fun and also let's not leave out when they finally get
Carolyn out of the other dimension or whatever yeah that disgusting shit they're like wiping off
of her face it looks like she's just covered in alpo well they use that shit in Ghostbusters 2 I
think it's just like pink goo ectoplasm I would I don't remember what happens in Ghostbusters 2 they do a
bathtub of pink it's well that but when Carolyn comes out at the end and she's going oh baby she's like
wiping that like chunky soup off of her face it's fucking disgusting yeah there's something very viscerally
gross about that film which I really enjoy um the biggest laughs uh because Spielberg is the best
attention laughs where it's just somebody saying something straight and it gets a huge laugh because
you're so tense that's the best kind of laugh really in these kind of mood but in these kind of
times Pat quite frankly yeah but it's when Rubensign goes uh you're right you go you remember that
no I don't remember the line I wish I remember the setup better but it's like uh he's like don't
she she goes I've got to go she's got to hear my voice and he goes don't you think she should hear
my voice I'm her dad she goes you're right you go it's like it's it's always every time I watch
like this massive laugh it's it her being like you know idiot I have to go yeah well no she's
scared basically it's the one moment where the midget's like yeah I'm terrified and it's supposed to be
funny it is it's a big laugh in the movie she's not a mid oh wait no we're not a little person I'm
sorry no no but I'm saying she's not even a little person right she's just short okay I think right
I think so I don't know little okay sorry well in any case if you've never seen it and I run into a lot
of people who have never seen this movie idiotic it being doing it has become kind of a weird cult
thing and it's uh to me if we're counting it as as a Spielberg movie it's probably my favorite
Spielberg movie uh it's not gonna top Raiders for me it does top Raiders for me Raiders is uh
it'd be blast for me but I'm sorry Raiders is a top tenor for me I would take that over
Pulitzer guys will never top in Indiana Jones flick but I will I would I would accept the argument
of Temple of Doom being your favorite yeah I don't understand when people shit on Temple of Doom
I fucking love Temple of Doom um but I also liked Crystal Skull and gave it a lot of forgiveness
so I almost uh today rewatch Crystal Skull I've only seen it once in the theater but it's time
for me to do a expectations lowered revisit of Crystal Skull look up until Shyla Buff starts swinging
on those vines which if all I remember if you can block that out of your head and just go oh god
yeah it's fine it's fine I remember there being a lot of prairie dog reaction shots in the Crystal
Skull meerkats okay meerkats it's fine but it's still fun when he like you know it's still got
its moments it's not a great flick but it's not sure it's not a disgrace you're just like
you know I have a bit about it in my eye can people say like this the worst movie I've ever seen
I'm like same in the worst movie Harrison Ford's ever been in no that's a long shot that's
absolutely not so anyway folks that's our show there's your bonus episode and now we're 10 you
happy a mother fuckers thank you so much folks for your for your patreon contributions
a special shout out to what what's the gentleman's name well we're gonna do the shout outs on a regular
episode because the shout outs are people that donated five or more get a shout out yes people that
donated 10 or more get this okay so we need to do the shout outs on a normal episode because
everybody that donated you know has to has to hear it yeah yeah so thank you for your donations
we appreciate it and the blade runner episode will contain the shout outs and that's it
that's it folks do we need to do plugs in a patreon let's do it now let's you know what let's
sleep it's not about us it's about you the exactly all right thank you very much folks we really
really appreciate it and that's why we're doing this and anyone who's giving money up at a time
when money is tight it's very much appreciated and honestly you know it helps to have a little motivation
to do this like we every week we were we're kind of like why are we doing this and to have a little
extra spending cash is a great reason well and we don't do it begrudgingly we're not saying this
sucks we're just like it's sometimes it's tough when it's just the thing you're doing as a labor of
love and it does help to have a little income coming in from it to make it a little more of a
job so thank you as much appreciate take it easy