I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell Welcome to We'll see you in hell, it's
the podcast about movies, my name is Joe Derosa, it's the only podcast about movies. We'll see you
in hell. My name is Patrick Walsh, we're going to be talking about HBO Max's original mortal combat,
mortal combat, I was just at my mother's for three days, folks, she asked me at one point if I was in
the practice, very sincerely, if I was in the practice of checking my breasts for lumps because
breast cancer too. Did you explode at her at that? I would. Refused it with can I ask you something
without you getting terribly upset? Wow. Had she asked me that on the first day, I would have
said, yeah, I'm good because it was the third day my response was, I don't know, I don't know what
the hell you're going to say, what are you going to say? Maybe I might get upset, you know what I mean
because we were at that point of like, it's just a Joe calm down, it's about your tits.
Actually didn't get upset. I thought what she was good at when she usually says that. Yeah,
there you usually what comes is something about like, why won't you go back to church? You
know what I mean? Right, something that's really like, oh man, don't start this shit again. Yeah,
that actually I was like, actually, I got to be honest with you, I do sometimes.
Right, fine. Yeah, my, uh, Ian, a mutual friend of ours. I saw him the other night and he
said that he's, they got this like cousin in the family, who's a smart mouth. It's a 10 -year -old,
like a mccullochulkin and home alone type. And Ian's over there the other day and he's like, hey,
so what's new with you? I haven't seen you in a while. And he goes, when are you,
are you ever going to get your own TV show? And he goes, why? What are you talking about?
And he goes, well, you're the fattest person I've ever met in person.
I laughed so hard. I know he was looking for some, for some sympathy, but my god, I laughed at that.
No. Uh, it might be, and he might be the fattest person I've ever met in person.
Oh, I'm joking. I'm kidding. Ian's not even that big of a guy. Why would somebody ask for that?
That added to the fun in this. It's just a guy who's, like all of us, a little, a little concerned
about our weight. So those comments hit pretty hard. But, uh, my father came out to visit.
I'll spare you the extreme details just in the off chance that he listens, but
it was, it was rough. It was one of those where you shut the door at the end of the visit,
like a horror movie with your back to the door, like out of breath.
Yeah, you go down and wash your face and you look up. He's in the mirror. Yeah, exactly.
I'll give you one highlight. And I actually sat down and just wrote it as a scene.
And it's a very funny scene. I don't know if I'll ever use it or anything, but I realized
I could just take dialogue from him directly. Uh, the man has always been on edge. And it's,
I don't know if it's the pandemic or what, but he was all his usual faults at about an 11.
It was very stressful. Morning one. He's like, I need you to take me up to the grocery store.
I got to get something so I can take a pill. Uh, you don't have any food here. This is after I
listened to every cabinet in my house open and close 50 fucking times. And I go, well,
dad, there is food here. Um, I'm happy to take you to the grocery store, but in the meantime,
can I get you an apple? He laughs really hard at the idea that he might eat an apple in the morning.
He's like, oh, you know, I'll have diarrhea all day if I eat an apple. But I'm like, okay,
great. Go to the grocery store. He's buying, you know, five pounds of macaroni and cheese,
five pounds of potato salad, all just like tasteless, deli counter shit. Right. And he buys
this wheel of cheese in addition to the macaroni and cheese. We come back to the house.
He's eaten the cheese. And when it's done, I'm like, I'm going to put this away.
Heather's very environmental. So she saves bags like if we have a bag of the granola,
and it's got the seal on top, she might save it and put fruit in the bag at a later date.
So I grab one of these bags and it's pink. And I'm putting my dad's cheese in it while calmly
talking to him about something else. And he charges at me like a bowl. He's adding the bag out of my
hand. And he's immediately yelling like in my face. What are you doing? That's expensive cheese.
What are you doing? I'm like, Dad, I'm putting it in the fridge to preserve. What are you talking about?
He's yelling. He's in my face. He's knocking it out of my hand. And he goes,
well, Patrick, it's an expensive thing to cheese. You can't put it in a bag where it's a pink bag.
What do you have in there before? Perfumes? You can't put cheese unwrapped in a bag that stored
perfumes, Patrick. Then I realized that he's so gone that he's just now decided that this bag
did hold perfumes. Even though that's not a real thing. There's not perfume bags. And if there
were, I wouldn't be storing cheese in it. So he's going on and on. He grabs out of my hand. Let me
put it in an actual bag. So he stores it in something else. Heather comes in to see what all the yelling
is about. I'm like, I was trying to put this cheese in this bag. She's like, so what's the big deal?
I go, I don't really know. And then he starts in with what he used to do when I was a kid.
Oh, Patrick got all upset at me because pulling me essentially. That's what he used to do.
I would pay money to watch that. I would pay money to watch that. Yeah. I would just choke the life
out of him. And this was like day one hour one. And it got so much work. I'm trying to tell you
a funny tale and not the dark tales. But I'm talking to Heather. And she's like, so he thought that we
stored perfume in a bag in the kitchen. And then we and just act it on that as if it was fact.
I'm like, yes. And I had therapy today before this. I've been sitting on zoom for hours.
And I shared that anecdote with a therapist just like, what do you make of that? And she was like,
normally, I'm able to diagnose someone. She's like, but each new story takes me down a different path.
I'm like, yeah, I don't really know. And finally, she goes, the one thing I will say that I hope
your wife walked away from this weekend with is how absolutely terrible it must have been for you
as a little boy growing up around that energy. And I almost just started weeping.
Wow. I was like, you're absolutely right. I'm like, she goes, if that's how he's reacting to like,
you putting cheese in a bag, imagine everything you've blocked out of like the first 10 years of
your life. And I'm like, yep, it's what made me who I am today, which is a complete mess.
I'm sorry to hear that. And I look, I would like to mediate the the conflict. Yeah. I understand the
concern of cheese that is quality picking up the essence of what was in the bag prior. But I also
get that you don't handle it that way. You just say, hey, would you mind if I just put that into a
ziplock? Because, right. You know, if there's something else in there, I'm weird about my cheese.
Just that's how you say I'm weird about my cheese. And then that's the end of it. He's weird about
everything. That goes without the thing. Just scream though and run and, you know, and then
patronize you with the whole. Oh, he didn't like that. So the cheese, by the way, when I was throwing
the receipt from the grocery trip away, the cheese costs $3 .99. Oh, that's what cost.
What was it like cracker barrel or something? Yeah, something like that. And how the wash is
the bags out, we use them all the time. It's just, woo, it's like we go to that lapargaleta that I
tell you in restaurant to sit outside. Right. Waiter comes up with the big face shield on. He goes,
can I get you guys something to drink? And my dad goes, yeah, we'll get a bottle of Jack Daniels
and three small glasses. Wow. All right. I'm on board for that. It has been sober for 30 years.
Oh, okay. So it's like we know he's joking, Heather and I, but we also don't understand the joke
or why that's a joke or why it's funny. And the guy staring at him through the face shield is looking
deeply confused. And he goes, it is the sort of alcohol. So he goes, well, I don't know if I can
bring you a bottle. I can definitely bring you three Jack Daniels. I mean, I was like, Oh, I'm kidding
with you. I'm kidding. What is the joke? I get the, these are, these are stories that make it sound
like John candy and plant strains where he's kind of a, yeah, I know. The man is evil. And I'm
going to stop there. I'm telling you the cute funny stories and not the stories that brought
fair luck at me. Fair enough. Fair enough. The, uh, I, I did a, uh, almost evident Castello
who's on first thing with my mom. Yeah. About creep show. Okay. She likes the show. She likes the
program. And I told her the other week, I said, mom, creep show season two is out if you want to watch
it, you know, yeah. And she said, Oh, thanks for the heads up. So we're sitting there and she goes,
put on a, we're trying to find something to watch, which is just miserable. It's just, it's just
a, oh, God. Yeah. And I'll say, mom, what do you want to watch? I don't care. What do you want to watch?
I go, that's not an answer. I, what are you in the mood to help guide me a little bit? We finally
landed on Mad about you, which was perfect. It was like, we, she didn't know about the reboot. She
was so excited. I showed her like four episodes. It was, that was perfect. Okay. Anyway, uh,
so she goes, put on creep show. And I go, okay. And uh, she goes, there's new ones, right? And I go,
yeah. And I go, here they are. And I go to season two. I'm scrolling down the little thumbnails. And she
goes, I've seen all of these. And I was like, you did? And she's like, yeah, I saw these. And I go,
you told me you didn't see these. And she goes, I saw these. And I go, okay. And then she takes
the remote and then accidentally goes back into season one by accident. Okay. She's going, yeah,
I saw all these. And I go, well, you're back in season one right now. I know you saw season one.
You told me you didn't see season two. Yeah. What season two?
Season two are these. The ones I just showed you. Oh, well, I saw these. All right, but you said
you didn't see season two. I didn't see season two. You just said, did you, the last one I saw
was about a werewolf. That was the Christmas special. That's not season two swear to God that she
goes, takes a beat as if scripted by Chuck Lori himself takes a beat and goes, did I see season two?
And I literally go, how the hell should I know? She jumps. She's looking at me like, why are you
screaming? I mean, it was it was insane, dude. It was how many seniors must just miss whole seasons
of shows that they love because they just can't figure out how to navigate it.
Did I ever tell you my grandma, my dad loaned her all the sopranos seasons because she loved
mob stuff and she knew she would love it. And she gave it back and she was like, it's so good.
The acting is so good, but I will say I'm just so confused by it. I'm so confused.
And my dad's like, well, there's a lot of characters and stuff, but I think they do a good job of
keeping it clear. I mean, what's the issue? And we talked for a while and come to realize
she had put in each disc, which had four episodes on it watched the first episode, the one that came up
deleted the disc and put in the second one. So she watched every fourth episode of one of the most
densely plotted series in the history of television. And did that for she watched how she watched the
whole show, missing every three episodes. They're old, you know, they're old. That's, that's,
oh, that's heavy stuff. That's heavy stuff. Oh, my God. Well, speaking of
Creep Show 2, Pat, if you don't mind, can we waltz over to this movie corner of ours?
Let's do it because I'd like to talk about that. I'll start with a picture I watched with my father
called Greyhound. It's an ideal movie to watch. If you have a parent and you need to kill some time,
it stars Tom Hanks. It's on Apple TV. And it was actually written by Mr. Tommy Hanks,
who I think has not written since going back to that thing you do, which is a very, very good
screenplay, I must say. So, and actually Tom Hanks wrote with another guy. So who knows who came
first, but the, the just is, it's a World War II movie, of course, with Tom Hanks. A first time
captain leads a convoy of allied ships carrying soldiers across the treacherous waters of the quote
black pit to the front lines of World War II. The movie is, it feels like something that came out in
like 1998. There's a, there's an excitement to the submarine battles. I like a submarine movie,
you know, but he puts so little into the characterization of it. It starts, Hanks meets Elizabeth
Shoe at like a restaurant. It's his girlfriend. She goes, I'm scared about you going to war or whatever.
He's like, I know, but I got to go. And then the rest of the movie is him on the submarine. It's
like, guys, don't, you don't have to put in 30 seconds of character development, either put in five
minutes or none. The whole movie is this. And then with like five minutes to spare, he, he dreams about
Elizabeth Shoe. It's like he has a quick flash of her to keep him going. So look, it was hard to get
to involved in this movie. And odd for Tom Hanks too, to not want to tell you more about this
character, you know, Tom Hanks can, can get the best writers in the world on these scripts to beef up
his character. I mean, this is just, you don't know anything about him. You don't know anything about
the people on board. So it's my same complaint really that I have with the superhero movies. It's just
a bunch of action. And I don't really care about it. It's about as average as a movie can be.
I will say my dad and Heather liked it more than I did, but it might have just been because we
had some sweet, sweet time in the house. We're even at the talk. But yeah, it's a, it's a very
average World War II movie, you know, it ain't saving private Ryan. I, I think I finally figured,
you've said many times on the show that your least favorite genre film is BioPick. I think I finally
realized what my least favorite genre is. It's submarine movie. I don't know what it is. Every time I see
submarine, I tried to watch down periscope yesterday. Oh, sorry. Is that with Kelsey Grams?
Yeah. Yeah. Tom Arnold. That's Kelsey grammar. Tom Arnold, I think, is McKale.
Maybe, right? Yeah. I just fucking, I didn't put it on in purpose. I just, I was watching
the Kojak, the Night Stalker on YouTube. And for some reason, when it ended, it led to
down periscope, which you can watch for free on YouTube. And I just as soon as I realized it was
sub movie, I turned it off. I was just like, I don't even want to give this a chance. Not that it was
any good. But anyway, all right. So Creep Show season two, you know, we're not, we're not going
to do it on the show. Pat has hit his Creep Show limit. I sort of did too. But I wanted to at least
give season two a chance. You know, I wasn't thrilled with season one. I thought it had some good
stories here and there. You know, you could pluck, in my opinion, maybe three really solid ones from
that season. In hindsight, I know I said there were more than that initially, but I changed my
opinion. I was excited to see if season two could bring anything more to the table. Thankfully,
in the first two episodes, they did. The first episode story one is, and I can't remember the names
of the tales, but it's basically, it's basically plays on as a new story that would have been the
wrap around story and either part one or part two of the movies themselves. It's about a kid who's
got a mean stepfather played by Kevin Dylan and the kid order stuff from the Creep Show magazine to get
you know, mystical dark magic revenge on his stepfather. Really cool new thing, new new take on
an old thing that Creep Show has done a few times already. I really enjoyed it. And I thought to myself,
oh, this could be the wrap around story for a Creep Show 3 movie. And then you could take the
four great stories between the two seasons and put those in as the stories. And you'd have a good,
you'd have a great Creep Show 3. I'm tempted to try to edit that together myself, but that's neither
here nor there. Second story in season two was not one of my favorites, but it was an evil dead
tribute. Ted Raimi starred in it. It had some great moments. It was a fun tribute to the evil dead.
It was a weird crossover that I wasn't expecting, but I did enjoy it. They didn't really stick the
landing, unfortunately, which is the problem with a lot of these stories. Episode two, however,
started with a short called Dead and Breakfast starring C. Thomas Howe. That was the best thing they
have ever done ever on the show hands down. I was like, Thomas Howe. And he was great in it. He's
really funny in it. Like, it was really good. It was about a murder house that was a tourist attraction.
And they did a really funny, sort of spiteful commentary on true crime podcast influencers who
exploit that sort of thing. And I don't want to ruin it. It's worth watching. They're taking shots at
our precious making a murderer friends. I think they're kind of just taking shots at everybody.
The way it's always sunny did with that one episode right at the end of it. They're like, no,
they don't do anything to help the the solve the murder. They just exploited it. But I thought it
was a very funny commentary. And I thought the episode had everything you wanted a creep show episode
to have. It was freaky. It was quirky. It was violent. It just, they just nailed it. And I was like, here
we go, man. They finally figured this out. And then the second episode in that or the second story
in that episode starts so great with the great cameo by what's his name? Oh, son of a bitch.
Did they bring Lil Yachty back? No, no, no, no. Keith David. Oh, great. And then that story kind of
goes off the rails and doesn't really make sense. Ashley Lawrence is in that one from Hellraiser. It
was cool seeing her again. But the story just again didn't stick the landing. But this being said,
season two episodes one and two, showing a lot of promise out of the gate. All right. And then
our friend of the podcast James Pinkstone said to me, don't forget season one first two episodes
showed promise. And then it really took a nose dive. And I was like, son of a bitch. And then
lo and behold, episodes three and four were, they were just, they were just just slapped together
shit show. And they were just terrible. Like, yeah, I just, they just, they just ranged from moments of
I don't care to this doesn't make sense to this is way too complicated to what is going on to,
I don't even care out ends like it's, they just sucked through and through. And now the season finale
is episode five. So it's a shorter season than last year, which is not a good sign. That might just
be a cause of COVID. I don't know. But also not a good sign. And I haven't watched it yet. Season five's
finale or episode five, the season two finale is a 41 minute episode starring Justin Long excited
for to see Justin Long, but they've proven time and time again. They are not good at these extended
plays. And, you know, these things, this is the problem with the, the, the, the, the, the new twilight zone.
And so many of these new anthologies, black mirror a lot of the time, the episodes are too long. Like,
I don't know why nobody realizes Rod Sirling was King because he figured out
22 minutes, man, you're in and you're out. That's it. Like, the season four of the twilight zone,
when they go to hour long, there's like two good ones, the rest of them fucking drag forever. It's too
long. So I would say if you plucked from this season, the story one from episode one and story one from
episode two. And you use story one as a wrap around. And then you put episode two as a story.
And then bad wolf down gray matter. And the companion from season one is your other three.
You know, I pretty saw a little creep show, hour 45 minute film on your hands.
Somebody should do that. I'm too lazy to do it. I'd love to do it, but I'm too lazy to do it. But
that would be at least we got that out of it. You know, so that's where that stands.
All right. I am, I am done. I'd have to hear, you know, major, major changes to ever return
to it. I just feel like they're not doing a good job on the show. I don't know how to say it.
I am loving the new season of Joe Bob. I think the picks have been great. You know, at last,
last season, man, he was going too big on the recent movies, like recent micro budget movies that
shutter maybe I had already owned or something. And this year, we're back to like shining a
last it was Mother's Day in class of 1984 last week. I'd never seen either one. I'd always wanted
to see both of them. So I've never seen either of those either. I want to watch that now.
Yeah, he's he's been great. And him and Darcy are back in the groove. You know, there was that period
over over quarantine where he looked bad and the set looked bad. And I thought he was going to die.
And everybody seemed tense. And it's a good show again. I watched Rolling Thunder.
I had heard Quentin Tarantino discuss it on that great podcast again with him and Edgar Wright
talking for like four hours about movies. And if you'll remember in the wake of Pulp Fiction,
like in the late 90s when I was working at Blockbuster, Tarantino actually had he would often come out
with like a Quentin Tarantino presents. And it would be some old movie from the 70s. He did switchblade
sisters. He did one about like a killer gorilla. And they were never great. The first few, you know,
like Tarantino is the kind of guy who like, okay, I love psycho four way more than psycho one. All right,
you know, like sometimes his opinions just seem to try to be making you upset. And sometimes he's
great. This was one of his recommendations where I wish I had listened to him a lot sooner. It's an
immediate favorite of the revenge genre. It's way better than like a death wish or one of these
movies that gets more praise. It's called Rolling Thunder. It's an excellent movie. I'm going to
just quickly read you the synopsis of Vietnam veteran returns home after years in a POW camp and
is treated as a hero. When thugs invade his home to steal the silver coins he received for his
service. They mangle his hand and leave him and his family for dead. He survives and becomes
obsessed with getting revenge, aided by his loyal friend Tommy Lee Jones. Now wielding a hook for
a hand he sets out on his mission of vengeance. So it's TLJ who is great in this, a very young TLJ.
Will you give him Devane, who's kind of a character actor who never really hit it big as the vet.
And they just go and get revenge. At first, you know, I think Kingpin was probably influenced by it.
They shove his hand into the, they drag him over and shove his hand into the
garbage disposed when it cuts it off. And then he's got the hook and he's got to learn how to use it.
There is some Kingpin feel to it. But the action is awesome. There is a scene, and Terrence,
you know, mentioned this scene. He was like, I've never shown this movie and not had this scene get a
huge round of applause. I applauded in my home, even though I knew it was coming.
Devane walks in, Tommy Lee Jones is like, what's up? He goes, I think I found the guy who killed my
wife and kid. And Tommy Lee Jones goes, oh, I'll get my gear.
Walks in and grabs a big shot. Got it. Everything. You know, it's like got a casual nature to it.
That's really fun. The revenge is really fun. The story is tight as hell.
He's written by Paul Schrader. Okay. This followed taxi driver, I believe.
That's what Schrader does. Well, man, he does a nice tight, you know, three characters.
It's really, really good. And it's like when he comes home, like
he knows his wife's been fucking around on him. He's like sleeping on a shed out back, you know,
and he's telling his kid, like, I just needed a little time, but to myself, you know,
like his whole life is gone when he comes back. You're rooting for him from the jump.
And it just goes to show you how much they fuck up these revenge stories by complicating them.
Even nobody which I loved, even John Wick, which I loved, it's always got to be some big secret
society of assassins and etc. To me, it's just more satisfying to have one guy going up against
somebody who fucked him over. Rolling Thunder is a new favorite revenge movie for me,
I highly recommend. I, whoops, dropped my phone. I purchased, and actually, I got it for free.
Amazon was doing the three for two deal. Yes. And I grabbed the Twilight Zone season two Jordan Peele.
Okay. Uh, I don't own season one. It is the only group of episodes of the Twilight Zone
entire series that I do not own. I own every aspect of the Twilight Zone that's ever been released
except for that because I really did not enjoy it, but I am going to buy it just as a completionist
and try to enjoy the two episodes I kind of liked. But what I saw season two was much more of an
improvement. So I said, hey, fuck it, man, I get a freebie here. Let me grab season two and check
it out. It's a huge jump in improvement over season one. Not enough that I think the show should have
been picked up again. I understand why I got canceled, but there were at least times in this in this
one where, you know, first of all, they weren't hitting you over the head with the social commentary
like they did in the first season. Second of all, they streamlined and simplified a lot of the episodes.
And finally, they managed to capture some of the Twilight Zone quirkiness that the first season I
felt never ever did. The first season just felt like a derivative of Black Mirror to me.
And my favorite episode, I'm not going to go through all of them, but my favorite episode was one
starring a friend of the show, Mr. David Crumholz, where he played a corrupt mayor. And
Damon Wayne's junior also started it as a man whose wife was the mayor and then she's killed in an
accident. And her underling sidekick guy played by Crumholz becomes the mayor and starts driving
what was a thriving town that she had helped bring to its feet into the ground because he doesn't care.
And the plot of this is that Damon Wayne's junior finds a model of the town like kind of like
in Beetlejuice in an attic. It's a replica and he realizes when he alters the replica of the model,
it actually alters the town. And just a really cool, inventive, fun, supernatural story. And that's
kind of what the classic Twilight Zone was. The commentary was a lot of the time sort of soft and
subtle like that. And they would have a really fun device that it all kind of hinged on. And I
thought it was great. I thought it was really great episode. I recommend if you have a chance to
watch the season watching it just for that one, the Jimmy, what's his name? Jimmy Smith from it's always
sunny. Jimmy Simpson. Jimmy Simpson episode was enjoyable. The episode with who's the guy from
I'm not for Chris six. He plays the cook in wet hat American summary and he's on like
CSI or not a CSI law and order. Yes, his name. Can I think of his name?
Come on, baby. Mariska Hargote and he's got a juicy ass. He does have a juicy ass. Anyway,
he's in a cool, I guarantee everyone's screaming it at the podcast right now. Let me look it up.
Yeah, he's in a cool episode about an alien visitation that I enjoyed. Chris Maloney. Chris Maloney.
You know, there's enough worth checking out in that season that I'd say if you see it for cheap,
you might want to grab it if you're a big TZ fan. I wouldn't go out of my way, but
how was Crumholz? I have a hard time imagining him as a mayor for some reason. He was great. He played
like a fucking worm. He was awesome. He was really great. And I tried a very good actor. Yeah, I tried
to compliment him on it. Of course, he was like, Oh, no, no, you know, David, it was good. I
really liked it. I thought it was good. He was, he was, and I mean this in an extremely positive way,
he was very appropriate, appropriately cartoonish because that's a thing that Twilight Zone used to
do. They would have these like really archetypal characters. Like, if you ever watch the monsters come to
Maple Street. Maple Street. There's that guy who's the villain in that story, basically, like
through the main villain who's the heavy sick guy with the Hawaiian shirt on. Right. And he's just like,
he's maniacal. He's fucking crazy, you know, and Crumholz played a character like that. And I was
like, this is the first time they've put a guy like this in a character like this into one of these
stories. And I think it's a tremendous throwback to the original show and what made the original
show work so well a lot of the time. You're dealing with a supernatural situation. Throw a couple
archetypal over the top characters into it. It makes it fun. I agree. I liked it a lot. Anyway. All right.
I saw a picture called femme fatale directed by Brian de Palma. And in really looking at his
IMDB, of course, if you haven't seen the De Palma documentary, where it's just him talking through his
movies with a bunch of clips, I highly recommend it. I love it. Yeah. Just a camera in his living room.
Yeah, exactly. And like clips, but it works. I don't know if they said this in the in the doc or not,
but femme fatale is definitely De Palma's last great one. And I mean, great. I saw it theatrically. I
remember being turned on by it, but I don't remember thinking it was worth a shit. And seeing it now,
I mean, it's sort of like it's clearly De Palma working with a lower budget than he had. But
just like, look, I'm getting up there, but I want to dazzle you by showing you the coolest camera
should I can. He wrote the script. It's a heist wherein a absolutely stunning woman who is wearing
basically like a bejeweled bikini. Like her tits are out. She looks incredible, but basically everything
she's wearing is worth an extreme amount of money. And the plan is that Rebecca Romaine Stamos
is so hot that she will seduce this woman and steal her underwear basically, her valuable underwear
that will replace it with fakes. And that's the heist. It's a clever heist for sure, but
man, De Palma just shoots the hell out of it. He's got, you know, it is a dual role, but not in
an annoying way. Rebecca Romaine Stamos is awesome in the movie. I don't know how she didn't have
an acting career because I don't think I've ever seen anyone look hotter than Romaine Stamos looks
in this movie. And she's really good. You know, she's as good as like a Charlie's Theron in this
type of role. I don't know why she didn't catch on. She was in rollerball and this.
I guess in all the X -Men movie. Oh, that's true. That's true. But she was, you know, the 18th
lead or something. I think she, I think she just, I honestly think she's just one of those people
that was like, I decided to focus on my family. I think that was it. Oh, good for her. She's
married. But Jerry O 'Connell, you shouldn't, you shouldn't focus on your family when you look this
hot. You should give the world a little more hotness and then go focus on your family. But she's still
smoking. She was in an episode of curb recently is like, yeah, she just made a receptionist. And I
was like, who is this young beauty? And I was like, oh my God, that's Rebecca Romaine. Stamos,
that's wild. Or just Rebecca Romaine. My Lord, I mean, she does a strip tease in this movie where I
look, I mean, we, I've told Jeff, I've fucked an alpha puppet before I stopped and jacked off. I
haven't done that. Jesus, God. I haven't done that while watching a standard R -rated film in years,
folks. Boy, oh boy. I'm just telling you, the palma knows what is hot, you know, like the lesbian
scene is extremely hot. Benderis is very funny in the movie. See, I mix this movie up with the
Benderis, Angelina Jolie vehicle, original sin. They came out around the same time. And that movie
was just those two fucking for two hours. I mix, I'm not kidding. I mix it up with point of no return
starring Bridget Fonda. Sure. That's a based on femme fatale, I believe, right? Or no, that's
basically a femme Nikita, a femme Nikita. Yes. And I get that mixed up with femme fake towel. I get
a moment. But coincidentally pointed over turn, probably the hottest Bridget Fonda's ever been outside
of. I've never seen it. Close second. And it might be first is Jackie Brown. I mean, the first is Jackie
Brown. I mean, she puts the Jack and Jackie Brown, baby. I mean, the month. By the way, I used to
I used to do it to the the picture from Jackie Brown in entertainment weekly's review of the film. I
would the matter with you. I'm an animal job. But I would just look at the picture of her and the
hero in the kitchen. And it was enough. Now, now I need a homeless man pointing a gun to my head to
it off. But folks, femme fatale is fantastic. It is a super underrated movie in in
the Palmas career. For some reason, the Palmas movies don't get the respect they're owed until
like 25 years later. So now you see a lot of people that love raising cane with John Lithgow.
That's a really fun movie. I always wanted to see it. Never saw it. It's fun trash. You know,
it's really well done. It's kind of Lithgow is is beyond over the top and he's over the over the top.
But femme fatale will get it to do. The only director who loved it back then was Ebert, who I think
gave it four stars. A notorious horn dog Roger Ebert. But the story works too. And they keep the
twists coming. Banderis is great. It's just big juicy, the Palmas set pieces with cameras flying
everywhere. So way better movie than like snake eyes or mission to Mars or any of that shit he was
doing after mission impossible. I think he's probably done. You said snake eyes was pretty good,
right? Snake eyes is fine, but it's fine because of what the Palma brings to it, all the camera
shit and everything. That's actually a good movie married to his style. I don't think we'll
see him direct again. What he does now is like almost like he did a straight to DVD, a rock movie
that was a disaster. And I think he's either slipping or he's lost it, but they're not gonna trust him
to the remake. Was a remake? The Iraq thing was a remake of one of his old movies. It was like a
modernized blowout riff, right? It wasn't blowout. It was a modernized version. It was about an
Iraqi American soldier falling in love with a Muslim woman. Yes. I don't know what of his movies
that would be, but yeah. I forget. It's like a kind of a retail, a retailing or something.
Okay. Passion. You know, he did that movie passion with McAdams that was pretty bad. I just,
he's got another one coming. Catch and kill announced. I got passion up on my, I got passion
up on my wood has now become a full video store section amount of unwatched DVDs shelf. Okay.
Yeah. I'm in the same boat. I bought it when I watched the documentary along with I think body
double, which is up there. I love. That's a filthy movie body dumb.
All right. My last casual casualties of war. Sorry. That's what it's a remake of. Yes.
Yeah. Not a scene for scene, but a similar where I guess a woman is raped by troops. I didn't
ever see it actually, but I'm a diploma completist by I don't want to watch an old man floundering.
You know, casual casualties of war. I saw once. That's enough with my parents. We rent,
you know, is it in that period where platoon had come out and everything? Like I was getting old
enough to think like war movies were cool. And my dad was, you know, he was a Vietnam vet. He was,
he was interested to see these films. And I was old enough that they would let me watch them.
And I we rented casualties of war. Big J Fox fans in the Deroza household growing up.
Boy, were we in for a rude awakening? We didn't know that's what it was about. And that was,
oh, my God, man, that movie is horribly, horribly disturbing. Yeah. You know, you didn't see J Fox
in a lot of pictures like that back then. It was for love of money. And casual casualties of war
kind of came out of nowhere. It was, it was in his, I want to be taken seriously phase. It was like
right after bright lights, big city and like, you know, he was doing all the light of day. He was
trying all this. And then in the 90s, he went straight back to the PG comedy. He was like,
they don't want me in this. Yeah, put me in greed and the frighteners. Let's go, baby. Yeah.
All right, I'll close out my, my theme this week, obviously, is higher anthology or anthology
period. I finally, and I did this at the beginning of COVID. And I never talked about it. But I'd
always wanted to see are you afraid of the dark, which was the old Nickelodeon children's anthology
horror show. I'm a big fan of horror aimed at kids. I've talked at length on this show about how
brilliant something wicked this way comes is Ray Bradbury has done a lot of great stuff. The
Halloween tree is another one of my favorite children's horror adaptations, you know, scary stories,
all that stuff. So I wanted to see, are you afraid of the dark? Because to me, it always looked like
a sort of a darker version of the goose bumps type thing. And some actors that I grew to really love
and other shows were on this as kids as well. Of course, I forget her name and I forget her
character's name, but the blonde, the blonde woman that Jez dates on Peep show, the American woman,
or Canadian woman that he dates. She's on this when she's like 12 is like one of the kids that tells
the stories, the Midnight Society, they're called. But anyway, so I just wanted to see the show. So I,
you know, we were locked in. We didn't know where we were getting out. It was 30 bucks for basically
the almost entire series on iTunes. So I bought it. And you know, I wasn't disappointed, man. It's a lot
of fun. If I was a kid, I would have loved it. And I can see how kids of a certain age would be
legitimately freaked out by the show at times. I would say it does get more, it does get darker and
more daring. There is more threat there than any of the goose bumps stuff, which is interesting
because at that time, when this hit Nickelodeon, I mean, I, I remember when Nickelodeon premiered,
you know, I watched it from day one as a child. I saw all the different iterations of Nickelodeon,
up until I wasn't old enough to watch it, until I was old enough to not watch it anymore. And it
remembered this came out right around the time. I was probably like 13 or 14. I was just old enough
that it was like I had missed the boat. And I remember thinking, though, that looks awfully dark for
Nickelodeon. Like this was when Nickelodeon was trying to tap into that tween kind of thing
for the first time. And, you know, in hindsight, I wish I would have caught it when I was
age appropriate. But watching it now, it's been fun. You know, it's not like I sit down every night and
pile on that. Are you afraid of the darks? But I don't regret buying it. And I enjoyed this show.
Well, you would probably love that orange years documentary. I mentioned last time I recorded
the Nickelodeon behind the scenes. Yeah, I got to check that out. And they go into that show and
they talk to the creators and stuff. And what they said was that Nickelodeon was obviously very
concerned about parents having an issue with how scary it was and fucking their kids up. So,
what they made them do was that every story had to have a basis in classic literature.
So like that's why you're seeing your Frankenstein's, you know, your staple people because they can say,
well, we're just teaching them about classic horror literature. So apparently, that's how they got
around it. I thought it was pretty interesting. And, you know, I never liked that kind of scary stuff
as a kid. I was a coward. I was thinking the other day that I used to say five years ago when people
would say, what's your podcast? I go, it's called, we'll see you in hell. It's about horror movies,
you know, I don't even really like horror movies, but we just kind of talk about whatever's on our minds.
And I can officially say now I'm a full on horror fan. I think through this podcast, I become a true
horror fan. It's a genre I go to more than almost any other. Yeah. You've come a long way since
the early days in your fandom. That's right. I have a quick news psycho. Please. I do too. Trailer
for the conjuring three, the devil made me do it has dropped sucked. It sucked. It's a shit trailer.
It's a shit. Well, here's my question. This is why they earned it. You see those two, like, I mean,
talk about two actors. I don't give a shit about Patrick Wilson and Vera. But when the camera hit
them, I'm like, they've kind of earned the place where you see them. And the theater goes, oh, sweet.
It's a conjure. You know, like, they're kind of iconic horror characters at this point. Yeah. And
man, this trailer sucked. Go on, Jeff. My question is this, did the trailer sucked or is it just so much
of more of the same? Yeah. I was like, my god, like, some of this is kind of cool, but they've,
this is the same shit over and over long period of silence. Thing runs up, stabby noise, scream.
I'm just like, I'm bored with this shit, man. And then by the time it gets to based on true events
from the case files of the Warren, it's like, guys, anybody that's taken five minutes to read anything
about the Warrens knows that they've been more or less exposed as completely fraudulent.
Yeah. You know, it's like, like, I'm just like, I don't know what the investment is at any point.
When that first one came out and none of us knew who the Warrens were and none of us had seen a horror
movie like that in so long, it was so exciting. And it was so riveting and scary. And then I thought
the second one took it to another level. And I loved it. And I thought the offshoots aside from
Annabelle comes home sucked. But this one, you know, look, it's the conjuring. I want to see what they're
I will see the movie. But I just was like, I'm bored, man. This is just like, I don't know. I'm not
seeing anything too new. And well, for me, it seemed like they got them out of a scary house situation.
And I don't think you want them out of the scary house situation.
I don't think you do either. But I also think they couldn't have done it a third time. So I don't
know what that's true. I also think when you start the first two movies with, but of all their
cases, this one was the worst. And then the second movie, no, no, this one was the worst by the third
movie you go, I come on guys. Let me just promise you, if one of them was the juiciest, the worst,
the best story, they would have led with it. That's how Hollywood works. They don't go, let's say this
for the third one because they're assuming that it will fail like everything fails. I have an
audio book, I have two audio books based on their case files that I listen to when I go to sleep
sometimes. And then I wonder, what's wrong with me? But I'll tell you the one I want to see is there's
a, there's a lengthy case file. One of the books about a corner or a corner attendee attendant,
they catch fucking the bodies. Yes. Yeah. And they, and they have, they're, they interview them to
ask him if he's been practicing in the occult because maybe an outside influence is making him
fuck the dead courses. Yeah. Yeah. I wouldn't give me that for two hours. I watch that. That's a different
couldn't agree more. Couldn't agree more. Folks, my, I thought I had some sort of announcement news,
but I mean, I, I don't, I guess I don't. There's a lot of stuff being announced where I'm just kind
of like, that's going to be a problem in in a year. You know, that's going to be something we don't
want to see a problem. Just a bad thing. Like what? What do you mean? Just a bad, well, there, I don't
know. I thought I had one in particular, but every, every piece of news, I see, I'm like,
I, you know, you know what I mean? Are you saying movies that are going to come out? Movies. I used
to, I used to half the announcements. I go, ooh, and the other half. Right. And now I almost
only go, well, I'll tell you what, maybe go, the announcement that Netflix is spending $70 billion
on the next year on new content. And that Amazon's, I think it was Amazon spent $400 million.
Just for the Lord of the Rings. For the Lord of the Rings show. It's like,
is anybody like why? I don't understand why this criticism of capitalism and gross
misdistribution of wealth and all these things that seem to matter so much to Hollywood.
Why all goes out the window when it comes to their product. And why the fans of Hollywood,
who also seem to be so pissed off about this sort of thing all the time,
seem to not care when it comes to the entertainment streaming into their living room. I just don't
get it. Like, yeah. What people really loved about Lord of the Rings is that he, you know, he had
an ample budget, but, but those three three hour movies that all became four plus hour movies when
you release his director's cuts cost less than the show's going to cost. And people like that
handmade quality of those movies, you know, there's a special effect. Sure, but there's also like a
handmade feel that Peter Jackson gives it. And what this tells me of their dropping all that coin
and the cast is completely unknown is that this is going to be an entirely computer generated world.
It's going to just feel like every other big fantasy thing, where it's just volcano after volcano
and ork after ork and, you know, I'm, look, I'm not suggesting that the Lord of the Rings movies
didn't use special effects. Of course, they did. But there we've, we've, we've seen the stories
in our lifetime. You're not going to do it better than Peter Jackson did it. So what are you doing?
I also know what are you doing? Who needs to see more of this shit?
Yeah, I found the movies at times exciting and at other times painfully boring.
Oh, absolutely. The Hobbit trilogy just went on and on and on and on. It had its moments.
The second film was pretty cool. Smog's cool the other ones. You know, but it's like, I mean,
an hour of of hobbits eating, eating cheese is how the hobbit begins. Yeah, it's like, who wants
to see this? You know, I say any other day I was like, you could argue, I guess, that Star Wars
are Marvel or whatever is repetitive. And I've argued it, but you know, look, I'm a Star Wars fan.
And if you wanted to tell me, Hey, Joe, well, who wants to see more Star Wars? At least in Star Wars,
they can go to space. They can go to the desert planet. They can go to the snow planet. They can
go to the lava planet. They can go to all the planets and have different landscapes and fight all kinds
of different people. Lord of the Rings is only grassy areas crumbling buildings and orcs
over and over and over again. It's like, how many fucking times can we watch this?
It's my least favorite story. You know, and I feel the same. It's why the Mandalorian didn't stick
with me is that that story of like, let's get from point A to point Z. And then each episode is
we go to B, then C, then D, then E, that kind of thing becomes so repetitive and boring to me.
You know, they're going to make it. And to watch those stories again, I don't have the interest.
I'm sure they'll do well. There's nerds out there, but like with $400 million, why don't
you make, I mean, you could give 400 geniuses, a million dollars and come back with 400 amazing
projects. They wouldn't all be successful. But like, God, I just, it's such a waste.
They don't think it through. They don't think what else could I do with this chunk of money? Look,
I know they're not going to solve cancer. No one cares about that. But uh, how about this?
A waste. One move. What if we only, how about this? Guys, what if we only spent 380 million?
And the other 20 we spent on trying to save live entertainment venues across the country.
So that's part of our industry to play your product that it's all going away. No one's taking care
of it. It's just like the world. It's the world. You know, everyone's like, hey, we may be
have 200 years left with the world, the way we're going. And everybody's like, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I know we know. We know we're working on it. But are you? Because we're all going to die here.
Anyway, uh, speaking of dead, I remembered what I did on the side, okay, which was
Phoebe Waller Bridge, uh, who did Fleabag, which is great, you know, it's a really good TV show.
She rewrote the Bond movie, the new one that will eventually come out to give it kind of a more
feminist slant and great. She's an excellent writer. I'm sure what she added to it will help.
Those movies need better dialogue. They announced that they were bringing her into Indiana Jones for
five five. Excuse me. I'm you're right. But we know what I'm going to say for
all right. So she's coming in for that. And okay. So you're like, all right, she's going to probably be
an archaeologist student or she's going to be a famous archaeologist going up against him. Maybe
they're going to try to bring her into her own franchise. Who knows? And we'll wait and see.
Okay. I like her. So I think that's great. But when I saw Harrison Ford up there,
presenting that Oscar, did you see that? Yeah. Because we should have talked about some
the last thing. He goes up and his whole bit was that he read negative comment cards from producers
on early screenings of Blade Runner. So he reads like all these negative things and then he goes
and that movie was Blade Runner. And the audience is all like, oh, you know, again, he's telling
he's telling the room you're all stupid, basically. And they're all like, yeah, we are. We are stupid.
But my point is now from every source I've ever heard about Harrison Ford is that he's one of the
beyond like a Cheech and Chong level of pot head. He's always stoned. Yeah. I've heard that.
So he's up there. His eyes are bloodshot. But he also seem to have like pink eye or some sort of weird
like big red clot in the center of his eye. His hair was, you know, thinning out. But he's a very old
guy. He still looks great and don't get me wrong. But he's up there kind of wheezing and it sounded
like it was struggling to get through his little speech. And he's like, and now we're going to
present the award for best editing. It's like a nickname to hear something. How the fuck is this
kind of going to be doing big action sequences? He's so old. I don't think he is. I think he has
said he's sending bridge out. He said, well, first two things. So first of all, Harrison Ford said in the
past, I don't know why I couldn't play Indiana Jones as an old man because he's a strategist. He
doesn't have to, he doesn't have to, he doesn't have to swing from vines. He's like, he's a brilliant guy.
Like he can, you know, he can use his brain. So there's that. Yeah. And then also I can't imagine,
and I might be wrong, but I can't imagine that the stall on this film
doesn't have something to do with the developing, the aging technology that Disney really likes
to use. And I think they're going to do some kind of Indiana Jones through the years. And I think
like, I think the wrap around of this thing will be old man Indiana Jones, like on one last mission
where he can't really do it. And he needs to send the kid out to do it for him or whatever. And then
he'll be telling these stories. And you'll see a Harrison Ford at 22 and then Harrison Ford at
45, then Harrison Ford, you know what I mean? I think that's probably what they're going to do.
I could be 1000 there then is then the movie's budget is $150 million. Let's say being being kind.
Then we're going to add 50 million on to that to do the D agent before we've even animated a
boulder to come creating down the cave. They waited too fucking long to do it, man. They waited
too long. I mean, when I saw him up there, he looks like your grandpa. He was struggling.
So I mean, and that's the thing is too, my theory might speak to the fact as to why they brought in
episodic television writer to rewrite the script. Right. So we'll see. But anyway,
speaking of it or not, that movie was called later.
Oh, great, great timing there, Harry. I got my Harrison Ford send off that I needed. I got
the Force Awakens. I got two hours of him, like on the brink of being able to play Han Solo for the
last time. He was right there with just enough in him still to do it. And like, that's all I
ever needed. And I, as I've just said in the past, I liked Crystal Skull and I get shit for it all the
time. So I watch it when we hang up. I haven't seen it since the theater. Maybe I'll really like it.
You're not going to like it. Yeah. All right. Look, it's got its moments. It's got its moments.
It's got some bad moments. And, you know, overall, though, it's, it's, it's not, look, I recognize
it. It's not a great flick. But I remember the opening being pretty cool. You've been opening
it's great. Yeah. Um, once Shyla Buff rides up on the motorcycles, when you start to be like, uh,
boy, all right. Um, anyway, speaking of special effects or movie this week, mortal combat 2021,
uh, this is a video game adaptation of the famous or movie adaptation of the famous video game
franchise, mortal combat. I'm sure you all know what that is. At least by name, if not by experience
and playing the games over the years, which is, God, it's got to be a 30, at least a 30 year old
franchise at this point. I played it on Super Nintendo. The only version I ever played. I liked it,
you know, this was a game I worshiped as a child. Okay. When you went into the arcade and they had
a video game where it looked like real people fighting with blood and impalements. And one of the
characters looked like Bruce Lee, I was like, holy shit. Like this must have thrilled you
that Holly would finally got this franchise right. Let me say this about the film.
The movie takes place. Uh, it's about a, uh, a new character named Cole Young,
yeah, who is a descendant of who eventually becomes uh, Scorpion. Uh, Scorpion is his descendant from
hundreds or is his ancestor from hundreds of years earlier, who is killed by sub zero at the very
beginning of the movie sub zero of the ice guy, Scorpion is the fire guy. Uh, there are versions
of them in the games where they're good. There are versions of them in the games where they're evil,
blah blah blah blah. The point is the movie opens with this sub zero dies. I mean, sorry, Scorpion dies
and it jumps a few hundred years. And we're introduced to this MMA fighter named Cole Young,
who is then brought into the world of mortal combat. He's got a birthmark in the shape of a dragon.
Uh, and he finds out that that means he is one of the chosen and a descendant of this
clan. Uh, and uh, he is then brought into the world of this tournament, uh, that takes place every,
however, whenever the fuck it takes place, uh, that keeps the realms in balance and, you know,
uh, keeps, keeps one of the realms in charge of the other realms and all that stuff.
Um, I have played these games since the 90s. I own, I believe every mortal combat that's ever
been released, every time a new one comes out, I'm extremely excited. And I always love it. I'm
never disappointed. I didn't know what the fuck was going on in this film.
Denjo imagine you're me. I watched this with, I watched this with Jay Oakerson,
yeah, the entire movie we were turning to each other going. I mean, I think this is awesome.
But if I didn't play the video games, I wouldn't know what the fuck was going on right now.
Like, yeah, I, I understood it to an extent because I play the games. So like when they would talk
about the tournament and, and the Netherrealm and all that shit and Shang Tsung and the sole leader
and everything, I knew what they were because I know the stories, blinds from the games.
So are they getting, are they getting that stuff just from the in between the fight things in the
game, the little scrolls that go up. The later games, the later games have full story modes.
Oh, okay. You know, there's all kinds of mythology you can buy out there and whatever.
But, but, and I think at one point the game, the booklets had backstory in them, you know.
Okay. Kind of like the he men comic books would when you were kid. So I knew like as I watched this,
um, Shang Tsung is the, he's the bad guy from the first game. He's the main bad guy, you know,
he started it all on him. So when he stepped, when the guy came in, he just looked like Shang Tsung.
I was like, oh, that's, that's going to be Shang Tsung. Right. And he eats people's souls and he wants
to control the, the realms and I knew all this from playing the fucking video games. They barely
explain it in the movie. And then when they do, they don't do a great job of explaining it. So
I was just like, like, like, like when cano shots. So one of the things in the movie is they bring
everybody to this temple to figure out their, it's a, there's a term for it. I can't remember,
but to figure out their special power. Everybody born with this birthmark has a special power that
they have to awaken inside of them. And that's how they explain why guys can shoot fireballs and
shit like that in real life. Like they can in the video game. Yeah. So my, but my, that's
this is my point. When cano shoots a fucking laser beam out of his eyeball. I was like, yeah,
finally, it's cano. I was wondering how they were going to justify the, if you didn't know the game,
you'd be like, what the fuck is going on? Why did that guy just shoot a laser ball out of his eyeball?
Yeah, that's how I felt the whole time. I mean, I had a, a light familiarity with the characters.
I remember like the music, I remember like, Raiden and like, you know, certain weight,
things that me and my friends would say, you know, but I don't know anything about the story.
And I think lately that I said this about basically all these HBO max ones. I think Warner Brothers
must be so grateful that they have been able to dump shit turd after shit turd after shit turd into
American homes have 500 million people held hostage in their homes, watch them because there's nothing
else to do and make these awful films into hits. Because if you look at this collection of movies
that HBO max, we were all excited. Oh, great. We're going to get a theatrical release every week.
Wonder Woman 2, the little things, con versus Godzilla,
Mortal Kombat, Tom and Jerry, probably the worst of the lot. And you didn't like, uh,
Justice League either. Four hour Justice League. And what I come away from these movies saying is not
that was bad or, oh, that sucked or whatever, I do think that. But I also think this is a,
this is a movie division. And I will pull this thing right off the internet if I ever have a deal
to write a movie for Warner Brothers. But everyone at Warner Brothers HQ has to be fired.
These movies are nonsense. And you can say that, okay, you know, people don't write good movies
anymore. And you're wrong. There's always talent out there. The fact that Warner Brothers is letting
these movies get this far with these budgets and then dropping them into our laps like here,
you deal with this. I mean, these movies don't make any sense. From moment to moment to moment,
they don't make sense. And I have an issue because I have trained myself to always be focusing on the
problems in a story that's the job of a showrunner. Unfortunately, because it kind of ruins movie going
for you. But I have a bad habit of always thinking about the scene I've just seen as opposed to the scene
I'm watching. And sometimes I can sort of lose my place in a movie that way. I admit that's a fault of
mine. But in these movies, I don't know at any point what is happening, why it's happening,
why anyone cares that it's happening. I can't put the basics of a story together in almost any of
these movies. And they're long and they're expensive and they're just getting shittier and shittier.
And people used to say this when I was 16. They'd be like, oh, Jurassic Park and all this
you know, Independence Day, all it is is just mindless sci -fi and special effect. They would
slit their mother's throat to have a movie as good as Independence Day come out right now. We're seeing
movies that don't even enter the realm of making sense, Joe. So I okay, so I'll say this about
mortal combat. And it's similar to what I said about Justice League. I think this is the best
movie adaptation of a video game that's ever existed. Oh, for Christ's sake. But here's why. Hold on.
Well, look, what's the competition? Well, that's part of it. But here's why. It truly is an adaptation
of a video game. I mean, now that said, just like I said, Justice League was truly an adaptation of
it played like a graphic novel. It didn't play like a superhero movie. Now does that mean that
this movie is good? No, because I think a movie is supposed to be accessible to everybody.
Does that mean I didn't enjoy it? No, I enjoyed it very much because I was seeing tons of things I
saw from the video games. They are bringing it to life. I found that very exciting. I think the
characters are awesome. They get me going. Did the Gore was that an invention of the movie or
have the games become that gory? Like there's a few scenes where the movie games are more gory than
the movie. When that woman's like insides come splattering out of them, we were like, holy shit.
There were a few that were rough. No, the game mortal combat 11 and 10 did that. I think that was
the first time they did it was in 10. It might have been the one before that. They do this X -ray thing
now when you fight and you do this special move and it zooms in an X -rays into the body of the person
you're punching and it shows you their bones breaking. It's wild. They're wild fucking games.
Yeah. In this movie, when I played it, they would just kick each other in the face.
Yeah, but blood would come out and then there were the fatalities even in the first game,
which they did. They did some of the original fatalities in this, which I thought was cool.
But here's my point. Everything that made you love mortal combat as a franchise. If you were a
movie, when they did it in the movie, it felt like mortal combat. It didn't feel like John
Ling was almost trying to do Mario Brothers. It didn't feel like Donnie Wahlberg trying to do Max
Payne. It didn't feel like the the weird hitman adaptation with Timothy Allafant. It felt like mortal
combat. It did. And so did the quite frankly, so did the original one, which is not a great movie.
No, I saw remember that in the annihilation. I never saw annihilation. But my point is, is they felt
like the video games, like the sets, the scenery, everything. They go to the pit in this one,
which is one of the most famous levels in the games. And the plot itself played exactly like a video
game plot. If you gave me this plot and you go, this is mortal combat 12, I would have been like,
okay, cool. And I would have loved playing it in the story mode and I would have had a lot of fun.
When you take it out of that and put it into a movie, your investment, first of all,
you're a little removed, obviously. When you're playing the game, I think you're a little more
invested to these details on what's going on because you're assuming the role of a character.
When you put it on the screen and now you're just an observer, your investment is obviously lessened.
And then when you bring people that aren't like me into the room to watch this thing,
that aren't going to get a kick out of the ice moves and how jacks gets his robot arms and all
these things. You know what I mean, like, you're just going, what the fuck is this? This is insane.
And I agree with you on that. It is insane. That said, I enjoyed it, but it's not a good movie.
Which is a weird stance to take. I would never tell, I was texting Pinkstone and I was like,
because he was saying he was going to watch and I go, hey man, listen, I'm going to tell you what,
I thought it was awesome. That said, if I never played these games, I would think it was a jumbled
fucking mess because I could barely follow it as somebody who's played the games. I don't,
you don't have a fucking chance of understanding this thing. But I am, it's nice to hear, though,
that it was good for fans, that it made fans happy because I'm assuming other people share your views
on the movie because most of these things don't please either the masses or the nerds who love it.
Like Mario Bros is a perfect example. Video game fans were like this sucks and the general
combat works for fans of the game and it's true to the game. Then that's good and it has a reason
to exist, but it's certainly left your average viewer out in the cold. I mean, Heather had no idea,
and she was very, the problem with, not, that's not a problem, but she's got a very inquisitive mind.
So it's always like she wants to know what's happening and so often when she watches one of these
big movies with them, like, you just got to let it go. They didn't figure it out. Why are you trying to
figure it out? You know, but she's like, but in this one in particular, she was like, but that
doesn't make sense because I'm like, Heather, no, it doesn't, but we're not going to go through all the
lore of, as long as it makes sense in the world of Mortal Kombat, they did their job to some extent.
But the games are insane, dude, you're telling, you play the story mode on the newer games,
you're teleporting through realms and time period. It's fucking wild, but it's fun. And really,
what you're there for, and let's be honest is the violence. You're there for what are the new
fatalities? What does scorpion do this time? You know, what's the craziest way you can kill a guy?
You know, like, it's, it's wild shit. You know, in Mortal Kombat 10, you can pick up an old woman
and throw her at somebody. Like, they're nuts. The games are nuts. So like, well, if these became
like a, a saw or a Freddy or a Jason or something where it's, we all go and see the cool kills,
I'd be down. For me, I'd rather they just shave off all the story stuff and focus on the fights
at that because that's all I cared about and enjoyed in this movie. It was a needlessly complicated
plot. And that's why I say it really was plotted like a video game. It was plotted as if,
do you hear that kill build to make it out? Yeah. It was plotted as if this was the next installment
in the video game franchise. Yeah. Because you'd say, by the way, it probably is. I'm sure they'll do
some tie -in. Well, you, but you'd say, okay, this is Mortal, it's, it's Mortal Kombat. The,
the basic premise here is, is there's an interdimensional tournament that allows for control over the four
realms. And you hope that the good guys win so the demon realm doesn't rule everything. It's
that simple. Why would you not just do that? Instead, they did this plot where it was like,
Shang Tsung is breaking the rules. And he's not allowing us to have the tournament. So now we're just
going to fight over here. And so I understood that. I got with that, but I'm like watching this for
the first time. You're like, what the fuck is happening? That's why I say it truly is the best video
game adaptation I've ever seen. That doesn't mean it's a good movie. And I would, it was one other
thing I was going to say. I forget 20 minutes in. I was able to say to myself, you don't have to pay
attention to the story anymore. It's not going to mean anything to you. And then I just was waiting
for the kills as if it were a horror movie. In that regard, particularly the really gory kills were
cool. I like that aspect of it. The only other real enjoyment I got was that my wife and I were laughing
at how many times they said, fuck, it was like clearly somebody at Warner Bros was like, you got,
guys, we got to earn this R. Let's get some fucks in there. Come on. Yeah, there was a needless
amount of fucks. Cano said fuck way too many times. I didn't like that they gave
not Syrax. The dreadlock robot guy. I'm blanking on his name right now, but I didn't like that they
gave him like this kind of queens. Almost like a super Mario voice, which I thought was kind of dumb.
Who's the big creature that goes around with them that looked like something like Scorpion King?
Okay. That's Goro. He's from the original game. He's one of the originals.
That's 90s style effects though on him. Yeah, that's what he looks like. I mean, it's weird.
You know, we're crossing into a weird world now because video games look so real. They almost look
like movies and then you make a movie of the video game and you have to do all these special effects that
you can't do in real life, which is what the video game is. But then sort of looks like we're in a
weird, weird gray area here right now with all this stuff. But I would say in closing, even the
climactic moment of the movie, spoiler alert, if you don't play the games, you're not going to understand
how awesome it is or why Scorpion rises from hell, throws a spear through Sub -Zero's chest and says
get over here in a ridiculous voice. Right. And it's the only time he speaks English in the entire
movie. It makes no fucking sense. But if you love the games, you realize how cool that is and that they
also played the original Mortal Kombat music in that one moment from the original movie. And I was
like, we were like, yeah, like, like, even though the movie wasn't that good, like, you know, so.
Yeah, I mean, my hog is hesitantly up. My hog is aggressively down. But, you know, it had
its stupid charm, I guess, if I'm being real generous. I mean, yeah, Tom and Jerry made this
thing look like, you know, like metropolis or something. I guess I'll say yes. It was better than
Tom and Jerry. I can grant you that. We don't know what we're doing next time, folks, but we will be
back. Of course, I don't even know what big ones are coming down the pike. But I know there are
some. Something's coming soon that I was like, Oh, I guess we're going to have to do that. Yeah,
I don't know what it is. But, you know, well, we'll surprise you. We'll bring some good good and
that shutter is doing. We should probably pluck one of those shutters out. Shutter has got shutter is
now releasing heavy amounts of shutter original DVDs and blue rays into like target and Walmart.
So they're creating an incredible amount of original content. So we should probably pluck one of
those shutters at some point next month and well, we were going to do in search of darkness too.
Oh, yeah. That's what it was. Let's do that. But I got to say though, I watched all four and a half
hours of it. I had a great time. And yet, I don't know what we'd say. You know, it's a time ahead
documentary. There's not much to say about it is blue shirt back. He's back, but they clearly took the
note to scale him back because they must have read every review of it ever. The guy, he's not
wearing the blue shirt anymore, but he was not in it to the extent that I almost texted you.
Thank God, they got rid of that fucking nightmare. But then about 45 minutes and he makes his first
appearance, but he's very slimly used. And I agree. That's kind of a pointless thing to review because
it's almost like a review. It's in and of itself. So that said, I really enjoyed the hell out of it.
They go, they go too obscure at times, I would say. And avoid, they still avoid some of the bigger
titles in favor of nonsense, but maybe that's just because they can't get the right out of who
knows, but it's very entertaining. Alright folks, that's our show. We'll see you next time. And we'll see
you in hell.