I see you like hell
And when the sound of your screams
Becomes the pain of my dreams
You know I see you
I see you like hell
Hi, everybody!
How is everybody doing? Good?
We should have gone to that sitting down rehearsal they had
I'm knocking shit over
I can't see any of you
That's what I asked for
Do you got room to slide there? Just a little bit?
I got room to slide. Are we sliding later?
I'm going to fall off the side of this thing
There we go
I thought you were planning something
No, we're close
No, I know
Also, what I asked for
Welcome to We'll See You In Hell
One of your favorite podcasts reviewing horror, fantasy, sci -fi, action, sometimes drama, sometimes comedy
Thank you for being here. I'm Joe DeRosa
And I'm Patrick Walsh
Hello
Back in New York in the city
She's missed me
But I ain't missed her, I can't say
It's not my town anymore
It's very cold
Very cold
And as we're discussing backstage, it'll be 10 outside
And then you go in
Oh, it'll be nice to warm up in here
Let's make it 140 inside
I went to a museum today
I'm like pitting out my shirt
And then you go outside and it's like Moscow
Horrible
But, you know, it's nice
You didn't fall back in love with the apple?
I didn't fall, I know
On your return?
I had my time here and it was enough
I was an NBC page here in 2003
And is my friend Elon here tonight?
No
Oh, wouldn't that have been awkward?
We were pages together
How are you, sir?
Doing well
Good, good
He's a good man
Where were you a page in NBC for a specific show?
30 Rock, baby
I did Conan
Not the show 30 Rock
No, no, no
The building
Yeah, the building
Okay
I did Conan and SNL
And by did you mean you fucked Conan O 'Brien?
And I don't mean the shows
I mean the buildings, Conan and SNL
Could I get a drink?
Me too, if that's possible
I'll meet you halfway
Whatever I gotta do
Jack and Coke
Oh, that's good
That's okay, thank you
And I'd love a silver tequila and soda
I'm a tequila man now
Did you know that?
I did
You were leaving LA, leaving Los Angeles
Not a moment too soon
LA wasn't sad to see me go
I gotta say, people
They actually gave me the plane ticket
And said, we've had enough, Joe
You talked enough shit, frankly
Is Phil here?
Phil, I really can't see you
And you're that close to me
Yes, I saw Phil at the Los Angeles International Airport
Which was very exciting
One in the morning, whatever time that was
And you said you were a teacher
And I wanted to ask you
Does that mean you had a sub yesterday?
Because this was Thursday night
Yeah, my wife and I are both teachers
And we were both really sick
They felt ill
You got subs to come to this?
These poor children
All right, well thank you
Anyone else from out of state?
All right, awesome
It's always nice
We're going to give some stuff away
That's going to come into play in a moment
But we should say
As a surprise for you guys
Not only
Well, we're going to do two episodes for you guys tonight
It's not just going to be one
We have to keep
We do have a hard out in the room
So we have to keep them to about an hour apiece
But we are going to do two
We'll save the second movie
It'll be a surprise
But today's episode will be The Rise of Skywalker
And it might be where our friendship ends
Because this movie changed my life
Oh boy
Yeah, it might end our friendship
Thank you so much
Thank you very much
Give it up for the wait staff
They're going to take great care of you
Take great care of them please
Anyway
Whatever you were going to give us
Cash, give them half
You know
I'm staying at this fancy hotel
I save up all my points on my credit card
And then me and the wife are here
Hello, Heather
We're staying at this nice hotel
Sorry, ladies
Bing
Just pointed to my ring, home listeners
Can't see it
But they did this thing that I hate so much
And they only do it to guys in a new relationship
If it's a 60 -year -old couple, they never ask
Because neither of you care about each other anymore
But they walk up and the guy's like
Well, sir, we've got you booked in a room
It is our junior suite
And it's 800 a night
And we've got you here till Sunday
Is that correct?
And he's like, yes
The girl's hanging on his arm all excited
And he's clearly taking her out for a big night
And the guy will be like, okay
Well, now I would like to tell you
For just 3 ,000 more
We have our emperor suite
Which has this, this, this
Two bathrooms, bidet, whatever else
And then the girl's eyes light up
And she's looking up at him
And you can see the guy wanting to murder
Him, her, everyone
And just get out of there
Before he has to pay for this
So this guy was like, I can't do it
I'm sorry, but thank you
And then she's like, oh
And he goes, no, I can't do it
I can't do it
So then he goes, what if I could give it to you
For 1 ,600 extra
Instead of the 3 ,000
And I wanted to intervene
And say to stop this madness
It was sick
Sick
What did he do?
So now this room
She's so excited to say this amazing fancy hotel
In New York on Valentine's weekend and everything else
And now there's this film on the whole evening
Where it's like, oh, but you could have done this
But you don't care about me that much
Awful
What did he end up doing?
Did he buckle?
He stuck with what he came for
Good
Yeah
You'll take the Prince suite
And you'll like it
But the girl was so clearly bummed
And I just think that sucks
So I go up to her
I go, hey, you want a guy
Who's going to drop 1 ,600 on you?
I'm in 318
No, I didn't
I was in 319
Folks
How are you?
Oh, boy
We
When I look at my phone tonight
By the way, I wrote notes down
I had a paper when we did the last live show
And my hands shake too bad
I get very nervous
Well, it's also the dependency on alcohol
Yes, and the dependency on alcohol
I requested this to be brown
In case I spray the back wall with diarrhea at some point
But blue, I think, will mask it just fine
I get very jittery and nervous
I don't know why
What?
Yeah
Calm down
Yeah, relax
All right
This guy ditched out a group of needy kids
To get out here
We want to do a giveaway before we start
We have some merch that we want to give away
As part of this first episode
So the first question was going to be
Who traveled the farthest to get here?
Right now the lead is Los Angeles, California
But now let me ask
Did anyone come from out of the country?
Yeah
What?
From where?
That's crazy
Wales
Wales?
Oh, my God
Did you have other business in town, I hope?
Oh, okay
All right
Oh, my God
We can't provide you a Wales trip level of entertainment
I assure you
Do you guys listen to the podcast?
Or were you like, oh, that just seems like a fun thing to do?
Oh, okay
So you're not fans
Get the fuck out of here
Who traveled on purpose the farthest?
So who traveled from out of the country but loves We'll See You in Hell?
They will love it in an hour and a half
But who already loves it?
Nobody
Thank you
That would be insane if somebody came from out of the country
So is LA the farthest?
I'm no cartographer, but
I'm from LA, too
Okay
Washington
Is that farther?
That's definitely farther
Give it to the gentleman
Vancouver wins
We're sorry, guys
We would have to do some tiebreaker for LA
You win
Isn't Vancouver out of the country?
No, Vancouver, Washington
Oh, okay, I'm sorry
All right
You're going to get a shirt of some kind
That's what all the prizes are
Yes
But we'll give it to you later, relax
I wrote down questions so we could do this trivia question
That was the first one
The second one is
Now, you've got to raise your hand
If you scream it out
No, no, scream it out and we'll just have to figure out who screamed first
I guess it's the best way to do it
That should work, especially since we can't see
I can see fine
I don't know what's going on with your eyes
I got this one
It's fine
Falling apart by the second
I have macular degeneration
Who knows what movie we did commentary on on the very first episode ever of this podcast?
Okay, that guy wins
Clear winner
By a long shot
Sir, you also get a shirt
Oh, they're here
Oh, sorry
Emily Florence
Come on
The matriarch of the show
Yes
Okay, so that guy, that's two
And then our third question
These get harder
That's what she said
Thank you
What was the name of the
Our nipples?
No, these get hard, dicks
These get harder, but she said it like to a group of guys she's having sex with
It's a woman with a line of dicks
She's doing like a blow bang
She's going down, she's going, you know, these get harder as you go
Oh, gosh, okay
The last guy must have popped a blue chew
Folks, let me, we don't have to do those ads anymore
No, no
Oh, thank God
The ads are done
Good
Those sweet $55 ads
Yeah, what a shakedown that was
I used my blue chew once
I used it once as well
That's probably why I have this vision problem, actually
I actually used it
I was, I called you, I was in Vegas
Yeah
No, this is true
I came over, presented myself, and you took me home
I was in, I was in Vegas doing shows
Shows
Yeah, and then I met a woman in Vegas
And she said, why don't you stay an extra day, just hang out with me
And I called you and I go, I am so shot
I can't spend another day in this town
I'm dying, it's too much booze, I'm dead
But this very lovely person wants me to hang out for an extra day
And Pat goes, do you got your blue chews?
And I said, you know what, I do
And he said, pop one of those and hang out, man
So I popped one, did nothing for my penis whatsoever
It was the worst tasting thing I've ever had
And then I blew shit in my teeth for the rest of the night
Passed out around 8pm
It's weird that they do claim to be this delicious thing
Just be a pill, it's a pill that you swallow
It really was a bad taste
A taste that almost makes you out of the mood to have sex
Yeah, yeah, yeah, you're about to have sex
She's like, why does your breath smell like chewable Tylenol?
Alright, what was the name, this is a tougher question
What was the name of the movie that I wanted to make
That starred a cast of old coffee breath actors
Dabney Coleman was one of them
Martin Mole, but I'm not casting him anymore
Does anybody know?
Starts with a W, that's a hint
Was about a witness protection program
Yeah!
That guy also gets the thing everybody else got
We didn't know either, Emily had to remind us what that was
Yeah, Emily wrote these questions
I was like, I don't know the answer to that
Then Joe made
Joe made up a porno version of that movie
With the old coffee breath character actors
And that was called what?
Great guess with dickless protection
But how would you do a porn, unless it was a lesbian porn
In which case, that's still a great time
Witness erection
Phil you got your shirt after all baby
Alright
Witness erection
Also what I call it when I get really aroused
Watching that Kelly McGillis topless scene in the film
Witness about the Amish community
She's a sexual being in that movie
She's not like a nun or something
She's hot
Kelly McGillis a lesbian also, did you know that?
Killed her career
They couldn't just make a movie about Harrison Ford becoming Amish
They had to be like no, there's got to be a ten in there that he bangs
Crazy
It's so ridiculous
It's not like Top Gun where you need Kelly McGillis
In there as a beard
You know Harrison Ford is a straight man
Tom Cruise is out playing volleyball with a bunch of shirtless dudes
For half the running time of the film
Hey Val, let me oil you up
But I'm into girls I swear
Yes, what else if I could
I'd love to get on
With the show and at the same time on
With the
Joe's little town
Blues
They're melting
Away
He's gonna make a brand new start of it
In Joe's New York
Right? Yeah, that was pretty good
That was pretty good, I liked it
That was good, I got tripped up
Here's where I got tripped up
The lyric, you think the lyric is those little town blues
Which rhymes with Joe's, it's these little town blues
No, I knew it, I made a little switch
Well, it's funny, every time I've pitched you one you go that doesn't even rhyme with Joe
But it's my thing so I can make up whatever rules I want
I wanted to get to New York, New York
We also could have done, we'll see you
In hell, cause it fits
Yeah, you could use any words to that melody
I would have kept going if I had been hit with a wave of hot applause
When I started singing, but it was real tepid
So I was like, I'm singing two bars and I'm out
Did you guys ever see Lost in America with Albert Brooks? Of course
That's my favorite scene in the movie is when the ad exec
Is pitching him the ad for the Lincoln town car
And he goes, I got a great song
This little town car
And Albert Brooks goes, shut up Ken, I'm stronger than you
And I will hurt you
It's a great scene
We have a quick news psycho to do
Before we go to everybody's favorite little corner
In town
That's right, it's mine
The news psycho on this episode
Look, we realize we're two months late on this
But that's just how we record these days
We have not talked about yet the second
Kevin Spacey Christmas Eve video
Where he doubled down on that first one
Even crazier
That means nobody in a full year said, Kevin
These videos are scaring the fuck out of people
And everybody knows that you're having everyone
You've ever jerked off murdered
And you need to stop doing these videos
No, he doesn't have any friends in his life to be like, Kev, baby
You're done acting
You're done
I think people are saying it to him and he doesn't care
I think he's off the reservation obviously
Did he do this one as the House of Cards character too?
Not only does it, he does it as the House of Cards
Kevin Spacey
Do my Kevin Spacey?
Oh, I forgot I had one
Who invited my mom, folks?
Oh, that I don't know
Here's what I do know
Here's my narration of Frank Underwood
This house just got a whole lot
Cards here
More tepid applause, fuck all of you
Every scene of that show he'd be like
This is my favorite rib joint in town
Mopping the barbecue sauce, that show sucked
And we were all just like, this is awesome
So, to answer your question
He does it again as that character
It comes out on the day the man is found dead
Comes out the same day
And then the monologue
I think three people who have accused him of sexual assault have been killed
That's serious
He's sitting in front of a fireplace, poking it with a fire poker
Which I've never seen anybody in a scene of anything with a fire poker
Where it wasn't used to murder another human being
So he's poking the fire
Stoking it, whatever the hell it's called
And he's doing a soliloquy almost about like
I'll say you don't want to mess with me because I'm a bad man
That kind of thing
And it's fucking bad shit, it's bad shit
He's clearly being like, I'm going to walk the line of a confession
In the public eye
He's doing like joker level shit
He's like, I'm going to leave all the clues but they can't prove it was me
It's fucking incredible
In the true sense of the word
Not like great incredible, like that's incredible
That guy would swallow a bowling pin
That's incredible, I don't know if it's good
I think you're going to pull this table out
It's wrapped around your leg or something, the cord
And it keeps pulling on my leg in a way that I find scary
Alright, what Joe is not mentioning folks
Is that he was the cameraman who shot the Kevin Spacey video
And did a fine job by the way
Did a fine job
Which leads you to ask
Joe?
I'm setting you up for your own bit right now
Why did you tell Kevin Spacey to do what he did?
I stopped doing that bit because I was like, I'm not sure we're supposed to be joking about sexual assault
But there was so much going on for such a long period of time
I've also been indicted six times because of that bit
That's true
Even on SNL or something where they'll make a joke
About somebody who does sexual assault
And the audience will be like
Aren't you on the side of not sexual assault?
I never understood that
It was weird at the Golden Globes when Ricky Gervais took the shot at them about Epstein and Weinstein
Or Weinstein and Epstein
And they booed both jokes
And then his response was like, fuck you, it wasn't me
You're the ones that are friends with him
I didn't do it
Did you see the Oscars by the way?
I missed the entire thing, I read a transcription of Joaquin Phoenix's speech
I enjoyed it
He's out of his mind
If you're going to do a passionate political speech
Cut your edible intake in half before you get to the stage
I mean, Jesus Christ
I'm like, okay, yeah, he's anti -racism
Agreed, done
And then he's like, we need more women in movies
And I'm like, sure, couldn't agree more
Folks, we're inseminating cows and we're taking their babies away
And we're making love to the cow babies
And it's like, what?
I didn't read that part
The only part I read was the part where he said instead of canceling each other
We should teach one another
I thought that was a very nice thing to say
And then he was like, look, I know I've been a scoundrel in this business
Which I think, again, was an allusion to horrific behavior
But he's like, bad little old Joaquin
And then everybody's laughing it up
I love that you used the word scoundrel, though
It's a very Han Solo word to use
I thought that was very cool
And then Zell Weger coming up, it was like, you thought he was crazy?
Where do you see the cocktail of pills I'm on?
Eyes glazed over little beads
You know what her thing is
She was in Jerry Maguire
Every actress in town wanted that amazing part
She was like 22 and gets Jerry Maguire
And then just nothing
Bridget Jones, I'll grant you
But other than that, she's just been chewed up and spit out
This is how bad shit Renee Zell Weger is
You know it's bad when they have to reel you in to play Judy Garland
When they're like, Renee, tone it down a little bit
Maybe you want to clean up a little bit for this one
Obviously the Oscars needs a host
You just feel like it's some event you're at
Like in a Holiday Inn ballroom
The guy who's supposed to be there running the show hasn't showed up yet
The camera keeps moving around
Who's talking now? It was a disaster
Terrible show, boring
I had a little party, a couple people over
Everyone was gone by an hour in
Just sitting alone eating a bowl of chips that was designed for 25 people
Finishing it off
He had that six foot hoagie
And the stripper came out
Just me
It wouldn't have been so awkward
I wouldn't have watched it even if I was
Two feet from a television set
I can't
This guy is
He is tuned up
I wouldn't know why
I couldn't want to watch anything less
Than the Oscar
There's nothing enjoyable about it to me
It's become the same charade as politics at this point
Nobody believes in any of this shit
Everybody knows the awards are bought and sold
Nobody's watching this anymore
I was so swept away when so and so got up
That's all gone, the mystique's gone
Once I was able to DM Tom Hanks
Without ever meeting him
The mystique is gone with all this
You didn't have to DM him the nudes
He asked
He didn't ask
You felt Parasite should not have won
Because it was not an American film
Yeah
I'm not kidding
Hold on
We are on record as thinking it's an amazing film
It was the best movie to come out last year
But there's a category called foreign language film
It's for foreign language films
They even said
This is the first time
Go fuck yourself
I actually have an opinion I formed on my own
I didn't fucking read it on movieweb .com
And then fucking regurgitate it in a podcast audience
Fucking come at me
Listen, as always folks
These are the remarks of Jodorosa
And not the podcast as a whole
I have a successful career
That guy drove from Toronto to be here
Now, here's my point
I thought the movie was awesome, I thought it was amazing
But there's a reason there's a foreign language category
If you don't want to do that anymore, get rid of the category
And just put everything in the one
Fine, that's fine
But when you have that category specifically for that
And then you give Parasite that award
And the best picture award
And they even came out and said, well we've never done this before
No shit you've never done it before
You've never done it before because you all got called on your racist horse shit this year
With your wall to wall white boy fucking extravaganza you had
And guess what
White women on stage crying about racism isn't enough anymore
You need to nominate some non -fucking whites
And they didn't do it and they got called out on it
And to cover their fucking asses
They broke their own rule
So that's why I said it was bullshit
It was a transparent bullshit fucking move
Period, it's true, it's true
Well I'm glad I brought it up
It's true
Well they did, like they had Beauty and the Beast
Was nominated for best picture
And then surely thereafter they announced the best animated feature category
And I don't think a cartoon's been nominated since
Toy Story 3, deserved
Best of the series
But yeah, it's a little strange, I don't feel anywhere near as strongly as you do
And I did feel Parasite was the best movie of the year
And also tied with Uncut Gems which was not nominated for a single Oscar
Uncut Gems was amazing
So was Parasite
But then put all the foreign language films
In that category
Then every foreign language film should be allowed to compete in that category
They're plucking one to try to grandstand
A little bit about something and it's like guys
It's obvious what you're doing right now
That's my only point, why have the other category then?
Just put it all together
What about they have the BAFTA's but British movies always win here?
Wait, what's that? No, foreign language film
That's a specific category they made up
You're saying British people speak English
Last I checked
Alright, folks
Are we getting to the, oh we're going to Pat's movie corner first
I hope
Yeah, we should get moving to it though
So we can get these two in
So I saw, and the title has already changed, but
I said saw
Can we get some tater tots for the gentleman?
Something absorbent
I saw
Birds of Prey, The Fantabulous
Wonderific Adventures of Harley Jane Quinn
And her merry band of women in nightgowns
Whatever it's called, the longest title
It's like the Fiona Apple album title
The one that goes on for like an hour
They retitled it because the fact that they're making these
Realizations after movies are released is insane
They spend all this time and money researching and they're like
Okay, we're completely wrong, let's just change the title
Sonic the Hedgehog, okay, everyone hates it, let's just do a new one
It's bad
I walked out of Suicide Squad, the last movie I walked out of
And I saw this just because I'm an AMC Stubbs A -list member
But it wasn't terrible
I like Margot Robbie a lot, it was visually cool
The fight scenes were cool
It's got a great Rotten Tomatoes score
I was surprised it was so highly reviewed
As I said on the old letterboxed
It's better than Suicide Squad, but so was
The Persian Gulf War
The Persian Gulf War was a much more diverse piece of work
It is what it is
If you enjoyed Suicide Squad, by all means you'll love it
I thought it was terrible and I thought that
Birds of Prey was fine
But visually it was cool
I'm doing a themed movie corner for this episode
I will be reviewing not one, not two
But three episodes of Perfect Strangers
Each of them
Each of them a very special episode
And terribly haunting
There are three episodes in season two that really shook me to my core
The first one
Is titled Falling in Love is Hard to Do
And the episode surrounds Balki going to night school
If you've never seen the show
It's about
A guy named Larry Appleton who lives in Chicago
And is from outside of Chicago
And his cousin, a mentally handicapped man
From a fictitious country comes to live with him
Who doesn't understand how anything works for some reason
And they made up a fake country so they could just keep making fun of him
If he was from a real country, they'd be like, that's racist
So they'd just go, meepios, that's not real
And then every episode he doesn't understand anything
So this one, in his night school
A woman who is in the class with him
Is in love with him
And Balki's head over heels for her
And then she shows up at the apartment
And she's like a ten and a half
And Larry's like, something's up here, this is weird
And then she's clearly using Balki
To get the homework out of him
For night school or whatever, right?
And then Balki's like, you're wrong
I'm sorry, this was The Wire or Perfect Strength?
Perfect Strength
So Balki is like, you're wrong about this woman, you're wrong about this woman
She's a wonderful person
So then Larry's like, you're going to fall on your face, but don't
So then Balki comes home the next day and goes, cousin
We are in love, she is my girlfriend now, whatever
And he starts to explain the conversation he had with this woman
Which basically was her saying, I live with another man
And I don't want to be your girlfriend
But again, for some reason Balki doesn't understand how anything works
So his interpretation is, she's my girlfriend
And then Larry's like, she's not your girlfriend
You need to call her and put this to a close
So he's like, you're wrong cousin, she's my girlfriend
So he calls her, and then the woman laughs in Balki's face
And hangs up
And then the last four minutes
Music starts playing
That literally sounds like it's music from
The funeral scene of a child death sequence
It is the saddest music I've ever heard in my life
And Balki sits on the couch going
I never want to fall in love again
Because it hurts too much
And that's how the episode ends
TGI Friday
Right into Family Matters
Skating that right into a Family Matters
There's a lot of fucking truth in that show, man
A lot of truth. Was there a tag? A humorous tag?
I don't think so. Like did he come in and slip on a poster?
I gotta be honest, I was weeping so uncontrollably
I don't know what happened at the end, but they get worse from there
I saw a film not pornographic
Entitled The Death of Dick Long
Has anyone seen that movie?
Man, I loved it. It was sick. Sick movie
But basically it is a movie about a bunch of friends
And they're all like, to give you an idea
They're in like a stained cover band
It opens with them playing like that stained song in the garage
And then their music they listen to is like Nickelback
And all that stuff, the early 90s
This is how you remind me
So then they are listening to all that all the time
But it's not really making fun of them
It's not like Napoleon Dynamite or something
It just treats them as people
And then one night there is an incident
And they drop their friend off at the hospital
They're all really drunk and they went out
They drop their friend off at the hospital
And the guy at the hospital, doctor, hospital guy
Played by Roy Wood Jr.
Who is a hilarious comic who I saw on the wall out here
Dear friend, he's in this movie? He's in the movie
Very funny comic
He is a small part, but he comes out and he's like, this is really messed up
And you know for a while that clearly something happened to this guy
Then it comes across that there's something wrong with his colon
That his colon has been shredded essentially
So it's like, did this guy's friends get drunk and rape him
And you don't know what's going on
Then it's revealed that this is a group of friends
All married, or mostly married
Who go out for a big night in the town, in their small town
They get drunk after their cover band rehearses
And have sex with a neighborhood horse
Oh, and his colon's all fucked up because the horse fucked it?
The horse fucked him, and this was like the first time
Is this a comedy?
It's online, it says it's a comedy
I didn't laugh, but
I mean, I saw a real video of a horse fucking a man
And I was bent over in hysterics
There's a documentary about that called Zoo
Which is about a guy who had this happen to him
And it's based on a true story
And this is also the plot of the latest Dr. Dolittle, is it not?
I know how to talk to him, baby
We don't do much talking anymore
That's our Robert Downey Jr. impression, that's how he talks
Boy, has that movie ever looked worse than Dolittle, by the way?
It got, I think, 11 % or something
It really fell on its feet
Even as an A -list member, I'm going to say it again, I didn't go see Dolittle
So basically what it's revealed, the guy's talking to his wife
And he's like, look, I know it sounds crazy
But for years we go up there and we have sex with the horse
This was the time that we let the horse have sex with us
And he's trying to explain it to his wife
And he's like, I know this sounds crazy and blah blah blah
And I was honestly sort of moved by this
Like, I didn't find the movie funny in any way
It's just kind of like, look, this is a sexual outlet for me
And it works for me
And you thought my comments on Parasite were troubling
Jesus Christ
Well, I kept the race of the horse out of it
Horse race!
Folks, the movie is
I think by the description you know if you want to watch it or not
But it threw me for a loop
And I gotta say, I'm always looking for something that makes me feel
Something I've never felt before
And this did, by which I mean
Becoming aroused by hearing about a man getting fucked by a horse
Fully aroused
Pat, I didn't know you were going to review that movie
And I'm so happy you brought up an animal themed piece of work
Oh, thank you
Because my second episode of Perfect Strangers is called
Dog Gone Blues
And this one starts out with
Balke bringing a stray dog home
Because it needs a home, I'm sorry, he finds it at the pound
And he brings it home and he's like, cousin
They kill the dogs there, we need to shelter the dog
Larry's like, Balke, our lease doesn't allow it
So then the next 15 minutes is a romp, farcical thing of them
Trying to hide the dog from the landlord
Silly enough, safe enough, until they get caught
I'm sorry, this was The Sopranos or was this Perfect Strangers?
Perfect Strangers
They get caught with the dog by the landlord and they have to give it away
So Balke gives the dog to a family
Consisting of a mom and a dad and two children who live on a farm
And the dog is going to have a great life there
And not live in this cooped up apartment
And then the remaining 10 minutes of this thing
Goes from Balke saying, I don't want to give my dog away
Again, the child death music comes in
Larry explains to him
He will have a better life, Balke
Then the family shows up and you think that's going to be the twist where it's nice
Balke, through the entire scene, hugs the dog
As if it had been fucking him
Like in your movie
In a very lovingly way
I didn't write it
Then the family takes the dog, thrilled to have a dog for their kids
And then the rest of the episode, and you won't be able to see this at home
Balke sits like this
As Larry tries to explain to him
That he did the right thing with the dog
No laughs, and it just ends
With a heartbroken Balke
It is so dark, but not as dark as the next one
Was it a late period, Perfect Strangers?
No, these are all in season two
Clearly they were still trying to find their footing a little bit
And then some new show runner came in
They go, guys, nobody gives a shit about the emotions
Have Balke fuck something up with language wise
And then they're waiters all of a sudden for some reason
Because it becomes that show
Every episode starts to become about like
Larry being like, oh my lord, my boss needs a new hat rack
And I said I could find him one
And the store is out of hat racks
I've got to build a hat rack
The dumbest plots ever
Or like Balke buys a hammer for Larry for Christmas
And Larry sells his nails to afford Balke's present
So now he has no use for the hammer
That's not a real episode, but that's why I'm a writer
That just came to me right now, and you could shoot it tomorrow
So when you said it's a dog gone
That was a play on words in the title, because the dog is now gone
Yeah, dog gone blues
Okay, got it
For my third and the last tomorrow
My wife and I are going to see the Harry Potter
Broadway play
Which starts at one, goes till four
Then you have dinner and come back
And it goes from six to nine
Oh my god, why are you doing that?
I love Harry Potter, as does Milady
You know he's not in it, right?
He's going to be there
He's barely in it, it's about like a new set of kids
Nobody wants it
I think it's a continuation
Harry's like 40
Who wants to see 40 year old Harry Potter
The saddest thing ever, the magic's gone
Can't get his wand up anymore
His wand's been limp for years
His wand's just hanging there
Yeah, he's been fucking Harmony on the side
Behind Ron's back, it's a dark story
Hermione, but fine
Sorry, I guess I'm racist that I couldn't remember that ridiculous made up name
Ron is 100 % bald by the way
Ron's got to be bald by this point
Ron seemed to be balding by the end of the Deathly Hallows
I'd like to see Ron morbidly obese in the play
They took my leg, Harry
I told you to stop eating, Ron
It's something
So we watched all 8 in a week of the movies
This is an underrated franchise, folks
These movies are fucking great
It has probably the most impressive cast
If you're putting all the movies together in the history of film
Every great British actor is in this thing
Except Michael Caine, where was Caine?
But it's just great
We were talking last night about how good Ray Fiennes is as Voldemort
I love those, but the only one I'm not that crazy about
It's not bad
The first one's the only one where I'm kind of like, it's a kid's movie
But then that second one starts
I feel like it kicks into high gear and doesn't let up
Except the sixth one where the whole plot is the dance
That's the fourth one, and it is the worst, I agree with you
It's the longest one
And it's about going to a dance
No, that's not the fourth one, the fourth one's Azkaban
No, the third one's Azkaban
This is Joe in a nutshell
I tell you that this week I watched all 8 movies
And Joe is insisting he's right about the details of them
I know the fourth one's Azkaban
You say what you want
I know it's Azkaban
Really, by the end they're just like adult movies
The first one gets a bad rap because it's kind of kiddy
But they're little kids, and it's setting up the world
And he cast it and everything else, you know, Chris Columbus
But it's a great franchise, I'm into it
I think my favorite was probably Azkaban
But the very last one is pretty fucking awesome too
The second half, part two of the last
Yeah, that's what you mean, right?
Yeah, I like the second one and the last one
Azkaban's my favorite too, because Oldman just comes in swinging
Oh, Oldman is great, well, Rickman steals the show, obviously
Snape is absolutely incredible
And I was this time, because I had forgotten, I was like, is Snape good or bad?
They really keep you guessing the whole time
But I used to do this bit all the time where it's like, no matter how innocent
Whatever Harry is doing, Snape appears
And Harry's at the drinking fountain or whatever
And then Snape materializes and it's like
Enjoying a cold drink
Mr. Potter
And he's like, yes
I'm allowed
Doing your homework, Mr. Potter
You assigned it, Snape
Yeah, Snape is dangerously close to a me too
Why are you in my bedroom?
This is not appropriate
Brushing your hair, Mr. Potter
And he goes so over the top at times
That the other actors are biting their lip to keep from laughing
In this very serious movie
Love it, I just love it
More over the top than Die Hard or anything
Or Sheriff of Nottingham
Remember, he's like, we're canceling Christmas
That's how big that villain got by the end
He was like, we're canceling it
Why? Why would that be on your agenda?
It's why Rickman to me is like a Pacino
Where it's like, they go big and when it works it's beautiful
And they go big in a way where it's hard for anybody else to go that big
And you can tell when Kenneth Branagh comes in
He's like, maybe I'll try to meet you
And he's like, nope, you go on ahead
Because he can't do it as good
Speaking of Pacino, since I saw The Irishman four times consecutively
I have been saying cocksucker so much
It has been burned into my head
Every time I get mad at someone I'm like, this fucking cocksucker
And I'm like, oh wait, I'm not in the mob
I think we dropped that word out too, by the way
It's not great
Last time I heard it on a regular basis was Deadwood
Pacino says it in every scene
He does
By the end of The Irishman he's saying it to his wife like
I love you cocksucker
He says it so much
It's insane
Alright, I saved the best perfect strangers app for last
What other podcast can you hear this on, by the way?
Alright, you ready for this?
That's right, this segment is called P .S. I love you
Perfect strangers, I love you
I forgot that, thank you, sorry we ran out of shirts
Give them yours
Perfect strangers, this episode also from season two
It's called Bye Bye Bicky
Is the title
Here's the setup, this is a classic setup
And I know you're going to guess exactly where this is going
Episode starts with Balki getting a phone call from his
Yaya Bicky
Which is the name for his 110 year old grandmother
I'm not joking, I remember that one
So she goes, he's like, oh cousin, this is so great
She's coming to visit, we have to prepare the house
So then the whole episode is Balki getting their
Chicago apartment ready for the arrival of his grandmother
So she feels like she's at home again in meatballs
Which includes, nothing short of, bringing a cow
Into the apartment, there's a cow in the apartment
In one part, and Larry doesn't freak out and go get it out of here
He just goes, oh Balki
The setup, you see it coming from a mile away
You're like, okay, at minute 14
Bronson Pinchot as Balki disappears from this episode
And then comes in as the 110 year old grandmother
Yaya Bicky, this is so obvious where this is going
I didn't see that coming
That's what they always did back then on the show
And I'm sitting there going, this is cringe worthy
How bad this is going to be
Oh my god, just get to it guys, get it over with please
Because it's going to be horrible
And then that doesn't happen
Because Larry gets a phone call for Balki
That Bicky has died in the airport
And then
That's your second act twist
The remaining 10 minutes of the episode
Is Balki having to learn how to deal with death
Which the last 5 minutes of
Is Larry leaving him in the apartment
So Balki can speak to his dead grandmother
And he's literally sitting in the living room
By himself going
When I saw the Statue of Liberty
It was the most beautiful thing I ever saw
And I could not have done that without you Bicky
Bye bye Bicky
Created by credits, that's it
Wow
I want to see it, I'll say that
You know
I mean I eat these things like during lunch
You know what I mean
Like I got a free hour in lunchtime before I got to go out
And do shows and podcasts and shit like that
So I sit down, I go, I don't want to think
Shit like that, these people paid to be here
You know what I mean, the stuff I do
But I have to, you know
My work day usually starts later afternoon
You know what I mean, so it's like
I'm not whining about it
People are just the worst
Every interaction, I just tweeted out
My top 10 favorite TV shows, even that
Can't just get tweeted out, I tweet out my top 10 favorite TV shows
And people are writing back, what, no wire
Yeah, no wire, if it was in the top 10
It would have been on the fucking list, you nimrod
I don't know, everything is in the discussion
These are my favorite TV shows, anyway
Perfect Strangers was not on the list
Yes, I won't tweet you anymore, sorry
But I get up in the morning and I write and work on stuff
And then I go, I'm going to take a break for an hour, eat lunch
And you don't want to, the world is awful, I wake up in a panic every day
I have anxiety from the second my eye sees the ceiling
Same
And you work, and then you gotta go out all night and be somewhat charming
Yeah
And then you go, I want lunch just to be
I just want lunch to be this free period where I don't have to think
So I go, I'm going to put on Perfect Strangers, what could the harm be
And then I'm sitting there watching a man cry over his dead grandmother
And it's just awful, and then I feel terrible again
I gotta wash it clean with an episode of Frasier
Frasier kept it tight throughout
Alright
So last night, we're getting to the movie
Last night I went to a theater I used to go to when I lived here
The AMC Times Square, to use my stubs
This theater has fallen into such disrepair
It's a nightmare, it was one of two theaters where you
You couldn't go to during the bedbugs outbreak in New York
Because the seats had bedbugs
I go in there
I could have moved my seat anywhere in the theater
Because it wasn't attached to the ground
I sit in the back row and I'm like, this seat isn't tethered to the floor
Or any other seats
You're going up 12 escalators
To get there, it's a nightmare of a theater
But I go in, by the way once, on my birthday
I knew nobody in New York, I knew not a single person
And on my birthday, I went after I got off work at 9pm
And I said, what movie do you have
That has the longest running time
That will kill the most of my birthday
And they were like, Cold Mountain starts at 9 .15 and goes to midnight
And I said, ma 'am
One for Cold Mountain
Also starring Renee Zellweger, and not a good movie
But I watched that on my birthday, I was very depressed at that time
And luckily, 15 years later, I'm more depressed
Sorry to interrupt you, we've got 14 minutes
We've got to get to the review, I apologize for rushing
I'm getting there, it's where I saw the movie
Joe talks about perfect strangers for a tight 40
We each did three things in the movie
I didn't know you were going to tell two more stories before the Star Wars review
Don't get mad at me because of this guy, don't get mad at me because of that guy
You left the story you were telling to tell a separate story
Look at these notes, people
It's all there
Looks like a fucking Stephen King story in front of me
Pages of notes
I care about this, I'm sorry
I went last night to see Star Wars a second time
Because I was like, okay, let me give this thing another chance
Folks, the movie isn't good
It's not a good movie
Well, the print looked like it was struck in 1977
It looked like they hung a lady stocking over the projector
But the movie is bad, folks
I don't know what to tell you
And this last trilogy has been just kind of sputtering to a close
The people who made them aren't on the same page
They don't like each other's movies, they don't like their own movies
The cast doesn't like the movies
It doesn't hold up
Go ahead, Joe
This movie
Oh my God
I pray that a light falls onto him
Not a death, not a death
But just something enough to put him in a chair for the rest of his life
Give me a moment with my Lord to just
Okay
I pray fast
No, I thought that this movie
Was an excellent ending
To a 40 -year journey
I've been on it my entire life
JJ Abrams was faced with the almost impossible task
Of finishing something he set out to do
Five years ago, whatever it was, with the Force Awakens
That Rian Johnson came in and just
Blew to fucking pieces
I prefer Last Jedi to this one
That's insane and I will strike you
It tried to do something different
Nobody wants something different at Star Wars
Give us Star Wars
Nobody wanted that fifth Harry Potter to suddenly be about car racing
I might get into NASCAR
Nobody wanted it to be that
You want a guy doing magic with the fucking weirdo
I'm saying Mr. Potter
That's what Harry Potter is
Star Wars is Star Wars
Force Awakens, I admit
Was a rehashing
I get that, but it was time to get the thing back on course
Get the fans excited again
Force Awakens succeeded greatly in that
Setting up what was supposed to be this amazing new adventure
Where Luke was going to be the Obi -Wan
And train Rey and all this cool stuff
And Rian Johnson comes in and goes
Now I'm going to spend the first 90 minutes of the movie
Making the greatest action hero of all time
In all of fantasy
A fucking whining prick on an island
Who's like, I don't want any friends
They might as well have Walter Mathau playing Luke Skywalker
In that fucking movie
And then in the last five minutes
Luke is Luke again and it was great
Last Jedi had its moments, I'm not saying it was a complete waste
But J .J. Abrams comes in
And they clearly brought him back
This thing kind of went off the rails a little bit here
They killed Luke, what are we going to do, blah blah blah
And J .J. came in and said right off the bat
My job here is to not just end this trilogy
It's to tie together all nine movies
And I thought he did a really great job of that
I thought the fact that he brought back the Emperor
And said this is where it all started
Where was the Emperor?
Why, where was he, how did they get him back?
So what happened? That should be explained to me
Maybe if you took the time to read the comics and novels like I do
You'd fucking know the answer to that
I'm 39 years old
I'm not going to hold your hand through it, Pat
You've got to do a little work on your own
I think most people have not read the comics that go to see Star Wars
Star Wars has always done that
People complain when Return of the Jedi came out
That there was no scene between Lando and Han saying
Hey I'm sorry I fucked you over and you were frozen for a year
They always kind of glazed over stuff like that
My point is this
I thought the fact that he brought the Emperor back
To bring everything back ultimately
To where it all started
Was awesome, it kept me guessing
I didn't know if Rey was going to turn or if Kylo was going to turn
I didn't know what was going to happen
I thought the sequence with Luke was Luke being Luke again
The Han Solo cameo
I didn't see that coming
It made me cry
I didn't see the facelift coming I'll tell you that much
When old Han walks into frame
And he does the I love you I know bit again with his son
It's like give me a fuck
They can't have one original thought in this movie
So now they're rehashing The Force Awakens
Which was like two ago
It's just doing the same thing again as that movie
Which was a rehash of the original movie
You get some of the same lines
Now we're going to reveal that the Emperor was Rey's grandfather
Who cares?
The Emperor was her grandfather
These reveals are ridiculous
Chewbacca is Jabba the Hutt's aunt
Who gives a shit?
I don't care about Rey, I don't care about the Emperor
The Emperor looks like Uncle Fester let himself go
The guy who plays the Emperor is like 90 at this point
I don't understand
Let me go through every scene in this movie that brought me to utter tears
Please don't
Let's start with Lando taking the helmet off
And it's Lando in the desert wept
Let's jump to
Chewie finding out Leia died and falling to his knees
And Wookie crying wept
Let's jump to
Why is Leia in this franchise?
She's been dead for years
They have a CGI Leia going like you can do it Rey
Why do we need this? It's absurd
Hey everybody, here's your Mr. Woke fucking podcast host
Complaining that they let a 60 year old woman into a movie
She's dead!
I'm complaining they let a dead woman into a movie
I'm sorry if I don't think diversity ends at death
I think you fucking pushed for it
Sorry that diversity is hard, Pat
The scene where Luke
Lifts the X -wing out of the water
And he couldn't do it in Empire and now he does it
Wept, wept
The scene where they go we're done, we're done
Nobody's gonna come help us
And fucking Lando Calrissian shows up in the Millennium Falcon
Doing the Lando laugh with the fleet of ships
To help them and it plays the Star Wars theme in its entirety
Cried my fucking eyes out
My fucking eyes out
And then finally, what's your name, Rey
What's your last name, Skywalker
I've got chills right now, this movie is so good
It's so good
But you're just not a normal person then
Like you have your own thing that you're bringing to this
That is not what a normal person brings to this
It's for me, this was made for me, you know what I mean?
This new franchise introduced
Roughly 50 new characters, to me none of them hit
Boyega, no, Rey, no
Black guy, woman
I'm just saying everybody, I'm just saying
Space Oscar Isaacs, who is white man, no
He didn't work for me either
BB -8, no, none of this worked
And I'm sorry folks, but the Mandalorian couldn't come up with any good characters either
Mandalorian is bad
So what do they got? Hey, let's make Yoda young
Because that's all they know how to do now
Well, it worked in 1977, so you're getting the same characters
The same interaction, and America eats it up
My criticism of the Mandalorian was
I'm glad you don't like it either
I find it painfully boring, and I have so many friends in it that I have to not say that around
It's good work
And then I go in a corner and scream into a pillow
No, I said to my buddy the other day
He goes, why don't you like the Mandalorian? I go, why don't I like it?
Because I don't want to see Omos Boba Fett rescue
Omos Yoda on Omos Tatooine
It's boring, just give me the real characters
Can I tell you how the Mandalorian should have opened?
This is what it should have been
It should have been about Boba Fett, first of all
The whole plot of that show is about a bounty hunter, a Mandalorian
Who's life and job gets thrown up in the air
Because of the destruction of the Empire
Here's how that TV show should open
Open, wind blowing, desert shot, desolation
Cut two, another desert shot, desolation
Cut two, what's that? There's a hole in the ground
In the distance, get closer, what's that? Oh my God
That's the Sarlacc pit, close up on the Sarlacc pit
Fucking grizzled hand comes out of it
Boba Fett crawls out of the fucking Sarlacc pit
Makes his way to Mos Eisley, goes, I need a ship
And I need a job, and they go, I don't know if you heard
The Empire is gone, and he's like, fuck
The Mandalorian, that would be so awesome
I agree, that's not what we got
I just gave myself chills with my own idea
You can't connect
And we'll talk about the Mandalorian in another episode
You can't connect to someone who you never see his face
You can't do it, I'm sorry
The women that they're adding to the Rise of Skywalker
We are going to talk about that
One also has her face covered the whole time
That was her decision
She had the Felicity haircut again and nobody liked her
Her reason was something like
I thought it would take away from the mystique
Something like that
She had no personality, no reason to exist
The girl, Rose, that was in the last one
The young Asian actress, they bring her back
They set her up as a big hero in the last one
And this one, her lines are, what, huh, where are you going, why
And then maybe, huh, again, are her lines
That's what she's got to do
They bring in the black female character also so you can kind of go
Wait, why is she on the edge of this scene?
They give her nothing to do
That's not true
At the end Lando thinks maybe she's his daughter because he fucks a lot
I didn't take it like that
I thought Lando was trying to crush them ass at the end of that movie
I thought it was open -ended and I liked it
There was a little mystery at the end of the movie
She's a quarter of his age
It's Billy Dee, baby
He's got some Colt 45s in the back, he's ready to roll
The jokes, it was like this thing was punched up by Mike Huckabee
Fozzie Bear would have rejected these jokes
Who is going to Star Wars for the jokes?
C -3PO goes, great job, Po
Then there's an explosion and he goes, I mean, bad job, Po
That's a joke in the movie
I wrote it down as I watched it
I wrote it down
C -3PO goes, you're not going to put that thing in my head
Smash cut to the thing being put in his head
These are perfect strangers jokes
That's a joke, the other one you just said was not
It is because I took it down while watching it
It didn't work
Obviously we're going to agree to disagree on our take on the movie
But I think the takeaway here is
It's just not a movie for you
You're not like a crazy star
And look, there are crazy Star Wars fans that hated it
But I just, people said, oh, it's all fan service
Yeah, it was, because we've been watching this for 40 years
And J .J. Abrams gave us the thing we all wanted to see at the end
Now, would we all have liked to have seen a live Luke
And a live Han, a live lady? Of course
But that's unfortunately not how it played out
So I thought he did an amazing job with the cards he was dealt
Luke looks like he plays bass for the Marshall Tucker band now
Like whenever he comes up
But the first time I saw it
I did like aspects of it, I saw it in 3D which helps sometimes
The second time the faults really rose to the surface
For me, we're split on it folks
One hog up, one hog down
Not even a sideways hog from you
No. Also, RC3PO and R2D2 LGBTQ
I don't know
I don't know, and you know why I don't know
Because it's not my business
I just wanted to list a lot of letters in a row
I thought that was kind of cute
That'd be funny if they just had a droid
This is our new droid LGBTQ
Guys, Jesus
Mask the message a little bit
Folks, we are going to say
We're wrapping this up
And then we're just going to start the next one
The next one will be a little shorter, it will contain an interview
And the film will be
A holiday based film
So speak amongst yourself what you think it might be
That's it, we'll see you next time
And we'll see you in hell