I'm here for BetRivers' online casino and sportsbook with poker icon Phil Helmuth.
And now, thanks to the excitement of BetRivers, I'm also a slots icon.
That's great!
And the same game, Parley icon.
Cool, cool.
A blackjack icon, a moneyline icon.
A roulette icon.
Take it from Phil Helmuth.
If you love games, BetRivers is the place to play in Bet.
BetRivers.
Games on.
Must be 21 plus and President of West Virginia.
Void were prohibited.
Terms and conditions apply.
Gambling problem called 1 -800 -GAMBLING.
The football season is full of guarantees.
And here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the Fanatics Game Day guarantee,
every single game day from now until October,
if your football bet loses,
you'll earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with Fanatics,
you're either winning or winning money back in fan cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to Fanatics Sportsbook.
Winning hits different here.
Must be 21 plus gambling problem called 1 -800 -GAMBLER.
Offer not available in all states.
It's Terms Apply.
See Fanatic's fourth book app.
Hello everybody.
everybody welcome to another edition of we'll see you in hell the podcast about horror movie
commentaries not about them where we do them and then you can watch the movie along with
it if you want how shitty would that be a podcast about commentaries we review commentaries
on horror movies I'm Joe DeRosa I'm Patrick Walsh and we're pleased to be here doing
this podcast now part of the Fangoria podcast network for more information about the
network, including other programs, how to follow this show, other shows, find episodes of this
show or of other shows or past episodes or whatever the hell it is. Visit Fangoria .com.
Let's get down to it. Today's movie is Hellraiser. Just a technical note, I am on one side of
your head right now. Pat is on the other. We do that so we're in separate years. So
in case you do want to watch the movie along with this commentary, the movie sort of goes
up the middle with us on either side of you. Stereo sound, I'm on your right.
Joe's on your left, we are aware the past couple of weeks I have been mixed too low, that'll
be corrected this week.
They're already saying it's corrected.
Terrific.
It's already corrected.
Also, we are now available on iTunes, which was a question a lot of people had.
You can download it, subscribe, review the show, give it a nice review, it would be
great.
We're starting out.
Be very helpful.
If you have questions or movie suggestions or recommendations or things you'd like us
to discuss on the show.
You can tweet me at the Patrick Walsh or Joe
at Joe DeRosa Comedy.
That's right.
Now, in this little preliminary bullshit talky period
before we start the movie Hellraiser, which
is what we're watching today, now's
the time for you to get on your device,
get on your Netflix thing, and find Hellraiser
as we talk here, and hit play, and then pause it
as soon as the picture comes up,
so we can start it all together in a few minutes here.
Pat, can I tell you what I did this week?
Please do.
Masterbated into a cup.
Okay, explain.
Went to the urologist, had a prostate issue,
nothing serious, relax, Pat.
Okay. I know how you worry about me.
What, I didn't really care at all.
What was it?
What was the issue?
I mean, we don't have to get into all the details.
I take a step forward you take a step away that's the dance prostatitis which is a very
mild prostate issue but my doctor was like look it's probably prostatitis we're just
going to make sure you got to go do a urine analysis in a semen culture okay not crazy
about them calling it a semen culture by the way that we're living in a semen culture
that's what I'm saying I hear you so I'm like okay I got to go to one of these places
and you know you go into the room and you masturbate sure I even asked a friend I go
what do they do? Can you bring somebody? You can bring people in if you need to. Anything
to get that nut into the cup. This is a woman with speaking kind of with
the language of the street. Yeah, well she's from the street. As am I.
But anyway, I go to this place, this clinic. It's a suite inside a building filled with
different suites. All kinds of offices and different businesses in this place. I go
into the, I go into the clinic, the lady puts two cups on the counter, she goes the bathrooms
down the hall to the left, meaning the public bathroom. She wants me to go whack off in the
men's, the common men's room. No, I thought that was a crime. First of all, that's what
Pee Wee Herman went to jail for. Yeah, it's no different being in a men's room. I guess
if you were to blame it on the clinic, they, you would be in the clear, but that's not
cool. That's not legal. Let me ask you this. Even in a stall it's not legal. Let me ask you this.
Who's able to whack off in a men's room? No visual stimulant. No lube. If I try to whack off
in my own bedroom with no lube or no stimulant. 90 solid minutes easily. And your bedroom doesn't
wreak of uh business man shit. Business man shit. Floor cleaner. Right. You know what I mean?
Yeah, I do there's not a hand dryer blowing just on repeat. It just doesn't stop somebody hacking a loogie into the sink
Yeah, it was insane. So I brought it home. I brought the cup home and I
Wacked off into it at home, but I had to use lube. So now I'm worried. I'm gonna
My urologist is gonna call me in and be like we got to talk
Yeah, I found that there's aloe in your jizz. Well, you definitely I don't think should have done that
Well, I didn't know what to do. How do you do it?
Can you work off without the lubricant? I've never used it to be honest. I can't do it
I don't love the direction this podcast is heading, but I don't use it. Why never have no no
Why don't you love the direction the podcast is headed? It's just like hey guys and then we're talking about whacking off into a cup
Yeah, well, it's what I did this week. No, I'm sorry. Is this too low brow for you?
Maybe maybe it is. Is this too low brow for you? Maybe it is. I was gonna talk about
You know the work of merchandise every productions room with a view howards and okay
No, no cup jizzing in those films the piano. I
Once stayed up to watch they made the piano
Yeah, like I don't think they did but I love the piano
They didn't but Harvey Keitel's penis is in that you call that art. No, definitely. No, right. Thank you
What was the move? I guess it was a room with a view and I used to
Stay at my friend's house, and I would stay up even after he went to bed to watch the nudity on cable
It was my only way to see nudity and it said a room with a view starting next
Nudity PG -13 for nudity, and I was like oh god I watched two and a half hours of this thing
And then I see Daniel Day -Lewis
Running naked down a hill into into like a river wait a second a room with a view is that's a
Hitchcock film
No
What?
A Room of the View is a Daniel Day Lewis British version of Ivory production.
I'm thinking of A View to the Kill.
A View to a Kill.
A View to a Kill is a James Bond movie.
Rear view window.
Mirror.
Rear window.
Rear window is what I was thinking of.
Jesus Christ.
Yeah.
Anyway, the point is I'm up at like five in the morning.
Can barely open my eyes waiting for this nudity.
And then I see Daniel Day Lewis's bare ass flopping around in a swamp.
How long are we going to take you to finish to DD?
It was like 10 minutes because I don't use lube as we discussed.
Alright let's start HellRizer.
Alright you should be all paused up by now and all set to go.
I'm going to count to three and then say play and we all hit play when I say play.
play. One, two, three, play. Now we're rolling. Here are your opening graphics. Do you have
any stories about masturbating into cups? Sadly I do. When I first moved to LA I had
no money and I decided I was going to donate semen. I got a trash can here full of liquid
gold because you wanted to create a life with your semen. Yeah, exactly. So this this
jerk off is going to go jerk off to create another jerk off.
Yeah, exactly.
So I drive out.
I think it's funny.
It's really a strong joke.
I said it to Pat before we started recording it he didn't like it and I think it's a funny
joke.
I thought you were kind of trying it out to see if it was worthy.
I gave you a firm no and here it comes.
So I drove out to Westwood and I go to this kind of shady looking clinic and they
did have rooms almost like peep show booths that you'd go in and play a DVD to jerk off
and like made made very sure you didn't touch anything in there and I go in it's a very
attractive Asian nurse and she hands me a cup and a DVD face down and I'm thinking well
it's probably going to be like playboy wet and wild yeah Jenny McCarthy right and maybe
an Olivia Newton John right or you like they'd give you a sports illustrated swimsuit edition
or something and I get back in the room and the DVD is called jam it all the way up my
ass part two, okay, which I was shocked by that in a doctor's office this was the material
they give you and what if I'm not into that by the way.
It's anybody's into that in that situation that is a high pressure masturbation situation
they're giving you filth.
Yeah.
They're trying to get you right to it.
It was really rough stuff and I'm in there and I'm thinking I don't want to take too
long and have her think I'm perving around. Well that's why she gave you a jamming all
the way to my ass part too. They don't want you slowly making love to a fucking Anna Nicole
Smith video in there with a with a soft focus. Right. I'm also thinking I don't want to come
out too early and have her be like oh this guy in case her and I make love later I guess
is what I'm thinking. She thinks I come to. Can I tell you the worst case scenario.
Yeah. You're in there forever with the jamming
up the ass video and this she's out there thinking this guy can't this guy's real
Demented. You just can't shoot. You must need something far dark. But I came out I handed
to her and as I'm leaving she was Mr. Walsh. We need the DVD back and I had been so nervous
that I was just carrying it with me. I was ashamed. I brought it back to her. Can I
can I make a joke here. Yeah. Were you carrying it or was it stuck.
That's good to your hand. No I washed my hand. That's a jizz joke.
I got now we're into the movie. It started our in Marrakesh or something. Yeah. The Indiana
Jones is sitting behind these people at a table somewhere. Terrible dubbing. I watched
this last night and especially on that scene. It's like I think the guy was speaking his
native tongue and they dubbed in like maybe they didn't want to do subtitles or something
throughout this movie. There's many instances where the dubbing is way off. Yeah it's
a low budget film. You know they did what they could. But we've got I would say our
main antagonist Frank. Many people think the antagonist of this film is Pinhead. No it's
not Pinhead it's Frank and he is toying with the box. This is actually exciting for me
to watch. This is the first time in movie history that you ever saw the box happening
on film. They went on made nine sequels to this movie. I believe it was. And this is
the first time you're actually seeing the box. They all involved the box. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. The what? How would they never make a Hellraiser porno about the box? Well, now I
always thought easy. Maybe they did. We don't know. We call it a ball. Hell dick razor. Something
like that. I don't know. Bulldrainer. Yeah, ball. Yeah. I always thought that Pinhead's
name was Hellraiser when I would see this at the video store and saying tell everybody
But how recently you thought that, too?
About a year ago.
I thought his name was like Jackie Hellraiser.
That's embarrassing.
The only thing that worse that would be if you thought
the monster in Frankenstein was still named Frankenstein.
No, I've learned that.
Now, Frank just got hooks in the skin.
He opened the box.
Hooks came out, evidently, hurt him,
as we're going to see in a moment here,
that he's been ripped to shreds.
Yeah.
And this poses my one question about the Hellraiser
franchising the workings of the box. These guys obtain the box to explore the heights
or depths if you will of pleasure and pain. I've never seen one person get pleasure in
any one hellraiser movie from the box. No. Every time they open it immediate hooks
in the face and they die. Is it is what we're supposed to believe
that they've chased the erotic eyes for so long. The only thing that can get them
off is true pain I don't think it's that I think it's that they're they've they've sunk to such a
depraved immoralistic level yeah that they are willing to to play with this box and then the
twist of fate is you die immediately okay you know like there there is no winning like right
it's a trap I know this part where there's a skin all over the floor and it's really gross
They're kind of fingering through it as if it's crawfish.
Yeah.
Like they're fishermen that just brought in a load.
Oh, so that's him.
I didn't even put that together.
God, I'm dumb.
So for those of you not watching,
Pinhead just put a face back together on the floor.
That's clearly a clitoris type thing he's doing there,
right?
When he reposed to believe that's a fingering move.
It's how you open the box.
It's super sexual.
All right, but let's just glaze over the dumb thing
you just did.
OK.
That we just watched me and get ripped apart by looks and then pin it comes in and puts a face back together on a floor
Riddled litter didn't ripped up flesh Pat didn't know that that was the same guy
Well, I guess it's because you only see the hooks going into his hands and then he's just kind of vanishes
I didn't really connect Jesus. Oh, oh literal wall. Should we call him? I am too logical with things
This yeah, you have a poster on your wall of Hellraiser. So you must love it. I love this movie
I love this movie. I love the second one and I am a big fan of the
fourth one, outside of that, I'm not too crazy about the other entries into the franchise.
But that poster up there that I have on my wall is the original poster, it's not the original
meaning it's an original, but that's the original poster before Pinhead became the sort of mascot
of the franchise.
Right.
As you can see there's a frightening clown on it.
And there's not a clown in this movie.
No, there's no clown in the movie.
and it's signed by Doug Bradley who portrayed portrayed Pinhead in all the movies except
one of them. And I heard that the casting search for a guy with all those pins in his
head just went on and on and on because it's hard to find. I mean in this coming from
the guy that knocked my jerk off making a jerk off routine. This now when I got that poster
Mr. signed this the cast some some of the cast was there Doug Bradley was there but this
lady was there that plays Julia the stepmother the wicked stepmother and it was weird meeting
her because she's so mean and evil in this movie and she was terrible charmingly lovely
in real life she got out of being the fans these like this couple is not in the other
ones now I assume is another is one of the future ones like set in Penn heads world Hellraiser
two delves into it and we should do Hellraiser two at some point because Hellraiser two is
the best entry in the whole really franchise Hellraiser two is awesome okay Hellraiser
one is one is great but Hellraiser two is really I really wanted to be out of Penn
heads world when I was in there I didn't like watching it I was watching it before bed
I didn't like it disturbed me. I had nightmares. He to me is one of the I mean to most people
I would think is you know he's definitely one of the great horror icons of all time but
he to me is the coolest of all the famous movie monsters and I'm a huge Kruger fan Jason's
awesome Chuckie why not you know I like them all the alien you know everything's great
but to me Pennette is the coolest because he's so elegant there's something he's
Very Darth Vader ask yeah well his sidekicks are the freakier ones in my opinion yeah that
one that I despise looking at you know what his name is no joke Pudgekins butter ball
butter ball yeah okay that maggots real man really gross I never have a maggot experience
oh yeah you want to hear about it I guess I had one myself I mean it's not that much
of a story I flipped over a piece of meat and there was a ton of maggots on it and I screamed
for 25 minutes at a horrible apartment. Where was the meat? I came up from the grocery store
like set it on the counter went about my business not for a long period of time and I came picked
it up and had like maggots all over. Well that was bad when you bought it. Yeah. Oh absolutely.
Well I used to go to the Vons at Melrose and Vine my apartment which at night they
enclose in giant black bars like a prison. Oh good. So they always had the most high
quality meats. Welcome to Hollywood kid. Yeah. Close the bars
that go jerk off in that cup of money. It was a real nightmare.
I had an experience in college. I lived with two guys. There you
go. There's your problem. And one of them was not ever doing
any dishes or anything. So my roommate Mark said I refuse to
clean anything until our other roommate Jim starts doing
dishes he just refused and it got so bad that finally Mark said I'm just going to do the
dishes clean the dishes got to the bottom of the sink screamed and ran across the kitchen
and I said what he goes look in there man and I looked in and there was a half eaten burrito
with maggots in it it was disgusting that's disgusting yeah I started gagging immediately
then we yelled who throws a half in burrito in the sink Jim did we yelled at him about
this is Christ we yelled at him now this is Kirstie coming in she is our
protagonist Pat you know the difference between an antagonist and a protagonist
right yeah gel I've sold two screenplays to major movie studios look at look at
the big shot now if what is this he's fully dressed having sex with her there
I didn't quite understand this yeah we're looking at she's looking at pictures
of Frank she's clearly got a lust she had an affair with him this man yeah
I don't ruin it for the people that I haven't seen yet.
I thought that it already been now.
Well, nobody's watching this for the first time, you know, maybe they are, but they can't
hear the dialogue.
So why would they be watching?
Maybe they turn the dialogue up loud.
All right.
Maybe they're doing it.
Let people do it the way they want to do it.
Pat, it's not your decision how they will enjoy this.
Let them enjoy it their own way.
They can, but I can also say that she had an affair.
She was just yeah, Julia the stepmother was just looking at pictures of Frank and he was weird because it was sex pictures
But he was clothed. That's why I say it's a sexual film, but I wouldn't call it gratuitous. There is some butt and a near dick
Clive Barker just released a book called the Scarlet Gospels, which was
What he said to be his final installment of the Hellraiser
mythology. Okay. And there was a really gross part in it where a demon made a guy spit into
his hand so he could jerk off. I didn't care for it. I didn't care for it. I didn't really
like the book. It was too it was too it was too like it was too raw or something. I can't
I can't put my finger on it. Now here's an interesting piece of movie trivia. That
this mattress up the stairs. Yeah. Swar the Italian looking guy. Swar these
are words we don't really use in this house. I'm kidding. That pin. But Doug Bradley was
offered that part. He said he said they said you can either play this demon and it's a cooler
part. The problem is is nobody will see your face. Right. Or you'll be in full view.
But it's just a move. Wow. What a strong decision. Yeah he goes well I guess I'll just play
the demon that seems more interesting. Yeah of course. Made his goddamn career.
here. Well has you ever done anything else. Yeah he's in other stuff. OK. But once I
was in a bar drinking and I looked over and he was standing next to me. And I said how
are you sir to is the greatest horror movie of all time. And he said no it's not no it's
not me. And I said yes it is. He goes no. Bride of Frankenstein is. And you can ask
Robert England he'll agree with me. OK. I took a sugar my beer and shouted in his
space. Take the compliment Bradley and he laughed heartily and took a swing of his beer. All right.
It was a good time. This post you have as a quote from Stephen King I have seen the future of
horror fiction and his name is Clive Barker. I read Ebert's review of this. Ebert hated this
movie and he said I guess Stephen King was thinking of a different Clive Barker. So why did
And Ebert hate the movie Hellraiser.
He said he can't believe all these people worked on something so empty and soulless
and terrible.
Like he really hated it.
Really?
Yeah.
And it's weird too because he likes really cool, like original visuals.
He loved Dark City a lot more than I did, for example, but I don't know, he couldn't
see the craftsmanship that went into this.
I think they did a really great job with this movie.
My favorite movie review of all time is his review of Kingdom of the Crystal Skull.
Yeah, you said that before. I'm one of the podcast. I said it on this one. Yeah. Well, then all right. Sorry. I'm just I'm just helping you out. Jesus.
I didn't know it was with a stenographer. Get off the weed, Joe. Or the grass, as Woody Allen would say.
Interrational man. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, yeah. Yeah, we both talked about that before, right? Yeah, we both saw a rational man this week.
There's Woody Allen's new movie. And there's a scene where, because it's a good movie. It's one of his dramas.
was I really satirical. I liked it a lot but he's writing for Emma Stone and Parker Posey
and Joaquin Phoenix and he's 80 years old. So at one point Parker Posey is like you should
come up to my room. I've got some terrific grass and the whole theater just like burst
into laughter and I can't believe that and when he Allen has said in countless interviews
he goes I'm not married to the words. Yeah. I just say get the gist of it. I don't care.
I can't believe Parker posed it and go can I say we she was probably scared to be like
hey old timer you know and then another point Emma Stone goes let me get one of those jazz
cigarettes. Oh God. I made that up. Oh yeah. Well remember
the part where Joaquin Phoenix said skittily be bought. Yeah. And I was he says is here
to stay swung a pocket watch around. Yeah. Yeah. This is he was doing that thing where
you wag your finger off to the side. Yeah. Yeah. This is now Frank is coming into the
house here. We're seeing flashbacks. This is where the affair for those of you that don't
remember when Pat forgot to say spoiler alert. It's not a spoiler. If it's going to happen
in 30 seconds. We're showing the movie came out in 1987. We're showing the flashback
here where they meet and you can see in Julia's eyes. She wants to bang brother Frank.
Right. It's her. It's her husband's brother. Do you. Now do you. I don't go for this
spoiler thing at all. I think if it's last night's episode of Mad Men and it's Monday morning,
you can't walk into the office and be like, oh my God, can you believe Don Draper kicked
that guy in the throat or whatever? But if a movie came out in 1987, we're past spoilers.
You can't be upset about it.
I mean, Pat, look, these are your rules. I'm asking you, what do you think? It sounds
like you're telling me what to think. No, this started by me saying, what do you think?
I'm telling you what I think which if we're not allowed to say what we think this podcast
is going to really be born. No I think that I think at any time if somebody
says you know don't spoil it for me you got to respect that you got to respect it but
come on I agree that if I'm good look if I you know if I if you know if I've never
seen the Empire Strikes Back okay and then I'm reading a magazine article today about
the Empire Strikes Back. I'm going to expect that it's going to blow the lid off of some
of the stuff for me. Sure. That I get. But I hate in conversations
because people do this all the time. Conversations. They'll go, you know, top gun or whatever
you go. I never saw it. Don't tell me the end. Yeah, they'll go. You've had 30 years.
Get over it. No, that you can't do absolutely. But you should feel comfortable discussing
top gun at lunch well of course but if somebody says something then you know you know we give
them a minute to cover their ears and hum you know so they don't hear it goose dies but
this is the part of the movie goose dies I know goose dies I've never seen the film but
I know goose dies Prince I like this move here now they're about to they're about to consummate
their affair Uncle Frank and Julia and his his first decision is to take out a switch
blade and cut her nightie off of her it's a bold first move I mean but you know if
she stays with you yeah you're in you got to keep her but it's a gamble she's if
she doesn't like the switchblade play you might be in some trouble well she
went for it man so I look at this he's banging her on her wedding dress by the
way what's strange to me is he's like he's the kind of guy who's gonna cut
your dress off with a switchblade but then he's allowing her to just calmly
lay down. It seems like he'd be more of a thrower. Yeah, he's gently kissing her breast.
Yeah. Pick a side. Oh, this is real gross when he catches
hand on this thing. Spoiler alert. Yeah. Well, I like the I like the cross cutting
between his wife getting fucked in the flashback and then trying to move the mattress and that
the grunting of the moving. That's very strange. The grunting of the sex.
And there's the knife. Yeah. And he cuts his hand with the ejaculation, I believe.
Yeah, this would be the scene where my mom would walk in if I was watching it as a kid
And I go
This is a strange thing to admit I saw this movie
Oh
God, I saw this movie when it came out in your dick as promised with my
Old tiny bit of dick shot there just a faint dick shot
So this movie when I was I think 12 with my parents see you have a very different relationship with your parents
an idea. My dad wanted to see it for some reason. He was like, I want to move with the guy with
all the nails in his head. That looks cool. All right. And we watched it. I remember this
part made me feel uncomfortable though. I couldn't see our moves low 17 and even in
a PG 13 if there was a couple and they started making out if it felt at all like there could
be any sex in the future. I went in and got a drink for maybe five minutes. I would
like carefully place cubes in the cup.
I can't do it still.
That's how repressed my family was.
I'm is.
I can't do it.
I was watching a movie with my mom and dad over Christmas
and I said, Mom, I'm just going to tell you now,
never admitted this to you, feel very uncomfortable
when anything nude or whatever happens
and you're in the room.
So I'm just going to, when you see me look away.
Yeah.
It's because I feel weird.
It felt, it was such a release
to just finally admit that.
And the movie you were watching?
Damn it all the way up my ass part.
part. It was bad Santa. Oh sure. See that's that's too blue for a family view. No it was
great. We had a great time watching it. I just had to look away during the fuck me Santa
parts. Sure. Show you what Gilmore girls that lady. Now I'm not criticizing the film when
I asked this question. What is the rule that the blood now the guy moves the couch he
cuts his hand or the mattress he cuts his hand. He goes up into the room where Frank
was killed his blood is dripping on the floor and now his blood is going to reanimate Frank yeah
what is the rule of that they don't explain it and to me i thought that was kind of cool
like when they when the guy just kind of shows up and you realize he's formed from blood i was
like i get it i didn't need anymore oh you know well excuse me like what are they gonna do like
have a piece of parchment float up and then like stick to the camera so you can read about the
legend or something. There's no one here to explain it to us.
It's out. But why but but then he gets he gets to escape hell
through somebody else's. I guess it's that it's that it's the
bartering of souls. If someone else gives their blood on
purpose or by accident you get to return from hell like but
that's what's weird too. I know I will think about it. It
has to be in your in the home that you you know like what
made his blood bring this guy back because their family because his heart was under the
floorboards you just saw it how did that happen why was his heart under the floorboards I don't
know but you know in horror movies I'm always just kind of like what are we doing now you
know I don't care Clive Barker has a very different approach than Stephen King which
is there are questions there are more question marks with Clive Barker yeah and I like both
for different reasons right stock footage of nature it looks like no that's not
that's reverse that's reverse claymation just really bad this was a really awesome
effect I thought this is great when his body's coming out of the floor and I
like this is really cool when his head forms it didn't form yet if this
reminds me of the fly yeah the gold bloom one or the thing and the dog the
horrifying dog that possessed by the thing it's one of the grossest things
It's horrible. It's horrible. Nothing to me is grosser than the fly and it's one of my favorite movies ever
We should do that one next time. Yeah, love it. It's no your Cronenberg
Tremendous piece work. I like when his head comes on here and forms and it cries like a baby
Because he's being reborn. Yes, and I'm trying not to talk over it
So we can hear it right now, but here the oozing. No, I want to hear when he cries like the little baby
Look at this, these are great effects.
Look at this, the slime and the fingers growing out.
That's, this is half their budget.
This had to be half the budget.
Yeah.
Right?
Yeah, it's really great.
Blood coming up off the, look at this.
See?
Yeah.
It's pretty cool, he cries like a baby.
I like it.
Did anyone get, when I said know you Cronenberg,
that there was a reference, a lyric
from British hip hop artist, The Streets?
I would imagine zero of you not a fan. I actually love the streets
I guess he's done because he hasn't released an album in ten years
But I love them don't care for techno beats the rhymes off -time with
Well, you're a very traditional hip -hopist and I embrace all kinds
Hey, can you blame me? No, I blame all kinds. I think read into this dinner party. See all kinds
Here's the hard part for me to understand is
You got the deer there at a dinner party now look at these people they hang out with they're
like the dorkiest fucking Mayberry couple on yeah that guy looks like you know he's married
to a woman who fucks with a switchblade yeah I mean it's like it's odd well but that's
probably what happens out there you know I got a friend back home in Missouri I won't
name any names who told me that two different married couples in their cul -de -sac were having
two separate affairs with each other and not not not a planned wife swapping thing the wife
of one and the husband of another started hooking up the other two found out about it privately
discussed it and then said hey if they're gonna do it we're gonna do it and started having
sex as well so they both just carry on affairs that they kind of may know about but it's
not officially wife swapping it's not an open marriage it's very dark very dark sounds
like a good deal I guess marriage man hey tough shit hey you know what they say
Patty you can't live with them you can't live without them you know why is what
women oh well wives marriage you know it's about as big a cliche as you can
get but it is true it is true I've never lived and I'm sure women feel the
same about that let's be honest we're terrible yeah well what can I say I'm
never banged a man so I don't know what annoying things we do we well I could I
could tell you what you do that's annoying I don't have to bang it see why
you have to do that anyone listen to this podcast can probably name 10 already
that's that's I don't even know why you do that sort of thing how do you hurt
why do you feel the need to hurt hurt people hurt you know it's true jerk off
make jerk offs yeah there you go all true that's a great bumper sticker jerk
Jerk offs make jerk offs make it make a million dollars million
Julia now is about to find Frank right in the room and this part is really creepy the way he like scurries up to her. Yeah. Oh
Yeah, he's just like a pile at this point
He's it's it's tremendous makeup and it always
Made me sad that he's the guy that plays Frank isn't the guy in the makeup
It's a different guy with a double really. Yeah, well, that's pretty clear. I mean, they don't look anything like I
Know but I don't know
What is that rats eating puke it looks like yeah, I mean what what?
Here she here he is Frank just grabbed her
This is very creepy. Look at that. Oh, look at that. Look at that. Oh, it's so creepy
It's not unlike the
Sloth guy in seven. Oh
Which is a terrifying movie. Oh god, this is just rough stuff
Don't look at me. I just grabbed you and chased you across the room, but don't look at me.
You're a skeleton with a little bit of flesh on your face who just grabbed me. What do
you want me to read the newspaper? Yeah, why don't you just stay in the corner in the
shadow and just say, just go. Excuse me. And then he says it's me, Frank. And she believes
them. Oh, she just believes him. Sup Frank. Jesus. Jesus. What? We used to get it on.
What? How quickly she accepts this? It's me. It's me, Frank. Maybe she thinks he just
got burned or something, you know. There's no way. No, they don't look much alike.
She already believes him. How long did that take? Yeah, let's roleplay this. Pat, it's
me Joe pretend I look like I didn't answer because I'm I'm in my car driving home. Oh
you think I'm hanging out with you. Me Joe. We're going to go get a hot dog. No seriously
it's me. That's literally what he just did. Yeah. Me. No no no no. And then he goes by
the blood on the floor brought me back. She's like I buy that. Yeah. All right. Well I gotta
get back to the dinner party yeah what else is on your mind Frank very very cool looking
makeup here I mean this is this is a horror movie done right you got a you got a creepy
zombie guy coming back to life slowly regenerating slowly up in the attic that's fucking creepy
enough most horror movies that would end there but then you got the Senate by it's coming
Yeah, they're coming man. Yeah, I can't I can't imagine that HellRazor 2 would be better than us because
HellRazor 2 is awesome. They go into hell. I don't want to go into hell. It's awesome
I had to live my whole life trying to avoid hell HellRazor 2 has
Arguably the greatest horror movie quotes of all time. All right, I'll watch it tonight
No, I'm not tonight. It'll be 1 30 in the morning. Want to hear a great quote from HellRazor 2? Yeah
Yeah. Pinhead goes, but fool us again, child, and your suffering will be legendary, even
in hell. Oh, wow. It's a great quote. Sounds like some tough suffering, Joe. Tough suffering.
That was the name of my post -hardcore band in college. We are tough suffering. One,
two, three, Phil. Yeah. This song is called Me to Do That Fake British Accent, like Billy
Joe Armstrong you a Green Day fan I was you know yeah like everybody I was in the early
days not even the earliest I stuck with them through all the way up through Nimrod oh well
that's still the early days Nimrod's a really great album and I liked a warning and I like
parts of American Idiot to be honest with me now church on Sunday is great late Green
based on. I don't know it. Now you got this guy too. I forgot about this third monster
guy in the movie. This bearded man that's sort of early in it. But it's still it's a third
monster to fill in the gaps between the other monsters. I like it. This guy looks like like
if you told me that this was Clive Owen 20 years ago I completely believe you. Who
her boyfriend. Yeah. Kirsty's boy because he looks like Clive Owen like before he became
I'm cool. I'm not getting a Clive Owen. I'm getting a young Matthew
Modine vibe for Jim. What are you talking about? I'm getting
a this man looks exactly like Clive Owen. Nothing like Matthew
Modine. I'm saying the wrong guy. Okay. Who's the guy from
beautiful girls? Matt Dylan. No, the main guy. Matt Dylan
isn't beautiful. He is. I'm not saying he's not. Timothy
Hutton. Timothy Hutton. I'm getting a young Timothy Hutton
vibe from this guy you know especially when I was an NBC page like when I was 23 I used
to get on a daily basis you look like a young Timothy Hutton look at this now Julia no thoughts
on that lying wide awake in bed taken so much by the fact that this guy fucked her so good
switchblade style before he died that she actually wants to go up and visit his goddamn
slimy body in the adequate. Yeah, it's insane. It's nuts. No sex is this
good. It's nuts. Look, she goes up to Sam. Yeah. Now, oh yeah. See, really, this is
kind of a similar plot to Little Shop of Horrors, where there's this creepy thing
in the basement that needs blood to get bigger and better. You know what? I never
put that together before until right now and you're absolutely right. I would
elective scene Rick Moranis in the stepmother role here. Sure.
Sure. Rick Moranis being laid down on the bed in a silk night
gown. Oh, you can have sex with me. All right. I guess that's
cool. Are you a fan of Little Shop of ours? It's one of my
favorite movies, especially when I was a kid. I would watch it
constantly. I love the music. I love Steve Martin and I think
he's hilarious. I love John Candy in it. Everybody who's
on candy playing in it. He's just the the host of that weird
radio show. Ellen Green. Everybody in the movie is awesome.
The music suddenly Seymour. What more do you want? Have you ever
seen the original with Jack Nicholson? I have. It's not a
great movie. Nicholson's great. It's not Nicholson's great in
it, but Bill Murray in that Nicholson role was tremendous.
It was incredible. And I think also completely improvised
from what I heard. Really? Yeah. Now on Broadway, Gyllen
Hall is playing Seymour. I'll buy it. I would see it if I
it there but it was in the Bill Murray role that I don't know who's playing the
dentist probably Lance Bass or something I don't know they just did a scary
nightmare sequence that was freaky so he's got a lot of good thing to keep the
freakiness rolling pretty steadily throughout for a movie where if you
didn't know any better you'd think that it was going to be all about pinhead
Yeah being like a sort of Freddy guy pinheads
Not really in this a lot. It's probably total seven minutes. I would guess
They do a good job keeping that
Freaky factor going. Yeah going strong, which I like quite a bit pinhead scared me his associates scared me much more
Like pinhead. I had seen him so many times. I was kind of like
Only bothered by the others that I thought were really really gross
Well, the the chatterer is this freakiest one. Yeah, I didn't and then in this there's that big thing that runs
Tortor in that hallway. That was really freaky as well. Yeah, we had another monster. Yeah, he's lousy with monster
These are things that are in just in Hill
Hanging out are their souls or excited? I didn't get an explanation. Well, that's what upset me about
This book the scarlet Gospels that just came out
you know before came out they were saying that they were going to really explain the the
cinnabites are part of the order of the gash yet another sexual sounding yeah but uh they
said they were going to kind of ex or clive barker said he was going to kind of explain
like what that was and and how they you know what the history of the cinnabites okay
and it didn't at all oh it's just a story about pinhead trying to take over hell
And he's kind of an asshole in it and it's not that fun, right? I'm I kind of quit on it halfway through
Feel bad saying that but I just wasn't feeling it man Clive. I'm sorry, baby
I'm sticking with you, but I just wasn't feeling it. How many so are none of the movies are added or none of the
Yeah, none of the movies are adaptations of the books
Are there this is an adaptation of the hellbound heart which I have if you want to read it
You can borrow it after sure is it faithful unlike this woman pretty faithful. Yes
Yeah, Julie is now at a bar trying to find men to go bring home to get their blood so she can rejuvenate Frank
Right because she needs that dick now. I was thinking because I watched this and actually laughed to myself
Now I put myself in her husband's position. Okay, so you're a man. You think you're happily married
You got it. You got a wonderful life. You're moving into a new home with your lovely wife and you find out
That she's cheated on you with your brother a that's like
step want like the most bare bones thing that she's done sure they had hot
switchblade style sex together then he dies she's so obsessed with him that she
continues to go upstairs and like basically carry on an emotional affair
with his charred remains right then she loves him so much that she starts
bringing home other strange men from bars she makes out with them whatever it
takes to get him upstairs then she kills them and feeds them to the corpse in the hopes of
bringing him back so he can fuck her some more right imagine finding those things out as the
husband this is a dedicated woman this is a dedicated woman well how on unsatisfying
must their love life be I mean that's the thing is this guy a chump or is she just
that rotten you know who knows the movie the way the movie plays it is that she's
just pure evil. I don't get why she married the guy to begin with. I'm confused by it.
Also by the way, security, she's lured this guy home from a hopping bar. It's three o 'clock
in the afternoon. Did you see that bar? Yeah, it was swinging. Yeah. It was swinging. What
bar is hopping like at 3 p .m.? I don't know. Maybe it's a Saturday job. No, please. It's
not. This guy's a businessman. That just skipped work. That was the issue you thought
Strand credibility and Hellraiser. I'm not saying credibility. I'm just saying, you know, okay
This guy didn't go back to the office. I'm just gonna go bang this fucking broad at home. Well, she took him
She took me not who wouldn't go who among us?
Would you go would you go look at this? She goes we don't need a bed
He's standing in a room where there were rats eating vomit. He is scenes ago. He is drunk
There's no way that room doesn't smell horrible. Yeah, there's a slime man sitting in the corner
But maybe that's a little hidden theme is like guys will do anything percent. I think that's part of it like the depth
You'll sink to for your pleasure. Yeah, please
What is your pleasure, sir? Plus? I mean this guy must have thought hey, I look like Phil Collins
I'm probably he's probably getting late all the time. You know, he's got that weird bold
Anti -bold spot in the middle of his head. This guy looks like Phil Collins. This lady looks like she was on ad fab
I've never seen women in England look like in the 80s and 90s.
This was like this was like England hot back then you'd call them all handsome.
Yeah.
Handsome woman.
I'd have sex with this lady.
Look at those big star earrings she's got on.
Yeah.
Now.
Big tall hairdo too.
Real tall hairdo.
No.
Look at this guy.
Heidi Whitey.
Oh Christ.
Now they cut that so it looks like he's staring into this man's butthole.
Well, I mean kind of liking it's the room is lit up. It's three o 'clock in the afternoon
You got some how is he not seeing?
The rotting man in the corner. He's you know, he's drawn to the flesh. I
Mean it just doesn't it doesn't seem likely to me
He's saying he's got to go pee now
Too much to drink tend to the old bladder the guys. Oh this guy if he could just get out of the room
There you go hammer in the head. Oh
She beats him to death with a hammer
Christ see they go the terrible way to die this movie
I've noticed they go a little further into grossing you out like any other movie of the species
He hits them a couple times of a hammer. No, he is jaw bashed off. Give it to me. Just a give it to me, baby
Now she's got this guy's blood on her face. He could have any kind of blood -borne disease sure
don't look at me Frank says again I just killed a man for you and still I can't
look at you do me a favor bring me a corpse beat of death with a hammer but
don't look at me yeah hey a couple demands and then once you've done them
I'd also gonna continue demanding certain things from the way but she loves it
though whoever played the Frank in the suit crawling around the floor deserved
an Oscar as far as I'm concerned it is the most disturbing body movement I've
Sure, what's that thing on the wall?
Oh, I just wondering that hand dryer. It looks like the world's largest
private bathroom hand -dry
Yeah, what is that thing? I have no idea. She's looking good though. That looks good though. That blood splattered on that black lace
Something sexy about it. That's a good shot. It's gone girl that a similar shot. Uh -oh
People ripping off
Babe, although I have mentioned two Fincher movies. Maybe he's a Hellraiser
David venture babe. Oh, that's my dentist. Yeah, I got yasser Arafan talking over to David venture
Look at it
She sucked as quick now. She's mortified
She comes back in and sees that his corpse has been sucked dry the blood and now she's freaked out
She's going. Oh Jesus Christ and they don't really show how he sucks it out
I mean is it through the neck vampire in the second movie? They show it. Okay, they don't show it in this one
Oh Frank can stand now
Yeah, this was very cool how this all progressed it gets a little more flesh on him each time
Look at this. That's very good makeup. Yeah, and I love that. He's constantly dripping right constantly dripping
Now do you think he's in pain?
Yeah, probably all those exposed nerves and everything, you know what probably one best makeup this year was like the last Emperor
Like some movie where they like put like a couple wrinkles on a on a guy to age him over 30 years
You know because why would anyone in the Academy watch this?
He uh the the for those of you not watching Frank is
He looks like the you know the the biology book guy
Yeah, like no skin you see all the organs and he's demanding that Julia come to him
So he can touch her and she let him grab a tit
Yeah, she let him get a tip grab in even though his skull is showing because there's no skin on it and
Her husband just came home. How do you explain this one?
Suck dried corpse on the floor and a
And a biology yet now imagine he opens this door and she's like, um
So couple things
It's not what it looks like
So I can explain
first
It's interesting. She's carrying very strange. Carrying the the
suck. Leave it in the room. Where is that? I didn't get
either. She's taking the corpse into another room. Leave it in
the gross room that nobody goes in. Yeah. Oh, hey. Could not
be sunnier outside. All of this. Yeah, she like fakes diarrhea
here. Oh, does she? The husband by the way seems really
nice too. He's very understanding. He's in something
else I can't remember he's in another horror movie I feel like it's like return to Salem's lot or
something okay and then she says she's feeling sick that's for those of you at home if you're ever
caught in the midst of a murder a double in the bathroom say you're feeling sick yeah apparently
that just gets you right out of it and then he's like oh I'll get you a sprite babe like okay cool
like and and what does she do go out and kill more men for this demon upstairs so she can fuck
a skinless body yeah does she fucks him before he's like regular right um yeah
yeah I mean he's not all the way back you got to imagine what does that dong
look like I'm just exposed a big fucking bloody dog a big bloody old swinging
dong this guy must be hung like fucking man or man but why yeah you think you
could see it though. Oh boy. Look at you. I love. So she goes into the room to find
him to to reef engage with this fucking abomination. And he taps her on the shoulder. She screams
right way. When are you going to be done being startled Julia. You're in. You're you're
waist deep into this. I would always be startled by this shit dripping up. Yeah. How do they
make them keep dripping like that right before each take just dump some onto the
top of his head you know God that had to be a miserable makeup process maybe
that's why the guy didn't play the part I did commercials the first acting gig
I ever got was a commercial for sports net New York where I played their mascot
who was a guy that a TV for a head yeah and they actually hollowed out a real
TV and bolted it around my head. How was that? It was excruciating. Yeah, horrible. It was
really heavy. It was really hard to move around and it would burn incessantly after like an hour
and I'd have to have it on for three hours of a clip. It was horrible. But you know, as bad as that
was, I couldn't fucking hold a candle to this, you know. Well, it's horrible. We had to do a
shot where I had to walk down the street and I couldn't see anything and they were like
a guy had to walk in front of me and just had to follow his voice. What was this for? Sports
net New York. Okay. But I was shocked at how many people knew it was me. They were like
I heard that you was in the they knew my voice. Were you handsomely compensated. No
it was a buyout. It was fine. I mean at the time I felt like I made a fortune but
You know, right what are you gonna do now? We're in a pet store and here's the guy again. I love this part. He eats the crickets
He's standing over this the like lizard tank
That's oh, yeah, this is really gross. Yeah, but then what is this guy? That's never really addressed. Oh, yes, it is
It's absolutely addressed. Okay. I wasn't paying close enough attention. It's so gross. What are those crickets?
Yeah, are those crickets? They're not crickets. They're
And this guy's eating them.
Oh, it's so great.
I love it.
Does she work in this pet store?
Yeah, I believe so.
Or is she just being like a good social person kicking
the guy out?
I don't think she was shopping for a pet, that'd be an odd.
I think it's odd that she works in the pet store.
Yeah.
People have to work in pet stores.
You need jobs.
This is the guy.
This is the sort of, he's the sort of curator
of the box. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Who's I assume is Satan? Has
there ever been a movie with more hand on the shoulder
scares? They've done it now eight times. You're doing
plenty of hand on the shoulder scares tonight. Hey,
would you do earlier today? I worked all day. Some of us
work for a living. Why do you ask? Make a living doing
standup. I did a audition for the Tonight Show that was
so bad Valin yeah the crowd was so bad that halfway through my audition I said fuck it
I'm not I'm done oh wow I just started doing other jokes pull the Larry David oh they were
terrible terrible audience so you were doing you're supposed to do like a five minute audition
set yeah just like I don't need I mean they were not laughing at a goddamn thing yeah horrible
does that matter for the booker I guess it does my friend is the booker and the tape
will never, you know, he'll never show anybody. Right. Get him
in a different tape another time. I'm probably my friend where
the book or I wouldn't have taken that liberty. Yeah. But I've
known the guy for years. I'm sorry to hear that. Well, what are
you sorry about? I wish it had gone well for you. Pat. We
live, we learn. You live. We breathe, we die. We breathe.
We conquer, we seduce. You know what I mean? Yeah, I guess.
It's it's another day. That's true. Well, you're not usually that guy Joe usually very despairing. I'm not anymore
I've been so positively with you. You've been stone drunk every time. I've expressed it to you
So you don't see that I also I haven't had a drink in 12 days. Oh, well, I also haven't had food
I'm doing a cleanse get him a medal everybody. I'm just simply responding to your accusations. I know I'm kidding. Come on
But it is true though, every time I tell you I'm happy, it's when we're in a bar drunk.
Okay.
Well, you're usually, to be honest, saying you're unhappy.
Huh?
You're always saying that you're unhappy.
Never saying that.
When am I saying that?
Joe, we've had this conversation a lot lately.
No, no, no.
I told you I was mad at my friend and then you said you sound like you're unhappy.
Yeah.
That was your saying.
I didn't say that.
Yeah.
No, you do.
All right, fine.
All right.
Are you happy?
I'm not going to scroll through the text.
I'm happy.
Yeah.
All right.
I'm happy.
I mean, everybody goes in and out of it.
But what tech?
What are you talking about?
What tech?
Well, I think we should talk about your happiness after the show.
All right.
So you're always like, I'm having a rough time.
I got to cancel tonight.
I'm I'm in a bad place.
I'm not dreaming these things.
But you're you say the same things.
Not even a bad place that you occasionally, you know, you have I don't I can't like
not hang out because I'm in a bad place. I think I just admit to it more than you do.
That's probably true. I think I'm more in touch with my feelings.
You're a callous Irishman. Yeah I mean that's all true.
You shove it all deep down in your soul. Right. You'd be good at you should get your hands
on one of these boxes from the Hellraiser thing and go to hell. That's what you want
for me. I I could see you being a guy that's like
fuck it. I want to see what the pain and the pleasure of the same.
Yeah. No, that's not going to happen. I feel like if we were in the Hellraiser movies, I'd
be the nice husband. You'd be frank. Wow. You really view us differently than I do.
Somebody would be bleeding you back to life. Now I can only orgasm if a homeless man watches.
I don't know if that's weird but so it's usually like if I pick somebody up it's like then I
also have to pay a homeless person that's a shame and a lot of times the the lady in
question is not up for that you know and I get that that's that's really a shame I
hate to hear it I really hate to hear it what I was gonna say last night I saw the
man from uncle. Oh, I heard it was great. No, I told you it was great. The reviews. It got
okay reviews. It's it's fine. Well, what were you expecting? I kind of didn't expect it to
be good, but like Henry Cable, the most boring actor alive. Army Hammer, the second most
boring actor alive. I like both of those guys and I enjoyed the Lone Ranger. I don't
like you like Henry Cavill and Army Ham I said cable first I didn't feel right
Cavill also didn't feel right I think you know I think you're thinking like
Cavizel no I know I'm not thinking of Jesus I don't think it's Henry Covill I
think he's a great I think he's a great Superman I enjoy him and Superman I
enjoy him in whatever works the Woody Allen movie those are the only two
things I hated that man of steel and what was he in he was like a fiance of
somebody's the guy that's like in love with Rachel Devin Rachel would or whatever name is
you know whatever works the guy that's like that lives on the boat all right he's quite
white sure he's quite charming all right sometimes you say somebody somebody that's not the somebody
that you said that it was Pat here's what I'd like out of you tonight one compliment
and not a criticism any other criticisms Joe you're unhappy you don't have your fact straight
talk too much about it masturbation at the top of the podcast. What have I done? I don't
deserve this. Nothing. I made an error on the previous podcast
where I said that the guy who molested the kid who directed Powder Victor Salva. I said
he made a movie called The Fun House produced by Francis Ford Copeland. It's not true.
The movie I believe was called Clown House because I looked it up and it was like Roman
Coppola or another Coppola. It is Clownhouse. It is and if I'm not mistaken Sam Rockwell is in Clownhouse
That might be a young Sam Rockwell. I've got to publish the clarifications now for previous pocket
I've been working on a Sam Rockwell impression forever. I can't get it down, man
He's not that easy to do. I can't get it down. You want to try you want to try easily slide into it into a
Giamatti and he seems kind of like a very toned -down Giamatti to me. I slide into a Giamatti
Yeah, you like your voice naturally without much doctoring
works as a Giamatti impression. A little bit. Yeah. There's a little I have a
Jerry Heller. I have a Giamatti look. Yeah. True. I feel like I could maybe take the
parts that Giamatti turns down soon. Sure. You know. I mean you look like here's
a common for you look like a more attractive version of a couple celebs.
Jared Vogel of subway Paul Giamatti. You know. A more attractive version. Pat I've
never said this to a person I want you out of my house for the love of Christ you fucking
cock sucker now Frank's about to kill this poor bastard all he's trying to do is fuck
his wife I honestly can't believe how terrible this woman is and she does stop the she's
trying to stop Frank from killing her husband though she's saying please don't her husband
thinks her look at this nothing that's a rat open over there oh why does he do that to
be like to be like I'm in control here that's so gross now also husband thinks she's crying
please no don't fuck me yeah now the guy keeps going that's what I don't understand to the
guy keeps going and she's going I can't bear it I can't bear it the first time I hear
I can't bear it. I'm wrapping up the love making. I don't think that he's ever
Heard his wife say well because here's why because upstairs she starts jumping when they first go upstairs before the scene
She's all over seducing him because she's trying to save him from Frank. Yeah, and then they go downstairs
And then Frank turns out to be in their bedroom. So now she has to switch gears
See yes
It makes perfect. I honest look
I don't know what it is with me. I honestly thought that she brought him up to the room. I
Think she did bring up to the room and then she had second thoughts. Oh
But I just thought they went in there because he's in the room
I didn't know he could get out of the room
Well, I couldn't get out of the room. I just assumed there were rules
You only see him in the room and has there been one rule so far in this movie
No, and that blood bringing people back to life because I was just like that brings demons
We haven't seen in an hour and a half. Yeah, that's true
you know I mean there's no rules because I was also like what since when is there a
bed in this upstairs blood drenched attic but now I understand I heard
Clive Barker on set he would say to people hey when they would ask
questions about the script you go you go hey Steve when would it roll with it
baby that didn't happen I heard that's what he would say it just plays it on
a boombox. This Chinese restaurant there and makes me so hungry every time I see it. It
looks. I told you I haven't eaten in 11 days. So good. So anytime I see food except in this
movie I'm not feeling hungry. I mean Pat listen you live the life of it's a real healthy routine
you have where you destroy yourself for six months and then not eat anything and drink
like vegetable juice for 18 days straight.
Once a year.
Yeah.
It's it's it's it works.
I'm sure it's a healthy way to do the thing to do to your body.
I mean actors do it.
Yeah.
Well you know actors they're healthy people.
Hey Pat I'd like to introduce you to my friend his name's moderation.
But you do the same job.
I mean you're you're a big I'm not drinking and then I let's get drunk.
No.
We're those kind of people.
It's a very Catholic thing. I don't think you're gonna take a little break from the booze sometimes
But like I never did this cleansing to not eat
To drop wait. This is my sugar. I don't know
It works for me. Everybody does their own shit
Well, I'm just saying when you drop dead
You'll know why yeah, I'll stand over you saying I told you so I
Would hope your reaction was something different than that. I feel like if I died right now in front of you
it would just still be the same stoic I you know I'm a little more emotional than people
think I haven't cried in a decade but and when I did it was at the movie about Schmidt
no it's a 127 hours the other movie I cried out see that's that that's the problem the
last my credit I think was when I saw 127 hours our relationship started with great
emotion you mean just that we liked each other we were it was fast friends but then we had
that Christmas text where you said Joe you texted me Merry Christmas you were the only
person I was going to text that to today yeah it was very nice I felt like we got off
on a nice emotional start and now I feel like you take me for granted well this sounds
a lot like other relationships I've been in when I've left town for for a week and
half you've texted, Joe, do you even miss me? You've texted that to me. Yeah. Well, you
know, these are kind of jokes. I know they're jokes, but the thrill is gone is my point.
It was gone. All right, PBBK. We're sleeping in separate rooms at this point. Yeah, exactly.
I saw we're both reading separate sections of the newspaper at breakfast. It's that we're
at that scene in singles where they're yeah, yeah. Hey, you. Hey, what is it when they're
read the paper. She's dating when Kyra said you're dating a really awful like. Oh yeah
guy. Yeah. Hey you. Hi. So just dead. The whole relationship. Second pocket. We talked about
singles as well. Why wouldn't you talk about singles. I know we haven't worked into this
one yet. Child molestation. I did. I brought the powder guy. Oh there you go. But man
from uncle. So I'm thinking I had a joke about this today but like a studio. You
come to them and you say hey I got army hammer hot off the lone ranger one of
the biggest flops of all time I've got Henry Kevill right and I want to reboot
a 60s TV show that no one knows with the worst title ever the man from uncle I
think it's a great title why on earth was this movie made and it cost a hundred
million dollars extra I looked it up cost 75 million dollars it was a bomb I
I just I don't get it
How these things get me how they how they decide what to throw money at you could make
Not not kidding here
One million dollar cool interesting movies that would all probably some would turn a profit, you know, that's not their goal
Yeah, of course, but what is it? What is their goal? They're losing money on man from uncle unless it makes money overseas or something
If they're like ooh superman
You know, that's not their goal
I mean you're talking like you've been in this town for five minutes you like you're chewing
on a piece of straw.
I'm saying why couldn't they why wouldn't that why couldn't they is not the question
Pat like anyone would know like it's it can't be a shock to them that some of these movies
bomb.
It's not a shock that the man from Uncle Bombs but it's how they've been doing it
forever.
They they put all their chips on one number yeah and try to make a windfall of money
right.
you know okay fantastic for completely bombed nobody six years ago so what should we do let's
make it again well and let's make this one suck too but that's Sony that's Sony you know
trying to you know they're saying hey they fucked it up once now Marvel's hot right we're
going to try to reboot it and do it right this time but then that director fucked it all
up apparently who was a cool director made the old Chronicle yeah Chronicle you
know I thought that movie was overrated but visually it was cool yeah it was it
did some new things it was fine Frank is now try by the way Frank just exposed
him not exposed like genitals exposed himself to Kirsty for the first time
right she also came to terms with this very quickly well now why did he
exposed to her because he's her. He's her dad, right? I don't know. He looks nothing like
herself. No, he's not her dad. He's her uncle. Okay. Yeah. Yeah. But he was saying come to
Danny. I don't I think he was just in the oh because she because she saw she knew Julia
killed somebody upstairs and then she went upstairs and then the half dead guy came
out like help me and then so the jig was up. She knew what was going on and then
Frank came out like hey come here and fuck me right your blood or something you
know like one of those things he was also trying to bang her correct yeah he's
a pervert he's so like man and this woman is still interested in him who
married woman yeah yeah Julie is a terrible person crazy look at these three
Yankees have who put these three people together to to they were they were a
Doop group on the corner that came up like literally the three people that run the food truck
Just were used as extras in the film. This is supposed to be set in London, right?
You know, I've never been able to figure or they I don't I hope they didn't give that guy Yankees cap
So we believe this was New York City. I don't think it's supposed to be set in London because nobody has English accents except Julia
That's true. It feels very British. It's clear that we'll look at this fucking hospital room. She's yeah, Christ six
You know you wouldn't see a hospital room like that in the States. I don't think you'd see one like it in London either
But fine. Have you ever been to London? Yeah, I have
Years ago, I didn't go to the hospital while I was there wasn't that kind of a trap
Look at that guy that doctor has some kind of weird makeup on
You know, I always wonder in both horror movies and in comedies like David Lynch always cast
completely freaky looking people like you've never seen before crazy faces everybody looks
interesting and it keeps you on your edge he doesn't even have to do any work really he
does everything's amazing that in comedies why wouldn't you cast like funny looking
people in these bed parts get some extra laughs look at this weirdo always casting boring
People's physical shortcomings talking deformities Jesus Christ interesting looking people get a big fat pig in there
We all laugh at the fat. So is that what you want Pat?
Fuck is wrong with you. No not at all what I was saying
I'm saying get people with some character in their face and these bit parts
They always have like generic boring looking people in movies. This movie's doing a good job. You got some weird -looking people
Right. I agree. I agree
interest let's say interesting looking interesting judge beauty like under the
skin there's a great example I love that movie kind of a horror movie you won't
watch it because of that guy I get it upsets me and that's an actual
deformity I know I don't say that to be mean it looks like the elephant man but
somehow I can't watch his real -life face is more unsettling than the elephant
man well I heard that if you go back and rewatch the elephant man now it just
looks like that makeup I don't know about that I don't know if that's true
I can't watch it. I can't watch mask. I can't watch the elephant man. I can't think and it's not out of
Meanness it's out of it. I find it very upsetting. All right
Now you were saying last week on the podcast what?
Show me something just you're like the director didn't want to have Freddy Krueger something you had to look away from
In horror, but you were like I want that give me something. I have to look away from and make it disturbing
Now you're saying the exact opposite.
No, at horror, it's, Kirstie just opened the box.
Here we go, Goy.
Here we go.
The wall just opened up.
That means Pinhead's coming.
No, it's, it's, see that corridor, Pat?
Yeah, this part really kind of bothered me also.
What did it bother you?
It's horrifying.
It's hell.
That's what, that's the gateway.
Did they have to make hell so horrifying?
line. Sparkle a little heaven in for us pussies.
What did you want? Hello look like Pat. I don't know. I thought it would be red.
Maybe a more like a Bam Bam Bigelow scene with a painted flames everywhere.
I mean give me one guy with a fork tail kind of shaking sure you like more of a hot rod
race kind of yeah I got you. Yeah I understand like the mascot of this
very podcast. I understand. I think that comes out
is disturbing and I also wondered if you can see the man's legs who's running it
I don't think you can I pause it and I was like I think I see this guy's legs
but maybe I didn't with horror I like gruesome and gross and yeah
disturbing and blah blah blah when it's a real person it upsets me because I
feel terrible for that person sure so it's hard for me to watch this guy
seemed really at ease and actually does full frontal nudity and under the
skin. God bless him. Yeah. Go for it if you're going to do it.
This part always reminds me of like a like this big war. He was big adventure is kind
of what the vibe is. It makes me think of like a Jim Henson kind
of. Yeah. The noise is it's making are really what makes it unsettling. It makes me think
of labyrinth. Yeah. Sure. You know because this hallway looks
like the labyrinth. Labyrinth always scared the shit out of me.
You ever see the dark crystal of course that one is
Like it to this day freaks me out. Yeah, I love it. It's one of my favorite movies of all time
It scares the shit out of me still I
Don't feel she's running fast enough. I
Would be running much faster. I think I don't think it's supposed to be like literally look how fat she's you know
She's running this bad. I think it's just she's running. Okay. She's running no pinhead. I wanted some pinhead there
We didn't get any pinhead he's barely in it right now. I've already said that
Oops, sorry. Well, well you did. I'm just pointing out. I've said it
There was a time when we used to listen to each other. I
Went when I lived in New York, I went down to I believe film forum on Halloween because I had no friends
I had lived there for two months and had not I don't think I'd said a word
You have one uplifting story about you moving to a city.
No.
You move here, you're gated into a prison,
you're masturbating for money.
Now things are.
Some kind of boogie nights, climax.
Yeah, it wasn't unlike that.
And you go to New York, you have no friends,
you're going to movies alone.
For three months, I don't think I said one word.
But the story's about the endings,
because I wound up with lots of friends
and having a good time.
But at first, I didn't know anyone.
So Halloween night, I had nothing to do.
And I went to film for them and watched this all night
horror festival.
and they showed Donnie Darko by yourself but by myself Donnie Darko the saddest
thing they've ever they show this movie called king of the ants that was
terrifying ever see that movie it's with William Shatner is it not no okay sorry
Pat I think George went is in it but it's really really scary
king of the it was about giant ants no I it actually was more of like a very
real -life horror kind of thing it was Stuart Gordon who did reanimator
Oh all right I'm in I want to see man it was really freaky and then Hellraiser was like
the 2am movie and I was like I don't want to get out of Hellraiser at 4am and then have
to walk home through the streets of New York I couldn't stomach that idea.
So I just went home.
It's a good thing you didn't because in that book the Scarlet Gospels I was telling you
about there these cenobites are popping up all over New York.
Yeah see I wouldn't have been good with that I do get very scared of things when
watch them alone. That guy is really gross. Who? Butterball? Yeah. He just licked his lips.
Yeah, I saw that. She's pretty scary. Why is her throat propped open? Do you have a problem
with it? It's all because it's awesome. That's why. All right. Oh, listen to her growling.
That's pretty cool. Like just take the pins out and let your throat close up. Let it
heal naturally. He's put a lotion on it. That's such a great line when he says that.
oh no tears please such a waste of good suffering no time for argument he's so
cool he sounds like Darth Vader I love him I love him so much now she makes a
deal with him here she makes a deal with him tell you what they're not gonna
take her take that pin out of your nose I'm giving more advice to this girl
slide it out of your nose then you don't have a pin in your nose anymore
more and sew up the neck hole that you have and you'd be a nice looking gal you get dates.
She doesn't want to sew up the neck hole. The point is this is who they are. All right.
The moves about being yourself is what you're saying. It's not. It's it's the whole movie's
a metaphor for goth kids. I mean let's be honest. Yeah for sure. You know a lot of
black leather and nobody understands me. I live in a dark box. I used to drink at
this bar in Hollywood called Bordner's and it was next to a club alone. No the sad
with friends and I had it was next to this bar that had a golf night every Saturday
and we would go just so we could watch these people and there was a girl yanking her boyfriend
around on a chain and dog collar and chain and he was wearing a shirt that said I have
a tiny penis and she kept like bring him around. I was like I want you to meet my
boyfriend he has a tiny penis and we're like okay it was like some weird
punishment they were doing and that boy was Jason Schwartz yeah he later became
Rushmore my my friend at work is reading the or listening to the
autobiography of the of Jason Schwartz no of Rob Lowe and tons of ass stories in
it well they said every chapter ends with so I was hanging out with this
girl and it was no big deal I mean it wasn't like she was anybody famous or anything but
in just one year's time she was Winona Ryder and every chapter ends like that he doesn't
tell you who the person is that he's talking about and then he goes does he does he bang
all of them I think he bangs most he was in the first sex tapes I know that was when
people gave a shit about sex tapes yeah he had a 16 year old girl and now we all love
them. But he was 21. But he didn't even get in trouble for banging the 16. Nobody even
cared about that part. They were just like, can you believe it's on video? Yeah. I don't
remember. Video taped the degenerate. Yeah. It was two girls, I believe it was. Yeah, that
girl there. That guy, I'm sure Rob said to the police like, Hey, you know, fellas, you
was 16 going on 40 and they high fived him and sent him on his way. That's probably
how that went down. I love it. I love it. Now who's banging Julie? Is this another flashback?
I believe so. Okay. She's having a flashback. Okay. Because
this is the final. We're in the final run now. She's preparing to feed her husband to
Frank. How good must this sex have been the sacrifices she's willing to make to get
one more taste. It must be Dick Almighty. Plus then he's proven he's not even going to be
faithful to her when it does happen. He's trying to hit on her niece. I know. The guy's like yeah
I know this woman's murdered ten men to have another taste of my dong but I think I'm going to hit
on her step niece. It's her stepdaughter for stepdaughter. It's his blood niece. His step
his blood niece. He's trying to fuck his blood niece. Sorry I wasn't following the family
tree of Hill resin. That'd be a good name for a harm movie. Blood niece. Wouldn't it. Yeah.
She's like your niece. But bloody. Now this is Frank in the dad's skin now. If you can't
tell by the boils in the bloody scene. Now how out of his head. How does that work.
How does he slip on the skin. It's the same thing that bothers me about Mission Impossible
When they put on the mask and they look exactly like the guy it's like it's ridiculous. You see the new mission impossible
I loved it. It was fucking awesome. I loved it
I said it was almost Mad Max good. It was so good. Yeah when he was down in that like washing machine thing
Yeah, it was that was amazing. It was tremendous the whole plane sequence was out of this world
Yeah, loved it his entrance into the movie him running over the hill and ducking
Can you get me on the plane? They're better than the bonds I would say it was so fucking good
But it does still bother me that they put on a mask and then they're suddenly the other person sure well two same body
To really overdid it, but like same body. Yeah
Every same everything two was like a dog walks up and then peels off a mask and it's Tom Cruise like two was ridiculous
That's ridiculous. That didn't happen. It didn't happen. Come on
Then on woo, you know real hit or miss that. He didn't do a movie since he was the biggest thing
It's in sliced bread for a while there. No, but he made you know how big sliced bread
this. Can't eat a sandwich. No that's Ang Lee. Wow. Oh I guess they all look alike to
you Joe. Ang Lee and John who could not be more different direction. I thought Ang Lee
actually made Mission Impossible too because I'm thinking of mission. I'm thinking of how
he made the Hulk. Yeah that's true. He also made Mission Impossible. How bad was that
Hulk when Nick Nolte bites into that electric wire. It starts OK and then they start switching
shit around and pretty bad. It could have been good. Well you know why wouldn't Edward
Norton play the whole. I like the Edward Norton one. That's the only one. Oh no. One is the
Eric Bana one. Oh God. The Ed Norton one is good. The Ed Norton's the one with Tim Roth
and he becomes a bombination. They all run together to me. But yes. Those Hulk movies
run together. Way worse. The Ang Lee one is the bad one. Way worse. The Norton one
good it's like that's part of the official Marvel canon in the Avengers and
everything well that doesn't make it good it's a I haven't enjoyed it I'm a bad
person to talk to about this I don't like this movie does she not know does she
not see the blood dripping out of her dad's head she's clearly blinded by
lust for this man who doing that wait who's blinded by lust talking about
the daughter oh the daughter yeah I don't know I guess she just didn't look
Oh, maybe she I think we talked through it. Maybe she does know it's not her dad
Or it may wait does no
That's is she does anyone come back for Hellraiser to?
Yeah, she comes back. I don't want to ruin anything, but she's back Kirstie's back. There they are. I
Love the thought that someone listening to this movie with us talking over it could have something spoiled for them
Well, here's the thing like hey he ruined this movie that I can't hear they broke they broke
another rule that Senate by just appeared and they nobody opened the box whatever though
why is Kirsty fighting she I'm confused I got damn it this is bad for the podcast Pat
I don't know what's happening in the movie right now I got really lost she doesn't
know that's her dad yet or she does she knows I believe no that's not her dad that's Frank
okay she still thinks it's her dad she thinks it's her dad why is she not noticing the
blood then on the side of his head she probably just like hey there's some weird shit going
on in this house my dad's head's all bloody by the same as his hair she's been through
a pretty rough day he's just got chased by a whole demon by the way how did she get
out of the mental institution that she was locked up look we've got a lot of questions
I'm sure she has even more right now. She knows okay. She thought her dad killed. Yeah when her dad tries to boner
She's like, oh, okay. I get it. She thought her dad killed Frank. She thought that dead body upstairs was Frank
It's not it's her dad. That's why when pinhead said we want the man who did this
She thought she was had to turn her dad over and she said no right I
Mean and this Julia lady is well the fuck this guy with skin hanging off of his face
Which is grosser than when he just had like his she just doesn't care
Oh there's the switchblade that he used to bang his yeah I like why doesn't he have Frank's
voice anymore by the way do you notice that I thought I thought he was getting a more
normal voice because he's becoming more normal now now he's got he that's just the actor
that plays the dad it's his voice yeah yeah they could they've dubbed everything else why
I'm not done done. Yeah. Oh God. Oh and he takes he takes Julia's flesh here.
That's the line nothing personal baby as he sucks her life out of her. But that's good
makeup. And I'm so surprised that this guy proved not to be trustworthy. After all she
did for him his face doesn't look any better after sucking out Julia's essence. Right.
Why didn't it heal his wounds up? Yeah, it should. Barker, breaking rules. Clive break the rules Barker. Clive break her. Clive break her.
Of rules. I love left and right in this movie. I still love the movie. I'm not shitting on it, but. No, I mean the unexplained is what the whore is all about, you know.
That'd be a good name for harm will be the unexplained
What's going on? I don't know the unexplained
That's the whole trailer
Cheech Marin is the unexplained
I don't know he needs work
Haven't seen him in a long time those Cheech and Chag tours they're mopping up man. Oh, all right great
Yeah, well, then let's cast somebody else. Yeah, and I can't believe you thought cheech needed work over Tommy
Yeah, well, I don't like Tommy
Well, I think she's carried Tommy for 50 years now. I think Tommy's very funny. All right. They're both very funny
Do you know Tommy? Not at all. Did you work with him or something? No, neither one of them. Okay
Hey, we used to work with you worked with Roddy Roddy Piper. Were you sad when he died?
Of course I was I I
um, I mean to tell kind of a strange story about it
I was doing the extras for the always sunny DVD and
and Rob McElhenney called him.
He was like, you guys gotta come down here right now.
Rowdy Rowdy Piper's on fire.
He's been telling stories for like four hours.
You gotta get him on tape
and we're gonna do a DVD extra like Rowdy Rowdy Piper tales
and he's telling like some of his best stories.
And by the time I got to set,
we were interviewing him and he was just like
very much not making sense.
Like his brain had been banged around so much
that maybe he had a good hour or two of stories
but then eventually it just stopped.
that's really disgusting but he couldn't have been more charming couldn't have been
more nice he was funny but the stories really disgusting the stories didn't make
sense because it sounds like you're saying Roddy's brain damage was
disgusting no he was a sweet delightful man he's very funny in the show I was
saying that head full of maggots was disgusting yeah well you got to
describe it to the people that aren't seeing this right now a head came out
of the darkness and maggots fell out of it yeah that was really gross
Rather a pipe or a grape, man.
It is gross.
I'm going to see if there's a way next Halloween
that I can do that to you somehow.
Fill a fake head with maggots and throw it at me.
Like a prank.
Well, let me tell you how that ends.
We never hang out again, ever.
And I don't answer your texts or calls.
So if that's worth it to you, great.
You would never hang out with me to get over that.
That's a guarantee.
If you throw a maggot -filled head at me.
No, I didn't say throw it at you.
I would just dip it next to you and freak you out with it
You'd never talk to me. Do you do it in your home like you're spilling maggots on the floor of your own home?
That's where really scared. Yeah, so now my floor is covered in maggots and we're not friends anymore
The maggots I wake up November 1st, and I delete your number from my phone. Really? Yeah
Jesus, sorry. You're a real fuck. I don't need friends that I can't trust not to throw maggot filled heads at me
One time my friend Chip got mad at me because we went down to the Jersey Shore
went to Atlantic City. It was me, my friend Chip, and my friend Scott, who you've met.
And I went into the bathroom. Did you fix your hair up nice? Stress yourself up pretty?
Yeah, for the tables. For the table game. It's Bruce Branstad's song, Atlanta City.
We went to Atlantic City and I like to reference things. Scott was in the shower and Chip
was on in the bedroom part of the room. And while he was in there, I went into
the bathroom and I shit onto the soap dish and then put it on the sink so it
matter with him it was one of the funniest things that are done in my life I
was I was I was uncontrollably laughing I couldn't get my shit together I was
laughing sorry and shit together because it was sitting on a soap dish ship was
so offended that he didn't speak to me the rest of the day and it was my
birthday you and I are kindred spirits because I think I would probably be like
Yeah, you're on your own this week.
Well, you're you're an animal.
I've never liked pranks.
I had for Christ's sakes, Pat.
Would you get over it?
I don't like them.
I think they're made your TV comedy writer.
You don't like pranks.
Yeah, yeah, you can be both.
The hell are you talking about?
That's really gross.
The Senate bites are here for Frank.
This is the big climax now.
Oh, look at her hair.
I never noticed that the weird Senate bite
lady has like strands of hair. Frank. They're going to take her. Here we go. Here we go.
I see. Now this is what they lost. With the set of bites. Okay. Everybody just said the
Kirstie. No, no, no. What Pinhead said. I just said the Kirstie. This isn't for your
eyes he's telling her leave this has nothing to do with you he's a rational man yeah he's
a rational man he's a judge he's like you seem like you could probably have a nice time going
with a fella to a movie and holding hands you don't need to be exposed to this underground
world of torture to have sex but you know and that's the thing I didn't like about
the new book is that they make him he's just like a raging asshole and you're like
this isn't what this isn't how he rolls people change you know maybe pain had had some misfortunes
in his internal demons change I didn't know that I thought kind of you could count on
somebody it'd be a centabyte Jesus Christ this is really gross and then this is the
part yeah I looked away for this when I watched where he goes terrible I love this line being
Jesus wept yeah that's funny why does he say that why does he say that like I
suffered as he did or something I think Jesus I mean Jesus wept means like this
is fucked up basically right I'm not a big Bible head so I think it's just I
think he's saying like this is my crucifixion all right well it's
thinks a little highly of himself. Well yeah Frank does think highly of himself and that's
a good little thing. He fucks women with a switch. That's true. Not with us. There's another
rule broken said about scraping the wall. Blood's coming out of it. Why are they coming
after Kirsty now. They just tried to save her. They just said they just said this
is not for your eyes. Get out of here and now they're coming after her. Why is that
happening. Maybe because she didn't get the hell out of there when they told her to.
She left didn't she. No she's. I don't know. She watched the guy say
as Jesus wept line. Is that what it is. I see hook one go into
my guy dressed in the skin of my dad. I leave. Here's. He's telling. Okay. So this
is the penalty. Now you got to come with us. You saw the other
right. Okay I get it. Now has there ever been a more warranted oh shit than that one. Yeah.
And I look and she's now cursey closes the box in order to I guess trap the Cenobites
again which they can get out of the box anyway we've seen. And I like the pinhead just
goes don't do that yeah hey yeah well they establish in part three that he can't take
the box from you it has to be given to him okay well that's how this work this is part
one so but why didn't he fly his chains at her a lot of questions here Clive I got a lot
of questions I'd like to get you on the phone I'd like to discuss this with you please
I got a lot of questions for Clive break the rules Barker and Chrissy is played by Chrissy
same actress and everything and two yes that looked out for her getting that part she's
in two she has a tiny cameo in three and she turns up again in like five or six six it
is actually boy I can't believe I remember that but I do what how lucky are you as
like a kind of an okay generic actor to get like the lead in one of these eight part things
you know what a dream I love to do movies like this yeah wouldn't this be a fucking ball
I mean like saw they're swapping out people every time but like that anything where you
can like carry it out except the one chick was in a few of them that's you know who's
the broad. She's a is the broad that was in a few of the sauce. She was a victim in one
and then she's in part two and she falls into like the needle pit and then she becomes like
his apprentice. I Tandy. She's got like a interesting name. She was on Becker. She played
the dumb girl on Becker. I don't know. Yeah. Well, what are you going to do? I interviewed
at all. I used to work for Cinematical, which was a great movie website for AOL. I got to
interview all these people from SAW. This thing's back now. Now this big, this dog
thing is back. And she grabs the box and electrocutes her. Why did that happen? Oh, I mean,
I hate to, I just hate to ask so many goddamn questions, Pat, but I'm sorry I am. Yeah,
I mean I think honestly because in writing stuff all you have to do is ask yourself these questions
and try to make things work and it's so exhausting that when I sit down to watch a movie I tend
to not ask questions and the people who are like well why did this why did this you know
I get it I have fun having those conversations but I'm never doing it myself I just let
things happen.
Well you know that's the world you want to live in.
It is like I question everything else in my life. I don't need to question the movies, you know
I spent so much time being like well, I don't know if this is right
I don't know if it's good. I don't need to do that when I watch a movie. Hey, welcome to Obama's America
That's what I say. I don't know what that means here kidding. Oh, it's a joke. It's a joke
I was making like a political joke. Sure. You don't get involved. No, I don't get involved
I have nothing against Obama. I take that back. It was just he's a great man
I thought it was a funny thing to say who do you think's running our country coming up here? It's Trump question good to be Trump
It's it could be it's insanity. It could be time for the pendulum to swing again
This is how it goes every eight years. It goes back the other way. I don't think even Republicans
Trust Trump run in the country. They don't but he's leading the polls. Yeah, he's leading the polls
All right, I can't go much further with political talk. I don't know what I'm talking about either do I okay?
Look at that shirt. I'm not even sure I know what leading the polls means
That's I read it today or something that shirt is the stupidest choice to end a horror movie unless it's like
Was the year that it you know, I mean Joe it's of the time
I don't know that was of the time
That's like something that kid or play would wear and house party three the pajama jam
Well, the funny thing is is every time he looks at that
Cross colors rayon shirt that he's wearing he's gonna go I fought demons in this shirt
Oh, I'd be down with that shirt my demon shirt. Yeah, every time you get it out of the closet
Do you ever wear it again? Or is that it? I probably wouldn't I?
Also wouldn't wear it because I would have to beat the shit out of myself if I saw me in that shirt
All right, here's comes the answer to your question about the
You know who's the bearded man or whatever. Yeah, he's coming back in in a second here
Give it a second Pat. Be patient be patient. Oh, there he is. See I might have been peeing during this part
What are these piles of fire by the way is this was this the house?
Just a field of like homeless people fires, I guess that yeah
Yeah. Very strange. I think, you know, and I agree with this. I think somebody like
Clive Barker, even though I don't think I've seen any of his other movies, I think he just
wanted to create a mood. I agree. And I dig that, especially in horror. I'm not knocking
it. I'm just asking questions. What's Clive Barker's like second most successful? Like
he did like Lord of Illusions. I don't think I've ever seen any of his movies.
night night night breed probably yes I think I've been tend to watch night
breed it's in the queue I am not a fan of night breed okay have you seen the
directors thing the directors cut yes okay I'm not a fan all right I'm gonna
watch I'm not a fan it seems to me to be a very creative dude he is very creative
and I think he's great I just you know but he never had another big like franchise
I can in movie other than that's right. This was the biggest. Yeah, but I mean this is to me
Despite all my questions, it's
It's masterful and right back to the beginning a new man gets the box great ending can't argue that I love anything that starts
Ends where it started Frank the monster in case we weren't clear Frank the monster Oliver Smith
Oh, now. Why would you do that? Did you think Shawn Chapman was like? I'm not sitting for all that makeup
Now I just think they probably wanted somebody look at this in the credits. I love this lead
Senna by Doug Bradley before they had a name. Wow. Yeah. For the end of Jackie Hellreza.
That's another cheesy part in the book that he just put out. There's this whole thing where
if you call Pinhead Pinhead he gets furious. Really? Because it's like don't call him that.
He hates that nickname. Yeah. Do they refer to him as pinheads in the movies or that
just what society called it's just kind of what the name he got from the fans I
guess okay caught on or whatever got you they put this thing in the book where
it's like you better not call him pinhead do a space he'll get real hot well
they took that from back of the future well whatever ladies and gentlemen that
was hellraiser yeah it was a wild ride that's makes two nights in a row where
the last thing I do before I go to bed is watch hellraiser well horrific
perfect visuals and then go to sleep. And count the minutes to Halloween, Pat, because
a head full of maggots is coming at you. And you need to treasure these last few months
of our friendship, Jeff. I haven't treasured the first few months
of the friendship. I'm not going to treasure the last right. Fair enough.
This has been we'll see you in hell. Again, you can follow us on Twitter or send us any
questions or comments or requests. Yeah, I'm at the Patrick Walsh P. A. T. R. I. C.
K. W. A. L. S. H. Joe DeRosa is Joe DeRosa comedy and tweet us questions thoughts movie
suggestions stuff you want us to talk about your thoughts criticisms look us up on iTunes
review the show give us that five stars we'd love it thanks for listening we'll
be at the mile -high horror fest in Colorado Littleton Colorado first week
in of October we don't know yet which day we're performing it'll be Saturday or
Sunday or not performing but we'll be doing a live podcast there details to
come but please come out for that it's gonna be a lot of fun you've been
listening to we'll see you in hell a presentation of the Fangoria podcast
network produced by Thomas DeFeo and executive produced by Ken Hanley of
Thangoria Entertainment for press opportunities advertising inquiries and
information about we'll see you in hell contact ken at Thangoria comm thanks
everybody thanks guys