Welcome to we'll see you in hell episode two here with Pat Walsh.
In the room talking freeway just how we used to do it.
A couple of guys sitting on a couch.
The only thing we're missing is a dog shitting on the floor.
Yeah.
That con would do that sometimes shit right in front of us.
I think we'll once right as the episode began, I remember it happened.
I think Emily's pulled that moment for the best of a few times.
Uh, Pat, I, I, I'm as I sit here in your house.
Yes.
I'm noticing just Blu ray and four K and DVDs strewn about all over the place.
Yep.
Are these new, new things you got that you're putting aside so you can watch them?
They're, you know, they're off the shelf in other words.
Well, so you got the naked gun, four K steel book.
Um, I've seen the naked gun maybe more than any movie, but I would love to see
what they did with the four K.
I haven't seen it yet.
When did that come out?
A couple of weeks ago.
Has it got police squad too?
No.
Damn.
And no, that's the only one of the franchise currently out.
Got the fugitive for that's just the first one.
Just the first, because I got the original and police squad all on
DVD and all the time I'm like, do I need to upgrade these?
But I don't know.
I got, I got the three movies and police squad all on DVD or actually on Blu ray.
Okay.
Um, the fugitive four K is supposed to be amazing.
I'm waiting for a special occasion because I love that movie so much
and it's supposed to look perfect.
And then all the haunts be ours.
A tremendous box set.
Yes.
Did you like, you told me what's the first picture in this thing?
Uh, you said eyes of fire.
I did not like eyes of fire.
Yeah.
I watched that with Joe Bob and it was not, not great.
I liked it quite a bit.
It was very, wait, Joe Bob did it.
He did.
If not, then I just watched it on shut or one of the other.
It's an interesting film.
It's fun.
It's kind of goofy, but, uh, it was like the witch, but bad.
I liked, uh, uh, witch hammer very much on this too.
Yeah.
Well, I love witch finder general and that's a dark one.
Witch hammer similar in the sense of like just a witch finder
who is just a piece of shit.
It's, it's, it's not even as horror movie.
It's just, he's just a terrible bitch.
He's a witch finder.
Who's a piece of shit.
What a great time in movies.
It was black and white.
It's like from the 61.
Um, yeah, I, uh, I just bought, uh, well, I told you I was at Amoeba
and, um, I, I, my shelf is getting, I keep ordering stuff and stuff is
showing up and I'm losing, I'm losing track of like what I've seen, what I
have, I'm, you know, I don't know.
I started doing the system where, you know, my shelving is deeper than
the depth of the case.
Yeah.
The movie case.
So what I do is I go through and if I haven't watched it yet, I have
it sticking out a little more.
I like that.
So then I can, you know, and then, and then I still don't watch it.
And I go downstairs and I boot up fucking, you know, perfect strangers
for the third time or something.
Uh, I had, I had taken away all of the, during the, one of the many strikes,
I took away all the apps, but then they all were a dollar for six
months at black Friday.
So now I have them all, but I mostly just watch my shit.
I try to pull five like these and I'm like, I'm going to watch those.
Those have been sitting there for six months.
I don't do it.
Instead.
I stare at my movie collection sometimes for 90 minutes without making a choice.
It's so stupid and wasteful of my time.
Yeah, it's tough.
It can't make a decision.
It's tough.
And the, and we've talked about this before, but the haunting, the haunting
that comes from knowing there's now a 4k or, you know, whatever.
And then I'm going, you know, arrow just did a 50 % off overseas sale.
And I almost bought RoboCop 4k, but I'm like, I have the goddamn.
Blue ray.
Like I don't, it's, it's, it's killing me.
It's the forget.
Well, now you buy the arrows UK and then they bring them out American.
Sometimes I'm like, Oh, I need that now for some stupid reason.
I still don't have the son of a bitch in psycho set.
I kept it.
I never returned it.
I never got the 4k.
I'm fine with the blue rays.
I'm sure they look great.
Uh, it's still a great set, but I don't have a region free blue ray player.
So yeah, this freeway too is already worth 40 bucks.
I mean, they, they only made 6 ,000 copies of freeway one and two on 4k.
Uh, vinegar syndrome seems to be the place to go.
I also got show girls there, but they're a little more expensive.
Well, that's why you got to come to New York and we'll drive up to the archive,
which is the vinegar syndrome store.
Uh, and it's awesome.
Um, I, um, have a scary stuff actually.
Yeah.
Can't believe I'm talking about this yet.
Speaking of RoboCop, uh, the RoboCop video game that was recently released.
I'm almost finished.
I've I'm almost at the end.
Uh, it is awesome.
It is awesome.
It is a first person shooter.
You are RoboCop.
You have the gun from the movie.
You know, it, you have his scope thing and it does like the green
targeting on everybody brand new game.
Yeah.
Okay.
And the game is just, you go into, you know, there's a story and you're, you're
trying to, you know, the, the, I don't want to give it away, but it's
connected to the first movie.
It recognizes the second movie and it's, it's, it's basically the third, you
know, would it, would a third version would have been good, a third movie
would have been good if it was this.
Peter Weller voices RoboCop.
They got Weller.
They got Weller and the Nancy Allen and the rest of the guests don't come back,
but they got their likenesses.
Okay.
So, so, uh, uh, what the fuck is her name in the movie?
God damn it.
Burke.
No, it's like Smith or something.
I forget.
Anyway, um, Harris, Harris, that's her name.
Anyway, you do a surprise, you, you can do these side missions where you do actual
police work, like you can, it'll be like, find this car and give it a ticket or you
could work the police desk and take complaints from citizens and stuff.
You don't have to do any of that.
You just can, if you want.
As RoboCop?
Yeah, as RoboCop.
And you have to make decisions when you're asked a question or whatever, and
then you gain points in certain directions where, you know, if you uphold
the law too much, it'll be like, you get like law points, but if you, if you bend
it a little bit to help a citizen, like you gain public trust and blah, blah,
blah, but the main crux of the game is there is a new, you know, sort of terrorist
element in, uh, old Detroit.
RoboCops got to stop it and figure out what's going on and how OCP is connected
to it and the bulk of the game is you going into dilapidated areas of rubble
and whatever, and blowing the heads off of dozens of people.
And I'm talking full head explosions, like wild.
It is Verhoeven violent.
Okay.
Like it is insane.
Are you killing like bankers?
Like, is there some satire to it or anything?
Are you killing just innocent people?
It's all, it's all scumbags.
Okay.
Yeah.
It's all just, you know, it's like RoboCop villains, like, you know, guys with like
green mohawks and shit like that.
Come overs.
Yeah.
Uh, it's wild.
It's wild.
I've shot a guy in a deck and he grabbed his crotch screaming.
You should have shot guys hands off and they're like, my fucking hand, man.
It's wild.
It's a wild game.
But they really went for it.
All right.
There's parts where you can like walk through the walls and shit.
There's a really fun thing where like there'll be a room full of criminals and
you go up to the door and it'll say breach.
Yeah.
And you hit the button to breach and you kick the door open.
And then it goes into slow motion and it's just like,
head explosion, head explosion.
It's very fun.
Maybe I should, uh, really complete the divorced guy trifecta and get
really into video games.
Well, I would say this, a PlayStation five, which is the one I prefer to the
new systems over the Xbox, but an Xbox, same thing.
But a PS five to me never hurts, dude.
It's a, it's a four K player.
Well, I have the PS four.
You can not a fork.
That's not a four K though.
But I have a four K.
Yeah, right.
But I'm just saying, yeah, it is.
The PS five really is a one stop entertainment shop, which is nice.
It's a, it's obviously a smart device.
You can do all your apps.
You can, you know, fuck it.
I mean, you could, okay, you could, and you got a real flat dick.
So I think you could get it in that slot.
A floppy dick.
Uh, I, I, I, I don't see any downside to having it.
You play some games, whatever.
It's also, you can switch regions a couple of times, like five times on a DVD.
Yeah, I've heard that I've never been able to do it.
So if you have used my PS four, I've used my PS four six times all during the
pandemic, all to play Sonic the hedgehog.
I have never played anything else.
So I probably shouldn't get it.
Well, what, uh, Sonic the hit, like the old Genesis version, or you got like a new
one, I got one that has like 18 games on 18 sonics on it.
I got you.
Are you, um, cause I wind up buying the old classic games when it, whenever I get
any new system, but, uh, do you play with people?
No, Pat, uh, I do most things alone these days, including the video games.
No, I don't, I never really got into the online.
I mean, I'll play with a friend if somebody comes over, but like I never, I
never got into the online stuff.
People are too good.
Right.
It's I get frustrated.
It's not that fun.
Um, and the games I like to play for the most part, aren't like online competitive
games, like I like fighting games.
I'm never doing it online.
It, I'll, I'll get my ass handed to me.
I will not enjoy it.
Uh, I like sometimes doing shooter games, but I don't play a lot of them.
That's your bulk of online play stuff.
I don't play sports games, you know, like how often are you playing the
Oculus Rift that we got over the pandemic?
Well, mine was stolen in the burglary last year.
So, so never, but I am, I rarely am either.
I used to love it.
I really did.
I'm tempted to get that.
Damn.
It's so don't do that.
Joe, you don't, don't get that.
Why that's too far.
It's supposed to be amazing.
Well, a lot of things are supposed to be amazing.
When I see people walking in the street with those, I'm like, please let them die.
I'm not going to wait.
People are walking around the street.
No, I want to get it literally walking through the street, making like hand motions,
like walking through traffic, going like beep boop boop only out here in this
fucking city.
I just saw it on Tik TOK or whatever.
I don't know where they were.
What are they doing?
I don't, I don't even know what it does.
It's, it's a VR thing, but apparently it's like, you got a thing.
You bought for whatever it was.
300, 400, 300, I guess you don't use it anymore.
And now you're going to get by the 3 ,600.
Well, I know it's stolen, but you don't use it anymore.
Well, I can't use it.
It was stolen.
You really cared.
You would track that guy down.
The thing that stopped me from Liam Neeson style and get your thing back.
The thing that stopped me from using the Oculus Rift wasn't that I didn't give a shit.
It was too hard to use in my apartment.
Yeah.
You can't, you never have enough space.
This is what attracts me to this Apple thing.
The Oculus Rift is very cool, but you never have enough space.
And there are, it's, it's got bugs and that bothers me that you can't.
It's never, it was never a seamless experience.
There was always a fucking issue.
I feel like the Apple thing, it's Apple and it's like, I don't know, man, if this
shit I'm seeing on YouTube, these videos of it, I'm like, I feel like they're going
to be like, no, man, we've got this.
And now I've also got a house where I could.
Yeah.
Is it just cool games or do they have more stuff that it
makes it some, what, why the price tag?
It's not just games, dude.
It's, it's a complete virtual, like lifestyle experience.
And you don't use, you don't use, you can fuck it.
I'm sure the porn ride on this thing is wild, but now I, I got pretty darn into
the, uh, the Oculus Rift porn over the pandemic.
I also don't use controllers with this thing.
Okay.
It's all hands free.
And by the way, it recognizes your eyeball.
So like when you look at something, it can open it.
It's wild, dude.
It goes directly to the government.
Why?
I'm sure it does.
I'm sure it does, but they've got me already.
I've done 23 in me.
That's true.
I've done ancestry and, uh, there was just a huge 23 of me hack.
I never actually did it, but I did it only because I'm adopted.
Right.
Um, did you define it where your parents are?
No, no fifth cousins.
I found a lot of fifth cousins.
Uh, and then, then some fourth, I think once there was a third cousin, but it's
never gotten, I've always said it.
Once it got to second cousin, I might reach out and go, Hey, uh, just, you
know, maybe you know who these people are.
Uh, but you know, what third would you fuck?
I mean, at this point first, I mean, I'm meaning you'd fuck your first cousin.
You'd send me a sister.
I'd banger.
I never met this woman.
No, you're an actual cousin.
I'm joking.
I'm saying I've never met them.
So it wouldn't be weird.
Well, some people don't think it's weird to fuck your cousins.
So, uh, I would, I guess up to second.
I'm not even sure I know what they all mean.
So I can't really say, I don't know.
Like how removed is second cousin?
You're probably fine.
At least getting a handy.
Yeah.
I mean, I don't know.
All right.
Fair enough.
Um, what about you?
What would you do?
Um, I don't know if I even have second cousins.
I, I feel like there's enough people in the world.
You know, I here's the fuck you mean.
Here's a couple of things.
I, is that a, you saying you don't want to make a baby?
No, there's enough.
No, what I'm saying is there's enough people in the world that I don't need to
fuck a relative, no matter how distant I'm only asking you because this was your
question, right?
No interest.
Um, no, I don't either.
Just not.
Um, Pat now has the mic fully pointed down at his chest.
Pat, let's go to that movie corner and I'm going to start with an in name only
sequel to the movie we're talking about today.
Freeway called freeway to colon confessions of a trick baby.
Wild title.
I know.
And Matthew bright, uh, who did both freeway and also tiptoes, which I have
never seen, but one of the most notorious movies ever made, uh, starring Gary
Oldman as a little person doing it.
Dorf style on his knees in a serious drama.
Have you seen tiptoes?
No.
Have you seen the trailer for tip?
No, it's a, it's a, it'll change you.
It's got Matthew McConaughey, Kate Beckinsale.
We'll watch it after this.
I pull it up now.
Why can't we just watch it?
Just, I'll tell you what you give me the remote while you talk about freeway to,
I will set up the tiptoes trailer.
I'll bring it up, Joe.
It's really no issue.
Um, so this guy, and I watched a long interview with him on both of these four
days because vinegar syndrome goes all out for, for B list, sometimes C list
movies, um, this Matthew bright seems like a relatively normal guy.
He's got kind of a hippie vibe.
He grew up with Jeff Bridges, but the movies he makes are definitely
not in any way normal tiptoes.
I will show you, Joe, you won't believe the cast this movie got, but I
went, I read about it on Wikipedia today, but just very briefly, I didn't
get deep enough to see that Gary Oldman was playing a little person.
Well, he had 150 minute cut of the movie that was taken away.
The producers cut it down to, um, 90 minutes at the premiere.
He went nuts and was screaming at them and he's never directed a movie since.
But, um, clearly a very interesting man, tiptoes trailer.
Here it is, Joe.
Well, that's the whole movie.
It is tiptoes official trailer.
Okay.
We're going to watch it.
That girl was on Seinfeld by the by, uh, freeway was written for and nearly
played by Gary Oldman, the Kiefer Sutherland.
Oh, that's interesting because Oliver Stone produced it and they got it to
him, but eventually Stone got him.
That's come down to the volume just a tad.
Okay.
So it's not blowing us out, but, uh, here we go.
Tiptoes.
Okay.
Jesus, they're open in the trailer with a blowjob joke.
Yep.
There it is.
This is insane.
How?
Wow.
And this is pre, you could say the M this is 20 years ago.
Yeah.
2003 in a trailer back.
This is the plot for those of you at home that can't hear the plot of this movie
is Matthew McConaughey's love of his life who loves him so much she's
begging to suck his dick.
Uh, before the trailer even begins.
Dinklage and, and now she's mad when she finds out his entire
family is little people.
Yeah.
By the way, Dinklage came out and said he had no problem with this, but he did
cause the Snow White movie to be completely reshot.
Wait, so Dinklage was challenged about this particular movie has no problem
with this movie or Gary Oldman playing a dwarf.
Why, why on his knees?
He had no issue with that because he was in it.
Probably Joe.
Kate Beckinsale, Dinklage is losing me, man.
Kate Beckinsale is stunning.
Stick command performances.
You don't hear command performances outside of dinner theater, but Patty
Arquette making an appearance two minutes into the trailer.
Command performance means you perform for royalty.
And I believe it's a live, always a live performance.
Why are they calling it?
That is ridiculous.
Uh, it is ridiculous.
We should go to Gary Oldman on Tiptoes.
We need to watch, uh, Tiptoes for the show.
And I think some people have requested it before.
Please.
A glorious part.
I wouldn't think so.
There, by the way, not only is he on his knees, but they're shooting
him from like a stepladder up top.
All right.
We can't just sit and watch.
It does look believable.
I guess sort of.
So, I mean, this guy, Matthew Bright, uh, we'll get to him,
but he was a part of Oingo Boingo.
And that is why Danny Elfman did a soundtrack to Freeway for $1 and yard work.
The producer and Matthew Bright went over and did a bunch of
yard work for Danny Elfman.
And that's why Freeway has an amazing Danny Elfman score.
I think an amazing score, actually.
The opening music to this film.
Well, we'll, we'll come back to the film, but the opening theme is truly great.
It's some of Elfman's best.
I'm shocked that it did not make the music in a darkened theater.
Yeah, it's great record because it is truly one of the best
things Elfman's ever composed.
But that record might've come out before.
Anyway, Freeway 2 does not have the Elfman score.
Basically all the people that Oliver Stone was able to get to help out and
chip in their time and services on Freeway 1 do not return for Freeway 2.
It's got a lesser budget.
It has a straight to DVD feel because it was released straight to DVD.
It stars Natasha Lyonne, who is, that's probably why this got
released by vinegar syndrome.
She has obviously blown up in a huge way.
This is when she is fully addicted to heroin in real life is when she
shot Freeway 2, Matthew Bright, the director also fully addicted to heroin
at this time, he claims in the, there's a 90 plus minute documentary on the
making of Freeway 2 that I watched every minute of my favorite thing to do is to
not watch yet another documentary about Jaws, even though Jaws is a classic,
like everything went wrong documentary or whatever, but just those generic
from the set stories, I don't like, I like troubled productions and I like
Arrow or vinegar or whoever does a two hour doc on, you know, return of the
living dead or something, you know, those are the ones that really fascinate me.
This movie, they talk about how, you know, he says, obviously me and Natasha were
very kindred spirits.
You find out that means they were doing a lot of heroin together.
Uh, the movie has when she was, by the way, like so hot, Natasha Lyonne.
I mean, I'll give you a witherspoon and Lyonne, I feel is more attractive
currently. She looks like she's addicted to heroin in this movie.
I love this. Well, like, like the slums of Beverly Hills, Lyonne.
It was a little before this. Yeah.
But she and also a very hot David Krumholz in that movie.
Full undie shot, Luck Be a Lady.
When I first met David, that's the first thing I said to him.
That's right. Pleasure to work with you.
I love when you sing Luck Be a Lady in slums of Beverly Hills.
And I've kind of seen your dick, at least the outline of it.
Can I see the box for this thing?
For sure. Well, so to tell you the kind of poor taste this movie has, it
opens with Natasha Lyonne in court.
Her lawyer is played by none other than great human being David Alan Greer,
a lawyer who is often seen getting hand jobs under coats
with like an ass in the bed next to him.
And who was playing the judge in this film?
But John Landis, a little wink to the home viewer, I guess.
Anyway, in the movie,
it's similar to Freeway, even though there's no connection between the two movies.
This one is well, Freeway is based loosely on Little Red Riding Hood.
This is Hansel and Gretel.
And they liked a couple of scripts of Matthew Brice at the time.
He was a hot writer.
And this was just a different script.
But they said, hey, Freeway was a hit.
They did this a lot to a lot of movies back then.
Let's just slap Freeway to on it and release it to home movies.
That's the way he got the movie made.
It's gross.
And to be honest, it was too gross for me because it has an obsession with bulimia.
Freeway is not really a gross out movie.
There's some gore in it, but nothing gross out.
Man, there's a lot of puking in the first half hour of this movie.
It goes on and on.
There's a thing where all these women in prison are puking into the same bucket.
And it made me sick, to be honest.
I hate the bulimia stuff in Nightmare on Elm Street five.
I really hate that. It makes me sick.
Well, there's no bulimia stuff.
It's that he feeds her to death because she's obsessed with her weight.
Yeah, it's just something I don't like to watch.
Everybody's got their limits, and that's kind of one of mine. Yeah.
So there's a lot of that.
There's a lot of puking.
There's a project.
You know, there's a woman.
What do you call it?
A guard at the prison.
At one point, she causes herself to projectile vomit all over this woman.
And you're like, what are you doing?
It sort of makes sense that this guy was on heroin throughout
because it's like freeway has such a control of tone
and character and like vibe that it's going for.
And this movie really doesn't.
You got David Alan Greer acting like it's in living color.
He's doing a broad sketch character.
You got a random like hot lesbian sex subplot that comes out of nowhere.
And then suddenly, in the last half hour, it becomes awesome.
Vincent Gallo is playing a transsexual woman.
Who is basically the witch who is capturing and eating children.
Because it is Hansel and Gretel.
How is he in it?
Is it a good character?
He is great in it.
They offered it apparently said to like Sigourney Weaver and these people.
But then they wound up like having a man play a drag queen.
It's a little confusing what he's even trying to be.
But it's a great performance.
And at the end, it becomes genuinely disturbing and suspenseful
as they try to get her out of this guy's lair in Tijuana.
And you learn that this witch that she keeps seeing in her nightmares
has actually been real life assaulting her for a long period of time.
It's very disturbing and unsettling, but
kind of beautiful in a weird sort of like maybe because it's Mexican.
I'm thinking Guillermo del Toro.
But I really like Matthew Bright.
And I'm excited to watch Tiptoes because he's definitely got a flair.
He doesn't know how to make a boring scene.
Just Freeway 2 is not a great movie.
It's worth a watch, though.
So, OK, so is it is it comedic at all?
Yeah, more comedic work. OK.
I watched Freeway is sort of about that sort of it is about
female liberation, basically.
Yes. So I guess sort of on tone of that,
I watched two documentaries, the first is Being Mary Tyler Moore,
which I loved.
It's about Mary Tyler Moore.
Nothing more, nothing less.
It's you know, she's a she's a fascinating human being.
She's an incredible groundbreaker for women in
and how they were portrayed on television.
And that's basically what they really get into,
like who she was as a person versus the character she played on television.
They talk about how, you know, Dick Van Dyke's wife,
you know, her the first big role is the Dick Van Dyke show.
And, you know, she was sort of America's sweetheart.
And then she does the Mary Tyler Moore show.
And they're dealing with things like, you know, they're dealing with
start to deal with women's issues and things of that nature.
And then she goes on to start doing dramatic roles in film.
And it's a really, really great documentary.
Mary Tyler Moore seemed like a magnificent
human being that made a huge difference
and is so incredibly admired and deservedly.
So it's one of those things you watch it, you're sad you never met her.
And it was really great.
I really, really enjoyed it very much.
And I would highly recommend it.
Did she die? Yeah.
Not that long ago.
Most of it happened.
Died from diabetes. Really?
Well, like, you know, complications as a result of, I guess.
But like, yeah, she had diabetes, like, and she was so fit her whole life.
And she had that shitty, like, you know, that that genetic diabetes, man,
like, which is that's that's.
It's great that she had the full life that she did,
because that genetic, that type of diabetes can be can be bad,
you know, if it's just kind of in the blood, you know.
My dad has always eaten horrifically and has never had any issues.
My mom eats unbelievably healthy, mostly vegetables,
and she's had high cholesterol her whole life.
Life's just not fair. Generally, it's not.
It's not. Anyway, what else you got?
Well, I'm trying to remember what else I've watched.
Oh, well, Pat, if I could just step in for a moment, please.
Because it was just up on the screen there. Yes.
People maybe will do it at some point, but I tried this true detective.
And, you know, yeah, it started losing me hard.
I tried. It's certainly better
than the other two seasons so far. Yeah.
And are the second the seasons two and three. Yeah.
And I certainly like the cast.
And if this had been season two, I would have been like,
yeah, this feels like season one again. Yeah. But.
I text you about this.
I'm like, I get real excited at the scary parts.
And then I got to watch one of the characters go like hate
fuck their their side piece.
I'm like, I don't have it in me, man.
I don't know if I could do this again.
It's just too it gets too depressing.
I'm like, it's it's only six episodes.
I still have to watch the finale and it's just been sitting there.
You know, I truly don't care about it.
And I was really hot on it like a lot of people were.
Almost everyone I know was like, oh, yeah, it's really good
because the vibes are there.
It gives you think the thing vibes.
But yeah, it just doesn't.
Everybody frozen in the snow is cool.
You know, I haven't really seen that, like, you know, they frozen solid.
They kind of are coming back to life, but they so far they haven't done much with it.
All right.
Well, is that yours, True Detective?
Well, I slipped the third one in and I got one more actual one.
But all right. What do you got?
Well, I honestly, clearly not much because I'm not really remembering it.
I did on HBO Max.
I did a picture, a documentary picture called
Love Has Won the Cult of Mother God.
Dear Lord, three hours.
Oh, God, strike strike two.
I know this three hours.
I'm generally not a cult documentary guy.
A serial killer thing can usually hook me.
But I had heard too many people say this was great.
And it was the cult, the cult docs.
Look, it's not great, but it's fascinating.
It's always so crazy to me.
A, that people go so insane enough that they think they're Jesus
and they're going to have a cult.
But but I get that that's narcissism.
That's whatever you want to call it.
What I don't get is how almost immediately
these people have 30 people willing to go along with it. Right.
You know, Scientology has decades and literature and buildings.
And I get that. I totally get that. But.
This woman, she has a vision board,
which is basically a big piece of poster board with pictures
of all these celebrities on it, including Robin Williams.
She claims she's mostly talked to by Robin Williams. OK.
This is a normal looking,
attractive woman in her 30s.
She just snaps. Her kids believe her.
You see these two like 20 year old girls who just fully believe
their mom is this like incarnation of God, Mother God.
There's a guy who shows up at the door.
He's like, I'm Father God.
And she's like, I've been waiting for you.
This guy just starts fucking.
Then there was another Father God.
But the second this guy comes to town, she's like, no,
I realized you weren't the right one.
It's this guy. And she just keeps plowing dudes, you know.
But more and more people keep joining this lifestyle.
They talk to her mother. The mom seems normal.
They talk to her sisters. They seem normal.
So that story will always compel me.
What what drives somebody to create a cult?
And then what level of hopelessness do you have to get to?
And I'm probably very close to it.
Sure. To just join a cult.
That's it's no different than you suddenly coming to me and saying,
I think I'm a god, you know, and I trust you.
I I I value your friendship.
But it would never I would never think to believe it for a second.
So how do all these people do it? Yeah.
It's fascinating every time.
And if you like cult shit, this is a really good one.
I'm glad I watched it.
I watched another doc, not a woman, no longer with us.
What happened to Brittany Murphy in freeway?
Oh, yes. Shit. I forgot. Yeah.
It is a two part documentary.
It was heavily criticized.
And I must say, as I was watching it from the jump,
I was like, this feels exploitative or something.
This doesn't feel quite right.
And then it cut to the opening credits after the cold open
because it opens with the call of nine one one. Yeah.
Her mother calling and crying and hysterics.
She won't move. She won't.
This is how it opens.
I'm like, this doesn't seem appropriate.
Like it seems wrong.
And then it jumps to the credits.
And guess who produced it?
Vice Jason Blum.
Really? Oh, Jason Blum.
I was not expecting that.
Wow. Wow.
Something that misses the mark on women's issues.
Oh, crampy Jason Blum.
Anyway, I continued watching it only because I was so curious
about this guy that she married. Right.
Who turned out to be.
You never really get quite a definitive answer,
but it's all all signs point to that he was a charlatan and a hustler,
and he was very controlling and using her for her money and blah, blah, blah, blah.
They basically say that. But then.
They basically say that it's basically established.
There's there's sort of a little bit of pushback from his parents,
but they even not not too much.
They're not like, no, not my son.
They're just like, well, like that one point they say to the mom, like,
you know, didn't he swindle you out of a lot of money?
And she's like, no, I gave him money.
He didn't swindle me.
I knew exactly what I was doing.
Should I have given it to him?
Probably not. Yeah. You know.
So did he swindle it from me? Yes.
But he is not a swindler.
The so anyway,
it's like it's very sad.
She got really wrapped up in.
She became obsessed with her image.
It's it's like that classic tragic Hollywood tale she got.
She gets obsessed with her image. Yeah.
They're telling her she's too fat when she's completely not.
And look, even if she was in what era, like, don't tell a soul that movie.
Well, it covers her whole career.
Would they tell her she's too fat?
Yeah. I mean, like, when did that?
No, that happens like right after like Freeway or after Clueless.
Like, yeah.
And they're Kathy Najimy was was a good friend of hers, I guess.
And they keep cutting to Kathy Najimy.
And she's she's like she was like a normal bodied woman.
Like, like insane.
But here's my point.
Even if she was fat, it's not OK to say that this is what this business is.
It's fucking horrible. So anyway.
You know, it's just very tragic.
She was in this very controlling,
abused mentally, at least mentally abusive relationship.
And and she died.
And and it was very preventable.
They talked to a lot of doctors and stuff.
And they're like, if she had just gone to the doctor like four days earlier,
she would she die of some pneumonia, pneumonia,
collapse from pneumonia.
Like they were like, this was so preventable.
It's crazy.
There were there are theories that she was poisoned.
The coroner was like, well, I don't know what to tell you.
Like, this was my ruling.
I there was no poison.
And they kind of get into that to how, like,
like people want it to be a certain thing.
And they get caught up in the in the story.
And they want it to be a little more than it is.
The husband died exactly the same way six months later, which is very weird.
Yes. There's also a lot of speculation
that the husband and the mother were involved romantically,
or at least inappropriately. Right.
I don't know if I buy that.
I mean, they were like they were sleeping in the same bed. It's like.
Yeah, that's not maybe it's not appropriate.
But I'm like, I don't know, the guy lost his wife.
She lost her daughter.
Like, maybe they were just fucking devastated and crying themselves to sleep.
I mean, it doesn't mean they were banging each other.
So, yeah, anyway, who knows?
But they they they keep
throughout this thing and not in a way of being like,
look at the damn Internet and what the Internet does.
They are using this as actual content that they want you to listen to, whatever.
They keep using footage from YouTubers
or like Instagram people or whatever. Mm hmm.
Are they influencers? I have no fucking idea.
But I'm talking about like these women that are like,
OK, so I you know how this works.
I do my makeup and I talk about a true crime thing.
And by the way, not like reputable true crime things
like our friends at my favorite murders like that.
The most half assed,
you know, whatever approach to discussing this. And again,
it's like it's like this it's like this blum shit.
It's like, what are you doing, dude? Yeah.
Why are you giving a voice to these fucking idiots?
Like these people are reputable.
And they they were on as like talking heads, talking about Brittany Murphy.
Buddy, they're not on shit.
It's clips from their streams and videos they made. Right.
And they're dropping it in with interviews from actual doctors
and the detectives and people that actually worked on this saying like,
this is what happened and this is what should have happened and blah, blah, blah.
And then it cuts to some girl like in her kitchen with a ring light on her face.
Yeah. Going like, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
It doesn't add up.
And you're like, what the fuck is going on? Uh huh.
Hold up a magnifying glass.
Yeah, I guess it's just and I again, I'm just like.
If the if the point of having them in there is to give empowerment
and give a voice to women who have a platform,
give it to women that have an aesthetic, a reputable platform.
Yeah. Or least are presenting some sort of insight or actual commentary.
It's just I don't understand.
It's it's it's anyway, the thing was fucking panned. And
I guess I guess it's worth a watch in in in.
It made me it made me appreciate Brittany Murphy more.
Made me feel sorry for her.
Yeah, she was great.
But, you know, here I am watching a fucking documentary
that's doing to her legacy what basically they complained
was happening to her in her life. It's it's exploitative. Right.
You know, so anyway.
And then to masturbate to it on top of everything else.
I had already jerked off so many times to the Mary Tyler Moore documentary,
particularly in what disaster year.
And all the footage from ordinary people really got me going.
He was kind of hot.
Well, no, it's just her talking about the dead son rouse me.
Anyway, my third, a quick mention of this doc on shutter
that's new to shutter that I really enjoyed called Dario Argento Panico.
It is brief. 90 minutes.
It's people always talk about how they don't want a documentary
that just goes through a director's filmography and people talk about it.
That's what I want. I love that.
I think one of my favorite all time
film documentaries is that HBO documentary Spielberg to two plus hours.
We go through his movies one by one and talk about him. That's all I want.
So I loved it.
It's it's shown.
It's got your boy Nicholas winding Reffen.
OK, talking a lot about what an inspiration he is and admitting
he stole a lot from Argento.
The love of neons and everything.
But Reffen goes on and on about Latter Day Argento,
which I had just written off as not needing to watch like the Stendhal syndrome on.
But Reffen loves later Argento, and it made me want to watch it.
Shutter has a lot of that.
The talking head portion is basically him, Guillermo del Toro
and a few assorted other people, including his daughter, Asia Argento,
who's kind of a controversial figure.
Why? Because she fucked an underage kid. Correct.
Yeah. And then the movie and then paid him hush money
and then blamed her suicided boyfriend.
Yeah. Yeah, she's sort of controversial.
That is not discussed in the film.
Oh, also as a pillar of the Me Too movement.
Yeah, it's a little weird. She that's not bad.
But it's half a look at the filmography with Reffen del Toro
and people that you want to hear talk about these movies.
And that's right.
And then the other half is boring,
but also kind of fascinating footage of Argento checking into a hotel.
Every movie, he checks himself into a hotel to write his movie.
And he's there. He goes about his day.
He's trying to get inspired. He's annoyed.
He connects with his daughters.
It's just a portrait of a very old filmmaker at the end of his life and career.
Juxtaposed with sort of a like the De Palma documentary,
the highlights from his filmography playing throughout.
I really enjoyed it.
It's if you're curious about him, or especially if you're a fan,
I would check it out. I will check it out.
And now on to Freeway
starring Reese Witherspoon at about 15, who Pat said was hot earlier.
He's all she's older than me.
She's when it came out. All right. Fair enough.
And now and always. OK.
She's always been older than fair enough. Fair enough.
She might be 18 in this plane.
I'm pretty sure she was.
I don't remember. But she must have been because she does.
I mean, she's getting she's no nudity.
There's the N word. There's there's other things.
But she's also like, I mean, I guess she can have an underage kid make out.
But the way the way her and Bokeem make out this thing, it's like it's pretty.
It's pretty heavy stuff.
But anyway, there is for for a movie with no nudity.
Freeway is about as sleazy as it gets.
And I have a way higher tolerance for sleaze than most.
I love sleaze.
I love when sleaze goes mainstream like your wild things
and like your freeway freeway.
If you know it, it's probably because it was on HBO a lot.
It was one of those that just got played constantly after its release.
It a little bit of backstory.
I know there's great documentaries if you get this vinegar syndrome thing, but.
Couldn't get it cast because of how adult the material was.
Every young woman came to audition for it,
including Brittany Murphy, who got given a smaller part,
including Alicia Silverstone, who went on to do.
Oh, that would have been hot stuff.
She went on to do, of course, Clueless right around the same time.
They were all auditioning for these same movies.
I would have liked to have Silverstone would have been.
I mean, Witherspoon is great.
But Silverstone, that would have been really interesting.
Yeah, I love Witherspoon in this Holly Hunter mode.
This and election are kind of the prime examples.
But I think Reese Witherspoon is incredible in this movie and Kiefer.
But basically, they had John Travolta and the producers passed.
They said, no, we're hot off of Pulp Fiction.
Pulp Fiction had not, I guess, been released when this movie was originally being cast.
Now, he was going to play the Kiefer part.
Yes. So that was going to maybe get him back on track.
Oliver Stone read the script, loved it, said, I want you to direct it.
I'm doing this thing called U -turn that's kind of similar,
which U -turn does have a very freeway vibe.
My friend, Matt, our friend, Matt McCarthy,
who I was with the wrestling show with yesterday, told me that.
He told me that exact thing that you turn similar.
They well, no. Well, first, he said that the Oliver Stone thing
and the Oliver Stone said, you've got to direct this.
Yeah. Then I said, it's so funny, Matt, because freeway.
I've been being told for like 20 years that this is a movie I need to see.
And I kept confusing it with Free Jack starring Mick Jagger
and Amelia Westavest. Not a movie you need to say.
And I kept saying, like, what are you nuts?
Like, you know, right.
And then he goes, that's funny.
I always confused it with U -turn.
They're they're similar.
U -turn is a real, real scuzzy movie, for sure, with done by Oliver Stone.
This is only produced by him.
But he Kiefer Sutherland was in Nixon.
Joe Bob tells this story, too.
But he converted the Oval Office set, brought him in and told.
He gave him a speech about the importance of art.
And at the end of it, he's like, you're going to do this movie freeway.
Here's the script.
And I convinced him to do it for his friend that was producing it. Very nice.
So Kiefer did it.
The most fascinating thing to me and you really you really get it
when you watch the movie is that Matthew Bright,
he said, I suck at plot.
I only like doing characters.
So I decided about halfway through, I could just graph this on
to the Little Red Riding Hood story.
And I think he does it very well.
He does. He sticks to it to the extent that in the end,
Kiefer actually dresses up like the grandmother, which is kind of crazy.
But it all works.
The the updating of it is really great.
And he got Kiefer and he got Witherspoon.
Witherspoon had only done a couple of Disney movies, like A Far Off Place.
And if you remember those early ones, which had the bear, Jack the Bear.
Yeah. Man and the Moon, which is a great movie.
And he said she got it.
She just kept like looking at him like, I think this is a comedy.
But they never talked about it.
But there was just something weird.
Said Kiefer did not get it.
And when he saw he never told him they were in a comedy or that it was a black
comedy or that it might even have any comedic elements.
So he said when Kiefer Sutherland saw the picture of the grandma
and it's that very like David Lynch grandma with like the bun
and her hair and everything, he went off the handle and was like,
is this a fucking joke?
Are we do play?
This is where I'm a child molester and the movie's a fucking joke.
Like and I get it.
I get how that would be really scary to be handling that really intense
subject matter and not know the tone. Right.
And this Matthew Bright was a big drug addict and kind of off his rocker.
So I'm sure he felt even more
uneasy about it.
But yeah, the movie is in a nutshell, it's a Little Red Riding Hood story.
It's Reese Witherspoon is going to her grandmother's house.
Well, she's well, she the reason she's going to her grandmother's house
is because her mother, played by Amanda Plummer,
has been arrested yet again for prostitution.
Her stepfather absolutely is having sex with her in some way. Yeah.
And her her stepfather is also arrested when the mom gets busted
because they find crack pipes because they free base right in front of her.
Yes. She her parole officer played by the lady from two and a half men.
Chata Farrell. Yeah, she shows up.
She's going to have to send her back into the system, as they call it,
to foster care.
She's been abused and molested in that situation.
She doesn't want to do it.
So she eludes the the
probation officer in order to get to her grandmother's house.
Yes, who lives in a trailer.
She's never met her, but she thinks that that that could be her salvation.
That's family she can go to. Right.
And then along this journey is scooped up by Kiefer,
who turns out to have ulterior motives, even though he is trying to
he's presenting himself as trying to help her. Right.
They also established that the I -5 killer is on the loose.
And he's playing Bob Wolverton.
It's not subtle with its no illusions, but I
weirdly Kiefer has never done anything for me in anything.
I don't care about him.
I don't I just don't care about him.
He wasn't my guy.
And then when I was growing up, I just never thought anything about him.
But I really loved him in that freaking Friedkin's
court martial movie that was just on show.
And you can use my thing and watch that, too.
I gave him my blog.
But I thought he was just great in it.
And then I suddenly was like, oh, this guy's been a great character actor.
Yeah, I love the American remake.
It's not as good, but I love the remake of The Vanishing,
where he kind of like him in this movie.
I mean, Kiefer and Stand By Me is one of the great bullies.
True. I'll give you that in cinema history.
He's great. I've always been a big Kiefer fan.
He's really, really good and creepy in this.
And eventually, you know, he tries to assault Reese Witherspoon.
She gets one over on him.
We learned that he is married to Brooke Shields.
Brooke Shields coming in in a wild, like almost like cameo.
Yeah, she she blows her brains out.
I was like, holy cow.
You know, I remember this was one I was 16 when it came on a video.
I would have been 17.
And maybe it was one of the first R rated movies I watched on my own.
And I was like, are they all going to be like this?
Because I hadn't seen so much of it.
But this one is a it's a hard R that had to do a lot of cuts.
And they were like, there's no nudity in it.
There's no nothing.
There's that shot of the girl standing up with no underwear
and the tight shorts with her camel toe. Right.
And maybe that's fake. I don't know.
But it's it does just exude.
Nastiness.
There's something about it much for me.
The first half, I watched it this morning
because I didn't have time prior to this, so I watched it this morning
before coming over to record. Yeah.
And I texted Pat that this was not a good move
to try to watch this in the morning.
You said it gets funny.
And I was like, you're out of your mind.
There's no way this is going to get funny.
And then as you said that.
It was the scene where Keifer Reese gets went over on him,
as Pat says, by she's got a gun, she shoots him, she thinks he's dead.
She leaves him for dead.
He lives and gets himself to a hospital.
He's in a hospital. He's got bandages all over him.
He's bleeding out. He's dying.
There's the team doctors.
Dan Hedaya, always great to see him also included.
Yeah. Dan Hedaya comes in as the detective trying to find this I -5 killer.
Yeah. Doesn't know Keifer is the killer is trying to figure out
who did this to him because they pick up Reese Witherspoon. Right.
As a suspect.
And he says to Keifer, is this amidst all this craziness,
is this the woman that shot you?
Yeah. He holds the picture up.
And it is such an absurd picture of Reese Witherspoon.
Hilarious. Yes.
It's it's a it is a laugh out loud moment.
And I was like, I guess this is about to get funny.
And then that's followed by the entrance of Brooke Shields.
Yeah. Being like, wow, centered in a goddamn chair.
Yeah. And you know what?
Yeah. That since that guy was on heroin throughout the whole movie,
the guy who is telling all these stories about the movie on the on these blu rays,
he's clean now.
My guess is he showed Keifer that picture of Reese Witherspoon
and Keifer flipped out because the grandma picture is funny, but not like that.
The Reese Witherspoon.
That's like a Christopher Guest joke.
Like, it's absurd.
I can guarantee he's got him and he's probably in all that makeup.
And he's sitting there after six hours in the makeup chair.
And he shows him the Reese Witherspoon.
And he probably freaked out just like he did in the movie.
Like, oh, so I'm in a fucking comedy.
He's probably also saying,
why would the detectives be coming to show me this picture
as the doctors are working on me and I'm screaming?
Like, yeah, it's so insane.
It's very heightened.
The man does not know.
And I've watched I'm going to watch Tiptoes too,
but he doesn't know how to make a boring scene.
And I will take that, as I've said on the show many times,
I will take a movie that's not boring over a movie that is good, but dull
or like technically fine, but dull.
And this movie is like super alive.
I think it's all about Witherspoon and Sutherland.
You'll never see Witherspoon do anything like this again.
She's tried to have it scrubbed from her record.
Really screams the N word in it at a few points.
She'd so she yes, she screams the book.
That's an interesting scene with the with the two cops,
because when the black cop is saying to her.
Well, he's just doing good cop, bad cop.
Never my answer, my own question, because he's prodding.
The movie doesn't let her off the hook.
She is racist in it and her.
But her fiance's black.
It's a very, very weird.
I'm not saying I'm not in any way justifying what she says.
I'm just saying, like, it's a very weird line they tread
because she's absolutely in love with Bokeh and Woodbine.
She's she is the love of her life.
And then she screams that stuff at the cop.
And it's obviously crazy.
But then she says, you didn't like that.
I don't like being reduced to being called a whore.
Because he basically says you're a whore.
And then it's a can I say that's what I love very challenging scene
because you're like, it's it's it's it's, you know, it's not just her.
It's not just her saying a crazy thing to a person.
Right. With with nothing behind it.
She says it and you don't agree with it.
But at the same time, you're like, is she racist?
Or is she just trying to make a point or, you know?
Well, she also says it to the John, the John who's talking to her dad
at the beginning or to her mom. I'm sorry.
The there's a black guy that Amanda Plummer's told her.
Her mom says her mom said so. OK.
Her mom's aren't racist, which I'm almost like, is that is that in there
to to to say, see, that's different.
The mom is actually racist.
I'm sure it is. But also, I know people.
That's why I think this movie is such a great like character study.
I know people in Missouri for sure who would only fuck black guys,
but were at their core deeply racist or, you know,
and the cops at the black cop says that that she says it to. Yeah. He goes.
What does he call her? A coal smoker or something like that?
It's a term I had not heard, but yeah.
And then Dan and I was like, what are you talking about?
He goes, it means she only dates black guys. Yeah.
And that somehow tips it.
Oh, that's what it is.
He realizes that and then that tips him off on.
She's telling the truth about not fucking Keith or right here.
Oh, that's right.
Because in the interrogation, he's saying all the provocative things
are about being a prostitute because he's trying to figure out,
like, were you turning tricks and did you just rob this guy
or did he actually do something?
And when he realizes, holy shit, she only dates black guys,
he then goes, I have to go back to the crime scene.
He realizes, wait, she she she she wasn't trying to fuck you.
He was being inappropriate. And then.
At the end.
They're like buddies.
Remember, they were the who?
The black cop that she says the crazy. Oh, yeah.
And Reese, she murders.
She gets to the grandmoms house finally. Yeah.
Kiefer is now on her trail, now fully physically deformed from her
self -defense attack on him with a with a what is that called?
Voice box thing.
Well, what what everyone remembers about freeway and that was even on the box,
I think, but it's that shot and they got it so right of Kiefer
with almost an Elvis lip, like fucked up mouth and face.
And then I laughed so hard when he walks into the courtroom.
I remember laughing when I was 16 and I remember laughing now, obviously,
but with the head, oh, you got to hit with the ugly stick when he comes in.
And she's like, wow.
And then keeps making fun of him as he walks in with the head brace and everything.
But then so it's her making fun of him, which is so funny.
But then it's also her lawyer going like, what are you fucking nuts?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. It's like we're in a courtroom. Yeah.
But I like that she has a code like that's a true character.
Her using the N word and so I mean, Tarantino can talk about all this shit.
Like that character would whatever.
But that's what's so fascinating about this Reese Witherspoon character
is that you're not really supposed to love her.
You know, nobody in the movie is a lovable person. No.
But but they do somehow establish her.
Yeah. And the two cops as people you're rooting for.
They end it with almost a freeze frame.
That's what I was getting at. Yeah.
She shows she gets to the house. Kiefer Sutherland's there.
He murders. She murders him.
And there's the nudity.
I forgot that is her grandma is tied up with her tits out and her legs spread open.
And she walks out of the trailer.
The cops realize they walk in.
They Dan had eyes got that great thing.
Yeah, he sees the dead body, sees the grandma dead.
Then he sees his key for death.
And he just keeps going as he sees each new detail.
He goes, holy shit. Yeah. Holy shit. Yeah.
Holy shit. It's ridiculous.
They walk out of the trailer.
The cops are like basically like you did our job for us.
Yeah, looks up, exhales and goes, do you all got a cigarette?
And they all start laughing and it freeze frames
like Colombo episode style.
Yeah. Which is the second movie I've watched this month.
The other was Injustice for All, where that movie ends with Pacino
looking directly into camera and it freeze frames.
Sully is the worst actual freeze from the ending I've ever seen
with the Clint Eastwood movie.
But I rewatched the Cisco and Ebert talking about Freeway.
They both loved it.
They both raved about Witherspoon and Sutherland.
And I just I wound up watching it with.
Joe Bob, he had a lot of great information about it.
I watched both of these four K's and I really recommend
if you have any interest in the movies,
because the documentaries are so in -depth, they interview
everybody involved with the production of the movie.
But I just think Freeway is fucking great.
And it reminds me of that era of independent film.
This was this was right around the time of like Fargo.
Happiness, you movies that aren't even talked about anymore.
Uly's Gold and the Spitfire Grill and all this shit.
Yeah. And even when they were bad, they were good.
It's it's I was going to say that this this is very of.
Excuse me, this is very of the era feels right in line with Reservoir Dogs.
You know, Pulp Fiction is the one that kind of blew the lid off of everything.
And then all of a sudden, indie films got a lot shinier.
Yeah, a lot more produced.
The indie companies got scooped up by the by the major studios and blah,
blah, blah, blah, blah.
But this feels very much still in that in that pocket of of
what was Link Letters first movie Slacker, Slacker.
And it's got that, you know, it's got that it's got that grit to it.
I mean, I watched the stream on shutter and it's it is gritty.
Like it is like the 4K is is insanely gritty.
Like it's it's a very grainy film, obviously.
And it was made for three million, which is not nothing.
And those, you know, those weren't big stars that Kiefer was a big star.
He got the movie made.
But and crazed that he was a bigger deal than Travolta at the time
or Witherspoon or Witherspoon. Yeah.
But I just think
you're seeing sort of both of them at their best.
They have especially like the 20 minute sequence of their like
meet cute of getting to know each other.
It's just great, completely believable dialogue
performed by two really great character actors.
Whether when Witherspoon left that character actor thing behind
to become a romcom person.
Man, I think we lost
we lost something pretty special because it's not like like Aniston
and all the people, Julia Roberts.
They were never character actors.
Reese Witherspoon started as a fucking legitimate character
actors and then stopped and did she was Holly Haunter.
Yeah. And did did an early on.
Did did like some some grittier stuff and then
kind of went back to it with soul surfer or whatever the fuck
that was called, like where she at least was doing a heavier surfer.
Not soul, sir. Wild, wild.
Yeah. Soul Surfer is about the girl gets her arm bit off.
Wild was literally just a woman walking through the wilderness, finding herself.
But my point is, is at least it wasn't like I got to move back to Alabama.
You know, you know, there wasn't that movie.
Old boyfriend lives there.
Yeah. And he's the sheriff now.
Yeah. Anyway, I I was was had mixed emotions through through Freeway.
But but in the end, I did enjoy it.
I I would I would revisit it.
But but, you know, I'd have to be in the right mood, but I would revisit it
and I would consider a purchase.
So I would say my hog is up for Freeway.
Freeway is a movie that has been growing on me since it came out.
I feel like every time I revisited, I like it more.
And it just reminds me of a time of indie movies where there was some really
awful and unpleasant and.
Gross things in movies that people got
like their worst thoughts and desires and put them on to film.
And I think we really lost something there.
Obviously, happiness is not a movie I would recommend to everybody.
Obviously, Freeway is not a movie I would recommend to everybody, but.
I miss the sense of danger
that you get in watching a movie where somebody is just letting their
freak flag fly.
I think that's a great way of putting it.
I would say Freeway is a movie I might not watch over and over again,
but it's a movie I'm happy exists.
And these kinds of things should be able to be made.
So another quick, fun fact that I had to share.
Because we always love practical shit on the show, but they had done
several six hour makeup tests for Kiefer for how bad his face gets fucked up.
And they said a couple of them, he came out after like six hours
in the trailer and everybody laughed at him because it looked so funny and stupid.
And he kept getting madder and madder because he's like, then my whole
so my whole day is wasted.
If it's just a joke that he clearly was having some trouble with the tone.
But when Reese starts having those like fantasies and not fantasies,
but the bad nightmares, they use those screen tests.
OK, so like when you see his face get stretched like the sound
garden video, that's actually just different tests.
So that was kind of cool. That's cool.
But yeah, really, even when I don't care about the movie,
when when they give you those in depth looks where everybody's
telling stories from the set, where it's warts and all,
where it's telling stories about people that fucked each other and hated each other.
I love that.
And these freeway movies both have some of the best
documentaries I've ever seen along those lines.
Check them out. I love this movie.
This movie makes me very hard, not the content of it, but my hog is up.
Folks, I will be on the road, as I said, South by Southwest.
Come see Salsa Windfall.
We're doing a big show on the 12th of March.
March 15th, Portland, Oregon, 16th,
Seattle, Washington, April 12th in Beacon, New York,
April 19th, Wilmington, Delaware and May 3rd, Hampton, Connecticut.
There's probably one or two other shows popping up
before the summer hits, but this is kind of the final run
before before I go inside for the for the summer.
So I hope to see out there all tickets and show links
and all that at Joe DeRosa dot com.
And if you're in New York, come to Joey Rose's seven days a week,
1130 a .m. every day, Joey Rose's dot com.
The Patrick Walsh on Instagram.
Not sure we're doing next month, but I imagine we'll do Dune Part Two.
I do kind of want to go see a big IMAX movie.
You know, it's been a while.
I will not be seeing that with a gun to my head.
OK, well, then it'll just be me.
I can't believe I forgot to tell you this. What?
Burying the lead.
I did the Not Today Pal podcast, the two Sopranos kids.
What the hell? I did their podcast.
And you tell them you had not really seen the show.
I told them I said, guys, I got to get off my chest.
We're going to have a bad show.
I don't like the sopranos.
Like, I'm not saying it to be inflammatory.
I'm sure they loved having a guest that they could bite into something.
Jamie, Jamie was like, I told them before.
And Jamie was like, she was like, you know, Rob has never seen it. Right.
Yeah. And he's like, yeah, I don't care.
And then she was like, we don't care. It's not a sopranos podcast.
And I was like, guys, I swear to you, I'm not saying it to be inflammatory.
I have to get off my chest or it's going to distract me the whole time.
Because I do a podcast where I've talked about that at length.
And if if I don't fess up. Right.
I'm going to get shit. Right.
And it was really fun.
They were really and it was fun because Jamie would be.
It just came out like today.
Yeah. Whenever I see clips of them, I'm like, I didn't know how much I like these two.
On the show, they're kind of annoying, but they're really, really lovely.
And she she was like, she's like, well, which ones have you seen?
And I was like, I was like, you know, man,
I started with that one where he hallucinates the woman.
And she's like, that's a terrible episode to start.
I go, Jamie, I know you made so many mistakes heard it all before.
And then I was like, I saw the finale. I liked it.
And they were like, so you like the finale?
I was like, I know I've heard this all before.
We talked about it at like length.
They were very, very, very, very cool, very cool.
So shouts out to both of them.
Really cool people. Anyway, I should have told you that earlier.
No, that's great. I'm very jealous.
Thank you, everybody. We'll be back next month.
We'll see you next time and we'll see you in hell.