Welcome to We'll See You in Hell, it's your favorite movie talking about genre
comedy flicks, drama flicks, action flicks, all kinds of flicks. I'm Joe DeRosa.
I'm Patrick Walsh. This week we're talking to you about a comedy slash kind
of documentary or at subsequent movie film and then it has you know 20 more
words like that Fiona Apple album but I don't know what they are. Yeah well it's
not important. I don't think he knows what they are. No but yes how are you
Joseph? You know I'm struggling these days with everything. Yeah not something
really crystallized how shit everything is for me. I've been watching a lot of
reruns of Carson. Uh -huh. Johnny Carson and there there you know it's it's a lot
of the interviews that I'm seeing are from the 80s some of them from the 70s
and you know there's a lot of talk of like you know booze and all that sort of
thing and it's it's not shamed or anything it's you know Gleeson's out
there getting shit -faced you know. Yeah. Ed McMahon's coming in drunk. Full
conversation between Carson and who was it about well it doesn't matter but this
is what I'm getting to. There's an episode where he interviews Robin
Williams which only reiterated to me or reinforced my opinion that Robin
Williams is the least funny human being that ever lived but that's besides the
point. Uh -huh. Carson and him are talking about cocaine it's 1982 Robin Williams is
clearly joking in the sense that he does do cocaine. Yeah. Because that's right
around right before Belushi died so that's when he was still you know having
a good time. Right. And then it goes to commercial because I'm watching this on
Pluto on the Pluto TV app so the Pluto TV app actually has commercials on it so
it goes to commercial and the commercials are modern because they're
modern commercials to sustain the app right. Yeah. So when it goes to commercial
it's a commercial where five different teenagers talk about the dangers of
vaping and how nobody's gonna control me I'm gonna be who I want to be and I'm
not gonna vape anymore because it ruined my life and I go fuck everything. Yeah.
These little pussies I mean Jesus Christ this is this is where we're at this is
this is why entertainment sucks now this is why everything sucks everybody's a
fucking pussy anymore I mean Jesus Christ Almighty this is what kids are
worried about vaping it's gonna it's gonna get worse before it gets better
and then it'll then there'll be a big overhaul a big sea change but but it's
gonna be a rough five years in terms of entertainment for sure. What could the
dangers of vaping be by the way? They're not talking about weed vaping they're
just talking about vaping. I remember talking to my therapist about it once
she's like the only way that like vaping or even being a pothead can like really
ruin you as if it's taking your motivation but she said like there are
people who wake up do a shot of a hit of vape and then throughout the rest of
their day they can't go five minutes without hitting the vape so then in that
state you're never not altered in some way unless you're vaping nicotine that's
what they were talking about they're not talking about weed vape they're talking
about like vape like a vape shop yeah then I don't know how that ruins your
life but I do know that that people you know it's the same thing as cigarettes
in the oral fixation you can get hooked but it's like you know there are worse
things you could do. As I drink a wine at three o 'clock in the afternoon yeah yeah
I don't know but anyway other than that I'm good I've been having fun I've been
writing a lot of horror fiction yes so that's been enjoyable I'm gonna bring
some of that to the people at some point hopefully soon and that's kind of how
I've been spending my time like writing some horror fiction playing super hot on
my oculus quest for exercise which is a John wick style game and it's so fun and
you actually sweat yeah you really work up a sweat like shooting weird -looking
mannequins that are trying to kill you it's very fun and also horrifying when
you turn around and there's a guy behind you with like a knife yeah you're like
ah so I've been doing that watching a lot of movies as always playing some
video games and then you know who are we kidding the activity that's taking up
the most amount of time is the booze uh -huh sure heavy ciggy intake these
days too a lot of booze a lot of smokes okay so I'm slowly turning into what's
face and I knew it would always head this way who's the guy that was like
skin and bones that lived till he was like 98 it was on William William S
Burroughs no no no no the guy from Twin Peaks oh yeah you think they're like the
man's man actor that everybody loved oh Harry Dean Stanton yes I'm going Harry
Dean Stanton over here look he lived a great life by all accounts yeah so
anyway I don't want to be too repetitive because we touched on some of the stuff
on the last episode but the big takeaway here is again booze followed by kids are
awful and nobody does any real drugs anymore I had been eating clean working
out hardcore etc and then you know the wife left she went with a friend of
hers they did the quarantine and they're at a national park type week so yeah I
was telling Joe yesterday I woke up and I was like I just wake up some days and
I feel like my head is on fire and like the rest of the day is literally hi he's
in LA folks yes and the rest of the day is spent trying to put the fire out all
by doing things that are in the long run worse for you than just leaving your
head on fire anyway I drove straight up to I haven't had the last time I had a
doughnut Joe was when you and I went to see that Jacqueline Novak dick sucking
stand -up show it was a show about sucking dick right yeah this was a funny
way to put it there was a lot of blowjob material that show I remember that the
show was called like get on your knees with Jacqueline Novak whatever I mean it
about blowjobs but um you and I after wandered off went to some abandoned
doughnut shop and at that was 11 p .m. I had this giant apple fritter that that
night was the night that set me out of LA that was I get that I get that we we
left that show and we wandered in a part of LA that should have things yeah for
25 minutes desperately trying to find a bar and all we found was the worst
doughnut shop that has ever existed and we sat there drinking coffee out of
styrofoam cups and eating really really bad doughnuts and that I think that
might have been the night I was like fuck this place I can't do this anymore
like I need a bar every three feet I was there too but then I stayed we also if
before the concert had the that remember that queso dip yeah it was the worst
Mexican meal I've ever had that place is legendary in downtown LA as being this
amazing Mexican restaurant and it was so shit it's not downtown though it's um
it's it's what part of town is that it's we went to the dynasty typewriter so
whatever that echo park but it's it's close enough that you're very close to
downtown we got a queso dip that ran us I think $17 I mean it was the most
expensive queso dip of all time yeah it was literally people I am not
exaggerating literally they took a brick of like Cracker Barrel come fuck
cracker bro that was like government cheese you know jack cheese like
white white jack whatever the fuck it was and just melted it but didn't turn
it any in any way into a queso they didn't like cream it up so you could dip
it so as we were eating it we realized not only is this flavorless it's free
forming into a block of cheese yeah and then it just got to this point where
you were like you had to like cut cut it with a knife and put it like shove it
chip oh that sucked it seemed alive in a way but like that the the other
infuriating thing about it is that in both cases the queso and the apple
fritter you know you're I forgot you went to you went to get an apple fritter
that was in the morning because you didn't get there we sidestepped into I'm
gonna get back there like that night the queso and the apple fritter in both
cases when you have these items when you add them to your diet melted cheese and
an apple fritter if you can call that a diet you want you need not only want you
need them to be amazing because you're have you're adding so many calories so
much fat so much terrible things for your body in one sitting that you need
it to be as amazing as you want it to be when you go to the store you're the only
reason you're getting those things is to help give you some semblance of
happiness mm -hmm and both of them were so bad that I completely understand why
that was a line in the sand for you with LA they were so bad but um well then
also too and then going to see like the 16th show that year yeah of a comedian
being wholly celebrated as you sit there you know thinking about the screenplay
rejected 18 times you're just like I can't take any of this anymore yeah it's
too much yeah I mean by the way this wasn't a bad show or something went to
Broadway it was nothing against Jacqueline who I don't know but she's
very funny she's a friend I'm just saying like it was just one of those
nights where you're like I just can't this this environment is not good for me
anymore no we were we were both I don't even remember us talking while we had
that coffee and the doughnut there was a real sense of of defeat in the air and
LA is great for this LA is great for this if they could somehow make a
business out of this it'd be there at second Hollywood it is great for if you
ever wanted to walk down block after city block and see every through every
90 seconds something that it looks like it's going to be a bar and then is like
an insurance agency or something I mean LA is real good at that and around that
dynasty typewriter I'm sure somebody knows to get a bar over there stat
because that place is popping as a venue now but like it it's always in these
areas where you need a bar like a bar would do so well there's people
wandering the streets looking for anything and it's just not there it's a
lot like when you try to get a parking spot then you find out there's a moped
in the front of the parking spot I think we even tried to go back to the
Mexican place to get a drink because we knew they had a bar and it was closed at
like 830 yeah well it's Sunday you know remember they also had that really
terrible mariachi band and it's like boy you can't even do that right like
usually that's the fun part oh yeah we kept laughing about that because we're
we're sitting there eating a meal that's the meal was like it was it was
terrible and I think it ended up costing us like $95 or so it was like so over
It was insanely expensive yeah and we're the only people in the restaurant and on stage is a 16
piece mariachi band doing a full concert and I remember laughing about like the
board meeting at the restaurant guys we got to cut costs where do we look just
a suggestion maybe we shave that mariachi band yeah what if we take the
fourth drum bonus off the payroll and put a little money into buying edible
cheese to serve to our patrons follow me I'm gonna take the dog for a walk but
just follow me we're gonna get there exactly yeah no it's so anyway so you
wake up the other day oh I mean that now there's really no story but I I woke up
and I was like like I have to like I said put the fire out and I wasn't gonna
it was very early I went up I saw daily donuts a donut shop one minute from my
house that I have never been into because donuts is a food that I have to
pretend doesn't exist yeah yeah I have that same problem I got a place two
blocks from my apartment yeah but I don't want to say the name of it because
I don't want to give away where I live but it's really causing me a problem man
and they were shut down for a while because of the parking and now they're
open again and I was like this is the last fucking thing I need right now man
like anyway yeah well I know I mean that night that you and I went that was
probably about a year ago maybe even more but I haven't had a donut since you
know like my family was always one of those that would get a dozen after
church yeah and then you're almost just in a coma the second you're done with
breakfast it's no way to start the day you know it's it's a back -to -bed kind of
breakfast a donut that was his breakfast every day he'd eat donuts at work
that was his breakfast at work and then would work sometimes a two -job day yeah
it's it's they were just wired differently at the back they really were
men were different my dad would wake up an hour before going into work
every day to warm his car up he'd have to go out and warm the car and then like
sit inside waiting for it anyway they were of harder stock right I go in it's
a lovely Chinese couple donut shops in Los Angeles there are for whatever reason
thousands of them or more than bars there are donut shops you never see more
than one person in them they're everywhere they always look like the
donut shop in boogie nights that Don Cheadle goes into they're all they're
all 70s style they're all really beautiful once you get inside yeah yeah
they have that vibe of you know yeah I love being in them but I hadn't been in
a year or so I go up to the guy I'm like give me an apple fritter and this is
this and maybe you relate to this Joe maybe you don't but when you're at a
donut shop or any place like this when the guy is reaching I so desperately
want to say no no no the huge one up in the front but I always just let him pick
the small one that he's gonna pick but I'm like you're gonna throw these away
anyway when they're not just give me that huge one not only can I relate to
it I have no problem saying no no I want that one I should it's it's Irish
Catholic shit or shame or something but I never say what I want to say and I
watch him grab this little one and then I almost said you know what I'll take
another because I'm used to the apple fritters in st. Louis being the size of
a catcher's mitt right huge you know like a day -long affair but I'm like okay
just get the one and then I saw my other favorite which is the cake doughnut
that's like a almost like a blackboard eraser size the one that's just like the
traditional doughnut you mean no it's a it's like a brick it's like a rectangle
okay it's it's perfect for dunking in a coffee but I don't know quite how to
explain it it's a cakey doughnut as opposed to I have no interest or no need
in my life for the doughnut that you bite into and it's just like soft and
airy there's well yeah so okay so a traditional doughnut like if you go to
Dunkin Donuts they have like yeah they're they're labeled like old -fashioned
doughnuts that's the old -fashioned yes yes I mean that is we've talked about
the man at length that is the Dabney Coleman doughnut that's the one he's
eating a hundred percent for sure yeah and and you know it's probably worse
because it's so heavy there's just got to be more in it yeah yeah it's a it's a
delicious doughnut and I got both I sat in my car and ate them and dipped dip
them in the coffee and that's one of those mornings a you know I hadn't had a
drink in three weeks or something so it hits you way harder the next day and all
that and that was one of those days just sitting parked eating doughnuts and
where I almost just started crying just sitting there and if I'm not mistaken
because I used to live by there at one point when I was in LA that is in the
same shopping center as the drawing room or is it is a is it one shopping center
up it's it's not only in the same one as the drawing no it's not it's one up but
it's right by the drawing room and it's also by La Pergoletta where I ate that
meal flies yes yeah and then you rustic so that's insult to injury is now you're
also seeing bars that you could go into like in the old days and have fun and
you can't I was never you know I've done some shameful fucking shit in my life I
have never once thought I need to go up to the drawing room at like 9 a .m. I've
never been that guy part of it said I guess I don't care about sports that's
usually why people pretend all right I did it once but here's why I was up all
okay let's say certain things may or may not have been involved we weren't vaping
that's not what kept us awake okay and at 6 a .m. the Sun was coming up and I
said you know the drawing room is open she goes let's go and we went in there
at 6 a .m. yeah it was half full already mm -hmm and there was a woman in there
that hated me so much that she yelled across the bar you're the reason Donald
Trump is president I don't remember what I said yeah I don't remember what I did
to piss her off to that point but I said something man that that and she got it
she got a bug in her fucking crawl for me man and she was stinking me and then
like once that started you know I'm like it's like telling a little kid don't
touch that I'm just I just start being an asshole now and yeah I got her I got
her angry enough to the point that she said you're the reason Donald Trump got
elected I've only seen that antagonizing side of you when I came to see you do
stand -up in Vegas in the very hostile room and I watched you turn and then the
whole show I kept wanting to be like Joe just go back to the jokes but you kept
going after that woman it was very funny but you I watched something snap and you
never really got back on track you just totally went on into that lady for the
rest of the time yeah that was that was the I was opening for Bobby Slayton I
think right oh yeah it was a very fun show fun weekend yeah that was that's
the weekend we saw sticks yeah that was great yeah yeah that's fun made a fan
out of me the it when I was a kid Paul's Donuts was the big move and Paul's
Donuts were like X I still I've been chasing that high ever since but they
they had a well there's the the custard filled which is the kind of gross almost
like a tapioca pudding filling uh -huh that I have no interest in and then they
had angel that's well that's a Boston cream with the chocolate icing on top
yeah my favorite donut of all time the Dunkin Donuts Boston cream is my favorite
donut of all time that custard is just it's just not it doesn't dazzle me I
got you sure but uh you know I I'll take a jelly over a custard like a powder
jelly or a sugar gel I don't mean to keep interrupting you but no please like
a I like a sugar jelly personally over the powder jelly I like yeah though the
wet wetter jelly yeah where it looks like it's tan with just wet sugar yeah
that's right yeah yeah now the angel cream would be the giant like you know
catcher's mitts style donut with chocolate on top but then what they did
with the angel cream was you watch them put in an icing bag like for the sheet
cake the most delicious you know my last meal will be a sheet cake they plug in
tip and then go and blow up to where you see it expanding like a frog who's
eaten something it blows up full of this frosting like cake frosting and I would
get two of those yeah those I did I do we were allowed to and I so I'd have one
on that Sunday and then one on that Monday to kick off my week of school and
I would be a comatose I I'll tell you something I did go on excuse me right
before a pandemic hit I was living in the East Village was when I first moved
back to New York I walked was a Sunday and it was an oddly warm February Sunday
it was like 61 degrees my favorite kinks song by the way an oddly warm February
Sunday right yeah yeah it was like 61 degrees or something on a Sunday so I it
might have even been in January so I walked all the way yeah none of us care
for Christ's sake you were trying to nail down this month for four minutes
yeah I'm sorry I'm sorry Jesus I'm coming unraveled pet what do you want
I know I forgot are we recording something right now yeah I so I walked
all the way to Mulberry Street walk through Little Italy well no sorry first
walked to Chinatown sat down got a three entree Chinese meal cuz I couldn't
decide I spent $60 on lunch uh -huh ate barely any of it it was way too much
obviously yeah then walked into Little Italy walked up Mulberry Street I was
like I'm gonna be bad and get a cannoli so I get a cannoli I eat it as I'm
walking doesn't it was delicious didn't hit the spot though needed more go to a
Dunkin Donuts in the East Village attempt to give the Chinese food to a
homeless man who yeah no thank you I'm strictly vegan which led to me tweeting
offered Chinese food to a homeless man today he said no thanks I'm strictly
vegan hey might want to loosen up the reins on that diet big guy which got me
shit on Twitter how dare you criticize a homeless man's eating habits I was like
well I just think you know you loosen it up a little bit yeah so then I go into
Dunkin Donuts and I get my special my special at Dunkin Donuts is chocolate
glazed you know which is the chocolate cake donut but with the glaze frosting on
regular glazed a Boston cream and a sugar jelly that's my four horsemen of
the apocalypse and you're doing on top of a cannoli on top of a cannoli and
let's not leave out the three course Chinese meal yeah which I'm sure wasn't
light on sugar right right I then need to stop at Dwayne Reed to get some like
toiletries or something I thought you're gonna say to violently spray the toilet
with diarrhea I'm so embarrassed about that I'm about to eat these doughnuts
slash I'm so excited to eat them yeah I decide the best strategy is stand in
denial inside of Dwayne Reed and eat all four of them Lord and when I tell you
these things I love Dunkin Donuts I can't say a bad thing about it those
donuts go down like shots dude I mean it's like I wouldn't go to Dunkin if it
was the last option on earth why is that I think they do shit donuts all right
fair enough good coffee shit donuts my favorite in all of LA is the donut shop
it's got like an Asiany sort of flavor but they sell Americanized doughnuts
there's it's a chain it's that Winchell's it's they're all there well
Winchell's is good I mean like it's I don't know it always feels weird to say
but I don't understand it I love it but all of these places are Asian run and
all of these places are usually a couple you know like it's almost always the
exact same dynamic and I just feel like they do way better donuts at those
places then you'll find at a Dunkin or any of the chains I just googled
Donut shops Los Angeles holy god Pete Holmes said to me once it was his
favorite commentary he'd ever heard about LA so one of his friends said I
don't like LA and Pete said why and he goes too many rogue donut shops which is
very true it's weird well there's the one Heather got me one year for my
birthday and I could not stomach even one of them it was a very sweet gesture
but it's from this place where they do like almost like each one is its own
creation you know like that the candy bar swirl it'll have like five Twix in
it and a crunch and a Reese's Peace and so I can't do it I'm sorry I'm not I'm
not 12 anymore I don't like that style of donuts I've never liked that I can't
stand like there was the famous one out in Highland Park that's that's like you
know it's cool because it's like every doughnuts named after like a punk rock
band right and it's clever and the and the recipes are interesting but I don't
like that kind of stuff I like it's like when you go to a burger place at Yum Yum
Donuts Yum Yum Donuts are amazing that's the place I was thinking I've been there
yeah but it's you know it's like when you go to a burger place and they have
like you know this one you know has an egg and sliced radishes on it and hot
sauce and you're like I just just a cheeseburger please like I don't need
the you know the toppings it's too much for me yeah there's a Bloody Mary place
in Vegas where everyone has like a giant stick coming out of it with four
sliders you know and like a piece of brie cheese and all that it's just
ridiculous it's disgusting it's like I don't a cheese in my drink it's gross
yeah like I'm trying to get drunk at 9 a .m. on a Monday can you can we show a
a bad blackjack hand I'm not feeling too festive right now right yeah I was a
podcast I really love double threat with my my favorite Tom Sharpling and Julie
Klausner has been provided me a lot of laughs that's one I'd recommend but they
did a very a very fun episode that was their favorite cameos by directors and
you know that's usually they don't usually have themes but they just went
with it your favorite cameos by directors and that the eventual choice
and very hard to argue with was the Gary Marshall scene in lost in America with
Albert Brooks where he's trying to get his money back in Vegas which they
played a clip and I was just laughing my ass off like and they they also really
nailed what is there but like I never really took away from it that Albert
Brooks is basically saying to him look we're not like all these other shitty
people here who come to Vegas and lose their money like I'm better than them
yeah that's that's the other like some more subtle joke of it that I missed but
just talking about that scene made me realize like I mean that's a man who's
who's just does some deep comedy you know you can really yeah it gets to the
core of like a human being which I I love yeah yeah that's a great scene I'm
not gonna give you your money back yeah yeah Gary Marshall's accent lends a lot
yeah oh yeah he's the best yeah you can be the place that gives the money back
thing you know then people will want to come here yeah but then they'll expect
their money back I can't give everybody the money back they also mentioned
Scorsese and Taxi Driver which is a much less fun cameo yeah blowing his wife's
face off and then you know Sidney Pollack and Tootsie who I wouldn't have
picked but then they played a clip from it and I laughed so hard at it he's so
funny as Dustin Hoffman's agent but I think Pollack is even better in Michael
Clayton Pollack's a great actor I'm gonna go with that I know you're not a
fan of the movie anymore but I'm gonna go with Rob Reiner in Throw Mama from
the Train when he's not a fan of the movie is too harsh I just didn't like it
as much as I used to when he's getting he's dropping Billy Crystal as the
client as he's telling him that they have signed his wife as their newest
client Billy Crystal's book yeah and and then Billy Crystal you know he's
like you know the whole crux of it is that he wants to be an artist and he
goes and he Rob Reiner goes so go go be an artist on Delaya Reba and then he
hands him that plant he goes there you go it's my favorite fuchsia live and be
well yeah yeah never explained why in the seed he's like moving the plants
around I don't know what the fuck he's even doing like I was I was just assumed
he was moving or something I don't think I have ever in a show seen an agent
character that didn't make me laugh outside of maybe the one that was
supposed to Jeremy Piven and entourage but like my god they Martin Short in
the big picture as the agent I love the agent on extras Stephen Merchant was
always so fucking close Stephen Merchant scenes are just the bloopers of them
trying to get through when the joke is that he writes boobs on the calendar on
the calculator right and them trying to get through like that bit without
laughing is one of my favorite outtakes things I've ever seen them going their
separate ways is I think a real tragedy because I think they had something real
special obviously but and then the agent in the flight of the Concord show was
hilarious I mean there's always a there's always just big laughs I think
because of how much I hate dealing with agents let's not forget Eugene Levy and
for your consideration oh sure but he goes there's nothing going on hey I'm
not gonna sugarcoat it you want sugarcoat and you go to one of the big
agencies we used to do this bit when I wrote for always sunny which was that my
we all shared this agent who was just such a bumbling sweaty guy like just he
was like Jack Lemmon in Glenn Gary Glenn Ross kind of vibe you know like
just like he had flop sweat all over him and we used to do this bit where he was
coming to visit us on set and he kept wanting to say on set it was just a made
up bit and then he got trapped in the the elevator is broken and he's
sweating so he's like ah shit you know I don't want to take the stairs he goes
to the stairs and gets stuck in the stairwell and is just trapped in there
violently sweating and being like boys I need you to I need somebody to help me
out and we used to do this bit all day like him being stuck in there talking to
himself like well you really did it to yourself you really did it to yourself
this time and we'd laugh and laugh because we all know I keep wanting to
say his name which makes it even funnier but I won't but that was gonna be a
story for your character that I was forced to write off but living biblically
I remember you telling me about that storyline and I was so excited that I
was gonna have like my own storyline that was just my share I wanted to shoot
like ten minutes of you getting increasingly sweaty and angry in there
and like just have fun with it add it into the show whenever it needed it and
didn't happen didn't come to be no maybe that's what set me out of LA you
stayed quite a bit longer I did took it like a champ took my first one like a
champ thanks to the great Sarah Gilbert for telling me she's the first one that
texted me when I got when I got canned and she goes happens to everybody this
is just this is not the end it's the beginning this is yes this is a sign
that you're part of the business which she was wrong I'm not part of it no
she's that whole that whole group and I like to think is just because I put them
together were the best they were the best people and then they're they're
wonderful they were wonderful group of people I in fact need to drop everybody
a line I was thinking of Cameron Mannheim the other day and Ferguson I
haven't talked to in a while Krumholz and I were texting the other day yeah we
text them yeah so Krumholz I talked to about once a month but but that whole
crew what a great bunch of people Galecki I gotta drop Galecki or all
those guys I talked to Krumholz Ferguson and Galecki I wish I talked to some of
the others they it was they were also kind of private people Gomez and Tony
Rock and all them not now there's anything wrong with that at all yeah
Tony I see just from comedy right you know but I knew Tony I've known Tony for
20 years had a baby yeah yeah I heard man I heard that's great I want to do a
real quick screaming in about two movie trailers one will have very little to
say I think but have you seen the new trailer for Halloween kills I have it's
it's it was supposed to already be out in theaters now and now it's coming out
next Halloween so a full year away and I guess that's why it was so brief it
was below a minute I didn't get much out of it except I was excited to see
Anthony Michael Hall but I don't even catch him he's in like Edward
scissorhands bully mode it looks like cocking a shotgun and I think he's
playing somebody famous in the Halloween universe I think he's playing Paul Rudd's
character yeah that's the kid that she's babysitting I guess in the first movie I
think okay so that's pretty cool I mean I don't know I saw it I was
underwhelmed but it's just a teaser there was nothing really there to be
whelmed by but I got to say this and I said this to Pinkstone when I was
talking about it I said look man now that they're doing a full trilogy of
these movies I think it's plain stupid that they're not brother and sister I
don't think there's any legs yeah I don't think there are legs to carry Jamie
Lee Curtis's character through four fucking movies including the first one
and her connection to Michael Myers without there being a deeper thing like
I'm just not I'm sorry I'm just not buying it like I don't buy what his
obsession is unless they have some new explanation of why he's so obsessed with
her but I just I don't know I'm just not buying it man well the first one in it
in addition to being I think we both agreed pretty underwhelming it didn't
really set up anything interesting for a franchise there's nothing there was
nothing new to it that made me want to come back my only guess is is that she
is going to become the dr. Loomis yeah where she experienced this guy
firsthand and now she's the one that has to go and warn people like he's coming
it's evil it's this so I'll buy that and maybe they'll do a good job of it but
you know I've said this I said this when we reviewed it my problem with that film
is it was well done and it's it's certainly a good enough of a horror
movie a couple stupid twists I didn't really buy but my biggest problem is is
you know you got Carpenter singing its praises and he's finally involved in
this and that h2o and I'll take this to my fucking grave I don't care h2o is a
better version of that movie it is far more in the spirit of Carpenter's
original film and how that last Halloween did everything that everybody
complained the franchise did in the sequels which was it became a gore fest
it was too sensational you know blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah and I
thought that h2o was a really really tremendous sequel I thought it dealt
with Jamie Lee Curtis's character in a far more interesting way I don't know
Carpenter has become like a Stephen King type figure where he just wants the
money he's happy to get money on things he did years ago and you'll get what he
truly thinks in five years when they're not making the movie anymore then
I'll be like yeah I thought that really sucked
what was the other trailer oh the other trailer for me I thought the big one
this week was songbird I watched this trailer it's so advertised I have no
idea what no I didn't watch it I have no idea what the movie is or I assumed it
was a movie about the worst track on Fleetwood Macs rumors folks the second
worst track the other one being Oh Daddy which is a song so bad it almost ruins
rumors but okay songbird is produced by Mike Bay okay it is a it stars like
people I hadn't heard of and to me more it was a movie that apparently was
conceived written and shot all during this pandemic it's it's coming out very
soon and is completely about the pandemic except it's even more intense
because they're coming into people's homes and capturing them and they're
I'm well I'm not sick I don't have COVID no why on earth would anybody want to
watch that right now I think it is so nuts and that's of course the reaction
to the trailer people are like this is in terrible taste why would I watch this
what's wrong with you it's still happening they used to comment on things
in horror movies but it would be at least a couple years after Vietnam you
know like nobody wants this shit in the middle of it we don't even know if we're
getting out of it that's Michael Bay trying to be Oliver Stone he's trying to
make the movie about the thing as the thing is happening like like stone it
was like W and World Trade and those weren't good movies and they were
Michael Bay you are not Oliver Stone by the way at all you couldn't make his bad
yeah so yeah not interested I have two quick ones as well the first I'll just
get out of the way I will be in the minority with this opinion I'm sure but
very excited to hear that as Zack Snyder's version of the Justice League
moves forward and continues to move forward at HBO Max it's bankrupting HBO
Max from what I hear good he's he is bringing back Jared Leto as a
thank God thank God I like that Joker quite a bit and I wanted to see what it
was supposed to be and I'm pissed off that David Aries movie also got a hatch
a job and we may or may not see what that movie actually is supposed to be
but I'm very happy that he's bringing in leaders Joker and I'm happy that he is
retconning some of these holes that have been left in the DC Universe because of
missteps that DC has made with their own film with their cinematic universe so
they seem to be writing now so that's exciting news for me but the bigger
story this comes via movieweb .com Amazon claims prime video users don't legally
own purchased content saw that yeah yeah buying movies digitally on Amazon prime
video will only get you a limited license to view the content which could
later be removed people look the headline says it all buy your media for
sakes if you're a buff yeah if you're a casual viewer and you don't give a shit
if the movie could go off fall off the face of the earth and you may never see
it again then don't but I mean I would think if you're listening to this
podcast you're probably pretty into movies and I would think that most of you
probably are buying your movies but if you're not you do not rely on these
streaming services don't do it you have to own your content and it's not about
do you put the DVD into the player every time you want to watch the movie it's
not about not using streaming streaming is very convenient and there are more
convenient ways to watch a lot of these movies then getting up opening a DVD
case putting it in the thing switching the input I get it the point is not that
the point is is that when it is not available you have it it's giving you the
option and media is so cheap it's ridiculous how cheap media is getting
because no everybody's turning their back on it so now it's the time to
strike this is gonna go the way of retro video games where you're gonna see in
15 years you know games that were you know by the dozen in boxes at yard sales
where they're like please just take it are gonna be you know that that's what
the now sell for a thousand dollars a piece or whatever because it's a limited
you know it's a finite product as my friend Mike Byrne says that's what's
gonna happen with with movies you know the time is gonna come around where it's
like you want to buy a blu -ray it's gonna be fifty eight dollars for a
fucking movie you know I've been flipping stuff left and right vinyl
albums DVDs and blu -rays and I've been making four or five times what I made
or what I paid to get the item and in some cases it's like why did I ever buy
this to begin with it's not open you know I'm like why did I even have this
and when you find out it's out of print it's the best feeling in the world it's
something you want to sell anyway that you can make really good money on so I
support my spending on Amazon by just flipping shit then you make a trip to
the post office once a week and that's it and not to mention to the editing and
the and the censoring that's going on you know a friend of mine told me he
bought the latest available season of it's always sunny and the D -Day episode
was gone because Frank dresses up as Roseanne Rose whatever her member she
had like the character that was Mexican and it was really important excuse me
and and the point was that it was inappropriate that was the point right
the point was that the other characters like D that's a really racist character
that's probably like that's the point they're not putting it that on DVD it's
not on the DVD it's removed yeah that's really weird this is nuts I mean come on
what the fuck is going on here yeah anyway no it's gonna it's gonna be a
rough five years of entertainment that is for sure they'll be a big drought
coming up sooner than we realize where there's nothing new coming and then
after that everything that comes out will suck because it's the stuff being
made under quarantine and while everyone is panicked about doing anything wrong
anyway let's go to the corner let's go to the corner I'm gonna pick three at
random this week you mentioned Jamie Lee Curtis I watched a movie I've wanted to
see for many many years called Blue Steel starring Jamie Lee Curtis as a
lady cop that was enough to get a movie made back then just a cop who's a lady
and Catherine Bigelow co -wrote and directed the film Catherine Bigelow who
has gone on to become of course one of the biggest directors there is but this
was right after near dark which is a great little vampire movie she did I
think a little bit overrated at this point you know people I think it is are
always going insane about that movie and it's always like okay guys I think
it's kind of a snooze but you know yeah well that there's one I sold my
blu -ray out for 150 bucks I bought it for five dollars she's anyway Blue Steel
is is a fun late 80s action thriller the villain is Ron Silver and he's a guy
who's just like super obsessed with Jamie Lee Curtis at the beginning of
movie she goes in to stop a convenience store robbery and winds up shooting
somebody killing somebody Ron Silver is there in the convenience store and just
becomes obsessed with this woman having this power to take a life away and he's
like a real sicko American Psycho type character so all really is it is a cat
and mouse between the two of them because it is Bigelow it's very very
well shot the actions very well done at the end of the day a pretty average
story okay movie all right I watched a little picture called The Fan starring
Robert De Niro and Wesley Snipes I never saw the film when it was new I was
always curious De Niro took a job as a knife salesman for a month to get a
character I remember that yes I remember that too they said he would come in and
he'd have band -aids on his fingers because he got himself so much I had
never seen the film when it was out I was curious you know you know Wesley
Snipes and Robert De Niro this was also in the from the letter of Cape Fear by
the way writer of Cape Fear directed by Tony Scott yeah and also done in the
time period of De Niro before you know De Niro had that really really bad patch
yeah this was pre that so I'm like okay there's no reason I shouldn't see this
let's put it on what a piece of shit oh my god it's a bad movie and it's not
yeah due to performances this the performances are very well done the
story just sucks the scripts sucks Tony Scott I like as a director but
everything he directs looks like it's under a heat lamp it like a fucking
Popeyes you know what I mean everything is like orange you know so I would
consider him a really solid action director who never made a great movie
never made an eight plus you know I don't even remember like what are some
of Tony's I'm blanking I mean he made Days of Thunder he did he did a run of
good but not amazing Denzel movies man on fire and you know good solid movies
but he just never took it beyond that he did domino which was kind of fun right
this this movie is terrible and so I wasn't surprised to learn that it was
actually mentioned in his suicide note okay yeah that's um it wasn't I'm just
kidding oh I didn't know like it drove him to his biggest it was Top Gun sorry
god I never saw it never saw Top Gun you don't need to see Top Gun couldn't do
one look right I think the new one look it's funny I got excited about the new
having seen the original but anyway Top Gun's fun you know it's it's considered
a classic but it was never my bag but it's a fun movie sure any look there's
really not much more to say this movie sucks it's just a bad movie it's not
worth getting into it was one of the first movies I one of the first r -rated
movies I could rent like it must have come out right when I turned 17 but yeah
not a good movie at all I saw and I've already been chewed out on the on the
letterboxed about it what every time I said on letterbox every time I'm
discussing the best horror movies ever some nerd spins around in a chair and
goes what about pumpkin head oh come on everybody's like ooh yeah pumpkin head
and I had never seen it and I was like all right it's time I bought the the
Dream Factory blu -ray I was like well since this is such a horror classic
obviously I'll just want to own it halfway through I was listing it on
Amazon it's not a good movie I own it I've seen it many times I own the
sequels I've seen those all maybe once in part two is called blood wings blood
wings yes blood wings is what a guy I used to work with at blockbuster video
called going down in a woman who had her period oh you've earned your blood
wings that's how pumpkin it is resurrected in the sequel guy goes down
in the witch yeah it's it's not a good movie I don't understand look I find it
enjoyable enough for two reasons it's a cool monster and and Lance Hendrickson
that's it I what I couldn't believe it didn't have a pumpkin for a head no it
doesn't have a pumpkin for a head it's just like home no matter what this is at
least it's gonna have a sweet pumpkin for a head it didn't nope now it doesn't
now and I and when I tell you that movie is head and shoulders above the three
sequels I mean pumpkin head and shoulders above the three yeah it's not
good and I get I argued it with people it's it's but it's another Jeepers
Creepers it's people think it's great and I'm just like what fucking movie did
you watch man it reminded me quite a bit of Jeepers Creepers but here's the
thing it's worse than Jeepers Creepers one and two I put very few things in the
category of worse than Jeepers Creepers one and two but we've had these
discussions but I mean I thought pumpkin head was bad I thought it was a bad
looking movie it seems like it's covered in a layer of dirt Lance
Hendrickson is not a compelling protagonist I'm sorry I like him
sometimes as a villain but he's kind of a void on camera I'm sorry well in that
movie I hear you I don't think that that's true of him I think in that movie
he's was I guess directed to be a very understated character I mean there's not
a lot to it either there you know that's not like the lines have any depth or
weight you know it's just it was just a lame story it reminded me of like one of
the direct to CBS Stephen King miniseries that nobody talks about anymore
like it just felt like that kind of level and I can't believe people think
it's a classic and then somebody was like weren't you moved when his son died
and then I'm like no I couldn't have been less moved I'm sorry all right yeah
I mean it's I mean yeah moved if you're moved by like the way an 11 year old
would write it I mean it's come on yeah I'm sorry Tony Scott's best movie true
romance oh yeah that is Tony Scott written by Tarantino that's a really
great movie I'll do a controversial one to match you mm -hmm and you're gonna
disagree with this mm -hmm but you pushed me to revisit something and I did little
show called the Sopranos watch the second episode loved it I remember
texting you said all right all right you're right I watched the second up very
good by the fourth episode I was pretty intrigued by the seventh episode I
didn't give a shit if I saw any episode of it ever again I find the show to be
trite stupid stereotypical absurd you know every other episode he's like I'm
like you know like a plot will be like I took my daughter to sleep away camp at
one of the councils like I got a whack worlds are crossing and merging and just
unbelievable ways the priest character that widely considered one of the best
television episode all time hey listen I know and you know not by me I'm just
that the priest character that comes in I mean it's unwatchable you got a guy
that looks yeah the most Anglo -Saxon man I have ever seen in my life supposedly
playing like an Italian priest and trading lines with Carmela like oh come
on nobody's better than Bobby D it's like oh my god man this is this thing
plays like that fucking play we saw with Burt Young I mean it was like it's
ridiculous I will not allow you to make me mad about the Sopranos again I'm not
trying to make you mad I know but he's he's clearly doing a bit a bit there
when he does these that's not him genuinely saying nobody's better than
Bobby D he's no no they talk like that a lot don't like like that that's their
bond is like the priest the priest is kind of saying it as a little I mean
I didn't buy that he like wants to he's in love with the therapist by episodes
like six it's like I don't know man and then the thing the coffee the Starbucks
singing where that idiot with the white wig who's that more on the walnuts yeah
that guy where he's like he's like that idiot with the white wig one of the best
characters in TV history when that guy's like it's not a way these these
gotchas coming to our neighborhood and sell cappuccino that's what a tie is
supposed to go oh my god it's terrible I hate it your issues with it are so
strange because it's also widely beloved by Italians so like you think I would
get it if like Italians were like this isn't real I don't like it but Italians
love it perhaps more than anyone if you think I'm gonna sit here and say that
Italians don't have as many stupid people among them as every other group
of people I'm not well people can be dumb I what you're referring like I
think the pilot is the worst episode of the show but I mean like pilot sucks
there's a cuteness about the mobsters because originally the show was pitched
as like a Simpsons set in the mob and it was passed on by every network and it
began so I think there's a little bit of cuteness in the jokes of the first
season that goes away I think the first season is great and gets better as it
goes but for me three is the best season followed by four back to two but I
really think it gets deeper and better as it goes if you're not gonna go there
with it don't go there with it I know when you watch all this shit and I watch
shit too it's no judgment while the Sopranos sits there I just don't like
the show I don't I hear you I that's why I gave it you made a great argument you
you're sitting there watching and it was like Clark's the animated series
ridiculous watching and you're like what are you doing yeah watch the Sopranos so
I was like okay and I did and I was really in like after that first second
up watching that second episode I was like all right I was wrong and then by
the time I got to like like I said like seven or eight maybe it was even ten or
eleven I just was like it's doing all these things and I'm trying to fight it
but these are these are all it's doing everything that I hate about this show
that I thought it did that I already thought it did like I just don't like it
I think he's wonderful in it yeah I think she's I think she's wonderful in
it I think some of the surprise and pre -reol is great I think a lot of the
supporting cast needs a lot of work I think that they are doing like like high
school play -level acting as these gangsters and it's like and it's written
to me the way I in my opinion after growing up in South Jersey and fill
outside of Philly and in these areas that were loaded with Italian people and
it's in an Italian family I'm just I just think it's a very cartoonish
portrayal but maybe I'm wrong I don't fucking know you know I mean maybe you
know maybe a mob guy from North Jersey will tell me I'm wrong but I just thought
it was like I just thought it was cartoonish I just didn't like it and I
didn't buy the world's colliding but here's the thing I'll say this in its
defense that was born of a time where that's what television was doing
everything every TV show at that time was worlds colliding it was always like
I'm a psychiatrist but I'm the one that needs help you know what I mean we're
like you know I'm a I'm a pharmaceutical rep but I'm hooked on drugs you know
like all right every show then was that weird worlds colliding premise well that
really all came from Sopranos so TV as we know it comes from Sopranos that the
modern -day model you know and all Breaking Bad and all these shows mad men
would say of course that's the model sure so the first season I think in
breaking so much ground at once when you go back now that's the one that seems a
little broad a little goofier and then the characters just get richer and
deeper as it goes down to like you know you Paulie Walnuts you wouldn't be
talking shit about Paulie Walnuts if you'd watch the whole show it's it's
hard for a fan to even hear but your criticisms are not ones I've ever heard
about the show so that's interesting but so it must be hitting some weird nerve
for you that it doesn't for others but I would certainly recommend watching I
mean it think of it as a show about depression as opposed to a show about
the mob because it's just as much about depression as it goes that aspect of it
I enjoyed which is also why I do I was like I felt like oh god you're like in
you're you're you do anything you want and you're a mob boss but you're scared
to tell your wife that your therapist is a woman it's like come on man like some
of this stuff is just like give me a fucking break here but anyway that's my
take maybe I'll revisit it one day I mean I think the reason he's he's not
telling us because he is attracted to her it was it was some woman he didn't
care about he would go home and tell her but I think he knows that his wife
is so smart that she's gonna smell it on him yeah all right maybe yeah I'd go
back to it I mean I really would I don't I don't think there's anything better so
I might and let me be clear just before we move on I'm not offended by it
nothing about the stereotypical thing of how it offends me in any way right just
don't like it all right and they talk about you know in season two I believe
there's a scene with Peter Bogdanovich who plays her therapist where he's
talking about the stereotypes of the mob and basically kind of commenting on it
from within the show I they address all your shit I would keep watch all right
let's go to our number three here my number three will be I'll do a TV show
as well I watched the second season of pin 15 I don't know if I've ever talked
about the show on here but I thought the first season I watched in one day and I
was like this is the best show on TV that it was very funny that was very
moving it created the whole world of adolescence better than anything since
freaks and geeks and the conceit of having two adult women play themselves
at age 12 works so much better than I thought I thought it was gonna be like a
that I get sick of in five minutes but they they cast really great child actors
and it really is the next great show in that wonder years freaks and geeks line
season two I think they they did what a lot of people do in season two which is
like try to get really really weird and try to get really really out there and
change kind of change things up and in the process it was not as funny it was
not as moving it was very you know I really felt a drop -off personally I'm
hoping they pull it back this it's supposed to be half of the season they
divided these two this season into two so I'm hoping they come back strong the
finale was great of season two there were nice moments but here's a good
example Joe as somebody who's never seen it this is it's a show about
adolescence you know like like and kind of like going through puberty and it's
very very realistic and painful in kind of a welcome to the dollhouse way very
dark and funny all of a sudden at one point in this episode and it's like two
minutes in one of the girls pulls out her boob these girls are you know 30
years old in real life pulls out a boo but it appears to be like a fake much
larger boo because they're not their breasts are actually taped down because
they're playing 12 year old girls she takes out her boob and the other girl
starts greedily sucking on her nipple okay this is two girls who are supposed
to be 12 in a hallway at school in the middle of a scene she takes her boob out
the girl starts sucking on it like greedily breastfeeding it's like a big
real woman's breast and they put it away and then they resume the scene okay why
do they do that what are you what are they doing why are they doing this you
know like it's not the tone of the show it's not the style of the show and when
you have a moment where one 12 year old girl laps up milk from another girl's
giant fake tit oh milk comes out of it you I mean yeah she's breastfeeding
basically once you do that then it's real hard for me by the end of the
episode to care about whether the characters parents get divorced or
whatever the story may be it's like sure so that you know I and I haven't talked
to anybody that kind of stuff worked for but it's like this thing of let's
just get really weird with it season two and and it's always a mistake but if
you've never seen pen 15 I do think the first season of the show is about as
good a season as I've seen in a long time and I think two was decent all
right yeah I haven't seen it I hear great things about the show I would like
to see it so I got to put it on at some point but I around I just haven't I
haven't caught it I'll close out with I don't know you know what I might just do
two today all right cuz I got my other ones kind of grouped here and they're
all grouped and I don't know I don't have one that could just slide into this
you know I'm saying yeah like when I have a nice even you know even layout
organized layout let's get to let's get to Borat sure yeah I Borat is streaming
on Amazon Prime for free I think a lot of big movies are gonna be going this
they made a ton of money off it what I don't think they realized though is that
that'll work for a Borat I don't think it's gonna work for James Bond I don't
think people want to watch that movie in their home are they doing that with I
thought bond was still going to theaters bond apparently and it was they were not
happy this got out but apparently they quietly went to the streamers and said
you can have it for six hundred million dollars she and they all they all were
too much right so that was it it was kind of a test Borat apparently got tons
and tons of views you know good for them I do think that comedy is kind of the
place like I I think that's also the reason people are being so easy on these
movies namely Bill and Ted you know I think like oh it's a free movie beamed
into my house at a time where I'm a prisoner so I'm just gonna of course I'm
like this but comedy is that I hope they start making more comedies you know
just to get them because they can be made cheaply and quickly and shipped to
the streamers if that's how they got to do it fine but Borat kind of came out of
nowhere they just announced that it even happened like about a month ago so I you
know I thought it was not as good as the first if that's what we're comparing the
first kind of had a cultural impact on like most movies it was huge I remember
seeing an opening night and like the theater shaking I had to ask if we were
in one it was at the Grumman's Chinese and I had just moved here and I asked my
buddy if it was like those shock seats that like William Castle used to do you
know like I honestly thought that there was something going on in the theater
where they were shaking it but it was just people laughing so hard at that
whatever but Borat the character is very funny I think that this movie is good on
a second viewing which I did do last night in preparation of this it went
down quite a bit for me it's once it's shock wears off it's not it's not really
doesn't really hold together as a film so much I don't think any of his films
do I don't ever saw the first Borat a second time yeah I never saw Bruno a
second time I love both these types of movies which is strange because I'm such
a huge Jackass fan and I can watch Jackass over and over and over again
somehow it doesn't wear off but yeah the Sasha Baron Cohen stuff a lot of it is
just the gasp of oh my god I can't believe he's doing this which is quite
admirable because it gives me anxiety and he puts himself in true danger so
that's interesting but but yeah I think after they're not rewatchable
necessarily to me I really liked Borat 2 just off the top I thought the opening
was funny you know which is scripted I enjoyed it was weird it seemed like it
a little more of a traditional scripted approach mm -hmm for about I don't know
maybe 30 % of the movie then the other films did the other films seemed to tell
more of the story just through what felt a little more like documentary style
shooting right this was a little more heavy into like we're gonna introduce
some characters and things like that but that was fine I thought it was all
pretty funny you know at the top and I would say you know for me most of those
jokes in the scripted segments were hitting at a little better than late
night level the performers were funny Borat is funny he's funny so I was like
okay but the jokes there's such a need for him to be topical that I wish he
would go away from it's always you know like a good a good specific example is
when they say you know there were black leaders that came after Barack Obama
and they cut to the picture of Justin Trudeau and blackface right that's a
funny specific joke but when it's just like yeah it'll be as good a cage as
Melania's and that kind of stuff if that stuff feels obvious and very Jimmy Kimmel
to me yeah no that that joke I didn't think was funny but I you know I guess
I'm talking a little bit more of the character driven joke like I laughed
really hard when he goes my wife is very nice not like you know like some of
those like sort of classic Borat lines that your way first line of the movie
yeah yeah so and then once it gets into the pranks it's really funny and it's
really outrageous and it's really crazy and that is not quite as well there are
moments they're crazier than the first film I think the first film was more
consistently insane yeah I mean that they're not they're nowhere near as
consistent as jackass any of them and they're at Borat 2 was nowhere near as
consistent as one that's definitely true like and when some of the times like
he'll run into the Mike Pence rally dresses Donald Trump with his daughter
over his shoulder or whatever and there were so many times where I'm rubbing my
hands together like this is gonna be good and that there was no laughs on
he comes in he yells a couple things and they escorted him out I was like well
shit you know like this should have been maybe cut out of the movie I'm glad you
got to Mike Pence but there's nothing funny here yeah no the Pence rally thing
was a letdown the gun rally thing was a letdown yeah because he released footage
of that where he actually they like came they figured out who he was yeah and
like you know and it's pretty intense but the thing itself at the rally it's
like we've seen him do that exact joke like three times now where it's like I'm
gonna go sing a crazy lyric song right you know at a at a Hick thing and and
like make everybody look insane because they're gonna sing along with it so the
the exposition throw the Jew down the well is just a more specific funny
version right and this one which I think was written by the Hick guy so so that
was it was the expose of it is shocking and and it's it's it's it is humorous in
its own way but like I just didn't really care too much I gotta say too
that like now with all this being said the cotillion dance thing where she has
her period I thought I was gonna have to go to the hospital is laughing so hard I
mean it was amazing well it should be said when you say she that is let me
get her name she'll be a star I think but Maria Bakalova who I had never seen
in anything but she is awesome I think she's not from here okay she's you said
that like you wanted to go back Joe no no I just mean that's why we've never
seen her at anything she's an actress from like Eastern Europe or something
she was every bit as funny as Borat I thought when I read that there were 12
writers or whatever however many writers they had on Borat and she wasn't given
one of the credits I'm like what the hell are you talking about like not only
does she improv a lot of stuff but you got her in a room with Rudy Giuliani's
cock so I felt like she should have gotten a writing credit but I think that
she will get some sort of supporting nominations because she was really great
she was able to hang with him like and it's it was very funny to watch her
crack up the few times she does like when when he's in the office with the
classic surgeon and describing what a Jew's nose would look like she's freely
laughing in that moment and other times you can see her laughing but for me
what it was was she was it basically boils down to the strength of the set
pieces so that one with her showing off the period underwear was pretty
incredible the beginning where the dads are talking or joking about fucking his
daughter while their daughters are right there being embarrassed you know that
was all really incredible right and and that's a great scene Giuliani of course
that's a big name and it's crazy what happens in my mind what not thinking not
that great that crazy because after it after the thing happened somebody was
like he's not married him I was like well then who cares he didn't do
anything wrong like a hot chick is like hitting on him and like let's go in the
other room it's like yeah go for it buddy like yeah I completely despise
Giuliani but she she's being she's acting like she's in love with him she
showed she gives him a book with pictures of a vagina in it she says do
you want to come into my hotel room where the bed is and have a drink with
me and then she's trying to help him get his microphone off or whatever like I
completely agree with you and she's saying that he thinks this girl would
want to fuck him but sometimes there are politicians that have this stuff happen
to them and and also too he's she's presented to him as an adult woman
everybody keeps going like he thinks he's having sex with a 15 no no he
doesn't she's presented to him as an adult like she is in real life she's 25
or something yeah so I hate to defend the man but then also you have Sasha
Baron Cohen wearing increasingly insane disguises so when he comes in as that
cameraman character I mean he looked like a muppet it was insane so he comes
and then he keeps bursting in and I understand they don't want to just leave
her in there so he does try something but it's like well how far are you
trying to go with this because where you got it right now is it looks like you're
trying to entrap an old man he didn't really go all the way with it although
it does look like he's at least trying to fluff his dick up but it wasn't quite
the gotcha craziness that I thought it was going to be well and that's the
the end of the first Borat he had to he had to make the plan with Pamela
Anderson right that was script like she knew that that was gonna happen when he
sacks her or whatever yeah but so then you do it in front of a group of people
that don't know what's gonna happen and then it's a crazy stunt and it's really
funny and it's nuts this was just let's get a guy that we don't like into a room
and make him and secretly videotape him by the way once he's in the bedroom it's
secret camera right it almost feels like a little like sorry for him like we're
like I don't like the guy but I'm just like Jesus Christ man like are we at
this that I gotta say like the lady that was the babysitter she she came out and
she said that she was kind of pissed off because she's like you know like she's
like I was told that this was a documentary about this woman finding her
liberty in our country and she's like I prayed for this girl like at length and
I was really disturbed by like what she thought she was allowed and not allowed
to do and I really cared so like Sasha Baron Cohen started to go fund me for the
lady kind of like look she got the shit end of the stick here and she wasn't in
on this but she was a good sport so send her some money if you would or if you
feel like it and I think she ended up getting like 60 grand or something like
that which is nice but I will say there there there there's a part of me when I
see stuff like this and it's probably why I love Jackass so much Jackass is
all I mean sometimes they do the dumb pranks where it's like you know the old
man's balls are hanging out of his whatever right who cares but I like the
thing I like about Jackass is it's them doing it to themselves like like they're
like I'm gonna climb to the top of that tree and jump out of it right and hurt
myself and that's it like this there is a part of me that gets a little a annoyed
at well you know dude like you're holding all the cards here and as much
as I can appreciate you showing the the darker side of humanity I don't know
that I necessarily enjoy watching that you know what I mean it's yeah you're in
a position where you're able to really pull these things out because you're
you're holding all the cards and then you start to see innocent people that
aren't bad people that are good people getting roped in and it's like well what
the fuck is this guy supposed to do you know what I mean he's just there yeah in
the in the first one you know like he gets on that bus with these frat guys
who are immediately saying horrific racist misogynistic things and I'm like
yep a they deserve it be you know like that's exactly who he should be going
after so in this one when he's got that scene with the two well one incredibly
sweet old Jewish woman there in the synagogue and he comes in dressed as the
giant nose and the you know marionette strings and everything I was like well
these women seem almost saintly they seem like wonderful human beings why why
would I be laughing at this why would anyone be laughing at this it almost
felt wrong to laugh at it then you've got the the other scene where okay he's
gonna make fun of these guys who believe these conspiracy theories but it's like
they also just let you an immigrant come and live in their home during a
pandemic well that's that's yeah that that kind of bugged me because I'm like
I don't agree with anything these guys are saying but Jesus Christ man like
they took this guy off the street like you know and then they got him running
around with that like if you're gonna do the the boner joke make it look like it
could be an actual boner in his underwear I didn't know what that joke was where
he's running around with a giant floppy dick hanging off his underwear I'm like
guys pick a tone here so I had some issues with with that stuff and who he
was going after but what I read this week before I watched it a second time
disturbed me even more which is that that woman the who kind of steals the
show the the old black lady who's gonna tutor the right daughter on like how to
be an American woman whatever she they auditioned they chose her like out of her
she got paid four thousand dollars to do it Mike says she's up to a hundred
grand by the way on that's great yeah I do think Sasha could have sent her some
money himself but whatever instead of asking his fans to do it whatever she
was flown out to Washington DC and did those scenes in a set the scenes where
we're supposed to be in her home and in her backyard they're a set that they
blew her out to in Washington DC where she was now gonna play that character
yeah she is kind of herself but she's also not and the way it was presented to
us as though they just found this woman off the street is kind of not fair so I
mean I get that it's not a documentary and they can do whatever they want but
then it's like well then how much else doctoring are you doing how much worse
did you make this Rudy Giuliani scene seem than it was and whether or not you
were a hundred percent ethical or not everything's called into question when
so much of it is made up that's wrong to me right I I mean my favorite moments
were the ones where they were this I mean my favorite is the period but like
a lot of it was just the smaller moments of like oh my god like how awkward would
it be to have to say this like when she gets up at the Republican women's thing
and she's like I put my finger in my cunt that was so uncomfortable it was
so funny and I was just like man that's the kind of stuff that sets me I love it
because it's just like you're putting that it's all again it's on you like
you're putting yourself in this weird thing like in the first movie when he
brings his shit to the table in the bag right that's where you get where you get
rid of the brown I was like that's a minute that was one of my favorite
scenes yeah because it gives you that thrill of like not only how seeing how
people react but also thinking how you would react and like what would you do
you know and you know the lady that does the cake for him in this movie where
it's like kill all Jews or something yeah it'd be ideal that woman say I'm
not gonna make that cake for you but also in some cases I think people are
just trying to be sweet to an outsider who doesn't understand our culture who
would bore at and are just trying to be kind of nice like sometimes they're not
these gotcha moments to me they feel like people just who may be hateful at
I don't know but it seems like it's hard for me to root against people who are
trying to help and be nice to bore at when it's that room of Republican women
or whatever even they were kind of nice to that girl you know there was the one
lady who was making shitty faces but it's like no they were nice to her the
yeah and the cake lady could you know maybe she thinks he's joking who fucking
knows maybe she realizes who the fuck it is right you know what I mean maybe
they tell her just do it it's for a movie you know who knows but yeah you
know you're getting into like that Michael Moore shit where it's like I
just walked into the bank and bought a gun and then like the real thing comes
out it's like that's not what happened man but yeah and I know I'm not I know
Borat's goal is well I mean it kind of is in its own way you know they do have
similar goals but I mean look the two elephants in the room well there's one
elephant in the room and there's one other criticism I have of the film again
I like the film I thought it was funny I hated with all of my being the moral
message at the end of it I fucking hate that Borat becomes a better man because
of his daughter right I hate that there's like this empowerment message at
the end of it and it's not because I don't like the idea of empowering women
or anything like that it's because it doesn't fit in with the tone of fucking
Borat the example I always use is nobody wants to watch The Three Stooges and in
the middle of it Simo go Jesus I'm sorry I hit you guys because I love you deep
down it's like you don't want to see that that's not what we're here for I
didn't want to see it in Jay and Silent Bob I didn't want to see it in Bill and
fucking Ted and I don't want to see it in fucking Borat I want to see that in
a movie that attacks or excuse me analyzes and addresses that theme yeah
and with characters that I'm taking seriously not with the goofiest
characters in movie history right so I hated that I hated it I I texted you
early on I was like my money is on he's gonna marry his daughter at the end
which I think if it was five years ago that's how that's how it would have
ended for sure so so I hated that I hated that like now Kazakhstan is using
Borat as like their slogan because he because he made them look so good now
it's like come on man what is this yeah the the patient Borat is patient zero
thing I thought was kind of clever but like the usual suspects reveal with him
dropping the glass and everything that not only is usual suspects a third or
25 year old film I just watched scary movie scary movie ends with a parody of
usual suspects and at that point it made sense like that's a really old kind of
in that I hated it in Bill and Ted where it felt like completely forced and and I
just didn't like that movie I hated it in Jay and Silent Bob but this movie was
designed I felt to be a more pro -woman movie I guess Sasha Baron Cohen has a
teenage daughter etc so I think mostly just because of her it sold me I found
it pretty sweet they didn't overdo it to the extent that I was bothered by it
I think they feel in betrayal of the character but so be it I think there's a
way they could have done that without being so direct with it there was a much
more clever way they could have done that they did it in such a pandering way
like yes and she gets to be a reporter and she's better than he is can you
believe it his daughter is better than he it's ridiculous yeah they could have
done a really really outrageous funny they could have had her moving to America
and starting some insane business that revolved around some kind of public
stunt that was empowering and and gave her independence and all these things
and it could have got the same message across in such a more creative and
brilliant way and to do it all the way what if she's a she's a hot blonde and
she's like not only not only was she great she got a job at one of the most
prestigious news organizations in all of America and she's walking into the Fox
News building yeah something there was because she looks like those women
Megyn Kelly and all them or have her become the premier in Kazakhstan and now
she's torturing people and the joke is she can do it just as good as the men
can or what there's just a million ways to do that message where it's still
really funny and valid and they just didn't they just it was in and I hated
that they that they I thought some of the jokes in the in the finale were
funny like the the bots you know as a black man I love Donald Trump sure
whatever like the fake Twitter bots and so I thought that was pretty funny but
then it just was so on the nose where like the parade and Fauci gets killed in
the run it's like come on guys Jesus Christ like this is just this is like
you said it's late -night humor but the elephant in the room that I wouldn't get
to and it didn't even occur to me till right now as we were talking about this
I mean you want to talk about a movie that's gonna be a sort of analysis of
let's you know of capitalism at its worst you know which is the Trump
administration and that's basically what it is defined as and an authoritarian
regime and all these things and then you release it on Amazon Prime I mean it's
come on sure sure you know like I mean there could look you and I have said on
this show frequently we love Amazon and we feel guilty about it but it's like of
all the places to release your movie with the big message about America and
how often I think going everything Amazon Prime I would say is the is the
most ironic one to put it on you know not to mention what a spokesman Sasha
Baron Cohen has been against Facebook in particular and like it's like okay
Amazon's horrible in a different way but it's essentially just as bad so
and you know the reason they chose Amazon Prime is my here's my guess but
I'd say I'm 99 % right is because Amazon Prime offered them the most money why
would they go anywhere else so that another double down on but that's that
that is this business it is people passionately fighting for things that
they don't do right yeah so there you go all right this just in just under the
fire as we close out this episode I just pulled up movie web people under the
stairs remake is happening with producer Jordan Peele so that's interesting all
right I'd like to see that and definitely could use a remake I liked it
but it could use a race Bruce I agree and it's been Peele's a good guy for it
with the you know given the commentary of the film so for sure anyway that's
our show folks you can check me out Instagram and Twitter Jota Rosa comedy
Jota Rosa comedian the new podcast with Sal Volcano and myself will be dropping
very very soon I know I've been teasing it for a while but it's coming and
another interesting plug Joey Rose's a sandwich pop -up shop selling classic
neighborhood style sandwiches that I created is gonna be happening at the
stand in New York City nice and that should be dropped that could be
happening by the end of this week meaning when you're hearing this you're
getting your own sandwich or you're getting a sandwich wing or something I
did I created an idea for a sandwich shop and we're gonna do a pop -up of it
at my buddy Paul's Club the stand so it should be pretty cool eight sandwiches
for eight bucks a piece that are gonna be better than any sandwich you're gonna
get anywhere else for an amazing deal that you won't find anywhere in New York
I promise you that anyway look out for promo materials they're coming soon and
we'll be launching again like either this week or I think next so that's
coming right up so check that out I will I can't but I would love a sandwich if
so would I quite frankly I want to can't stop thinking about goddamn donuts yeah
well I'm sorry I'm sorry sorry I'm at the Patrick Walsh on Twitter and
Instagram I have been tweeting more lately just out of pure boredom thank you
all for joining us on the patreon it grows each day we can't say how much we
appreciate that thank you to Emily for handling our communication with the
Hellions she's always on top of what's coming up even though sometimes we're
wrong we told her we were doing Evil Dead we're gonna push it but you get it
she usually knows the score and I have not received it yet but Emily texted me
yesterday that a Hellion by the name of John Wolf John I believe we have met and
sent the three of us me Emily and Joe a copy of a horror anthology that one of
his stories is featured in called off coffin blossoms so thank you for
sending us that we will read I haven't had a chance to read it yet but I don't
have a link but look for coffin blossoms which John has a story and
congratulations John yeah congrats it's awesome man and I look forward to
reading it as well and we are still loving all the fan art and everything
we'll be back with our Evil Dead app we'll be back with a review of the
creepshow animated app we'll see you next time and we'll see you in hell