Welcome to we'll see you in hell people time to talk about movies again
Joe DeRosa here and Patrick Walsh here brewing up a hot pot of Joe with Joe this morning as we
talk about the film John Wick 4 colon John Wick kills everyone on earth. Is this one
Parabellum or the last one was Parabellum and this one is just they went back to just
last one was Parabellum I bought a beautiful Parabellum last week at Nordstrom
it's like a glove I don't know what a Parabellum is I've seen the movie I don't remember what it
was do you know what that word means? I think it meant uh a lot of uh killing a lot of traveling
to get coins from people yeah oh it's a firearms cartridge interesting it is yeah it's got many
things it's it's cartridge that's the first answer that comes up but then Keanu so take
this with a granite salt because he's not very bright but he says Parabellum is Latin second
half of a Latin phrase Parabellum means prepare for war that is yeah I remember reading that
actually when it came out um this means war what is that Daffy Duck yeah or Wallace
Sean um impressions are similar I must say yes uh Wallace Sean star of the latest released Woody
Allen film where he is married to Gina Gershon so finally uh Woody's setting him up with somebody
age appropriate at least it's not Selena Gomez on the arm of Wallace Sean yeah Woody's like I'm not
going to be in it the cyan river in Paris because he can't he gets to shoot in international waters
now Woody steps out because it's not a he's like I'm too old let me get a younger chap in here like
Wallace Sean you know somebody really vital and sexy I'm thinking of Wally thinking about calling Wally
uh the that was that was um Rifkin's festival was the name of it but his new movie coming out
right and it was about Ron Rifkin hosting a wine festival correct yeah exactly sort of
Ron Rifkin's curb they called it like his
it's uh the new one he's shooting is a French like thriller like something or other with
with all French actors with yeah you know Polanski started doing that too at some point
I feel like too I feel like when when when you when you can't crack the American box office anymore
go make one of these dry ass foreign films I feel like those I feel like those are easy to make you
can always go make an artsy foreign film and people go that's brilliant you go yeah I just made the
most boring thing I could I think that we are unable to tell when acting is bad when the actors
are foreign when they're speaking a different language I mean it's impossible how would we know
so that's why foreign films generally get a pass because the critics are like yeah I think that was
pretty good acting I'll go as far as to tell you uh southern accent or New York Italian accent
can't tell if it's bad yeah that's enough to throw me off the set I can't think of one movie with
people with southern accents where I'd say that's bad acting I can't think of one right now it's a
valid point I mean but you don't like the Sopranos Italian accent so but that's New Jersey I don't
think I yes all right fair enough uh but I don't think the acting is necessarily bad I just don't
like the show well maybe I'm full of shit I don't know but it was more of a bit I um I always like
a southern lawyer character you don't see it much anymore but it used to just be a staple flipping
through the channels of course but there was also other like lesser matlocks out there for a while
my grandma watched them all yeah like the guy remember hunter hunter wasn't even a lawyer he
was just a bald cop with a giant head I like the southern lawyer there's the there's always the
scene where he's tilted back in his chair with his feet up sipping a whiskey in the dark on the
phone well I hope y 'all are ready for what I've got in store tomorrow because it's going to be a
hell of a shooting fight fight in that court you know there's always that scene mopping the brow
those southern lawyers and southern characters they're always drinking and then if you watch any
movie from the 50s every scene starts with a large tumbler of whiskey being poured for any discussion
anyone comes over oh let me pour you a triple bourbon as we discuss something at noon in the
garden it must have been a wonderful time well what's weird too about the southern whiskey thing
it's always piping hot there wasn't a setting where they were piping hot it's like it's whiskey
it's like john candy in jfk style you know what I mean like Louisiana like they're wiping the
sweat off and then they're drinking whiskey neat yeah I'm just like there's got to be some
it's like in it's like Mexico with tequila like there's got to be some quality to these alcohols
helps in the heat I don't know what the hell it could possibly be but
weird whiskey for me whiskey or a red wine three sips and I'm 20 degrees hotter yes
yeah red wine really gets me yeah you'd think you'd want something cooling I tried finally
watching my first hot ones last night you seen this you seen this hot ones I'm a big fan I met
the guy finally at a party and talked to him for a while about hot ones and I was like
I just was like it is fucking crazy the guest you're getting on this thing and he was like
I know it's nuts right like yeah even he was like I don't I don't know yeah it's cry it's wild
well they must sign something where they get an approval of the cut or something but I
the one I watched was Florence Pugh who I was unaware was British yeah she seems nuts in a
way she was like really weird and kind of funny which I was not expecting but outside of a little
perspiration on her upper lip nothing happened and I watched this for like 20 minutes no they they
they get that just means she's a baller and she can handle it like they get people go sideways
on that thing my favorite one ever is the Gordon Ramsay one because he that was the first one that
came up I should have just watched that but I was watching with somebody else that's my favorite
because like halfway through it he's like oh fuck I've got to taste fucking food tomorrow you've
ruined my fucking taste bud and at the end of it the guy the host goes can you give us can you give
us a drop or whatever you know like I'm Gordon Ramsay's hot ones and he just goes fuck you
it's very funny I'll watch I'll watch they're all just on YouTube they're all just on YouTube
but I mean that show is it it is it is like the most watched show in America it's a crazy how
big it is it's like they've got like bus posters and shit in New York where it's like like Kevin
Smith Kevin Smith when he was doing Jay and Silent Bob reboot said publicly he goes we tried to get
on hot ones and they didn't want us like that's how big the show is it's crazy and why do we need
like I'm sure that guy is great he seemed like an okay interviewer but was it just his idea or is
he does he bring something special I asked sauce if you will I asked him about that and I said tell
I said correct me if I'm wrong I get the impression that the original idea for the show is
is won't it be funny to watch people try to do a legitimate interview while they're sweating from
hot wings and he goes no yeah exactly that's what it was and then he goes and then it develops into
this other thing where now it's become they have like real like they get into like really
heartfelt shit on there it's it's interesting but and now the wings are sort of secondary to
to the conversation but um but uh you know I hope to do it one day I don't think I'll ever be famous
in them I mean you're not you're nowhere near Kevin Smith famous so nowhere near nowhere near
Jason Mewes famous nowhere near let's be honest Randall or Dante famous
I think you're around Dante famous but if you guys both went to a diner he'd get recognized
way more than you though well I'd put it to a test let's put it to a test in Jersey definitely
but you know come dance with me in Wyoming Hicks see what you've been uh out touring
uh yeah like crazy I just was in uh thank you to everybody that came out had a had a basically
sold out run in uh Chicago Batavia Detroit and Grand Rapids I just got back amazing shows thank
you everybody and uh I'll be back out again I'll plug at the end but uh yeah it's been the touring
has been really nice I'm doing finally doing the venues I want to do the exact kind of venues I
want to do the exact show I want to do yeah everything is how I've always wanted it I'm
finally out there doing things like way more like an indie band or something versus you know dealing
with a uh a bachelor party at you know some club in a mall you know with six opening comics and
a check drop at 45 minutes and all these things I always really hated but uh but dealt with uh and
now I'm in like these little music venues and it's awesome it's been really great
so you're finally completely satisfied and happy yeah never going to be a problem ever again
never going to need another drink yeah that's great speaking of which yeah oh
I turned one on last night hey well it was Tuesday
they had the party I was gonna stay in and and they had the after the Patrice O 'Neill benefit
was last night in New York the annual benefit and they had the after party at the stand and I
wasn't gonna go and then Paul my partner and and also the guy that owns the stamp my partner
and Joey Rose is not in not in love um he just was like come on man come to the party and I'm
like all right fuck it I leave my house at 11 oh no and I'm like this is gonna be one of those
in New York what what happened how do we end up here nights and yeah sure enough it was we were
as soon as I got to the party the first person I saw was Shane Gillis and he was like what's up
let's get fucked up I was like okay I was like dude let's let's just take a breath for a second
he's got a gun out pointed at your head
yeah he's dancing around in his undies uh -huh with a twirl on the gun I saw it was fun it was a fun
night on the Amazon I'm looking through the new movies to rent or whatever and they had something
it was called like Gilly and Clive what was it Gilly and Keeves that's their sketch
oh I didn't know the man was making sketch comedy it's very that was even his thing super oh yeah
he's great at it super viral on YouTube very viral on YouTube yeah they're they're great you
should watch them they're really funny all right all right you know all right I don't see why you
don't watch them all right over here watching Florence fucking pew eat hot wings it improved
my opinion of her so or it impuged my opinion of hers I cannot understand how at the height
of her career she's she's still even broken up with him making movies with Zach Braff I'm
sure her agents were like baby I know you like the guy but uh yeah I don't even know what that
movie is but the let's talk I think that's how they met isn't it I think that's why they were
dating oh the movie just got made a long time ago I thought they made it post -breakup but I could be
wrong I often am I mean you know the uh it's I mean it's a Zach Brett I mean Zach's Braff's movies
are usually except for going in style yeah it was the Morgan Freeman thing um you know his movies
are usually pretty under the radar no well I mean Garden State was huge Garden State that was a
sleeper yeah and then you know I'm sure you donated a lot to his second movie to get that off the
ground oh remember when he was taking up a collection I forgot about that yeah that that's
really when America turned on Braff the uh and yet he made enough money to make his movie off the
people so that's wild isn't it isn't that wild let's talk the pictures shall I get I yeah go ahead
you know no go ahead I um yes I saw you know what I rewatched I've been on a Billy Friedkin kick
movie he's good he's great um and I guess I could probably do three of his but I watched
probably his most recent good movie which was Killer Joe you ever see that thing no I you know
I hear it's great uh I I don't know why I never watched I think with Friedkin since The Exorcist
is my favorite horror movie of all time I'm always sad that it's not a horror movie
with no I hear you he's and the ones he made in the 80s and 90s here and there are all pretty bad
but um it's really good Killer Joe is not horror but it's close it's just like
unpleasant it's night uh NC 17 which is a rating you barely even see anymore and when I watched it
granted the movie is is fairly disturbing but there are so so many more R rated movies that
are way beyond this so don't go I mean if you're if you've been putting it off because you were
like whatever's happening in this movie I don't need to see it it must be fucked up it's not
like that but there is an extended sequence where Matthew McConaughey takes a chicken wing holds it
in the place of his penis uh and has Gina Gershon blow the chicken wing
Woody did this scene in Rifkin's festival with Wally Shaw
Wally was Wally the one with the wing or the one sucking in the scene
you want me to suck your wing
I mean I'll do it but uh Killer Joe yeah that that's the big centerpiece when I finally looked up
the poster for the film it's a big chicken wing which is in super poor taste because like
it's almost like when you know like doing the hair gel and something about Mary like it's a funny bit
but this is a long extended scene of graphic sexual assault so it's kind of odd to use that
in your marketing but um the plot of the movie in and of itself is uh like something you'd see in
a Tennessee Williams or something fucked up from the 50s but it's Matthew McConaughey is a low
budget hit man there's a trailer park in Texas where Juno Temple who has looked like she's 16
for 20 years uh lives with Emil Hirsch her brother and also her parents played by Thomas Hayden Church
from TV's Wings and Gina Gershon from Rifkin's festival is she is the sister and brother having
sex in this it seems like that kind of movie Emil is clearly attracted to her and there is
hints that in the past he has taken things a little too far but it's not really in the movie
anyway they hire McConaughey to do a hit to get some insurance money they don't have the money
to pay up so he says how about as a trade -off I fuck your 16 year old sister slash daughter
uh and they agree Thomas Hayden Church is like yeah we can set that up so McConaughey comes over
he holds the family hostage um you know certainly the most memorable scene is going to be that
chicken wing uh oral assault McConaughey's great in it this is one of the early days of him being
good in movies when it was like surprising still um and it's got a great vibe to it
Freakin did this and he also did Bug you ever see Bug Joe I own Bug I think and Bug is a horror
movie but I know I still haven't watched it I think I've got the dvd behind me over here but uh
yeah Bug's great it's Michael Shannon and Ashley Judd and it's like a psychological horror but
both of these movies are very similar and made around the same time and I think what Freakin
was doing is kind of what Altman did when Hollywood stopped giving him money which is film
really good effective versions of plays on the cheap but he can get great actors because of his
stature as a director so it is a film play the plays by Tracy Letts who is now probably better
known as an actor uh you've seen him in Ford versus Ferrari this guy crying in the car and
a million other things that he's in when you say but but wait a minute when you say film a play
you don't mean like he's shooting it he's just staging a play and shooting it you mean like
he's taking a play script and shooting a cheap indie I got you yeah cheap indie Altman did that
throughout the 80s too like he did the uh secret honor with Philip Baker Hall as Nixon and it's
basically like a dark knight of the soul for Richard Nixon it doesn't look like a play but
basically they just shot the script of a play yeah um so that's what Freakin did for a while
they were way better movies than the turds he was making throughout his uh 80s and 90s period but
I recommend it it's a weird interesting fun little movie it's kind of sexy in a very wrong
way but I enjoy that kind of thing check it out all right uh I watched a documentary on
on the airplane uh called the Pez Outlaw uh very interesting documentary about a guy
who was was I don't know if he named himself this or if he was given the name the Pez Outlaw
because he in the 90s uh became an a Pez dispenser enthusiast uh because he liked going to toy shows
and stuff like that and he started going overseas to the where the Pez dispensers were manufactured
uh and finding models that were not released ever in the United States because the United States
branch of Pez was putting the kibosh on some of the designs so he would go over he would buy
hundreds of these things for pennies on the dollar right from the manufacturer
fly home with them and sell them at toy shows for hundreds of dollars a piece to avid collectors
um he became he made five hundred thousand dollars doing this uh I believe was the number
he then took that money
Pez was after him they wanted to shut him down he was being very arrogant about it
uh they didn't like that he was doing this obviously but they for some reason did not
put any you have to register your product with customs to say like somebody is not allowed
bring this into the into the country in bulk unless it's us and they never registered that
for whatever reason and that's how he was getting away with this through this loophole
so they couldn't stop him but they did actively try to shut him down and things come to a head
when they get him they they do finally put the kibosh on him bringing Pez dispensers into the
country and then what he starts to do is he finds another loophole where he gets his own Pez
dispensers made and manufactured um and those sell well and then Pez steals his things that he's
doing and and and makes them and they sell them for cheaper and they shut him down yet again so
it's a story of this guy's journey through all this and and here's what bothered me about it
it's a good movie and the guy is kind of fun and quirky and charming in his own way but
you're supposed to like be rooting for him against the evil Pez corporate suits of America it's like
yeah but everything he's doing is wrong like he's finding these like loopholes to sell a product he
has no right to be selling at a price that he has no real right to be selling it at
yeah and then on top of it he's like flaunting it in the company's face and then at the end when like
he finds this loophole where he can make his he can actually legally get his own Pez dispensers made
and he makes like color variations of existing Pez dispensers and then Pez goes well fuck you
and they and they just do it too and they sell it at a fraction of his price and and shut him down
you're supposed to be like oh my god this poor guy he put everything into this and it's like
but yeah it was a legal loophole he found to sell a product again that he has no right to
fucking sell he didn't design these fucking things oh you made color variations like big
fucking deal like i get the that collectors get off on that shit but you know i've got no problem
with people manufacturing things that aren't being manufactured you know like in other words like
i've bought video games from guys that make video games because the video games are out of print
right and the ones that are out there for sale are selling for hundreds or sometimes thousands
of dollars so they're like look dude we'll we do repros and we'll make it look exactly like the
original product and we'll sell it to you for 40 bucks i got no problem with that i think that's a
fucking cool thing like you know the company certainly isn't going to make new ones yeah that's
not really what this was like this was like no the company is deciding not to sell these products in
the united states whether you have a problem with that or not is besides the point they have the
right to do that so you're going to take it upon yourself to do it and then when they start to get
pissed at you about it you go you start kind of waving the finger in their face right you know
and being like this is my calling i it just kind of spoke to a lot of what i a lot of the problems
i have with the current culture with like like well i should be allowed to do it it's like yeah
but you're not so i don't know what to tell you you know it's like yeah if you're going to go on
instagram and show your penis or your vagina or your boobs or whatever it is and then be like
fucking instagram took my post down this fucking platform sucks it censors us it's like no no no
platform has rules right and that's what the platform does like that's what it is like you
know like i don't know i don't know like we're all and then you're then you're going to call
elon musk an asshole because his big thing was like i'm going to make twitter free again
it's like well he's saying the same thing you're saying like i don't whatever like my point is is
it's a privately owned platform they have a right to do what they want to do
and this company is a is a is a is a obviously it's a privately owned fucking or maybe they're
stockholders but you know what i'm saying it's like yeah i don't know man like i guess so like
you know like i don't feel sorry for you you had half a mil and this is what you chose to sink it
into after right after you shouldn't have got that half a mil to begin with you're going to
look the gift horse in the mouth and keep going like all right i guess so man yeah um i don't i
don't know it just it was an enjoyable watch but overall it kind of bugged me something tells me he
gave himself the name the pes outlaw now now that i've heard the full story he is claiming
throughout this thing that they had people trailing him and stuff and the guys at pes are like nobody
was trailing him he likes to make up these stories he thinks he's like this espionage character
whatever because he loves tom clancy books and whatever but then like they interview people and
like no i was paid to trail him so you don't know who's telling the truth about what or whatever
it's it is very much like a clancy thriller and it's set up like that he loves tom clancy books
it sounds very similar to paul t goldman on peacock which was one of my favorite shows of last year
you would probably enjoy this movie i'll check her out i'll check her out anyway um i sure
i was texting joe clips all day sunday from the movie hustle uh wait one of my favorite
burt reynolds one not the adam wasn't that the last adam sandler movie also called hustle
okay it was also maybe called the hustle but it was called hustle and a solid sports drama i guess
i've heard um they briefly tried to push him for a best actor oscar and then somebody i guess
whispered to them like guys this is embarrassing don't do this it's got to do with it
wildly good reviews hustle i had no idea it's solid yeah it's um i my favorite aspect of it was
sandler and queen latifah as a married couple which is a small aspect of it but i was like i
want this movie i don't i don't want this to be the c story of a sandler basketball movie because
they they were so great together they had such great chemistry together um anyway hustle yeah
that's an interesting team up i like that i did too uh and one of the rare occasions where one of
the happy madison guys is not paired with a woman who is a hundred times more attractive than him
it's usually like kevin james and uh emily ratajowski are in a movie together um i've been
following the films of robert aldrich who has made huge movies small movies but he had like a
very long career perhaps best known for what happened to baby jane which is one of my favorite
old movies which kind of reinvigorated his career but he is a guy who tarantino talks about in his
great book cinema speculation he talks about him on his podcast which is actually so in depth his
podcast with him and um the guy who co -wrote pulp fiction roger avery and who also killed somebody
with his car but they talk about like one movie from the 70s like this week it's the great waldo
pepper with robert redford which is a movie i saw when i was a kid and don't remember anything
about and then you see the running time of the podcast is two hours and it's like i love
tarantino but i don't need to hear him talk about the great waldo pepper for two hours he also
interrupts roger avery on this thing roger avery doesn't speak have you heard this podcast joe
no i i i tarantino should never be doing a discussion podcast he can't he can't
defer to someone else he just talks over them the whole time yeah in the uh in the jango movie
the the documentary about yeah jango wait was that what it was i think it is yeah it's about
all the jango i think yeah tarantino it opens with tarantino describing the first like three
chapters of the once upon a time in hollywood novel to finally circle around to getting to a
point about this is what the italian movies meant back then like it's like jesus christ dude like
you forget for a minute you're like am i watching a movie like a bonus feature about the once upon
a time in hollywood novel like it's crazy how long he talks for without taking a breath
yeah and and i love it i love people talking passionately about like obscure
movies and stuff like that but even when i've seen them there are times when i'm like quentin
you should not have this much to say about this movie um but aldrich did one of tarantino's
favorite movies kiss me deadly which is one of the all -time great film noir movies i absolutely
love that movie uh he did the longest yard and at some point burt reynolds kind of gave him his
back by bringing him in to do his movies and his movies just are scuzzy they portray the
underbelly of people the characters are often racist and horrible and amoral all like for his
entire career that's the movies he likes to do this is no exception hustle is about a cop
played by burt russell burt russell burt reynolds i'll take that i'll take that mashup
burt reynolds at his absolute laziest uh 1975 like he's at the top of his career and just not
trying too much when he's acting um catherine denou the the amazing french actress playing
his girlfriend who is a hooker these cops always had hookers in these 70s movies girlfriends
hooker girlfriends movie starts on like a fun boy scout trip not unlike the beginning of the
actually except on this one they find the body of a dead teenager that's how the movie starts
great kickoff to a movie uh from then on burt and paul winfield team up to track down what went on
there's gross characters everybody's corrupt that's a classic aldrich move the cops are corrupt
you got earnest borgnein playing the chief of police in the charles dirning role
he says some of the most horrific things in this movie i've ever heard it reminded me kind of a
cop with james woods which i talked about on the show where it's just you could take clip after
clip put it on twitter and have people screaming about it for an hour and a half it's just crazy
but i love a borgnein by the way when borgnein's name pops up in the titles and the credits i get
excited i escaped from new york we just reviewed yes i was like oh borgnein's and i didn't even
realize it in the 70s you're always going to get a borgnein a jack warden or a charles dirning and
they're always good to see but it's always going to be one of those guys as like a mentor or a
judge or something or a chief so uh um there's long scenes that had me just look they're not
technically funny but they made me laugh just with their 70sness and how on pc the time was
but you got bert by the way you got diversity bert's partner is the great paul winfield a black
actor um who's there hearing all this racist shit too which is kind of what gives these movies
a life because it feels real you know it feels definitely like the time period but um they're
talking at one point about this girl who got found keep in mind she's a teenage girl
and reynolds is like oh yeah she was just just flooded with semen i mean her whole body was
flooded with semen and then uh borgnein's doing one of those hand squeezer things of course behind
the desk the things you do to get your hand strength up and then he's like really well
where where was the semen bert's like every orifice you know chewing his gum it's like
coming out of every orifice as they say as they say uh it's a wild movie that's how they talk
about everybody um when and an early scene it's ben johnson from the last picture show and bert
reynolds brings his girl out on the slab his 16 year old daughter and as they pull the slab out
she has these she's topless and her giant boobs bounce and her dad punches bert reynolds in the
face and he's like you're gonna cover her up you're gonna cover her up and then winfield's like
you're going to jail buddy you don't hit a cop and then bert pulls him aside and he's like hey
as long as you be cool i'm not gonna press charges it's fine i understand you're going
through a lot he goes hey buddy buddy you're right we should have covered her up it's full
of those great little moments you know all right all right just and there's just something insane
about showing a man his hot dead 16 year old daughter that just i mean that that to me is
the beauty of aldrich and why tarantino loves him because tarantino is the same way he makes
every scene memorable and fun and uncomfortable and that's why i love his work joe i'll do another
airplane watch uh and this is a rewatch you know i went down a stephen king rabbit hole recently
yet again and i got the hankering to you know we had we had i had reviewed in the movie corner
the pennywise documentary i'm sorry the yeah the the the about the making of the mini series of it
um and then i started listening again to the audio book and i was like you know what i really
want to watch that new it again maybe i was wrong i was too hard on it and i rewatched it on the
plane what a pile of shit it sucks it really sucks and when this thing came out i remember
saying to people the mini series is better and it's scarier and people were like oh shut up
what are you talking through and i'm no it is it is time has proven it it god it's a bad movie
there's just nothing to it there's nothing to and i love and this is on topic for today bill
billy scars guard he he scratches me where i itch i like that kid he's good i love a bill hater
yes well i didn't watch two i just watched one yeah hater doesn't come until the second one right
but uh i mean the second one's worse than the first one i know that much but like
jesus christ man it's there's just no no pun intended teeth to the thing yeah
and and all you just you just start to feel like no pun intended like they were just
clowning around on set you know yes i do we do 30 of them i mean no pun intended but
all right carry on this thing doesn't float for me folks um i just was like you know in
in listening to the audiobook after watching the documentary and then rewatching the mini series
um and then in anticipation of this i was like i was like thinking of all the things they could
have explored that they just didn't they just did worse versions of everything they already did in
the other movie yeah like and there was so much you know there's a great thing in the book where
where the guy has to like a neighbor has to carry armless dead georgie to his mother
right like and it's like this horrible moment and it but it speaks it it gives you so much
for the character to understand and and and maybe it's just like oh that's too much in a movie i
mean you can watch a kid get his fucking arm bit off and crawl for his life but you can't show a
dead kid to the mom i guess i don't know right like it's just little moments like that like
in the book like the reason he's scared to go into the cellar to get the sealant for the paper boat
like that's all explored and this again it's just nothing it's just like oh i've got to run down to
the creepy cellar it's like who gives a shit just cut that out like cut that part out you're wasting
time where you could put other elements into this to explore his character there's there's sort of
there's sort of i don't want to be too repetitive because we went over this already but but you know
there's sort of the fat shaming thing in it there's sort of the racial thing in it there's sort of the
gay bashing which it opens with if i recall correctly the second one does they actually
did show that which i was like oh cool they're actually getting into some of why this thing is
yeah you know there's sort of the inappropriate stuff with bev and her father
it's just all this stuff that they just never explore to show you why these kids are the losers
club why they come together why they have the ability to defeat it why what their personal
how their personal battles are more frightening than this monster and that's what gives them the
bond and all that they just get into none of it and do a completely jump scare milquetoast version
of the mini series and exactly what tim curry demanded they not do which is do not put me in
scary makeup just make me look like a clown i'll do the rest fuck scary makeup my issue with those
movies is the cgi well that like a clown becomes instantly a million percent less scary if you're
shit it's like no that's not what this is yeah or like yeah it gets like roger rabbit uh yeah
judge what's his name judge doom judge judge doom yeah when they did the uh needle drop in part two
with the just call me angel of the more when the thing blasts out of the guy's mouth i don't even
remember the scene specifically i just remember that being one of the weirdest moments in the
history of movies except for the other moment in it too when peter bogdanovich is directing
the film version of it
bizarre bizarre i think i like two more than one though just because it was something different
at least they went a different route from the mini series here and there um i don't remember
what our review was i remember it was bad yeah i i remember being so fucking mad i remember saying
thinking two started much better and i was like oh here we go they're going to write all the wrongs
then it got so much worse and i was like this is the way that you know ends with pennywise becoming
a little baby right yeah you're gonna watch this dairy prequel thing huh you're gonna watch this
dairy prequel thing for hbl max i'll watch it you know just like i keep watching all this shit
that they keep letting me down with you know yeah fingers crossed uh ghostbusters afterlife
part two started filming akroyd and hudson definitely back leading the team i'm excited
to see what they do with this they're back in new york that's exciting you know what do you mean
akroyd and hudson back meaning murray's not murray is supposedly back but they confirmed it now it's
not confirmed i don't know what's going on but the the synopsis the official synopsis is that ray
and winston are leading the new team like which i love that i'm i'm i'm in i'm i'm i'm off
how exciting is going to be to see a new dan akroyd movie like that'll be fun you know like
see him be funny again i'm into it i agree i agree anyway the last time he was genuinely hilarious
in a movie is rose point blank 96 97 he's really funny in that but beyond that not much else yeah
so all right you know tommy boy i guess his cameo is kind of funny went a little heavy with the uh
who's he and tommy boy got a little cameo at the end a little heavy with the pine tree air freshener
there didn't you buddy he runs uh the the auto parts store at the end um i finally watched the
seven year itch uh i've been going through a lot of directors couldn't care less yeah i know
well i love billy wilder billy wilder of course yeah has made some of the greatest movies of
all time double indemnity sunset boulevard some like it hot etc etc don't like it out on broadway
right now some like it hot on broadway yeah musical version of some like it broadway people
nobody nobody i don't think anybody would know uh by name but uh i i might go see it
um yeah billy wilder also did the apartment he did you know he's done a bunch of great movies and
then some really dark stuff this is one of his lighter movies for sure but the themes are really
sort of they're they're not 50s style themes it is this guy the plot of the movie is basically
with this narration they're like new new york men it's a very madman type era they're like the men
of new york they send their wives and daughters off on holiday for the summer and then it becomes
time to get on the hunt and it's all these men who drop their wives off at the train station to go
on summer vacation and then immediately start trying to fuck women um and the movie treats this
as it's a very commonplace thing that every man does and then our hero does the same thing he
he finds he lives downstairs from maryland monroe and he spends the whole summer trying
desperately not to fuck her um what a problem yeah what a problem so billy wilder himself called
this movie a nothing picture he was like the the play was great because it was a guy who
fucked a hot young girl who lives upstairs while his wife and daughter are out of town that's a
story this movie isn't a story he's just trying not to fuck and so he was kind of
production code and shit of the day he couldn't show things couldn't have the guy cheat you could
have movies about cheating at the time but you couldn't have comedies about cheating where they
were acting like it was funny interestingly enough so the guy if it was lemon you know jack
lemon did 10 movies with billy wilder they're all great if the guy had been jack lemon trying not to
fuck maryland monroe i could see this being very funny but unfortunately it's this actor named tom
who's pathetic uh has no charm i've seen him in movies of the 50s before but he's got like a
canier vibe an older less funny less good canier um where he should be the boyfriend that gets
cheated on at the beginning like he should be a side character but somehow he gets elevated to
the lead and it doesn't work i never like canier in a lead that's how i felt about this dude he
he's doing his best maryland monroe can't act let's be honest about that this is the movie
where they blow up her skirt with the disgusting hot sewer subway great air on her pussy sounds
like the most horrific thing ever uh that air smells so bad when you get blasted with it yeah
and then there's then there's the air coming up from the great folks oh um this movie at some
point what did become funny about it certainly none of the jokes in it but what became funny
about it to me is how desperate they are to get the audience a glimpse of maryland monroe's tits
but they can't because it's the 50s so there's a scene where suddenly the two of them are playing
piano and maryland monroe is bashing her hands on the keyboard like ralph and the muppets and
you're like why are they playing piano for five minutes and then you realize that every time she
moves her hands up and down her jugs bounce up and down in her dress she's wearing this cleavage
then there's a scene where she goes oh you've got an air conditioner can i try it and he's like yeah
sure she goes over with a silk shirt and for a five minute scene lets the air blow up so you can
like see her nipples here and there this is what a movie was in those days billy wilder was probably
like script doesn't work let's just show them some nipples wherever we can um it's not very
it's not very good billy wilder has 25 movies that are better but somehow it's considered a classic joe
this just didn't pat the early rotten tomato reviews of super mario brothers movie
are in i'm not going to do a third movie coming in with a hot 55 percent
okay top critics audience score is 98 percent okay uh i knew i knew it was going to suck when
i started seeing the audience early audience reviews saying it's a love letter to fans and
people where do we stand with this shit do you want fan service or do you not yeah these fans
fucking one minute it's two don't placate me with this bullshit fan service to do something new and
and then oh my god my my penis was soaked from how fucking endearing the fan service was
i mean jesus christ yeah it's it's the internet was right chris pratt is all wrong as the title
character oh i love that mildly amusing swift noisy and unrelentingly paced
all that pristine computer animation is akin to polishing well what mario finds in pipes
during his day job oh that's a good one from a a doubt uh pixel thin premise and a plot propelled
by a candy induced sugar rush the super mario brothers movie is an overstuffed 90 minutes of
colorful colorful inoffensive fun everyone is micron deep pixels without much in the way of
personality roper liked it your boy roper really liked it so they paid him off um yeah i mean you
i don't even want to see this thing and i'm a goddamn video game collector it just once i saw
in the in the second trailer that smash brothers was in the movie and then in the third trailer
where they're doing mario kart i'm like guys it is there any are you leaving anything off the table
in case you want to do another one of these anything everything every element of the entire
franchise is stuffed into this goddamn thing look here's donkey kong look here's the mario
carts look here's super smash brothers look here's the character that didn't come out till mario
fucking four or whatever it's like jesus christ guys take a breath like the plot that they're
looking for princess peach who knows yeah who knows okay i i think i would assume so yeah but
i bet you it's not because in this day and age and i'm not saying this to be inflammatory but
it's true in this day and age they wouldn't make that the plot probably because that's not empowering
her you know that she needs to be rescued by a man or whatever like and i don't say that snidely
like the but that is probably the truth i doubt that that's the plot so you know what i bet if i
if i was pitching this i would go in and be like and i by the way i would have sold this probably
unfortunately i thought of it after the movie was made princess peach has to rescue mario and
luigi from a castle yeah that's what i should have pitched well here you go here's the synopsis with
the help from princess peach there it is that's the first set mario gets ready to square off
against the all -powerful bowser yeah to stop his plans from conquering the world so basically
they're doing sort of the plot of mario brothers 2 which the video game i mean which is the
essentially least canon of all the mario video games uh but maybe my favorite i love too it's
really dark and weird this will not be dark and weird this will just be whatever but i don't know
man you go we're gonna finally make the super mario brothers movie let's not do it at all like
the video game that made everybody want the movie to begin with super mario brothers let's let's
start let's immediately start by changing the plot of that and then we'll take it from there
okay i guess so guys i mean i don't know yeah you could do you could do a parallel
thing where she does get kidnapped by bowser but then she's doing like the jonathan harker thing
in dracula's castle where she's escaping from bowser and then like gets out and joins up with
mario in the third act and then they they conquer but you know what i mean it's like
oh god because jack black is playing bowser this might be something i see just because i feel like
he's not not not only the funniest person working in movies but maybe the only funny person currently
working in movies where at least you can still rely on some laughs even the jumanji movies he
brought the fucking laughs i would like i love i like jack black i do not like that he's in the
latest episode of the mandalorian i saw him and lizzo are playing like the king and queen of
something yeah it's like guys i don't mind that that's like 70s muppet show shit you know that's
why i mind it yeah and the mandalorian is is lousy with celebrity cameos i'm sorry i stop putting
amy sedaris in it as a goofy scrap metal you know mechanic or whatever it's like too much
stop yeah they got the first season they got heratio sands in there is in a blue makeup
it's like you know christopher loyd's in this new it's just too cameo -y um anyway uh yeah you
got jack black here this killed me keegan keegan michael key said in an interview he goes i wanted
to make my voice unrecognizable as toad then why the fuck are you playing toad what is the point
of you playing it then get an amazing voice artist to do this i agree like god damn it
keegan michael key uh is exactly the the level of celebrity that means absolutely nothing to
any member of the family going to see super mario brothers no one is seeing it for keegan michael
no nobody's seeing it you do you think the kids are lining up for anna uh taylor joy
anya taylor joy as princess peach you think the six -year -olds are excited about that
oh mom the lady from the witch queen's gambit didn't she was in the chess show
um fred armisen is in it oh stop it well he's usually funny but i hear you
sebastian's in it maybe funny huh i said let me guess is he playing a creep playing everything
he's in he's playing cranky kong because it's not enough that they shoved fucking donkey kong
into this thing they've got they've got donkey kong spinoff characters in this too this is how
bloated this fucking movie is yeah by the way don't put donkey kong jr in put in cranky kong
what the fuck um let's talk joe about a little picture called john wick chapter four strangely
we got john wick john wick chapter two john wick parabellum then we're back to chapter four uh and
you'd think it would have some sort of name like end game or something because it is kind of a
close to the john wick franchise but i have learned now that they are doing
an anna day armis spinoff of john wick okay called like ballerina or something yes um
and they're doing the show i don't know i don't know how spoilery we want to get with
john wick we're gonna go i'm gonna say now we're this is full -on spoilers guys if you have not
seen this movie you should not listen to this if you want to see it i i can't not discuss this
without the spoilers because they're too significant to the movie yes i thought um well
then let's just hit him hit him with the the hind right up front here you got john wick passing
away in this film which was a shock to me as much of a shock to me as james bond dying at the end
of the latest james bond they somehow kept it out of the uh marketing and they both had the same
sort of feeling to me which is well i know you're doing more john wick i know you're doing more
james bond why the death but um my guess is keanu reeves probably said four is gonna be it for me
you gotta kill me off if i'm gonna do it it's my guess because otherwise they would keep these
going forever and i gotta say i wouldn't mind it i thought that this one while being an hour too
long at three hours was at least two -thirds action and that's a great ratio i don't give a shit about
the mythology at all but i thought ian mcshane was hilarious in it for some reason he was just
hitting me in the right spot i think he's funny he was great and um and that's the first time they
made him sort of funny yeah i agree um and the new guy uh who joe says they're probably spinning
off because he watched the post credit sequence i did not but the new guy's name what's that the
name is cain character's name is cain and the actor's name is donnie yen who is a martial arts
performer he was awesome he was fucking awesome kills the movie yes they must have worked so hard
to get that part right because clearly they want to spin him off but he plays john wick but blind
which leads to just all sorts of just awesome shit uh great addition has he been in the other
movies i don't i don't think so maybe he i was wondering if he showed up in one of them as
in a bit part then they brought him back i can't remember but he they did a lot of nods in this
movie to other things cain is clearly a nod to daredevil yeah daredevil um and they did it really
cool you know that thing he does where he sets up doorbells around the room and every time a guy
walks by the doorbell it goes bing bong and he knows where the guy is and right that was awesome
my favorite scene in the movie it got a huge laugh was when the towards the end
when the guy he's technically working for goes you can't kill me and he like beats him to the
ground and he goes i can't he goes you're right but i can hit you motherfucker he says motherfucker
the way pacino does and he spits on him yeah that was a great moment um i loved the other
new character mr nobody the guy with the dog uh which which i was like oh here comes a guy with
dog this is gonna this dog is gonna play significantly into this somehow and sure
enough he's trying to kill wick through the whole movie and then wick saves his dog and the guy
that's when the guy's like all right uh which i like it's there's just so many moments like that
and and for the fourth movie in a big franchise i appreciate that john wick still cares and tries
you know the either the guy writing the scripts is better than most people working in hollywood
or they take the time to get these movies right because look again way too long unquestionably
well it really holds your interest and it's funny and the action works and these side characters
who don't even say much you like them you care about them you root for them uh worked it all
worked this was this is my big take this should have been part three and it should have been a
trilogy yeah part three was completely unneeded part three was a lot of going to point a to be
sent to point b to get sent back to point a again it was it was a lot of filler it was not necessary
it wasn't needed and it made the length of this one feel too long because we sat through a two
two plus hour part three this if it was part three in the franchise it would have been a perfect
trilogy um you know uh there's a lot i want to say first of all how fucking eerie is it
that that actor that just died that plays the concierge dies in this movie almost immediately
yeah i was like what the because when he died i was like i wonder what they're going to do with
john wick now like and he just he gets killed i was like that is fucking eerie man yeah so
and maybe he was sick and just said to them guys i'm sick i can't work and maybe they're like well
then we're going to kill your character because we're not going to replace you so right uh but
who knows but um but he was awesome by the way he uh yeah he was in my buddy and your buddy
uh jake wiseman i met anger bretson did a hilarious show for comedy central called corporate
yes lance reddick's only comedic role i've ever seen him in and he's amazing in it and they loved
him they said he was the best that's awesome um and then let's get to we're talking about
other characters scars guard just killing it in this thing as the french whatever yeah
he recognizes that if you're gonna be the villain in a three -hour movie you better turn up the
ridiculousness a little bit for some reason we've gotten into this place where the villain is like
boring stoic character scars guards doing a different accent in every scene i mean he's
just being weird it's almost walking in certain parts loved it and i love the winks to can't
there's a lot of winks to the audience here like guys we know that this is over the top but
isn't it fun every scene scars guard is in he's eating some fancy dessert he's got some he's got
some dining room set up out of field for no reason like it's crazy there's the one scene
where he's got people practicing horseback riding circling him as he has a meeting like
he's wearing like he's on a roof doing like a tupperware party for housewives while telling
people to go kill john wick and then in like teddy ruxpin outfits in every scene like velvet
like top coats and it was crazy it was so it was awesome that's what it needed uh the fighting
fighting was unreal it's like uh you know i don't know if we've ever talked about the raid and the
raid two on here but those are kind of the best fighting martial arts movies the last 10 years
or so but wick gives them a run for their money and usually it's the down and dirty
um to be honest stuff from not america um that is the most awesome you know they just do it
better in asian countries generally these types of movies but john wick uh man the fighting is so
inventive and it goes on for so long that it's crazy how it just keeps topping itself there's
a final scene where john wick has to get up a gigantic staircase that's very video game like
there's a million people on the stairs trying to push them down and then they do it goes on 20
25 30 minutes he gets to the top and gets knocked all the way down and has to refight up the time
it's funny you say video games there were several moments in this movie where i thought to myself if
i was playing a video game and that happened this is a part that in the video game where i go oh
fuck you because you do this whole thing and then they're like nope now you got to do this
right in fact there is a john wick video game and in the in the sequence in the house when they're
in that abandoned house where he saves the dog they shoot it like the video game they shoot it
like a top down uh twin stick shooter and i was like oh that's a really cool nod to the actual
video game of john wick and like yeah so that was awesome um every room they're in like they go
there's a scene where uh the you know ian mcshane has to give john wick an assignment or whatever
like always but they're in this art museum and it starts with like 30 seconds of ian mcshane just
walking past these gigantic beautiful paintings and it's like okay i part of me is going guys
trim this up a little bit and the other part of me at some point two hours in maybe was like oh
this movie just is about excess the they're like we're going all out we're showing you the greatest
locales we're giving you the coolest shots the coolest one -liners it's uh that's i'm glad you
brought that scene up because i was laughing at how long he was walking it's so long he's going
to meet bill scars guard and then you realize like oh that's to show how fucking wealthy this guy is
yeah this is like just one of his many crazy rooms in right that he oh whatever it was just like so
um i was watching the action in this thing you're right they pulled out all the stops
let's talk about the third act where they do the complete warriors nod they do the they did the
warriors they literally said in the third act we're going to do the warriors we're going to
have a lady come on the radio and talk in this like hipster code right to say where john wick is
as he moves through the city and we're the entire third act is going to be the warriors and they did
it it's fucking insane that thing in the circular thing with the cars yeah this is bad shit
no totally that is i didn't even think of it and i watched the warriors in a theater two weeks ago
which is not not great for me but yes they were exactly the same and she plays nowhere to run
that's that's from the warriors that's right and i was like why did they put this shitty cover of
but you're right yeah she plays nowhere to run nwa did that in a hundred miles and running that's
the first they they do the warriors nod in the middle of the song and start playing that song
and then it goes back to the song they're actually doing yeah uh so when i saw the warriors i was
like oh wait that's the thing from nwa and realizing oh no this nwa is the thing from this
right right and then in this i was like wow that's so cool that they're doing it and they're doing it
exactly that it's it's a tribute they're not stealing it the one thing i oh the fucking
the whole sequence with the guy and the fat guy in the fat suit that guy was awesome yeah
that guy was awesome man yeah yeah i mean there there are so many action scenes and i will say
they keep topping one another for three full hours which is really all you could ask for
and that's why you're coming to these movies they know that they did a great job here to me
the original john wick is still the best because of the simplicity of the story you killed my
fucking dog now i'm going to kill everyone on earth love it love that movie three is on the other end
of the scale it seems like it costs 300 million dollars more than the first one but to me it's
second best of the series because it's taking that simple premise to like the most beautiful
extreme it's why we're there it's what these fast and the furiouses want to be but they just
wind up being lazy and they don't they don't have the skill to uh to pull it off i just think it's
it's a great franchise i don't know how far into these spinoffs i'm gonna go you know i'm not the
i see in annabelle four i like the conjuring franchise i don't necessarily go deep into the
others but i do love the john wick franchise one of the best franchises action -wise maybe of all
time i'm curious what they'll do and i'm curious how much i'll be interested yeah uh but they
uh and in the end he has the standoff he is the duel with cain yeah uh
uh he you get the idea that he lets cain win because he knows that cain actually wants to kill
bill scar's guard and he he needs he needs to win the duel in order to do that
i know we're spoiling a lot but i i can't remember the exact details of why that is but anyway um
and and you get the idea though that john because john wick says to cain
you owe me one uh and he does it because cain loves his daughter and these guys are threatening
his daughter and there's a beautiful moment in the end where he has john wick as he's dying has the
flashback of his wife and you know that he's going to meet her but i will say it then cuts to he
falls over and then it cuts to ian mcshane in front of his grave i do wonder is he actually
dead or is he like i'm gonna be i'm gonna you know for all they know i'm dead you know i don't
think he's gonna do another one i think this should have been the end we don't need another
one of these i was trying to explain how awesome it was again to paul my business partner last night
and he was like i don't know man that's what they do in the last fucking one and i'm like i know i
know i know it sounds like it's just retread but it's you have to just see it and but but as i was
right that was i i've gotten enough the makers of this have a movie coming out
so anyway just real quick it comes full circle in the end he's buried next to his wife it's
beautiful he said he wanted loving husband on his tombstone she has loving wife on hers
and it all comes full circle in the very end which is which is really nice to uh to see because
i felt like in the third movie it's stored it sort of gets a little bit away from i don't know
there was something about the third movie where i didn't quite remember why we were all there
i felt like it had kind of gotten away from his wife it had kind of gotten away from his uh you
know the everybody thinks oh he's doing all this for the dog well he's doing all this for the dog
because his wife gave him the dog and the that was a you know that was the love letter from his wife
to him um but in the third movie i kind of lost track of like it just got so deep into the
mythology i was just kind of like wait wait a minute he's doing this for his wife what the
is going on in this one i felt like they finally got back to the you know and brought it full circle
that this was all for his wife and then seeing them together buried next to one another with
the same reflecting tombstones was really sweet um it was i actually it was awesome had forgotten
that he or forgotten his wife died in the first one i was like oh right yeah yeah so anyway didn't
there should have been a little grave for the dog next to the two of them
loving dog uh but these the makers of this the trailer came out was was in front of this
i forget what it's called they got some fucking movie coming out about an old man
in germany in the 40s who discovers gold and then the nazis take his gold from him
okay and and every and then it like starts showing all these people talking about the old man and
they're like he is not one you want to cross whatever the guy's like 70 and then it's just
i forget what it's called i don't know i don't know no idea okay and then it's just shot after
shot of not him killing nazis in the craziest ways possible one of them is you see a landmine
fly through the air and hit a nazi in the face and it explodes and it says in the trailer
the most fun you will ever have watching nazis die and i was like this movie looks fucking
awesome i was so i'm i don't know what it's called i forget but it looks fucking awesome man
anyway um didn't see that true preview i'm very interested is it called sisu
yes his name is okay then uh i just found it online christ i tried watching that a man called
auto holy god the tom hanks it's terrible it's bad yeah real bad it's terrible like really bad
yeah and then the worst aspect is them shooting the flashbacks of the kid that looks nothing like tom
as the young tom hanks well then and hits his actual son but they i mean if you're going to use
an actual son go with colin at least colin's probably like dad i'm not i'm the only one of
the three kids that's got a career here i'm not playing you in a movie yeah or hanks is like i
got to give another kid a shot here i can't have the rapper certainly you wouldn't want chet hanks
talking in a jamaican accent in this movie but yeah i did not like that man called auto did not
like it one bit oh god man and like the cliche of like he lost his wife and then became a bitter
man and oh but not too bitter because we still got to love him every second of the movie
and in the first five minutes i was like i relate to this guy 100 when he's doing the thing at the
store where he's like i don't want five feet i bought five feet of rope not six do not chart
i was like i relate to this so much i would do this and then from there just i was like this is
now it's getting like i don't know it gets dumb i don't know i think it's pretty dumb all right
folks uh we'll be back with uh reviews of from beyond um possibly scream six and definitely evil
dead rise uh jota rosa comedy on instagram and twitter you can also catch me out there on the
road um well first i'll plug joey roses uh if you're in god damn it i'm trying to pull my dates up
if you're in new york please come by and see us we're open seven days a week we open at 11 30 am
every day and i'm on the road uh on april 20th cleveland ohio at dunlaps corner bar april 21st
and 22nd at the attic uh in columbus ohio port comedy club baltimore maryland april 20th and 29th
and may 3rd back at the crane theater uh in new york city uh and then may 4th and 5th pittsburgh
pa bottle rocket social hall uh come on out and see me jodorosainfo .com for tickets
the patrick walsh no longer on twitter possibly dropping instagram soon as well so i don't know
where you will find me but i like to have some link to the outside world of social media um
miss pat show is airing on bt plus watch it there so you can see it unedited
and that's that's really all i got uh we will be back with those movies i think it's probably safe
to say that as joe and i get busier and i'm about to head down to atlanta again for work
that the episodes will probably start happening maybe one a week as opposed to the two every two
week schedule just know you're always going to get your four keep your fucking mouth shut
thank you everybody we'll see you next time and we'll see you in hell