Folks, it's We'll See You In Hell, back to talk to you about some new horror
flicks in this Thanksgiving season.
Smile Two is on the docket today and Pat is, you're smiling.
You're, you're in a good mood.
You sat down smiling.
Just like everybody in smile and smile too.
I'm in a great mood.
Everything's going well.
Joe and I were just talking about our fitness regimes.
Yes.
Um, kept that off camera.
We didn't want you guys to think we were getting too ahead of you in terms of
like our physical fitness and, um, just overall quality of life.
Yeah, it gets, it sounds exclusive, you know?
Yeah.
I didn't want anybody feeling left out or alone or whatever, but, um, I have
been personal training thrice a week with my boy, Dirk and his lovely wife.
Uh, it's great.
I just can't lift my hands over my head anymore.
Those days are gone to me.
Now it's a husband, wife, like team, like they train, they both train you.
Yeah.
Is that what you just said?
Well, it's a little, yeah.
Uh, Vince used to go there too.
It's in my neighborhood.
It's a little bit of a good cop, bad cop vibe.
Like, you know, they give you eight exercises and you're supposed to
do like 10 reps of each.
So you just keep going one to the next, one to the next, one to the next.
And then I'll be like, Hey, this number six, it says it's called
like prisoner twist crunch.
Like what, what is that?
It sounds like a breakfast cereal.
What's that one?
And, uh, he'll look over at me with complete disgust and say to his wife,
like, can you help him with this and walk away?
Like, I can't believe he still doesn't know how to do all the exercises.
And it makes me very insecure.
And then I work harder and I think he knows what he's doing.
Okay.
I mean, that doesn't sound, I'm sure it is hard or challenging or whatever.
That doesn't sound bad though.
Eight exercises, 10 reps each.
I feel like you get burned through that in 30 minutes.
Well, then you, then you start over and you do it again.
Oh, I thought you were saying that's it.
I was like, that sounds like a snap.
No, and it's tough.
Like, so like the first, you know, you start the thing off with like a squat
where your taint is like touching the ground and you got like, you know, 200
pounds that you just, this is before you're even in the gym.
Yes.
I like to drop it low at home to kind of stretch out.
This is, and this is at the trainer's house, folks.
He, he sits on the ground.
We sort of get him hard, I guess is the word.
And then I do a real low squat onto his lap.
If you want to call that gay, you can, but that's not how we see it.
It's just stretching and it stretches.
Oh, it stretches.
Dirk's not gentle.
Um, yeah, I was telling Pat, I just, Dirk's a real man with a new daughter.
Being Dirk don't engage in a pre -physical training intercourse.
That was a joke.
Um, hell of a name for a trainer.
Dirk.
I know, I know.
That's wild.
I don't, I'm sure I've told this story on air, but when I was, I was training
with him before my wedding and I talked to him about how I got this new job on
the cool kids and he goes, who's on the show?
And I, I rattle off the names.
And then when I said David Allen Greer, he goes, can you get out of it?
Wow.
And I I'm doing sit -ups.
I looked up at him and I go, what?
And he goes, I've been working in this town 25 years, man.
You don't want to take that fucking job.
And he was right.
You were right, Dirkie.
Dirk, that's great.
You got like a, this guy's all service.
This is, he's, he's like Danny Aiello and Jacob's ladder.
Like you go to him for one thing and then he's given you all this other.
That's beautiful.
Yeah.
You can't tell a personal trainer.
He looks like Danny Aiello though.
You're going to have a problem.
That's great.
Yeah.
Dirk, you remind me of Danny Aiello from Jacob's ladder only physically.
I was watching, um, the Martha Stewart documentary, just the first hour of it.
Okay.
Enjoying myself.
I enjoyed it, but they showed this.
It's always rough in a documentary when they show you like, people
weren't so kind at the time.
And they show you like, what was an SNL sketch?
Like a 1988 or whatever.
Holy shit.
It's Danny Aiello talking to, I forget who's playing Martha Stewart, but
he's the host clearly.
It's probably do the right thing era.
And he screams in the Martha Stewart's face.
He goes, this is why your husband left your ass.
It was like right after her husband and she did honor and left her.
I was like, good Lord.
I guess comedy was, I mean, I certainly miss the edge of comedy, but, uh,
sometimes you look back and you're like, Oh boy, that wasn't very nice.
Remember when they had, um, has she host the weekend?
Everybody thinks these like hard pendulum swings of SNL are, are new.
You know, like people are talking about how like they had the, they had
Kamala on the one week and then the next week, uh, burrs out there being
like, feminists are ugly, you know, like people were like, what is going on?
That's nothing new.
Do you remember like in the eighties, uh, when Sinead O 'Connor did the show
and tore up the picture of the Pope, the famous moment, the next week, Pesci
hosted, did a monologue where he goes, if I was here, I would have grabbed her
by her and then the joke is that she has no hair, but he's saying I would have
grabbed her by her hair and the crowd's like, woo woo cheering.
Yeah.
You know, and, uh, with the hindsight of time, I feel like, uh, Sinead O 'Connor
might've been the one who was more in the right by criticizing the Catholic
church for pedophilia, as opposed to Joe Pesci, uh, endorsing yanking a woman
around by her hair, we had our priorities a little mixed up at that time.
And as much as I'd rather listen to one of Joe Pesci's albums over
Sinead O 'Connor's album, I will say she is right.
She is right.
She was right.
I, my favorite, well, one of my favorite things about the great Chris Christofferson
was that at that time he went out and gave her a big hug and supported her at
that big Bob Dylan Madison square garden concert, everybody was booing her off the
stage, Christofferson walked out and gave her a big hug and told everybody
to shut the fuck up.
There's, there's always when something like that happens that pisses off like
the whole church crowd or whatever.
There's always the one guy that's like deep in the country weeds that everybody
thinks would be the guy that's like right on, she shouldn't have done it or
he shouldn't have done it, whoever that comes out and he's like, y 'all can
go fuck yourselves, but you know what I mean?
Like it's, there's always the one guy in that, in that moment it was Christofferson.
So always nice.
It was a lot of, uh, outlaw country fellas in that world.
They just respond to the, the underdog, regardless of their way of life.
And then you got modern country folks, uh, just not, not that way at all.
And that's probably why the music sucks dick.
Yeah.
There's some good new, there's some new country that's very good,
but a lot of it really sucks.
Um, I, um, well, I was going to talk about my
physical routine.
Um, I don't want to, um, I don't have a Dirk, uh, but what I do have
that I'm the proud new owner.
Uh, I texted you about this yesterday.
I thought it was worth talking about the pod finally pulled the trigger.
I've been saying for over a year, I'm going to buy every Burt Reynolds
mustached action movie from the eighties.
I will own all of them.
I've never seen any of them except Malone and Sharkey's machined.
Uh, yeah, Malone and I'm alone.
I didn't see till I bought it.
Uh, but I finally pulled the trigger and I bought all of them on, uh, Amazon.
Some total of, uh, $80 for all of them.
They're not, did you get any of those like Warner brothers, like four movies
on two disks kind of things, or these all individuals?
They offered some of those and I didn't want it.
I was like, I don't want the pack.
It's going to have two other movies.
I don't care about in it.
Yeah.
So some of these, I had to get on DVD because I wanted them solo.
I wanted them as their own thing.
And then also the Blu -ray of Sharkey's machine was an extra $15 in shipping
from Europe or so I was like, I'll get the DVD.
That's fine.
Anyway, we got stick, which I remember stick.
Oh, that's based on the Elmore Leonard.
I believe I think always saw the box for that as a kid in the store.
Never saw it stick.
It's weird.
Cause Burt Reynolds did all of these junk Elmore Leonard adaptations.
And then Tarantino made Elmore Leonard, like the hottest thing in the town.
Yeah, it's, it's odd.
Um, we got Sharkey's machine, of course, heat.
There's a Burt Reynolds movie named heat.
Never seen it.
That's not heat.
It's a different heat.
Um, yeah, this was remade as a Jason, Jason Statham movie.
Uh, I forget what it's called, but whatever.
Um, one I've never heard of called physical evidence.
That was the one that I've never even heard of.
I've never heard of that.
That's crazy.
Let's see here.
Physical.
Oh, it doesn't even bring up the movie when you type in physical evidence.
It's him and Teresa Russell.
Yeah, this is, this is when he was like right before evening shade drops.
Yeah.
This is when he's teetering into direct to D to VHS.
This is like what is starting, like him needing the Tarantino
comeback or whatever.
And then last but not least, Pat rent a cop with Liza.
Yeah.
That's the one I really want to see.
I'm going to watch all of them.
Uh, I'm excited.
And, uh, I mean, I feel like this is all these together with Malone.
I'm going to make my own little box set.
Why is there not a box set of all the Reynolds eighties action movie?
That that's a no brainer in my opinion.
Well, certainly a no brainer.
Uh, it looks like physical evidence was originally conceived as a
sequel to Jagged Edge and was meant to have Glenn Close and Robert
Lozier reprise their roles.
They used to do that a lot.
Like they develop something as a dirty Harry movie and then go, and
nah, we'll just do this with somebody else.
Well, the interesting one that they did that with was, what was the
Bruce Willis movie where he's like on the boat striking distance, striking
distance that was supposed to be diehard three.
Yeah.
And then they were like, it's not good enough to be diehard three.
They were right.
Yeah.
So, um, it looked at physical evidence directed by Michael Crichton.
I didn't know that.
We didn't know that.
It's a weird time in the eighties.
Did he direct movies?
I guess so.
I've never heard of this before.
I mean, I could see him adapting one of his own books or something, but.
I just watched.
Yeah, he directed.
I just watched a bunch of, uh, I won't do them in the movie corner
because I did them last year, but I started my, you know, Thanksgiving
movie watches or whatever, which always include when Harry met
Sally and you've got mail.
Uh, I've never seen, believe it or not, Sleepless in Seattle, which
is considered Nora Efron's, you know, masterpiece, obviously, because
it never seemed to me, it just never struck me as, as funny or as charming
or as fun as some of the other movies she made, it seemed kind of sad.
I would.
The only thing that's sad about it is that he is a widow and that's just
kind of how the movie begins, but, uh, Sleepless in Seattle is great.
I would say if you want to give when Harry met Sally and A plus, you got
mail an A, Sleepless in Seattle is right there with an A minus, but to
me it's the weakest of the three.
I think generally considered better than you've got mail,
but people love that more.
It's, it's grown a reputation over time lately.
So the reason I bring it up is I started watching a bunch of stuff
about Sleepless in Seattle because I'd never seen it.
Yeah.
It was the one I didn't know any backstory with, but I was reading
about it.
It said the script floated around.
Somebody wrote the script.
It floated around.
It was passed on by every studio.
And then whoever acquired it said, we got to bring in somebody
to make this funnier.
It's too sad.
So then they brought in Nora Efron and she did the rewrite.
Yeah.
And then they said during the rewrite process, they just made her the director.
And I'm like, she had never directed anything.
I mean, it's wild.
They were just like, you're going to direct it.
And then she became a director after that.
Um, but I guess that kind of just happened back then.
You could kind of just get shuffled in because you proved your worth elsewhere.
Yeah.
I mean, a woman director was much more of a rarity.
I think David S.
Ward, we talked about on the show, the guy who wrote major league in the sting
wrote one of the drafts and was maybe going to direct, but, um,
I love Efron.
I love, uh, mixed nuts, which gets a bum rap.
I watch it pretty much every year.
I enjoyed lucky numbers too good.
Lucky numbers of solid.
Sure.
You know what?
I'm wrong.
That's not her directorial debut.
She directed a small film called this is my life, I think saying it.
Um, so she had directed something, so I'm wrong, but Efron.
I'm a huge fan.
I mean, I, it's, she's one of those people that it makes me sad
that I'll never meet her.
You watch an interview with Nora Efron.
You're like, this is everybody's favorite aunt.
This lady is so awesome.
And she's so funny.
I love her books and I love a lot of her movies, even the ones that are considered
bad, but you want to talk about, some people just get the pass and other people
don't dude, she, she ran on good credit for a long time.
I mean, she's got a string of movies that flopped and then she ended on a high
note with Julia and Julia, but I mean, she's got like five in a row before
that that were panned that made no money.
But you know, it's weird.
Now, like that was a time where if you made your $25 million movie.
And let's say it only brought in 15, you know, it was a loser.
You can still kind of keep a float because you weren't costing the
studio $400 million dollars.
But now people rarely get more than one big miss.
It seems like right at this moment in time, unless you've made a hundred of
these giant special effects extravaganza is then they let you do it until you die.
Basically.
Yeah, I don't know.
I, I, I miss that era.
I guess, look, there's a lot of Indies out now.
I'm trying to be positive about things.
You know, I, it's, there's, there's less excitement when they come straight
to like Amazon prime or something, but we still kind of get those kind of movies.
They just tend to look like shit and not be as good as they used to be.
Well, the next episode we do is heretic and, um, I guess that's an Indy, right?
It counts as an, I mean, eight 24.
It's hard anymore to say it's an Indy, but yeah, I mean, I think the, that
horror is, is one of the few genres that is pretty much consistently lower budget.
Even smile too.
I would bet they pulled it in under 50 million, but I don't know that for sure.
Um, let's go to the movie corn, talk about some of these films.
Um, I will start with the Apple TV picture wolves.
Oh yeah.
And, uh, that's the exact right reaction, Joe.
If you could, if you could imagine that a movie starring George Clooney and
Brad Pitt that everyone would forget that it exists, it's been out for months
and no one has watched it.
And then when you remind people about its existence, they go, Oh yeah.
And the movie probably costs $250 million.
George Clooney, there was rumors that these guys made 40 million a piece for
wolves and they asked them and they both had these like shit eating grins.
And they're like, that's, that's crazy.
That's over reported.
We don't want to mess the business up.
You know, we don't want to, we don't want to report that, but you could tell they
did make 40 million a piece for this movie.
Um, and it sucks.
It's terrible.
Really?
It was, yeah, it was written and directed by John Watts, who I have discussed
quite a bit on this show because I loved his first movie cop car.
And from there he went on and did nothing but spider -mans.
And now he is, I'm like, okay, he's doing a crime thriller.
He's back to cop car, but that movie costs 2 million bucks.
Now he's got a budget.
This is going to be awesome.
Man, this just stinks.
It's a, it feels like an Apple TV movie.
Everything is gray.
Everything looks like it costs, you know, way too much to look drab and like shit.
Um, the movie is Amy Adams, who was not Amy Adams.
What's her name?
From the office, Joe, Amy Ryan, gone, baby gone.
I love Amy Ryan, love Amy Ryan.
Um, great to see her again.
She is hooking up with a very young man, like early twenties.
Um, he dies.
She makes a call to a mysterious figure and George Clooney shows up to
help dispose of the body.
Okay.
To cut, you know, to cover up this high profile crime.
Um, after about five minutes, a second fixer shows up to solve the crime.
Brad Pitt.
So imagine like Winston Wolf and pulp fiction, and then a
second guy shows up to do it.
So you're like, okay, sort of interesting.
Like these two guys competing over who's going to help.
And they both think they're the best and whatever.
All right, I got it.
And for two hours, you watch these guys muttered under their breath.
Like Rick, you fucking asshole, you jerk.
Oh, what, you know, you're getting a little old there.
What do you don't know how to bend over and tie your shoe anymore?
It's like grumpy old men, except for two 55 year old hot dudes.
So it doesn't work at all.
And there's no good jokes and no good insults and no good quips.
It's just two guys saying fuck you and shut up to each other for two hours as
they both try to help this woman out.
The guy they think is dead.
Spoiler alert runs away.
So he's running through the city in his briefs and you got Pitt and Clooney
out trying to get him back.
It just doesn't have a pulse.
The kid's name is Austin Abrams from a euphoria.
Didn't care for him.
You're just, uh, these guys who, who have always kind of relied on their
charm, their charms drying up.
And at a time where we care less and less about celebrity Brad Pitt and George
Clooney batting their eyes at each other for two hours is not, does not a movie
make, I hated this movie, Joe.
All right.
Well, seasonal watches that I haven't discussed on here before that, at least
that I know of, uh, doubt, I rewatched doubt for some reason, movies about the
church, Catholic church, Catholic upbringing, that sort of thing always
feel appropriate for me at this time of year, the fall.
I don't know what it is exactly.
Why the church movies usually rarely take place in the summertime.
They always seem to take place in the fall.
The leaves are falling.
The wind is blowing, which is a heavy theme in doubt.
Um, you know, there's a physical coldness in the movie and sometimes an emotional
one, uh, I don't know, it just makes me think of the holidays.
Um, this movie is awesome.
I really regret that I didn't see the play when it was on Broadway
in this latest revival, but if you haven't seen it, Philip Seymour Hoffman,
Meryl, wait, the play or the movie?
Who was in the latest Broadway.
Well, I saw it with Cherry Jones 20 years ago.
We talked about it.
It was Liv Shriver and, uh, and, uh, the lady from Cagney and Lacey.
Oh yeah.
Tyne Daly.
Yeah.
Which good for her, but I just didn't know she was still working.
Um, yeah, I like Liv Shriver.
I like Tyne Daly.
I'm hard pressed to think that they could compete with Philip Seymour
Hoffman and Meryl Streep.
Um, Viola Davis, not less.
Yeah.
Viola Davis, uh, and Amy Adams is, is in this movie.
Um, I've seen this movie.
That is one of my favorite movies.
It really is.
It's, it's a fantastic film.
I've seen it probably 10 times.
Every time I watch it, I think I'm going to get closer to being able to
determine whether or not he actually did the thing he's accused of doing.
And every time I'm like, no, I don't know if he did it or not.
This is like, it is so pitch perfect and keeping you guessing on
either side of the accusation.
Um, and it's just a riveting, riveting performance and it's the best kind of,
I'm not saying, I shouldn't say the best kind of movie, but movies that are this
simple and this direct, in fact, it's one of the things Nora Efron said in one of
the interviews I was watching with her about, you've got mail.
She said, when you have a good story and a good structure with good characters,
you can have a six minute scene of just Tom Hanks and Meg Ryan confronting one
another in a coffee shop and it's interesting.
And she was like, because, excuse me, she goes, because that's life.
That's what your life is.
Your life is not car chases and explosions.
Your life is conversations and awkward moments and what have you.
Um, doubt falls into that category.
100 % believable characters.
It really resonated with me because it addresses the change in the church's
approach to society, which was a thing that was still lingering and resonating.
When I was in Catholic school in the eighties, uh, there were still these
old school nuns that really, you know, went hard in the paint for, for the
traditional doctrine that all kind of changed in the sixties.
There were more rogue clergy that were loved by some and disapproved of by
others in the parish and within the church itself.
Um, and I, you know, I was in Catholic school at the time that like the shit was
about to hit the fan with all of the molestation stuff and everything.
Uh, I'd never seen anything like that happen.
After everything got exposed, I found out one of the priests I went to that
was at my high school was guilty, which was wild.
Um, yeah.
And by the way, not the guy you would have thought it was.
There was a priest at my high school that was real flirty.
Turns out he never did anything.
It was this other guy that you'd never would have suspected.
Um, anyway, um, the first priest just like the thrill of the chase.
Yeah.
He's the, he liked the hunt, but once he caught him, he was, he was done.
He's that, that priest was Jerry Reed and Smokey and the Bandit.
You're like, they were like, you get out there and flirt.
Then they won't notice what they're doing over here.
Um, anyway, doubt's a great movie.
Uh, it's, it's, it's, it is a play on film.
Uh, it's challenging.
It's interesting.
And you have great empathy and sympathy for every character in the film, uh,
despite all of their foibles and, and flaws and whatever.
It's just, it's just a riveting.
And by the way, most importantly, and I texted you this thing's a masterpiece.
It is a 10 out of 10 film clocks in at what an hour and 45 minutes, which
means your watch time is about an hour 39 because six of those minutes are credits.
It's yes, this is what a movie should be.
Everything doesn't, I'm sitting here.
I sat down to watch smile too, and we'll get to it.
I text you, I go, this thing is two 20.
What, what are we, what are we talking about here?
What is going on?
Smile too is two 20.
So, as I told Joe at the time, Billy Ocean told us the entire story of a young
Caribbean queen in under five minutes.
Something to think about something to think about, uh, watched out.
I almost don't want to get into any more details.
Obviously you can get the gist of what, what it's probably about with some of
the things I've said, but if you haven't seen it, sit down and watch it.
It's also, by the way, it's one of those great dramas and movies that has depth
that you could actually watch with your family and not feel uncomfortable the
whole time, even given the weight of what the movie's about, it never gets like
awkward or graphic or, or, or gross or whatever.
It's just, it's just a riveting film.
It's not like testimonies or like, it's not like a door shutting and a light
going off, even there's nothing even like that suggestive about it.
It's just kind of like all off camera.
And that's really what makes it.
I mean, it's, it's Philip Seymour Hoffman's movie.
Like he, you, you go for, you hate him one minute and you're sure he did it.
And then you're like, this guy's too.
That, but that's the problem with it.
When the times you do like him and think he couldn't have molested these kids are
the time he's being really charming and sweet and funny, and you can't, that's
your decision maker for who's a molester and who's not, you know what I mean?
Right.
So, um, I, I can't recommend doubt enough and, uh, yes, check it out.
Um, I watched a brand new movie that I really enjoyed called flip side.
Uh, it was produced by Judd Apatow.
This is a movie that probably cost five cents.
Um, it is a very cheap documentary about a subject that probably, uh, I would
bet most people in my life would hear this and go either I'm dying to see that
or, oh God, that sounds way too intense and personal.
I don't want to watch that.
Um, and it's somewhere in between.
It's not, it's not a miserable slog.
It's just a movie that's really honest about a topic that a lot of people
don't like to talk about, which is failure, which is what about
these people who pursue a career in the arts?
And it just never happens for them.
That's most people that pursue a career in the arts.
So, you know, a celebration of that is a great idea for a documentary
and kind of a beautiful thing.
I really enjoyed this.
So this is about a guy named Chris Wiltshire, who we know a lot of people
like this Joe, they assemble a career where they're sort of in entertainment
for like 20 years, but there might be a five year period where they don't work.
They're never getting that project that they're excited about.
They're always working in sort of a lower level.
So this guy's career consists of things like he made his own, you know,
student film out of college.
He was asked by Judd Apatow to produce and direct the, like, um, making a
funny people documentary on the funny people Blu ray.
So that's the kind of job where you're like, Oh, cool.
I'm working with Apatow and all the, you know, all these cool comedy
people and everything, but you're not the guy, you know, you're making
these supplementary material.
So this guy's always talking about how he just felt like, why can't
I get into this business?
And we see clips from so many started and aborted documentaries that this guy
started and his family's there in the background and he's like, I feel like
failure because I started 20 documentaries that I didn't get anywhere
with, but then I remember my family and my wife and kids and like, I can't
be mad at them for keeping me from my dreams and maybe I wouldn't have made
my dreams with or without them and blah, blah, blah, just the kind of life
questions, career questions, deep questions that everyone asks themselves
and everyone stresses about, but I've never seen it put into a documentary
like this and I really love that.
He also talks about this old jazz photographer who's, you know, looks
like he's 90 years old and he spent his entire life photographing Miles Davis
and all these jazz greats.
He finally gets a little credit and praise for it as he's on his death bed
at age 90, so we follow that guy a little bit and you know, he comes out
and everybody's clapping for him and he's just uncontrollably crying because
no one has ever appreciated his work in his entire life.
There's this guy who owns this record store in New Jersey that he grew up
working in, the guy, the filmmaker, and it's this record store that looks
awesome to me, but it's just crates on the floor and crates everywhere and
the guy likes kind of this chaos of the store.
Then a new record store moves in down the street and everyone starts going
there cause it's cleaner and it's better.
And this guy goes back to his old haunt, this old record store he used to work at
and it's kind of about how this guy's getting up there and he's 70 years old
and nobody comes to his record store anymore.
And it used to be the hot shit in town.
And he, maybe if he cleaned it up more, it would do better,
but then it wouldn't be his store.
And you get it.
It's just a movie that it's, it's almost like an NPR type thing.
It just looks at the lives of your average person and asks them about
their embarrassments, struggles, failures, regrets.
It's not a tearjerker.
It's actually very uplifting.
I really enjoyed the movie and it's on Canopy for free.
If you have a library card, that's the only place I can currently find it.
Maybe it's on Prime too.
Joe, another bunch of movies that put me in the mood for the season.
All of the Rocky movies make me think of the fall.
I think mainly because the training sequences, he's always outside in the cold.
Rocky was on my list.
Yes, it was.
Now I rewatched, not just for the season, but also because of the
Tyson -Paul fight, Rocky Balboa, because as I was watching the Tyson -Paul
fight, the preliminary stuff unfold, I was realizing this is the
exact plot of Rocky VI.
It's the old Titan fighter that people say couldn't possibly fight anymore.
Going up against this young new fighter who's considered kind of a punk.
People don't really take them seriously.
He might be a good fighter, but they're saying he's only winning because he's
not meeting any formidable opponents.
It's an exhibition spectacle for entertainment purposes only, blah, blah,
blah.
The parallels were ridiculous.
Down to Tyson's only ability entering into that fight was potentially offering
brute strength versus the agility of a young fighter or whatever.
Now the Tyson -Jake -Paul fight, unfortunately, turned out to be terrible.
Two men dancing around to collect $20 million.
Tyson made $20 million.
I think Jake -Paul made $40 million or something.
It did not have the beautiful triumphant ending that Rocky VI does, because it's
funny, in the press conference in Rocky VI, the champ says to him, look, we're
doing this as an exhibition.
If he starts trying to hurt me, he's going to get hurt, so keep it cool out
there and nobody's going to have a problem.
Dance around and whatever.
And then of course, Rocky goes in and gives him a real fight.
And that's the beauty of the movie.
Rocky VI is awesome.
It is arguably my favorite of all the Rocky movies.
I mean, you have to say Rocky I, because that's the masterpiece and that's where
it started, but as far as Rocky movies I return to the most, Rocky Balboa is the
one I've gone back to the most.
I was crying from scene one of this movie.
It opens with him at the graveyard.
You realize Adrian's dead.
He's at her grave.
You know what she meant to him.
He's estranged from his son.
He's trying to fix the relationship.
He's got nothing.
He's got nothing in his life that is emotionally fulfilling for him.
He feels like it's all left him behind.
And then he realizes, as he says in the film, there's still some stuff in the
basement, I need to get it out.
I need to fight again.
It is an awesome, awesome movie.
It's the training sequence will get you up and out of your seat,
cheering the fight at the end is great.
The whole thing is awesome.
Just go watch it.
If you've never seen it, watch Rocky Balboa.
It's, it's a, it's a, I love it so much.
I love the movie and I love his portrayal of Rocky Balboa so much in this
movie that if I ever met Sylvester Stallone, I would be legitimately sad
that he's not that person.
Like you want, you want him to just be Rocky Balboa when you meet him.
Just like when you meet Martin Short, you wish he was Jiminy Glick, even
though I'd love to meet Rocky or Martin Short as, as they are as people.
Sometimes a character is so robust.
You're sad that the person playing the character isn't actually the way they
are in real life or whatever, but, uh, I can't, my favorite choice.
Yeah.
My favorite choice with that character is when they give him the little glasses
and he almost starts to look like an old lady in Creed.
I just thought that that was like the perfect direction for him to go.
Yeah.
Um, I agree.
I saw Rocky Balboa.
I think it was the first movie I saw at the theater upon moving to LA.
I definitely needed a kick in the ass career wise, inspiration wise.
I cried throughout the whole thing myself.
It is probably number two to the original Rocky for me, but it's amazing.
I love it.
Can't recommend it enough Rocky Balboa.
Check it out.
By the way, by the way, real quick, arguably, excuse me, was Stallone the
first guy ever to do a legacy sequel?
I'm watching this thing and I'm like, I remember when they announced that he
was going to do this and everybody was like, wait, what he's making another
Rocky movie and it led to Creed and all that stuff.
Right after he did this Rambo coming back, he did Rambo.
I'm like, is Stallone responsible for like the reboot legacy sequel thing?
Like I feel like he might be.
I, I would think he can't be, but I can't really think of anyone else.
It's wild Terminator and T2 was only like seven years apart, so it's different,
but I'm sure we can think of one, but I can't.
And also too, he does it perfectly in Rocky Balboa because every nod to the
first movie is done in a way where if you know the first movie, it has extra
meaning and if you don't, it still makes perfect sense.
He just really nails it in this thing.
It's a great movie.
What about Hustler Color of Money?
Um, well, the thing is, well, I get you, yeah, theoretically, sure, but what to
me, the difference is, is Color of Money is a true just sequel to the Hustler
because it's not about re glorifying Paul Newman.
It's about Tom Cruise, but that's, I guess that's also how legacy
sequels work too, where the older guy comes in.
Yeah, that, I guess that could count.
Creed is a better parallel to Color of Money.
Creed is Color of Money, I guess.
I say Rocky Balboa because it's not just a sequel that came years after anybody
thought it would have been done.
It also leads to the ongoing of the franchise, like which Color of Money
didn't, it was just a sequel and that was it, which I still think it's a crime.
I want to make a third installment to that series so bad where then where
Tom Cruise is now the Paul Newman guy.
Yeah.
And there's a, there's a, I mean, they look, if they're making
Days of Thunder two, then we might look, we could get that Color of Money
sequel, Days of Thunder was not that much bigger a hit than Color of Money.
And Color of Money was certainly more critically acclaimed.
Have you seen the Ben Stiller as Tom Cruise, Color of Money spoof
that he did for SNL?
Yeah, it's awesome.
That's pretty funny.
His Tom Cruise is like, it's, it's, it's such a great impression because
it's an impression that nobody did.
It was such a weird impression and he nails it.
Well, and he nails the cackling better than anyone could, the laughing at
himself, like in his own little world.
He nails that so well.
He also did on the MTV awards of a Mission Impossible Two sketch as
Tom Cruise that I still remember.
And I only saw it one time, but he was pitching Tom Cruise that the motorcycle
fly through the air in this fireball.
And then he goes right when you get to like the peak and the motorcycles,
like on top of the fireball, you're in midair once you look at the camera
and say, this mission just got a hell of a lot more impossible.
Oh, made me laugh.
Stiller's great.
I don't know what the end of his career will look like, but, uh, I'm happy to see
it, I guess this new movie, he's like babysitting three kids.
It looks like an R rated adventures in babysitting.
I can't wait.
I mean, I hope he can, I hope a lot of these guys get old.
I haven't seen the trailer.
I watched the trailer.
It's, it's okay.
I think it's, listen, everybody's saying like this returned to form for Ben
Stiller, it's going to be so great to see a comedy like this again.
But you watch the trailer, you're like, this movie is clearly going to be
half heavy drama, you know, really.
That's also very funny at times.
I shouldn't say heavy, but it feels like like the Family Stone or something like
that, where it's like, it will be very funny, but there's going to be a lot of
So you mean a masterpiece, an American masterpiece?
I love the Family Stone, but I'm saying you wouldn't go, you wouldn't watch the
Family Stone and go, what a return to form for Luke Wilson being back in a
comedy like old school.
It's, it's, you can tell it's going to be quite serious.
Um, does it have a Holdovers vibe?
Yeah.
Comedy drama kind of?
A little, a little less serious than Holdovers or a little less
potentially artsy.
I also, look, I'm going to see it.
I'm concerned it's going to weigh too heavily and you'll know after you watch
the trailer, I'm concerned it's going to weigh too heavily on the kids being
funny.
Sure.
Cussing.
All they do is kids cussing.
Yeah, that, that can suck.
When they just start, like that movie, Good Boys, I was like, oh, the only
thing you came up with for these kids to do was cuss that then it's, I mean,
South park is that to some degree, but they were, you know, so far beyond the
norm that it was, it was genuinely shocking again, but I don't know, old,
old people cussing and, and kids cussing is always like good for a joke, but I
always worry when that's the whole movie.
Uh, I saw for my consideration this awards season, his three daughters, it's
new to Netflix directed by Azazel Jacobs.
Has there ever been a name that sounded more like a demon that would appear in
a new exorcist movie than Azazel?
Um, his three daughters is in the mix for a lot of, uh, acting awards,
particularly this, this Oscar season.
And okay, you know, this is much more in line with the kind of movie that always
used to be awards bait.
Uh, it is three sisters, Carrie Kuhn, who I love Elizabeth Olson, who I love
and Natasha Leon, who I like.
And I'm glad that they don't put her in everything like they did for a year
there because she was in danger of becoming very overexposed, but these
three play sisters, their dad is dying.
Natasha Leon is the stoner black sheep of the family who has been taking care of him.
Yeah.
Elizabeth Olson is the happily married, um, very kind of, uh, new age mom kind of
gal, and then Carrie Kuhn is the extremely uptight judgmental can't believe
that her sister smokes pot while she takes care of the dad, you know, on and
on and on these three bicker and fight.
There are moments where it feels very lived in like a real family arguing.
There are moments where it feels like a play where it's just three actors trying
to outdo each other and, you know, delivering monologue and, Oh, you're
done with your monologue.
Well, then wait until I share my monologue when I, and then, you know,
that sort of shit gets a little old to me.
It feels a little performative.
There's a Woody Allen -ish quality to this where it's like very serious,
heavy monologues in a New York apartment.
Uh, they don't leave the apartment.
It's about 90 minutes.
So it gets a little claustrophobic.
And for me, even though we are dealing with a dead dad or a dying dad and the
three sisters trying to figure out, um, their own bullshit to try to make his
last days on earth, a little more peaceful.
It weirdly doesn't hit on an emotional level.
There's, I can't imagine anybody seeing this and crying.
Not that it has to be that to be good, but it's also not particularly funny.
It's just kind of this slice of life about three sisters.
Um, again, the kind of thing Woody Allen used to do, the kind of thing,
the Sundance Indies always used to do, but I don't know.
I don't think there's anything special about this movie outside of having three
really good actresses as the sisters.
It's average.
I don't think we're going to see a lot of this come awards time, but Hey,
so on Netflix, you're paying for the membership.
You could do a lot worse on there than this.
It's a, it's an okay, a little character drama show.
Um, last but not least, uh, another type of film that always gets me in the
mood for this fall season is anything about New York, uh, that really, and I
hate to use the phrase makes New York a character, uh, but you know, I guess
because of the song autumn in New York, I just always sort of associate New
York with, with the autumn with the exception of do the right thing since
it's hyper focused on it being the hottest day of the year.
Um, but, uh, this last movie is Saturday night fever, which embarrassingly, I
will admit I have seen in pieces throughout my entire life.
I don't know that I ever sat down and watched it start to finish.
Uh, I did my God almighty.
It's, I mean, I'm not saying anything, but it's a fucking masterpiece.
Jesus Christ.
This thing.
And dark, did you did?
Well, did you watch the R rated version or the PG version?
No, I watched this because definitely the hard R version of this movie.
Gang rape version.
Yeah.
The, uh, I'm not going to, I'm not going to derail your review, but there, there
was a R rated version released in theaters that became a huge hit, but then
there were all these young people who wanted to see the disco scenes and like
watch the dancing and they couldn't get into the movie, so they re -edited and
re -released a PG version, which they'd used to do occasionally, but not very
often, so I for years had seen the PG version and then when they released it on
4k, I popped it in having never seen all these scenes.
I was just like, holy shit.
It's a, it's a completely different movie.
One is a dance musical and one is a very somber, depressing coming of age movie
with a little bit of dancing in it.
But, uh, go ahead, Joe, make sure you get the right one is what I'm saying.
Yeah.
I didn't know about the PG version much like passion of the Christ is the only
two movies, Deadpool, Deadpool 2, Deadpool 2, passion of the Christ, there's a good
box set, the PG version of three extremely graphic films.
Um, uh, you know, look, it's, it's, it's not, if you haven't seen the movie, I
think given the soundtrack, given the popularity of the soundtrack, given the
popularity of all the imagery from the film, from over the years and whatever, I
think it would be easy for you to just assume it's this basically music video of
John Travolta dancing disco and everybody loved it cause disco was popular.
That is not what this movie is.
This is a gritty, uh, exploration of a man who is the biggest fish in the
smallest pond coming to terms with the fact that everything he values greatly
doesn't have a ton of meaning and he's lost in life, which redefines the, that's
why the, I mean, the Lear, if you listen to the lyrics of staying alive, the
breakdown is somebody helped me.
I'm going nowhere.
Like, and that's kind of the part we all just glaze over.
We always think it's like this fun disco song.
And it's like, no, the song is about like, I'm just staying alive.
I'm just living.
Like there's, there's no direction to any of this.
And that's very much with the movie.
One of the things the movie gets into, it is a no apologies depiction of a certain
type of male that lived in a certain type of neighborhood in the 1970s.
Um, the characters are nothing short of reprehensible, uh, all of them,
uh, not the entire time.
Some of them like Travolta have redeeming qualities and you hope
that they better themselves.
But I mean, there's some tough stuff in the movie, um, Distur outwardly disturbing
to say the least, um, it's a heavy, heavy flick, but it's real, it's raw.
And it's, it's considered to have cultural significance for a reason.
Like it's, it's an amazing movie.
But what's so funny is, is when you see this movie and you see the places it goes
to, especially in the third act, and then you see like Madagascar does like a spoof
of the opening and you're like, it's weird that like kids, like, like the
Muppets did a Saturday night fever record.
And you're like, it's so weird.
Like that these kid things, I mean, they're satirizing it because it's a
pop culture phenomenon at the time.
I get that, but it is, it's weird.
It's a weird, when you see some of the content of this film, uh, the
funniest parody of Saturday night fever is in airplane, which is when I was a
kid, that was my favorite sequence of airplane.
I thought that was so fucking funny.
Now I didn't watch the sequel because it's, you know, it's considered one
of the worst sequels of all time, but I did watch it by Stallone.
I own it in 4k and I have never seen it.
I can't believe you have that in fork.
That's come on, dude.
That was when I was on a buying Tara 4k and that's, that's the
one that made me go, that's enough.
Pat, you need to be more discerning going forward.
Well, the last, can I tell you the last scene of staying alive?
And it's the only scene worthwhile in the movie.
I've, I've watched, I think almost all, because the problem with staying
alive is none of it is about him.
There's one scene where he goes back to the neighborhood and that's
what the whole movie should be.
The whole movie should be the neighborhood has moved on and he is
trying to, but is struggling and it's not, he's moved on.
He's goes in, he's now in Manhattan.
He's dancing on Broadway.
Yeah.
It's just not what you want.
And, um, yeah, but that character would not be a dancer on Broadway.
That doesn't make any sense for that character.
It's just, yeah.
So in it's about the same thing as Rocky becoming a dancer on Broadway,
but the last scene and the only scene that ties you into the first one
and man is it fan service.
Everything works out in the end.
He's finally got his shit together.
He's finally figured it out.
He says to his girlfriend, he kisses her.
Big moment.
And then he goes, you know what I want to do?
And she goes, what?
He goes strut and he walks out the door of the theater, staying
alive, starts playing and they, they redo the opening of Saturday
at fever with him walking around Times Square.
And it's the, I got chills just saying the scene.
It's this, it's this, it's like seeing Han Solo come back on the
Millennium Falcon and force awakens.
You're like, this is what we wanted.
Where was this for the first 90 minutes of this thing, but you don't get it.
But that's, that ending is sometimes when you catch up with these things
as an adult, um, you have a very different experience with them.
But I remember watching on the Simpsons Bart saying that, like, you know
what I want to do strut, and then he does the walk around town.
But when I saw Saturday night fever, I was like, that's not in this.
Now I realized they were parroting, staying alive, which is an
even more obscure parody.
But, um, Saturday night fever at any record store, you can get that double
album soundtrack for like a dollar 99.
If you look in the discount bins, cause every everybody's parents had
at least one copy of it.
And I still throw it on every three months or so.
It's like, it's the best disco album.
Disco albums are usually a lot of filler, and this is just
like two hours of gold dance.
If you, if you're cleaning your house, could do a hell of a lot
worse than the Saturday night fever soundtrack.
And I put it up there, you know, it feels like it's in the same New York,
the same seventies New York world of like, uh, uh, of a Rocky, of a dog
day afternoon, a Serpico, you know, you could see Tony Manero sort of being
in that company of all those great Pacino, Dustin Hoffman, De Niro characters.
And Travolta was kind of on that track, but boy did his career
derailed for a decade easily.
Look, who's talking was his comeback movie.
If, if that gives you any idea of how far he had fallen.
And by the way, also, yeah, Travolta it's look, who's talk it's huge
comeback, huge smash success.
And then they immediately, he immediately derailed again because
he did the two sequels and the sequels are God awful.
Anyway, that's all I got.
Anyway, that's my three you did.
Did we both do three?
We both did three.
And now we move on to the movie at hand, which is the sequel to surprisingly one
of the most successful horror movies of the last 10 years, smile.
It is called of course, smile too.
Aside from the Kyle Gallner character who my date said, Ooh, I love him.
And I was like, you love Kyle Gallner?
Uh, anyway, there's no one else in this movie that's carried
over from the original smile.
It's a whole new story, a whole new, unless I missed something.
I only saw a smile once Joe told me to read about how the curse works.
And like, you're going to be a little lost if you don't read up on it.
I did read the Wikipedia.
I still felt a little lost in spots during smile too, mostly because
I feel like they invented a little bit of their own logic here and there.
And I wasn't always clear on, which is the case with a lot of these movies
outside of, you know, gremlins or something, if they don't, if they don't
say the rules explicitly, sometimes you're like, wait, what smile too,
in particular, when the, when the smile thing becomes a monster.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on.
Hold on.
I want to stop this.
Sorry.
I don't mean to cut you off.
I want to stress, I want to, this is one of the reviews where I really want to
stress if you want to see this movie, don't listen to this review because this
is going to ruin everything because there's no way to talk about the
movie without ruining every twist.
Yeah.
So, so just a fair warning, but we'll give us, give us the plot walkthrough
Joseph, if you would.
Well, the plot walkthrough is the same thing as the first one.
It's the, the last person that has the curse in the first movie is the
boyfriend cop at the beginning of this movie.
Yeah.
He's trying to pass off the curse to a couple of drug dealers that have
murdered people, which is a good little piece of writing.
He's a cop.
He would be aware of these guys, right?
When he goes to do it, it goes haywire on him.
He ends up passing the curse inadvertently to a guy that just buys from them.
And it turns out that that guy that buys from these dealers is the supplier to a
pop star who is a, you know, an Ariana Grande, Dupa, Lepa, whatever, you
know, the big pop star type, he deals to her.
You find out that she is just getting over, uh, a year of rehab and, uh,
addiction and whatnot.
Um, this is, she's about to do her big comeback tour.
She's on the Drew Barrymore show.
Yeah.
Giving a public apology.
Um, and she is struggling to not relapse.
Uh, however, she, you find out that she was in a car accident, which
led to her going into rehab.
Her boyfriend was killed in the car accident because of her addiction.
They will not give her painkillers for the back injury she
suffered in the car accident.
So she is forced to return to her former drug dealer, the kid that the
curse has been passed to in order to get some Percocet because she, she
can't blow this tour, because if she cancels this tour, cause she can't
do it, her career will be over.
Um, that's the basic plot.
Of course, when she goes to buy the Percocet, the kid passes the
curse to her and she is then haunted there on through the rest of the film.
It's, it plays out very similarly to the way the first movie does.
Everybody around her is pushing her to account for her past mistakes, for
her to be the best version of herself.
She's on the right track and everybody is very proud of her, but as the
curse starts to taunt her and haunt her and what have you, people start to
think that she's just relapsing back into her old ways and she's
going to fuck everything up.
That's the basic plot.
The reason I, I interrupted you in telling the audience that's listening
to this, that if you want to see it, tune out is because they do something
in the middle of this film that was a big ask, but I do think it worked,
which was in the first movie, the hallucinations were, were, were part
of the curse and the hallucinations were pretty intense, meaning like a
person, the, the, the, the main character of the first movie, like her
therapist would come to her house and then it would turn out the therapist
was the demon and the therapist was never even actually there.
It was just a taunt or whatever.
This one, they take it even further, farther.
That was a good scene.
I remember that.
Yeah, this one, they take it farther where you realize at the end of the
movie, the entire second half of the movie was her hallucinating and
none of it ever happened.
Um, that's a big ask, you know, uh, I thought it worked, but you know,
that's, that's a, that's a huge, that's huge.
It's a big ask.
I don't remember in the original smile, things like this giant red demon that
like overtakes her at the end of this movie, like that, I, I, I was just kind
of like, what am I watching and what does this even have to do with smile?
I did have to do a little bit of reading up on the Wiki and kind of figure
out what was happening, but it didn't matter to me.
I think that this guy, Parker Finn is really, really good at creating a
sense of dread, um, using special effects to show you something really
wild that you've never seen before.
There's a lot of moments in both smiles.
Like when this thing is reaching its fist down her throat, you know, um,
that you're just kind of, it's one of those things where you're like, are
they going to cut away from this?
Like, this is crazy.
Um, felt a little like drag me to hell in spots, which is one of my
favorite horror movies.
I just, I dug it even when I wasn't a hundred percent sure of what was going
on. Um, there's a, there's a surreal, a crazy element to these smile
movies that I really like.
And I think this guy is very good at directing horror.
Um, I don't know why this was so long.
Seems needless.
I assume we'll get a smile three.
Well, uh, yes.
What Joe?
No.
Yeah.
I'm saying, well, yeah, I'm saying when you said that I'm, I'm, my, my
reaction is saying, yeah, they definitely set this up for a major, for sure.
Huge.
See, uh, yeah, I think we will get a smile three.
And then I can't say I'm pumped.
I'm, I'm cautiously optimistic, but this guy, Parker Finn, who has a big
overall deal now at Paramount to kind of make whatever movies he wants, uh, his
next movie is going to be a remake of possession, which we discussed on this
Joe and is an amazing horror movie about divorce.
So we'll see.
I don't know what that will be like.
I don't know if it will be a faithful remake or what, but like, this guy's good.
You know, he's not like some hack, uh, horror guy.
I like what he's doing from a writing standpoint and from a directing
standpoint, the shots are always interesting.
The scares are always interesting.
Jump scares are not, um, are not the only thing here.
They're there.
Don't get me wrong, but they're effective.
And there's also just a lot of stuff like this big red monster at the end.
We're like, my jaw was just kind of on the floor.
I was like, what, what's happening?
And that feeling is very exciting to me, especially in a quote, generic
horror movie that like everybody's going to go see this goes to some really
weird, interesting places.
And the Britney Spears or Lady Gaga thing, you know, we, we've seen many,
many horror slash addiction movies.
Um, just like smile was a horror slash trauma movie, and we've
seen way too many of those.
The horror addiction thing has been done in like the evil dead sequels and so
forth and many, many other movies, but it works here and it's like, it kind
of raises that interesting question of like, are we responsible for the
downfall of these pop stars?
Like I love chaperone's music.
It appears she's losing her mind because of the public.
Um, not again, not the most original theme who are we responsible for this pop
star, but the themes are there.
They're explored in interesting ways.
I liked smile too, quite a bit.
And I liked this franchise.
Uh, I liked it quite a bit too.
I didn't, I was, I said on the podcast, I hated the trailer.
I was not excited.
I was like, Oh God, it's about a pop star.
I don't care.
But because this guy is so good with the writing, uh, he said that the
27 club is what inspired him.
He said he went through many iterations of what the sequel story would be.
And when he landed on something, it was when he started reading about the
27 club, Janis Joplin, Kurt Cobain, these rock stars that all died at 27.
And he said, that's it.
That's, that's where I want to go.
And I think it works.
I think it's great because one of the things they, they tackle in this is
what if when a pop star is acting like a crazy person to everybody, it's not
entitlement and fame pollution and whatever it's that they're being
tormented by a demon and it's forcing them to act in a way that seems insane
to everybody.
I thought that was really smart.
Um, I thought that, uh, the thing was well executed.
I thought the jump scares worked.
I did jump a couple of times, uh, but that's also because as you already
said, the mood and the aesthetic and, and, and the tension is all there
in other places, um, the acting was all great.
Um, I, I really liked it.
The big red monster at the end.
That's just what they, they do that in the first movie.
It's different.
It looks different.
But the idea is, is when the demon finally goes into you, it's like,
that's what you see.
That's why every time somebody right before they do the horrible suicide,
yeah, they look up into the air and they're going and they're terrified.
The other person is going, what are you, what is going on?
What are you looking at?
Um, this one, excuse me, it's hard.
It's very hard to do interesting
suicide scares in horror movies.
They've been done so many times.
It's hard to find a new disturbing way that a person does something
terrible to themselves in front of you.
Um, but this one had one of the best I've ever seen when that kid at the
beginning beats his face in with the weight, I was like, Jesus Christ.
Like, yeah, yeah.
Each time he pulled the weight away, the whole audience was like, I don't
want to look at this, which, yeah, it was great.
And then when his ghost starts haunting her, you're like, I don't
want to see this guy's face.
I don't want to see this.
You know, um, yeah, it seemed almost like a, like, you know, the same way
that, uh, exorcist movie that we watched the last or the third at whatever it
was, the, the, the one that we liked, um, they did that possession and homage.
They did the exact same scene of possession with the woman in the street.
And this, with the face kind of deteriorating, reminded me of
irreversible, one of the most disturbing scenes in film history.
When it opens with them, like beating the face off a guy with a fire extinguisher.
I still can't unsee that scene.
I saw it in, you know, 25 years ago and his influences are great too.
You know, it's not like so many horror movies these days, substance included.
It's like, what'd you watch the shining?
Did you pause the shining before you shot this scene?
Like it's always the same references.
And this guy seems to have a little deeper reference point.
Um, I love Naomi Scott.
I had no idea who she was.
It said she was in the new Charlie's angels and the new Aladdin.
Um, but she's great as the pop star.
I thought she was really, really good.
And it was cool to see Jack Nicholson's son, who I don't know if he's a good
actor or not, but he looks exactly like Nicholson and you know, you definitely
get those vibes from him, which is cool.
I didn't realize that was his son.
Yeah.
Uh, and that was kind of a little shining homage.
Um, it says here, Parker Finn intentionally left portions of
the first film ambiguous.
Uh, wonder, I wonder if you did, uh, with various plot lines unresolved to create
the opportunity to explore these details in a sequel, so additional installments
may explore the backstory of the entity, but he would like to keep its mysterious
nature intact, always smart.
Nobody cares about the backstory of the entity.
Um, he says the third film would be notably different from the first.
There's still a lot of interesting stuff to explore in the world of smile.
I hope we get it.
I will be, if not first in line, I'll be in line and I will watch smile three.
And the movie ends, which just to call back to what you were saying
about the setup for a sequel.
The movie ends with her on stage at her first big show of this tour.
She succumbs to the demon and she does the horrible suicide on stage and the
entire sold out arena witnesses it.
So my assumption now is the third movie will be, there is a plague of thousands
of people infected by the demon.
I have a feeling the third one might be called smiles.
I don't, I, I hope.
But, uh, but, but I'm like, that's a, that's a hell of a setup for, for a
third one, uh, so, you know, who, and I'm sure they'll say, well, some people
looked away and other people watched it or what, but they, they do make a pretty.
Well, you got a great setup for whatever the third movie there.
I mean, you could do a zombie type thing.
If you don't know who, who actually saw it, who didn't, who was pretending
whatever, I mean, it leaves it open for a lot of good stuff.
Um, but, uh, my, uh, I, I, I liked everything about the movie.
I had one small criticism, which was when they reveal finally the car accident,
the truth about the car accident she was in, you see that her and her boyfriend
are driving on a wooded road.
They're both doing coke.
They're both really wasted.
They have a fight.
He's being an asshole, but she gets so mad at him.
She literally makes him drive off the road and he dies and she
fucks her life up because of it.
I thought, because the first movie, what the main character was trying to
overcome was the fact that she allowed her mother to die, uh, as a child,
because her mother was an addict and didn't help her when she was overdosing.
You know, that's, that's a, uh, you know, depending on your take, you could
say that's a heinous thing, or you could say it's a traumatized child
that doesn't know any bit, whatever.
My point is, is that's a much more in my head, forgivable offense.
So in the first movie, it's a little more of a sympathetic character
who succumbs to it, which makes it tragic.
I thought in this movie, especially since the character in this movie
keeps saying everything I touch, I hurt, I hurt everybody around me.
I need to, I need to fix this.
I thought this was going to go in the other direction where she
actually was going to beat it.
And they didn't do that.
They were like, no, no, she's still going to get killed by it.
So I don't even know if that's a criticism.
I just thought it made the end a little less tragic, um, you know, than the first
one, but, uh, but I liked it.
I think it's a great flick.
I think this guy's doing good work.
And, uh, my hog is up for smile too.
My hog smiling.
My hog is smiling as well.
Not quite laughing, but it's certainly smiling.
Uh, I thought both of these movies were really interesting.
I'm definitely going to check out Parker Finn's take on possession.
And I would love more movies in the smile franchise.
I hope they don't get carried away.
Pull a, who wants to be a millionaire?
Give us like 18 movies in the smile averse.
You know, sometimes people get a hit in their hands and it's just like, what
if we did one from the point of view of the first smile creature or whatever?
They will probably ruin it.
But for right now, we got a really strong horror franchise.
I'm a fan.
Our next movie will be heretic or heretic.
It's depending on how you pronounce it.
Um, we are on Instagram at see you in hell pod.
We, I am on Instagram at the Patrick Walsh and, uh, Joe, take it away.
Just, uh, folks plug in the December 6th, seventh show in Somerville, Massachusetts,
crystal ballroom holiday, my big holiday show, uh, come on out.
I'm doing a set of new material.
Uh, salsa windfall is doing a full set.
Got some surprise guests coming through.
Uh, just come on out.
It's going to be a lot of fun.
Uh, tickets are available, joderosa .com and, uh, we'll see you next time.
And we'll see you in hell.