I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, and when the sound of your screams becomes
a thing of my dreams, you know I'll say, I'll see you in hell, you know I will.
I'll see you in hell, you know I will.
Folks, it's we'll see you in hell, and we're back, back, back to talk about Bratz,
the children's cartoon here featuring the heavily makeuped toddlers.
Yeah, I actually watched that one.
Was Bratz racist? My remembering of it was that even the commercial was shockingly racist.
I don't remember being racist, I remember being like the children being really inappropriately
dressed, Bratz with a Z. The girls with a passion for fashion was their slogan.
I just had a meeting at Mattel, and since Barbie they're like trying to make every doll and board
game they've ever had into a movie. I don't know that it's racist, I don't know how old
these girls are supposed to be, I mean it's a kids show, I mean the skirt length is wild.
The Yasmin doll was Latino, Sasha was African -American, and Jade was Asian -American,
so they, oh okay, the Bratz helped normalize ethnic features that were once looked down upon.
So they weren't, they were the opposite of racist, they were supposed to diversify things,
that's great. And then Bratz, the movie,
is that even related to the Bratz game? Or are they Bratz dolls? That I don't know.
It doesn't look like it. Oh no it is, Yasmin, okay. So there was a Bratz movie made as well.
The dolls also appear to all be borderline anorexic. Yeah, when I met at Mattel,
there was a very, very nice lady there, smart lady, and she was like,
you know what we're really looking for now is a writer on Balderdash.
And I laughed, I just thought that she was joking, and what I learned more and more in
these meetings is there are no jokes anymore. They're making Balderdash into a movie. And I
was like, well I played that game every Saturday night with my friends. I was a loser, I was in a
virginity club in high school, and we would play board games and not drink. And the most
popular of our games was Balderdash. This is a game where they give you the dictionary definition
of something, like let's say a hairbrush, and then the real definition is this piece of wood
with bristles on it is how you comb your hair. But then everybody else in the group makes up
definitions. You get it? Yeah. So what you're trying to do is get everyone to guess your
definition by making the most realistic sounding fake definition. And the more you get above the
actual definition, the writer you are, if you guess the right definition, you get points too.
But it's a card game, essentially. There is nothing about this thing that would lend itself to
a feature film. But they're just like, every product we've ever made is going to get made
to a feature film, is like their current MO. So you can expect a lot more board game movies to come.
Remember when we thought Disney ride movies were like the end of society?
Like Pirates of the Caribbean, Jungle Bears. Yeah. And then, yeah, they just kept coming.
They're supposed to be rebooting Pirates of the Caribbean now. Yeah, because it's only been what,
four years? Yeah. Since the franchise ended, it's, you know, let's reboot it right now.
And why did the franchise end? Because they were spending $300 million on these movies and they
stopped bringing in audiences. Why do you think that's going to change four years later?
Dummies. Really? I feel like my coffee isn't, you're hearing this coffee machine?
Nope. It just ended. Okay. Good. All right. It just seemed insanely loud this morning.
Yeah. I don't get it with this stuff. I was just going to say something though. You would,
you'd said they're rebooting, oh, Balderdash. I had a friend, well, you remember Rooster Teeth.
We were going to make that movie with them. It didn't happen, but I know we're going into
the office there one day to see my buddy who, he's not there anymore. He works somewhere else.
So I feel like I can, I feel like I can tell this story without getting him in any trouble
since he's no longer there. But I went into his office, he was in development and he had like a
dry erase board with like upcoming projects that they were working on. And one of them was Paper
Boy, the video game. And I started laughing. I love Paper Boy. I go, what could this possibly
be about? Yeah. He's like, I just...
That's kind of been the funniest part to me. I've been, I got new managers, so I'm going on a bunch
of new meetings with movie people and it's always funny, but like they don't believe the shit
themselves. The top brass working in these positions, the heads of major studios, they're
like, I know it's so fucking terrible. It's so stupid. Like you wonder who wants this,
what we're getting. The executives don't want it. The creatives don't want it. I guess it's the top
brass, but like I was telling you about that guy who said like his job is to put more lore into
movies in the hopes of turning them into franchises. And I was like, dude, I fucking hate lore in movies.
And he was like, so do I, dude. So do I. Well, because they watched it. They watched it work
really well with John Wick. There ain't no way John Wick was supposed to be what it ended up being.
It was such a simple, small little movie. Like, you know, guy, wife dies, she leaves him a dog.
They come and they rob his house. They kill the dog. Why'd they rob his house? Oh, because he had
this past life we don't know about. And they awaken the sleeping beast and he kills everybody.
I mean, it's just so simple. And by the time you get to the third movie and he's getting sacred coins
where he has to go to the desert to talk to a guy and cut his finger off, you're like, what the fuck
is going on here? They add and add and add and add. And they are always wound up with a project that
is less good than the original. Yeah. So Stranger Things is kind of like that. I still enjoy the show,
but it's like, you know, it's like, I don't know, guys. Yeah. The upside down. Yeah. It was a cool
idea. Now there's a guy that orchestrates it there who's the lead king demon or
whatever. Yeah. I never watched the Institute. I don't fucking know. I'm like, all right,
whatever. When I saw those episode running times on the new season, I dropped out 90 minutes each.
I was like, nah. Well, that was the second half. They split the season in two. The first run of
episodes for that last season were they were normal episodes. And then they took a break.
And then they said, here's part two of season five or whatever it was. And they did three
episodes that were like 90 minutes each. And I'm like, yeah, stop where it stopped.
And by the way, it ended on an awesome cliffhanger. It ended on like an awesome
cliffhanger where you were like, oh, that's great. They just revealed who this bad guy is
and what his role in all of this has been all along. Yeah. And like, that's really cool. Very
cool. We're done. No, we're going to give you three more 90 minute episodes that could have
been their own season where they fight the guy. It's never worked for a show. Sons of Anarchy,
I was watching and then I was like, I don't know if I'm going to make it to the end of this fucking
thing, but I've committed so much time. And then halfway through the run of the show, all the
episodes go to 90 minutes. And I was like, all right, I'm going to fucking kill somebody if I
have to finish this. Yeah. Who's got the patience? Who's got the time? It's why I've never watched
Breaking Bad or Mad Men or Game of Thrones. Because by the time everybody was telling me
I needed to see it, they were like three seasons deep. I'm like,
guys, I'm not going back and starting this now. There's too much shit in my life that I got to
watch. But I say you can always make time for the true best. Well, that's true. The Sopranos,
the Breaking Bad. Maybe one day I will. But the older you get, the more you feel that
thing of like, we all say, why does anybody watch trash TV or whatever? And people say,
because people work all day, they come home, they don't want to think, they just want to kind of
decompress. You start to get older, you do feel that no matter what your job is. When you sit down
to eat dinner and you're putting the TV on for the first time and you're like, my God,
what a slog life is. Just reflecting on the day of just ball kicks and jaw punches. You're like,
I don't want to dive into anything right now. I hear you. I've been watching more and more stupid
shit with my life. I'm on Vanderpump Rules spinoffs. Yeah, there you go. It's bleak. I hear it.
I don't want to be by the end of my life watching like Sesame Street though, you know?
I played the Arnie documentary and had never watched it and I'll review it in the corner,
but I watched it. I put it on last night when I was feeling tired. I decided I was going to sleep
on my couch last night. I love sleeping on the couch. Okay. And I played it three or four times
straight through. It would play all three episodes. I'd wake up, the TV wouldn't be going.
I'd start it again. Yeah. Play it straight through. Got up this morning, started my day,
started it over again. Just let it play straight through. I found it very comforting.
It's not that good, but - Well, we'll talk about it.
I'm glad you were comforted by it. Speaking of Mattel, they have cast
the star of The Idea of You, the bad Anne Hathaway movie
as He -Man, Nicholas Galtzine, who is a thin, non -muscular,
which I'm not criticizing him. I'm just saying, why is he portraying He -Man? Nicholas Galtzine,
he looks nothing like He -Man. He talks, acts nothing like He -Man.
We're at a time now where wrestlers who do look like He -Man are starring in Ricky Stenicki and
big comedic hits and are like frail pretty boys are playing He -Man. I don't get it. I don't
understand it. I also don't care about He -Man, so it's not that big a deal to me. Well, I'll
tell you what it is, and it doesn't make me mad, but this is what it is. They're trying to demasculine
He -Man. They're trying to make He -Man more of an approachable, less stereotypical. They're not
going to cast a Schwarzenegger as He -Man now. They're like, no, that's too manned. That's too
manned. He literally has his pronoun and his name is how masculine he is.
Just to give you a frame of reference here, He -Man got criticism in the 80s as being too male
and too this and too that. In the 80s, the cartoon was getting criticized. Can you imagine now?
It's so long ago. Now it's that times whatever, so that's what it is. They're like, no,
we're going to put an approachable. Plus, they want women to want to watch this.
If women like a guy like this, according to their testing polls or whatever the fuck,
they're going to put this guy in it because I guess the average woman now is more attracted
to a guy like this. There was a time where that was different, where the Stallone thing was really
in. No woman, regardless of who's in it, is going to see a He -Man movie. That is stupid.
Not you, but if that's what they're thinking. They're thinking of the next audience.
They're thinking of how do they get their hooks in these 17 -year -olds. This all very much applies,
by the way, to the movie today, Bretz, but that's what it is. They're trying to figure out how do
our hooks in the 17 -year -olds, so they're carrying us for another 40 fucking years
on this thing we've already drained every last goddamn dollar out of. It's never enough.
It's never enough. Holy God. Yeah, it's all investment boards and, you know, you got to
show the numbers. Yeah. Profits up or not. How do we get them up?
Take a meeting at Paramount now. They leave you with their Wikipedia page, which lists every movie
that they make, that they've made at Paramount. If you want to pitch them something, you pick one
of those movies and say, I'd like to remake it, and here's how. That's the way you get a project
set up at Paramount. There's no other way in right now. Speaking of Paramount, News Psycho,
Frasier coming back, season two. I'm very happy about that. I didn't think the first season was
very good, but I think that they could make it better. But Gill and Bulldog are both confirmed
as characters in season two. I don't know how much they'll be in it, but Dan Butler and Edward
Hibbert are set to reprise their roles. That's exciting. For one officer for the whole
season. It doesn't say. Okay. But I'm happy about that. Kelsey Grammer also said,
last season he said, we won't go back to Cheers. Now he said, we've got some great ideas for Cheers
characters. Yeah. We want to do something with Ted and we want to do something with Diane. So,
I feel like this could go the route of Picard where they came back in the first season of Picard
and everybody was like, this isn't Picard. Right. This is like a different thing. We don't like this.
And then the second season, they brought a few characters in and they were like, look, Q's back
and this guy. And then by the third season, which my friend Terry was the show runner on,
they were like, can we just do a next generation story, please? And then everybody was like,
this was the best next generation thing ever. It was awesome. So, I feel like they might do
that with Frasier. They're going to just slowly creep back to making it Frasier again.
Why didn't they bring in Roz back? Roz was in an episode last season, but only one episode.
Look, here's the problem. They made him go to Boston. So, how do you get everybody now over
fucking Boston? Which I wouldn't be surprised if at one point he's like,
they just have him go back to Seattle. Right. He's like, I made some mistakes. I gotta go back
or whatever. So, we're curious to see what happens. But shouts out to my boy Terry, by the way,
who is doing a reboot. He's redoing Enemy Mine. Okay. That's an interesting choice. I like Enemy
Mine. I saw it as a kid and it freaked me out real bad for whatever reason. Lou Gossett Jr. and
Dennis Quaid? Yeah. Okay. Wait, who's the creature? Lou? Lou plays the alien, yeah. Oh,
okay. But Terry Metalis, great guy. Yeah, he's doing a reboot of Enemy Mine. That's interesting.
Speaking of reboots and Lou Gossett Jr., because we can kind of connect anything to a reboot in
today's conversation, Officer and a Gentleman getting remade with Miles Teller in the Richard
Gere role. Perfect casting, I'll say. Yeah, that's good. Teller looks a lot like Gere. Not that he
has to for this, but he's a similar performer, but a better actor than Gere. Gere has always been one
of the biggest letdowns as a performer to me. But I like Officer and a Gentleman quite a bit.
I just feel like maybe it's naive to think people should go back and watch the OG movie. I don't
know. I just don't know what you're going to do to make it much better. And Lou Gossett Jr. the
whole time calling him mayonnaise and all that. I can't imagine that's going to still be in there.
So you're just watering down a movie that's already like a sweet mom movie. I think they're
going to take away what little edge that movie has. It is an R -rated movie with hot sex scenes,
and they're not going to be able to do any of that anymore. So who knows? I like Officer and a
Gentleman quite a bit. I wish there was more remaking of OK movies that missed the boat the
first time. Honestly, Enemy Mine is a good choice.
Well, that's one of them. Well, that's also the practical magic thing we were talking about.
It's like they're going to take something that really worked.
OK, true. I can't complain. Maybe they'll get it. But that's a sequel. I'm talking about a remake.
Every sequel is a fucking remake anymore. It's all the same.
That's true. It's tough time.
Let's get to that movie, Corn. What have I seen?
Well, I'll start while you look. I watched -
Please, John.
I liked this quite a bit. I know you said you didn't think it was that good, but I liked it.
It's better than Sly, I'll say that much. I didn't see Sly.
It's three episodes. They're each like an hour and five minutes each.
Whether you're a fan of Arnold Schwarzenegger or not, his achievements
across the board are extraordinary. They're extraordinary. He literally went to the top
of everything he's ever done. He was the top at it. It's wild. It's divided into three parts.
The first one is about bodybuilding. The second one is about movie star. The third one is about
politics. In each one, it's like first episode, trials, tribulations, setbacks, keep going,
keep going. I can do this. I can do this. Becomes Mr. Universe. Second one, I want to be an actor.
Gets a role as Hercules, movie bombs. Phone doesn't ring, doesn't ring, doesn't ring.
Four years later, he gets Conan. Boom, boom, boom. Becomes the biggest movie star on earth.
Third movie, third episode. Wants to get into politics. Sort of is in it. Can't make up his
mind. Might do it, might not do it. Announces he's going to run for governor. Wins. Then slumps down
to where he's got a lower approval rating than the guy they recalled and then reverses the rating
and gets a high approval rating before he leaves office. Every fucking thing he does,
he does it to the best of his ability and manages to grab the brass ring.
I very much appreciated that they did not stray from any of the controversy. They talked about
all of the allegations of him being ropey with women. He says, now he says, he goes,
whatever I said, however I tried to make it sound like it was a different time, whatever. He goes,
it's all bullshit. It was wrong behavior and I shouldn't have done it. Period. He owns it.
They address the out of wedlock kid thing with the housekeeper. They go at all of it,
and they go at all of it very objectively. There's no slant to it. There's no
lesson to learn or figure wagging. They're just like, hey, here's a thing you did that's
fucked up. Let's talk about it. And he does, and they do, and it's covered, and it's balanced.
And I don't mean balanced because giving him rope to get off the hook. I just mean it's done
like a documentary should be done. It presents the information. That's it. So I very much enjoyed it.
I find him to be a really fascinating guy. He's somebody I would really... I bet you he's
so fucking fun to drink with or just... Legendarily he is. He's considered the guy,
the most fun. Or just to sit and talk to. I bet he fucks with you a lot. He does it a couple
times in this where he'll look into camera and he'll get really... He'll go into the Terminator
character. I bet he does that shit all the time to people and whatever. And it's so funny.
Excuse me. It does end kind of a somber note where he talks about how he and Maria
Schreiber are still friends. And for the big holidays and events and everything,
the whole family still gets together, but they're divorced now. And he goes, but it's just not the
same. And there is that element at the end of like, hey, what is it that you will sacrifice
if you go for everything that your heart desires and every dream? Eventually there's some fallout
and he's very much owns, I've made some major mistakes. And he says at one point, he goes,
I hurt enough people and he wants to make up for that and whatever. So there is a sadness to it,
but overall I thought it was a very, very interesting doc. And I think he's a very
interesting guy. And I love that politically he went in as a Republican and then started filling
his cabinet with Democrats. Yeah, weirdly. And I don't know if it's just growing up with him or
what, but his little speeches that he would post on Twitter during the pandemic and stuff like,
if the guy has any inkling at all, he should be running for president and save us all. I really
love the guy. I know he's not perfect, but yeah, you're right. He's also not from this country.
But yeah, I did like Arnold. My issue was my interests are always going to lie with music
and movies at the top. And when I watched Arnold, I wanted more than just cursory nods to each of
his big movies. I wanted that middle hour to be stretched to two and really dig into like every
project he'd ever done. That's all. I don't care as much about his political career or his upbringing.
Although it was very cool to hear that guy say that Arnold told him he was going to be the top
in those three fields and then he just did it. As much as the idea, the concept of positive
thinking, as much as whenever my therapist brings it up, I want to punch her. There is some truth
to it. If you tell yourself when you wake up, I'm going to do this, as opposed to look at this,
as opposed to there's a reliable disappointment in the line from American Splendor, you can change
things. Sometimes things are too corny to even share with the pod, but I had a real dark period
of time where a therapist told me when you wake up in the morning, brush your teeth with your left
hand, which rewires your neural pathways because your hands like, but I've never done, it's like
trying to give a hand job or jack off with the wrong hand. It's like your brain doesn't know how
to do it. Do that for a week. It'll reset your neural pathways. And while you're brushing your
teeth, look yourself in the eyes and say, I love you over and over and over. And I was like,
Jesus Christ. And I'll tell you what, man, did it work? The first day I did it, I started crying.
I was like, wow, I needed to hear this, even if it's from myself. I don't know how I'm getting
there off Arnold, but self -talk, positive self -talk, it can really help. I mean, there's a guy who was
like, I'm going to do the hardest things in the world to do and did them. I think when you do
watch Sly Joe, you'll realize what a botched job it was. That's watching Sly made me appreciate
Arnold a lot more because it's such a nothing documentary. Anyway.
Well, yeah, and I'm a big Sly. I'm a big Sly fan. So me too. I hesitate to say this because it's a
criticism, but I don't get the, Schwarzenegger displays a certain human quality I don't get from
Sly alone. Yeah, you'll feel that in Sly as well.
Yeah. Like there's something, I don't know. I think the immigrant aspect of it has a lot to do with
it. Like he came here, he had a dream. They were like, fuck you, you talk weird. He was like,
fuck you, I'm going to do this. And he does it. There's just something about it where he's got,
there's a warmth to, again, I've been fan of Sly so long, but that's why I fall in love with
Sylvester Stallone every single time I watch Copland or any of the Rocky movies.
And then I watch like an interview with him and I'm like, oh yeah, he's not like the lovable dumb
guy. Well, I mean, to me, his more difficult performances or something like Copland or
something where he's, because he actually tries to be that sort of fake pretentious guy in
interviews. He's always like pursing his lips and all that. It's not him. He is a really good actor.
He's a better actor than he gets credit for. I don't think he is the dumb ass, but you do want
him to be sort of. I rewatched Man on Fire directed by the great Tony Scott R .I .P.
And of course I love Ridley Scott, his Napoleon stunk. And I think he's on kind of a losing
trajectory of late, not totally, but I just don't always like what he's given us. Tony Scott,
I like his style. I mean, he's Ridley Scott with like a Tarantino pull. And I might just be saying
Tarantino because of true romance, but I love how he puts together a movie. They're very flashy.
It's like Michael Bay, but more controlled, more elegance to it, I guess you would say.
He's a better filmmaker, of course, than Michael Bay. And I'm a Bay fan too, don't get me wrong.
But I like the way Tony Scott puts together an action movie. He has the same problem as
Ridley Scott and that he doesn't know how to make a movie less than two and a half hours,
regardless of the subject matter. Man on Fire is essentially another equalizer movie, but it's
literally 230. He plays Creasy. Creasy's art is death and he's about to paint his masterpiece.
Ex -CIA operative Creasy reluctantly accepts a job as the bodyguard for a 10 -year -old girl
in Mexico City, played by Dakota Fanning. They clash at first, but believe it or not,
they eventually bond. And when she's kidnapped, he's consumed by fury and will stop at nothing
to save her life. That's why I watch Man on Fire. I'm writing a kidnapping project and I'm trying
to watch some kidnapping movies for inspiration. But it's a really good movie. I'd say it's
definitely equally as good as the equalizers. Take your pick. Denzel is awesome in it. Dakota Fanning
is fucking awesome in it. I watched that Uptown Girls, which I talked on the movie corner. I was
possibly up for a rewrite of Uptown Girls, so I watched it for the first time. And it's decent,
but I was blown away by the performances of Dakota Fanning and Brittany Murphy. And it made
me realize we're always bemoaning the loss of comedy actors, but we've also lost dudes. Glenn
Powell does nothing for me. I thought Hitman was wildly overrated. And that movie made me realize
we're also missing ladies. We don't got good ladies anymore. Dakota Fanning, now it's just
she didn't to me become like a Jodie Foster where when I see her, I'm like, I accept it. I just don't
for some reason. But as a kid, she was the best child actor, like one of the top five of all time.
She holds her own with Denzel like it's easy. And I've seen interviews with Denzel where they
ask him the best actor he's ever worked with. And he says Dakota Fanning. She was an amazing prodigy.
She's great in this. And yeah, I mean, I guess that's just it. When I watch these movies now
lately, let's say 2005 and before, I just saw Unforgiven the other day in the theater, you know,
it is that old man feeling of they don't make them like they used to. You find yourself saying it. We
say it on here all the time. We did some talking in the last pod about how when you hear those words
coming out of your mouth, you believe them, of course, but you also just hate yourself when
you're like, oh man, back in the day, things used to be better. But they were. And then the sad part
is that's what our dad said before us too, but they really were better. What can you say? I just
feel like the kids coming up today are missing out in a big way. I think both us and our parents
would have to agree that things have certainly hit a new low. Everybody does agree. You know,
there's just there's no beating heart. There's no personality coming out of movies anymore.
And what's weird, you know, is that Man on Fire, obviously I'm getting way off the subject of Man
on Fire here, but it's not perfect either. You know, I didn't love Man on Fire when I saw it
in theaters, but like what Joe was talking about a month, a month or two ago with Blades of Glory,
how I have made the realization because I'm all and my thing is my depression has gotten way worse
as I get older. So I'm always like, maybe I'm so depressed and now I don't enjoy anything.
But what Joe was talking about with Blades of Glory and what I'm talking about now with this
is these are movies we saw in theaters 15, 20 years ago. We thought were fine and moved on
with our lives and you watch them now and realize they're pretty fucking good because you're
comparing them to the modern standard. That's how I realized there was a true slip happening
and that it wasn't happening within myself. It was happening in the business. Just things
don't know how good you had it. Yeah, exactly. You know, Man on Fire is a fun junkie action movie,
but when you compare it to Bad Boys 4, it's like, no, that was maybe a masterpiece.
So there you go, Joe. I have one more in the documentary field. I watched Remembering Gene
Wilder. I did too. Terrible title, but a nice documentary. I love that they use his audiobook
as the narration because you do feel like he's there with you and telling his own story.
Wild that he talks about. Didn't it make you feel though, Joe, like I listen to audiobooks all the
time and I particularly like to listen to celebrity autobiographies. Did it make you feel like, why
don't I just get some pictures together and play them over somebody's audiobook? I was like,
does this even count? No, because they got a lot of interviews and they had a lot of interesting
footage and no, I thought all the home movie stuff and I thought they had a lot in there.
True. All right. And it was also wild when he goes,
I got stationed in the military at a hospital in Phoenixville, Pennsylvania. I'm like, that's where
I'm from. So I had crossover with Gene Wilder. Yeah, it's great. You know, it's heartbreaking
at times. You know, the Gilda Radner stuff is really tough. And it's wild that like, you know,
I always had the impression of them that they were these like perfect lovebirds and there was
never a problem in the world until she got sick. And it is not that. They talk about how like,
they had a really kind of strained relationship, that she actually drank too much when he met her.
I'm like, Gilda Radner? She seemed to me always like somebody that had never had a drink,
like would like, you know, they just like to go to like Disneyland. I completely agree.
Yeah. They used to bury that stuff, you know, like that was just a generation that never
talked about stuff. So you never think of them as having those issues.
You know, and, you know, did you find they went a little abruptly from Gilda into the later wife?
To me, it was like a fraction of a second. And he was like, I was so much, he's saying he was
happier as he's ever been with her. I got the impression. I could have spaced that out from
Gilda a little. I got the impression. I don't mean this callously. I really don't. I got the
impression that if Gilda Radner had not gotten sick, that marriage would not have lasted.
And that she got sick at a time when they thought they were going to turn it around.
They talk about this. They say like she, she was, she got pregnant and she was so happy. And then
baby there was, it was going to be stillborn or something. And then the pregnancy didn't work.
Very tragic, horrible thing. But they, you know, they talk about that. And he's saying at that
point, he goes, he goes, she was happier than ever. And I realized this, he goes, this can work.
And I was like, oh, that means it wasn't working. And then he, and then she gets the diagnosis and
he talks about how she was crying and she's going no more bad news, whatever, and whatever.
And I'm not saying I don't think he loved her and vice versa. And I'm not saying I don't think he
didn't want to be with her. I just get the feeling that if she had not gotten sick,
their lives would have maybe taken a different trajectory as a couple.
Sure. Sure. It's all speculation.
Right. But then with the second wife, it's, there's, they don't mention any problems. They're
so here was my cue on that. And I'm interrupting just because I just watched it yesterday. But like,
did you think that maybe the second wife was involved with the making of the documentary?
No. Okay. I mean, maybe she was, I don't know.
No, it really, it changed the narrative about Gene Wilder as being this love affair for the
Gilda Radner that everybody thought of and replaced it really with what you're saying,
a marriage that was not by any means perfect. And that he found true happiness with the woman
after Gilda. And I was like, I think the documentary would only make that claim if
the wife had been involved, but I might be wrong. I heard it before. That wasn't the first time I
heard him discuss that. But also too, this also revealed, and this again, this is something he
talked about in his book, but he talked about how like he and Richard Pryor were not like buddies.
Like they had great chemistry on screen, but they were not like friends. They didn't pal around.
So I thought this really shone a light on the truth of what we, we had a lot of,
we all had a lot of assumptions about his life and who he was. And this kind of showed you a lot of
it. The truth of a lot of it. But then also too, I knew that he and Mel Brooks were,
seemed close, but my God, like I didn't know they were that close. Like, you know,
like that stuff was beautiful. It's wild seeing Mel Brooks. He's, he's like in his 90s. The guy
still talks like he's in his 40s. It's insane. There's literally no difference between him now
and on the set of Blazing Saddles. There's no difference. He hasn't even like slowed down at
all. You know what? And I hate saying anything like this for fear of rubbing somebody the wrong
way, but I feel like the Jewish people keep their shit together till the end, better than most other
races, in my opinion, other creeds, whatever you want to say. What do you mean? I feel like there's
elderly razor sharp Jewish men and women and other ethnicities, religions and nationalities,
whatever. I think any, look at Al Einstein, Joe. Look at Al Brooks. Well, I was going to say,
I think any, the closer you are to the other place, meaning not here. Yeah. The closer you
are in family to where your family came from originally, the sharper the older people around
you are, you know, like these people. Usually I find that people that are once or twice removed
from the people that first came here to plant the seeds often have, there's just something about
like an appreciation because that's it. There's something about having an appreciation
for aging and all that stuff, not seeing it as a cursing, appreciating the wisdom. And
that's all the stuff that allows you to flourish as you get older, you know, and traditions are
important. You know, a lot of people don't have any traditions or I don't mean like groups of
people. I just mean individual people don't have traditions because their family doesn't practice
them or whatever. And I'm always envious of the of the Shabbats and the family dinners. And I think
big reason that non -Jewish families don't stay as close is because they don't have those traditions
in their life. It's a devastating thing. The amount of loss we've had in my own family,
which was Italian American, we've lost almost all semblance of that. And it's devastating
because it was a really, really big part of my life. It was really important to me.
And I don't have a family, so I can't really contribute to continuing on anything.
Because what am I going to do? Yeah, just so it's tough. It's tough.
I'm saying just in my field comedy, you look at the elders of Jewish comedy, all 80 plus,
Larry David, Woody Allen, Mel Brooks, Albert Brooks. You know, that's my Mount Rushmore,
pretty much of Jewish comedians. You know, those guys are all 80 and older and sharp as a tack.
There's something to be said there. I don't know. Chevy Chase ain't sharp as a tack anymore.
You know? Is he Jewish? No, and that's my point, Joe.
Yeah. Well, you could say the same thing with black comics, too. Older black comics usually
stay well in the pocket. That's true. Yeah.
You know? Yeah.
But this also could mean there's just a lot of black and Jewish comics.
And that's true, too. That's true as well.
Yeah. Where were we? What the hell were we even talking about?
I was just saying, remember Gene Wilder. I liked it very much.
Yes. I did, too. I guess I wanted more, but you're not going to get more because he's dead. What I
mean is I wanted more of his life and how it also left me feeling while we did actually dip into
almost all of Gene Wilder's movies, no matter how minor in this documentary. And I realized,
A, I hadn't seen half of them because they just have such terrible reputations.
But B, he was a really hard guy to cast, right? That is a type that you have to kind of build
a movie around. And a young Frankenstein doesn't come around every day. He was too odd. He wasn't
Andy Kaufman, but he was just an odd guy to fit into a movie. And maybe that's why he made so
much shit. He really did make some bad ones. I've seen almost all of his movies and outside.
And he lost gems. I know the prior ones are good.
Sherlock Holmes's younger brother, smarter brother, whatever it's called, that's got some
funny parts. The world's greatest lover, I thought, sucked. Anything he did with Brooks.
Because he wrote Young Frankenstein with Mel Brooks, but I always thought, boy, you'd think
he'd take at least, it'd be at least half as funny as Young Frankenstein. But I guess apparently
they're not. Well, the true tragedy there is, Mel Brooks said the next thing was going to be,
they were going to do Jekyll and Hyde. Which, God almighty, would that have been amazing,
watching Gene Wilder, Dr. Jekyll, Mr. Hyde. What a part for him.
Then some Jekyll and Hyde thing, comedy, went into production and they were like, well, there goes
that, we can't do it. Which is so fucking lame, because I would be willing to bet you money,
the only reason that fucking Jekyll and Hyde movie got greenlit was because of how successful
Young Frankenstein was. Yeah, and then the one that was actually -
They also made Dracula with our love at first bite with George Hamilton. They made tons of those.
And then the one that was made is completely forgettable, whether it's good or not. So
that was it. And, you know, Wilder went on to, you know, Mel Brooks said at one point,
I remember in an interview, he said, he was like, you know, I love Gene, but Gene stopped caring
about being funny. And I was like, yeah, that's a bummer. He kind of just doesn't want to be funny
anymore. He wants to write books and whatever, which is great. Like, God bless him. But, you know,
it was, I felt like there was more. Gene had a CBS sitcom, didn't he?
Yeah. That I feel like I remember this watching it.
It was okay. It was called something wilder, I think was the name of it.
Oh, it is. You're right, Joe. Oh, 94 to 95. Wow. That was way later than I thought. I definitely
watched something wilder. It's fine. You know, and he did like his later movies. Well, he did those
goddamn detective movies. They didn't even talk about those in this thing that I can remember. But.
Well, now what are you talking about? Because I thought you were talking about Sherlock Holmes's
older brother when you said all the shitty detective. No, no, no. He did like you have like a
Matlock. Yeah, he did made for TV detective. He did like four of them. It was like a series where
he played this detective. That I didn't know. It was, it was not, let's Matlock a little more
she wrote kind of vibe. It looks like it's looks like it's called murder in a small town.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. He did a few of those. Oh, wow. It's literally.
Let me, I got to send this to you. The poster. Oh, it's an A and E original movie. Yeah. Jesus.
That's bleak. All right. I'm going to send this into the chat. Why is it so hard to do anything
with zoom or am I just stupid? I think it's a little, there's that negative talk again,
a little of both a little available. Yeah. Look, I'm not technically minded. We do know that.
You just have to copy the image and then paste it into the thing. There it is. A copy of the image.
Yep. And then you do the old right click paste. I never right click. That's just not my bag at all.
Not something I do a lot of it all, man. Still hasn't arrived. For those of you listening at home,
the, uh, this is wild. This is like wild and then it comes in and it's a link. You still
out there. It should have gone. Oh, look at that. Look at that. He's, he's literally doing
the, the, the chin on his fist pose. Like he's thinking. And in this picture, this is still
young enough, vibrant gene while there it's like, we could have been getting, and after this,
he did the guest run on Will and Grace and he's fucking great. And I had no idea he was on Will
and Grace. I have not seen the program. Um, but those clips they showed looked awesome. I was like,
I should watch more of the show. They're bringing back Gene Wilder. He was great on it. And it's
like, I was like, God, there was, it was like, there was more meat on the bone that we didn't
get. And maybe that was his choice, but it's very sad at the end when he's like,
he's suffering from Alzheimer's. They show the 92 Y interview clip where he's like, and then,
and then we were the one in the prison and the guy goes, uh, stir crazy. And he goes,
yeah, it was stir crazy. Wasn't it? Like, and you can see that he's very confused and it's like,
God damn it, man. It's so honestly, that's when I started writing. Sometimes I forget how my
texts come across, but that's when I was texting Joe, like, isn't it terrible that like, we all
know how bad life is now, but then at some point you lose your mind and then your faculties and
your boners and everything else. I just sent this to Joe at like 3 p .m. on a Monday afternoon.
Yes. And I responded, but that's where my head pops in.
Please move out of Los Angeles, Pat. Not that I'm much better, but.
Yeah. No, it's, it's, I don't feel this age. Again, it's something I'm sure many a dad has said,
but like there's a midlife crisis happening at age 43. I don't plan on living longer than 86.
I'm in a midlife crisis. Yep. Yeah. I hear you, dude. You know, I just got this new job.
Uh, which I'll talk about next time, but I was all excited. I was like, isn't this great?
Wow. This is going to be a good, this is a good job for me to get. This is really good.
Yeah. And then you start to think about like, what, what doors could this open and what could
I do? And then I just went, I was thinking that I was getting all excited and happy and everything's
going well. And then I just thought you're 46. What are you, what are you talking about? You're
46. Like you're not 20 to eight. You're 46. Like you better do all this fast. It's horrible.
It can still lead to great things. You know, your career, especially in this business, as my dad
always told me, Dennis Franz didn't hit it big till he was 50. Um, and he told me this after maybe,
maybe three months of not succeeding, uh, out in New York. He told me about Dennis Franz,
but he was right. It can happen at any time. You can pop at any time. You can kick it, you know,
a start in a new direction at any time. I'm actively trying to change into a drama person
or at least an hour long person. Um, at 43, you know, you just, and you know, I think everybody
got frozen for three plus years. We all got stuck on pause and we're all, I noticed this in every
interaction I have in every, whether I'm at the store, whether I'm online, whether I'm in a
business meeting, whether I'm in a pitch meeting, people are off. They're off. We had three years
where nobody was working and now we're all trying to get back into the groove and we should be less
hard on ourselves. You know, everybody lost some years there in the mix. Yeah. And it's easy to
forget that I have a habit of thinking it's always ground zero. It's always the starting point again.
And, uh, it's easy to forget like, no, dude, you did all this other stuff for the last two
and a half decades. That's stuff that you did. I tend to think that none of it matters and that
I'm always just starting. And it's like, no, you're not just starting. You've been doing things.
This is now the next step, but like this is your career, your restaurant tour.
Yes. I basically go to therapy now to pay, to pay her to remind me of what I have going on in my life.
I, you know, I'm like, well, I'll be unemployed for two days and I'll be in therapy going like,
well, I'll never work again. So there's that. She's like, Pat, don't you have X, Y, Z, A, B, C?
And I'm like, oh yeah, you're right. But, um, we forget we beat ourselves up. I know when I was,
you know, 30, I thought 43 was impossibly old. All those cliches are true. When you're in your
40s, you're just out there, you know, a squirrel trying to get a nut. You don't think of yourself
as an old dude. I don't feel old. I've never had a back issue in my life. Knock on wood,
knocking the block of wood that supports my back. I'm fine. Do you have back shit, Joe?
Not that I know of. I don't really, I mean, I don't know if I have any, I don't know. I
feel the same. Anytime I'm trying, I'm down on myself about that. I'm like, but Pat,
did I ever tell you about that exercise I did in therapy that really helped?
Even more LA for a moment. No, I know. I told you about that. No, no, no. I always thought you
forgot that you had, I was like, oh boy. I had developed Alzheimer's. No, it's a different thing
and it's real quick, but she was like, and I just feel like I might've mentioned it. It was very
impactful to me. She was like, imagine you're 10. Cause I talked to her about my cool aunt. My mom
is very straight lace, but has a very cool sister who was playing talking heads for me when I was
nine years old. So I, she got made me cool from an early age. And she was like, imagine that you're,
your 10 year old self and you go to visit you, the cool uncle. My sister doesn't have kids
either. I'm not an uncle and I don't have my own kids. She's like, imagine you're 10 years old,
a little boy, and you go to visit yourself in Los Angeles at your house in the Hills
with an awesome view of mountains and Los Angeles and, you know, decorated just how you like it.
Massive music collection. Every album you've ever wanted to listen to every movie you've ever
watched. Dream home theater set up a cat who loves you. Don't you think that little you would
go back to Missouri and be like, Oh my God, my uncle has the coolest fucking life.
Yeah. And I was like, wow. Like that made five years of sometimes pointless therapy
worth it to me. That hit it to me. I was like, yes. And all that is is gratitude. It's another
way of being gratitude. And I realized we're starting to sound like Pete Holmes is podcast
here, but, um, that's what it is. It's resetting how you look at your life. We get so stuck in
this waking up and being like, Oh, another fucking day of this. But that's what the
tooth brushing thing does too. It's just like, change one thing, change the way you're looking
at it, change the way you're coming to it. And it helps a lot. You know, it helped that, that helped
then you forget it and you're back to depressed, but, um, that's life.
All right. That's what the people say. Let's talk about, and I guess maybe we're feeling
nostalgic because Joe and I watched rats this week. Uh, I guess it is based on a book by Anthony
Michael Hall that I did not, not Anthony Michael Hall. Sorry. I I'm already mixing them up. Um,
Andrew McCarthy. Yes. I couldn't remember his name for a second.
Well, and that's, that's what this movie is all about. Basically what I thought this was going
to be is a look back at that time of the, at the John Hughes movies at St. Elmo's fire at
all these movies, putting young hot actors together. Um, maybe some comical discussions
about who was and who wasn't in the Brat Pack, whatever. But I thought for the most part,
this would be a clip heavy, um, fun look back at a time I was alive and really enjoyed watching
movies. So I was excited to see it. What it wound up being was a surprisingly bitter
and in my opinion, fucking toxic look back from Andrew McCarthy, who is, I'm sorry, and always
was the least interesting of the quote Brat Pack and all its affiliates. I disagree with that very
harshly. I mean, maybe, maybe you've got people who, who are worse, but I love favorite McCarthy
was always my favorite. I always loved McCarthy. I was a big fan. We'll come, we'll come back to
that. But, um, he just, to me was always white bread. You know, I really love pretty and pink
Molly Ringwald. That's an iconic role for her. John Cryer. That's an iconic role for him. That
sort of sexually ambiguous, weird, best friend of the hot girl. Um, James Spader is a classic
villain in that he's basically got cocaine dust on his lapels. His name is Blaine, which was very
funny. Um, and then you've got this generic piece of shit, Andrew McCarthy, and I never liked that
they wound up together. The original cut of the film, she wound up with Ducky, which is not
and everyone balked. Um, not that wasn't a duck pond balked, but, um, to me, McCarthy was always
just the guy who was there. And he, and this thing has an axe to grind, much like the star of our
previous movie in a violent nature. He is very mad at the label of the Brat Pack. This was one
article written by a guy who basically coined the term. He was supposed to write an article
about Emilio Estevez. He wound up writing and coining the term the Brat Pack, which was a spoof
or a play on the words, the Rat Pack. Um, so they were basically saying, Hey, here's another group
of young, talented people, roughly the same age, but the sort of derogatory label of Brat.
I read the article this morning or at least looked at it. The article is pretty mean to all of them,
but what Andrew McCarthy seems most upset about is, by the way, he's not mentioned in the article.
Oh, McCarthy is, McCarthy is not referenced, which makes this documentary even weirder
because the documentary ends with him confronting the guy who wrote the article. Who's like an old
dude now. And he's like, do you know what this did to us? And, um, in my opinion,
I always saw McCarthy as the leader of them though. He was to me, he and Ringwald were like,
to me, at least, I mean, maybe I'm sure. Well, anyway, you're, so you got three years on me.
You know, I saw these movies on home video. Maybe there's something about the way that Brat Pack
was presented. That's different than how I know it, but I never even thought of it as a negative.
So when I saw McCarthy so defensive in this thing, I'm like, wow, he seems really upset about this.
And he thinks it hurt him his career. When to my mind, he was never going to be that biggest star.
He's not talented enough, but now Joe's saying he's the favorite. So there we go.
Well, he's my favorite and McCarthy was in tons of stuff back then. Uh, I, I just always loved him
and, you know, weekend at Bernie's heaven help us is one of my favorite films of all time. He's
awesome in that. Never stop. I find McCarthy to be extraordinarily charming and on screen and very
funny. Uh, this, in the, in this thing, a little pretentious, I think he thinks a little more
of the Brat Pack than it was, uh, meaning the article now, look, I didn't experience it,
so maybe I'm wrong, but I get the take or I got the impression that he's lending way too much
credence to this article as being something that prevented him from having things in his career
that he would have had otherwise. And he's also putting way too fine a point on the importance
or relevance of the Brat Pack where it's like, guys, it was, yeah, it was a big thing in the
way that Britney Spears was a big thing. You know, it's, it's not, didn't shift the fucking
plates beneath the surface and it didn't move the mountains. It was, it was a thing. It was
very popular thing. And you all worked quite a bit, like quite a bit. All of you have gone on to
do other things. Now, one thing McCarthy does not talk about in this, uh, is the fact that he's
recovering and he has talked about how drunk he was through a lot of this and whatever.
So that was kind of like one of the elements of it that I didn't like was like, dude,
talk about like the other things that could have played a contributing factor and stop making it
sound like this one article and this label. He says to Estevez, Scorsese and Coppola aren't
picking up the phone to call members of the Brat Pack as if they were going to pick up the phone
to call these actors anyway. Guys, you're a bunch of 22 year old kids. There was a thing happening
where people wanted to see teenagers starring or portrayed in movies. It was a big thing that was
happening. It was very new. You guys did get to a place of notoriety and exposure and fame
that you would have not gotten to given the, without this trend that was happening.
There is truth in the article that you've cut the line a bit. Whether the guy was mean about that
or not, I can't say. I didn't read it. I just know that that's something mentioned in the article.
The author himself says, I perhaps could have been a little nicer in places, but I just portrayed
something. I depicted it. And by the way, I promise you, when this guy went out to dinner with them
and they're all at the top of the fucking world drinking 22 year old LA 80s, probably Coke,
whatever, I promise you they probably weren't the coolest fucking people to be around. And he was
probably like, these guys all think they're who the fuck they are. And they don't get how this
works. It'll be fleeting. I'll take them down a peg. And there's been a billion articles like that
in the past. This one caught fire. I liked that the guy was unapologetic about it. And I couldn't
believe that McCarthy was rolling his eyes. I think he thought this guy would drop up to his knees
and apologize. But when he says these big directors didn't want them, Stanley Kubrick
wanted Anthony Michael Hall for Full Metal Jacket. And Anthony Michael Hall's ego blew that up.
He turned that project down. But that's just not the case. Kubrick wanted Anthony Michael Hall,
a textbook Brat Pack kid. Scorsese was working with Tom Cruise a few years after this.
In Color of Money, Tom Cruise, at least a tangential part of the Brat Pack.
Demi Moore, who he talks with in this thing, had massive, massive stardom on into the 90s and 2000s.
And she was in the Brat Pack. It's like he doesn't make any of these connections.
She's incredibly insightful. She's incredibly insightful. She's so balanced. She's so
level -headed. She says at one point, she goes, you took this term and allowed it to speak to
something that was already inside of you. And he admits it. He goes, oh my God, say that again.
And he realizes, you just nailed it. This was something I was struggling with and I
gave credence to this article because of it. I thought she was amazing. I thought Rob Lowe
had a good perspective on all of it. But you talk about Anthony Michael Hall. He's not in it.
He clearly is a guy that's like, hey man, I'm not against talking about it. Anthony Michael Hall
will always pop up at those Breakfast Club thing, the panels or whatever. He's always being funny.
He's always in a great mood. He's become a beloved character actor. He's taking that path
and he's great at it. And he's just like, yeah, I'm doing my thing, man. I'm having a good time.
Molly Ringwald didn't participate. She was like, yeah, I'm just kind of moving forward here.
No big deal. Tom Cruise, they show an interview clip of him at one point where he goes,
I need to do what's good for me. And you're like, yeah, that's why this guy
is not worried about an article called The Brat Pack. Estevez. Look at Estevez's career.
You forget how much shit Emilio Estevez has fucking done.
And it's because to me the Estevez scenes in this documentary play like a thriller.
Like Estevez clearly doesn't really want the company. You get the impression McCarthy's like
on his street and he comes in. Estevez looks alarmed from the jump, but then McCarthy just
starts unloading on him about all this stuff. And you can just see Estevez being like, I want this
out of my home as soon as possible. And Estevez winds up being cool and a good interview or
whatever. But if I'm McCarthy and I'm editing that footage of myself, I don't know how I would not
look into Estevez's eyes and be like, because I'm too self -aware, but I would just be like,
holy shit, this guy did not want me there. How do you not realize that?
McCarthy has, there's an aloof, it's not aloof. That's the wrong word. He's just not attuned to
it. There's something, something's off. I can't tell, I don't know what it is. He's just a little
socially clueless at moments in this. There's the thing where at the end of the interview
with the guy that wrote the article, they come to the common ground and McCarthy goes,
this was amazing. Can I give you a hug? And you're like, wow, what awesome closure.
And then it cuts to as he's leaving the guy's house and he's going,
do you think you could have been nicer? And I was like, why are you still asking him questions?
You just did, you just did the makeup. It's done. And even if this part of it happened,
cut it out. The end is you hugging the guy. What it really made me, and this is why I
guess it wasn't a total failure because I really hated watching this for the most part.
And I really, I did not like McCarthy for the most part, but this kind of like just, you know,
navel gazing, looking back is always kind of gross to me, especially when McCarthy is blowing up
the importance of what this was to an outrageous degree. But what I realized was,
I'm not going to say something is callous is like cream rises to the top because there's a
lot of luck in this business and a lot of crazy things that go on and personal problems and ETC,
but what I enjoyed the most about this and got out of it was watching 10 different people with
varying levels of modern day success. And you can tell from five minute interviews with each of them
why they are where they're at. It's in my opinion, Estevez is basically his hands are up the entire
conversation with McCarthy as if to say, step back from me. And that's a guy who has worked
steadily, but has stayed completely out of the public eye to the point where just seeing him
talk as a normal guy was kind of jarring because I feel like I've never watched him be interviewed.
Demi Moore comes up. She is, she is gorgeous. She's cool. She's a modern woman. She feels
completely at ease and comfortable with herself. I've listened to her autobiography. She had a
movie at Cannes coming out. She understands, and this is all stuff I'm just assuming from
watching five minute interviews. She understands you got to kind of just chill and let life do
what it's going to do. Andrew McCarthy, our host into this world is so bitter and so obsessed with
looking back that to me, I was like, I cannot be that person. I will say nobody likes being around
that person and everyone has ups and downs and you can't be the one talking about my life sucks,
my life sucks, my life sucks because at a certain point that energy is pushing everybody away.
That's what I took from this movie. Your energy, how you present yourself to the world is important
and he comes off as a whiner to me. I don't think he's pushed people away. I just think that there's
a, you see a difference in perspectives and one is to me the healthier perspective than the other.
I didn't find him bitter. He's never angry. He's never like, what the fuck? He's just,
he's kind of laughing about all of it. Like, well, this wasn't good.
But I think just saying Scorsese is not going to call breath back is bitterness.
Ah, maybe, you know, I think it's,
I think it's, you know, an unawareness, you know, I think it's right. I don't think he's saying it
like, he doesn't say it like, I could have been that goddammit. He says it like, like, you know,
it's like when you're talking to somebody and you go, yeah, man, had to leave the job, you know,
dude, it's just kind of like, you know, when Dr. Dre did it, you know, and you don't stop and go,
I'm not comparing myself to Dr. Dre. I'm just saying like, you know, I'm just speaking colorfully.
He doesn't say the part where he goes, I'm speaking a little colorfully here. I'm not,
you know. So that's the part of it where I'm like, I don't think he's bitter. I think he's just a
little unaware and not tuned into. You realize you sound a little self -obsessed and arrogant and
whatever right now. But I think the perfect depiction of the difference between his
perspective and what I would say is the healthy perspective is Estevez because Estevez talks about
how he turned down that great script that he really wanted to do because they wanted him
and Andrew McCarthy to do it together. And he said, I'm sorry, like, I had to get away from
anything connected to this, whatever it was. So there's a guy that did see the article as bad,
that did see the label as bad and went, okay, I have to work differently now. And he did.
Right. Whereas McCarthy is going, you know, it's the article's fault that I couldn't work
differently. And it's like, no, it's not, it could be, but more likely it's a thing you've
hung on to too much. I mean, there's a, I just watched after I watched this on Hulu, or tried
to watch, it was terrible. But I tried to watch some fucking movie, something horses with him in
Ringwald. And it's like later phase, brat pack years, something. It's terrible. Fresh horses?
Fresh horses. Yeah. It's a terrible movie. When you look at these filmographies,
they all have, not only including, especially Ringwald, they have some miserable years in there.
John Cryer, I know pretty well, he's a super well adjusted, nice guy, family man. I met with him
about a show years back, really, really nice guy. And it never would have occurred to him, aside
from me bringing up how much I love Pretty in Pink, he's not ever talking about the brat pack
or that. He is the director. He says very specifically, he was not part of it. He says,
that's true, but certainly adjacent. And you know, he had a very similar trajectory, but he had in
those late eighties years, they all, they all made such shitty movies and such career choices.
Maybe that's what they were offered, but you didn't have to do them. Like that's what's sort
of weird about this is it's like, you're also responsible for your own career. You had all the
opportunities and privileges other people had. Now John Cryer just hung in there, remained a good
guy and eventually strikes gold on the biggest sitcom on television. That could have been you,
McCarthy, and it still could. Well, Cryer actually says the opposite. I was kind of pissed that I
wasn't a part of it because it was like a cool kid thing. So here's the thing is like, excuse me,
in the exploration of the effect of this article, they kind of demonstrate what the article was
talking about. It's like, what exactly are we complaining about here? That you only got to be
in six hit movies in your twenties and it didn't go on longer? This is what the article is talking
about. You got a lot really early and you don't know how that is supposed to work because you've
jumped the line and you don't have the experience to know how to process all this problem. It's
literally what the article is saying. Or at least what they say the article is saying in the movie,
because again, I didn't read the article, but they talk about that was a big part of it.
And I think this, I enjoyed the documentary, but I think it could have very much benefited
from a summation at the end of something saying, you know, maybe this is what it was. Maybe it was
that we did get it all too fast too soon. And because of that, we earned this title of the
But also maybe it was because we were so young and lucky and gifted that we were unfairly labeled.
There's a duality there that does exist, I think. And I would have liked that to have been -
Do it as a parody of The Breakfast Club. Do it as that final narration. But there we were,
a blonde, a brunette. That narration lends itself to that. You could do this kind of affectionate
wrap up. Instead, they end with that Judd Nelson bit where I'm like, are we coming back after the
end credits to hear what Judd Nelson has to say? But that was a joke. You remember that when he
goes, Judd? Yeah, I like that part. That part made me laugh. What's so bad about that part?
They say throughout the movie, like nobody knows where Judd Nelson is. And he's like kind of the
bad boy rebel. And then the last thing is his phone rings and he goes, Judd? And then it cuts
to the end of The Breakfast Club with him putting his fist up. I thought that was a funny end.
And you have to then include that conversation, don't you?
No, to me, it's very - It didn't happen.
No, no, no. I actually thought that might be real that moment. But to me, the insinuation was,
Judd Nelson has said, I'm not participating in this. We don't have to say it.
The last shot of The Breakfast Club is us letting you know he's still this guy and he's
not going to play ball. Okay. All right. That's how I took it. I thought that was fun.
But Ali Shidi also comes off, everybody comes off well in this.
Well adjusted, yeah.
McCarthy does too to an extent. It's just, again, he's got these moments where you go,
ah, dude, you're a little out of touch with what I think what this is.
I mean, for me, he was always a low point of that group. And this made me like him significantly
less. And I think part of it might just be my own OCD and kind of obsession with looking back that
has plagued me my whole life, that I recognized parts of his personality that I didn't like.
But yeah, I was just like, to me, it was a cautionary tale. It was very
do not become this guy. Be thankful for what you have. Be happy with what you have
and trust and the knowledge that you get a real cool job at age 46. You can get a real
cool job at age 66. You just got to keep living your life and be nice to people.
That's what I took from it, which I guess is a great lesson.
Fair enough. My hog is straight out on this, doc. I think it's worth a watch.
I can't tell you you're going to love it. I can't say you're going to hate it.
That's worth a watch.
Yeah, mine is down. I found it extremely annoying while watching it. And I would say
I did hate it. But now today talking about it, I realized it inspired a lot of
thought and conversation and myself. So I guess it's a good thing.
We will be back. Not quite sure with what we've been toying with the crow in honor of the upcoming
Crow remake, which I suppose is coming out at some point.
It got pushed back. It got pushed from June till August. And there's one review has leaked
and it was the guy I think that was on the project and then was removed.
Yeah.
Or somebody like that. Or maybe somebody did the I don't know, whatever. But this review,
he was like, this fucking thing is unwatchable. Like it is a fucking disaster.
And I've been, I know the star keeps wanting to distance himself from it in interviews and stuff,
which is not a good sign.
No. So I, yeah, because we've all wanted to see a crow movie that's all brightly colored.
Anyway, we'll be back, folks. Thanks for listening. We'll see you next time.
And we'll see you.
In hell.