I'm here for Bett Rivers online casino and sportsbook with poker icon Phil Helmuth.
And now thanks to the excitement of Bett Rivers, I'm also a slots icon.
That's great! And a same game, parlay icon. Cool, cool. A blackjack icon,
a money line icon, a roulette. Take it from Phil Helmuth. If you love games,
Bett Rivers is the place to play in Bett. Bett Rivers. Games on.
Must be 21 plus in present in West Virginia. Void were prohibited. Terms in conditions apply.
gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamber.
The football season is full of guarantees, and here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October, if
your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fancash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning or winning money back in fancash,
guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook, winning hits different here.
Monthly, 21 -plus, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamberler, offer not available in all states,
terms apply, see Fanatic Sportsbook app.
Welcome to, we'll see you in hell the podcast that is part of the Fangoria podcast network
for more info about that network, including other shows.
Maybe you want to follow them, maybe you want to follow us, you want to find episodes
of our show or their shows, whatever, go visit Fangoria .com.
And here we are, my friend, Patty Walsh, hey gang, and I are sitting here, second beer
the night about to discuss the conjuring part two and then also probably the conjuring.
Yeah. I think we're hitting that. It's probably just out of theaters headed towards DVD. You
don't want to spoil something. Ghostbusters felt like we had to talk about it because it was
so much in the public eye. Conjuring two, you should have seen it by now if you were going to see it.
So that's your spoiler alert disclaimer. Spoiler alert, right.
are we going right in huh you want to to the discussion I mean we could the
conjuring discussion we could we front load of the last one with a lot of
chit chat and we can we can chit chat well I mean we were just recorded the last
one that's nothing's really happened in the five minutes of break time that we
know what I got nothing else I'll tell you my ass is sweating right now it's
a little hot in here on a leather chair. It's always a nice feel. Yeah. Yeah, get that itch.
We'll go into it. We can of course be her off as we always do. My my review is this. Conjuring
one saw it up here with my lady up at the Vista like a Friday night 10 p .m. And that place is kind of
the perfect place to see a horror movie. He's got all these like, you know, gypsies with glowing
eyes you know sculptures up and you know it's very old time yeah I love it
there yeah ten chlorophyll lane late show with you the visit fucking loved it's
also a theater that would traditionally the audience gets very into the
movies audience was loud there was this grown man who screamed in such an
effeminate manner in the conjuring that the audience laughed for like five
full minutes afterwards it was such a great genuine scream just had a
This is the first one down first one. I thought it was
Certainly one of the better horror movies of the past, you know, five six years now pat before you even continue
It sounds like you're ramping up. I'm ramping baby. It sounds like you're ramping up to say you maybe didn't like this second one
I'm ramping. I
You're gonna sit there and tell me you didn't like the conjuring to I was
deeply bored by the conjuring to
I wasn't scared remotely.
I thought it kind of lost all the charm of the original.
I think a big part of it was Lily Taylor,
who's great and the kids and everything.
The clapping thing was just a great gimmick
that they executed so well.
This had no set pieces to hold my interest that I can recall.
No real jumps.
The nun walking around wasn't scary in any way.
Story kind of held together.
It was just boring as shit.
And those two ghost hunters I'm getting bored of them, you know, you're getting bored of them. Patrick Wilson
Campion every goddamn movie
It's enough. Give some give some to Thomas Jane once in a while. Well, I mean you can't recast
You can't cast Patrick Wilson. I know. I get sick of all the Wilson and
You know from Iga I do like her. I really loved her in orphan, which is a great fucking horror movie. Orphan is shit
Oh, and you're everything so far that you've said about Conjuring 2 is wrong.
You didn't like Orphan.
Okay, let's, let's, we're off to work in for a second here.
All right.
Yeah, no.
Orphan is cool and the twist is so stupid that it ruins the entire movie.
I think the twist is one of the best twists for Christ's sake.
It's the most memorable twist.
It's it's an it's idiotic that I have seen the twist is idiotic
I loved it and have maybe even better than the conjuring. I have maybe never had a better time at a horror movie than going to see orphan
I the audience was howling with laughter screaming the scares are real the character shits real
She's great in it scars guards great in it fucking orphans great in it. I loved it. I
I think the twist is so ludicrous boy. I love that when she
Spoiler alert reaches over and starts feeling his upper thigh there the audience was
Flipping out and for to be flipping out that much in a non -scarce scene in a horror movie
I was like that's a twist that fucking works. That's a that's a twist that goes for it
It doesn't I know they had an alternate ending because I'm sure they were like guys. We're gonna need to test this ridiculous ending
certainly ridiculous you know to me it was it was every bit as like fun and kind
of exciting a reveal as like the end of fucking psycho it takes a big swing
and it and it worked for me it's it's it's that the part where she seduces him
is so a believable yeah it's executed in such a believable fashion that I was
convinced this girl's got to be 18 and she just looks young or something and it's
like no she's 13 and actually breathed in his ear like that which is kind of
weird but that's not why I didn't like the movie that was a very ballsy scene
and my hats off to him for doing something that daring but you don't look
if you haven't seen the movie I'm gonna ruin the twist the thing she's 45 she's
not eight get out of the house it's like nobody with that like Gary Coleman
condition looks that convincingly like a child when they're 45 they're small
but they look like a small older person I mean look my heart is dead as a door
now why is it that I could open myself up to these things in movies and you can't
I would never even occurred to me to play the logic professor on that one. I'm
been like, well now, would she really look like that? I'm like, hey gang, great
fucking twist. It's a shitty twist especially. Were you surprised? Well, no. No, I
wasn't surprised and I was I was very disappointed. I can't recall if I
guessed it or not. I remember the movie leading up to it. I remember I was
It was wholly disappointed that there was nothing supernatural at play.
I thought that was what was keeping my attention, that was what was keeping this exciting
for me.
I loved that.
See, that's crazy to me that you would have rolled with a supernatural twist.
Yes.
But not the very real thing that happens in it.
There's so many logic loopholes you have to jump through.
I jumped.
two two to actually believe that a 45 year old woman has been pulling this off
successfully for 30 years or whatever it's been it's like why can't you just
jump I don't want to jump I'll tell you what I jumped at the conjuring to it scared
the shit out of me at a great time I and I will say this yeah just to set us
off in the right direction and I mean this and it's gonna burn your butt I think
the Conjuring 2 was the correct version of the Conjuring 1.
I thought it was a similar story.
I said they did everything.
They did wrong in the first one right in this one.
Folks, you're at it here.
I mean, look, I think horror is just in a real bad patch.
When I said the Conjuring is one of the most fun horror movies
the past few years, I meant it.
I don't think it's a masterpiece, but it's far, far, far
of periods too. And I am shocked that you were scared by anything. It was scary. It was
suspenseful. It was really scary. Scariest part of Conjuring 2 was the trailer for that new
Ouija Board 2 movie which looks kind of horrifying. How dare you. What you you coming to my home.
I didn't see Ouija Board 1. It's not well it's not called Ouija Board first of all.
And it's a bad remake of a bad 80s movie, but didn't see any any of what I didn't see the we just either
I don't know why I just said it like I saw them. I'm just only assuming that it's not a great movie
It didn't look great. We did too does look pretty cool. Yeah, it looks scary. I like that looks scary, but let's not fear off
Conjuring to because I really want to go through why I think this I keep trying to veer off because it bored me
You know like I they did everything right that the first movie did wrong number one
It was rated R and not PG -13. Yes for what for being scary. I don't know
Really they went PG -13 and they have a massive
Worldwide smash and then they went to R for the sequel. I think so let me look it up
I mean
I mean, somebody's got to challenge these wild claims.
Looking it up.
Go on, because you were making a list
and that'll give me time to look at it.
First of all, it's rated R and the first one was it.
Might not be true.
Second of all, it's such a more interesting
and believable concept of the haunted house story
or approach to the haunted house story
than the first one is.
The first one is literally just,
They move into this house and then suddenly something's bought like haunting them and oh, I guess it came from this music box
Second one once again it comes from music box and it comes from a horrifying music box because it's that like
Lanky man dancing around in it. Yeah, that guy shows up later. I love the idea that little scene with him at the end of the
Hall and a little tent some of that stuff worked. I thought he drew out the Joltz way way like it like as far as Joltz scares goes
I go just in the limit is a master. Yeah
Well, he drew him out to the extent that the movie was as I just saw
Two hours and 15 minutes long. Was it rated R? It was rated
Yeah, I think that's a crazy choice and probably why they lost it's on the money on the sequel
They didn't lose a ton of money. Did they that well the you know the gross in terms of one to two
went down about two hundred million dollars, I think.
I loved it. I rewatched one after I saw two.
Now my mom had my mom and dad with me when I saw the movie.
My mom, it was the most scared I've ever seen a human being
in a movie in my life. Really?
She was literally covering her face and threatening to leave.
She was so scared.
My God, I had nothing.
Two days later, we watched the conjuring one.
My mom said, is this going to scare me as bad?
I said, it's nothing compared to the second one.
and she sat there and just halfway there goes,
you're right, this isn't scary.
It just paled in comparison.
The only really scary part in the first one
is the clap part of scary.
And then the part where the ladies
like on top of the dresser or the wardrobe thing.
Yeah, what it might, I mean, look, I know what I saw.
It might be a Friday night sold out,
packed house screaming and yelling,
helped conjuring one a bit for me
and seeing part two at the Armanian Grove, the Glendale Galleria, with about four people
in attendance at about a 4 .45 p .m. show, but I was so bored and I checked my phone
eight million times to see what time it was.
I don't understand.
I don't understand that you have the audacity, but I saw it with hate it too.
You have the audacity to sit here as the co -host of a horror, predominantly horror movie
podcast.
Yeah.
And to talk like this, just right out of your ass, into a mic.
I could say this to you about Orphan, and I just did.
I think to slap in the face of Orphan is a great mistake.
Meanwhile, we talked, you and I saw it in City as three together, and we could talk about
that.
We're both like, I don't even remember, there's nothing to say about it.
Orphan, everybody remembers Orphan.
That says something right there.
well everybody remembers plan nine from outer space it doesn't mean it's a good
movie you know everybody remembers you remember a lot of things you know I
remember watching divine eat dog shit literally at the end of pink flamingos
and to me it's which I love but I'm not saying that that's a it means it's good
yeah you just eat dog shit there's so many movies that like on the drive home
I'm like I don't even know if I remember one moment of that as being you know
Standing out to me or being memorable or fun and they'll ever think about it again almost every time I go out of the movies
orphan I remember it all
beautifully shot
It was very beautifully shot. I remember the blood spill in the snow sequence was it kills
The opening
Was so disgusting that I was like I don't even know if I'm gonna be able to take it
And the whole rest of the movie pulls back on the gore the openings that just like it's a birth dream
where it's like very bloody and orphaned tentacles.
Yeah, I don't remember.
Yeah, there's tentacles.
I guarantee that they were like,
hey, we got more of a thriller on our hands here.
You got to put something real disgusting up front
and into the script.
There's tentacles coming out of Regina.
There's a lot of blood and like instruments and shit,
but then I remember when the baby comes out,
it's kind of like a demon tentacles type thing,
which is probably why you were thinking supernatural.
Well, look, I'm going to give Wurfing another shot on your say so, please, on your say so, please. I'm going to go revisit it with an open mind. All right. I own it. If you want to borrow it.
I can afford my own DVDs. Thank you very much. All right. I don't need any handouts. But you can't afford the DVDs. I don't buy horror on Blu -ray because I like it to look as grainy as humanly possible.
You see how's the devil I did you love it. I liked how's the devil quite a bit
That's a great. I actually one of my favorite genres going now is the
Kind of affectionate but still scary on its own tribute to like 80s horror. Yeah it follows
You know the guests your next all those now I sat in a bar the other name my friend Steve who I love
Dearly and I mean he swore up and down that it follows was the biggest piece of shit
He's ever seen in his life and I just couldn't I just didn't understand what he was talking people are pretty pretty split down the middle on it
I've heard the same. I love it loved it. You and I saw it together
The Adder we walked out saying there's only been two other times. I've been that freaked out in a movie that old dude coming down the hall
A lot of those like old people falling or and stuff were just really really terrifying. Well my my scariest
moment in that film was when the ladies peeing herself and walking
the teaser yeah and then outside you said when the tall guy walked up
behind her yeah that that got you yeah and then we both said the the most
scared I ever got in a theater was the girl throwing up in six cents that was
for me I had a 105 fever which I found out the next day and I actually thought
that I was going to die when I saw that it scared me to such a degree probably
fever helped the other five what the hell was going on and you're in your life
well five seven I had strep throat in my throat it almost like closed off but
I didn't even think about a fever and they had I had to have some
positives it was a real scene one of five seven you can die from that yeah yeah
it was bad my sister like practically dragged me over her shoulder into the
urgent care it was real bad did they make you do the cold shower thing to bring
your body temp down? Like in Jacob's ladder? Yeah, I did some of that. What I did, I used
to get strep throat, every Thanksgiving -ish, never had it. Second, I got health insurance,
never got it again. My throat would essentially close off, and my buddy Mike told me, hey, if
you ever get strep throat, what you do is you wad up a peanut butter sandwich, a full peanut
butter sandwich. Wad it up into a tight ball and just swallow as hard as you can, the entire
saying which watered up. Now when I came to find out is this guy would have a sore throat
and for some reason that like coded and helped him and kind of stretch things out, he said
he was not fucking with me because I told him that I did this and it almost killed me.
And I believed him. He was like, I was not fucking with you. It worked for me. But at about
two in the morning, I was like, I'll do anything to make this stop. Medicine isn't working.
walking, watered up a PB sand, swallowed it, it immediately fully lodged in the tiny hole
in my throat. I could not scream. My parents were upstairs asleep. I was like 17, and I
swiped onto the floor, a plate, and broke it. Praying that somebody would hear it. My mom
came running downstairs, and I was like, and there's real gross. There was like a lot of reaching
in on a wet fingers and peanut butter covered fingers coming out and tried to
make myself puke and she was like Pat what the hell were you thinking right
so I was too old to be doing something this stupid and I was like Mike told me
it's the only thing to help she's like he was messing with you obviously right to
this day it's a it's a source of controversy right I it could have been he was
messing with me and then when he heard I was stupid enough to do
do it and almost died. He backed out.
I think that's what you're doing to me right now with Orphan.
You're trying to go back and watch it.
I don't give two shits if you watch it,
but I would give Orphan an A.
You hear how he talks?
I give Orphan an A.
You can't see it like hell.
What did you know?
Here's the thing. You can't just say the conjuring
to was boring and it's just because it's boring.
What was boring about it?
There were good amount of scares.
There were good amount of scary sequences.
I liked how I liked the mystery of are they going to figure out how to defeat this thing.
I liked how they did figure out how to defeat the thing.
I liked that that none kept haunting her through the movie.
I really didn't care about the none.
I mean, me and my buddy were very bored.
the audience did suck it was kind of a boring crowd I guess but just like it had
nothing for me the little the little thing that was kind of like the Bob
Adooc type thing you were talking about the skinny man yeah I liked that
nothing else what was he called red look look look that up what was he called he's
not called the skinny man he's called like the you like Bob Adooc by the way it's a
fine film, but I wouldn't say it was scary or that memorable, but I mean it was well
done. I thought her and the kid were both great. Yeah, I thought, I thought
everything was in place. I just, you know, it just didn't really excite me because
again, it's, you know, if it's, I want it to be supernatural. I like supernatural. I
don't like where at the end you find out it wasn't supernatural. It was all on
their head or there's actually a logical explanation. I mean, I just, I don't
know that just that's that always feels like a letdown to me uh what what what do
you got here on this guy from the conjuring to you know name. I guess I'm going
to the old wiki page because there's the song it's the the Lanky man the
Lanky man yeah walked around and they're doing a spin -off film with the none yeah
I'm excited about that why what's the problem did you enjoy Annabelle Annabelle
I didn't see it. I own it. I've seen it. It's not great. Did you enjoy what was
that other puppet one from like seven eight years ago? Childs play? No, no, no.
Like the one that came out like around the same time as Transformers. Dead Silence.
That is just, there's also Justin Lin. Yeah. And it's not a good movie. Okay. And I
couldn't have been more excited to see a horror movie than I was for Dead Silence
Because I love evil puppets. I mean it's it really gets me okay, and it's it's it's just bad in fact
I just read a thing where it was like
Bad movies by great hard directors and his was dead silence
Because I've revisited so many times and I'm like I've got to be missing something like this guy doesn't make bad movies like he
And it's terrible. Yeah, it's just really so Mark. You do one of the final destination. I don't think so
I mean, here's the problem, that's, you love the final destination franchise, I had a lot of fun with as far as I can remember every one of them.
I mean, the first two, and those kills I remember now, 15 years later.
The first two were enjoying bed four or five.
It's like, who gives a shit?
Those to me really brought back the spirit of in a different way than it follows and all those but brought back the spirit of kind of
The cheesy 80s horror. Yeah, and I liked it quite a bit
That's what I wanted from Dead Silence. I thought it was gonna get back to a sort of child's play kind of thing
Who's stars in Dead Silence? Well, Donnie Walberg. There it is
And he does this thing through the movie. He plays a cop. He plays like a hard boiled cop
And he does this thing through the movie every scene. He's always got an electric razor
And he's always shaving wherever he that's like his thing wherever he's going. He's always that's his character development
Yeah, and it's like what what the fuck is this?
I would not speak to that man
I'm not talking to you until you put that not not even in your pocket because I want little shavings falling
You actually go wash your face off then you can come back and interrogate me about my whereabouts
on the night that this puppet killed a family.
And then of course, he's the character
that eventually has to learn to believe
as he investigates the show.
He realizes the puppets are doing it.
It's a cool story, too.
It's like a witch lady that like Lord Children in
and it's a really cool story and it's scary
because there's puppets, but it's not good.
It just doesn't, it's not well done.
You a puppet master, fam?
I can know, I like the first one.
I mean, those are, I never saw any of them.
Those are the what's it called what's the company that does those full moon or whatever, you know, and they did
They did those and they did demonic toys. Yeah, probably robot jocks
They might have done the reanimator films, which I'm a huge fan of now. Do you where do you go on child's play?
I've only seen one. I love child's play one. I love child's play
two I
I think I like three.
I don't remember I've been seen it in a while.
Is that like a military base?
Yeah, I think I like it.
I just can't remember I've been seen it in a long time
and I really liked the curse of Chuckie quite a bit.
The bride of Chuckie and C to Chuckie,
I could care less about it.
I didn't like when they went in that comedy direction.
I kind of dug them, those I definitely saw.
So I've seen more of them, just the one.
Now, you people aren't here to see this,
but Pat looks as if he's about to fall asleep.
I'm wide awake.
I know you are, but you still have an answer to my question.
And I think it's because of the way you're sitting.
What did you find boring about the conjuring part two?
It's a very difficult thing to put into words
why you found anything boring.
It's the same thing as, do I find it funny?
If I laughed, I found it funny.
If I'm bored, I found it boring.
And I was bored the entire time would I would I have liked it more at 90 minutes?
Probably would I have even noticed the missing 45 probably not?
It was it was a bit longer. I'll give you that. It's too long. I'll give you that horror and comedy should not be longer than like an hour 45
It didn't happen. Well just I mean look the great horror films of our time are definitely longer than that
The exorcist the shining look if you got a fucking all -time classic then then take your time
But you don't I don't think with conjuring too. I think that's what he was attempting to do
It felt like of it felt like an unsettling late 70s horror movie to me
mid 70s horror movie
With the choice I mean, but it is literally it's the same movie it opens with them at another case. Yeah
that will come back throughout the film to bought them,
no pun intended, at the end of that sequence,
it turns to have still shot of the two of them,
the demon hunters, a text thing scrolls up the screen
that says who they are and then ends with saying
but one case was so evil.
So both of them start like that,
then it shows the title
And then it's they go to a haunted house and all the same shit happens again. One of the kids gets possessed
Or somebody in the house gets possessed. There's a ghost here or something bad happened here. I
All I can say is that before the original
And I was born by the second. I don't really know what else to say
But I haven't heard many people speaking passionately about the conjuring to really and in fact no one
No one critics friends everyone always if they thought it was okay or what's it got on rent?
Tomato. I'm curious. I'm gonna take a guess. 85 percent. That's probably a little
hot but I think it did get a nice little while. I'm guessing 85 percent. I would be
surprised if it wasn't in the 90s. I know the original ones. Yeah. You know.
Conjuring to run tomatoes has a 80 % only 80 right well I would have guessed 85
as I did Pat Conjuring one has what you're saying in the 90s
well if somebody didn't come on now do you think if you saw the conjuring
to let's pretend that was the first one yeah do you think you would have
good board I mean probably just I find I found them very boring the original
has an 86 I found the actors boring there was no real standout there was no
one to root for I didn't care about the family or the kids I can't tell with
Patrick Wilson's a good actor I really loved him in the second season of
Fargo I've liked him in things hard candy that girls episode was kind of fun
I liked him in that, you know, I think he's, he has never done anything different than
that.
Although in Fargo, he had what I eventually rose was a very difficult role where he is
just playing a purely good and nice man in a terrible world and he was really, really
great in it and he grows up to be, not a spoiler at all, Ted Danson in it who was fucking
amazing in Fargo.
Wait, he plays the Young Ted dance.
Fargo's the best show on television.
I've never watched Fargo yet.
It's the best show on television.
I heard it's amazing.
The first couple you're kind of like, I'm not sure I'm on board and then from then on it's
fantastic.
And it's got nothing to do with the Co -Embrothers movie.
It has a lot to do with the Co -Embrothers movie.
And there's multiple nods in every episode, multiple, for like a serious Cohen fan.
They reference every one of their movies constantly.
So in what ways is it connected to the Cohen brothers film Fargo?
Because everybody goes on, it's not the same characters, it's not the same time period,
it's not.
Finding out is actually, you know what?
What?
clearly I sense that I was wrong and they made fun of me for this at work when
Fargo was on much as I messed up vacation Patrick Wilson does not grow up to
be Ted Danson and I made that mistake on the show as well so folks don't
hold this is why I don't trust your opinions on these films no I just cuz I don't
think you know what you're watching half the time I bet you were inside that's
It's a it's a minor it's a minor point there are characters who grow up to be other characters
And they look nothing like the person they're supposed to be I feel like you were watching inside out
You thought it was the conjuring to you didn't know no, no
I'm pretty sure that Colin Hanks grows up to be nope, not I don't I have to watch it again
I'm on the case the fun of the show is finding out in what ways it can
In what ways it connects, you know, I'll say that when Bishemi buries the money and puts that ice scraper in there
that plays a big role in season one, that money.
Because it's after the movie season one.
Right.
But then the second season is like in the 80s,
or something, right?
Yeah, well, they'll say stuff like,
no, second season is in the 70s.
Or 70s.
And first season is in the modern day.
Yeah, well, it must take place after the film.
Yeah, it does.
And they'll reference like,
Well, you know, all that's crazy shit that went on in brainer and still like that, you know
There but there's nods to all the Combrose movies all the time musical nods
Dialogue nods etc. So it's a combo. Let's give it their blessing, but they're also kind of like
You know not involved in anyway. They're not involved in anyway. It's just a they they're EPs on it
I'm sure they get a nice check on it, but they're not involved. I'm sure they had to say
okay and that dude his name's Noah Hawley created the show and I think the
guy did a fantastic job. It's essentially it's essentially taking the
universe of Fargo the film and expanding it and saying this is a much bigger
thing. Yeah. These people all have you know other roots planted elsewhere and
things that let events that led to them doing this thing in the movie. Yeah and
And it's very funny and it's also got like crazily good action sequences and everybody
in it is great.
Actors you haven't seen in a while.
Everybody shines.
Strongly recommend.
All right.
I auditioned for the show.
I didn't get the part.
What part?
Do you remember?
It was some guy on a cold road who comes into town.
That could be literally anyone.
I remember though line is like something like he's like has a he squares off with the cop on the road
And he's like well look at this to been just talking on the side of a cold road
He's like some bad guy coming in. Okay. There's gonna be trouble character. I don't know. I've never seen the show
Okay, that's just what I auditioned for though. They again could have been kind of a lot of people
Yeah, what do you want from me Pat? I'm already on one hit show. I can't be on two
I saw the purge
Election year you went to see that I did I really enjoyed the first purge with obviously some reservations
I thought right was a great low budget, you know thriller
Ethan Hawke was great in that I came to run with Ethan Hawke usually
The second I thought was the whole time in the first one. I'm like this is such a genius present
presence
Cremace? Cremace, Jesus Christ. Such a genius premise.
Grow easier in yourself. It's alright.
Why the fuck are they keeping it contained in this one house? That was my whole thing.
I was like, somebody came in and pitched this idea. And the guy behind the table didn't
go, you don't want to know what's going on in one house the night of the purge?
Right.
You want to be out in the purge. And then, of course, two brought that home. I thought two was
was good. Three starts with a scene of like the president's advisers all sitting
around a table and this guy acting sort of the worst performances I've ever seen
in a theatrical release movie he's like well bring this seward I can't
do I'm gonna lose my voice he says seward you know I don't say that word he says
bring this cut all right go spusters people I don't say it all right but it's
such a ludicrous performance that kicks the movie off and you're like is this a
joke and wait this is the president because I'm trying to look up as you tell
this story yeah this is the guy who plays the president
his performance yeah yeah yeah but who knows when it comes when it's Pat
That was telling you, could be a 11 -year -old kid for the president of the United States.
One of the other.
I have been diagnosed as having an OCD brain and it makes it hard for me to focus on things
but I won't take Adderall because I think it turns your brain to mush.
All right.
So it starts with the scene and what happens in this scene?
He's like, it's election year so it's basically they're kind of loosely alluding to what's
going on now I felt like but very loosely because I'm sure it was made prior to it.
Oh, they sure those movies out real fast.
The actor you've seen a million times, he's been good in other things.
His name is Raymond J. Barry.
Just a terror.
I'm sorry.
Now somebody's going to at him or something.
He's been great in many things.
But and I'm sure he was directed to give this absolutely ludicrous performance.
rame and jay bary who plays with the key place the president
i already tuned out i'm not listening sorry the president or perhaps an
advisor i've already
all right i watched these a long time ago you know i saw it a long well the
the poor selection you came out a month ago he wasn't that long ago
it seems long to me when i walk out of it i'm like all right i don't ever need to
think about it again
oh yeah i know this guy yeah of course rame and jay bary
All right, so he says the cunt in our purge needs to stop it. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. And then what?
Oh, yeah, he's in training day. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. He's great. All right. Plot. Mass.
To set. Nope. But what is Charlie Ruff? Yeah. Okay. So he is the part. No. No. Charlie. Listen.
And FFA headed by Caleb Warren just focus for you her as a threat to their rules
So it's the new new founding father. Yeah, they're like they want to do the purge
She's gonna get rid of the purge and she could get elected. Yeah, and he and she's a tight threat and they want to kill her
The seaworth so then they want to kill her during the purge obviously. Yeah, exactly. Okay. Um, so then what happens?
You know the the scares are weak. There's
you know, some terrible humor attempts.
You've never seen anyone in the movie before.
It looks like it cost about a million dollars.
Right.
You know, I'm surprised they couldn't just put a little more time into it, I guess.
But it is election year.
And that now that I'm saying it is why probably the movie was so rushed and cheap.
It's because they wanted to get it out before the election.
Right.
Could almost guarantee it.
Yes, I would guarantee that too.
I would guarantee that too.
all right because now Joe they don't make movies they they try to make
release dates you know you know I'm told you're not paid to act these days you're
paid to perform yeah I think the great Al Pacino once said that all right so the
purge election you're sucked I mean you know but here's what it confuses me is
that somehow you're putting because I didn't even see it because I was like it
looks stupid I don't care enough yeah I'm also not a huge fan of those kinds of
movies. But are those kinds of hard movies? You know, like slasher stuff, violent, physical,
like just people being violent. It's got to be really special like Halloween or something
like that for me to be into it. But, um, why do you think we don't have new slasers coming
out? They do. That was Halloween for a third time. But that was all they were doing for a while,
like Wolf Creek and Cry Wolf and all those, like that was like, I feel like, I know what you
did last summer, all those movies and scream the whole 90s, that's why I sort of feel like it's
time again because that's been 15, 16 years at this point. I mean, the collector is not too old.
I mean, what is that five years old? Maybe four years old. Never saw. I think that's a slasher.
You consider that a slasher movie? Yeah. I caught three minutes the other night. It was like,
boy, this is measurable of a movie called Captivity with Alicia Cuthbert being held in the basement.
I remember seeing the trailers for that this was I was like is am I watching Hall of Cost footage
It made me feel so terrible just that few minutes. That's why I don't like stuff like that
It makes me sad. Yeah, I'm like this is just stuff I'd hear on the news and I'd be depressed after yeah
Well, you know, Heather and I went up to see
Just any movie that was starting sometimes that's fun to do go up to the grove and try to see something
So we're like all right purge it is Heather hates scary movies, but it starts
And they got this whole family tied up and screaming and crying and this guy's like slapping them around and they're bloody and everything and I look over and
And there's eyes are huge and she just look kind of traumatized and it's like let's get out of here and go see this Mike and Dave and then we probably had a
Probably had a much better time and overrated that movie because
because Heather was like, thank God I don't have to sit and watch this anymore, but then
I went back and saw it anymore because I got to be a completist if I see five minutes
of something.
Really quick too, just to come back to it, full circle, well that full circle, we veered off
on Orphan. Here's the alternate ending. In an alternate ending for Orphan, Kate, after
Kate saves Max from Lena and they escape, Lena is seen hurrying into her room. There
she is shown with a face covered in bloody cuts while she reapplies her makeup which poorly
hides the cuts. She then puts on the dress she wore on her first day of school and greets
the police at the top of the stairs by cursing and introducing herself as
Esther. How does the movie itself end? She dies, right? And the orphan as it is?
Yeah, yeah, they're killing her own and both into the, oh that's right, it's the
ice, right? Yeah. Okay. Well, you know who produced the movie DeCaprio? Did he
really? Yeah. Well now I'm worried that I talk so much shit about it. I'll be
ruined in this town. Roger Ebert gave a orphan 3 out of 3 .5 stars. Only as a 55 % on
rotten trees. Was that while alive, Ebert? Yeah. You know what I find baffling now is
that they'll include on reviews, open their listing reviews, RogerEbert .com. And you're
always, it always throws me like, I don't know that it should be called that anymore.
We're at Rich Roper is my go -to guy now that Ebert's gone. Okay. I always check with Richard Roper. He seems to have a very fair balance of
painting. Yeah. I always liked Roper but to me he was kind of, you know, it's kind of how I felt about
Cisco to some degree. I always said it wasn't an Ebert guy through and through. Roper, he never really talks too
passionately about anything he's always just kind of like I don't know he doesn't
move me one way or the other I just like that he has I found his opinions to
be very accurate I like Peter Travers at Rolling Stones reviews too but he
Peter Travers to me the worst mover viewer alive I think he praises things too
easily a lot of the time you think he's the worst why I could talk for four
hours about Peter Travers nobody would want to listen but I could do it why I
I think he's got to be getting paid A right reviews are like that Pete Hammond guy when he was writing reviews paid reviews for max
I mean get paid off by the studios and he got found out all right for deadline
another great website
so
Peter Travers will say things like oh
Like he'll be talking about Mike and Dave or whatever you some innocent comedy and
I'm making this up, but let's I'm using that as an example because we're just talking about he'll be like
Sure the
Sensitive culture police won't like some of the you know
He's always putting himself in this rebel outsider stance. He's a 65 -year -old man
Right who's a fucking dork. There's nothing cool about him and he's always like, oh, I
realize it might not be everybody's cup of tea. That's how he approaches every
review and that no one could like this special jewel. But him because it's
outside of the Hollywood sister. All right. And if you really read every view
with that mind of him acting like he's some fucking outsider while praising every
single movie that comes out. Well you ruined it for me. Yeah he's garbage. You sure
that I think he gives way too much praise to things a lot of the time. But I do
essentially like what he has to say yeah I think the worst movie reviewer of all
time is Sandy Canyon Canyon sucks yeah and I don't know if he's everywhere I mean
Charlotte sucks but you gotta love those like Rex Reed reads it old bitch what a
fucking bitch that guy is he is sassy I like him the bet I like him I mean there's even
sassy here there's like that that guy online that always stirs people up Jeff
Wells or whatever and then there's the ultimate this guy even though I know he's a troll
He used to write for I believe the village voice when I live in New York. I would
Rip the paper open so fast like getting newsprint and cuts on my hand dying to read his article so that I could be upset
And I would go I know he's a troll
I know and you'd flip it open and all he does is
He's released his reviews a little after everyone else's and whatever everyone else says
he says the opposite.
I love it.
He was online saying recently saying that anyone who refers to Bill Cosby as a rapist
is racist and it's only motivated out of racial hate and in the comments will be like, but hundreds
of women and he'll be like, you're a racist too.
and it's almost admirable and he's a black guy which so you know it's kind of
harder for him to attack but he'll take these weird racist slants on movies
he praises I wish I had examples for you but he praises only dog shit and he spends
all his time shitting on movies that everyone loves that's well that's what
But Sandy Kenyon would do, but he wouldn't, but he would do it not in a trollish way in
a way that, and if you're not, if you don't live in New York, his movie reviews would play
on the TVs and the taxis.
And he, you know, something, you know, wonderful would come out, you know, like the prestige
I loved so much.
I can't remember what he thought of it, but like, there's a turd.
Yeah.
Dan DeFlipsey, and then third is DePref D.
I mean, when it came out, I loved it so much.
I thought it was a masterpiece.
Cool movie.
And he'll just shit all over that.
And then meanwhile, he'll do a review of like Morning Glory.
Just can't say enough nice stuff about.
The Rachel McAdams movie with the air.
Can I say something?
It's good.
I liked it too.
But I'm saying high praise.
Yeah, yeah.
High praise.
Oh, I enjoy seeing Ford, you know,
sure, who's his graphic exterior by the end of the film.
I liked it. I know. I watched speaking of Diane Keaton.
Love the Cooper's. John Goodman, Diane Keaton is a
Christmas movie. Olivia Wilde, whatever.
I love almost every Christmas movie.
I love Goodman,
fine with Keaton at this point.
used to love her. I'm like, I'll settle in and have a real nice time with this thing.
Folks, you would not believe how shitty this thing was. Steve Martin is narrating it for some
reason. He's not playing a character. That really bothers me when somebody distracting is narrating it.
It's so obviously Steve Martin who played Diane Keaton's husband in Father the bride. So right there,
You're like, why is this happening? It would any narrated father of the bride as well
So nothing makes sense. I guess they probably wanted him and he was like I can't do it
They give it to good men
And he's like I will narrate it if you throw me a million bucks
Just a real disaster you hated everyone in it. It's like a dysfunctional family movie
But you want everyone to die it's Alan Arkin and June squid and I remember my mom
expressing her extreme disappointment and surprise that Christmas with the
cranks wasn't a good movie. I mean, she talked about it the whole Christmas
that year. I've never seen it. No, it's not good. You know, you never know
with these things. It looked terrible, but she was like, you know, it just wasn't
good. Like how shocked she was that she thought it could have been great. My
buddy Ian, you know, because I like Paul Blart Mall Cop. That's the movie where we'd
all be like, oh, of course, that fucking sucks, whatever. But then the people that
watch it. No. First after that movie is funniest shit. It starts so strong. Very
funny. It's also with him and his mom is gold. It's another Ghostbusters
scenario for me. Yeah. It starts strong and then it just falls apart. But a lot
of comedy. I mean, when he's eating that fucking pie and he's talking
himself and he's going, pie fills the cracks of the heart. It's it's great. And
then it's just it just goes to shit, man. That's why I always watch a shitty
comedy I watched the bench warmers on your recommendation the other day some laughs but I I always love my favorite review of a comedy is something that everybody hates
like my buddy Ian was like talking about wild hogs and I was like I'm seeing that piece of shit like everybody knows that's bad and he kind of got quiet and he was like
quite a few laughs in there
couple laughs all right I'm like all right I'll DVR wild hogs did you DVR I got it's been sitting there for a while I haven't watched
Yeah, the hardest I laughed all year was was watching bench warmers for the first time and watching a man
Projectile vomit against the door of a porta potty because John Haters shit smelled so bad
I was yeah
You told me about that and I was waiting for that scene it was gross
And that was a funny little that movie had some funny parts love it was funny
The yeah, love it's as great in it and even better vomit gag is in the fucking doover when David spade pukes
We talked about it here.
It's seen in the doover.
And the best part of the bench whimmers is
they just let Rob Schneider be a straight man.
They didn't even try to let him be funny.
Straight man.
Thank you.
Who is actually in the love scene with his impossibly gorgeous wife
has pulled the covers up over his nipples
when he's sitting in bed after she leaves.
He's like, and not played as a joke.
He's trying to pass it off as natural while covering his body.
Yeah, Rob Schneider who stands, I guess, 4 -9 in real life, just believe he's like this dreamboat
jock from high school, like just had all the ladies and stuff.
Never revealed him in 20 minutes in and I was like, what?
Have you watched Rob Schneider's Netflix show?
It's a shit show.
It's disgrace.
I'm sure.
It's terrible.
Single cam?
It's a single cam.
It's like his version of Curb Your Enthusiasm.
I tried to watch it because my friend Jamie is a big part of the show and I love him and I wanted to support him.
I tried to watch this within five minutes of its starting.
He's at the airport bitching about his assistant being late to pick him up.
And then it's him, my buddy Jamie comes in who's playing the assistant.
He screams at the assistant and his whole thing is like, I have a 40 -year -old assistant.
what's wrong with me and it's like you're just coming off like an ass nobody can relate to this
people don't have assistance yeah yeah and it it's just like it's supposed to be like look how
funny it is that he's being a dick and it's like it's not funny he just seems like a dick I
I mean well no I won't even talk about I was gonna talk about a show of a comedian who's a friend of
yours that bummed me out this year but I'll they'll do it after all right well you want to cover the
Mike and mouth it like we did in the last thing?
Sure, here we go.
Just for a running theme.
Yeah.
Just a lot of material about how difficult fame is.
And when your whole life becomes fame,
of course, that's what you're thinking about.
But the quickest way to lose audiences,
and if not just they lose interest in you,
to actually have them dislike you,
is when you spend all of your time talking about the perils
and the difficulties of fame to the point where your entire show becomes about that.
Yeah, that's nobody wants to hear it. Nobody wants to hear it. Pat, look, look, I'm not
gonna lie to you. I got hot dogs in the fridge. I'm dyin' heat. I can respect that.
Plugs, new fiction column up now on Finguria .com, some severe situations. By the time this episode
drops, probably the second story will probably be out by then. So check that out and we should
be in the dead heat of August by now, so come see me in Edinburgh. I am here now in
Scotland at the French Festival. Joderosacomedy .com for all the details of the shows and things,
and September I will be in Arizona at St. up Scottsdale. I will also be at a casino in Minneapolis
list that I can't remember the name of right now. I apologize.
Pat, I am at the Patrick Walsh Twitter Vine Instagram. I also recently did a second appearance
on an extremely funny podcast called Hollywood Handbook with Sean Clemens and Hayes Davenport
a couple good friends of mine. It's just a very funny improv show. You go in. The premise of
of the podcast is you're a Hollywood douchebag. And it's supposed to be like the worst conversation
you would hear at like a Hollywood Starbucks. And it's very fun at a good time. They are
critically acclaimed, but they were talking about how they don't have a lot of listeners.
Give it a listen. You like you like us? You might like them. If you want to listen, I'm
on the one called ShareRunner's panel. That's it. You've been listening. We'll see you
in hell presentation of the Fanguaria podcast network produced by Thomas DeFail, executive
to produce by Ken Hanley of Fangoria Entertainment.
For press opportunities, advertising inquiries and information about what we'll see you in
Hill Contact Ken.
His email is KenatFangoria .com.
See you later.