Summer is here and Bed MDM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer or check out
our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz.
Only available at Bed MDM Casino.
Spin on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 fortunes, Mystery of the Lamp,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand.
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action.
Bet MGM game sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 plus to Wager, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania, and West Virginia
only.
Games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as normal, durable site credit slash bonus bets unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
The football season is full of guarantees, and here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October, if
your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning or winning money back in fan
cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
Winning hits different here.
Must be 21 plus, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gampler, offer not available in all states
terms apply, see Fanatic Sportsbook app.
This is a head gum podcast.
Howdy, Helens. Welcome to another episode of We'll See You In Hell. Over there is my dear friend, Patrick Walsh.
Oh. You had me with the dear friend, but this sarcastic tone kind of turned me off a little bit.
No, I was doing like ladies and gentlemen in here in beautiful Hollywood.
Okay. Alright, then I'm fine with it.
Remember that kind of an answer?
I do. I do.
From back in the days the golden days of this tinsel town. Yes
How are you Joe?
I'm okay. My mood is all over the place anymore. I don't know if I'm coming or going but
For the most part, I guess I'm fine. I just did a show
How did it go? It went well, but my heart is not in any of my material right everything I have in my act
I don't feel like doing and I have to go do shows all weekend
No, I just did shows all weekend.
Why don't you bring back the hits?
Cause I can't remember who I am.
For a squeaky wheel, I can't remember who I am.
The guy says he's got 15 items.
He's in there with 22, that kind of stuff.
Yeah, wait, what is this?
15, say that again.
Don't you do a bit about how people say
they're gonna have 15 items in the 15 item or less land,
but then they have 20.
And then about how you always get the car
with the squeaky wheel that veers you off with.
Oh, my super market rancor, super market chunk.
Yeah, yeah, that's, that's good stuff.
Yeah.
That's good stuff.
I do.
White hot dogs coming packs of eight and bones coming packs
at 10.
That kind of stuff.
Yep.
Don't forget the generic cereals routine.
Sure.
Uh, you know, that's like sucky charms.
Yeah.
I believe it's your closer now, which I thought was balsy because it's, it's funny.
but, you know, well, I do it with that big four -leaf clover with the slash through it projection
behind me. And the Irish don't take well to that. Take your take kindly to that.
You were a pioneer in the field of stand -up comedy with the overhead projector in the back.
Yeah, like a chemistry teaching. Literal overhead. I project things onto the ceiling.
Yes. It's like a planetarium style comedy show.
And you have not yet taken my joke pitch of saying when a joke bombs at which it does. I'm sorry
Yeah, I'm afraid of saying oh, I guess that joke was over your your head
And then parentheses projector
I
Think that should be your closer personally
I'll try maybe I maybe I'll try it this weekend meeting Pittsburgh
Which are the shows that when the listeners are hearing that are the ones I just did yes, but physically I
I'm not there yet because we're recording this before.
But maybe I'll give that a shot in Pittsburgh.
Over, and then your hair has to be kind of low.
Over your head projector.
And then the parentheses have to go around projector.
But deliver it in like a sort of like a,
like a reader, rudder.
Yes.
Like throwing that last word away.
Right, exactly.
Over your head projector.
Yeah, that kind of thing.
I got you.
Wendy Liebman really more is the master of that.
style. I guess, again, I guess, the sort of that as well.
Huh?
Gaffigan does a little of that as well, but with the little whisper at the end.
Yeah, but I'm not, I'm saying more the, the like, when you've been like subliminal
man, like Kevin Neal and, yeah, exactly. When somebody goes, you know, I was, I was really
held under water, you know, I mean, he's sort of like the funny word in at the end. Yeah.
That was Wendy Leibman's thing. She was, very funny. She was very good at that. I mean,
she still is. She didn't die or anything. I tell you, I love Kevin stand and I love Kevin
sitting but Kevin Neal has never done it for me. Folks, that's the closer than when that
gets in the laugh. I go, I guess it went over your heads. Projector. Folks, Joe, we're here
this week to talk about Colt of Chucky and we'll get to it. But you know, I tell you, I've
really digging around the old forums, the old Facebook forums, and I think people genuinely
enjoy when we kind of don't talk about the movie at all.
And then, you know, your, your dorks get all angry about Blade Runner.
You're opinion is stupid, whatever it's like.
Okay.
All right.
Yeah.
I guess I'll give you a minute.
Do they present an argument as to why it's stupid, though?
Yeah.
Because every single person that told me they liked it, when I was like, here's why I thought
it sucked.
A, B, C, D. They were like, well, yeah, all right. I mean, I don't know. You know, nobody
was able to say, no, you're wrong because this is actually that. And you don't understand.
Well, if you're looking for an entertaining movie, then yeah, I guess you wouldn't like
Blade Runner. Yeah. So, um, but my favorite thing that I discovered this week in the Facebook
page, and I will say by and large, it is, it is a very supportive, friendly community as
well, which I really appreciate, as always, my favorite things are when you guys post
quote chains from the archives. I love it. I love, you know, me too. You know, sometimes
we're, we're not always there during them. It's frankly, it's nice to hear what we said.
We're not always mentally present. You know what I'm saying? I've never listened to one
day in my episode of this. I find that crazy. And I've been asking you, I want to hear this
Patreon. And those of you who have signed up for our Patreon, which is at patreon .com slash
WS I no WS why I H POD. Where's the POD come from? What? We're also a POD fan site for the fan POD.
WS why I H was right. We'll see you in hell pot. All right. That makes sense. What was POD's big hit?
you're asking the wrong guy they had a huge hit you're asking the wrong guy
now if you want to dig into some better than Ezra yeah was POD a metal band POD
was that that same kind of shitty like like disturbed you know like no they
weren't that hard there were more like a pop a roach I'll find it so someone did
point out Julia Pevelina that the game we were playing was called secret Hitler
She's correct. Yes. I couldn't remember it the other day. I said fascist versus monkeys or something
Another guy said Ed Mosquitz. He loves cult of Chuckie
I think we might disagree with you. You'll find out but what I want to most call attention to
Is if you haven't been to the Facebook page go there. We'll see you in hell
So it's our only fan page. It's got a really nice following and
And a gentleman by the name of a rod dot, which I guess could be his actual name. I don't know.
Is it the baseball player a rod? No.
A -R -O -D dot. If it is your name, it's an awesome one. If it's an abbreviation, I'm sorry. I can't give you credit for your actual name.
He I guess painted I don't paint it or at least drew me and Joe like in an in an action horror movie poster. Yeah, we'll see you in hell. It says we'll see you in hell with Joe to
Rosen Patrick Walsh. It's got our logo designed by Joe the devil with. No, I didn't design it. Oh, an artist at Fangoria or that was commissioned by Fangoria design that and then I said,
Can you put 3D glasses on it so okay? So it's got a movie thing so I put that little touch in right if it was
The writer's guild they'd have to give me a credit on it. Yeah
Well
Anyway, I don't know if you if you got close on this thing Joe
But me and Joe were flipping out over this one. I saw this weekend. You see all the you know leather face coming after us
It's all that in the background. I mean it's an just an incredible
painting. And I urge you to check it out. We're gonna post it on our social media. But it's incredible.
Thank you so much. I was very impressed by that. There's a lot of people requesting it on a
t -shirt. We'll get there and people will be compensated as need be, etc. But thank you, sir.
Thank you so much. It's a very nice A -Rodum assuming is a mail name, right? Yes. It's a very, very
cool painting. That's nice when the fans do something like that. Your buddy did that song like
the remake of the library and re -recorded the theme, which is a Jonerosa Ridge. I did write the theme,
but you were singing it and I asked that you put on 3D glasses so I kind of have some credit on
the song as well. I won't give it to you. But sure. You never said on with the Joe, I don't know if
that matters. But you don't know if it matters. I think you want to estimate why people
listen to the show. And why people listen. It would arrive, but I couldn't fuck it up.
Sorry. Here we go. Now that we've finished this 20 minute intro, let's get on with the
show and also on who is a very classic one and then in a sound effect little new little old
exploded at the end yeah it's like a force awakens old little new uh I got this letter in the
mail today tell me I get clearing house two pieces of mail today that first is from 21st century
audio, audio insurance, who I'm not with. They're trying to bring you over to the, uh,
20 ,000. Yeah, I, you know, I met, I'm gonna bring you into the 21st century. Yeah.
Sure and style. I met with them and they passed.
It also wasn't a safe bet. So it's, you know, it's one of these things where you get the letter that
says you could save more money if you were with us. It says out of 23 million, 753 ,441 drivers in
in California, Joe DeRosa is one who qualified.
Now, this, that went out to everybody.
Of course, yeah.
So, but I read it for just to set up the next thing.
This is the kind of despicable bullshit,
you know, scam mail and everything that you get.
And, you know, it's, it's you read it and you got really,
you know what I mean?
It's like when you're walking through the mall
and the guy with the steamer is like,
hey man, I'm willing to give you a discount today.
Like just me right well. Thank you. It must be my lucky steamer day, you know, so anyway
So but you expect that from a you know a bullshit run of the middle company
I get this big manila envelope
It's got like red writing on it and shit the goddamn thing looks classified. It says don't do not bend mm -hmm
Look at the fuck is this I
Open it from Easter seals
Okay.
It's a calendar.
It's like a charity, right?
Mm -hmm.
Okay.
For kids.
Good charity.
I give to a couple kids' charities.
I'm not saying I have to pat myself on the back.
I'm saying that so I don't come off like a guy that scoffs at children's charity.
Sure.
Uh, so I open it's a calendar, which is why it's a do -not -bend, and I'm like, okay.
Wait, can't bend a calendar?
I don't know.
That's not really the point.
Here's the point.
You ready for this?
Yeah.
It's a calendar I didn't request or anything, obviously.
Right.
They just sent it to me and it's every day to Easter or do they?
No open it up to other day. This is for seals that don't understand when Easter is happening
It's to educate seals about Easter the rebirth of Christ all right and please don't send us hate comments
It's a I'm joking. I know it's a children's charity for disabled children. It's a nice thing. They're doing but I already give to two other ones sure and I'm not part of this one
and I get that they're trying to recruit people in,
but I don't like how they do it.
Ready for this?
Here's the letter.
Dear Mr. Derosa, people said we were taking,
ready? Underlined.
A big risk by sending out beautiful calendars.
Oh wow.
Underlined again.
For free.
They said it would never work.
While people would surely keep their calendars
and enjoy them throughout the coming year, we'd never hear back from them again. Then it goes into
bold and underline, but I have so much faith in this program and in folks like you, we're going
ahead anyway. Wow. These are my grandma's guilt tactics here. This bugs me. It's like don't
Easter seals. You're supposed to be better than 21st century auto insurance. Yeah. Don't do this.
Yeah, don't don't give me this fucking rub. This is bullshit
It's like it nobody ever said any of that. I don't know what state you have to make it a big mistake, Maria
You can't give people calendars. They'll just enjoy them. By the way, this is what the calendar is every month
There's a picture of a flower every month. It's not a great calendar. So Easter I guess, you know, Easter's bloom and whatever so you got fun
There's it who what what where what state is your life in that you get a flower calendar in the mail and you're rubbing your hands
Gotta like I'm gonna get one over on the on hand a charity for disabled children. Yeah, nobody is saying that nobody is
Nobody's going suckers. I'm gonna have a great time with this thing
Me and my flower calendar are going to Atlantic City
But your new dress flower calendar just fucking a flower calendar on the sofa pants around your ankles
Yeah, you give it a you give it a diamond necklace and one of those big blue velvet boxes
Hey, I was thinking more like a pearl necklace folks
Talking about coming on the neck of a flower so that that that bothers me that don't don't give me come on me
I hear you. Stop. I hear you. Stop. Shoot me straight. You're charity. You're trying to help kids shoot a straight. I
Not long ago
Received from my alma mater Webster University in Missouri
Actually owned and run by
Webster by Emanuel Lewis. Yes, you portrayed Webster
Well, that's why they named the show that yeah, yeah, I know
It was a you know, there's a guy on the cover kind of a side show Bob looking guy a hip
hip -young guy and then it says help us plant a seed in children across America and just kind
of this guy standing there smirking at you help me plant a seed in the children of America kind
of a thing right I just I couldn't believe it there's a there's no there's no quality control anymore
No, there's nine.
There's things getting thrown out.
Like somebody should look at this, go.
You sure plant a seed in children?
I think we should probably rewrite them.
Yeah.
That's what I've got.
Oh, it went out.
It's, it's great.
I know, I have a problem with the wording of all these things.
Yeah.
Uh, you know, when you go to the supermarket, it says, you know,
or you get a lot of your material.
Well, this is, yeah, this is, I got the whole routine
and I like to go and I, I'll do it while I'm in line.
If the clerk's laugh, I know it's good.
Yeah, because they're hearing this stuff all day.
Sure.
Well, if you pay with your credit card or your debit card or whatever, most supermarkets
now it'll say, would you like to donate $1 .5 or $10 or whatever it is?
Do it every time.
I never do it because I donated another place.
I don't trust something that far removed from the actual source.
Yeah, that's probably fair.
That's just me.
Yeah, but like
And also ever since defending your life where rip torn told Albert Brooks like you don't get any credit for the people you gave to in the street
Uh -huh. I'm like let me make sure I give right to the to the main place. Sure. Anyway
But it'll ask you to donate that that was a comedy though, right?
Right. Yes
Okay
And here's what bothers me about the wording when they ask you for the money
they say, would you like to donate a dollar to end world hunger? Right. It will never end. No.
No. To me, that's a sales tactic. That's a pressure sale. If you're not giving money, world hunger
will continue. World hunger will continue no matter what people do. It will never end. It will always
be a horrible, horrible problem. So I'm not saying don't give, but don't say it to me like that.
Well, you're trying to now get me into a guilty place that if I don't give the money
I'm somehow part of the fucking problem right now
But isn't a big part of the of any charity asking especially the people outside of a grocery store per say guilt
It's really all they have
I gotta tell you I never had a problem with the Sally Struthers technique showing you sick kid or well
The the the the the the of course the footage is always very upsetting right it's very sad
But like I never had a problem with somebody just saying to me like look man, here's all we need
We need 65 cents a day. It's the price of a cup of coffee. This is what that will do. That's the best tactic
That's a just straight. It's like here you go, right, you know
I give to the journalists of St. Jude's Hospital. Yeah
Because it's very straightforward. They're like look. Here's what we do
We provide free care for kids that have cancer. No child will ever have to pay
Well, if they're family, we'll never have to be pretty harsh if they were like,
fork it over, kid.
You know, but they're like, no family ever have to pay if they're kids here.
We want to, these kids are in terrible condition and like we want to help them.
And could you give?
Here's what we could use, but anything helps.
It's like, yeah, thank you.
You're being honest with me.
I would like to give to this charity.
Yeah.
I don't like, once, once tricky language and all that stuff starts coming in, then I start
getting into that head space of like, also they never tell you at the supermarket, a dollar
to end -world hunger. Who? Who's it going to? They never tell you the name of the organization.
Yeah, I've done it every time I've gone to the grocery store, but now you have me thinking
I shouldn't. They've never once said the organization on the little machine. It just says do you
want to give money. And it's like, maybe it's going to the guy working by in the place so
you can buy himself a lunch and he just kind of sets it up.
Yeah, I also love that wrap too.
Like all these supermarkets are collecting money
to end -world hunger.
Meanwhile, I've never been to a supermarket
where there wasn't a homeless guy out front starving.
Sure.
It's like maybe you walk outside and give that guy a dollar.
Maybe you give that guy five bucks.
Yeah.
You know, it's all just, something's fishy to me
about the way some of these charities operate.
And I don't like it.
I hear it.
And then that's common knowledge that a lot of these nonprofits
Profits just none of the money gets to the cause and all that shit. Oh, you mean it goes to the CEOs have a lot of money. Yeah, whatever it is
Yeah, I mean, I don't know it be charitable folks. Yeah, be charitable. Just, you know, I'm not saying don't
I'm just saying you know be charitable. Hey, I agree
Patty. Yeah. You got anything for the movie corner? I mean, we just recorded two days
ago. And we recorded two this and the bonus Patreon, which I meant to say earlier drops
on Halloween, October 31st. Yeah, we're going to put the Patreon, the bonus episode out
on the last day of every month. Just coincidentally, this month that happens to be Halloween, how
appropriate. But it'll go on the last day of every month because I'm not exactly sure
how Patreon works yet. And I want to make sure that if you donate, I don't want to put it up,
and then if you donate after you don't get the episode. So last day of the month, it'll go up.
It's already recorded. It's the topic is Pat and me discussing our favorite horror film.
I discuss my favorite and he discusses his favorite. It's a very long episode. It's about an hour
and ten minutes. So you get you get a little extra for the money and we can't thank you enough
for the donations. Seriously. If you want to hear Joe talk about Jack Frost and me talk
about Uncle Sam, that's the pot. We only like horror movies with the hologram cover on
the VHS. Right. And not the Michael Keaton Jack Frost, which was scary enough. I didn't
really see anything I went to see Depeche mode last night okay and how was that
well I'll tell you I I guess I thought I loved Depeche mode until I was
staring down an hour of new material now yeah you can't you gotta get out of
that now they didn't even fucking play policy of truth one of their best songs
they didn't, which a song until I was 31,
I thought the chorus was Colosseum Truth.
Like in the Colosseum Truth.
Wow.
So they skipped policy of truth.
Tell me they gave you a straight up personal Jesus
and not some horseshit like broken down version or something.
No, they did personal Jesus, they did enjoy the silence,
which is an amazing song.
And you know, other ones.
a great loss to Peshmo track is never let me down again. That's a fantastic song.
They do the lawn chair song. What's that? One where the guys walking around the chair,
the whole video. All I ever wanted. Only have a need. And as you hear in my, that's enjoy the
silence. Oh, it is. Yeah. Okay. Words are very unnecessary. And the lead singer, you know,
him and the end this co lead singer, they look very fit but very old. And this guy looks like
a more depraved perverted John Waters. He's got the pencil, the pencil thin mustache and he's
up there in like all leather. And it is a creepy look that honestly may have hindered my enjoyment
of the show. And then his co -singer looks like flea. If flea had been, I mean, I don't even know
what to say had been through a really traumatic like a year being tortured kind of experience.
And I'm just going to go out and live and say this flea is not a great look at me. No, but I mean,
when they're up there singing and like on that giant bowl screen, I was like, whoo. And I mean,
I mean, look, I've seen Jeff Lynn on that screen
and he looked better.
I don't think Jeff Lynn is a bad looking dude.
He looks kind of like somebody who'd play
in the electric mayhem, the Muppet Band.
I agree with that.
I always feel like he looked like a dog
that has turned into a man, his dream.
The dog dream came true one day and he became a boy.
Yeah, exactly.
But I don't think he's like, if I saw him,
I would just be like, who's this guy's dad that's over here?
Right.
He looks like a 70s dad.
Yes, exactly
But yeah, DePesh mode which which doesn't count as seeing something, but I saw them and I also
I've been lightly enjoying the new season of curved there. They're scattered laughs
It's always entertaining and better than most things on television. So I can't criticize it too harshly
It's not it's not the classics, but I'm enjoying myself. All right fair enough. I tried to watch the film
society. What's that? That's a horror movie I've heard about a
zillion times. We should do Raw by the way on Netflix. I hear
that's okay. Insanely intense. Cannibal movie. Alright. So
anyway, I saw society. I kind of have paid attention to it.
That's why I tried to watch it. It's, you know, it's it's
It's okay. It's just a movie. I've seen a zillion times at Amoeba. I've seen the cover.
I've heard about it. And then I saw it on Amazon Prime the other night and I was like,
oh, that's cover I always see. What is this? Who's that? Nobody that I would know their name.
And then I looked at the description and it said not for the faint of heart or the week in the
stomach or something. So I was like, all right, let me check this out. That's about a kid who
things his family doesn't get him and doesn't accept him. Everything's kind of strange and
he thinks something's up. There's maybe some big plot. Everybody's telling him he's paranoid,
then of course eventually he realizes family. And everybody in the high society where he lives,
these sort of elite, like one percent or types are actually these, this sort of big like
conjeeling alien monstrous thing that wants to eat him, I guess.
Yes. So I thought that that aspect of it was cool. I thought it, you know, it's from 91 or 92.
I thought it was an interesting commentary on the elite. Yeah.
And I did like that there was the aspect that that they all sort of would come together
in this blob, is disgusting blob creature. I like that that was a factor in it too. But it
It just wasn't a great movie.
It was just kind of boring and it took a,
it was a real slow burn and it had a lot of bad acting
and then it would have great acting.
It was very confusing.
There'd be scenes where I was like,
wow, that was so well directed and so well acted.
Then I'll go to the next scene and I'll be like,
is this a different director and cast?
Like what the fuck is going on?
So whatever, and I know that's a negative apologies,
but I do have a positive.
I also on Amazon, I started watching the nightmare world of HG Wells, which is why the nightmare world of HG Wells, it's an anthology series that came out this, I guess in this, I think this year in Britain.
It's got, it's only four episodes the first season, but it's got, who's the guy from Mr. Belvedere?
It's got Mr. Belvedere.
That's one of the episodes.
It's just an episode of Mr. Belvedere.
The guy from, he was in Crystal Skull and he's in Sexy Beast.
Ben Kingsley.
No, no, no.
But Indiana Jones is like sidekick in Crystal Skull.
Ray Winston.
Yeah.
He plays HG Wells.
Okay.
And he hosts it and sort of narrates it throughout the entire episode.
And I watched the first episode and I fucking loved it.
The guy, it was about this old man, the guy that plays Dumbledore in the Harry Potter
movies plays.
And I called GamBomb.
Yeah.
Well, two guys played Dumbledore, actually.
Well, the second, the guy that played it him mostly.
So he plays this old man who's dying and he goes to a very young, viral man who's brilliant
and a medical student, and has no money.
And he says, basically, like, I don't know if you know me,
but I'm this famed philosopher.
And they're all shot, which I thought was cool,
in the period that they were written in.
So the whole, that makes it very moody
when it all kind of has that like sort of a Christmas Carol
kind of vibe to it, you know?
Anyway, he goes to this kid and he says,
look, I'm this famed philosopher, the kid knows who he is.
He's like, I love your work.
He goes, I'm dying.
I don't have long on this earth. I need an heir to my fortune. I'm interviewing three
people. You'd be the third that I think are worthy of my legacy. The one stipulation is you have
to change your name to my name. That's, I mean, the kids like, okay, the kid gets the gig. They go
out to celebrate. The guy drugs him. The kid wakes up the next morning. He's in the old man's body.
the old man is now in his body, and then he's got to figure out how to get back to his
own body.
And this is, I'm going to ruin the ending, but he goes to arrest him.
Well, maybe don't because maybe we won't check out the show.
Well, then go check it out.
I really liked it.
I really enjoyed it.
I'm very fond of it.
I found it on Amazon Prime.
The nightmare world, it might be worlds of HG Wells, check that out.
And I guess we can move on to Joe's scary stuff, yeah?
sure. Quick one this week. Video game. I'm just gonna kind of stick on this
video game track I've been on. I got the game. Did I talk about butcher yet on
the show? Video game butcher which was also advertised on bloody
disgusting today and I've had the game for a while. I should have talked about it
sooner. Very fun game, super hard, super violent. I got it on the Nintendo Switch. It's also available on
Steam. You play a tiny, tiny man with a gigantic gun and you run through very alien -esque, meaning
the film alien -esque worlds, blowing people to pieces, cutting them up with chainsaws, making them
splattering to blood against the wall.
That's basically it.
It's just an insanely violent, futuristic,
alien, weirdo game.
It's very fun.
Okay.
Butcher.
All right.
And we're at minute 31.
So I guess we can just get to the movie.
We're not even asking if I have anything for Scarif's side.
Oh, I didn't want.
I'm sorry.
I assumed you didn't.
I apologize.
But I finally did it right for the first time on the last one.
Yeah, even though it was what a repeat wound up being a really okay. What do you got? I don't have anything
Cult of Chuckie
Cult of Chuckie C. O C now first off can I say something real quick?
Please I don't mean to cut you off
I'd like to tell the audience about the brief heart to heart. We had in the bar last week
What was this? I don't know if you remember it. I'm sure I remember it. We were pretty deep in at this point
We had our remember a spirited discussion about Manchester by the sea which I rewatched and fucking loved and was thrilled to know you love as well because many hated it
We we were we had recorded two episodes. We had drank a
Considerable amount. We'd had something drink. We went to another bar. We drank there
We went to a third or second bar. We went there. We drank there Vince showed up. Yeah, then we're drinking with Vince
before Vince showed up, we were talking about the podcast.
We had a very, very sweet moment where you said,
Joe, I just love you, you know?
So that's one of the podcasts we disagreed usually
in the old days we'd go at each other
and so I didn't even want to do it
because I love you so much.
It's a patty, I felt the same damn thing.
I didn't want to insult you.
It was a really beautiful, beautiful moment.
Well, very brief though.
Yeah, I think that there's an element of people missing our fighting, but I don't, I don't either.
I think the world has become so horrible that why would you want to fight with a dear friend?
I agree.
Well, we always argue about movies and shit, but yeah, don't see the need.
Joe, what is your history with the entire child's play franchise?
I created the characters.
Oh.
I wrote the first three films.
I mean, I think you'd be doing better, frankly.
They, I signed a bad deal.
I signed a shoddy contract.
Like most wide -eyed do's do when they come to this town.
Right.
No, my history is when I, when I was a kid, I saw the, I got to be honest.
When the first one came out, I, there was not a movie I probably was more eager to
see.
I was about 12 years old when it came out, you know, I liked horror movies, they're like,
here's a horror movie about a doll that murders people.
I was just like, sign me, the fuck up.
Right.
The trailer had the, had the, had the shot of the babysitter being thrown out the window
and falling.
Yeah.
And it was like a real stunt lady falling through the sky.
Like, I feel like 12 was the perfect age for the Chuckie franchise.
Yeah.
It was, it was a great age.
So I couldn't wait to see it and, uh, I got to tell you, when I, when I started thinking
back on the franchise this week, because I knew we're going to do this, I remember seeing
it and thinking it was pretty good.
Yeah.
I wasn't blown away it certainly didn't hit me the way nightmare in Elm Street did I like Tom Holland quite a bit
Yeah, I like Don I think Don Mancini is the guy that writes and directs them. Yeah, I've written all of them
I liked them both quite a bit. I like their work, but um, I
Just remember just kind of being like yeah, it was pretty cool. I guess
But I liked it enough that I wanted to see the sequels when I was younger parts two and three I
I loved because they were just non -stop like Kills sure and there was no build -up to when's the dog gonna turn evil
It was just like it's it's an evil from the beginning and it just kills everybody
You like a simple film
Well, Halloween two was 14 to yeah, you know, at that point
I also remember this too. I didn't like the detail in the first film when I was a kid that it was a serial killer
who possessed the doll.
I wanted it just to be a haunted doll,
like an Annabelle kind of thing,
which also is basically a serial killer,
the possessor of the, but as a kid,
I wanted it to be like the devil doll or so,
you know what I mean?
Yeah.
So anyway, I watched two and three as a kid.
I really liked them when I got older.
I didn't hold my attention as much.
four and five, which were bright and seed of Chuckie,
I was out, I didn't care for them going meta,
I didn't care for the comedic aspect,
but when they announced Curse of Chuckie,
which is part six, and they said it's going back too hard,
it's going back to scares and whatever, I was very excited.
Now let me quickly catch up to where you're at,
because I don't even know what Curse of Chuckie is,
is I didn't know it existed.
Child's play one and two,
somebody started at a slumber party
when I was 13, I left the damn room.
As I've said before, I was a pusher.
I watched one and two pretty recently.
One is a good little thriller, I think.
Yeah, it's good.
Now that I'm older, I like one quite a bit.
Well, man, it's got a good sense of humor and I like it.
Two, pretty empty, pretty hollow, pretty, it was fine.
and then three at the, what is it, military camp?
Yeah.
Fine, you know.
Bride, watch with some friends, pretty stupid, you know?
Yeah, it's done.
Seed, who portrays the seed of Chuckie?
If they have a kid, who's the voice?
I don't know, it's like in English,
for some reason he's got an English accent.
I don't fucking know, I was out with C.
I think Curse is before Colt.
Yeah, so tell me about Curse.
Well, Curse?
I've never seen Cedar Curse.
Curse is great.
All right.
Curse is the, in my opinion, without question,
next to number one, the best of the franchise.
I mean, it's...
Why have I never even heard of it?
The actual release?
No, because it was a directive video.
Yeah.
And, you know, I think a lot of people had tuned out
at that point because they thought
they'd just become a comedy series.
Right.
it. What's the print? What's the gist? Fiona Dorif, who's Brad Dorif's daughter, she plays,
I forget her name in the movie, but she plays this girl in a wheelchair who lives in a house,
and her, can I quickly ask, is Fiona Dorif in a wheelchair? Not in real life. Okay, just in the movie.
So she plays a girl in the wheelchair in a house, her mother, who was very overprotective
of her and shelters her, dies.
Her family comes to stay with her to console her, and the chucky doll shows up, and shit
starts going bad shit, and in the end of the movie, she basically gets blamed for it, the
authorities think she killed everybody in the house.
right so it's a you know it's an intense it's an intense you know one
location thriller much like the first one yes it's about somebody trying to
convince everybody else they're not crazy and that this doll is alive like the
first one and there's just cool twist there's cool knots the whole franchise
like just when you're like wait a minute how come Chuckie's face looks fine when
in the last two movies it was all like stitched up and everything. So do they kill him and
he ends up in like the box with just his head that starts cursive Chuckie? I mean that
cult of Chuckie? Well hold on, let me finish with curse first. You know through the movie
he looks strangely, his face looks strangely perfect. It did in this one too. And it's odd
and you're like kind of like throughout the movie you're like why does it look like that?
right and also in the last two movies he had stitches in his face like are they just ignoring those
movies I guess I don't know yeah and then toward the end of the movie he he takes like putty off his
face and you realize it was a disguise and his face looks like Chuck E from the they just did really cool
little nods like that you know like Jennifer Tilly shows up at the very end and and gets the dollback
and then she mails it to this strange address at the end of the film and then
at the end of the film, you realize the address she mailed it to is Andy Barclay
who's the kid from the first two movies. They brought back the actor from the first
two movies because he was replaced in the third film. It did a very good job of
getting it all back on track, bringing it back down to earth, showing that this doll
has this vendetta against this kid. He still wants to get to him. He's going to get to him however he
asks to. And it was scary and intense and fun. And they also didn't have Chuckie making jokes every
five fucking minutes. That being said, I was immensely excited for Cult of Chuckie because I thought, okay,
here we go. We're off and running. I've heard from many people that it's great. Curse or cult. I don't
I don't agree.
By the way, I think it's very, very stupid in this day and age to name a two sequels
in a row curse and cult because you might not even know there's a new one.
You might be like, oh, I saw that one.
Yeah.
It's a little tough.
The new one I felt just as an overall to begin with, yeah.
I felt that they basically negated every good thing they did in Curse of Chucky.
they made Chuckie a complete wisecracking like jokester again was curse well received or
poorly received that would have led them to go back to the other was well received enough
that they got funding to do another one right I mean it couldn't have been that this one
had a limited theatrical release well and cult is a great looking movie considering that it
couldn't have cost more than a couple million dollars yeah look it was shot incredibly well
on a low budget.
It's shot very well.
Great shots on it.
And it's acted well.
Yes.
It's not.
It's too hokey.
It's too goofy.
Yeah.
And it makes no goddamn sense.
And like, you know, it's like.
It really made no sense.
It makes zero sense.
Yeah.
And I mean, it gets to a point in the writing.
So for those of you that don't know, the reason it's called Cult of Chuckie, and this is
a reveal later in the film.
And look, I don't think this movie is good enough to avoid spoilers.
I'm sorry.
Everybody's gotten Netflix if we're doing a Netflix instant title you can always watch it before we start
Right, I think that so the reveal late in the in the game is that
Chuckie has figured out a way
Several Chuckie dolls are showing up at this mental institution that Fiona Dorif has been committed to
It doesn't make any sense that they send her to this thing because they believe she's a mass murderer
then you find out later the only reason she's there is because her doctor is basically hypnotizing her
and then fucking her which is a weird dark twist that just doesn't need to be in there like I don't
really get that but whatever I guess I guess you I guess you need a you need a device to get her there
so if that's the device fine so now when he kisses her that that to me was the only thing I saw
that indicated something untoward was happening that's like that just was a suggestion that there
was a lot more going on.
Well, he says like, I always enjoy
these little private sessions.
And I was like, no, he hypnotizes her
and then I guess he has sex with her or something.
Like, yeah, why does that?
Why do we need to do that to the hair when I'm the film?
It's needlessly creepy.
It reduces her character.
It's like, but also too, I can live with it
if you're saying there's, we need a way
for the doctor to get her here.
I think it'd be much cooler if the doctor believed
in her in some way and brought her there,
which is what he tells his bosses.
Right.
That's how he gets her there.
I think it's much cooler if that was true,
and the one person that believes in her gets killed.
Instead, it's everybody's against her
and everybody thinks she's crazy until it's too late.
So, whatever.
But it's called cult of Chucky,
because a bunch of different dolls show up,
and then you realize Chucky has figured out a way
to put his Charles Lee Ray, the killer,
has figured out a way to put himself,
or his essence into several different bodies at once.
For some reason, he's choosing to only do this
with more dolls.
I don't know why.
He's not just putting himself into people,
which is his whole goal in the first three fucking movies.
It's to just get into Andy Barclay's body,
so he doesn't have to be in a goddamn doll anymore,
but he decides instead to do this very convoluted plan
of putting himself into several doll bodies,
Yeah, and then going after not Andy Barclay, but but Fiona Dorf's character so
But Andy Barclay's in it. He is in it. Yeah, for some reason
Well, he's got the head of the dial from Cult of Chuckie. Yeah, or from Curse of Chuckie
Now did he get that in Curse of Chuckie? He gets it into the end of Curse of Chuckie
That I enjoyed when he's like giving a joint to Chuckie and they're like fighting. I liked all that show
I thought that was very cool. Yeah
I don't know. I don't get it. They never really explained like, I mean, I'm sorry, like I'm
not trying to shit on Don Mancini, but it gets to a point with the writing where it's like,
dude, how long do you think about this for 10 seconds? Like Chuck, he actually says at one point,
he goes, thanks to a spell I learned on voodoo .com. I can now put my spirit into every, it's like,
Really? This is the plot. Yeah, you know, at least bring in the Jamaican woman to give him a spell something
Here was my initial frustration with it. I had been looking forward to it
A because I had heard all the positive feedback
Me too and B because I was expecting it to be an actual cult right my mind either it was
Chucky running a cult
Like that people were like like wanting to fuck him and like under his spell basically. Oh, that's cool
I mean right there cult of jucky. I'm like, what a sweet idea for movie or
A cult of people because I knew that at some point
It became a new nightmare type thing where there was like Jennifer Tilly played herself right which she doesn't this one very
Confusingly or that's the fifth one. Yeah, it's that that's another confusing part. Yeah
you don't really, it was very hard to tell if Jennifer Tilly was Jennifer Tilly or if she was the
Charles Lee Ray girlfriend and then she even says at one point it's I lose track sometimes.
And then there's the whole thing where it's like
Chuck E's whole like in the end of this this is the part that made no fucking sense to me.
So at the end of the movie when all the dolls but one are dead I think it is.
Chuckie decides he's going to put his spirit into Fiona Dorif, so he does this.
She then magically can walk, that makes no sense whatsoever.
Your ability to walk has nothing to do with your personality or essence.
So that makes no fucking sense whatsoever, but suddenly she can walk fine.
And by the way, Spinn and Wheelchair her entire life
stands up immediately.
No atrophy in the leg, nothing.
Just can just walk, it's fucking ridiculous.
He decides to go into her body and you're like,
okay, well that's, he's always wanted to go into a male body.
Why is he not going, well, hey, maybe Chuckie has changed.
Okay, I'll accept it.
it, because there's a perfectly handsome young fit man that he could go into and he chooses
instead to murder him and then go into the girl's body, who's crippled, yet he knows he'll
be able to make her walk somehow.
So you go, okay, maybe Charles Lewey just wants to be a woman.
Maybe this is a take on gender and the gender discussion.
Okay.
Cool.
Then fine, I've accepted that.
But then at the end of the movie, he walks outside,
Fiona Dorif and Jennifer Tilly make out,
and then Chuckie and Fiona Dorif's body just goes,
well, that was different.
And Jennifer Tilly's like, I don't mind it.
And she's like, okay, you know what I mean?
And it's like, well, why is that part in there then?
Yeah.
To take that part out, you're gonna have him going to a woman
and then he's gonna be weird about it?
Like, it doesn't make any fucking sense.
And then the female girlfriend, the bride doll,
was in the backseat at the end for some reason.
The kid still hasn't shown up the seat of Chuckie,
and they drive off, and I'm like,
where does this even go at this point?
Chuckie just not only went into the body
of a person that goes against the type of body
he's been trying to get into for the entire series,
you want me to just swallow that on an immediate dime fine okay fine but not only
that he's also now gone into the body of the woman that everybody believes is
responsible for several murders yeah the whole reason he leaves his body in
child's play is because the police are closing in on him and he's a fucking murderer
right so he does a voodoo thing to go into a doll to hide himself thinking I'll
get out again and then I'll be free in a new body. So at the end of this thing, he finally
gets into a goddamn human body and he goes into the body of somebody that everybody thinks
is already responsible for the dial crimes. Doesn't make any fucking sense. I'm still
pros trying to process your use of the phrase. I'm expected to stop on an immediate dime. That's
But cult of Chuckie to continue my sentence from 30 minutes ago.
Sorry.
No, no, no.
I enjoyed that thoroughly.
Either Chuckie's a cult leader or Tilly, etc.
Like we're now in like the postmodern world where everyone loves the Chuckie movies.
And you a scream thing where they're like a cult and they love Chucky and they're trying to like somebody trying to act out murders in his name or whatever
Yeah, and they go this is a lot of fun that isn't there and when it opened in an asylum like so many other horror movies
I was like I don't want to even want to watch this now
But there's nothing more dreary and boring than an asylum to me. I just it's always go there. I like shutter island
I know you didn't thought careful wellness was okay. I didn't like the horror story in the asylum. I
Get tired of it. I like kukus nests
But I think when he says this is a kukus nests. They're trying to do a nod to Brad Dorif
playing Billy Babid and in
kukus nests. I
would imagine so
Which is an amazing character an amazing performance, but I'm sure Dorif is just like really guys
you're going to remind everyone that I was once nominated for best supporting actor.
And now I'm voicing part six in a doll murder franchise.
Seven.
Yeah.
But here's the thing.
I don't think Dwarf Mines.
I think he's like into these things.
Yeah.
I think he's having a good time.
He's getting paper.
But it's also too.
It's in a lot of ways.
It's his legacy, which is cool.
It's like Robert England being Freddie and whatever.
Yeah.
It doesn't mean all of it's good.
But I respect that.
But, you know, the thing is, it's also in this, it's not just in an asylum, it's in this weird,
uber, like, futuristic, modernistic fucking asylum. Like, it's, it's not, which, to me,
hurts the atmosphere of the film. It looks beautiful. But when everything is slick and gorgeous
and white and silver and chrome and it's not scary.
The environment is not scary.
It looks actually like a nice,
I remember thinking through the movie,
like this doesn't look so bad to live in this place.
Well, it seems incredibly not strict.
I mean, before you're even oriented with the setting
of the story, two of the inmates are fucking each other.
You know, I was like, they're fucking each other
in a stairwell, one of them in a wheelchair.
These are two insane people
and an orderly doesn't notice?
Then a guy with multiple personalities
who's potentially violent talks about
how his outside privileges were taking away.
Which are like, would he have outside privileges?
And then he disobeys the restriction and goes outside
and then nothing happens.
There is no repercussion for it.
There's no repercussion for anything in this film.
Everything seems to have just been thought.
But also to like Chuckie, in the first few movies,
the murders Chuckie would commit were,
there was a linear sense to, he was on a,
there was a journey he was on.
He had a goal and to get to the end goal,
or the end game rather, he had to kill people, right?
Cause that's how he rolled and I gotta get rid of this guy
so then I can get to that guy,
so then I can get to this lady,
so then I can get to that lady.
And this had none of that this said just him being like I'm just going to kill people for fun the other thing too
And chained up and then he he throws that compressed thing into the air so it shatters the glass above
Or I'm like, so is he jigsaw now?
Well, and then also a broken piece of the elaborate traps a broken piece of glass cutting a woman head off
It's like come on and then well the guy with the multiple personality
So he has one personality a day.
I know, again, I'm not watching a documentary,
but so one day he's Mark Zuckerberg the next day,
like, it's not how multiple personality works.
Like, do the, go, at least go to the Wikipedia page
of multiple personality disorder.
Well, here's the thing, I have no beef with,
if you wanna portray it in a much zanier way than what's real.
Yeah.
Yeah, but for Christ six, how about you tell your actor do a different voice for this person?
There's something different.
He's doing literally the same voice and everything for every personality.
And then he just goes, and then she just goes, oh, he goes, you know, I created a social
media site.
And then she just goes, oh, so today you're Mark Zuckerberg.
It's like, what?
Yeah.
What are you talking about?
Um, stupid.
The other part that really bothered me, another huge logic hole was when Chuck, he's
talking to the one lady who thinks nobody can see her
or whatever, and he goes, and she's,
because that morning they're in the group therapy
and she goes, Chuckie called me on the phone last night
and you like, I think she's obviously just being crazy.
And then later when she runs into Chuckie,
he's like, you're the crazy bitch I talked to on the phone.
It's like, I'm sorry, the committed woman
is answering the main phone at the asylum and then Chuckie is so sloppy that he's saying
it's Chuckie. Tell me. Hello, it's me, Chuckie, that I'm coming over there. Yeah. Why is Chuckie going
to the asylum? I don't know. Did he have a grudge against wheelchair girl? They explain in curse of Chuckie
the, um, the, her relation to the whole thing, I can't remember what her relation to the
original thing is, uh, the original story is, but there's, she's got some tie to it.
So that's kind of why she's there. And that's why Jennifer Tilly is mailing these dolls
to people because she's, she's exacting Chuckie's revenge for him or helping him do it. So there
There is a connection, I'm blanking on what it was, so I guess his bloodlust will always
outweigh his rationale or his logic or just the fact that he apparently can jump into
any fucking body he wants.
So go jump into Tom Cruise's body or something, like watch, I don't get it.
And why was she breastfeeding him and then killed him?
She didn't kill him.
Oh, because she killed her baby.
She put a pillow over him.
Because she killed her baby.
That's why she was in there.
No, I know.
I got that.
But then she's breastfeeding him and then killing him.
And then it opens up her actual real dark drama of why she killed her own baby.
Yes.
With like 10 minutes to spare in the movie.
This is what we're doing.
No, it was a little earlier than that I'll be fair, but it's it wasn't look it's I'm not saying it was good writing
I did like when Chuckie said he got to suck on a titty
Yeah, I mean yeah, I guess so you know, I mean look it's it's a it's a it's a bad movie
I mean I think in addition to me not wanting to fight with Joe
We find ourselves agreeing on everything because everything is very bad
I'll tell you, dude, I'm terrified because you know how much I love Star Wars, and I got
to tell you, I can't remember the last time I've seen anything that came even remotely
from Hollywood.
Forget about the big budget shit.
I was watching that inner that clip with Thor today, while Chris Hemsworth on, he was
on some like Australian talk show promoting Thor Ragnarok.
And so they first of all, they show a clip from the movie and it's him in the Hulk in
the clip and he's talking to two other like Asgard warriors or something and he goes, I
need to assemble a team to take down the bad guy and throw a ragnarok.
And the lady, the female one goes, what are we called?
And he goes, they're revengers.
And I'm like, this is, this is like a Leslie Nielsen level joke at this point.
Fucking Marvel movies.
Yeah.
Anyway, that's not my point.
My point is, I'm excited about, well, sad is way too strong as I hate all superhero movies.
But more excited about Thorangorak because of the director who did hunt for the world
of people, which I loved, Taika, YT or whatever.
And I, you know, I like a lighter tone in this shit, but yeah, I mean, the trailer appears
to be like almost like, you know, date movie, scary movie, superhero movie.
That's what it feels like to me.
It feels like a fake cheesy bullshit.
And again, they stole from DC.
Again, they stole from DC.
The Wonder Woman theme that came in in Batman versus Superman, and then it was of course
was reprised as the main Wonder Woman theme in Wonder Woman.
And it's awesome.
And it's like this guitar riff and these drums.
It's fucking, it's awesome.
It gets you excited when you're watching Wonder Woman.
It's her music.
It sounds very Led Zeppelin.
Then, of course, the Thor Ragnarok trailer comes out.
And it's, wow.
And it's like, they just, anyway, that's not my point.
My point is this, they cut back to do the interview
for the movie. And I guess the anchor on the show fucks up because he goes. This is a huge
spoiler, people. So if you have not seen this, you don't listen if you care. He goes, uh, he goes.
So yes, wait, are you about to spoil something? Oh, yeah. Huge. Huge. From about Laura Rangeron. Yes.
Why? Because because it's such not a spoiler that it's, but it's, they acted like it was a huge
All right, well then you got to love people. No trust me. You won't care
I just said it's a huge spoiler. I don't care but people do care. I've jumped saying this is a been 36 years old
I don't care about spoilers at all and if you're into the Thor this is a spoiler. Yeah
Here comes the the the bad girl the bad guy in the movie is a woman bad woman in the movie whatever the villain
Excuse me
The guy goes I think it goes so
So this villain your sister
She's trying to kill you through the whole movie
You see a sister keeps trying to kill you and Chris Hemsworth grows.
Wow, mate, mate.
No, not cool.
You can't come on.
And it's like because that was a big reveal.
And it's like, this is your big fucking reveal.
You've been fighting your fucking brother for two movies.
Okay.
And he keeps coming the fuck back.
We can't get rid of Loki.
And now there's going to be a sister nobody's ever heard of and just shit.
It's just shit. It's shit writing. It's shit movie making and I can't
I'm so scared that I'm gonna go see the new Star Wars and be like this is just like every other god damn
Fucking thing that comes out of these movie these studios you've liked all of them
So why are you worried about because I'm worried that my that not that movies have gotten worse
But that I've gotten to a point in my life where I just can see the writing on the wall and I just can't enjoy it anymore
They did with studio stuff. Yeah, they did a very, I would say almost a stirbing
South park about this about how you stop enjoying things at a certain age and
I'll find it and send you the the links you can download or whatever, but
It was it was so depressing to me because I was like, yeah, it's true. Just like how everything just starts to suck. So it's like
It's an age old question for me. Am I old and I've seen too much stuff
So I don't like anything anymore or it's stuff worse and I think honestly it's both
But I know for a fact
Movies are worse. There's just no question about I agree. I agree now the guy who's like no movies is good as goonies
Goonies is the bet that guy's an idiot right, however
You know we're getting maybe one truly great movie a year and used to get three for a summer
I can't remember the last time I saw something put out by a studio of any kind now outside of the indie the truly indie studios
Which there are not many left
But outside of those you go and see stuff and you just go Jesus fucking Christ man and if it's not
This cookie cutter homogenized bullshit. It's some art house dickweed jerking himself off to the point where you're like
like, oh, why don't you just go paint a picture
with your own come?
You know what I mean?
Like, there's no winning.
There's no winning.
And folks, head on over to the Patreon this week
if you'd like to purchase a painting
that Joe and I made with our own come.
It's only $20, which I think is very reasonable.
Especially if you take the come and make a baby out of it.
You get sort of a half me, half Joe, half you
if you're a lady.
And if they sell out folks, don't worry. We'll keep them coming. Oh, they'll always be plenty.
I assure you, um, wrap this damn thing up. Yeah, I think if we're discussing our, our
comments time, um, folks, thank you. This is a week of thank you. The Patreon, uh, you know,
It means a lot. We talked about it on the last one. It means a lot. It's a hassle as two grown
men to get over and do this every week. But to know, we get a little change in our pockets,
it's nice. And as I was discussing the way over here, a cup of people complained about it, the price
or whatever. If you don't want it, you don't have to pay for it, folks. You're getting four free
episode a month. And if you want to confuse me, that there were a few complaints like like it's
too much for the extra episode. It's like, but it's an extra episode. Right. If you want the fifth,
then look at it like this. And you're, you're paying, you know, if it's 10 a month, you're paying
$2 a piece for them or something. Like, how about also for two and a half years, we did it with no
money. It's all been free. So yeah, I mean technically you've been getting this free forever.
It's just it's just something we got to do or else the podcast stops and we really
very much appreciate it. We do. We had a moment. I know we alluded to it on air but I don't know if
you're aware of how very close we came to packing it all in. All these ads that we've done,
Let's just let's just be real with you for all these ads that we've done thus far
Joe and I have each pocketed
Now that might be a fault of our host. I don't know
But I mean, you know, I'm just telling you we're not we're not rolling in it from this podcast
I don't really appreciate those of you dead and we're not putting any pressure on those of you didn't
But if you want that bonus episode. I'll tell you. It's a good and
And God damn it I didn't want to sit through Blade Runner 2049 true their sacrifice happened in here look
Oh folks, I got off work work today. I wanted to go directly to bed instead
I watched cult of Chuckie on my phone at the gym
So that I could do this. I never would have seen cult of Chuckie where we're doing it. We're doing it
So thank you for your support. Thank you. Thank you for the
the uh the Facebook page which is fantastic thanks for the tweets etc now do we need to do a weekly
shout out of names are we doing a monthly shout out of names do we have new I think it's oh
shit I don't know I guess buy weekly we'll do a buy wait is this the last episode of the month though
no where is one more Halloween yeah okay so then we'll do it again on Halloween to get anybody we
you might have missed the first.
Yeah, I think that's best.
We'll do every other week.
We'll announce the new names.
But yeah, guys, thank you very much.
I am on Twitter, Instagram,
at the Patrick Walsh.
My show living Biblically is more than likely
premiering in January, but I don't know.
Just trying to get that word out.
We haven't started promos yet.
You know, I'm telling you, it's a funny show.
Joe.
Joe DeRosa Comedy on Instagram come follow me please and I'll talk to you
soon. Bye -bye. That was a hit gun podcast.