I'll see you in hell.
And when the sound of your screams becomes a thing of my dreams, you know I'll say.
You know I will.
I'll see you in hell.
Folks, welcome to We'll See You in Hell.
We're here to talk to you about poor things.
And I'm not talking about my relatives, folks.
It's a little picture.
We're not talking about the women Joe has dated.
There you go.
Pat, how are you?
I'm all right.
I took a bite of one of these RX bars right before recording started.
And now, now I pay the price.
What is an RX bar?
I'm talking with my mouth full into a microphone.
It's a terrible sound, I'm sure.
I'm sorry.
What is an RX bar again?
It's one of these deals that's like three egg whites, six almonds, you know.
No BS.
I'll tell you what bothers me about the RX bars.
I do like some of them.
But some of them have like 12 grams of added sugar in them.
And you're like, that's BS.
That's not.
Some of them have, this one I just looked, has natural flavors in it, which means unnatural flavors.
Like, you can't say you have no BS.
You're full of it.
Yeah, it really bothers me.
But then some of them are hardcore, like, you know, it really is just the four things.
It's weird.
I'm tired of this no BS campaign in our culture.
There's that thing on HBO Max, because you have the one with the commercials, and Pat gave me his login.
Let's upgrade that, Pat, when we get a chance to the no commercials.
No, because I wouldn't have it otherwise.
I would not have it.
I'm paying $2 a month.
I'm doing Black Friday deals.
Although I would want to watch the end of Curb, I guess, for some reason.
We'll talk about that in a minute.
But the commercials they show a lot on HBO Max are that company, I don't know, it's some fucking food company or something.
And they're like, getting rid of the bullshit.
And they bleep it.
It's like, there's no bigger bullshit.
There's no bigger example of bullshit than a company with corporate money enough to advertise on HBO Max.
And then in their slogan where they say we're not about bullshit, they bleep the word bullshit on HBO Max.
It's like the whole thing couldn't wreak more of bullshit of, you know.
As FBoy Island.
I never understood.
It's HBO Max.
Say fuck boy.
Why are we not saying fuck boy?
What is the problem?
I talked with Nikki Glaser about this.
She doesn't know either.
Really?
Yeah.
I'd like to ask her.
I'd like to.
At a brunch.
I was just like, you know, it's called FBoy Island Fine.
Why aren't they saying fuck boy on the show, which is rated TVMA?
They say fuck, but they won't say fuck boy.
She's like, I don't know.
Probably because it's cultural appropriation.
Yet another term hijacked by the whites.
Started by the black community.
I think I was watching Barfly, which I had never seen.
I'll get to that in the movie corner, but with Mickey Rourke.
And Barfly came out in 87 and he refers to somebody as a fuck boy.
When did that term start?
I started hearing it three, four or five years ago.
It was started in black culture and I think it was in the 80s at some point.
Oh, okay.
Same as woke.
Same as, you know, a lot of things.
Honky.
Why is honky bad?
Jibass cracker was one.
Like cracker I get, it's a bland, boring white food.
What does honky mean?
I'm sure it's got something to do with like, you know, there was a time when whites would
honk their horns to, you know, do something horrible.
And then he's a honky, which meant a racist or something.
I don't know.
That's my assumption.
Yeah.
I could look it up easily.
I won't.
Is the word picnic racist?
I keep hearing that now too.
What?
Pat.
Oh, it's a, no, it says this is false.
Picnic?
Yeah.
The word picnic was used to describe festive events attended by racist whites where they
would lynch black men.
The post alleges that the word picnic itself stems from the N word.
This I'm looking at Reuters.
I think they're pretty reputable.
They're saying none of that is true, but that's something I've been hearing lately.
Where have you been hearing this in interviews for jobs?
This is usually the stuff they lead with at a job interview in LA.
So what do you think about picnic?
We want to fill you out for the writer's room.
What's your side?
And they all stare at me in the zoom.
Yeah.
To decide if they want to continue.
No, it's I've been doing a pilot with miss Pat and we just were talking about the history
of these terms and why they're bad and if they're bad and blah, blah, blah.
Somebody was saying that they had heard morning was bad.
M -O -U -R -N -I -N -G.
And I know master bedroom recently has been done away with because it comes from Slave
Times.
I'm not saying any of these are crazy.
I'm just saying I had never heard of them until recently.
And I'm kind of like I enjoy the history of words and the history of how things started,
you know.
So I don't know.
We on there's a there's a term in comedy writing called a clam.
And that means like if you if you go like I hate Joe, I just think Joe's a fucking piece
of shit.
I don't like him.
And then you go.
He's standing right behind me, isn't he?
You know, like where Joe walks up behind me.
That used to be used in every night court, every sitcom of the day.
He's standing right behind me, isn't it?
That's a clam.
So if you pitch that in a writer's room, a nice way to say, yeah, that's an old joke.
We've heard it a million times before is to say that's a client.
It's like a expression.
But I had a boss once who claimed that he and you could probably guess from my past
stories about who my bosses were.
He claimed that he invented the term.
So as in like on a sitcom when they go, yeah, well, you know, I have been studying jujitsu.
So he claims he invented that.
Oh, and that in that context, not in the like.
So you're telling me it's not going to happen.
But not not that way.
The other way.
I think he kind of claimed ownership for all the so's.
And I've seen movies where they do that prior to this man even being alive, probably.
But it's interesting, like especially in the comedy world, you'll every room will have
like an old guy, you know, an old guy who's got the experience.
I'll be that in about five years.
And it's interesting because a lot of these old guys think that they invented jokes and
they're just wrong.
I'm sure comedians do the same shit, don't they?
Like Richard Lewis thought he thought he invented the wife from hell.
And maybe he did.
But yeah, apparently he really does claim to have that wasn't just that was a storyline
because he really did claim that, which he might have.
I don't know.
But oh, I know.
Yeah.
It's just kind of so generic that although maybe it's just become part of the lexicon.
So we don't think of it.
I watched a couple of Lewis specials.
I used to love anything but love with him and Jamie Lee Curtis.
That was my intro to him.
A romantic sitcom.
But of course, I love him on curb.
And I realized that outside of seeing him maybe on Johnny Carson or something, I've
never really seen a full Richard Lewis standup set.
So I watched a couple and they were great.
Really funny.
He's awesome.
He's got he's got there's a there's a box set of three.
Yeah.
And they're all very good.
But like there's like the first one is a little too early.
The last one is a little too late.
But there's the one in the middle or whatever.
That's like, holy shit.
That's like his, you know, it's his masterpiece or whatever.
And and they're great.
And it's been nice seeing him on curb.
I was I was happy to see he was able to I was going to make a ghost joke.
He looks so much like a ghost on the show anymore.
It's I had friends over the other night.
I had friends over the other night to watch a movie and I showed them what Richard Lewis
looks like on curb because they weren't watching it.
We paused it and I felt terrible in my soul.
But then I was like, you know, Richard Lewis would love this.
He knows I'm sure went on set.
He was like, I know I look like a ghoul or whatever.
But he did some some some very last minute plastic surgery, like as he's about to go
out.
I think he did some plastic surgery.
Maybe.
Am I crazy there?
I couldn't tell if it was I couldn't know if it was that or if he was just like kind
of frozen up because of the issues he was having.
And it made his face have a tightness.
It's hard to tell.
It bums me out.
I'm glad it's nice that Larry David put him in as much as he did, because I think they
both knew we're running out of time here.
And it's nice also that Larry David was like able to make jokes about his condition
without saying you're sick or something, but being like, you know, that's not a nod.
What the hell kind of nod are you doing right now?
You didn't even move your head, you know, like stuff like that.
So I was glad to see that they had this last hurrah.
But it really does bum me out because it's like you think back to like the earlier
appearances of him and he's so he's so vibrant and like moving around and he's
every scene was him rushing in and being like, fuck you, you're a fucking asshole.
You know, and like to see him not be able to do that and they have to write around him
clearly having to stay in a chair.
You know, I'm not knocking the guy.
It's yeah, it's a it's just it's a bummer.
It's sad.
It's the end of an era and it's it makes me sad.
Yeah, his Larry David's, you know, press release about how they grew up in the same
hospital and you know, like I'd never seen Larry David when I really thought about it, be
sincere about anything.
And he was like Richard Lewis made me cry today.
I'll never forgive him for that.
And with a little joke, but I was like, man, I just even thinking about Larry David crying
made me really sad.
Yeah.
Well, and by the way, he doesn't even say cry.
He says today he made me sob.
I'm like sob.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's as human as this guy gets is a sob or his lifelong best friend died or whatever.
Yeah.
Look, the man and of course we all know this, but the man did nine or no, he didn't do nine
seasons, but he definitely laid down the template for obviously one of the greatest sitcoms
ever made my favorite ever made.
And that is a show where the motto was no hugging, no learning.
But they carried that for nine seasons.
There was never a sweet moment on side film.
Not that I can recall anyway.
There might be a moment where you're like, oh, these two are friends, but that's about
it.
Except, except, and this is one of my problems with the finale.
I know we differ here.
They did that bullshit fucking montage with the Green Day song.
Oh, fuck off guys.
That was so lame.
And then because it's not them.
It was the Golden Girls or something.
I've been like, okay.
But then when the plane's going to crash, Jerry, I've always wanted to tell you.
Oh God, guys.
Stop it.
Oh, did we always.
Oh, what does the land say?
She's, she's, she's about to think she's about to say she loves him, but she doesn't.
Yeah, clearly.
That's what it is.
And I'm like, come on guys.
Stop with this.
Yeah.
Come on.
All right.
Lay off.
Not that long of a network sitcom back then with no way that they did it.
They did something really spectacular.
You say that to network executives.
Now they're like, this moment's too mean or something.
And you're like, what about Seinfeld?
And they always say the same thing.
You can't use Seinfeld as an example, no matter who you're talking to.
Why it's like they hated.
I think what executives must just hate for years.
Whenever they say this moment is too dark, the writer always goes, what about Seinfeld?
And they go, no, you can't say that.
I don't know why.
Whenever they let a creator do what they want, whether it's good or bad, it's always a successful show.
For the most part, if they just leave people alone.
Right.
Well, yeah, that won't.
Hire good people and trust them.
I guess that's what they do with Seinfeld.
Like they let them.
I guess to the idea is to, you know, I don't defend these people often, but in their defense to say, look, guys, Seinfeld was lightning in a bottle.
We can't use that as a barometer here because Seinfeld under any other circumstance would have failed horrifically.
Like Jerry has even said that in interviews where he's been like, they just left us alone for whatever reason.
And then it got, you know, they lucked out that whoever the fuck the exchange of executives was at that point, they just didn't fuck with them.
You know?
Yeah.
It's I may have mentioned it, but it's become, you know, obviously a legendary show.
And it's also become kind of the driving tone of comedy for a while.
Comedy was very mean.
Always Sonny obviously came straight from Seinfeld.
Now comedy is far too nice, in my opinion.
But I remember the season.
It was the season seven finale where George's fiance licks the poisoned envelopes and dies and they all shrug and walk off.
And my mom was so bothered by it.
She stopped watching the show.
She talked about it for days afterwards because you had never seen that.
It was crazy.
And it ended the season.
So you knew there was no next week.
We're going to make this right either.
It was like, see you next year, guys.
This woman that we've been following is George's fiance.
And they all are just like, see you later.
I love that that your mom stopped watching the show.
It's there's people out there that will do that.
They'll go.
My mom used to do that.
They lost me when they went all political or whatever it was, you know.
Yeah.
They just bail on a show.
They defined their enjoyment for seven fucking years.
It was always funny when my mom gave up on a show, too, because she never once watched a TV show or a movie without reading a book at the same time.
So it's like I don't think maybe you're paying full attention there, Mom.
But she'd laugh.
She'd be reading a book and she'd laugh at every punch line on the show.
It was very weird.
Multitasker.
Speaking of people that aren't what they used to be.
Well, it ties into my first movie corner.
I'm not trying to rush us over there, but no, it is it is directly connected.
With the Richard Lewis thing.
Well, actually, should we just talk?
Should we just make this whole movie corner about curb and not do an episode about her?
No.
Are you going to?
Because I can't do a season until it ends.
If we're going to do a curb episode, then we do it after the season ends and we talk about.
No, no, no.
I'm saying let's not do a curb episode.
It's not going to be a nice episode.
I'm saying instead of in lieu of a curb episode, do we just dedicate right now the movie corner to having a very deep discussion about this curb season so far and just leaving it at that?
And when we leave it alone after that, because I have a lot I have a lot to say and I don't want to title an episode curb because I don't want these opinions to be as out there.
Whereas an obvious as you know, as as they usually could be because this this hurts me.
This hurts me.
It hurts that the show.
Anytime I go back and watch anything from the first seven, eight years of the curb, I am blown away.
It was unbelievably consistent, unbelievably hilarious, just as groundbreaking as Seinfeld in its weird way.
The man had two of these shows, a true comedic legend.
But if he had wrapped things up after that Seinfeld season, we're talking about an unassailable masterpiece.
Since then, it's been hit and miss.
Usually the seasons will have a couple of good ones, a couple of weak ones, and everything kind of comes out in the wash.
This season we're on it.
You know, we got two more to go in the history of the show.
This season has been very bad.
It's just been very bad.
Now, this is what I want to do with curb.
And this is the thing everybody does now.
I.
I have a friend who works in television that told me he recut the last Indiana Jones movie into the version he thought it should be.
Like, people do this.
People edit things.
Topher Grace did that Star Wars edit where he was like, I'm going to edit them all together as one move.
Like, you know, people do these reedits now.
Fans do it.
And look, most of what we get is glorified fan fiction anyway.
So I don't got a problem with it.
I all the time make playlists on my phone where I'll take an album and I'll be like, this song should have been here and this should have been the second song and I'll rearrange it.
And then I'm like, oh, now I now I feel like I got a good album out of these guys.
Whatever.
So De Palma and Coppola and a few directors go back and do that a lot to a different kind of their film lately.
So with curb, here's what I propose we need.
You take you excise season five from.
You just put it to the side and then you do the whole series and five season five is where he finds out.
He almost drowns in the beginning.
He finds out he's adopted.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That was gross.
He's still with Cheryl.
Yeah.
So that season works perfectly fine.
Encapsulated by itself.
It doesn't lean on anything.
It doesn't pull from anything else until the finale.
I'll get to my point.
You take that.
You put it aside.
You make a box set where it seasons one through the Seinfeld season without season five.
You let those play consecutively, which they will.
The Seinfeld season ends with him getting back together with Cheryl, but she's annoyed by the glass thing.
Then right from there, you make season five the final season where it starts with him almost drowning.
He's back with Cheryl.
You don't continue the breakup because she gets annoyed about the coaster argument or whatever.
They're just back together.
He almost drowns.
He finds out he thinks he's adopted.
He might be a goy.
He goes on that soul searching thing to find his parents, the whole fucking thing.
Right.
And then it ends with the best ending you're ever going to get in Curb Your Enthusiasm.
He does his first selfless thing, which is giving Richard Lewis the kidney he needs.
Richard Lewis prospers with the new kidney.
Larry David dies doing the one nice thing he's ever done.
This is how season five ends.
That's the heaven season.
Yeah, he goes to heaven.
He annoys St. Peter so much that they send him back to Earth.
And he lives and you're like, there he is.
He will never leave this place.
He's too annoying to go anywhere.
Hell doesn't want him.
Heaven doesn't want him.
He's just stuck here annoying people.
And also, too, don't forget right before he dies, when he's getting his last rites on his deathbed, the priest or the whoever is like, is there anything you want to repent for?
And it does the full montage of every season leading up to that where everybody's going, fuck you, Larry.
Fuck you.
And then he just goes, yeah, it is the perfect ending to the show.
That's that's how it all should have ended.
That was in there, right?
Or are you adding that?
No, no, that was in there.
After season five, after the finale, I called Jeff Garland because I had just become friends with him because I had opened for him at Carolines.
And I go, yeah, is that it?
Are we done with Curb?
And he goes, honestly, I have no idea.
It's up to Larry.
Like, he'll let us know if we're going to do another.
I go, seems like we're done.
I don't know what you do after that.
Like, that was great, you know?
Right. That should just be moved to the final season.
And then everything after the Seinfeld season, like you said, we don't need it.
There's some funny episodes in there.
I think the Michael J. Box storyline is in there.
But it all then after that point, it's just like the gay kid was a hilarious episode.
There was some good stuff.
Yeah, there's great stuff.
But you don't need it is my point.
And chicken. Yeah.
You could you could then cobble together all those loose episodes that are awesome.
Yes. And the remaining seasons and go.
So here's a bonus disc with 12 other episodes that are not connected in any way,
that are just great bonus material.
And then you'd have a perfect like 10 seasons of Curb Your Enthusiasm.
I want to do this. I think it's a great fucking idea.
Do it.
I guess you can just watch it in this order on streaming.
But you could.
The theory is, and I have heard this from friends of mine.
I do not know, but I was discussing this with friends of mine the other day.
And my friends are under the impression,
and they convinced me that Curb is going to end with Larry in jail,
just like the Seinfeld finale and do the exact same thing.
And when Jerry said, well, you know, we might be doing something with the Seinfeld finale.
You know, remember when that happened?
It's going to be that there are others like what?
So I think that might be what it is.
And everything we've been following with Larry now for two seasons is him
trying to stay out of getting in trouble for that mishap he did with Tracy Ullman
and trying to not get fined or sentenced or whatever.
So I do think that's a pretty good theory, but we'll see.
It's also very Larry David to be like you hated the Seinfeld finale.
We're doing it again.
Well, it's you just said what it's going to be.
You just you just nailed it, whether it's your thing or not.
I have no idea, Pat. It's not my business.
But you just nailed what it's going to be.
And what it's going to be is is he's going to be in jail with the Seinfeld characters.
I think so. Yeah, they're going to be there.
And there's going to be some play on.
His he's imprisoned with the stain on his.
He's imprisoned with this thing that he has been criticized about
throughout his career, this horrible finale that everybody hates or whatever.
And somehow it's going to be some meta.
I mean, you know, like like a deconstructing Harry.
You know, my characters have come to life kind of thing.
Yeah, I do. I think it's definitely prison.
I don't think on a show where Larry has discussed Seinfeld so much
and we've had all the Seinfeld people on, they can do that.
Have like George Costanza sitting in a jail cell next to him.
But we'll see. I just think it involves prison in some way.
Period. It's got to. We'll see.
And the Seinfeld finale, obviously.
But this season, you know, I'm shocked to say that like the highlights
are characters I never even really loved before.
Like Vince Vaughn has been a highlight of this season as whatever.
He's OK. Something Funkhouser.
I'm a huge. I'm a huge. That's not me knocking Vince Vaughn.
Let me be very clear. I love Vince Vaughn. No, no, no. We all.
I think they're wasting him. They don't let him do anything.
Like, it's just. Well, you may not have gotten to the episode
where him and Larry have a big kind of yelling match in Larry's foyer or whatever.
I saw that. OK, the one from last week,
I think it was episode seven that was very Vaughn heavy
with the girl that works at the Disney store and everything.
That was funny. That's the one this season that I thought was good.
And that was funny.
The rest have been. I haven't even laughed.
And they're all 40 minutes and I do not get Tracy Ullman.
They're running out of things for her to do. She's barely on it now.
It's just like. I don't know, Garland seems very weary.
You know, it's just like everyone looks tired and old.
Well, I said to it happens. My friend said to me.
He said, he goes, it's too much now of them having fun
with each other and not enough regard for the audience.
And that's what it is. Like, they're not.
And then I said, also, it doesn't feel like the band is together anymore.
I go, Jeff is barely there.
They won't address Funkhouser. Right.
J .B. is like a stranger to them.
Like they talk to him like they've never met him
and they've made him cartoonishly idiotic.
It's like, what is what is this?
Like, it's ridiculous.
And the laughs that come are always like popping out of improvs.
Like J .B. Smoove, when he's talking about pissing in a bowl or whatever,
like, you know, he'll say something so weird that you kind of laugh,
but it's not it's not what it was.
And you can't say the stories aren't like, you know, working.
They're tight. They all intersect.
But the magic of it is gone.
You know, it's just like he dips into his past way too much.
We get a lot of recycled stuff.
We get a lot of recycled bits, stories from Seinfeld and Curbs.
I got you. I got you.
And, you know, that we're talking about 20 years of content.
You know, you can't keep coming up with new shit.
I also still watch and I'm still excited to watch every Sunday.
It's one of the few good comedies on television,
but it's just not hitting like it used to.
It's a bummer.
I'm at a point where I'm not excited to watch.
I forget that new episodes even came out.
The only reason I remember is because my friend Chip will say,
Did you see the new Curb this week?
Or you'll text me something very cryptic about it.
Yeah.
This week's Curb, dot, dot, dot, you know, and I'm like, oh boy.
So that's the only reason I even remember that new episodes came out.
And, you know, I ended up binging the last four the other night on a Sunday.
I was so miserably hung over on Sunday.
I went way too big on Saturday night.
Like a fucking like a damn fool, Pat, as they say, a damn fool.
I was so hung over on Sunday and like I just had to put something on where I didn't have to think.
And I was like, well, I'll put on these four Curbs I've missed.
And I didn't not laugh.
I thought like, you know, we talked about this a little bit.
I thought the Lori Loughlin storyline was funny.
I thought it was a funny concept of like he's going to he feels bad for her that she's been blackballed.
So he's going to give her a second chance and he's going to recommend her for this golf club, which which raises.
Remind me, just say, help me remember the point about the golf club.
It's just a second.
And he gets her in.
And then the joke is she's like underhandedly like cheating everything.
And she's got like she's got a handicap bumper sticker.
She's not handicap. She's paying off people for the good slot on the court.
You know, well, that's I was like, that's a really funny.
That's funny. And that's funny that she was willing to do it.
It's sort of like the Michael Richards thing when he came back after his cancellation.
And but I was texting with you about it.
You made a good point. You said, yeah, dude, it is funny.
I don't want a whole episode of the last season of this show devoted to this.
Like, she's not part of this. Yeah.
And the only thing anyone knows woman from his full house, you know, just like a cheesy bad 80s show.
And why are we giving her this opportunity to rehab herself?
You know, like that's something you do on SNL because it's a weekly topical show.
Like already it seems like this news story was three years old.
And for me, I just am like, I don't want this.
I want to know what's going on with the people I like and care about.
You know, that's what I thought.
So the golf club was what I was going to say. Yeah.
This brings me to my other thing.
This season is so riddled with white people problems, as I bet.
As I bet Miss Pat would put it.
White people problems of like, guys, we're supposed to be sad that Lori Loughlin can't get into a golf club.
Like, fuck off, guys.
I'm supposed to be things with Larry talk, you know, talking about a hundred bucks that he needs from somebody from like 1991.
It's like, come on, guys, you because you had the opportunity to not make him the Seinfeld creator.
You could have done that because maybe I'm an old guy, but we know he's got billions of dollars.
They talk about it. They talk about it. Yeah.
The thing with Richard Lewis, where they're buying a car, they're going to buy a $150 ,000 car.
Yeah. And then they're like, it's got a must.
From Steve Buscemi. Yeah.
By the way, who doesn't play Steve Buscemi, which is just confusing.
Which threw me too. Threw me too. Yeah.
You got to wait sometimes like a minute into a scene before you know if you're talking to Buscemi or just some guy.
Yeah. Yeah.
And and then they don't they call him by name.
You don't know they don't want the car because it's got a must.
You're like, guys, what are we doing here?
And then there's the whole thing. Yeah.
Then there's the whole thing. Well, you know, that's that's not about the B .O.
The tomato sauce, the car. Yeah, that's a good point.
I forgot about the car. That's a good point.
I forgot about that. And then he buys the car.
Because he feels bad because he insults Steve Buscemi's character inadvertently about a colostomy bag.
Then he buys the car out of guilt.
And then Richard Lewis is mad at him like, fuck you.
That's my car. And you bought it.
Guys, you would just give your friend the car.
And then there's a haggle of I want three thousand dollars off the.
I'm like, this man was just about to buy a one hundred fifty thousand dollar automobile.
This is not believable.
It's not believable that they keep a lawn jockey in front of the Airbnb
because Susie doesn't want to leave the security deposit, which is fifteen hundred dollars.
Yeah, it's the big problem with it is that like we're you know,
even when the stories are cleverly put together, if you don't believe the actions everyone is taking,
then you don't care. You don't go along on the ride.
It's just not viable a lot of the time.
And that's not always because the money either.
There's stuff in here where I'm like the Larry David I know would never do or say that.
Like when Larry David all of a sudden really cares about somebody, I'm like, why though?
When like I don't get the whole thing with Tracy Allman.
He would be like, leave. This woman's annoying.
Why would he care if she starts drinking again?
None of it makes sense. And she's been there for two years now.
Larry dumps and Jerry before him dumps women for the most callous, stupid, nonsensical reasons.
This woman is a nightmare.
And he feels he has to stay with her because he made a pledge to some character we've never seen.
Well, the one the motivation is off camera is clearly he thinks that's a great character and he wants it on the show.
It's fine. It's a fine character.
But but the execution of it is just lazy.
I don't know why he's not writing better again, to my friend's point, because they don't care.
They're just like, we're having fun. Who cares?
It doesn't have to be this. It doesn't have to be.
It's kind of like with the Star Wars prequels, you know, with like when George Lucas was like,
oh, it doesn't matter that Hayden Christensen doesn't have an English accent, but but Darth Vader does.
You're like, no, no, no, that that should matter.
You should connect those things like these guys think like these details don't matter to the viewer.
They do. But but here's the thing, too.
The thing with the scheming is so like terribly plot like the thing with like
Jeff is going to secretly make Larry power of attorney in case he dies in surgery.
And then and then Jeff's like, we got to figure out how to go see my lawyer without Suzy knowing.
I'm like, what is this, a three stooges plot?
This is ridiculous. Say you have a meeting across town and goes and then the way they come up,
the thing they come up with is, you know what?
Your lawyer is in the same building.
We'll say we went to see your lawyer when we really went.
Guys, say you're going to lunch.
What are we talking about?
You're going to Mars. She's not going to see you.
It doesn't matter what you tell her that that's it's one of a million little examples
where you're just you want to yell at them like, guys, wait.
And you have to be on their side through all this devious shit.
Or it's just a show watching bad people do bad things badly.
I don't know. I I'm still excited to see how it wraps up.
I hope I'm not right. I hope not 100 percent right anyway.
But it's not it's not what it was.
It is one of the best shows of all time. And I can't hate it.
But, you know, yeah, it's it's been a bit of a drag.
Also, like the guest stars, you know, Ike Barinholtz comes in.
He's doing an accent beyond Borat.
You got that guy that owns the Chinese restaurant who's like, oh, oh, oh, you know, like Larry,
also right out of a three stooges short.
I mean, this is he lives in Brentwood and the guy owns a Chinese restaurant.
Oh, oh, no, Larry. No.
No. Anyway, they also, by the way, play the I don't think you just said this part.
The gong. They don't do a gong.
They play like like it's not that sorry, it's not the Chinese restaurant guy.
It's the Japanese guy that runs the country club that they're members of.
Yeah, I'm sorry. When he comes in. No, no, no.
But they also have the Chinese restaurant guys where it's like, what are we doing?
Yes. But then when that guy comes in and yells at them in the country club, it's like,
like it's playing like Mr. Miyagi type music.
Like, it's crazy. It's crazy.
Anyway, folks, we're talking today about the multiple, multiple award nominated
and winning film from Yorgos Lanthimos.
Poor Things stars Emma Stone as a young woman who, while pregnant, jumps off a bridge to commit suicide.
Willem Dafoe finds her, takes her child's brain, her unborn child's brain,
and puts it into the body of Emma Stone, sort of a Frankenstein type deal.
From there, Willem Dafoe, who's like an old crazy inventor with like a weirdly disfigured face,
who burps large, intact animated bubbles for some reason, didn't quite follow that.
Well, he, no, no, no, they explain that.
Willem Dafoe, he is a subject of insane medical experiments that his father conducted on him for the good of science.
So he has all of these maladies now as a result of the things his father did.
Oh, the burping was one of those things?
Yeah, yeah. He says because of something, I can, I cannot process gas the way a human being.
So I need this machine to help me emit it.
I missed that. Okay.
Yeah, yeah. Sorry. Go ahead.
But yeah, so you have Emma Stone, this, this, you know, pretty young thing.
And then you have the men who become obsessed with her.
Rami Youssef, a terribly miscast Gerard Carmichael,
and Mark Ruffalo in like a very broad comedic performance about a guy who's like, thinks he's a big stud.
But in the end, he's broken by this woman.
And really what they're all trying, the reason they're all obsessed with her,
A. Emma Stone's a very attractive young woman.
But where the movie gets in most of its shots and most of its thematic points is that it's these older men wanting to control a young woman.
And they love that she has a baby's brain.
Ultimately, when she leaves Willem Dafoe, Willem Dafoe comes up with a dumber, younger woman.
And that's really where the movie is making a lot of its points that men want something they can control.
They don't want women to find out about the world at large.
They don't want women to know how much better they could have it.
They want to control them, et cetera, et cetera.
So there's, there's, yeah, go ahead.
There's there. I just want to interject.
They do it because only because it's relevant to the men.
They do it in each man represents, from what I could gather, a different phase of man controlling a woman.
Now, it's not all underhanded.
Some of it is out of love and protection.
Some of William, Willem Dafoe's, his motives are not great, but he's also very damaged from his upbringing.
And that is sort of justified.
And his, his mistakes are eventually forgiven to an extent.
But he's very much the father.
Then Rami, who's age, who's actually younger than Emma Stone, is is is sort of like the it's like the puppy love guy.
Like we're high school sweethearts.
I don't want you going off to the big college because they'll want to marry her right away.
Lock her down. Yeah.
Then Rufalo is this and she develops as this is happening.
She's becoming smarter and more exploratory.
She discovers masturbation.
She discovers sex and she becomes obsessed with sex.
That's when Rufalo comes.
Rufalo tells her I'm the best.
I'm the best sex you'll ever have.
I'm the best at sex.
And if you've only been with one person or no people, then you think that's true.
So there's that too.
What it's saying is men don't want you to go out and play the field because you'll learn that sex, all kinds of sex is different.
Some things are good for you.
Some things are bad for you.
You know, but like he wants her to think he's the best because she's only been with him.
So when she sleeps with other people, it destroys him.
So he yeah.
And he steps in right at a time in her life where as the guy that's like, hey, I got some money.
I got some status.
I want a young sex pot on my arm and look like a big shot, but I don't want her to fucking talk or whatever.
Because when he starts to try to bring her into his social circles because of her underdeveloped brain, she does not have tact and she whatever.
And there's that scene where he pulls her in the other room and he's like, you will behave.
You will.
You will limit your responses to these three sentences or whatever.
Right.
Then so she dumps, as you said, she dumps Ruffalo.
And then then it's the phase of the woman taking control of her own sexuality.
And I thought that this part of the movie was very interesting because I do think there's a fine line between whether you're male or female, controlling your own sexuality, being in control of your own sexuality and being taken advantage of through your sexuality.
And I thought they danced around this that line very well where there were moments with sex where she was very in control.
And then there were other times when she was prostituting herself, not every time she prostituted herself, but some of the times we were like, she's better than this.
Like, this is not a good thing for her to be a situation for her to be.
So I thought they handled all that well.
And then, of course, but I think then the character liked those experiences like when that I think she liked the guy who just like put it in and came immediately.
Even though it was creepy, she liked the big dude who stunk and was like ramming her really hard.
Then right after she was like, I kind of like being just rammed like an animal, whatever.
So, yeah, it's well, but that period.
But then there was also I think there was also the dad that's like, I want you to show my boys how to have sex.
And it's very disturbing. So I thought they did.
I mean, you know, she had no boundaries.
She had, you know, that's what she needed to learn in that in that period is boundaries.
But I also think that that's part of it.
And a journey a lot of people go through is like, I want to fuck everything.
What if I find out that I love some weird thing?
You know, so there's there's an exploratory nature of that, but also it gets a little scary and a little uncomfortable,
as as would having sex with a bunch of randos, you know, of course.
Yeah. At this point in the movie, she's she's come pretty she's she's developed.
She's become now an independent woman.
She she knows what she wants. She knows what she doesn't want.
And she decides she's going to return home when she returns home.
She finds out the truth of what Willem Dafoe's character had done to her and why she was alive.
She resents him greatly for it.
She goes and rediscovers the husband she knew before she had killed herself
and discovers quickly that this was not a wonderful life she was taken away from,
that this guy was was a domineering, abusive husband.
She then after that guy gets injured, she I forget what she did.
Something happens to him where he gets brain damage.
I can't remember what it was, but he tries to drug and rape her and she knocks him out.
That's what it was. So she then goes back to Willem Dafoe,
who's now dying as a result of all these things that he's dealt with all his life physically.
And she does forgive him on his deathbed. He does tell her he loves her.
It's a very nice moment. It's a very nice depiction of sometimes parents, all they can do is their best.
And yeah, sometimes they make big mistakes, but his heart was in the right place.
And then she takes up his mantle and her ex -husband or former husband,
whatever is now the brainless person in the garden.
You see that the second underdeveloped girl that Willem Dafoe had is now developing and learning.
Yeah. Yeah.
Well, they turn the Christopher Abbott character, her ex -husband, they turn him into a half man, half goat.
They put his brain into a goat.
And the ambiguous ending is sort of it's now the woman has the power.
Will she do a better job than the man did when he had the power?
And it's just kind of left there. All in all, from point A to point B, it's a well -told story.
It's an efficient, for the most part, story.
But let's get into is it an enjoyable story?
I could not. I texted you pretty early into my watching of this.
And I said, Pat, does this heat up or is it just Emma Stone talking like Tonto for two hours?
Because I can't do that.
It really bothers me that every time now we depict either an American Indian or a monster in a movie,
American Indian from back in the day, I mean, or a monster, they give them the same speak.
They do the whole you like cake, cake like me.
It's like, first of all, it seems stereotypical.
And, you know, I have no idea if American Indians talk like that.
That's how they're depicted. So it could be fucking racist for all I know at this point.
But let's just put it over into the other camp of its monster speak in these movies.
Like, guys, can you think of a different way to have a fucking monster talk?
Like, I don't know. A baby doesn't talk like that.
We're supposed to be dealing with a baby's brain.
A baby doesn't go you, me, friend.
Yeah, that's kind of interesting.
Like they used to do the sketch on SNL where Beck Bennett was playing a baby who worked at an office.
And, you know, classic SNL sketch is just a guy being a baby in an office setting while wearing a suit.
But he's so and I don't even give a shit about that guy.
I mean, he's fine. But he was doing a really brilliant impression of a baby and how they act physically and how they talk and what they do.
Everything that the Emma Stone character and the Margaret Qualie character are doing in this is not really like a baby or like a small kid.
You're right. It's just kind of like, well, what are you doing?
It's just it's like a choice they're making.
So I don't know. Everybody loved Emma Stone in this.
She won the Oscar. I personally thought that Emma Stone gave the most annoying acceptance speech in the history of of time.
I really hated it. And I like Emma Stone.
But it made me change my opinion. Worse than Will Smith's.
I don't think anybody's top of Will Smith's for me.
No, but yeah, she just really bothered me.
And like you're the favorite one and everyone thinks you're going to win.
And then the whole like sitting frozen in her chair, like who me?
I just it drove me nuts. But she's good in the movie.
She's constantly I don't know why she got mad at Jimmy Kimmel's innocent joke.
She's constantly naked and fucking in the movie.
Wait, she got mad at what joke?
Kimmel was like they showed some little clip and he's like, sorry, that's the only clip we could show you from poor things.
That joke's been been happening at the Oscars forever.
It means there's a lot of sex in the movie. It's an adult movie.
And she looks at her husband and goes prick, mouths it and got caught on camera and et cetera.
But it's like you really can't make any jokes about these people.
They take everything so fucking seriously. But regardless, that's not the movie.
I saw the movie once in the theater. I thought it was a half hour too long.
I still feel like it's a half hour too long. No reason for this to be 230.
You cut one of the guys.
I don't know how they didn't just cut Gerard Carmichael, frankly, because he's really, really bad in this movie.
What was his purpose? What was his purpose?
Like, what was that character's purpose?
Probably diversity, Joe.
And I do think sometimes that happens where a movie is an extra 20 minutes too long because they're like, oh, wait, we have to address diversity now.
But then cast diverse characters as the leads.
So couldn't agree more.
Also, with the new rules, I mean, maybe they couldn't have even gotten nominated without.
But without Gerard in a key role, I don't know.
I'm curious if he's in the book or not.
Now, I talked to Jared Logan about the movie because Jared read the book.
And Jared said the book is much funnier than the movie.
And Jared also said that he didn't think the movie needed the Terry Gilliam vibes.
And I agreed. I said, yeah, I go, you know, they do these Terry Gilliam visuals throughout the movie.
And I go, yeah, it make it gives you an expectation because it is so blatantly Terry Gilliam.
It is blatantly fucking Terry Gilliam nods or ripoffs or whatever you want to call it.
And then when you see that, you then have an expectation.
This is going to be this is going to get all Gilliam.
And it never does.
And it's like if the book is funny, make the movie funny to go along with these wild visuals like Terry Gilliam would.
And it's like, no, instead, we're going to make it almost painfully serious, kind of disturbing.
I will say they're they're making many attempts to be funny, I think, in Poor Things, the movie.
OK. And I think that it's not really your ghost's strong suit, because when I saw it at the theater, it was getting, you know, L .A.
laughs, but big L .A. laughs where people are like, look how smart I am.
And they also laugh in L .A. to be like, I'm laughing at Mark Ruffalo to let you know I'm not him.
That's a lot of things guys do. Like, I'm laughing at him because I'm not him.
Very performative. But.
I when watching it again last night on TV, I was able to not be looking at all these crazy visuals at the time when they go to Lisbon looks exactly like
the Venetian shops at the at the Venetian in Vegas, you know, where they have the fake roof.
It always creeps me out. I thought they shot it there for a minute.
Yeah, look, I really appreciated the visuals much more the second time around.
It gets a little annoying with the little fish eye lens in the first half hour.
It's like, come on, guys, like you don't have to do this.
Like every shot does not have to be something kooky.
But as a long form, too long form metaphor for.
Feminism for the woman's journey before kind of, you know, a woman who goes from like.
Losing her virginity to marriage, you know what what that can look like.
I thought it was really great. I really got much more into it on the second viewing.
It's a smart movie.
It everybody in it is good, except who I mentioned.
And I love your ghost. My problem is, I think your ghost is getting less good over time.
Dogtooth, I think, is a masterpiece, one of his early movies.
I love killing of a sacred deer.
The favorite was great. The lobster was great.
Four things is great. So I don't know what I'm talking about.
I just. Yeah, I was.
He's a good director. I'll always go see what he does.
He's got a new movie coming out with like pretty much all the same cast that looks kind of interesting.
I like the dude. And with all the shitting we do on movies being lazy or not having anything going on upstairs or whatever,
it's real hard to to pick apart poor things for the few faults that it has,
because I do think there's a lot going on here that really works well.
I liked it. Gerard's Gerard's part, because I realized he's the only guy we're picking on.
I also realized how that could not. No, I know. I know.
It's not it's not his fault. Let me anyone else.
He's just he's not he's not an actor.
He's not strong enough to do to do that kind of role that that role should have been Donald Glover.
And there would have been it would have leapt off.
They offered it to him. Yeah.
And it would have been like, wow, OK, you know, it just it's it's it's weird.
The old lady also seemed to be like an unnecessary character to me.
I get that she was sort of the the the outside female mentor.
So I guess that needs to be in there somewhere with a story like this.
Sure. She's almost like this passive Gloria Steinem or something.
Yeah. But I think they could have merged that character in with like the madam.
The madam could have been that person, and it would have complicated and nuanced
the character of a woman saying, you're going to sell yourself for sex and money
and you're going to give me the money.
But also, I'm going to kind of teach you a thing or two about feminism.
That would have been more interesting and it would have tightened things up.
Rufalo, I thought Emma Stone was very, very good in this.
It's not her fault.
They wrote the opening half hour of her dialogue like like a like a robot breaking down.
But I thought she was really, really good in it.
And I thought Rufalo, I loved I'd never seen Rufalo play a prick.
I don't think. Oh, that's true. That's true.
So that also, you know, outside of his his romcoms where he was always the straight man,
he hasn't done a lot of comedy either.
So his accent was questionable.
It was kind of slipping in and out.
It was there that it wasn't there.
But his emotional performance was very good.
Defoe always delivers.
I was impressed with Rami.
I've known Rami since he was 16.
I've only ever seen him in his acting wise.
I've only ever seen him in his sitcom.
And the sitcom he was on with Scott Baio when he was like what was that?
It was fucking sick with Scott, I forget.
Anyway, but I was impressed with Rami.
I thought he did a good job.
You know, like I thought he I was like, all right, yeah, he's making this work, man.
So I agree with you on the directing.
There were choices where it was like, we're just going to try to be.
We're just going to try to be interesting.
Every shot should challenge.
It's like, what is the point of the fish?
You said the fish. What's the point of that?
What's the point of early on when we're looking at everything through that fisheye?
It's like, no, man, that you're doing too much.
You know, that's it's an old silent movie trick.
They didn't do it that much in the silent days.
Scorsese used it to to impact super powerful moments in the age of innocence,
which is not one of his best.
But, you know, he uses that fisheye for very clear moments.
The two characters touch hands.
And to modern audiences, that means nothing.
But back then it meant fucking.
So he zooms in on the hands and you get it.
This is showing you scene after scene.
That's just in a circle.
It's a lot like The Lighthouse, another movie that really grew on me over time.
But I was just kind of like, why am I watching this movie take up one fourth of the screen at the theater
so that they can go see we used a different lens or whatever and show off?
If it's not helping the storytelling, why are you doing it?
And more often than not lately, I feel like it's not helping the storytelling.
I got to tell you the world of the world.
Gilliam's not making good movies anymore and nobody's really the heir to him anymore.
And I'll say that this is a pretty good facsimile of what he does so well.
Terry Gilliam, I got to tell you.
Dare about must just be.
I'd have steam coming out of my ears as well as Frank Dare about like like I can't.
I can't get a black and white on the mist and you just put out the lighthouse.
I have to choose. You put up the light.
You just let this guy do half the fucking movie in black and white, and then it goes to color for no reason.
I guess I get was it a metaphor for now she's exploring the world?
I don't even think that's what it turned color.
I think it turned color when she still lived at home with Defoe.
Yeah. You know what? It's very interesting.
You say that because I thought it was the Oz thing, too, of like Dorothy.
Now that she's seeing world outside of Kansas, it gets colorful.
But that's not true, because when she's at her lowest point going to kill herself and her baby, that's in color.
And that should be the blackest and widest part of all.
Poor things.
I had one other thing to say.
About the.
Yeah, maybe I didn't.
Maybe I didn't. Maybe that was it.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's a good movie.
I mean, you know, it's fine.
I'll never watch it ever again.
It was good.
And I'm glad I did.
You know, I clearly have a little sort of undiagnosed ADD, ADHD or something, and it's sometimes I miss things in movies sometimes.
And in this one, I found myself struggling so hard to follow it from a story standpoint that watching it again really helped me appreciate it as an extended metaphor where it works much, much better.
So I liked it a lot more on this viewing.
We will be back with Ghostbusters.
What is it called?
Frozen City?
Frozen Dinner.
Frozen Empire.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yes, I am on Instagram at the Patrick Walsh.
We are on Instagram at See You When Hell Pod.
And as always, thank you for your love and your Patreon support, Joe.
I have a couple quick plugs.
Well, as always, come to Joey Roses.
If you're in New York City, we're open seven days a week.
Isn't that lovely?
Sandwiches and drinks.
April 12th, I'm going to be in Beacon, New York at the Town Crier Cafe.
April 19th, Wilmington, Delaware at the Queen Wilmington.
Hamden, Connecticut at the Space Ballroom.
On May 3rd, and just announced, Newport, Rhode Island, May 25th, the Jane Pickens Theater as part of the Rhode Island Comedy Festival.
JoeDeRosa .com for all of that stuff.
Thanks, folks.
We'll see you next time.
And we'll see you in hell.