I'll see you in hell back again April second episode here to talk about
we're not monkeyin' around today when we talk about the monkey Stephen King's
latest well not his latest but the latest adaptation I guess I don't know
they're making an adaptation a week at this point I think this is the newest one
old Osgood Perkins back with well I'm just gonna say it at the top I haven't seen
a movie this overrated since Oz's last movie long legs but here we are so we'll
get to it we will get to it the monkey is the monkey even available to rent
currently I guess I rented it 1999 oh my god well they do that when it first
comes out when it's still sort of tail end to theaters it'll be 20 bucks to
rent it and then in another month it'll be 799 but we needed to review it and I
couldn't seem to get my ass to a theater to see it so but that's I was like well
that's what I would have paid if I went to the movies anyway so I guess you
know it's all the same director Frank Derribon originally held the film
rights to the monkey and planned to start working on an adaptation after the
mist but the project never materialized I would have enjoyed Derribon's yeah God
I was assuming that would have been a better film he was the flanagan of his day
with this as far as Stephen King was concerned like he was the guy he absolutely
was I think he's superior also if you've never read his emails to the AMC
television network from their criticism of the walking dead that is a must
read Apatiles got an amazing one of those from when they canceled undeclared
where that where they you can find online the letter he wrote to Fox and Derribon's
letters to the I mean they pretty much killed his career he doesn't really work
anymore it just like killed him and I get it it's it's well worth reading let
me see if I can find one of those okay in the meantime speaking to new movies
out I think it's still in theaters but folks screenboat is out and I am in it in
a foreign screenboat I'm in screenboat what are you in screenboat I don't want to
say but I gotta I pop up in there but screenboat is out is it's the latest in
this new trend of you know horror movies based on iconic cartoon characters
this one is based on steamboat Willie and it dropped April second and it's
only in theaters I think it's still out if you go to the Wikipedia page if you
and you look at the cast list at the very bottom it says Tyler Posey Brian Quinn
and Joe to Rosa make cameos that's very cool I'm very excited I never thought I'd
get to see my name on a Wikipedia page as being part of a horror movie but this
is from the guys the this is from the terrifying crew directed by Stephen Lamort
David Howard Thornton who plays the clown and terrifying play steamboat Willie
in this and yeah you know it's it's a lot of fun Michael Levy one of the
producers and a friend this was very fun to be a part of I'm really happy it all
worked out and and it all came out of a night of drinking I was out with
Michael and Brian and we were all drinking and and Michael said would you guys
want to be in the movie and we were like yeah so folks when they tell you
nothing good comes out of alcohol they don't know what they're talking about
idiots keep drinking anyway go check it out if you can it's fun it's goofy you
know it is exactly what you think it's gonna be it's a horror movie about
our comedy movie about steamboat Willie and it was shot on the ferry that was
purchased by Paul Italian my business partner Joy Rose's and Pete Davidson
and Colin Joseph that ferry that's where they shot a lot of it so this is this
is very much all in the family so check it out hope you see it hope you enjoy
it and that's it I will definitely see it for you but the the mushroom trip
that put me off mushrooms for the rest of my life involved a lot of steamboat
Willie imagery so I probably won't be able to finish the film honestly all right
fair enough I found the Daribont stuff so a little backstory Daribont and AMC
were feuding over lots of things ams the shows a unbelievable smash hit and for
season two AMC one of the shows budget cut by 25% of course they wanted all
season two scripts before filming began which doesn't happen on any television
show and they were feuding is all we knew but then when this stuff went to court
a lot of these emails came out I'm always of the mindset of the creator is
always right these network executives are never right but he probably didn't
need to take this tone here's here's a collection of a few lines from these
emails that were in the trial this first one was sent to Gail Ann heard the
executive producer also a former wife of James Cameron producer of the
Terminator etc Daribont says fuck you all forgiving me chest pains because of
the staggering fucking incompetence blindness to the important beats and the
beyond arrogant lack of regard for what is written being exhibited on set
every day I deserve better than a heart attack because people are too stupid
to read a script and understand the words does anybody disagree with me then
join the C.Cam operator and go find another job that doesn't involve
deliberately fucking up my show scene by scene it's a beautiful message please
let's stop invoking the writers room there is no writers room which you know as
well as I do I am the writers room the fucking lazy assholes who are
supposedly going to be my showrunners through that responsibility on me
after wasting five months of my fucking time
Ray Charles could operate a camera better than my camera operators these
directors it's like we yanked some kid with no experience out of high school
and put her in charge of directing a show here's another one you need to pay
attention to the mother fucking script I even choose my goddamn commas for a
reason in all caps so you know you can you send these people to their breaking
point pretty easily it doesn't take long I love it but he's not really working this
guy did Shawshank redemption green mile walking dead one of the biggest shows
ever got fired off his own show and now barely works I think between the
walking dead thing and the kingdom of the crystal skull experience he had what
happened there well he wrote the I guess original draft and then they brought in
David kept and like rewrote darabounce yeah draft and apparently he was
devastated by what they did to his script and you know I mean if you watch
crystal scum I'm the biggest Indiana Jones fan on earth but if you watch
crystal skull it's like it couldn't be less frank darabounce so I think
probably he had to experience you know and he's by the way this is the guy this
is what this business is here's a guy ride and high fucking green mile which is
the most revered Stephen King movie ever next to Shawshank redimp well he did
Shawshank too right he did yeah so he does Shawshank it is green mile you know
can you do it again he does do it again yeah and and then and then he does the
mist and it's like this runaway hit people are saying this could be the best
Stephen King adaptation ever and then he goes right into the crystal skull
experience followed by the walking dead and he's just going what the fuck guys
like what what who's dick do I got a suck over here like what do I got to do it's
you know I it's got to be maddening yeah well and then like you know why aren't
they working with them because he's difficult everyone in this business is
difficult if the product is good and with and darabounce case it always is he
doesn't make bad shit I guess he made them a justic that wasn't great but oh
majestic didn't bomb it didn't bomb I don't think it was a hit but it didn't
bomb anyway Joe what's new with you I just got back from Cabo San Lucas yeah
heco I had a lot of fun down there but not much going on I'm back from Atlanta
I'm settled was it a romance trip it was me and my lady friend went down nice
it was great we did some whale watching so all kinds of whales and then
mostly just kind of sat around had a had a deck with a jacuzzi on the deck
looking out at the ocean it was wonderful now are you still dry no drinks
nothing that's correct that's why can great really hasn't been a problem the
drinking I don't miss the weed yes absolutely wow all right well that's good
I I'm not doing that and I got shit face 24 7 and Key West and yeah loved
every second of it was this a stand-up cruise or something Brian we I talked
about it briefly in the last episode of Brian Quinn loves Key West he was like I
want to put a festival together so all my friends can go to Key West and have
the best time and he did and it was awesome it was me Jamie Lee Simmons who is a
woman in my life an important woman in my life let's not defy let's not use
used labels but you know you brought it up but yeah but she she she was there and
and Steve burn was there and Rachel Feinstein was there we were the and Jake
jiggy was there and who's jiggy jiggy is one of the jokers guys and works on
the show and part of that world great guy man and and then Chris Johnson I think
we were the five whatever that was six stand-ups and then like the guys from
the tell them Steve Dave podcast were there so Brian Johnson Joey Fattone was
there okay of in sync fame and is that everybody you know I might be missing
one or two people my apologies if I am but anyway it literally was like Brian
was like come down Wednesday the festival attendees get here on Friday you have one show
on Saturday and you leave on Monday I was like okay so that's basically what it was and it was
yeah outside of doing that one show it would literally be like you know hey can you go judge
the belly flop contest at 2 p.m. it was like uh-huh it was you know it was wake up get breakfast
have a mimosa get the day rolling it was it was a blast man there were a lot of
to be intoxicated and still judged belly flop competitions that I felt did I
felt I was off my game do the alcohol the stand-up I was fine yeah excuse me but no it was it was super fun
man the fans down there were amazing it was only 200 people 200 tickets sold so it's basically the
same 200 people at every event Ming from comic book man was there Ming and I hosted karaoke together
we had a fucking blast singing songs watching Joey Fattone sing I Want It That Way by the Backstreet
boys for karaoke was it was a highlight of my life it was really amazing watching that
probably sounds better than the guy who sings it in Backstreet at this he sounded amazing it was super
fun to watch uh I've got video somewhere of all of us we all stayed in this house together
of all of us drunk at like 2 a.m. in the kitchen of this house having a dance party and uh Joey
was teaching me and Steve burn how to do the ends the buy-by-by dance he was like he like taught us how to
do it was insane it was an insane surreal experience it was the most fun trip you could you could imagine
but the point is as I was not sober I yeah I don't know how to have fun sober and I don't know
if I'll ever know how to have fun which is a sad thing to say but yeah you gotta be having sex
extra places that you need another vice to replace it that's no I have that vice too I
it's yeah but you know still after you have this actually like I want to go get drunk now yeah
or vice um crazy than the last month you met two of your musical heroes uh Liam Gallagher and
Joey Fattone Joey Fattone yeah both uh yeah both Joey's the second of the in sync people I have
gotten to know a bit who's the other I also met Chris well I met and did a show with the Chris guy
yeah I don't know him anywhere near as well I'm like friends with Joey at this point I've done
a bunch of shit with him and he's he's the fucking best dude ever he's the most fun awesome he's
on Broadway right now on that and Juliett shall uh huh I'm gonna go see it I think but uh
anyway what what is Andrew liat it's like the pop pop musical comedy about like if she didn't die
like Romeo dies but she lives and then like what happens her afterwards but all the set all the
songs are like I think like boy band songs and stuff and I don't know it's it's a big hit on Broadway
but it's you know I haven't seen it but he's in it uh so I'd like to go see it just to see him in action
but um but anyway um that was it that was like the latest thing Jamie and I had a really great time
down there and um you know she she was awesome to be on the trip with she she's she's super fun
and uh our show that we did with me and Jamie and Chris and Rachel was super fun and you know
we hosted a we all co-hosted a ghost tour down there where it was just wild it was just a wild
fucking time it was super fun there all right telling you more to tell you
less about I had a good time and more about how unsover I am yeah versus your sobriety so um
you know we'll just we'll just compare notes every week and see how it goes for both of us I
put that's fine um yeah I don't I don't I don't really miss the drunken it's just I became a weed
guy at some point and I was like I'm I'm keeping the drink up for no reason yeah you think you'll
smoke weed ever again oh yeah yeah yeah absolutely fair enough um all right let's get to that
movie corn and let's get to that unique horn because I saw death of a unicorn oh god
the new a 24 film I almost asked Joe hey are we gonna do this on the show but I was I was just
not gonna put him through that once I saw um death of a unicorn is terrible and
I guess because it's 824 we're not hearing about that you never hear anything negative about
this company I don't understand it you can't hear a negative word about anything put out by this
company they make bad shit a lot can I can pet if I'm saying exclusively I'm saying they make bad
shit we're allowed to say that people may I interject for a moment please yeah I almost post this
on Instagram I'm glad I didn't so I can say it here 824 it's fucking over do you see the cast
of Ari Astor's new movie I all I saw was uh walkie and and Elvis yeah well well also it's a movie
about the pandemic because we all want to fucking see this now anyway Ari Astor's new movie 824
super indie better to do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
and he saying I may never the copo saying I may never walk again and I know you were intoxicated but I also know it wasn't your fault and despite me knowing what's true I will not I'm not going to rat you out because God is the only judge of us and his wife is saying praise Jesus praise Jesus as he's saying this Zamekis has this woman going literally like evangelical in the
tunish and absurd and anybody with half a brain would go this is not how you would do this if it was real yeah in real life the woman would just be saying praise Jesus you know she'd be saying it she wouldn't be screaming it right because this is stupid. Um so that prompted me to go because I said well this is interesting because we were just talking about Zamekis and this was one of the things I said was good that he's going to do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
because he just the way he talks but he's he's in two scenes he's literally in two scenes I went to the Vista to see Grindhouse
and you know here's another one like 1941 that I guess I'm just going to keep revisiting forever because I think it'll
grow on me and it doesn't. I thought I loved death proof and that planet terror was a bit of a letdown
planet terror sucks yeah and death proof is when Tarantino's worst by hand by far his worst not even close
the dialogue in this thing is worse than a Tarantino's spoof yeah like the diet I mean he's got
the lead black character Austin's hottest DJ jungle Julia oh boy obviously Tarantino plays with
rice in ways that are occasionally a little uncomfortable jungle Julia come on come on
on quit by the way if you have not seen it's on the it's on the Jackie Brown 4k which you should
all on because it's excellent but if you have not seen Tarantino on MTV like Total Request Live
for the Jackie Brown special he's doing more of a black accent than I think I've ever heard a white
person attempt yeah he's he's weird maybe you could even say problematic in the sense of like he
does that thing we're like when he makes a movie he adopts the culture of the movie yeah that he
did it with kill bill where like he's like in Japan dancing to like these like Japanese punk bands
and he's like yeah man you know I but it fucking I bought a samurai started the airport because yeah
yeah it's it's wild and and semolo jaxons on stage with him nobody's calling him out but Jackson
looks pretty uncomfortable I mean he's he's doing like he might as well be uh well feral and
anchor man too the voice he's doing um anyway death proof was surprisingly not great the amount
of talking in this movie before the fun stuff with Kurt Russell and the car start and the dialogue
sucks there's none of the usual memorable Tarantino dialogue these actresses outside of Rosario
Dawson I like them but couldn't he have done anything to differentiate these characters this is one
of our great writers I don't know if he was I mean he is unquestionably but I don't know if he was
going so much for the B movie experience that he was like I'm just not gonna try real hard on this
one I'm just gonna write this in an afternoon I'm not sure what went on but it's it's it's not his
best it's actually the opposite the end yeah what I was gonna say here's my biggest problem with
these two movies yeah death proof I'm sorry uh planet terror is a movie that sort of
feels like a grindhouse movie but has effects that are way too obviously modern and it's an
homage to John Carpenter yeah who's not that he's not grindhouse so it doesn't work because you're
like well I'm taking out of it because that explosion was clearly just a computer animated whatever
yeah death proof Tarantino actually pulls off the aesthetic and it actually does look like an old movie
but then he's got the characters pulling out cell phones yeah like just set it in that set it in
the 70s why are you why are you it's so confusing to me it's so confusing to me I just don't get it
I agree um Kurt Russell is far in a way the best part of it yeah him like screaming like a little girl
at the end when they get him is great but man I didn't remember this thing being 110 minutes
especially when you're part of a double feature quentin like get it down to 90 for a Christ say
uh and you could with death proof and not miss a god damn thing right I don't know I was uh
very led down by the experience I think the the idea of grindhouse fantastic I remember being
very excited about it when it dropped and enjoying it when I first saw it but yeah it's just
it does not really work and it's absurdly long the trailers uh the fake trailers you know are really fun
um but then I also learned that concept's been done before there's a movie called movie movie
that's the first half is one kind of movie spoof the second half's another and there's fake trailers
between it there is a precedent for it too so it's not wholly original and it doesn't work it's it's
about look planet terror is among Robert Rodriguez's best uh and death proof is definitely
Tarantino's worst but the movie just doesn't hold water for me Joe um
um debating which one I want to do well I guess I'll do these two because I haven't done it um
disconnected from what I said earlier I used like to have a theme but uh I was talking about sitcoms
in the last episode so speaking of multi cam sitcoms I watched mid century modern
which is the new Nathan Lane sitcom that's sort of like an all male gay version of the golden girls
uh co-starring uh the late Linda Lavon and the other two actors I have to look up their names uh
I keep forgetting their names because I wasn't that familiar with them Nathan Lannamat Bomber
Matt Bomber and then Nathan Lee Graham who I would argue steals the show but um um you know
when it first started I was like the first episode or two I was like this is like sort of
camping over the top and you know like a lot of modern sitcoms it's a little too gag heavy
and not enough character driven uh for for for my taste but
sure enough I ended up getting hooked in and sitting there and watching the entire thing
ultimately I enjoyed it and in the second to last episode of the season when Linda Lavon's
characters killed off because she died in real life sadly I was in fucking tears and I was like I
guess I've connected with these characters way more than I thought I did um it's it's very golden girls
with Nathan being the Dorothy character um uh Nathan Lane being the Dorothy character
Matt Bomber being sort of a blend of Rosen Blanche where he fucks the most but he's also kind of
the the airhead and then Nathan Lee Graham being sort of there to be a little bit Dorothy
uh and and and a little bit Blanche in the sense of his vanity and whatever Linda Lavon was
certainly in the Sophia role as the mother who kind of had no filter um speaking of Pamela Adlon
she plays Nathan Lane's sister in it and I think she's gonna come in and now take the place
of Linda Lavon's character which would work nicely she she's she's Pamela's good in that role
she's she's good in a you know brash you know no filter character kind of role um and she's funny
in it as is everybody else you know look whether you like the sitcom or not
you know I don't think it's gonna be your favorite you know just given the fact that multi-cam's in
in modern day it's they just they're hard to land in the way they used to it's it's a different
world we're living in but when they land they land you know uh the work of Pat Walsh lands for me
and I think that Pat if you saw this you would approve the uh um and it's Nathan Lane you're gonna get
three laugh out loud moments in every episode with Nathan Lane without question and you might get some
also with the some of the other characters as well I look forward to seeing season two see where it
goes they're off to a good start and it's certainly a stronger effort I'm sad to say
than the cancelled phrasier reboot or some of these other things I've seen so I think it probably
falls somewhere in the vein of of like a misspat style sitcom just in the thematically not at all
but just in the sense that it it definitely goes for it with the jokes I mean the jokes are wild
some of them uh and it's you know it can be as blue as it needs to be or wants to be so
I enjoyed it I look forward to seeing what happens yeah I think that R rated thing is kind of the
the only way multi-cam can survive yeah it just it it gives it a special pop that it's it's missing
um my last one is the king of comedy which I saw here at the uh american cinema tech and los
fielis a classic you know it uh is martin scorsese one of his few true comedies and it is really really
funny it's robert de niro as rooper pupkin one of the great characters ever he is a man who lives in
his mother's basement he is obsessed with the entertainment business you know we still have
these people to this day obviously the comedy feels just as fresh and smart and spot on today as
it ever did he deniro's character is obsessed with jerry louis who is basically playing johnny karson
and scorsese wanted johnny karson in the role but karson turned it down jerry louis is fucking fantastic
in the part he's he's amazing in it like he really is the arrogance he's awesome yeah well awesome
it's you know it's a way toned down version of his buddy love you know it's a way more realistic
version of it but he just exudes money and wealth and power and he's also not an asshole which is a
great like it's a great thing for his character like he's a you know he's a prick he's a
rich guy you know but he hears out rooper way longer and way more than he needs to and my my
assumption in watching it this time around is that he recognizes some of himself in rooper it's
hard for me and i'm certainly not at a johnny karson level of success but it's hard for me
um not to help out everybody that reaches out to me or sends me an email because i remember
the desperation of being in their shoes and i think that's part of this is that jerry louis just sees
the desperation in deniro and doesn't want to hurt his feelings it's an interesting thing because
if the whole movie was get the fuck out of my office and get the fuck out of my face right and there's
not much conflict to it he kind of lets him in a little bit um this the early on scenes of deniro
trying to get his jokes and his material into jerry louis are incredible they're not quite the
birthplace of awkward comedy but they're certainly one of the touchstones along the way of what led
to like you know the british office and this the awkward comedy becoming the dominant form of
comedy for about 15 20 years king and comedy is a big uh milestone in the world of awkward comedy
for sure um and then the other brilliant thing it does much in the same way that phrasier said how
are we going to make phrasier who was a pompous arrogant dick uh in the cheers world we we all like
him there because there's 30 other likable characters how are we going to do it on phrasier
and they said we need to bring in somebody more uh you know effeminate whatever you want to call
it snooty snobby and that was niles it was a brilliant move and it immediately makes phrasier more
of a blue collar type persona what this movie does is okay how are we going to stay in the headspace
of the nero for two hours this isn't taxi driver per se he's not like you know a deranged murderer
so how do we stay on his side and stay in his corner they address that by bringing in the great
Sandra Bernhardt who plays a woman who's even crazier than rooper pupkin and who is even more
obsessed with Jerry Lewis than rooper pupkin she is genuinely scary but also the funniest part of
this movie by far and Sandra Bernhardt you know she was on letterman a lot during the 80s she was
for you know she dated Madonna she's been on shows and movies she was on two broke girls for a season
I met her she was great but how this movie didn't pop her off into the stratosphere I don't really
understand it's in my opinion it's one of the all-time great supporting performances I love her in
this movie I love deniro I love Jerry Lewis in this movie and it's it's one of Scorsese's greats
it's a true classic and it couldn't be more timely Joe um well in that vein uh my last one
is I rewatched the late shift this is a movie I revisit every year it's about the late night
wars between Leno and letterman to obtain the tonight show after Johnny Carson stepped down
it's it's a I love it man I think it's one of these movies about showbiz and the book was a best
seller and and you know apparently is very good I never so I never read the book books right it's
apparently or I'm sorry not apparently um it's it's a great take on showbiz and the inner
workings of all of it and the dirty dealings and whatever and it feels like it's insightful and
it's allowing you a peek in unlike and um you know our good buddy Dave Cremholts is in it and I'm
not trying to be in a dick but unlike in my opinion the studio which I watched which to me felt
way more like a bunch of cool kids kind of winking to camera and saying we get it and it's like well
yeah I would assume you do you're all at the top of this business right with many of you playing
yourselves uh that's how famous everybody in this cast is I felt like the late shift was was
kind of showing me behind the curtain in a way that I didn't often that I don't often get to see
or wasn't quite as uh well that's all I'll say anyway uh John Michael Higgins is tremendous
as Letterman Daniel Robock is great as Jay Leno but the star of the show here at Kathy Bates
playing Leno's manager um and uh what is that woman's name damn it Helen Kushnick Helen
um who sued actually for her portrayal in this uh uh Reno Santoni poppy from from uh
side-felt yes and also uh Dirty Harry's partner in the original Dirty Harry pop stuff treat
Williams is in this uh treat Williams plays uh uh what's his name uh Michael Lovitz
it's just it's just a really fascinating movie I think the the battle for that show was incredible
um and what transpired afterwards was was probably equally as incredible I know the author wrote a
sequel that was about when the whole Conan thing happened I'd love to see them make that a movie
but uh in the meantime uh this is well worth a watch if you haven't seen it the late shift it was
in a made for HBO movie but this is right around when the made for HBO movie started to come actually
like theater quality and I don't know perhaps the studio uh gets more into this type of stuff
or or whatever as it goes maybe I need to give it more of a chance but you know it's just so
many goddamn famous people that it took me out of it but uh but this this was quite the opposite
uh yeah yeah I've been enjoying the studio I should say who would you cast as Conan
because I did read the Conan sequel as well which was great what would I cast as Conan I mean
what would you do Dennis Leary Dennis Leary look I'm throwing something out I don't fucking know
oh yeah it's gotta be Conan and when he's like 30 years old yeah I mean
I mean one of the you know the guy that play you know be good Conan the guy that played uh
who's the kid stays in the picture Robert Evans the guy that played Robert Evans in the offer
Matthew good yeah you'd be good you're good Conan the bigger issue would be who would play
Letterman and Leno because now I feel like these well these guys might be a little aged out at
this point to still play the part uh my well Letterman was always a little older Higgins is 62
you could probably still get him in the Letterman get up and it would work no you could no these
guys could because these guys it was you are from forgetting this was like years and years later
yeah so the so the Leno and Letterman were in their 60s when all that happened I think or damn
near so yeah I think they then that'd be great I would love to see them reprise the roles and do
a sequel that'd be awesome I don't see it happening but I would love it I don't know I just got a
update here before we move on to our movie of the week that Robert Zemeckis teaming with Jennifer
Lopez on Netflix adaptation of the last Mrs. Parish from the writer of flight
so now instead of Denzel it's the same team but instead of Denzel we got Jennifer Lopez
probably not a step in the right direction Robert history will prove me right yeah um
Pat take us through the plot of today's movie The Monkey I'm gonna take a quick wee while you
explain to the folks what happens well shit yeah go for it but uh I saw The Monkey months ago Joe
saw it yesterday I guess but um it's a little tricky to explain because I feel like it completely
loses its way at about the halfway point but basically we start with a flashback to 1999
uh there is a man played by Adam Scott who is attempting to return and destroy one of those old
toy monkeys that plays the symbols um he's like I want you to please take this you know he's at
a pawn shop like you sold me this I no longer want it take it from me blah blah blah and before he
can the monkey plays its drum and the shop owner is disemboweled in a very graphic and disgusting way
after that Adam Scott disappears and his wife and their twin sons discover the monkey that he
was hiding they wind its key well by the way sorry do you even stop you he wasn't hiding it he burns
it alive yeah alive but he burns it and then all of a sudden it's in the closet right off the bat
you're confused that's a great point so you should take over because I saw this three months ago
he burns the yeah it starts with with with with uh with Adam Scott saying bringing the monkey into a
thrift uh pawn shop yes and he says I need you and he's covered in blood and he says I need you to
take this off my hands and the guy says no returns on children's toys yeah which insinuates that
he bought it at that pawn shop correct um okay he goes you're covered in blood Adam Scott says it's
not my blood and he says if this monkey's drum stick comes down on the drum something bad's going to
happen we don't want that to happen sure enough the drum stick comes down and the guy that owns the
pawn shop dies a horrible death Adam Scott then gets out of flame thrower and burns the monkey up
and screams take that you son of a whore which was the immediate second I knew we were going to
have a humor problem in this movie yeah we do have a humor problem yeah because it's trying way too
hard to be funny and it's the son of a whore thing that that phrasing has been used so many times
in movies to yeah to be funny and it's never funny it might have been funny once uh well also
there's a few things I want to stop and say here the disemboweling of the shop owner and then later on
they go to like a uh a hebachi type place where there's another murder that the the kids take the
babysitter to get dinner and there's another there's there's lots of graphic comedic frankly kills
in this movie for me that's the highlight the movie says in its opening scene we're going to be
outrageously cartoonishly violent and it goes for it I love that aspect of it the kind of more
evil dead aspect of it but as Joe is talking about the opening scene of this and as I'm looking at
the Wikipedia and being reminded of this movie it this guy written addition to a humor problem
Perkins really has a plotting problem yeah he he does not land these stories before he starts
shooting long legs was such a riveting sounds of the lambs rip for about half its running time
and we haven't had a lot of good sounds of the lambs rips we used to get them all the time
but I was like well fucking hey this is awesome and at the halfway point almost exactly that movie lost
its way big time as yeah and the monkey is the same so the monkey is the same um go yeah
the starts I'm sorry but I'm sorry sorry sorry sorry but here's the one more thing I want to say
about this opening scene because I I'm confused again why does Adam Scott bring in the thing to
return it and then blast it with a flamethrower why not blast it with a flamethrower why are you
returning it I don't know it's killed people you know and you're like I'm gonna take it back with
a receipt there's no logic to it even in even with the thing where where the drumstick hits inside
the shop yeah as the movie unfolds the insinuation is that he would have had to wind it again
because that's the only way the drumstick will hit the drum as you have to wind it yeah then why the
fuck did who just died and why would he wind it again if he knew that this thing was bad news or
what I don't know man it then then starts before the movie kicks in starts the heaviest the heaviest
voiceover and again narration where I'm like oh you've got to be kidding there's no need for this
just complete voiceover every fucking scene with the with the so it so it starts with the these two
twin boys well and my question with the voiceover is were we given the voiceover because the studio
said I can't make heads of tails of this fucking probably probably so um anyway the twin boys
amidst voiceover from one of them at an older age are in their closet or in the closet in their
father's room they find out that we we learn the dad has left um they go into the closet of their
dad's things and they find a box containing what the monkey again I got a problem here the thing
they talk about these are things your father found in his travels in the military yeah they
pulled the monkey out it clearly looks like something from Asia the way it's packaged in everything
yes you know like wait a minute so this way he got this in Asia but he tried to bring it to a
pawn shop but the but wait no the pawn shop said no return so we got it at a pawn shop but it was
packaged like this from a fucking pawn shop wait why is it what the fuck is going on right so
whatever that these are just detail things you can get past them I guess but um and the plot is the
boys find the monkey they play with it they learn quickly that if you wind it up somebody will die
uh and you have no control over somebody dying who you and despite who you want it to kill
uh they aim it well I'll get to that I I've got so many issues with this movie I I wrote all this down
um where is it I already mentioned the flame thrower bit the second death in this thing is as
Pat mentioned the they're at the Habachi thing and the babysitter yeah the babysitter is killed
because the Habachi guy swings his knife and accidentally hits her throat now a throat slit
believable full decapitation you're supposed to believe that a guy swinging a chef's knife
that barely grazes the woman's throat yeah it's enough to fully decapitate through the neckbone
everything her it is so fucking stupid okay this is what we're gonna do we're just gonna do
we're dick okay fine then then they go now you want to talk about humor issues they go to the
the they show the funeral of the babysitter the priest gets up and in front of an entire congregation
looks in the coffin at the woman in the state of the woman and goes oh fuck yeah guys what are we doing
here what is this this is fucking stupid this is dumb that scene is followed by the mom with the
two boys sitting in the cemetery doing this bleak monologue about death like we're all gonna die
with it this thing is trying so hard so but the time I got to this scene I was like okay all this
movie is gonna be is the crazy deaths we're dealing with Saul and this is this would drive me I
saw many of the Saul sequels in the theater and it drove me crazy because every time I watched one
I would go this movie is fucking stupid it's written terribly the humor that they're going for sucks
the shocks they're going for suck all this is is the fucking loony tunes contraptions and people
are so dumb they sit there and they go oh shit look at that her fucking eyelids got ripped off
or whatever happens and then they go that was awesome and it's like it wasn't awesome there were
few scenes in it that you thought were cool but like oh my god man dear god the mom saying to
the kids when when when the kid goes at one point there's a 10 year old kid he goes mom were you in
my room she goes I haven't been in there since I found that stiff sock this is what you said your
10 year old kid is how you talk to your 10 year old kid okay well Joe and I'm telling you as a guy
who's written five billion of them that's a multi cam joke like that is a that is a family sitcom
multi-com Joe that stiff sock I found here there's a lot of that there you know forget
you know a lot of Marvel movies for example have a comedy problem but and I like this more than
the Marvel shit don't get me wrong and I didn't really like the movie a lot but he doesn't or
Perkins clearly it doesn't seem to get that like you do have to sort of pick at a certain point
you know comedy horror is very very difficult you can do it if you're taking both things pretty
seriously he is treating the comedy as if it's the naked gun it's I see his treat he's treating
the horror like they like the evil dead and it's like okay you're doing this part right yeah you're
going crazily over the top with the violence and look a lot of these kills were really inventive and
fun for me a lot more fun than than the sock kills some of them were great some of them really were
and the and the the shocked laugh and oh my god and everything from the audience was was warranted
a lot of the time but I was surprised at how much this was just a stringing together of the kills
then in the end in the home stretch like the last 30 minutes that's what I actually saw this with
Pinkstone in Atlanta yeah I've been talking to him a lot about it I could not follow the fucking thing
when they bring in this other character this like bumbling cop here wasn't there like a bumbling
cop character no hold on let me I'll bring us there I know you're talking about the guy in the back
seat of the car yeah no no and just like what are we watching I I couldn't follow it at the
beginning of this thing too they want to show that one of the kid one of the two brothers one's a
deck and one's like a nerd the nerd one is getting bullied by an all-girl gang yeah who hang out in
the boys bathroom for some reason yeah guys get a fucking handle on this fucking gender shit please
please if you're gonna make the bullies all girls don't have them hanging out in the all boys
bathroom how about that for starters because it takes place in 1999 so so there is no unisex
bathrooms yet so so fucking right at properly if you're gonna do it please and also I don't even
know what the statement is supposed to be there no boy ever gets bullied by an all-girl gang
so if you're trying to say that this is a form of female empowerment you're failing because
what all you're saying to the audience is this kid such a pussy girls can beat him up yeah it
doesn't work it doesn't make any sense stop enough it's stupid the the but again another cheap
attempted humor that just doesn't fucking work there's another scene where they went what their
mom dies because the kid winds up the monkey and he wants it to kill his asshole brother and instead
it kills the mom the the they then have to go live with their aunt and uncle who's where their uncle
tells them as ten year old that they're swingers their uncle played by Osgood Perkins yeah these are
all just terrible gag jokes that have nothing to do with anything yeah Elijah Wood turns up at
one point oh wow playing that same these characters are written like eastbound and down and it's
like guys you can't do this in a whole then it doesn't make me take the horror part seriously it's
too crazy it's too fucking crazy a hundred percent when they go over to Elijah Woods you know we're
doing a Tim Robinson sketch you know it's like that you're adding in a comedic character for the
comedy that that scene had no basis in the plot that I can recall he's a care a big comedy
character suddenly given valuable screen time in a movie that hasn't landed its dramatic beads
properly there's a wild Chris Cuomo cameo which I didn't understand at all that I miss what what
happened there he's just wanted that when they show the montage of people getting killed because of
the monkey yeah there's a guy I'm I would bet my life savings it's Chris Cuomo uh you know it's
weird um I got here's but let's get to the real so anyway eventually it flashes forward
to when the brother is in the monkey you're right to when the brothers are grown up
and it's they put they throw the monkey down the well after their mom dies and say nobody can
ever find this thing yeah they grow up and clearly now the nerd brother has a son
and an estranged wife uh that he wants to protect at all costs he's terrified this monkey will come
back and kill them excuse me and he hasn't talked to his asshole brother in in years um so this is
the second half of the movie in this and I won't go through every beat but this is where the biggest
problem with the movie is the it is very established in the second half of the movie that if this monkey
were to turn up again all you have to do is not wind the fucking key in the back of the monkey and
then it can't kill anybody yeah yet there's this convoluted fucking plot about how the twin the
asshole brother shows up again and is obsessed with finding the monkey because he's going to make
his nerd brother take care of it to make sure nobody winds it again but the nerd brother doesn't
want to take care of it because he's afraid of it and then it turns out that the asshole brother
actually doesn't want the nerd brother to have it he wants the monkey for himself why so he can
wind it up and kill the brother because he realizes the brother wound it up it had their mother killed
and he hopes that now the monkey will kill the brother and his son and and and he tracks the
monkey down he spends his life trying to find this thing he finally finds it and realizes it's
that it's where it's at his aunt's house who dies uh the the aunt that had to raise them after his
mom died he finds out it's there and it's going to be sold at a yard sale somehow he figures out it's
going to be sold at a yard sale or a state sale and instead of just going to buy the thing
himself where nobody would recognize him in a million years yeah uh he sends he hires an idiot
kid to go get the monkey there it is so the kid goes and buys the monkey it's the kid from Halloween
ends yeah as soon as you see him you hate him because he's the character that ruined Halloween
anyway he goes and buys the monkey and then he doesn't want to give them he gives the monkey over to
the asshole brother but then he wants it back why because it reminded him of his dad which they
never explain it makes no sense and the kid not knowing the monkey has any powers
becomes so obsessed with the monkey because it reminds him of his dad he holds up the
nerd brother at gunpoint with his kid and says you're going to now go to your brother's house to
get me the monkey this thing is so fucking convoluted it makes you I'm confused by what you're saying
it makes no sense I wash it and was confused and now I'm confused by your recap like I'm they bring
in that guy when they bring in that guy the kid from Halloween who I guess must was he disguised
as a cop or that I just imagine a cop uniform I maybe I just imagined it I don't know but um
yeah he's in the backseat of the car and he sends those wasps
do you remember that he winds the key and then they the key gets wound up and a bunch of
an a wasp nest opens up and yes the entire nest fly into the kid's mouth it's mouth yeah that's how
he dies and it looks it looks for a movie that did great practical effects up to that point it looks
so fake and computerized and it's just so dumb yeah it's really wild that that that area there
where he's in the backseat and the wasp are flying into his mouth and I I just felt like
this movie has completely lost its way to what to the extent though this was pretty
long I mean I don't know which movie was done first they came out within a month of each other
but like this guy does not have the cart cart a blanche where somebody shouldn't have stepped forward
and said hey the last third of this movie makes zero sense I haven't even gotten to the fucking
pale horseman oh okay so yeah throughout the movie they keep making right I guess they I
I needed clarification from pinkstone on this oh he did well he didn't know when I saw it with him
we were both like what the fuck was that oh he told me he did know but you didn't know and he
was like no they kept referencing the pale horseman throughout the movie and he was like he was like
saying how you not in a shitty way but he was like I think Pat missed the reference he was saying
it was dumb but he was like I was stupid no he didn't say he was stupid he was saying the the death
showing up at the end was dumb yeah plus but he said you were like what was that and he was like oh
they kept referencing the pale rider of death throughout the movie and then he actually shows up at
the end and I did the same thing I go he goes wait do you see this thing at the end and I go what
was that I don't understand and he goes pat didn't catch it either they kept referencing
throughout the movie the pale rider of death that was death showing up at the very end of the movie
and I go that's not in the story why would you show literally show debt that was insane well
totally it's like when he said that it wasn't like I was like oh I never heard them say that I
remembered references to the pale horseman it that doesn't explain the leap to no
an actual physical embodiment of a pale horseman walking right yeah it's like what a movie about
a killer monkey that you twist a key and it kills people where your rules are already so fucking
convoluted that two guys who watch horror movies for a podcast couldn't follow it by the way what
what are you what are you doing like why are you bringing in a ghost horse into that by the way
in this finale the brother winds them the evil brother winds the monkey up
it ends up killing it does like a drum roll and you're like okay I guess it's going to kill a lot
of people now and then you see a plane crash happen yeah you're like okay that was the drum roll
yeah then it does one final hit which ends up getting the asshole brother killed
then the nerd brother and his son leave intact they've got the monkey they got to make sure nobody
winds it again and as they drive down the road you're seeing people everywhere dying and terrible
things happening whatever and you go but that's not how the monkey works it's done being wound
everybody that would have died would have died within the confines of the last drum hits it did
now it's just like it can just kill people whenever it feels then what's the point of not
winding this fucking movie sucks it sucks it is the equivalent of an 80s Stallone action movie where all
you get the only payoff are like bad one liners and cheap kills whatever and big explosions
are they fun to watch sure are some of them creative absolutely do they land in this the movie land
in those moments fine but the movie as from a narrative standpoint is fucking terrible from a
character standpoint is fucking terrible it is yet another one of these god damn Stephen King
adaptations where the story is so thin in the fucking short story and they've tried to now expand it
into something so much bigger and it's like then expand it into something bigger but that doesn't
mean making it confusing this is a pretty simple fucking concept guys yeah I mean it could have gone
a million different ways especially if you're gonna be here that much from the story the monkey gets
into the wrong hands whatever it is it just doesn't take off it doesn't make sense I have never
written even a comedy script where the producer didn't say to me hey I had a few questions for you
why if he does this here does this happen later you know it's it's part of the notes process
and I do not understand how producers would not have said hey none of this makes sense in the
home stretch because I also don't think there's any I don't think it's me missing stuff for some
failure on my part which is sometimes the case don't get me wrong but I really felt that this was
just bad screenwriting yep the guy is an undeniably talented director and I have found something to
admire in every movie he's made even the real small low budget stuff I really liked black
coats daughter for example which is a no-budget movie but the guy's gonna keep getting bigger and
bigger budgets and at some point he's gonna have to bring in another screenwriter like you had
source material here this wasn't an original and you you blew it like for me I liked it more than
Joe I thought that the violence and the kills were a blast you know almost across the board I like
a big gory like that's crazy look at the blunt the brains flying everywhere I like that shit but
God did you have to let it go this out of control in the end like not only did I not care how it
ended I was angry at the end that's how badly the story was resolved and it's really frustrating
because I like the guy's shit like I'm I'm there with him you know for like half the time I like
Theo James I like the kids I like Tatiana Mazzlani I like Adam Scott at the beginning of it I'm like
okay like I'm I'm with this thing you know I came to play but you got to do your part too you know
shit blowing up for two hours does not a movie make hugs down for the long it's barely down
because there is stuff to like but it's down and it's so it's a sloppier movie than long legs
and which was fucking sloppy yeah it was same thing confusing convoluted two-mitch shit going on
such a simple premise and they just ruined it my hog is down hard enough to hit that drum
to kill to kill a love one inadvertently yeah folks we'll be back uh second half of the month
well that we are in the second half but we'll so we'll be back very soon with uh an episode of
apartment 2a and rosemary's baby and uh we don't know what the fourth episode possibly maybe
we'll do that rhamony episode uh as the fourth this month uh we keep teasing that uh
but uh anyway folks thanks for tuning in uh we'll see you next time and we'll see you and hell