Hey yeah there you go it's your on it got a bowling
there. You got a bonus hat right in your gooch. It's a bonus in your ray. All right.
It is. It's your bonus app. We got a big one today. We are, as I guess we are going
to announce, so am I as well tell you, but I think we're making a change. We're going to take
a little hiatus for my nuptials and my honeymoon. We're going to come back hot with season
five season five. Somebody pointed out to us that season four is now at like 53 episodes,
which I guess means it's been a full year, but that's great. And I quite frankly couldn't
be happier to have left. So this is the last episode of the month and the final free episode
yes, is the infinity where episode. So I'm very happy and classic and a good entertainment
fashion to leave our listeners with a cliffhanger. Will they return to this questionable controversial
and divisive format? Some people have did some people hate it. That's, at any time we do
anything. That's what it is. And that's what democracy is, people. But a lot of folks
were like, they should be done with superhero movies. I saw that a lot. And then a lot of
people who's feeling seem genuinely hurt because they they are like, now I can't watch these
things that I the only thing I love, I can't watch anymore. And then some people were like,
because we ruin superhero movies, right, which means you might not love them enough folks.
And then some people are like, I love this. This is fun for me. You know, yeah, people have
different strokes. Some fans said they enjoyed that it was, they said it reminded them of
them trying to explain a movie to their friends. Yes. Which is why I thought people would like
it because people who have often complimented us and said, you know what I like about the
show? I feel like I'm watching a movie with two friends that keep getting distracted. Yes.
So why would a description of the movie be any different? No clue. Anybody that wants to hear
me do a point by point, 100 % accurate description of the Avengers movie. I mean, you get too much
time on your hands. Well, across the board, everyone said Joe was so wrong about every aspect
of the Marvel universe. And I don't know if that's true or not because I don't care. But
I that was a that was across the board. People thought you were very wrong about a lot of
things. You know what I'd like to do? No, I got to be honest with you. What I'd like to
do. And I'm not going to hold you to this because then you got to watch the movie. I'd love
for you to watch that movie. And you tell me how fucking wrong it was. I was. I wasn't
that wrong. I will. I glazed over and botched things for comedy effect. But overall, I told
you the goddamn movie. I mean, I didn't make anything up. Sure. Anyway, you know, you're all
taken thanks to seriously. Let's be real. We're going to get into these questions because
I don't know if we have four hours of questions. I don't know if we have 20 minutes of questions.
But we're going to get going. And if we've done the question before, it's going to be politely
passed on. You know that, folks. And we'll do as many of these as we can. I mean, if it
gets to a certain point where it's ridiculous, we can't yes, we can't do all of them. But
we're going to try. Yeah. I mean, we want to give you a nice long app because we are taking
a little time off. But, but for real folks, we haven't taken time off in a very long
time. But there was a period where this podcast, we do like one March first. And then the next
one would be like late July. And honestly, it wasn't a bad time. I got a lot more work done.
Edmund Agabo asks, have you ever thought, and this is a very interesting question. Have you
ever thought about working together on an independent project? No rules, no holds barred
anything. Joe's. And the truth is, with no details, Joe and I have been talking about
doing a little project, perhaps. Yes. That's all that is true. Can't tell you anything.
But we spent a little time on it. That is true. It may or may not come to fruition. Look,
I like that he did specify, you know, no rules. Like, yeah, you know, like, like this thing
is just burdened down with right legislation. Sure. I was sure. Anyway, I think you just
meant no network interference. Hey, we don't have any. Yeah, at the moment. The, no, that's
fine. Yeah. No, I appreciate the question. Yeah, we, we do talk about that stuff. Yes. Yeah.
I mean, a big part of it, honestly, of us not working together beyond this is it would
kill me to lose a friendship with Joe. And kill me. You know, I imagine day four of
working intensely on any project, the friendship would be done. The friendship would be done.
Yeah, it's, but it would be lovely. And we did. Well, yeah, we worked on a show, but you
want to talk about rules. There were a few rules on that show. A little interference, but
that was also a good scenario at the, the sitcom because you were over in the wing doing
the writing. I was down on the floor. Right. And then you swoop in and say a thing and then
you bleed. You know, it wasn't like we were like sitting at a desk together. Yeah. My buddy
Mike at our bachelor party really made me laugh. He was my bachelor party. He was like telling,
in the process of telling Joe that he liked his character was excited to see all the shitty
gets into in future episodes. And Joe's nod in his head like, yeah, yeah, man, yeah, man.
And I was like, you know, the Joe never going to be on the show again. He was washing on the
app or something. Ken Hanley says two part question. One, who do you think you are? And two,
how dare you? Ken really hated that last episode. Ken did. I screen shot at Ken's blistering
shots at Joe on the last one. Couldn't even make it through blistering. Yeah. Why did he
pick on just me? I think people like me more. And also too, I'm just going to throw that out there
for anybody that's sided with Ken and who also said that I was way off base. And Pat's usually
the voice reason. Ken once said on Facebook that Halloween three is the best Halloween and that
it can't be argued. He actually said that well, it could be argued by everyone. He gave his order
of Halloween movies. His number one was Halloween three. And he said, this cannot be argued.
I remember them. So I love you, Ken. But, you know, let's not act like we're all, you know,
glass houses, baby, glass houses. I love the passion of our fans. I love that we pissed them off
some time. It's all good to me. Yeah. And I know that there is a new fan fiction about you and I.
That's apparently lengthy. And, and spectacular. And I have not had time to read it. I believe
that's your boy Scott Patten. I want to thank Scott for writing it and sending it in. I, I have
not had a chance to read it either. It's 18 pages. Yeah, I mean, I've got a little bit going on.
And it's the continuation of the last one, I think. I'm very excited to read this thing. And in fact,
let me give another shout out to, is this him Tim? Yeah, Tim paints the world on Instagram. I don't
know what is, what's his real name, though? Tim paints the world. Tim Timothy Atkins from
Tim from Sweden, who sent us a DVD copy of a dark place, the comedy show with Matt Barry. And,
oh, nice. A few other folks from England, but we weren't able to watch it because we had a,
we neither of us had a region -free DVD player, but, but it was a very thoughtful thing. So thank you for
doing that. Can's actual question. What 80s film property would you most want to adapt into a hit
YouTube red series? And, you know, I know, I guess we're not doing movie corner, but my dear friends,
John Herwoods, Hayden Schlossberg, Josh Eald created and ran Cobra Kai on YouTube red. I went to
the premiere. I watched all 10. They did a great job. It's a very entertaining show. I look forward
to seeing it. But what 80s film property would you most want to adapt into a hit series? That's a great,
like, I guess they mean update Cobra Kai style. And I would say,
oh boy. There's, there's so many good options. I'm surprised they ain't cracked open labyrinth.
Oh, that would be great. I mean, they are bringing back Dark Crystal, which is exciting. Yes.
Has a series? Yeah, Netflix series. Okay. I'll tell you mine. And I just thought of it right now.
Yeah. I think this is a golden idea. Go ahead. Weird science. Weird science. The boys
now middle -aged men meet up. Life hasn't turned out the way they wanted it to. They're estranged from
their wives, kids, whatever it is. Sure. And they try to create perfect middle -aged companions for
themselves, including children. Well, you can definitely get Anthony Michael Hall and you can definitely
get McKenzie, whatever his name is. I don't know if you can. That guy won't ever do like he never
does any of the bonus stuff for you know, like on the weird science DVD, Michael, Anthony Michael
Hall says like McKenzie, wherever you are, yeah, you know, like it was fun, like, but nobody,
I don't know what he seems to have disappeared. My buddy has a great idea with the weird science franchise
that I almost just casually dropped. I'm going to let it go. But okay, I hope he, I hope he can make it
out. Does it relate to mine at all? No. All right. Well, good. Then we can both have our own.
Great. Great question. Ken, Ken has another question. The only person I'll allow to have more than
one is Ken him. Best haunted house haunted attraction experience. Universal Hollywood hard nights,
the exorcist house. Okay. And the crampus house somehow was potentially scarier than the exorcist house.
They made a crampus, the movie house. Yeah. At Universal. Yeah. Halloween and hard nights.
Movie made 13 million dollars. Well, that fucking haunted house was scary as shit, man. That big gas
crampus coming out of a closet. That is not, all right. It's not not scary. I despise haunted houses.
I once went to a Queen's Stonehenge show where they were supposed to have this like, you know, like
get your blood and heart check before you go in haunted house and people were puking and shit.
That's not for me. I don't do that shit. I remember when I was a kid, maybe five, six, seven,
my dad took me to a haunted house in the lake of the Ozarks. And when you stepped on the mat,
it just blew air at you. And I don't even think it was an attraction. It was just like cold air came at
you. And I started hysterically crying. And since I didn't, I don't think I had seen any of the
attractions yet. So that's not for me. Never was. Also, like, you're giving people chainsaws
to run at you. What if they're mentally disturbed? It's just some guy who's like 18 who signs a form.
I've often wondered how nothing ever goes wrong. Because one of the things they did at hard nights was
the park, the theme of the actual park, like, just when you were walking around was the purge.
Yeah. So you had people like dressed in like steam punk outfits running up to you, like waving
like knives in your, I mean, obviously they're, they're rubber or whatever. But I'm like, you could
still poke somebody's fucking eye out by accident. Like, they were getting really close. I'm like,
I don't understand how there's never an accident. Nobody ever like freaks and punches one of these
people because they can't, I'm sure it's happened. You know, I saw somebody get their hand hit
because they grabbed the side of the haunted hay ride in Griffith Park, which is fun, actually.
But some guy jumps up and grabs the side and got reached over and bashed his fingers. You can tell
the guy was really hurt. I love a haunted hay ride. I'd like to do that. We should. It's very fun.
They have it every year. Amanda Liebson inquires, what actor or actress would play you in the inevitable
docu -drama of this podcast? Well, mine's obviously Paul Giamatti. I mean, there's no other actor
that could. Yeah, I think it's got to be. Play me. And for mine, I don't know. I mean, the only,
the only name I've gotten on a regular basis through the years is Timothy Hutton.
Timothy Hutton. But he's not funny. I'd like to see a young Martin Mall play you.
Marty Mall. Yeah. Yeah, I don't know. I'm going to say Emma Stone. I mean, we want this thing
to have good box office. All right. And we both have Reddish here, which I can admit now. There's
a little red to my hair. Okay. Okay. Can I ask a third question? Not worth pushing it, Ken,
but here we go. Most inappropriate time, you've laughed during a public film screening or Q &A.
I once laughed really loud during a movie about human slave trafficking when the lead character kept
yelling, my son over and over. And I suspect everyone has had one of those moments. Mine 1 ,000 %
was secaria, which is a movie I loved. But when I find dark shit very, very funny, it's some sort of
weird coping mechanism or something. But when Del Toro is calmly detailing how he's murdered the
guy's family. Right. Or he's going to murder the family. I don't forget exactly what it was. I
couldn't stop laughing. I just thought it was so bleak and funny that like sometimes really dark
makes me laugh the most. Sure. I don't have one that I can recall. I will say this though. And I wasn't
laughing. But when I saw Gran Torino in the theater, yes, I was confused. I couldn't tell if they
were trying to be funny or not. Sure. Because I told you my story of Philip Simmer Hoffman howling
laughing throughout Gran Torino. Oh, you did say that didn't you? Yeah, I was can howling laughing.
I was watching. I was like, this sounds like it like the way your like uncle would pull you aside
and tell you like an inappropriate jokes at a party. Like is this supposed to be funny? It would
be as a wild tone to it. I don't know. I mean, it's got the kid from the sandlot as a priest,
the fat kid. I mean, I don't know what's going on with that move. I want to see it again. I would like
to revisit it because I've only heard people either say it's terrible or it's amazing. I didn't like it,
but I'd like to revisit it. I don't know anyone who thought it was amazing, but I watched it with a
laugh track by one of our most acclaimed actors PSH. There were numbers for why it was going to be
the final dirty Harry movie, which would have been pretty cool. That would have been awesome.
And I still think they should do it. Yeah, you know, it would have been cool to see like retired
dirty Harry and then he dies like an honorable death after he's kind of a slightly crooked cop
all those years. I agree. Now, wasn't dirty grand Paul the last of the dirty Harry movies? No.
It's not out yet. Apparently, it's called dirty Sanchez. Okay. Okay. And it's just him
in an old age home wiping his feces on people's faces. Right before we tape this, Joe and I
watched a video, you can find it online. It's a woman complaining about her donut order at Tim Horton's
donuts. And after about 30 seconds, she's had enough. She leans against a wall, shits on the floor,
picks up her shit, throws it at the teenage donut clerk, wipes her ass with an napkin and throws
the shit staying napkin at the guy. It's not pixelated in any way. Now you can watch this online,
Google it if you dare. One of the best things I've ever seen. It's great. How does that tape get out?
How does the manager or Tim Horton's go? We're going to release this to the public. I'm glad he did.
That's all I know. I'm glad he did too, but I'm just saying I know. That cannot comply with
with franchise standards. No, no. It could be a cop took it. I mean, who knows?
Sometimes cops look at these things and they slip it to a friend and they don't show this to anybody
and then it's on the internet. Who knows? Fixing, you know, you're in a menace to society thing. Yes.
Brooke Adams inquires. Maybe this has been discussed before, but top three favorite bands?
I guess that's got to be an all -time question. I mean, that's that's difficult.
I don't mind. Go for it. Fumantiu, Motorhead, Bad Religion. Wow. All right. That's my three.
You like a hard rock and tune. I do. Yeah, and I like a sing song and tune.
I find that both bands will bring you both. Okay. A stone groove, if you will.
I'm going to say and don't hold me to this, but I'm going to say Elvis Costello on the attractions.
I'm going to say Queens of the Stone Age and I'm going to say
Pixies. Yep. They're all great. Samantha Lippard inquires. Creepiest encounter with a fan.
Coolest encounter with a fan. Can be fans of the podcast or just y 'all's larger body of work.
You know, all my I recognize yous come from Vine and they're always very young girls and it
honestly, they're not. It's just a girl saying, Hey, I like your stuff or whatever, but
it always felt creepy because I felt like they're dads or something. And one time these two very
young girls sat at my table in Vegas. They were like, are you having like are you partying here?
Like we should hang out. Right. I was like, are you guys even 18? Like what are we talking about?
Right. That was mildly creepy, but it's nice to be recognized at our level where you're getting
recognized once a bloom wound. It's nice. Yeah. Yeah. Drunk history once in a while.
Been had any. I haven't any creepy ones. I've had ones where like a guy. It's
usually a guy who's too drunk to understand when the conversation is over. Sure.
That's pretty nuts. I wish you though, right? Yeah. Yeah. That's me following them home.
So when did you first start to like me? Yes. But it's usually I'm approached
oddly approach, but stand up more by men and podcasts more by women.
It's almost exclusively one or the other. Yeah. But it's the guys that don't know when to quit
usually, but but not all of them. Just some of them. Sure. And what about that period of time where
Robert De Niro was a knife salesman. And he was sort of your biggest fan and started kind of
honing in on you and your family. Well, that's back when I played Major League Baseball.
It was a long time ago and I can't believe that was a movie. I'd love to see that again.
And he worked as a knife salesman for like three months leading up to the movie.
De Niro worked as a knife salesman. Yeah. They should have been coming with cuts on his hands.
I mean, the movie made sense to me at the time. I was. It was decent. I never saw it. But I was like,
oh, yeah, it's like a taxi driver kind of thing. That was decent. I never saw it.
Gary Myron asks, who was Joe's biggest musical influence for Demon Riot?
Oh, wow. Thank you for listening. A few people have heard it.
Honestly, Tom Weitz was the biggest influence. I wanted to I was trying to make songs that sounded like
you know, if Tom Weitz used like electronic instruments like his catch your songs,
that's basically what what I wanted it to sound like. So Tom Weitz mainly.
Okay. Cody McNair asks, if either of you could bring back any cancelled TV show,
what would it be? Pat, you can't choose your own. Thank you for that. Sure.
You know, I mean, the ones I truly love, I would be too scared to have them back and have them suck.
You know, I don't need to see Seinfeld now. Well, it's a cancelled though. He said,
well, yeah, cancelled. All right. That's true. You know, we're getting a lot of these like
are we get we got arrested development, although, you know, I'm not sure what that was. I think the
new season is supposed to be better. Um, cancelled show. Joe, you got one? I'm going to go with designated
survivor. Uh, you watch designated survivor. I don't watch it. But I read yesterday it was cancelled.
It's my dad's favorite show. He has talked to me about it endlessly. Is it key for that one?
Yeah. Okay. And when I saw it was cancelled out loud by myself, I went, oh no, I really feel sorry
for my dad. Sure. He loves the show. When I went to, um, uh, I did a WGA one day showrunner training
course because I had never run a show and I was like, I should do this. And the guy who did most of
the talking was, uh, I believe the showrunner of designated survivor. And he must, it's what it's
what people do because your life becomes the show. And you forget that most people don't watch the show.
But he would just say like, I mean, you all saw this episode, right? Of designated where we were. And
you're like, no, no one has seen designated survivor. But it was, it was funny to me. Your dad would have
been able to answer. Um, yeah, if I could bring back anything, you know, I can't remember the last
time a show's cancellation infuriated me. I, I don't know. You know, what I really liked if I'm being
honest recently was love. I could have watched six more seasons of love. Most of my friends hate it.
There's something so pleasant about it. And I would watch it all 10 in a day. It's the only show I
binged. It is cancelled. Yeah. I loved love. They got three seasons on Netflix. Have you
ain't seen it? Check it out. Man tons of people have issues with it. I like. And lady dynamite guy
cancelled too. It was an interesting show. I understand the cancellation. That was too weird for
even Netflix, I think haters back off got canceled. That never seen it. That lady's got like, she's
like one of the biggest YouTube stars out there. It's like, I assume they didn't follow her to the
thing. I mean, if they were getting the numbers, they wouldn't cancel it. I assure you. Yeah. Anyway,
okay. This one's a little, I'm going to edit this one a little Scott Patton asks, Pat, whatever
happened to your writing partnership. How do you feel about writing partnerships in general?
Yeah, I used to have a writing partner. The shitty thing about it is you split your money in half.
Your every week your paycheck is cut in half. And eventually, that gets to you.
Having a writing partner can be very helpful in the early days of your partnership.
Help you navigate it. It's a terrible brutal business. It helps to have somebody to talk about it
with. So I'll go for it. But, you know, in my case, I felt I could do it alone. And, you know,
there you go. Mike Madrigal asks, Mike, go to Mr. Suit Records when you're in Lancaster, Pennsylvania.
Go to Mr. Suit Records. Who do I talk to about getting a reboot of cold check the night stocker,
starring the boys, follow up. Who should play cold check and who should play the editor,
Tony Vincenza? I've never seen the show. But you can talk to everyone in the world and they will
all tell you no. But Joe, what do you think? I think I'm without a doubt the grumpy,
hard -boiled editor. Sure. I think you're you're more the frisky detective. Frisky sounds
hard, but, you know, Tony Vincenza. Yeah, nobody's buying me as a Tony Vincenza. That's for sure.
They did reboot cold check at one point with I'm going to have to look it up. But cold check was
rebooted at one point to to to to to no success really. But I actually agree, Mike, you uh that's
interesting that you asked that question because I recently bought the cold check double feature
DVD. And I was as I was watching it, I was like, why is this not a fucking show? Like this could be
a show now. Yeah. And you know, somebody should remake this. And then I looked it up and it was
like, oh, somebody did remake it. And it didn't work. So they're probably not going to remake it again.
I'm trying to find let's see legacy. No, come on. Yeah, here we go. 2005 television series
Stewart Townsend played cold check. Okay. Who also played Dorian Gray in the League of Extraordinary
Gentlemen. Yeah, I remember him. I think he was in Dracula 2000 too. He's from Dublin. He was
married to Charlize Theron. Nice job, dude. But anyway, he was in the Tully by the way.
The interesting flick. It looks pretty good. I mean, it's I liked it. I like a lot of uh
rightman stuff. It seems it seems to be sort of an amalgam of his other movies. Yeah, it is. But it
had a really interesting third act development, I will say. Rightman. Rightman's movies feel like they
inspired like the Hulu boom or like I agree. The white people having issues. I'll tell you my one
issue with Tully. They have Ron Livingston, the guy from office space. Yep. And Mark Duploss. Right.
And Duploss is playing Tully's brother. Livingston is playing her husband. So there are scenes where
they're like standing next to each other. They look like identical twins. And they're not they're
not brothers. It was insane. Yeah. Yeah. When I saw the trailer, I remember thinking, oh, Mark
Duploss is in this and then going, oh, wait, no, it was Ron Livingston. Yeah. And then at the end,
realizing it was both when they're next to each other. I mean, my eyes were going back and forth.
I couldn't tell the two apart. Uh, Mitch Oliver asks, who would you rather take to prom Betty
or Veronica? Uh, the dark cared one. I think it's Betty. No, it's Veronica.
Veronica. Okay. I think I'm Veronica too. Interestingly, and I just texted Joe this. I was asked
if I would have any interest in running a new Archie cartoon. In the same world where we have Riverdale,
an Archie cartoon. And then my agent sent this to me and was like, they, they, they, they'd like you to
have a pretty vast knowledge of the Archie verse. And also some experience and animation. I was
like, I don't really have either. And I'm not sure I can pursue this. If you want me to like create
the Archie world, you know, I was actually happy to hear that they're doing a cartoon. I think
it's depressing that the only iteration of Archie comics out there right now is this fucking murder
sex romp. I mean, it's, it's a good show. But I think there should be the light side of it too.
I can't believe Archie has been around this long. It's four teenagers hanging out. I mean,
I don't understand what why people return to this, but here we are. You got me. Lorenz Bunganiers asks
to Joe. I don't know if this is okay to ask, but since you've mentioned it on the emotional hangs
podcast, and since I'm just really curious about it, I was wondering if you've had any more
sexual experiences with transgenders. I have not. But thank you for asking. I'm not, I'm not
adverse to it. You know, you know, we'll just get him in the right time. Approach him. Ask. Yeah.
And thank you, by the way, to all of you, telling me, congrats, and enjoy my honey moon and all that.
I'm not reading it, but I appreciate it. Thank you. That's nice. Steven Rees asks,
have or will you and Joe ever collaborate on a movie or a TV script? That was kind of the first
question. Hope so. Michael Rose asked, did you guys like fire in the sky? And do you think moving
violations would have been a hit with Bill Murray instead of John? I remember moving violations,
and I remember it being kind of funny, but I was a kid. I tried to revisit it recently. Yeah.
It certainly would have been a bigger hit with Bill Murray. Yeah. I would imagine Bill got the first
offer before they went to John. And I used to love fire in the sky. It's a terrifying and really
kind of naturalistic, almost alien sequences of some of the scariest things I've ever seen. Yeah,
great, great, moving. DB Swaney, baby. Who else know? Huh? He's a nut. DB Swaney. We also got a
rubber Patrick in there. Yeah. Playing like that, like a hillbilly guy with a pickup truck.
Do you know speaking of DB Swaney? I don't even know if I told you this, but
your competition for the role of the beloved role of Gary on CBS's Living Biblically was DB
Swaney. He came in an audition. He had giant button chops. He was funny, but it just the star of fire
in the sky and the star of the cutting edge. But he came in and it was a funny audition. It was too
big, but it was funny. And then at the end, he was showing a picture of this girl on his phone.
And started humping his phone. And it was just kind of like too much. DB, but he was great. And
I later had dinner with him. And he drank a bunch and told hilarious stories. He was a nice man.
Starting hanging out with DB Swaney. Yes. Douglas Wood asks, what is your choice for your
unlimited last meal if and when you're about to be executed? Always a reliably fascinating question,
a window into people's lives. I know dessert for me is a full sheet cake. Finally, I would be
freed to eat the sheet cake. And then hopefully I would just, oh, I think we talked about this
once. And you said you wanted to eat so much that you shat to such a degree that the pigs who
juiced you had to clean up your shit. I think we had that discussion. Yeah, I'd like that. I'm going to go
you know, probably from a place that closed here in Los Angeles. My favorite dish at my favorite
restaurant was the Massaman Curry at Red Corner Asia Thai. That followed by a full sheet cake.
I'm going seafood buffet. The one that we go to? No, no, good one. Okay, like unlimited lobster
clams. What do they call it? Steam clams. Yeah. Mussels in a red sauce, crab legs, the big ones.
Yeah. All right. And then a big, then I also have a sheet cake for dessert, but mine will be chocolate.
Now, how about we get a half and half sheet cake? So we're not glutton and they juice us right next
to each other. All right. I'm going to do it where you hold hands. David Belinger asks, what are your
favorite movie soundtrack albums? Terrific question. Oh, man. Mine is hands. My number one is
hands down the judgment night soundtrack. I thought you might say that. It's a great soundtrack.
I love it. It's never gotten old to me. Okay. I love it. It's great. Followed closely by the
trespass soundtrack, which is one of the great hip -hop compilations of all time. It gets almost zero
recognition. Cool movie too. I would say Boogie Nights is a big and the cassette I listened to
while mowing lawns for several years was the American graffiti soundtrack. I also used to look,
that's like, you know, 40 great oldies. And I used to listen to the Kirkland soundtrack a lot,
which is kind of great old soul music. But, you know, lately it's hard to argue with like a
pulp fiction is a great one. I remember my parents got it from me and I was so excited. I had not seen
the film. Anna Boombox. I played it. It starts. Any of you motherfucking pricks move. I like
secured every motherfucking one of you. Yeah. My mom deleted the disc, put it back in the case,
and said, good thing I kept the receipt and walked it out of the room. That's rough. That's rough.
Yeah, but all at Tarantino's, he does great work. He does great soundtracks. And the carpenter's
stuff now is great for writing, as I've recommended. I agree. Alex J. Walker asks, who are some of Joe's
favorite hip -hop artists that are currently putting out music? Well, Tsar Face is my number one.
I say that a lot on different podcasts. If you're not familiar, it's 70 and esoteric who were,
or sorry, seven Allen esoteric, who were a duo from Boston and they teamed up with Inspector
Deck from Wu Tang. It was my favorite Wu Tang member and they did Tsar Face. They've got about
five albums out at this point. They really crank it out. They just did an album with MF Doom called
Tsar Face Meets Metal Face. Very good stuff. So they're way, way, way up my list.
I still like a lot of the digging in the crates crew. They still put stuff out, show an A .G.
Lord Finesse and Diamond D. And those guys. And then Wu Tang, I'll say too.
Also, they are still making music. Yeah. Now, are we going to get to hear that
scurrelly? Well, it was taken away from them so possibly. They took, yeah, I hope so.
I love that the judge took it. I mean, I hope they just made a shitty album.
He played snippets of it on the internet and it sounded good. Yeah.
It sounded good, but I mean, you know, I heard 30 seconds of it, that was a fucking thing,
but I'd love to hear it. Right. Yeah. Well, you didn't ask me, so I'm not going to tell you.
I do love one of my favorite albums for getting high to is Young Thugs album,
where he is naked and covering his dick. I don't remember the name of it, about three,
four years old, terrific album, Young Thug. And you introduced me to a gentleman named
Chink Strugs, who has a song called I'm a Coke Boy. I love the song I'm a Coke Boy. He's a great
rapper. His name sadly is Chink Strugs. I don't know what to tell you, but he's great as well.
Yeah, so there you go. Now, this one I was hoping we would get because I wanted to ask you to do
this. Have you done this Yanny or Laurel thing yet? No, it's a sweep in the internet like that shirt
that half the people thought was blue or whatever. Remember that one? No.
Half people were like, this shirt's blue and the other half were like, what are you talking about?
It's yellow and it went on. All right, I'm going to play this. You tell me if you hear the word Yanny
or Laurel. I know exactly what I heard. But Heather this morning heard the other one. It's nuts.
Honestly, we wondered if we should even get married if we since we both heard different things.
All right, here we go. Yeah, I agree to Twitter's use of cookies, bitch.
Yanny. Yanny. I am blown away. I can only hear Laurel.
He's clearly saying, Yanny, I hear very clearly Laurel. This is honestly very interesting to me.
I don't hear anything close to Yanny. I don't hear anything close to Laurel.
Well, maybe we're not supposed to get married either, Jim.
I mean, I'm going to tell you, I find that shit really interesting. I don't understand it.
Now, how about this? Let me set the stage for this. I stumble up, shit face, saturday at the wedding
to the mic. Yeah. Socks. Let me say one thing and I do this for the whole audience.
Yeah, and then I go, the beauty of these two kids, one of them heard Yanny, the other heard Laurel.
And that's what it's about. Yeah. And don't explain what you're talking about, Yanny.
Because I'm sure like my grandma will know exactly what you mean when you get up there.
Lawrence Crazy Horse Anderson, a fantastic name, asked during the final scene to the series,
what was revealed about Joe's character and the Amazon show by night? I understood Joe was the
Rod Sirling host character, but the final scene was intended to make him a part of the show and give
his character more significance than simply being a host. I didn't get the reveal, but maybe I'm dumb.
Love the show, Joe. Well done. Thank you. It was fun to be a part of it. And watch by night on
Amazon. Prime if you can, please. Yeah. It's, you know, look, I'm kind of in the dark too. It's hinting
that this, the basic hint or idea is that I've been in that room and who knows where in time and
space it is, with, with these recording devices, recording these accounts that I'm remembering, these,
these, you know, these, these happenings that I'm aware of, which are the stories that you see.
And then the, the wolf who comes in in the, in the, in the fedora and the coat is obviously
connected to these things somehow because you see him in some of the stories. So I guess the idea
is that eventually we'll find out how I got there and why I'm there and why I know these things.
Is there going to be a season two? I don't know. I guess it depends on how well it does.
When did you shoot this season one? It didn't shoot in like a week and you just shot all the
above and the afters thing. They already shot the stories. And then we were looking for somebody to
come in and be like a host. And then yeah, and then during that process, they made me a little,
a character a little bit bigger. I don't even remember you going to shoot this or
I shot everything in a day. Oh, okay. Well, they and the voiceover and everything like the whole
thing I did in a day didn't take long. Samantha Kiefer asks, which A24 film is your favorite?
Lady Bird disaster artist, sacred deer, Florida project comes at night, lobster, ex -Mahina,
witch, moonlight, etc. Tusk. Oh, oh, Joe. I mean, I love that you throw that back out there because
it just gives me so much more credibility. I haven't seen killing of a sacred deer. I've been dying
too, but I've heard it's like painfully slow. So I've been waiting for the right time to do it.
And I also haven't seen it comes at night, but it's very divisive movie. My favorite of those
is probably Moonlight or ex -Mahina. I thought there were both great movies, you know? Very different
movies. Good. Scott Sweeney asked, did you guys know that 90s alternative rock band lit still
exists and have gone country? What a wild world? I knew hoodie is gone country. Oh, is lit?
Not lit. Is lit. It's been a while. Lit is you make me come. You make me complete. Who's saying
it's been a while? Because that guy does stained that guy does country now. Really? Yeah. You know,
good for them. You gotta, you gotta adapt with the times. Hoody's made more money as country than
he did with Hoody. Hoody knocked it out of the park. Twice. I met Hoody's Pete and I were hanging
with the guy. They lead singer of the national whose friends with Pete, I guess. We went to some
post Grammy party and Hoody was there sitting completely alone. Couldn't have been nicer. Delightful,
man. I got no beef with Hoody. I hated his music, but what are you going to do? Why would you?
And then Samantha Lippert says, this news will have Pat feeling palm -freetly miserable. So,
I must have talked about my experiencing lit on the podcast at some point, which I don't remember.
But I saw lit at one of those 90s nights. Sugar Ray, gin blossoms lit, etc. They were good. Palm -freetly,
what the hell is that mean? They're song as you make me come. You make me complete. You make me
completely miserable. The night of, I was very high and I started singing. You make me palm. You make
me palm -freet. You make me palm -freetly miserable. They want you on the Archie show. Yeah,
exact. That's Archie level comedy right there. If my offer from Bazooka Joe doesn't come through,
I'll go do the Archie show. Will Potorf ask, hey guys, what are your all -time favorite video games
of all time? Kind of a redundant question, Will. You put all time in two places just so you know.
Also, Joe, have you ever played the Dark Souls Bloodborne games? I feel like they'd be
right up your alley with their horror influences and difficulty. Glad you guys love the art. We
truly do. Thank you for doing it. I was joking when I made fun of your grammar. Lots of love.
My favorite video game of all time, I have two. I have three. Mario, for we, the most satisfying
game -beating experience I've ever had in my life. Paperboy, original. Can't get enough,
and Tetris can't get enough in any form. Joe, my top three video games, Devils Crush,
for TurboGraphic 16, Resident Evil 4, for Super Nintendo, and Miss Pac -Man, Hyper Speed Arcade.
And then, yeah, I haven't played Dark Souls, but I did play Bloodborne and it was a gorgeous game
and it was great, but it was too fucking hard. I couldn't get anywhere in it, man. I just kept dying
like over and over. I couldn't, and everybody I talked to where I was like, I can't get anywhere.
They're like, yeah, dude, it takes a lot of practice. And I was like, I only have so much in me, you know,
like, but it was a great game. I just wish I could have been a bit better at it. Yeah.
Okay, pretty cool stuff. Tim Letzo inquires, Joe, when is emotional hangs coming back?
I don't know if it is, you know, when Ferral Audio folded, we lost our network and we didn't have a home
for it. And that coincided with Kurt being out of town and myself being out of town at different times
and, you know, scheduling stuff. So I don't know, I mean, Kurt and I have talked about it. We're open
to the idea of potentially bringing it back, but we need the right, you know, it's got to make sense.
We got to have time to do it first of all. And then we also have to find a home for it.
I don't want to, what I don't want to do is start an episode, do an episode, put it out and then
we can't do another one for two months. Right. You know, so yeah, but thank you for asking.
And then he asks, muah, what is your favorite movie from the criteria and collection?
It's tough to say. I mean, the latest sounds of the lambs won is fantastic. I was going to do it for
my next Joe's scary stuff, but man, it's great. It looks great. I love the night of the Hunter one
for an old movie. I love the days to confuse one. I mean, they do good work.
Nick mascara asks, why did Joe tell Disney to ruin the Marvel Cinematic Universe?
Salamanders says, have you heard that song?
See, these are jokes, people. A couple of jokes. We can skip that one. I'll read it for you. Have
you heard that song? The mom number five, where does he meet all these women? Who are these women?
That's pretty fine. It says Seinfeld Boys. John Watt asks, how about an episode or bonus episode
reviewing at least the first episode of the Freddie's Nightmares TV show? It's the only episode
that tie in directly to the continuity of the films and it turns 30 this year.
Look, I'm all for that. If Pat, if you want to do that, I would love to do that. It's the, it's the,
oh, it is one of maybe three episodes of that show and it's still not great, but it's good enough.
Yeah, it's good enough and it also really set us. I was a fan. I mean, I was, when they announced
Freddie's Nightmares was coming out, I was beside myself. I couldn't wait to get my eyes on it.
Yeah. And that first episode is truly misleading because as he said, it's the only one that ties into
the story of Freddie and everything. And then after that, every episode is just a shitty dream
sequence where the person doesn't know if they're a sleeper awake. Yeah. And Freddie doesn't show up
except at the beginning to be like, this week's tale, you don't like to do like a crypt keeper thing.
Sure. But I'll review that absolutely. All right, I'm curious to see it. I have them, I have the
DVDs. I will lend them to you. Emily Florence asks, can we go to hometown buffet when I come to LA
for the live show? That's an immediate yes. Emily and Ken have been doing amazing things. We are
putting some live shows together. Thank you to both. Thank you. I've never been to hometown buffet.
I've been to old country and I've been to the Vegas, seafood buffet here in Glendale, which is for
some reason called Vegas seafood buffet. Real shit showing that place, man. Yeah. The Glendale one
was passable. The other one is breathable. Yeah. The Hollywood one is rough. Yeah. Let's do, uh,
yeah, let's do it. hometown buffet, I think it might be what old country buffet turned into.
I think that's right. Or it's one of those Wendy's Carl's Jr. situations where it's a different name.
Adam Loundsbury asks, what are your favorite movies that were made before you were born?
I was born in 1981. I mean, there's tons. I guess I love Alfred Hitchcock's notorious. That's my
favorite Hitchcock movie. I watched the other night. Incredible movie. Incredible movie. I'll say that
for now. There's a good recommendation for you. It has an exclamation point at the end, which you
don't see enough. Airplane and notorious might be the only two. I'd have to go with Star Wars. It
came out two months before three months before I was born. Okay. Cut it close, but you know, that
was the year I was born. So I'm going to go with that. Good answer. Mick Mack, no questions. Just
love and thank you. Thanks for the laughs in the community. You fellas can an Emily have built
around this podcast. Thank you. Enjoy the break as always. I'll be digging through the archives. Anytime
I feel the need to hang with the fellas having an amazing wedding summer and break from the pod.
Love y 'all like a plate of food. Oh snap. Oh, by the way, since this is a bonus episode we should
announce this. The patreon, you know, we'll put it on pause starting in May. Yeah. Yeah. So, you
know, obviously we're not going to ask people to donate when we're not putting out content. So we'll
put it on pause until we return. Yes, that's important to note. Tristan Avery says it's starting in June. I
wait, what the fucking month is it? No, it's May now. We're mid May. June 1st, it'll pause. Okay.
So you'll get charged for May and this will be the bonus episode for May and then no charge after that.
Right. There until we're back. Tristan Avery asks, have you played your PlayStation VR at all?
If so, any horror games, many of them are genuinely frightening. I would love to. I have not really
played my PlayStation at all. I played that game where the big rock man was beating up the city
or it's called like Crank or something. Crank? Crank 2. Why don't you give me that VR?
You see this collection. I know. Forged here. I know. What are you going to do with it?
Well, I'd like to at least try it, but I'll give it to you. You come over here. You play it when
you're here. I don't work. I was joking, but the fact that you went for it. Okay. That's great news.
Steve Kaupa asks, system of a down is an all -time favorite of mine. I even met their drummer outside
the Glendale Cheesecake Factory last July. I was probably inside. What is your favorite system of a
down album? Do either of you own system albums on vinyl or CD? If neither of you own one of their albums,
Jesus, this guy, backup singer. I recommend 2002's steal this album or 2005's mesmerized hypnotized.
I've only heard the singles and of course I love. Wake up.
But I'll check them out. I think front to back toxicity is their probably their strongest album.
Sure. I love mesmerized. I didn't like hypnotized. I thought that hypnotized sounded.
It was very differently produced than mesmerized. It was much mudier. Yeah. And I also thought that
it sounded like it sounded leftover to me. It didn't. It was not as good as mesmerized though had
that great song. Yeah. Everybody's coming to the party. Have a real good time.
Yeah. I remember that one. And mesmerized has my favorite system of a down song on it. But I think
toxicity is just a bigger, probably more complete album. There are a median, right? Yes.
But no, I don't have them on vinyl. I only have them on CD.
I'll look Vinzland. Sorry if that's wrong. I'm sure that's wrong. Seeing the new predator trailer.
Thoughts. Joe text me other day. New predator trailer looks horrible. It's terrible. I watched it.
I was sort of indifferent to it. It looked kind of generic to me. I'll see it. Chain black. I love.
I will see it with with hope. Yeah. But it's a bad trailer. That trailer is cut together like a TV spot.
You know, a month into promotion. That is not a premier trailer. There's no hero shot of the
fucking predator. The times they do show them. It's like side angles. I'm like, what are you doing?
It's an iconic monster. This is a huge sequel. Like this is a return. Like
puts some suspense into this thing, man. So I thought that the trailer was bad.
I'm not thrilled that there's a god damn joke in the trailer. Because I feel like the whole
tone in the movie is going to be joking. Right. And the fact that they even have to slip a joke.
I mean, you watch the trailers for any of the other predator movies, even the bad ones.
There's not a god damn joke to be had. Yeah. So the fact that they had to slip one into this,
I was like, that's not a great sign. I'm not also thrilled that one of the main characters
is clearly going to be this little kid. You know, Shane Black right and direct it.
He directed it. I believe he wrote it. I mean, it's never written a movie that's bad.
I'm not I'm not paranoid about it. I agree. I love Shane Black. I, as I said, I'll see with it.
But it did go through extensive research shoots. And there's been a lot of, you know, clamoring
around it about like, you know, what's going on with this? When it ends, the thing was announced
the long fucking time ago. So I don't think Shane Black fucked anything up. I think if it sucks,
it's the studios for it usually is. Yeah. Sarah Catherine asks, can you guys review hereditary
as soon as it comes out? I need to know if it's as good as the hype. I don't think I'm more excited
to see any movie than hereditary. Yeah, wait. And we'll do it for sure. I can't wait. And yeah,
that's definitely on the list. Looks great. Tim Kalfblish also probably wrong. Kalfblish.
Have you ever had broken bones or something requiring some immediate medical care? Do you have a
story for it? It doesn't have to be an SCD, but it's encouraged. Yeah. I broke probably both wrists
falling on my face, walking home from a bar, not that drunk. And I was so embarrassed that I just got
one casted up. And I kind of let the other one go because I was like, I can't walk around with two
casts on my hands. And I've ever read it ever since. I have like a weird clicking in my wrists and I'll
probably have arthritis, but that's it. I only have broken fingers. But when I was a small boy,
I fell and banged my chin on the edge of a coffee table and had to get stitches. All right,
that's probably. And there's still a faint scar almost like an Indiana Jones or Tina Fey.
Yeah, I fell off my huffy sonic six and got amnesia when I was a kid. I probably told that story.
Oh, wow. That's pretty cool. Parents had to wait me up at one three and five every morning and ask
you my name, address and phone number. If he says he doesn't remember, he's fine. That's normal.
I also was not permitted to see Beetlejuice at the theater because it would upset me. And I was
furious because I really wanted to see Beetlejuice. You could remember that you wanted to see Beetlejuice,
but you couldn't remember who you were. I snapped out of the amnesia pretty quickly. So then
when your parents awaken you're up, it's like, all right. All right, Chuck Andrews asks, do
stand -up comics have to hand out flyers on corners in LA? I think they're getting that from crashing
problem. Well, they don't, but that was a thing in New York. Yeah.
So LA comics more privileged or just lazy, probably both. I get that LA is where it all happens,
but with Netflix and HBO having more shows filmed in NY, do you still have to live there to make it
in comedy? No, not at all. For the record, I'm not an aspiring comic, which is curious.
You're better off in New York if you're trying to make it in comedy.
Well, I would say either or right. There's a thrive either or, but I'd say if you're,
if you're only goal is I want to be an undeniable comedian, I don't care about anything else,
you're going to get a lot more bang for your buck in New York. That's probably true. But yeah.
He also asks, what are your three favorite metal bands, which is kind of your answers the same,
basically. Yeah, I'm not a big metal guy at all. All right. Yeah, we can keep moving. Okay.
Anthony Guajardo asks, you guys both clearly hated the dog shit that was Chappy. I'm not a fan either,
but the soundtrack is one of my favorite things to listen to. Is it Diane Word? Do they also do the music
for it? I have no idea. Do you guys have anything like that where you hate the movie, but love the music?
I can't separate it. If I'm hating a movie, I'm not like, ooh, but I like this tune here. It doesn't
happen. You know what? I think I do, I think I do have one. Okay.
Yeah. You know what's a great soundtrack and not a great movie. And I'm going to get blowback
on this. No pun intended blow. The movie blow is like, like, it's like an impression of a
Scorsese movies are very entertaining to people of that age, boondocks, saints, and etc. But
I remember liking blow. I'll give it another shot. I like Paul Rubin's in it. It doesn't, I don't
hate it. I don't think it's terrible, but it goes, it goes, it's ridiculous with these squids. It's
the freeze frame and the voiceover. I didn't know what was up, but what was down. It's very interesting
to me how many times Johnny Depp has played gangsters like he's not in any way Italian unless I'm
crazy. Donnie Brasco, black mass, that one. The black mass he was supposed to be Irish from Boston.
And he's still, it's, I love black mass, but he sounded like he was from the like the Bronx. Yeah.
Yeah, I don't have that. And I do want to just state again on the record how much I hated
Chappy. Tucker, fuck Chappy. Tucker Roush asks, if you could remake any film, what would it be and why?
You know what? I would love to see, and it's a classic, but they've already made sequels that have
kind of tainted the brand is Midnight Run. You're not going to do better than De Niro and Grodon, but
I'd like them to not cast comedians, cast some real actors. I talked about Gosling and trying to get
more, well, you know, I'd like to see it with with some serious actors of today, you know,
with Gosling play. It might doesn't have to be Gosling. No, but I think he'd be great in the
De Niro role. He would be. He would be. And then the good adjacent Bateman maybe in the Grodon role.
I like that. Who's the modern day Grodon? I mean, Grodon is a true original to me. I mean, he's
doing some, nobody's doing the man's a powerhouse. Yeah, but I told him not my shoes. Actually,
he's in him with Jason Bateman called the X and he's the only funny part of it. Bateman's funny in
it though, because he plays a prick in a wheelchair. I always find that funny. But yeah, Grodon's
the guys, the guys and I'll tell you what, I'd like to see it with Gosling and Grodon. Yeah,
still Grodon. Grodon is an 83 year old guy running from the mob. Yeah, I'd do that.
Yeah, okay, there you go. Do you have one? What do you want to see remade?
Not really. No, I like that idea. Okay. Yeah. Sean Pinnock, are you guys open to bringing any other
people into the hoghouse like special guests? We're just talking about this. We've never done it.
But I think it couldn't hurt. I think it'd be fun. Yeah, we were just talking about this. We're
very open to it. We know that Karen Kilgarif would like to come be a part of an episode and we'd
love to have her, be a dream. And if we were going to do this, I'm assuming she'd probably be our first
guest. But yeah, maybe some special episodes. We were thinking for the commentary episodes, it would
be fun to bring in a third person chicken kind of. Oh, that would help tremendously. Yeah,
mediate, pat me. Yeah, maybe even keep us watching the movie. Remind us that we're doing a commentary.
Kevin Marcinik asks, how much would I have to pay you guys to do a live episode at my birthday party
next year? It'd be a smaller audience, probably just the three of us in my danger pad, parents basement.
Depends on where you live. I mean, if you're in LA, that price is real low. We'll be there.
But if you're in Alaska, you know, they'd have to be an airfare. Yeah, probably.
Yeah, that's nowhere you live. I mean, look, everybody's got a price. I mean, Springsteen plays birthday
party. That's true. We'd do it, Kevin. Talk to us. Talk to us. Money talks, baby. Leo Lopez, what are
your most unexpectedly emotional horror movie experiences? Sometimes a good script is a good
script. Also, Joe, I'd love to, okay, one at a time. Most unexpectedly emotional horror movie
experiences. Okay. My number one is the orphanage because it starts as this really kind of creepy thing.
And you think that this burned up kid is the ghost is burned up kid is evil and whatever. Right.
And you realize the Annie's not evil. He just like wants to be loved and it's this beautiful.
I remember seeing it with my girlfriend at the time. She was crying like it was, it was beautiful.
Yeah. And to that, very similar. I would say pan's labyrinths knock up on me as well in a similar way.
Right. Also, Joe, I'd love to hear you explain the razor soft line of Sega Genesis games to an
interested Pat for us Gary stuff segment. I'll tell you. Wait, I'm sorry. The what? The razor soft
line of Sega Genesis games. Oh, razor soft, the developer. Okay. Of of Sega Genesis games.
What did razor soft, let me see what they developed. I'm not we're not going to do it right now, but
let me see razor soft. Joseph Ray goes in choirs. What are some of your guys favorite Netflix series?
I got to tell you, I wish there were more that I love. You know, I know everybody wants to be in
business, you know, doing shows with them. But it's rare. I feel like it's one a year that I really
love. I of course, I love love. As I said earlier, I like stranger things.
Yeah, I don't know. What are you like on Netflix? Stranger Things is my favorite by bar. Yeah.
You know, I don't know. Yeah, no stranger things. I'm going to go with that. That's my favorite by far.
You know, the other ones I dip in and out and I enjoy them and stuff, you know, but I like
stranger things. That's I'm excited for it to come back. I care about the kids. I want to see,
I hope the actors all do well in their careers like I just I really am touched by the show. Yeah,
I agreed. Alex Shipley asks, is there a movie that made you cry unexpectedly? I got caught off guard
by how to train your dragon. Yes, I mean, of course, I yes, my big two are the final scene of
about Schmidt where I had to run ahead of my friends so that they would not see me cry. So embarrassed
was I and like right out of high school or something. And then 127 hours, a very similar thing where I
could not stop crying on the walks of the car on the way home. My friends were getting uncomfortable.
I feel like and I could not stop crying and they're both about closing yourself off emotionally. So
there you go. But that's it. That's the last time that happened. I think several times when I've
watched the untouchables that I'm not expecting to cry, start crying when Malone dies. When Connery
gets killed. Yeah. And I for some reason never expected it and it happens a lot. Okay, that's
that that that one's got me a bunch of times. John Devers, how do you guys feel about Stephen King's
the stand reportedly being developed as a mini series for CBS all access? Well, I'll tell you
it's at CBS. It's going to be a goddamn disaster. That's a guarantee. I haven't seen anything on all
access, but CBS does terrible work. They give terrible notes and they're terrible people.
I look, I mean, look, I'll watch any Stephen King adaptation. I'm really excited for this castle
rock anthology show coming out. Me too. The bar is pretty low with the other stand adaptation.
It's fine, but you know, he's never even about it. No, and I got to say too that, you know,
the problem now with the stand adaptation is there have been so many. It's not Stephen Kingsford.
It's it's just what's happened in recent years. There have been so many movies about plagues wiping out
the civilization. I think they're going to they're going to have a challenge to make this feel, you
know, as original as it was at the time again, right? But, but you know, I'll watch it. I mean, I'm in.
I thought they were doing a movie with McConaughey, but then I guess probably that dark tower
killed that, which I never even saw. Well, McConaughey played the man in black in the dark tower. Yeah.
And and that same character is also in the stand. He's the devil guy in the stand. So maybe they
were going to have him cross over and start like a Stephen King multiverse kind of thing.
But yeah, the dark, I'm reading the dark tower right now. It's a great book.
I had never read it. I didn't know much about it. And it's really cool. It's very like Star Wars
esque. I never read those. I was not into it. Didn't see the movie. But then I was like, well,
I want to see the movie now. Like so I went in online and started reading up on the movie. And the movie
sounds terrible. It's supposed to be. Yeah. Yeah. Like so I don't know. I'll watch it one day.
Kevin Driscoll, what who are your strongest writing influences?
For me, unquestionably John Hughes, I just, I love that he makes every line funny and interesting.
This new kind of harsh re -examining of his work is valid, of course, but it's also a little frustrating.
I mean, the man did so many great things. And some things are unfortunately badly dated. But, you know,
that's, that's what, that's what the entertainment industry is all about.
I agree with Bill Maher's point, which as a sentence, I rarely say, on the John Hughes thing.
He's like, you can't expect woke to have happened before woke existed. You can't go back 30 years
ago. People hated Bill Maher for saying that, but, you know, they did. They hated him for saying that.
But I mean, that's how progress works. It's true. I mean, otherwise it's just consistency. The way
you progress as you look back and you go, Oh, remember when that was okay? That's not okay anymore.
That's fine. But to say, you know, I question whether or not John Hughes was a decent man for missing
this. Sure. It's a come on, man. I'll say though, you know, when I was in like the, I sold a couple
screenplays, a couple like teen movies, whatever. And they seem to encourage for a while, like,
what if it's like an ugly fat girl that they're hooking up with? And like, you know, that was always
like the gross thing like the guy had to like close his eyes and kiss a fat girl or some.
It was never a period in my life where I thought that that was cool. I think what they're saying is,
people should have known it wasn't right at the time. And I see, I see both sides of that argument,
you know, but I don't, I don't really love beating up John Hughes because he had long duck
dog in a movie as rough as that character is to watch now. Well, that, that I understand, yeah.
You know, it's 1980, whatever. Maybe you don't have a gong sound effect every time the Chinese
guy walks in. Yeah, that was nuts. Yeah, that, you know, some of this stuff I can see.
And you know, look, when I first saw the breakfast club as a kid, I didn't think it was okay to
grope a woman. Sure. But I also understand that the movie features characters that are fucking
troubled. Judd Nelson is playing this fucking problem kid like he's fucked up. Yeah, a lot of times
now when people get upset that a an awful character like uses a slur or something, it's like, well,
but are you not supposed to paint the truth of these people? Look, dude, I'm, uh, that, that does
concern me about, you know, Lars, there's a big stink about Lars van Trier's new movie. A hundred
people walked out of the car and screening. Look, by the way, these cons and cons things,
I'm talking to him now, but these cons screenings, there are two options. One, the entire theater
booze and walks out or two, a 49 minute standing ovation. Right. I thought the French were supposed to be
like not easily impressed. Well, who's standing up applauding for 10 minutes? I'd like walk out.
Well, let me tell you this too. The, the hundred people that walked out were American filmmakers
I guarantee it was probably eight people. And, but anyway, but there's all this stuff on, you know,
it's disgusting. One, one woman wrote, yeah, the torturing of women and children is not
art and it never will be. And I think that's kind of boiling down. I don't think that's the point.
I don't think he's sitting there saying, isn't it artistic to torture people? Yeah. It's a fictional
story. He says in the fucking trailer, the voiceover is Matt Dylan going, people say that we get our
baser things out through our art that we can't express in real life or whatever. So maybe it may be
it's a commentary on humanity. Why is it? Why is the only interpretation? This must be what Lars
Von Trier wants to do to people. Sure. I think that's crazy. Somebody wrote the act. I can't remember
the actress's name, but they were like watching her get tortured. And it's like, you're not watching
her get tortured, right? You're watching a character she's playing get tortured. Yeah. And this
person was in the goddamn movie. Like she clearly was okay with it. So it's like just the man is a
provocateur who made a critically acclaimed movie where you saw a dick get nailed. Well, that got a
ton of shit at Khan too. Yeah. I mean, don't go see a Lars Von Trier movie. It's that simple people.
He wants to fuck with you. He loves it. Yeah. One guy wrote, can't Lars Von Trier just make a
normal movie for one? It's like, should you know what he does? And you're still pissed? Yeah.
The number one is that it's like, why did you go if you don't like what he does? Don't go then.
Right. Anyway, uh, who was your favorite filmmaker? Ask Patrick Baxter. Scorsese is easy for me.
Joe. Uh, favorite filmmaker. Look, I, you know,
another controversial figure, but I can't deny it. Over my lifetime, I've gotten the most enjoyment
out of Woody Allen's body of work. Like I, he's, he's put out the highest percentage of stuff
that I've enjoyed. You know, because he also puts out a movie a year. So if you don't like one,
you're like, who cares? There'll be another one next year. I run Scorsese for you. Woody Allen.
Uh, only because of, uh, quantity, okay? Because Scorsese made a bunch of movies too.
He has, I love Scorsese. Scorsese does a lot that I don't care about. Sure. So once you start,
once you go, okay, I don't want to see Cun Dund. I don't want to see, uh, silence, silence.
I don't want to see the, except for the snores. One of the ones with a plane and the sun in the back
ground. Sure. Uh, those are few and far between. But, you know, good fellows, of course,
Cousine. Yeah. Yeah. Maybe. All right. I don't know. Cape Fear, Raging Bull, taxi driver. I'm going
to put Cousine. I'm going to put Scorsese, neck and neck, but I will say this. I related more to a
lot of the characters, the characters I saw depicted in the Woody Allen movies, the neuroses and,
and Albert Brooks is a big one for me. Love Albert Brooks. But, but he, that he tapered off in my opinion,
in a big way. Chris Goodnight asks, what comic books does Joe read on any sort of a regular basis?
Traids or floppies? I don't know what that means. Uh, no, I do know what that. I don't know what
floppies means. Trade paperbacks, I think, right? And then probably just the paper floppy comic. I
assume. Well, I read mostly the collections like graphic novel, either graphic novels or the,
the, I forget what they're called, like the omnibus, whatever collections. I'm not reading anything
at the moment. I'm reading fiction literature at the moment, but the last thing I was reading was
saga, the swamp thing, which I'm still not finished. And I would like to finish, but it's six volumes,
and it's terrific, but it's a lot. It's a lot of swamp thing. A lot of plants. It's a lot of swamp.
But it's, but it's pretty damn good. I really would like to read. The next comic I will read is,
is white, his Batman white knight, which my friend John Harwoods told me about. And it's a story of the
Joker taking a new medication that makes him sane. And then everybody thinks Batman is the bad guy
for treating an insane person inappropriately. That's a very, very sharp,
commentary for what's, you know, what's going on right now. So I'd love to read that.
And I haven't read a comic since Alf had comics. That's true. Alex Nelson asks,
what were each of your first official writing jobs? Mine was my, well, my first unofficial was
Robin Bigg, the MTV reality show. And Robin Bigg, we're not speaking to each other in the third season.
And I was brought into right things for them to say. But that was as a quote creative consultant,
because you can't be a writer on a reality show. My first official writing job is it's always something
filled up. And mine was the Pete home show. Yes, the late nighter. Yes. Actually, it's not true.
That wasn't my first job, but that was the, I wrote for some other stuff before that, but that was
the job that got, again, it was you build as a consultant or whatever. That's the job that
got me into the union and all that stuff. We are, we're down to like the last three, Joe.
We're very close. Okay. I don't know how long we've been going here. This is our longest yet.
About an hour and 15. Okay. Maybe not. William Shanahan asks, most overrated comedians or comedy
actors. Oh boy, where to begin? Well, most overrated comedians and comedy actors.
I got to. I think this is dying out a little bit, but I'm going to say the the boom of handsome actors
being comedians. It reached its bottom with Baywatch where we paired handsome with handsome. There was no
funny. Right. Man, the rock and Zach Efron. Yep. You know, like an Efron, a Timberlake, all these people
who, you know, have just kind of because they're attractive and we're shocked, they're not idiots.
They're suddenly comedians. That doesn't work for me. And then my other one is just this huge tier
of 20 or so comedic actors who play every supporting role in every major comedy. And I'm not saying
they weren't funny at one point, but you get sick to death of looking at these fucking people. Do
their one very limited thing over and over and over. And of course, I can't name any of these people
because I'll probably work with them all at some point. Yeah, I'm kind of tired of awkward
getting sick of it. That's still a thing. That's still a thing. I don't know what I'm saying. I
don't know how ridiculous the words are coming out of my mouth. It was old, you know, four seasons into
the office remake. Yeah. You know, at this point, it's just unfucking bearable. It's, you know,
so talk like an adult is always what I want to say when somebody's like, yeah, I can't stand that too.
And look, I'll say this flat out. Most comedians these days are doing one of two things. They're doing
baseless or unsubstantial sex material where they're trying to be cute and clever. And frankly,
both make me inherently just sick to my fucking stomach. I can't fucking stand it. People, I also
can't stand the amount of people that are trying to have suddenly have a perspective on things.
And it's like, dude, you were talking about skateboarding a week ago. Shut the fuck up. So,
you know, comedy really sucks right now. There's not a lot of people out there kind of being honest.
And I think that's why podcasts are doing so well. And I'm happy for my friends who have successful
podcasts because I feel like it's people being themselves and being honest in a humorous way.
But they're bringing some truth to the, to the table. You know, I mean,
that's what I like. That's why, you know, and there's not a lot of stand -up doing that right now.
So, when you see it, it's pretty great. Sure. Yeah, in terms of stand -up comedians,
if you want to talk about most overrated, I mean, I can't name them. I got 24 year right here.
20 of people that infuriate me. But I'll say something positive.
John Mulaney's new special, great. Talks about it last week. Cat Williams, new special, great.
Great. You know, those are two guys. So, Laura Kightlinger, the other week at the end of
Laura Kightlinger. Fucking fantastic. You know, these are people that are being themselves up there.
And they're not afraid to take some chances and be honest and may the audience be damned.
So, that's, check them out. Excellent.
Jason Wybell, favorite works of Asian cinema and know the Great Wall doesn't count.
I love audition. I love old boy. I guess I do love kind of the extreme Asian cinema, if I'm being
honest. I'll go with all the original Bruce Lee flex. Sure. They're really fantastic. And you know,
enter the dragon being the sort of white album of those, right? Of those. But Chinese connection is
great. I mean, I like, I like that sort of stuff. A rod dot worst, most embarrassing date stories,
especially if they involve going to the movies, but overall is fine. I mean, mine is way too long
to tell you an hour and 20 minutes into this thing. But I have had some dates that would, oh boy,
make you go bold. Me too. Just dates that went from one staggering low to the next.
But the one I remember most, well, again, if I started, I want to, I'm not going to tell you the whole
thing, but it ended with me making out with her in Union Square Park in New York. And about 45 minutes
into getting real heavy with it. She was like, I feel like I need to tell you something. I have
hepatitis. Oh my god. And not knowing if you could catch it that way, which you can with certain
strains, it was fun. I freaked out. And she didn't appreciate it. But I was like, well,
you got to tell me. Yeah, yeah. That was the, that was near the end of a, a night that was just
unbearable. But some maybe some, maybe another time, maybe on a commentary if we want to kill some time.
I once took a woman to see predators. Yeah. And she walked out without you. Yeah. She, she kept talking
through it. Yeah. And I shushed her at one point. And she goes, are you fucking kidding me?
And she walked out. She's like, I'm fucked this. I don't want to see this stupid fucking movie.
Anyway, walked out and I had to chase her out of the theater. I thought you were. So you stayed.
I stayed for about five minutes. Yeah. And I'm just going to stay. And then I was like, I can't
stay. I got to go. You know, right. I did take a girl to see a requiem for a dream once because
something else was sold out. And she walked out of that as well. And actually was very upset with me.
And I said, I didn't write it. Yeah. I mean, it's like you, like you knew. I mean, for Christ's sakes.
Anyway, why did you tell Thanos to do what he did? Very good.
And this is the last one, Ben Lee, favorite class in high school or college, favorite teacher.
I mean, you're not going to know who they are. You're not going to know who they are. That's true. My
favorite class in college, well, I, I'll, Roy Zurich, who made every character in every movie in history,
gay and thought that I think I don't know to this day if he was insane or if he was fucking with
a class, but any movie you talk about, he'd be like, well, you know, obviously Bruce Willis and
but a lot of my film study classes in college were a blast. And the one screenwriting course I took
probably changed the whole course of my life because I loved it so much. There's a couple. I, uh,
I'm Mr. Dowd by theology teacher in the 11th grade, uh, who once, uh, when I was talking in class,
called me up to the front of the room and said to me, I swear to God, if you don't stop talking,
you son of a bitch, I'm going to knock you out. And he was joking and it was hilarious. Wow.
And I laughed really hard. And, uh, and he laughed a bit too, but he was telling me to be quiet.
He was just doing it in a really crazy, funny way. And, uh, I went back and told my friends what he said
and they were dying. It was awesome. That's, that speaks what I was saying earlier. Now, huh?
Can't, can't threaten a bunch of student in the mouth. Yeah, you can't. What am I going to do? Go
bang it. Hey, Dowd. Right. Right. It was okay at the time. And it made me laugh. And he was
being funny and it made him laugh. Sure. Give a shit. Anyway, um, uh, that's our show, folks.
Uh, that's our bonus episode for May. This was a nice juicy, almost hour 30. Yeah.
Hope you enjoyed it. No plugs, no nothing at the end of a bonus. You know that. We'll see you soon.
When we're back with season five. Thank you so much, everybody. We'll see you next time.