How do you do Hellions it's your bonus ep for the month of uh what month is it august
it's august it's a hot august morning pat and i are here at 9 45 in the morning it's already 80
fucking degrees outside just absolutely terrible i find myself wearing uh long sleeve shirts and
jackets just to kind of trigger it i was talking with our buddy trevor about that the other night
at the bar he i was like i noticed we're both wearing jackets what's going on we had the exact
same reason sick of this want to try to maybe fool old man weather but then you just wind up hot
it always got like a light spritz on my upper back yeah it's you know you go to a party a nice
young lady comes in for a hug you see the face kind of fall as it presses into a damp and you
appear to be wearing woollen pants no these are actually quite light they are they are i was
going to say that that can't be i i'm maybe a big part of it is just today is going to be
uncomfortable and bad why don't i just embrace it i'll be wearing steel wool like a monk
by the end of the month torture myself
um it is a rare uh morning edition i'm enjoying a cup of morning joe with my morning joe joderosa
hello pat how are you i'm good i went over to the duncan d's this morning duncan donuts we get
starbucks all the time at work and frankly i'm sick of the taste of it i think it's a bad coffee
especially to be america's number one choice i like starbucks i can bake i can make better at
you know like when they got the diner pot in the uh the uh break room i like that better
i don't know the what what what type of coffee is going in that diner pot
yeah that's true maybe it's really good coffee now joe wanted hot i assumed yes he said uh
get me a black coffee black like my soul i took the simile one further and got a black
ice coffee like my soul and they gave it to me in a bucket yeah that's a big uh for some reason
the ice coffee always comes in a bigger cup i guess they're like oh because of the ice i just
feel like it's another way they're ripping you off with the regular coffees it's too much to hold and
frankly like this is i don't feel good about the environment would you say it's for this giant
plastic monstrosity would you say it's uh hard to handle like the black crows yeah
pray the little thing let me light your can it goes a mama i'm joe hard to handle now yes around
there's your on with the joe for and then i'll reverse it we don't do those segments on this but
let's pretend i said on with the joe at the beginning let me see if i have sipped peeled
and win couldn't couldn't be a gross or three words together sip peel wins disgusting the girl
wrote good luck on my cup i think she probably was into me she probably doesn't do that for
anybody else yeah it says please enjoy any size ice tea for one dollar after 11 a .m jackpot
any size now do you think there's a bigger size than that no there's just small medium and large
that's large that's a large yeah i set them both on the the roof of my car to get my wallet out
and a light breeze almost took this 10 pound iced coffee right onto my head
it's too big uh i'd like to elaborate on the black like my soul joke
it's harder and harder these days to come up with black coffee jokes right you just can't do the i
like the coffee like i like my women it's been done too many times and maybe my favorite is an
airplane with the little boy yeah i know the little girl yes she goes black like my men
yeah yeah she's like nine every great movie's rated pg
and also conters a giant pair of uh tits one of the rare pg movies with tits they show tits an
airplane huge jiggling breasts when the plane is going through turbulence um a woman runs it runs
through topless and like just shakes them back and forth and then runs out of frame
really in a pg movie you don't remember them um i guess i probably do but didn't realize the movie
was pg i think i always thought airplane was rated r it feels like a rated r movie it would
have been 13 but they didn't have it yet okay the uh speaking of 13 actually now though i don't think
you can get boobs in a pg -13 i think that's an automatic r which is insane uh it gets stricter
it used to be that you could get one or two fucks off in a pg -13 i think you still can as long as
it's not i fucked her it's got to be like fuck whatever i have a friend who recently was diagnosed
with breast cancer um just terrible very unfortunate she's a lovely lovely person
and uh she posted a picture of herself having like a ceremony ceremony with all her friends there
and she was topless in the photo but very tastefully done and fairly
fairly covered to be honest with you but it was kind of like a last celebration of her boobs
um it was it was a moving a special photo very clearly very important to her and to her life
got flagged uh by someone on instagram for inappropriate content jesus christ why does
care i it boggles the mind i mean even even if even if you are for whatever reason
uh grossly offended by that photo why do you care enough to try to get the person kicked off like
who is so offended that they go i can't stand seeing it in my feed no and also unfollow yeah it's
it's a hell of a it's a hell of a week i mean we're back in a trailer hitch up to the apocalypse
and people are flagging a picture because they saw a nipple nipple they probably suckled on just
30 years ago different nipple their moms but you know what i mean yeah yeah it's uh
it's it's it's i don't i don't understand where the priorities are anymore the uh it is i mean
you're saying a hell of a week i assume you're following the news
yeah we don't have to get deep into politics trump thing where it's like
he praises the one guy that just goes down uh with the criminal activity doesn't doesn't
roll over on the other guy it's like no he's fucked up too he's like he's a bum he tweeted
this morning as if he's uh you know shecky green he was like hey if you need a good lawyer might i
recommend michael cohen like what what you're going to jail you're all going to jail
i mean here's why i don't think anybody's well i mean those guys are going to go to jail but the
i mean people forget this during the uh reagan administration uh reagan i believe it was
it was something like 25 people were indicted and from his administration on criminal charges it
was some insane number and yet you talk to you talk to the average republican about reagan they
say he was the greatest president of all time they love him seemed to just kind of coaster he did
two terms like i honestly didn't know that 25 people in his he got uh yeah there were a lot
of people in his organization that uh that that were indicted on different criminal charges and
not um and i believe one of the most heavily investigated was the uh attorney general at that
time g gordon letty i don't remember if that's who it was at the time very bad at uh history
g gordon letty i think he was in the 60s wasn't he no that was what's his face that dressed up in
the dresses j. edgar hoover yeah 70s maybe i'd look it up but i don't care i got most of my uh
of that time from the movie dick starring kirsten dunson stars and stripes bikini what what is that
movie about it's actually a really really smart well -done movie when they had like a teen movie
a week throughout the late 90s early 2000s it was one of the bright spots kirsten dunson michelle
williams and they're like two dumb teenage girls who get swept up in watergate and they have like
these great comedic character actors playing all the key figures like dave foley and a bunch of
people that's right didn't bruce mccullough direct that i believe no andrew fleming who did hamlet
too but bruce mccullough is in it as woodward and bernstein as one of them i i would not be
surprised if everything joe and i have said detail wise in the last five minutes has been wrong
from from film to politics i don't think any of it is right just wikipedia the movie dick
uh this is a this is a free one so we don't have our usual slavish this is actually the
option of the detail the free one well this is actually the one that everybody pays for
this is the could be more opposite than of the free one it feels free to me because we are not
tied to any uh you know free in a spiritual sense in a spiritual sense i feel there are no rules
here about no rules just right yeah yeah you can be whatever you want here have you been watching
the uh oh you don't have shutter do you i don't have shutter uh i've been watching on shutter the
uh and this is not a movie corner because we don't do segments on this i'm just
just kind of something to talk about like bonnie rate uh i've been watching the joe bob briggs
last drive -in that's what i would get shuttered for yeah so i have shiver i have shake and i have
shutter this is a man that writes jokes for a living shimmy east it wouldn't have been a great
joke without that east yeah i know this i can walk you through why you're a pro yeah the uh i'm
serious i mean that um the uh it's too early to emote but i did mean that anyway thank you joe
you're welcome he went on i uh i was watching sleep the sleepaway camp one yesterday love
sleepaway camp he goes on this uh goes on a tirade about the governor in north carolina who
wouldn't allow for the unisex bathrooms yeah and uh breaks the entire thing down into an
andy griffith episode of how that governor was barney fife instead of being andy griffith yeah
and just you know and just being like well you know old ed likes to wear a dress ain't nothing
wrong with that barney you know like any sounds beautiful and he really broke it down like
it was a really really great uh take on it yeah it was a perfect analogy to the andy griffith show
does he show the movies unedited oh yeah yeah yeah and he takes he pops in every half hour or
something yeah yeah i'd say every 20 minutes maybe all right you know maybe every 15 it's
sort of around commercial break time but it's not too frequent right uh yeah i mean i think it's i
mean is it worth getting all of shutter for that i mean i i well you love shutter how much is
shutter i think shutter is worth it period yeah uh and i think if you were a fan of that show then
yeah you'd very much enjoy the 13 episodes of this and wouldn't say god damn it why did i subscribe
um but i used to watch them but then i would get frightened by the movies and turn it off i was a
good lineup on this one too it's it's tourist trap it's sleepaway camp it's um uh uh hellraiser
it's um there's a couple like like there's a couple like hellraiser in there that are just
really good solid sort of mainstream horror movies but still have that drive -in quality
and then some of them are like you know like legend of boggy creek some of them are truly
right sort of drive -in exploitation type flicks uh but it's good i think shutter's great
i'll get it i'll get it and watch that for sure i think that sounds like a fun evening
yeah well it would be 13 movies it'd be 26 hours of your life did he stay up or they probably just
shot no when they first did it he did it live a live marathon yeah all right yeah old man too
he's 65 yeah did you know he plays uh the guy in casino i do i think i told you that
probably two weeks ago on this very podcast you were like he's in casino when i said yeah
i knew he was oh yeah he's the guy who i'll check the tape you check the tape they'll be missing like
because i'm a corrupt son of a bitch
joe and i saw golden girls live oh yeah with a z i forgot for uh drag queens and then a midget
i'm who sorry little person who uh portrayed uh a girl scout and also a short man from the episode
where betty white dates a little purse little purse yes um in in my opinion it's the funniest
show i've seen in years i was scream laughing it was very funny the b arthur for god's sake
they they actually had like kind of a burly guy who was like come on rose and what if you if you
ever see it and i will see it again the real secret of it it's all funny but the secret is
keep your eye on the b arthur which is to me the secret of the show as well i didn't agree with that
love the b arthur b arthur is my favorite on the actual show yeah i thought she was great in this
show too yes but i did not think she was the show stealer i thought betty white was the show stealer
in this show that is an acquaintance of mine drew drogy who is a very very funny comedian i thought
he really ran away with it in a in a in a special way he was sort of parodying an aspect of betty
white that you don't necessarily think about but then as soon as you started doing it you were like
that's perfect yeah where it was just kind of like a almost almost hammy which she is a little bit
yeah no i i thought he was uh he was my favorite um who's great but i'm not knocking b b was great
too i just i just didn't think that yes uh that that didn't that didn't define the show for me
i thought b arthur who i i acknowledge was a man i um no no i the uh ruma ruma clannaghan blanche
wait the person playing blanche the person or you mean actual ruma clannaghan the character
of the man playing ruma clannaghan i was i was attracted to uh he was a very attractive woman
yes yes um and then the sophia sam pancake who has been in like every sitcom of all time
i thought was funny our friend jimmy smugula bridges who sat next to you oh oh oh i thought
you were saying sam pancakes real name was no but jimmy thought uh the sophia could have been a
little more accurate but i don't need accuracy from these performances the uh look i thought
i thought she was great too but my the reasons i enjoyed uh betty and rue so much
were that they played them as as very exaggerated versions of the um they were their impressions
yes it was like if you saw a comedian do an impression of these people that's what it would
be uh i thought that b and um they had the b arthur and kabuki makeup which i thought was a
choice i thought b and um uh sophia were a little there was a little a little too much
winking to the camera for me like every time sophia would make one of her great quips
like she'd like wink to the audience and be like yeah i got you you know like like it was funny
but i just i i kind of liked the more the the over overly dramatic portrayals of the characters
right but i did like it when they would say like a true clunker as every golden girls has a few
clunkers and they would just look out at the audience and be like oh like we didn't write
this kind of thing i like that vibe i didn't care for that part of it i felt that it was
didn't an unfair knock they showed uh period accurate commercials yeah they were great for
aids chocolate the chocolate that makes you lose weight unbelievable still unbelievable that come
out in the 80s uh and i still find myself telling people about that who've never heard about it's
really something to see this is people who've like i lost 20 pounds i've got aids and like
clicking their heels and they spell it with a y because they know that there's a horrible disease
called aids yeah i think this was right before it was officially mainstream and they put the company
under i think i would imagine so uh they also had white diamonds elizabeth taylor which my sister
and i used to crack up at how cheesy those were yeah those session by calvin klein uh bill cosby
reaching out to a woman from a refrigerator being like come on give me some of that pudding
very disturbing it was just a great a great time it was a great show i really had a lot of fun now
wait who's sam pancake what's he in sam pancake has done guest spots on like most sitcoms would i
know him can you stand your will and grace's your your i'm sure a frazier i'm sure uh can you tell
his his his real name is sam pancake perhaps a stage name but but i mean that's what he goes
by on the shows yeah all right hold on i'm gonna look him up he's a funny guy because he did look
familiar he was funny uh the yeah it's it's a show i highly recommend it was sold out all weekend
it's coming back to la in january if you're here that's that's who played sophia it's that guy yes
correct oh i know who that guy is yeah you've seen him and and he's 50 years old looks great
yeah well uh gay don't cray you know the old expression he's been in tons of stuff he's very
curb enthusiasm remember he was the guy at the shirt store i feel like well i felt there's a
hundred scenes of curb where he's like trying to return a shirt but it was one of the early
ones where he goes to return a shirt and the guy they get in a big altercation it's very funny all
right he was also apparently in space station 76 now what's that i don't know okay uh over her dead
body i'm just reading off some of i remember over her dead body credits here kitchen confidential
bradley cooper okay the hell was that it was a short -lived show that was about anthony bourdain
actually it was yeah now did you see burnt with bradley cooper as an yet another bad boy chef
that's what i thought it was that was a terrible terrible movie was kitchen confidential a comedy
yeah it was like a single cam fox comedy probably 2006 right before wedding crashers
bradley cooper wow all right got good reviews canceled quickly but it was based on the the
bourdain memoir okay now this is before he was dead this is before he was dead significantly okay
now joe why did you tell asia argento to do what she did that's god damn it that's what i was trying
to get to earlier and i couldn't think of a name when i said speaking of 13 well this is a wild one
i mean this is truly wild uh in in in have you seen the picture of her with the boy when
you saw it i saw it and uh in a statement in a statement released by the harvey weinstein team
so take it with a grain of salt uh take it with a thousand milligrams of i'd go as far as to say
this possibly quite probably yeah the only statement ever given by the harvey weinstein
defense team that we might agree with okay this displays a stunning level of hypocrisy
well i can't believe they even commented on it i know but with everybody it's not well he's the
only one he claimed he weinstein claim is is i'm not defending weinstein but he claims that he is
uh he's steadily claimed that he has not done anything um non -consensual so this was their
to jump on of course and it but especially with her because she led the charge he was very
adamantly saying none of this was non -consensual uh penthouse who who am i right for yeah as you
know uh they and pose for i pose for them yeah well i stunt dick for them they use other guys
faces but i'm the stand -in for the cock shots is that you on the legs over your head pointing to
the b -hole shots yes yeah yes okay it's my butt asshole and then they put another person's face
all right i thought i recognized it but i wanted to put uh anyway they they released an article
written by um i forget the woman's name but she's uh she's actually the woman that got into the
text fight with michael che and it was on page six oh yeah yeah yeah she wrote an article called
toxic femininity that really went after was very supportive of the me too movement but it really
after agr agento and rose mcgowan saying these people are bad for this cause these are these
are exploitative uh sensationalists and and they're and they're they're they're they're they're
playing dirty and whatever and she got a lot of shit for it obviously and then two weeks after
it drops this agr agento thing comes out and i was like oh wow well so and it came from the
new york times too it wasn't like this came from some fucking yeah and then her cover of a lot or
you know we don't know it's all alleged but she was like anthony bourdain paid him off it was his
idea oh god it's like you're gonna throw your boyfriend who killed himself a month ago under
the bus by the way people are kind of saying you may have yeah triggered such a thing although
you have to of course have a level of depression that would bring you to there let's not open that
can of worms there's a lot of dangerous territory we're circling here but fine asia uh agento
rose mcgowan the issue is yes these people don't seem 100 mentally sound rosanne another example
but these are people who were sexually abused that makes you not mentally sound allegedly though
allegedly and allegedly and allegedly but like i i mean here's my thing with it if you're going
to say if if asia agento is going to run around saying we got to believe victims yes and we need
to listen to the victims when they speak up and we're going to say at all costs we should believe
these people right and then her first line of defense is this kid's lying i didn't do that i
mean it's it's it's insane lena dunham doing the same shit although she wasn't involved in you know
what's lena dunham saying this was a while back her one of her writers uh who also wrote for
fact but uh this guy uh writer for girls it seemed like allegedly had a thing for younger women
uh a seven he had sex with a 17 year old girl got caught lena dunham immediately takes to twitter
after years of saying believe the victim and says i know i've said believe the victim in the past
but i know this guy so well and i know he couldn't have done it because she worked with him yeah
she had no other proof she just said i know he couldn't have done it well and and and look and
again i it's all alleged on every side on all sides on all sides it's alleged good people on
many sides uh so it's all alleged i'm not saying i believe or don't believe anybody i'm just saying
it's a very very confusing uh shitstorm here doesn't help the fact that robert rodriguez
who was a big supporter of rose mcgowan she threw him under the fucking bus and then he had to come
out after publicly supporting her against weinstein and saying this guy's a scumbag or
all that stuff he had to come up probably and be like she is not telling the truth about this
situation that she's describing uh from the grindhouse movie uh she knew for a year that
there was a nude scene in the thing she knew for a year that harvey weinstein was producing this
she knew for a year that she was gleefully involved in this right and then now 10 years
later she's saying she was sideswiped and all that and he goes look i'm sorry like it's it's
it's just not true like i didn't do that to her yeah that doesn't help you know it doesn't help
so it's you know it's unless he's lying people we don't know well this is the thing now we now
going to get into this thing where people it's going to become it's going to become the right
versus the left with this just like this is what they want they want nothing to seem real so that
every allegation seems fake well and this is what will happen is people that want to people that
now have been like chomping at the bit yeah to i think it's champing to to defend a guy like
even though he's gross and most likely a fucking arch criminal
bare minimum harvey weinstein has raped five women it's i mean it's i would think it's gotta
be with the numbers of accusations that have come out right so it's it's like cosby it's like there's
too much i believe all there's too much there's too much smoke here for there not to be five yes i
believe all cosby's accused yeah i mean so anyway um the uh the people that are chomping at the bit
that just want to weinstein to be innocent because they want to get a point for the men
now are going to use this as their ammunition to say well see everybody's full of shit right and
then there's going to be women that double down for asia argento that don't call out the hypocrisy
on her side and it's going to become like the politics it's going to become a far left and a
far right contingent that are screaming and making all the noise about this and then there's going to
be people like us who are sort of in this middle area where it's like guys we're not saying don't
believe anybody but we're saying we also can't not say that all the time too like it's got to go both
ways here so it's like when michelle obama will do an interview and say hell and then trump will
be like can you believe this disgusting bitch pig said hell you know like and his supporters like
yeah yeah it's uh it's the darkest time i've i'm familiar with uh i've never seen anything like it
no i don't know that i'll never ever see anything like it again but i will say for the rest of your
life i will say i've predicted it for years yeah i knew it was coming and all my friends told me
to lighten up joe why are you so down the world's not a bad place welcome to the shit you fucks
yeah it is funny to see all these people like i just can't seem to find a happy moment and i'm like
yeah where have you been i feel like the guy your eyes have been opened i feel like the guy that
said the fucking sulfur tablets and waterproof flashlight in his in his closet yeah all this
time that everybody made fun of and now everything's going down and i have pure water and light well
we're like michael gross and reba mcintyre and tremors they tease us for having a bunker full
of elephant guns yes but then graboids come up from under the ground yes and then and then
you know they tease you for having yeah loaded weapons all around your house then all of a sudden
they say jamie kennedy's in this next one and then you're glad you have the gun i did a show with him
the other for yourself not for jamie kennedy i'm sure he's a nice man how was he uh he seemed nice
enough i guess i didn't really talk to him okay i got kind of drunk big surprise and uh
and at one point i ran into him on the way to the bathroom and i go hey man props on tremors man
good for you now weren't you worried you might take that as a slam no i was saying it as a
compliment okay the movies aren't my thing as you know but i think that's cool anytime somebody
gets to be in a sort of iconic franchise like that sure he's like thanks man i appreciate it
we're think we're gonna do another one man so you know he was very thankful all right he's a nice
guy how much money jamie kennedy had i asked him that did you yeah and uh he told me he gave me a
number he asked me not to share it but i mean scream he would have made 30k for the entire run
of a show on mtv the lowest paying network of all where he did everything i bet he walked away with
a million dollars total his x factor show wasn't on mtv that was on like that was on like the cw
and that was the cw before upn or whatever yeah it was like one of those things he made a million
for three seasons probably and he doesn't seem like a guy who during the late 90s and 2000s
was smart with his money so making a bunch of wild speculations and generalizations
i would say he's got around a half million dollars
uh all right but he might be one of those guys who surprises you and has a mansion
um well i'm forgetting malibu's most wanted i mean look he did a lot of big movies that
that were critical failures of the mask but like you know he definitely got paid for those
son of the man um he's uh he's got two million dollars he was also dating jennifer love hewitt
don't forget he might have so maybe he got a maybe he got a few bills off of her you know
beautiful woman i haven't seen her in years still looks fantastic but jenny and i you know when we
were kids we were just two crazy kids in love running around this town just having a just
having a wild day of dreams and wild nights of passion and i love to hear and we lost track
after somewhere along the ghost whisperer this is probably the most important time to say allegedly
because jennifer love hewitt will sue if she googles joe and here's the this happened i have
no involvement with jennifer love hewitt yeah anthony boudin paid me to say this
uh so we're gonna talk on today's show about a movie now we've seen a while ago
but um now it is already hitting on demand and video i think it's out vhs beta uh it's a film
called gaudy about the life of john gaudy as you'd expect do you want to get there or you want to
just mention it and come back to it later come back to it all right i mean we're not going to
have a ton to say about gaudy that's true i think trying to squeeze more than a 20 -minute review
out of this thing is asking for trouble yeah it is a troubled film i did a tweet about gaudy that
uh triggered a tweet from john gaudy's daughter directly to me which was a real thrill
uh what did she write again let me find it it was something about the well we should save it for
when we talk about the we'll save it i'll have it because i remember now it's a reference
yeah it's a reference to a part in the movie the uh i was uh forgive me forgive me my friend
i hung out uh oh actually never mind uh kurt uh his name is kurt ziegler
okay yeah the the wrestler no that's dolph ziegler dolph ziegler kurt ziegler is a fan of ours
okay uh he's a smart man he's uh i was in dc doing shows recently yes and uh kurt came up
to me after the late show saturday and he said hey man i don't know if you remember writing this
to me but i told you i was going to come see your show in pittsburgh and i was going to drive like
three hours or something to see it yeah and you said don't do that because it's a sunday night
show there could only be 10 people there i don't want you to drive all that way for it
and and it was a small show because there was a huge game going on in pittsburgh huge stealers
game uh so he showed up at this show in dc said he drove two hours okay to see the show uh said
he had a great time thank god because that's a little you know you're a little worried like
well jesus right hope you enjoyed it but anyway i spent a lot of time with him after the show we
we had a drink uh i on him of course i wasn't buying it no i bought him a drink uh actually
i didn't buy him a drink a lovely 21 year old woman who was at the show bought me a drink and
then bought him a drink okay and offered to buy us both drinks um so thank you to her whoever she
was um didn't return the favor she went back inside to watch the third show which was an
11 o 'clock show that i was not part of yeah okay so i didn't have a chance to um but uh
you know we hung out you know we discussed joe's scary stuff one thing leads to another
we we're married yeah uh vegas is just a hop skip and a jump on a on a plane
we should go again soon i have an itch uh so do i and i believe it came from that prostitute
anyway curt it was good to meet you it was nice hanging out we had fun and uh i i'm shocked and
and thrilled and and uh uh uh delighted delighted is another word i'd add to it be muse appreciative
yep grateful yep humbled okay by the fact that we have fans that uh get this giddy about this
show i mean he was i told him a thing i was going to do for scary stuff and literally just like
we're talking and i was just like oh i should do that as a scary stuff and i wrote it and he was
like oh this is cool man like i can't believe anybody looks at this show like that it's very
nice the um the new network i assume the transition has gone well uh i love reading the comments
seeing the arts sometimes it takes me a while i just saw a hog house picture that was very cool
by i believe will potthorpe um and the facebook page is always a treat i save it i don't check
it all the time i save it for when i'm feeling particularly angry and then i go all right people
like me and i met a very lovely young woman after the earlier show that night okay but it was very
brief i talked to her for a moment they had some pictures of you and some some fans up on the
instagram oh cool she took off i'm blanking on her name only because we didn't hang out for
very long yeah we didn't hang out at all we just kind of talked for a few minutes and then she left
um but she was lovely too and she was i believe
somebody told me they were coming out to la for the show awesome um are we sold out
i have no idea oh i don't know yeah well you know check it what do you think i you think i care
about the numbers pat it's not why i do this now if i can touch one fan i'll tell you when i meet a fan
who who loves this show dearly i liken it to the way a father must feel when he says i can't believe
a boy looks at me and calls me daddy sure uh and then also i can't believe i have a son
yeah um
what's that oh made in america dancin goldberg that's a pg -13 that's got a
yes yeah i remember that not being great really you the ted dancin whoopi goldberg will smith movie
wasn't fantastic is that when they were together or when they like where they met and hit it off
uh i think that's when they met i find i found it disgusting at the time the amount of jokes
like late night jokes about how could ted dancin be with whoopi goldberg but they still sort of
continue like you'll see on twitter like never forget ted dancin data whoopi goldberg it's like
these yeah they're they're age appropriate adults who are both funny um and charming who found love
the only reason you're having some issue with this is racism these people are all disgusting
hypocrites yeah they get out there and they say you shouldn't fat shame yet every one of them will
make their fucking kirsty alley jokes and all that shit they're all completely full of shit um
and whoopi goldberg at a very memorable moment at comic relief uh she went she told everybody to
shut the fuck up about ted dancin doing the blackface joke at a roast yes and she said i
remember she said on comic relief she goes this wasn't about him doing something in poor taste
this is about i was fucking somebody i wasn't supposed to be fucking yeah i remember i actually
forgot that he came out was it a televised roast no it was a it was a friars club roast and he
comes out in blackface it's her row she's being roasted right what jokes did he make off of that
i don't know but he's dating her it's like this shit drives me nuts it's like if if if if you're
the closest person in my life i .e. my girlfriend right and i know that you'll think a joke is funny
and it's your event where we're roasting you and i do that joke who the fuck is anybody at that
point to say hey that's not right it's like no this isn't about you this is me to the person
i love right now yeah and we're in a goddamn restaurant i mean generally you're not conveying
that love through blackface look but i do see i come from a strange family papa
come here i've made up my face
um well let's get to gaudy let's get got as should have been the poster tagline for this movie
get got i would have liked it more so my tweet was and i think this moment from gaudy really
sums up the film there is a scene in gaudy where gaudy's boss stacy keach tells gaudy
a truly that the can let's just before you read this tweet sure sure the casting
it's it's it's i love travolta it's hard enough to get your head around travolta playing a mobster
even though travolta is an italian name you don't look at john travolta and think streetwise mobster
no they push it even further they got stacy keach the most non -italian man that has ever lived
playing his boss uh which made no sense to me i will say keach was one of the few who brought
a little class to the proceedings i like keach yeah he wasn't bad uh there is a scene in gaudy
where gaudy's boss stacy keach tells gaudy a truly electric john travolta and i mean that
here's the quote you're going to need the support of all five boroughs queens brooklyn
statin island he slowly lists the five boroughs of new york to john gaudy then at the end he says
and put them together he puts all is a finger out for each one he goes put them together they make
a fist i forgot about the fist punch line angel gaudy john gaudy's actual daughter
tweeted back to me i think they did that for the people who wouldn't know what the five boroughs
were since the movie will be shown in other states and overseas shaking my damn head
so i would have thought she was just like hey fun fact right but that shaking my damn head makes
me think she did not approve of the film yeah no she's being like oh god forbid they don't
spell it out for people that live in south dakota exactly uh she says uh her bio by the
way is oldest child of john and victoria gaudy animal lover but disrespects rats
well yeah i mean her dad got sammy the bull there she is there she is sammy the bull rolled over
that's right one of the biggest rat turncoats in mob history um anyway what did you think of the
film well first let me say the film was travolta was much better than i thought he was going to be
yeah i actually felt bad for him afterwards i said you know if this was a well -written film
he he probably would have gotten some accolades he was he did a good job with it um i also felt
if it had been like a uh an fx or a tnt or something it would have a they would have
taken the necessary time to tell the story and b some of the stuff like him you know in the old
age makeup and you know in the throes of cancer in prison and stuff he was good in those scenes
it's the kind of thing where if it wasn't rushed through with travolta playing john gaudy from age
14 to 80 then uh you know we would have been able to appreciate what he did more because
he wasn't bad and he was doing what he could with astoundingly bad material the movie came up now
the reason pat and i saw this was it got a zero percent when it first came out so we said we got
to see this thing uh i also like the gaudy story i was a fan of the already existing movie called
gaudy that was made for tv armando santa i i wanted to see it uh i was curious uh especially
then because it had a zero percent i was like oh man this thing's going to be so bad it's good
uh pat said you know i don't know if we should review this for the show because it doesn't
really fit our wheelhouse i said pat some films transcend genre and i believe this is one of them
i agree um the movie was bad it was bad it was very bad uh it wasn't so bad it was a riot it
wasn't ed wood bad no we weren't howling throughout but there were some pretty some special moments
it was shockingly confusingly bad it reeked to me of a movie that had been overshot and they
it was probably a mess and they tried to save it in editing with some sort of narrative
and it didn't work we should add it was the directorial debut of kevin connelly who portrayed
e on entourage and i think debut and also final bow and the movie couldn't have felt more like
a storyline movie from entourage right if adrian grenier was playing gaudy himself at some point
in the development i'm sure he was just like we gotta just do this thing like an episode of
taraj did you think they called it taraj i think they called it taraj taraji p henson he
his visual sense i mean he was completely ripping off every mob movie ever made
sometimes way too obviously so the music he was using were the most obvious mob movie
of all time then all of a sudden smoke on the water right is the first one it starts with
gaudy two camera trivolta two camera being like this is my story this is my town or
something like that he turns around like troy mcclure style he's looking out across like the
the new york skyline and he turns to face camera and is like basically like hey i'm john gaudy
this is my town it's like unbelievably on the nose yeah and then smoke on the water and then
a setup line like it all started many years ago yeah and then slow motion camera uh drifting
across the hudson river as bad pretty bad stuff um in the 80s they start bringing in some more
music cues like the pet shop boys west end girls and i kind of liked that although these people
would never have listened to that music so no choice i liked that too but that was just a
scorsese jack yeah of course that was scorsese in uh casino like using like whip it right and
and i can't get no satisfaction the devo version it was it was a cool idea it's a cool juxtaposition
but it doesn't it doesn't work because it because you're like that's you're doing a
scorsese thing i know what you're doing right now um there are shots that don't match up to each
other there are plot lines that are introduced and immediately abandoned there's that girl that
comes up and she's like how you doing to john gaudy's son and you're like oh i guess this is
starting a romance and that never goes anywhere well they are married later but they never explain
it why are we treated to like the moment they met just i don't know that's what i mean i feel
like this thing probably had so much other footage i it felt like a six hour movie condensed to 90
minutes uh there's absolutely no story absolutely no story there's nothing propelling you from
scene to scene no big events happen well they'll be like john the feds are after you for this and
you're like wait what yeah and they'll literally say things like johnny you know those guys have
on us for years we've seen the clues and you're like wait no none of this was mentioned what is
happening right now it's there's a lot of points where it's like i guess we'll just assume they
know about john gaudy then there's other things where they hold your hand so much that you're
like oh i got it e the end of the movie does a uh does an almost uh malcolm x style uh tribute to
yeah they have black and white shots of like murals in his honor and people are like he despite his
criminal activity he put like x millions of dollars into the community he was a hero it's like
why the fuck didn't you put any of that into the movie none of that is mentioned the whole movie
is like that's what makes it a cool story right is like this guy does heinous things yeah but also
he's he's he's loved in the community because he actually does take care of people right
and he is sort of the last bastion of the old school mobsters like he respects the code
yeah they tell you that as an afterthought uh during a montage featuring a song written for
the film gaudy by pitbull oh jesus yeah i forgot about that yep it was uh i mean let's let's talk
the actors kelly preston john travolta's wife clearly i mean it's not hard to see how she got
that part i always liked kelly preston i thought she had a good comedic career ahead of her in
jerry maguire she's got that amazing intro where she's yelling don't ever stop fucking me and she's
naked and it looks incredible and i was like she's funny in her other scenes with tom cruise
and then never really went anywhere which is fine okay but now she's here and you're like
this could have been your comeback she's doing like
i mean what would you even call that like on a living color sketch about the mob
this couldn't be this couldn't have been her comeback the part was not substantial enough
for it to be a comeback the movie was not good enough she's in a lot of it though she's like
johnny you're always staying out late she told me you were gonna be home to take care of the kids
i made a chicken i guess dinner's getting cold they may i mean they gave her
yeah it did feel like a sketch because this movie felt like a sketch yeah it's like what else do you
do with it what travolta was doing was almost sketchy yeah sketch comedy well when he's playing
but he got it at age 25 when john travolta is easily 60 those scenes were a little weird too
they didn't do any of like the x -men uh de -aging they just kind of gave him a little more hair
and we're like now he's 25 now i just looked up uh kevin connelly e kevin connelly yeah first
picture that came up is him with the words kind of a dick printed across his face
all right god he still has a zero percent uh it's got it's up to 24 on metacritic which i
know fairness i think is fair i don't think it deserves a zero no you know what i'm confused by
is when you look up gaudy it says john travolta is playing gaudy kelly presn is playing vitoria
gaudy and al pacino is playing anne yellow della croce then it goes to stacy keach and the rest of
the cast so was he in it and cut out this i'm telling you this movie had saved and editing
written all over it i don't think those travolta to camera things were originally in the script
no i think they were like we got to bookend this somehow john can you come in for two hours yeah
and talk to the camera the movie ends with him addressing camera going if you lived another 5 ,000
years you ain't never going to meet another guy like me and he walks off camera it's one of the
worst lines i've ever it was almost like it was almost like if adam mckay was on the sideline
on drugs pitching the lines in like he does with will farrell you could live to be a thousand
yeah and you'd never meet a guy like me it makes no sense and the only thing that could have made
it more perfect is if as it cut to credits they should have had dice going oh yeah that would have
that would have really put the cherry on top of this thing uh the the supporting cast it's got
pruett taylor vince in a pretty key role he's good the guy with the weird eye who plays like
his right hand man these people's names he he tries you'd know pruett taylor vince he's been
around i'm sure i know by face but not by name uh that you see people like in the background of
shots who have played key figures in like good fellows in casino so like you'll see some guy
walk through the back of a funeral scene and be like wait a minute that guy was in eight
episodes of sopranos so clearly a lot of stuff was left on the cutting room floor
it's just a nuts movie there and they were using its bad reviews in the ad campaign which i've
never seen they were like critics give it a zero percent but audiences love it so check it out they
were like let's get ahead of this it didn't work obviously but i gotta tell you i wouldn't
i wouldn't dissuade anyone from seeing it for what reason because i see so many movies that
are boring that make me feel nothing and this one had sort of a scrappy spirit to it where it was
kind of yes so bad in parts that it kind of carries you through you're watching it kind of
traffic accident and there's a fascination to it and also i like trying to piece together where
a movie went wrong sure i would love to you know like one of my favorite things to read is an
oral history of a movie where they get like all the key players to talk about their experience
i'd really love to see one of those on got it for sure i remember seeing the i watched one of those
about uh staying alive the sequel to saturday night fever yeah and uh a guy goes they cut to a
production he goes the first mistake was letting stalone direct you know where did you see this
it was like the e true hollywood story one of those fucking things i usually wind up reading
them like there's a great boogie nights one that was in vanity it might have just been the travolta
like a travolta documentary and they just had that part in it oh yeah about how bad like how
that movie like basically tanked his career for a while i haven't seen staying alive i love saturday
night fever but was he he was in a broadway show in that staying alive staying alive if i remember
correctly if i remember correctly he's a he's now a dance teacher okay and maybe he's also on
i don't remember but it's travolta in a lot of leotards yeah him trying to show a young
hungry dancer the the beauty of dance and and you need you need to want it god damn it right
well he's right there it's one of those things it's just everything that made
the the reason saturday night fever is cool is the absolute value that these neighborhood kids put
on the disco yeah it's it's these kids that have you know sort of troubled and sorted lives
yeah and and there's a sense of humor about it like when his parents are making fun of him for
his hair and all that that's they're kind of letting him off the hook and they're letting
the audience kind of make fun of him as well yeah and it's like it's like but it's you know
to me the takeaway was always like this is the this is the valhalla for these kids this is what
they have that they can carry worth with or whatever and um staying alive is nothing
it's it's that's all gone now it's just a movie about a guy that dances it's like who gives a
shit right you know uh i think the only time i've ever seen this done but i saw saturday night fever
on vhs and it said on it with a red band around it pg version and i watched it whatever then years
later when i saw the actual r version it's a much darker movie there's like a sexual assault and all
kinds of stuff well and there's the famous line too where he goes congratulations you a cunt yeah
that's the big line that i remember when i saw the uncut i was like whoa yeah holy shit yeah but i
never known that to happen any other time where they released two versions on vhs an r and a pg
uh it is an awesome piece of film who directed saturday night fever john badham who did
shit all kinds of movies he did stakeout oh you don't like stakeout i never saw it i never
cared oh something i'm gonna another say publicly can i say this publicly yeah he did war games too
short circuit i always liked emilio estavez yes richard drafus bothers me always love richard
drafus he bothers me he's i think he's really cheesy and a lot of shit i think he's really
arrogant he bothers me yeah he just fucking annoys me like when he's i don't know did you
ever watch those like shitty mob movies he made like the comedies with like bert reynolds that
terrible but like drafus is literally being like that was the thing with the guys like and i'm like
dude you're this bad you don't you don't understand that you shouldn't fucking talk like that in this
shitty movie wait what about burr reynolds no richard drafus oh i'm sorry i thought you said
movies with burt reynolds why did i hear burt reynolds i said because of those see now you
weren't listening to me i got a lot of shit for one second i was looking up john badham he said
what did he direct uh the uh don't put it on me don't blame me well the uh it's like i'm podcasting
with a ghost uh no drafus yes did did that shitty mobster movie with burt reynolds yes the crew or
whatever yes and look the movie's not good but everybody's doing their best with it but then
you got richard drafus doing the voiceover and he's in the lead role and he's literally being like
this was tommy tommy didn't take no crap from nobody and it's like you should be a better actor
to know to not do that yeah like it's ridiculous it's fucking ridiculous what else would he have
done in that film do a normal accent that's a guy going it's funny if if i talk like this it's funny
it's like no it's not because you're not funny i like richard drafus jaws bob huh have you seen
what about bob i think he's very funny i never really liked what about bob um once around with
drafus and holly hunter and danny aiello there's a great movie that nobody has seen recommended
highly never saw it i love danny aiello yeah it's a great story when i met him no he's in my favorite
episode of tales from the dark side ever yes it's called the odds okay and uh me and pinkstone
quoted all the time it's about gamblers yeah and me and matt mccarthy quoted quite a bit to one
yeah um so anyway i met danny aiello at gotham comedy club he was downstairs in the lounge
because he had just done a show upstairs and i was doing the next show and i said hey he does stand
up i don't know if he does he does stand up shows i don't know if he actually does stand up on them
but like he'll do shows with stand -ups and i think he sings no he's not dead danny aiello
continue i think he died well i'm gonna wait till you look it up because i want you to hear the
story all right gonna gotham comedy i say to the manager that night both can you take me down to
meet danny aiello yes i'm a huge fan he goes yeah of course takes me downstairs you know and he's
like mr aiello this is joe de rosa he's a comic and he just wants to say hi and danny's like hey
nice to meet you kid by the way you know and i go uh i go danny i gotta tell you i love the odds
yeah from the dark side and uh and i just i yell a line at from it i go you're a loser lacy
which is a line that he yells at it and he goes oh an aficionado all right sit down he talked to
me for five minutes about making that episode nice he's like i love that character so much
i got so into it i was like nice this is cool because your average actor that went on to make
big pictures and all this stuff yeah you know they'd be like oh god you know when i did the
horror tv you know he was like dude that was awesome i love doing it yeah and i got the same
thing from um lance hendrickson i tweeted lance hendrickson uh because my favorite episode of
television ever is the cutting cards episode of tales from the crypt okay and i tweeted at lance
hendrickson and i said his first line in the movie is half a grand howdy uh because he plays like
sort of like cowboy gambler and i wrote half a grand howdy i just wanted to let you know that
cutting cards is far and away you know not just the best episode of tales from the crypt but the
best episode of television ever and he wrote back and he's like thanks buddy we had a lot of
fun shooting it man you know i was like that's fucking cool man nice it's just cool when people
appreciate the small stuff daniel is alive yeah i know i told you he was i was wrong uh
uh i can admit that i haven't seen him in anything in 10 years
no he well i think he's retired oh okay i think he has a club in hoboken
all right called like danny's place or something where they it's a comedy club
and if you want to perform at it i heard if you didn't know who you were you had to go and audition
and you had to do your act to danny aiello alone in a room i would imagine aiello is not a guy who
likes your uh alt comedy i don't think danny aiello is enjoying a cait berlant let's say well well
but here's the thing here's the strange interesting part about aiello yes you know i view the guy is
you know he looks like a traditionalist or whatever he put out a he put out an album
where it was it was rap remakes of sinatra standards where he sung the sinatra parts
and then like a rapper rapped over the beat i'm like look that's pretty out of pocket for a guy
like aiello it's true and he was he was like he was like this has never been done before
you know like he was he was excited about it so were these actual rappers or like no it was one
did like a whole album with him all right think they ever met i don't know pat i don't know danny
aiello personally well i'm just talking to you about a thing i saw on the internet i just kind
of wish i was doing a podcast with danny aiello sometimes i guess listen i wish i was too yeah
uh folks that's our show uh there's your goddamn goddy episode we say goodbye and you say aiello
all right we gotta get out of here no plugs no segments on the special bonus
app but enjoy this and uh we'll see you in september for the next bonus later guys