Here is your bonus ep
bonus bonus bonus
for january, it's very merry
it's the fourth
bonus bonus bonus
bonus ep, Pat how are you?
I'm good, we uh
we're really bad with the the kickoff songs for these bonus ep's
your last one was like here's your bonus ep
I mean they're bad so I'm not trying to make them good Pat
I'm trying to the joke to me is that they're bad
so weren't on this no plugs no segments
no plugs no segments unfiltered hog house
coming to you live from the hog house
the thick veiny pull back the sheath
to reveal the uncut dick house
right yeah uh no segments but we have a nice
discussion let me get to our special topic
we're doing another list this week this is the top five
event movies of Pat and my uh our lives uh so we're each going to name
countdown style our five top event movies the things we are most excited to
rush to the theater to see throughout our lifetime i'm excited for this
i am too i have i didn't plan mine out because like i just immediately knew
what the five would be i named my five for pet
and then after they were all star wars movies i was like
let me break it up just a little bit yeah uh but uh yeah
where there we've got some we've got some juice cook in here
juice cooking juice okay relax all right calm down all right not everybody's
saying terrible shit all the time
Joe how's it going Pat it's going well you know i was sitting here tonight
cooking yeah as you could smell when you came in i was making some
i could smell what the Joe was cooking yeah it smells pretty good it smells like
thanksgiving me i made some paleo stuffing yeah uh
and you know what you learn when you make paleo stuffing
no the whole battle with stuffing is just the five spices that's all it
is that's what makes it taste like the stuffing you could sprinkle that
shit on anything it would taste like stuffing i didn't know stuffing had five
spices what are you using instead of bread i use almond flour and you beat it
with eggs and it it you know it creates a
bready consistency that you can use and honestly i can't
there's a bit of a textural difference but not a huge difference um and then you
chop up some vegetables and saute those and put those in but the spices are like
thyme margarine not margarine sorry tarragon tarragon whatever the
fuck it's called rosemary sage but i mean it's amazing
parsley say rosemary and uh what's that
Simon Garfunkels one but you take that's how that's how badass Simon Garfunkel
where they released a single about spices
called parsley sage rosemary and thyme
i really don't like those guys and that doesn't help
but anyway the second you get all these spices together in a bowl you're like
oh that's stuffing i could just eat these spices right right anyway
you know what i uh i have started to do
man man it's uh you put a sweet potato in the microwave
for five minutes it's so hot the skin falls right off
you puncture the skin it comes right off and you stick your dick in it
you fuck that sweet potato till it ain't sweet no more you know what i'm saying
until the until the skin's falling off your dick till those yams become
candied with come Jesus Christ shocked myself uh
no you you begged the sweet potato five minutes you peel the skin off
you put it in a bowl with i do egg whites
and you you whip it all up you got this batter that's uh sweet potatoes and egg
whites yep and you make pancakes that are better
than actual pancakes um i'm not kidding you they are better
and health of course significantly healthier than pancakes uh we talked about
the other day at breakfast i also make pancake
sometimes with uh banana almond butter we might
talk about some of the fucking podcast did we are we repeating ourselves
i don't know i don't know it'd be bad it'd be bad one thing to repeat
ourselves on a regular app to repeat ourselves on the app that people are
paying extra for would be bad let's get off of this we'll add an additional
minute at the end for this look i mean you had to listen to how to make
fucking vegan stuffing uh we're off to a bad start
paleo stuff paleo stuff in it all right you scumbag
um what's happening in your life joe i mean as but the reason we almost
stopped this podcast is the only time we ever saw each other was to do the
podcast right we decided to keep doing it now here we are the only
times we can be okay are here on the pod that's not true we hang out a lot
you came to my birthday party but i mean yeah and then you were gone for the
whole weekend we hung out last week you we came over
Friday night and hung out for video game night you left
Saturday i went on a romantic getaway with my sweetie
yeah and i heard she was trying to get away from you the entire time
what has some truth to that what's some truth to that where'd you take her
is i'm kind of ice skating rink resort kind of thing you know for about three
years i've had a gift card to this place terrania a resort
in uh it's about an hour outside of the city of
Los Angeles okay absolutely beautiful and uh you know it's a classic LA
gift you know how like i never tell you this story like i donated giz when i
first moved here i ever talked about this in the podcast uh no but the the bad
part was the woman wasn't requesting it
um to a clinic you mean yeah so it was in westwood there's this place called
ditty Reese which is a uh it's a place in westwood so it's huge with UCLA kids
it's called ditty Reese ditty Reese all right and it's a place that used to be like
the go -to spot if your parents can to town or whatever now it's way too far
you go to westwood the seamenbank is the now the the cookie place they give you
they give you ice cream between two cookies and it used to cost a dollar
i'm sure it's now this is not the sperm bank it's behind ditty Reese i thought you were saying
the sperm back was called ditty Reese no all right ditty Reese was this place uh it was two cookies
with ice cream in the middle for a dollar now i'm sure it's 1495 but when i first moved to LA it was
a big deal and i once when i was out there i thought well shit i'm gonna have to move back to Missouri
i have no money i'm not succeeding i hear what am i gonna do i go out ditty Reese with a buddy of
mine and i see an advertisement for this place jizz hundred dollars a load wow i'm like shit i'm
gonna do this three times a week i got a trash can in my office full of liquid gold yeah you're like
Tom Hanks in a punchline remember he says that's how he's making his living was coming he says
i've never seen punchline and i own it i bought it for a dollar i've never seen it uh it's worth
a watch i mean it's not a fantastic would you say it's the most accurate portrayal of the life of
the stand -up uh many stand -ups have actually said that hanks is the one i'm serious i'm not
making a joke that hanks is the one actor that actually seemed to catch like the rhythm of a stand -up
properly like he does sound like a stand -up in it and it's very dark it's the first i it's always
gonna have a shadow over because i saw it when i was a kid for the first time i should watch it i'll
watch when i was a kid i saw it for the first time and it was like the first time i ever saw
Tom Hanks playing like a darker character yeah but that's a line in the movie he's like you've got
seen turner and hooch in uh i never saw turner and hooch what i was a canine kid myself
turner hooch is so much better than canine i'm sure it was i zigged when i should his egg but i mean
yeah he had to pick one of the dog movies i went with the one with the fatter man and it it just
looked more fun to me but anyway i also loved belushi because that move that movie uh the the
smart guys or whatever he was in with him and john real man real man yeah i love that movie as a kid
so i did too one of my favorite Conan bits is i always used to love Tom Hanks that he was the only
big star that would go on Conan when he was on at 12 30 right he just thought he was funny and loved
and uh they were like you know tom we wanted to thank you for coming and gracing our our little show
and we we decided to reunite you tonight with one of your your co -stars one of your favorite co -stars
and he's like oh okay great and they bring out the skeletal remains of hooch
one of the darkest things i've ever seen on television and hanks loved it it was hilarious they bring
out a dog carcass on Conan anyway that's up there with and then you can finish but let's just stay on
this for one second yeah that's up there with uh well when hanks was on jimmy glick jimmy glicks spit
out a bunch of gumdrops that he had in his mouth and hank picks the pangs picks them up off the ground
and eats them which i admire but it's a funny man my favorite reunion reunion bit is uh when uh when
uh harrison Ford was on i think it was letterman maybe it was Kimmel and it was before force awakens
and they're like we have your old co -star here because we know you're doing a new stars movie then
then chubaka comes out and harrison Ford goes on this tirade about how chubaka fucked his wife
and he's just going get out of here you son of a bitch she was my wife that's great yeah i was really
if you don't force him like the kind of guy where if you don't make a hundred percent sure that he's
in on the joke and gonna do it that that's a joke that's gonna backfire you couldn't bring out the
remains of chubaka and and hope that Ford would laugh no no this was clearly clearly planned yeah yeah yeah
but uh it was funny that was i think the third tweet i ever posted years and years ago was
harrison Ford seems like the kind of guy who wouldn't speak to you for days if you beat him at putt putt
and i stand by that i don't know man he seems like he's got a nice sense of humor but uh
i've heard he's the biggest pothead in america uh i've heard the same and i love that i love that about
him too i he he's i've heard him and aniston or like the biggest kind of a less pothead i couldn't
love jammy anymore we'd actually divorced pit and aniston because pit was too much of a pothead he
was like the character in dromance right and he was he was not attached emotionally he was
completely gone from the relationship but then once they split up aniston missed the weed and kept
at it's what i've heard here's a little fun fact for about friends for you okay originally in
phrasier the role of ra's i knew this was lisa kudra replaced five days before i think shooting
yeah uh and then she got cast in front so it all worked out so what i'm trying to say is as i am bound
for a major successful sitcom role since i was taken out of your show that's true you you will be in
the next friends yes um anyway i know you've been watching a lot of phrasier you never finished your
thing about i will all right i'm sorry i bet yeah i've been i'm in season uh i think seven or eight right
now i always love phrasier when it was on to masterpiece i watched five the other night didn't smile
i i appreciated the writing which five first five uh well it's like any other show it takes
a minute to kind of get their stride i don't like the i like it starting with the second season
because that's when he gets the haircut and he looks yeah like he looks through the whole show
and he and the dad starts being a little friendlier right and you know the first season there's a lot
of awkward like where the dad's like your mother would be ashamed every episode yeah and it's like
they get away from that a bit and they start to build a bond in season two it's beautiful by the end of
season 11 like niles is coming in he's like hi dad like you see the love it's such a beautiful
character arc i'll stick with it of course i mean i watch it the first time around but uh i had read
this onion article about this episode that was they said it was the best sitcom episode of the 90s
and i'm like oh here it is on hulu i got to watch this thing season three it's the leap year episode
and he's telling everybody you got to take a chance yeah that's a leap year and then at the end
he winds up singing the song and he sings the lyrics badly and they were describing this as the
the one of the greatest sitcom scenes of all time it wasn't funny it was a rip off of frank
dribbins uh butchering of the national anthem and then they could gun and i was really thrown by it
they had five different critics at the onion raving about that's not a good episode that's an
episode that when it comes on i skip it like that's not a great one you want to see a hilarious one watch
merry christmas misk mousk moscavitch i think it's called okay it's my favorite of the phrase your
christmas episodes and the plot is he starts dating a girl her and her mom come over the girl
realizes that treasure is not jewish and he has to pretend like he's jewish for the mom and it's a
total far it's a the best episode is a phrasier the pharsical ones where i agree the sword fight
episode was always my favorite one it's a total pharsical thing and it's like niles and the dad
pretending they're jewish and everything mm -hmm it's really really fucking funny uh that's one of my
favorites i might start working through i'm i'm i'm working through all the family i'm on season three
i had never seen it i mean i i'm doing a lot with these sitcoms i want to get i want to be a master
look me too i bought an entire i bought the entire series go on the family yes i got up to like five
i was loving it don't get me wrong but i was just like i got to take a break it's it's all in that house
there's so much it's oppressive yeah you know so you got to you got to take a breath but i mean you
want to talk about another brilliant show i mean jesus christmas um anyway folks about my giz
i go to this place i say so this is a hundred dollars of a toss basically she goes yes i am not
exaggerating when i say that the nurse behind the counter was porno hot and eight she was an Asian nurse
from vaguely flirtatious i had just moved to la i was probably twenty six twenty seven yeah they
got to get you in the mood they're gonna have nurse ratchet back there she goes there's two rooms
back there um she goes we'll give you some materials here and she sets a dvd face down on the table
and she goes just take your time coming out whenever you're ready and as i'm walking back to the room
i flip the dvd and it is called in a medical facility
jam it all the way up my ass part two so it it says jam it all jam it up my ass and then it's one of
those where like a cartoon character hammers in a sign that says all the way like the little add -on
i always like a zany porno myself yeah so i'm like jam it all the way up my ass part two jesus
a will i be able to follow the story having not seen the original there you go b which is the only
joke to work making that seriously that's the only joke to make but b um the assumption that i
just be a guy off the street needs to see really aggressive anal porn as opposed to just like
you think in a medical facility they'd give you a sports illustrated swimsuit type deal
no they apparently they want you out i guess well they yeah and i mean also might
our dear friend pinkstone told me a title of a porno movie once in the song college
we've we've quoted we've referred to the title that to this day it's the funniest porno title i've
ever heard my life and it is sink it deep or get the fuck out
haha joe i've heard that from so many women in this time
which part of the sentence the whole the whole thing here's the thing dude when i went i talk about
the story of this in my act when i went to to do a semen's now i had to do a semen sample
because they thought i might have a prostate issue right which i ended up not but i had to go to do a
semen's now either there was gonna be like that like i go and they give me a porno whatever the lady
at the nurse at the place where i went she gave me a cup and she goes men's rooms out our front door
down the hole on the left and i was like wow that's a public men's room yeah you want to go
whack off in the public men's room right now wow so i'm not gonna tell the whole story but i went down
i was like i can't do it yeah i went back i go i'm sorry i can't do this swear my life she goes
that's okay take it home and do it there why would you do it there i go really why don't you
open with that next time lady yeah yeah i go into this booth i shut the door it's pitch black
of course all you can think about is how every surface in this little booth must be full of com oh
yeah i insert excuse the pun the DVD jam it all the way up my ass comes up and we're talking about like
girls just being brutally fucked in the ass i'm watching this i'm uncomfortable i'm thinking
i don't want to come immediately i also don't want to be in here for 30 minutes and then
have to face this asian nurse yeah yeah i was panicked i got it done and what i felt was a very
reasonable amount of time i walk out with a cup of jizz the whole time you're like is this gonna be
a lot of jizz is it too little jizz um you know like what do they see in here just being her first rodeo
i know i know but i walk out of course you're nervous i hand it to her um i start for the door
and as i open the door just uh mr. wash i turn i go yes she goes could we um we get the DVD back please
complete accident i'm holding the DVD it look like i was trying to steal jam it all the way up my ass
i tried to make a joke about it she did not so much a smile and help me out no she got what she needed
out of you it's done the lap dance is over yeah get out of the room i give it back to her
and i go so when does the check arrive i thought all these forms she goes well this is your preliminary
to make sure that your your stuff is good so you don't get anything on this first time i'm like oh okay
it felt kind of used drive home car breaks down on the drive home i'm sitting on the side of the road
having just jerked off in a cup black clouds of smoke billowing out of my right 97 satter than i bought
for a thousand dollars i'm like why did i move to Los Angeles the question i still ask myself to this
without the commerce smoke i go home they come back they're like look
26 year old dude you got good grades in college you're not a mutant
you you pass come in you can do up to three donations a week i'm like 300 dollars a week
done can we still do this yeah why am i not doing this you'll hear why in a moment okay
i go in i do the first one i hand it to her she hands me a coupon for one free AMC movie
okay an AMC movie theater i go i thought i get a hundred dollars a ton she goes yeah but the first
time just to kind of get you in the system we just give you this AMC pass i'm like all right i go to
use the AMC pass here in Los Angeles it doesn't cover the full cost of the movie okay because
LA movies are so expensive i had to pay three additional dollars all right so what happens the second
time second time i go in i jerk off and she goes so just so you know i'm i'm obliged to tell
i have to tell you after this point your semen can be used in the production of a child the first
time is making sure everything is good the second time is making sure the first time was not a fluke
and i get all that now your your face is going to be in our book of like dudes that they can
pick right they can read about your background okay okay and by that she meant it could be used in
pregnant woman not that they were going to build a model of a baby out of your semen yeah okay good
good that's good to know it's a professional kind of place i go in the back i jerk off i hand it to her
and i say now excuse me i just want to make sure because i haven't asked this question yet but
the kid once it grows up like can't look you up right like that will smith ted dancin movie made in
saw in the theater and thanks for blowing one of my event movies now but i go uh the kid can't look
me up down the line right she goes actually as of 2003 or whatever when a child born from a semen
donation um turns 18 in the city of los angeles if they go to the sperm donor place and they say i
want to find out who my father was the city of los angeles is legally required to tell them who
they're that's it that's all that stopped you Joe so so like i get married i have kids and then you
have a grown kid that shows up and says hey apparently you were the donor thank you can i get some
money oh stop it can i get me some money you don't think that kid might ask for legally uh up
up bound to uh uh give him any money or her any money i couldn't do it i couldn't like have somebody
show up my door and be like oh this is my son now that's the exact way i want to have a kid
fully grown kid shows up we got different hey kiddo how you doing let's go get a few beers huh
cuz i'm thinking i don't even know who i'm gonna be married to it that was a single man at this
point i'm like what if my wife freaks out what if anything i i i said throw it in the trash answer me
this the place is there i could go do this right now i could go make three hundred dollars per week
just to masturbate Joe you know you can make money donating semen you know that i didn't know i could
make that much money i'm telling you this they're not gonna love you smoking weed that i don't smoke weed
they're not gonna love certain things about your lifestyle i drink is that going to be a problem
for them you can lie about it but it'll probably be a problem oh why about it all right go donate
just they never said a man can't drink when they're trying to get pregnant i've never heard that before
that's true uh i just i couldn't do it could i couldn't do it it's twelve hundred bucks a month
to go have a great time with apparently some real filthy movies too and this is what they were
showing in in 2007 who know i mean they got to be woo yeah woo woo yeah well i don't even know
how i got on this i was gonna talk about how like the amc pass wasn't enough to see a movie
you know guys i don't know how pat got on this story about getting off i need it oh oh oh
bad he did folks um pat drink your damn wine you know i poured you a glass of
some nice red wine you're barely drinking it over there well i'm not a wine sugar
Joe it's not shugging pat it's been a half an hour i'm sipping like a gentleman um all right well let's
get to our first one uh the topic for today i don't want to do this five to the i mean i guess
we want to say what here's the number one movie we were most excited about five i'm not going to
be able to quantify them we'll just say five in any order i'm gonna be able to quantify them i'm
gonna quantify my number one the restaurant any order we're gonna discuss folks our five biggest
event movies the five times we were if i have this correct most excited to go to the motion picture
where it was an event yeah yes okay go ahead you can go first
unless you want me to go first i'll go first because i can tell you need some time to think
go ready yes uh number five tells him the crypt demon night okay uh and i talked about this on the
podcast we reviewed it but uh Pinkstone and i were were insanely rabid uh tells him the crypt fans
you couldn't pull us away from that show when they announced they were actually going to make a movie
that was an original story uh that wasn't taken from the comic books we couldn't have been more excited
we were so thrilled to hear the whole team was involved um and i mentioned this again on the show
i was so excited that we went on opening night that was sold out we had to buy tickets to another movie
then sneak in sure uh and even though i was on a date with a girl that i desperately wanted to
impress when the lights went down i yelled pinkstone because we were we had to sit in separate areas yeah
and then he made fun of me later like i can't believe you were on a date and you thought
that that was like the right thing to do and i was like dude demon night superseded everything
tonight for me like i can't believe you went on a date and brought a male friend well we were going
as a group it was like a soft first date like we were going as a group of friends and it was kind of
like him yeah i think he's cute like and then you know we all went out like in a no pressure zone
kind of date uh but that was a huge huge event film for me as a kid all right we're a kid teenager i mean
sure isn't that young sure um all right i'll just i'll just go myself um for me
i think i would have a to say well see the only one i truly know is my number one here's what
i'm gonna say this is gonna be the shocker the rest might be a little more expected i'm gonna
reference the i believe 1992 film starring john ritter palm dober and Eugene levy
and the picture is called stay tuned this was an event picture for you i was a weird fucking kid
the rest are gonna be a lot more traditional is this the one before we started recording where you
said i got one that you're gonna be like i just believe about i remember pleading with my dad and
usually it was a rating issue like i begged my dad to see pulled fiction forever and it was just a flat
no stay tuned was pg i was like i'm so excited we have to go opening night we have to none of my friends
were talking about stay tuned this was the movie that was supposed to be directed by tim Burton but
eventually it was just not that basically was just a bunch of parodies of movies and television not a great
driving over miss daisy i know i remember it's it's sort of the like more mainstream version of
uhf that's exactly right yeah uh and i did love uhf i love uhf still stay tuned for me doesn't hold up
it no of course not uh it was a parody movie and i was very into the parodies at the time
and i just remember being like i think probably because when you're 12 that's the age when you're
starting to kind of be like able to control when you go to the movies and like if you want if you
demand something your parents usually take you to see it and you start to realize that i was obsessed
with seeing this movie saw it i liked it i probably laughed way too hard because i had put on such a
show but how i wanted to see it sure but even as a kid you were like this probably isn't as good as me yeah
yeah and they did a wains world spoof and of course i was very obsessed with wains world which could
could just have easily been on this list but it was less interesting uh i remember all my friends
after a batting cage when i was on a baseball team we're all going to see wains world and my dad was like
it's PG 13 so i need to see it before you can see it right and all of my friends went to see wains
world on like a Saturday afternoon and i had to wait till it came to the fucking dollar show and then
wains world is a fucking masterpiece but i wouldn't go that far but i think it's a good movie
it's one of the best comedies ever made in my opinion but uh top 10 comedies ever made
it's one of the best comedy it wouldn't be my top 10 but i think it's one of the best but that's
and that means it's not one of the best comedy i like a lot of com wains world you know listen i'm saying
it's good i think wains world invented a lot of the shit that modern comedy takes that is true
it really did and as far as being an s and l movie like holy shit oh christ it's it's head and shoulders
above i mean the only other s and l movies that could maybe come close are i i hear the ladies man's
very funny i've never seen it but it's fine feral's funny and it's funny uh night at the rocks he's
pretty funny at the rocks bar is fun or rocks bar excuse me um i only blues brothers the only one
i put up with well blues brothers is the number one ever whose brothers is probably right s and l
adaptation movie but just as good i mean these are both classic companies in my opinion i bet you
still better than your family is kind of funny Stewart says his family is a great movie but it's a drama
that's what people were not it's a drama about being in a family of alcoholics it's a drama i'm not
saying there aren't a few laugh attempts but it's like a serious movie about 12 step addiction
so they tried to do like the whole like remember when they did the spin -off from merley marie
tyler more and ed asner suddenly it was like a yeah our drama about journalism and it worked
was i telling you about unis you did tell you about unis but you did not tell these fine listeners
of ours about unis and that's something we need to talk about right now i haven't watched it yet
because i'm too excited and you better wait for me you motherfucker come over and watch it all right
please i was i wanted to make this so special that i haven't watched it in like two weeks but my sister
my sister and i get along fine but you know she lives in Missouri we don't talk much
when we were kids we were not really close either but every night we would watch two episodes minimum
of mama's family which in my memory is one of the funniest sitcoms ever made and i'm sure it's dog
but i love mama's family it was uh
bam bam bam bam bam bam bam bam bam bam bam bam bam bam bam yeah just hit comedy white
white trash vicki Lawrence played mama and in the early episodes carol burnette played unis
because mama's family was a spin -off yes from the carol burnette show yes carol burnette played unis
the miserable and like it wasn't always a dark character she was very unhappy the whole family was
kind of unhappy but it never it was always just kind of hiccups yeah Betty white played uh uh uh uh
an aunt room a clan of hand well Betty white played the like sort of trampy aunt and room a clan
and played like the bible lady which is why they switched roles right and golden girls
and all these characters were gone in the later seasons of mama's family but my sister sent me
the box set of mama's family and it was six seasons which i was blown away that the show even
lasted that long this was a show that after its first season was all straight to syndication which
they don't even do anymore yeah it was just a syndicated show uh this box set i'm looking through the
special features and what do i see but between the carol burnette show and mama's family they released
a 90 minute film a TV film a drama featuring all the mama's family characters but like a Tennessee
Williams player they're all struggling with being unhappy with alcoholism i read a review of this
thing that got me so excited that this might be one of my top five most anticipated thing
the the thought of like imagine watching like your favorite sitcom as a dark like staged play drama
and i have brought i have brought myself to watch it because i'm too excited uh i'm going to watch
it with you it'll be great i can't wait to see this and now i want to watch Stewart saves his family
i remember Stewart says the family being very interesting my i know my dad wanted me to watch it
because he was uh n -a -a and i remember thinking boy this isn't funny at all because they always
thought Stewart's part is dark comedy i don't think it was a drama no there were at least the the back
half is a pretty serious drama really yeah all right it's all dramatic actors in the in the roles
like out franken and uh folks who else yeah pat why did you tell al franken to do it he did
hi threw it back on you for once um you know because he's good enough he's smart enough and dog on it
i wanted him to sexually assault a woman while he's left well you're a man that always says the
perfect retort and that's why you run a tv show i've said it before i'll say it again thanks Joe
all right my number four casino yeah uh when i heard uh now i was a kid i was 12 years old and my
mother showed me good fellas she almost forced me to watch the movie what a dream i had to sneak it
yeah you weren't allowed to see pulp fiction you were 26 years old uh no i i my mom i want good
fellows with my ear pressed to the speaker of my 24 inch television my mom sat me down she said i
want you to watch this movie i really think you're gonna like it i'll watch it with you they're
gonna curse a lot i'm just warning you but yeah that was her big concern not these stabbings in the
gut and the stomping of people's faces him offering his wife a stack of cash and then pushing her head
down on to his dad he doesn't push her head down she she goes down because he goes he goes i can i got
to go oh all right yeah yeah hashi uh oh no in the in the jail they uh you see the guy forcing the what
the you see that in the in the call booths and then in uh it's seen all past you pushing the head down
yeah pisty pushes the woman's head down the bones head yeah it's not sharing well he does push
sharing stones head down later but the first time he does it for the foreshadowing you know this is his
thing is when he walks the he gives the woman the tour of the restaurant and then walks her out to
the car as he's explaining the properties of veal yeah yeah and they get into the car and he goes he goes
that pink feel you can pound that shit for days it'll never get tender and he just yeah he goes move
over sweetheart yeah he slides over he slides it uh anyway uh it's an outrageous film uh i was uh the
casino i was excited for it because when i was a kid as i said my mom made me watch good fellows
i didn't want to and then i watched it and i was obsessed with it from that day forward uh i just
loved it so much so when i heard they're making a sort of pseudo sequel to good fellows uh it's
called casino it's different characters but it's based on a book by the same author that wise guy was
written by it's got the same cast essentially uh and my mom told i remember mom telling me about
casino she goes oh and they're going to have all these cameos by famous casino comedians like vegas
comics and i was like i mean sign me the fuck up yeah when i was 15 the first concert ever saw was
Sinatra with Don Rickles opening so i already had something else an infatuation by first concert was
weird al at six flags well i'm not surprised yeah that's right that was 32 at the time the uh no i but
i had such an infatuation already with this world i was just so so excited i remember being in college
it was my freshman year and i remember me and all my friends and my little dorm hallway
the rowdy friends rowdy friends what do you mean all my like all my rowdy friends are coming over tonight
what the hell is that Monday night football oh no i don't know do you think i watch a foot by
i don't know Joe no one cares less about football than me i know all my rowdy friend you know
oh you're ready for the football that's hey Williams junior yeah that's right yeah you know you know a little
but didn't get fired because he said something crazy i'm sure he did anyway
we all went on like you know a a Wednesday night or something you in the family no you're
me and every friend i'm sorry and i was so excited and i remember when it started i was watching it
and i was i was enjoying it because it was very good fellows ask but i remember the one thing i was
upset about was over the first 20 minutes or so i was like and peshy's really playing like a nice guy
in this one i don't care for that and then the scene comes where they're in the bar and uh the guy
tells the nero to take the pen and shove it up his fucking ass right and peshy takes the pen stabs
the man repeatedly in the neck the man's on the ground crying and whimpering and peshy steady over
him going what's that ace what's that you hear sounds like a little girl whatever the tough guy
told my friend is sure the pen is fucking it yeah and i was like holy shit they just put this into
like tenth gear right this is gonna be nuts and and of course they did and i loved every second of
that movie i i loved it i had such a blast watching it i was 15 i remember every single thing about
casino coming out and if i had been allowed to see it Joe this would have definitely been on my list
but i can't say a most anticipated movie that i was not allowed to see sure well what is your next
anticipate i was so excited at at this same the exact same year this is how good a December uh
denero had heat came out yes which i did sneak into an absolutely fucking loved of course that's
very impressive because when i first saw it i'm a little two years older than you when i first
saw it when it came out i was bored to tears it took it took my friend uh rob net off who's uh
who i was in theater with at in college uh who who was in my opinion the best male actor in the
program uh and he said to me he is one of the greatest
brick and mire of your that the atom's god if you will maybe the christian bill
but anyway uh he he i remember him saying to me like no you're wrong about he you need to watch
again it's one of the best movies ever made yeah and then i watched again and i was like oh now that
i'm not expecting patino and denero to be in every scene together this is awesome that's sometimes
that's all it takes yeah i felt disappointed as well that they weren't sharing more scenes together
and then what's so funny is at the time they were able to inspire that sort of excitement whereas
now patino's doing directed on demand shit i'm so excited for the Irishman to come out and i'm
just praying to god it's not uh let's not jinx it all right go ahead score says he doesn't make
shit he doesn't make shit no he didn't make vinyl which i wouldn't say vinyl was shit i just
directed the pilot yet i just didn't like vinyl it wasn't shit i just didn't like vinyl was
shit he also did silenced which was shit but it meant a lot to him so well but also critics really
like silence they did i can deal with critics liking it at least silence kundun i'm saying
Marty these are your these are your movies i don't need them i know he goes down that road
once a while it was a religious man he was like i want to make a picture about the first
pope's childhood yeah i know i'm gonna please don't Marty um i was because i was so excited about
casino but couldn't share with my dad why because he didn't know i had seen good fellows i couldn't
see casino he went one day by himself he was probably my age and went and saw it at like 2 p .m.
and i was so jealous and he raved about it and you know i have friends to this day who like
a scene of more than good films i don't agree but i get it i don't agree either but i i could tell you
i could be swayed at the right in the right moment i could be swayed but uh but so so your
heat you saw heat you're in your loving it i'm gonna go forward a couple years to my most anticipated
which was i thought you were saying heat was your number four no oh pat but i'll get i'll get to it
quickly jackie brown great uh almost made my list and in a very similar situation i had seen
pope fiction on the sly but jackie brown hit at a time where i was newly 17 and able to see whatever
the fuck i wanted and it came out at like christmas time and the trailer was fantastic trailer was
get ready the four top song get ready yeah get and i i i was so fucking excited and the movie
more than lived up to it and it was so many people have these stories of going to see it all hyped up
on that pope fiction high and being let down for some reason i never was i loved it from the jump uh
that's another one i didn't like as much it took a couple watches for me to get it
yeah i love the film now uh originally we were going to do our top five movie villains of all time
for this episode right we changed it but my number four was odel roby from jackie brown uh but um
we don't need to go much in a jacket brown we've we've covered it endlessly on this podcast
but that's that's my number four that's a great flick man um it almost made my list it's probably my
number six to be honest yeah uh my number three okay folks sorry but from here on out it's all uh one
note for me uh the phantom menace well look i'm not saying it's a great flick i'm just telling you
when george lucas announced suddenly in the late nineties that he was going to make more star wars films
of course i was beside myself um i wasn't quite as excited that they were prequels but i was really
fucking excited yeah uh and i remember sitting in the theater with uh again with pinkstone and uh
my friend scott who you've met hoffman very many times and my friend jamey jowett all deer friends
and old friends and we were sitting there i remember us gripping hands as the lights went down like
this is about to happen right now uh now the only reason it's not higher on my list is because
early reviews of it so bad well no early reviews of it attainted there were early reviews of
phantom menace that were like it's not good the cg yes i guess i remember hearing like Howard
stern two days before and he was like it doesn't make like it looks like they're not even in the scene
with the things cuz it looks fake and the kids stinks and whatever so that tainted it but it didn't
take away from the fact that this was one of the most exciting moments of my entire life that i was
gonna see a new star wars movie something we never thought would happen sure um
afterwards outside the theater we definitely had the like yes uh woo what did you think of that
yeah i supported it through and through and was like look i liked it it's not exactly what i wanted
but i'm gonna stick in there with it saw it a few more times liked it
saw the attack of the clones a bunch of times like it even more saw a range of the Sith like
it even more so uh i hung in there patiently yeah um but uh but still it was a wonderful experience and
and you know that's it uh i need to go back to the future
but i was excited to see back the future three the other two i was too young for but i was very excited
three is a it's made for tv movie it's terrible i think it's fine but uh the lease of the series
certainly but by like a thousand percent um i need to go back to and i need to tell you a little bit
about who i was as a kid so when i was 1990 i'm nine years old the same age as young Kevin McAllister
mr. McCulley Culkin right and when home alone dropped every one of my friends was very excited to
see it because it's a kid kicking ass right but i gotta tell you i even at age nine was so obsessed
with the writing of mr. John Hughes right uh i had seen Uncle Buck the year prior and it became one
of my all -time favorite movies which it still is and i was just like okay everything about this movie
is designed for a ten -year -old boy to lose his shit sure but what my friends did not have
was the knowledge that it was written by my personal favorite filmmaker at that time and one of
them to this day mr. John Hughes he wrote home alone i was so excited and also i wasn't following
there was no ain't it cool at this time uh there was no way to find out this shit
but i saw an entertainment tonight thing where at the peak of my excitement i'm like when will
home alone come out god damn it i was insisting that my parents i remember as if i was on trial
telling my parents this one cannot be like that man this one cannot be like all the other ones
we have to wait for the dollar show we need to go to the mall and pay full price right five seventy
five which it was at the time to see home alone and if i have to pay for me and you i'm gonna
do what i have to do to make that happen i was so excited to see home alone i was pleading with
my family because and then after all this all my excitement on entertainment tonight i saw that
mr. John candy was playing some sort of role in home alone and then you're already talking about
probably one of my most anticipated movies right he was my favorite star of the day right i was
violently shaking when i went to see home alone at the holiday season around thanksgiving with
my parents the candy cameo isn't much either it's kind of a bummer you want it to be bigger
oh i think it's so funny really that it was all improv he's funny when he's playing the clarinet
i remember but like you just it just made me want more john can when he tells that story which was improv
about how when he was young his parents left him overnight oh i forgot about that yeah
in a funeral home with the body and he was all the body right he ever fussed all that shit
i mean i think john can he's incredible in that movie all right you're right it's it's a bigger part
than i remember yeah but i mean we're talking that this is at a time still when i'm nine ten years old
where i know for a fact without having seen it that plan strides on will be one of my favorite movies
because my two favorite actors at that time were steve martin john canny and still i could not see it
because it was rated are and i'm like this is a new movie coming out i was shaking and i love the
movie so much that at that time it was my favorite movie and it remained that way until
my number one choice which i will get to momentarily but home a lot of course number three you got
two more yeah i know okay but i'll get to my number one when i get to it all right all right fine
i remember wanting to see plane trains and on to be automobiles so badly because
uh i remember like entertainment tonight or whatever the hell the like magazine shows were at
that's all we had back then yeah honestly a better time i remember them showing the rental car scene
with steve martin and being like steve martin takes a funny twist in this too you might not expect
from steve martin and it played the scene it was all beeps and i was like i can't wait to see steve martin
say fuck repeatedly i couldn't i i was living for that scene when uh scot night scot
offman once again and i rented it do you think we were talking on the super dark times episode which we
recorded earlier a little peek behind the curtain which by the way might come out after this or before
this i don't know yes do you think and this to me is the age old question do we just know too much
now and that is why nothing is fun and nothing is good and we're not excited about anything because
we know everything before we walk into the theater uh it's part of it but no it's it's it's it's an
actual fact that uh look we talked about phrasier earlier you know so it's funny you bring this up
because i was thinking about this the whole season seven or six whatever plot line is that dapney
falls in love with this lawyer named donnie who's not who he's niles divorce lawyer who plays donnie
i can't remember the actor's name but he's been on curb your enthusiasm as soon as you see him you're like
oh yeah that guy all right and he's the best dude yeah and because he's the best dude that's what makes it
so crazy and amazing when niles goes to the wedding and finally tells her at almost at the altar
i love you and i'm sorry and she runs she's a runaway bride yeah and i was watching and i was like
they would never do this now they would be like no dapney will be too unlikable and it's like no it's
not that she's unlikable for leaving the nice guy it's that she's so in love with niles that she has
to make a terrible sacrifice for it and that's the difference now there is no they wouldn't let you
make a movie like home alone now no absolutely not they wouldn't let you make it so it's that it's
the nuance that's that's gone yeah anyway my number i mean luckily outside of stay tuned which i
remember enjoying at the time all of mine really lived up to my my dream that's the goal i mean do you
have any that you're we're just a slap in the face i mean i never saw thanda menace as a slap in
the face i was disappointed but i wasn't sure i wasn't like i said i was like okay this is
clearly a slow start but we'll see where it's going and my experience as a guy who who didn't love
star wars as much of my friends was we all go to see star wars can't get in settled for the matrix
become very very interested in the matrix right and then when we saw star wars it seemed old -fashioned
and even stupider in comparison it took me a long time to come around in the matrix because everybody
at that time was like the matrix is the new future of fuck star wars and i really took that
personally right much like when i went to see uh misses doubt fire and it was sold out so i saw a
perfect world with clean ace wood and gevin cosner which is an a plus movie right that's when i
learned that like what everyone's telling you to do is not always i saw doubt firing the theater i
didn't like it i didn't eventually but i don't think it's funny not fire spot i'm not saying it's
without humor i just don't think it's that good of a movie it's a schmaltcy i don't like it
anyway i'm noticing a pattern with your movies and my movies my movies all needed a precedent of
excitement there was an nostalgia even with every movie i'm picking they were all set up by something
i already loved yours are just you saw a fresh thing and you were really excited about the idea
that's interesting i mean jack you brown came off of pulp fiction for sure except for that one
though the other ones are like yes that's true that's true um okay my number two is
another star wars film the force awakens we don't need to go into this deeply all i can say is this
i was on red eye once when that was still a show on fox news when they announced that lucas had sold
lucas film uh to disney and that they were going to do a sequel trilogy to the original star wars
trilogy with the original cast members they brought it up they were made everybody in the
most excited i could human possibly be right now i can't wait for this uh gym norton was on
that night he said why why are you excited about this and i said because it's literally to me
like somebody telling you the Beatles didn't die they're still alive and they're going to put out
three new records i was just like i never forget i never thought there'd be another star wars movie
i never in a zillion years thought there'd be another star wars movie and i'd see fucking Han Solo
and Luke and lay again and Chewbacke and whatever so like uh well Chewbacke was in Rembrandt's of the
Sith so but you know it was awesome it delivered everything i wanted it to to deliver i loved it
salt multiple times in the theater i cried multiple times in the theater out of joyous nostalgic excitement
and i just fucking loved it man so uh that was that was a huge one for me i i knew you uh through this
time i i knew you to be very excited about it i and i and i like that you can still have those moments
as an adult i really don't i mean that the most recent of these like i were talking like no country
for old man or something like right and it was just an established director who i love right um but i
don't get i don't get that pumped anymore which which really bums me out is an ongoing source of
of trauma well i mean star wars is really the only thing they can do it for me right i can't think
of another unless they said they were going to do like an official sign felt reunion or something
like that like sure there are a few things that that exist that if they brought it back i'd be that
excited about right but uh but anyway what's your number two my number two and and no protect ord
i'm gonna have to go with
you know if i'm being real i'm gonna have to go with boogie nights
oh i ever wanted you to be was real i'm going from this the year basically when i
uh you know became a man like those late 90s were very big for me because it's different than most
people i was now freed up to see not only new orated movies but movies i have been hearing about for
years do the right thing and all that raging bull sure good fellows reservoir dogs i'm watching
all this shit that i had been dreaming about seeing but when when one of these things would come to the
theater it's a very big deal so like we're i'm lumping a bunch of movies that have nothing to do with
each other except maybe sex and i was i was a horn dog as well i also did not have porn at this time
right boogie nights a movie that is rightly compared to good fellows sure one of the only ripoffs that is
i would say in the same ballpark yeah boogie nights a movie about pornography so everyone's
raving about this movie it's Paul Thomas Anderson i can't wait to see it i'm excited to see it
and this element of like seeing potentially graphic sex and nudity in a theater sure
which i had never done in my entire life it was like 18 and couldn't uh and i went to the Esquire
theater which was maybe an hour from my house which sounds like a porn theater i know it didn't say
hello as but the Esquire it's still there as far as i know but they had six shitty theaters and then
the biggest screen in the Midwest was their claim to fame and they showed boogie nights in the main screen
and generally they would show the big blockbuster on that but they were the only theater Missouri sure
that first week that had boogie nights so i was like i am going to see on this giant screen
pornography and that my interest going in was very purient whatever you want to call it sexual
and uh i loved and then continued to love that movie so much that i saw the five o 'clock
who was uh uh i went by myself i walked out i uh i had a burrito next store and then i saw the
15 as well i've never done that in my life wow saw twice and i just was like that that was a time
for me the reason it was also exciting if i'm being real all my most anticipated movies are when your kids
you're most excited absolutely but that was a time when i was like i can get out of Missouri
i want to do something creative i know i know what i want to do and like hearing that that guy was like
27 Paul Thomas Anderson and all that i was like this is this is this is incredible and to see a movie
that for all intents and purposes is porn good fellows right on the big screen because that was
at a time where you're like well fuck i'll never get to see good falls in the but now occasionally
they'll bring it out of the repertory house but uh well christ thing about what people did before
there was video rental even can you believe they just had to wait until they showed it on tv again
but and i do think that would make for a fascinating episode of this podcast i i think there was something
so beautiful about that though oh no i agree i agree i'm just saying yeah when i think about like
circling in tv guide like you need to record at three fifteen yeah this movie which you've been looking
for for years it's gonna be on tv like i think the future generations have really lost out on that
show it's a bummer and it's it's it's the excitement of going to the video store and saying you
know uh do you have you know indiana jones in the last crusade and them saying uh you know what we
have one copy left right be like oh can i please can i have you know like it was so special and then
also these things like the this is the time when vhs cassettes cost if you like lost it or something
or damage it you'd pay like ninety five dollars uh which is one of one of the funny bits on
side fell when he what's the movie they always keep seeing uh uh rochelle rochelle where you like
loses the copy and the guys like that's ninety five dollars right what there's a question yeah things
of change and when you say any end of jones it reminds me of one that i've left off my list but if
i'm being real my friends came out here from Missouri when i first moved L .A. and i remember that
morning us or the night before we were gonna buy tickets for crystal skull i know you like more than
most but we were like all right well let's say we wake up in noon we have a little lunch and then
at some point we were like i'm too excited yeah it's one of the last time that felt that we were like
we need to be there for like the nine a .m. show at the arc light yeah i saw that by myself that one
guy where we sat afterwards uh you know again i wasn't thrilled i liked it though i liked it fine uh
but but that was one i saw that opening day at nine or ten a .m. alone yeah because we were already well
into trendy lucas sucks territory and i was like i'm not seeing this with anybody it's gonna
fuck it up for me right um but anyway but just like the matrix is the pain of
phantom menace me and those same friends ten years later had our pain from crystal skull eased by
and glorious bastards i loved it but what's the connection there we saw them in the same week
oh okay i'm pretty sure i mean somebody might prove me wrong but i'm pretty sure we walked out of
Indiana Jones we were so miserable and we were like we gotta see something else and then luckily
the feelings we wanted to get from Indiana Jones we got from a glorious band yeah glorious
bastards is a great pick man and i'm glad they're doing a fifth Indiana Jones because i'll see it
i'll definitely see it and i just know a buff huh no love buff the rumor is no love buff just
Harris and coming back i know the big talk was that love buff was taken over the franchise no no
that was really that's not never everybody repeatedly denied that it was rumors but i'm just happy
after hustle have died in force awakens yes to get to see Indiana Jones hopefully right off into
the sunset i want to pretend that Harrison Ford will live forever i hope so they did a lot
right i mean having Karen Allen on their excited me but boy it was not great for me uh my number one
as you said the there's never more excitement than when you're a kid this is yet another star wars
film uh but this is hands down the most excited i ever was in my life i've said it for
thirty some years at this point return to the jedi was the most excited i ever was
to go to a movie now you got to understand so you were six jedi count yeah i think i was about six
or seven i was about to go into first grade so six i mean i was two i don't have i was six and i
had seen empire uh a few times i saw it in the theater uh when i was very very young that's probably
four three or four and then uh and then i'd seen it subsequently on home video or whatever and i
remembered i knew the i knew the story i i knew the story so here you are you're a six -year -old kid
i remember saying to my mom one day when does the new star wars come out and she goes i don't know
and i said mom i bet it's taking so long because they're still paying the actors from the last one
you know like i remember i thought that was like a hilarious joke uh anyway when they said this
thing was coming out i didn't see trailer one of this fucking thing before i got into the theater i
remember my dad telling me we're going to a Catholic grade school today to have an interview to see
if you you can go there and he said guess what if things go well we're gonna take it to see return
to the jedi tonight he was probably gonna take me either way but he was just getting me all worked up
you know i just got excited here in that so over how exciting a preview was yeah the only way
you saw a preview was going to another movie so i'm out of my mind excited i go dad have you seen anything
he goes i did see the preview on tv the other night i was like what what did you see tell me anything
was Han Solo back what's going on he's like they didn't show much i just saw Luke and Darth Vader
an elevator which is a scene in the movie girl from the epinema playing yeah yeah we went to see this thing
again you're six years old you don't have any concept of Hollywood you don't have any concept of
i want it to be this i want it to be that all you know is i want to see the my favorite characters come
back please let Han Solo be okay he was frozen in carbonate and this thing was just a chain of
dominoes for a six -year -old one after the next i mean they they tell you in the scroll and the opening
crawl like Luke has returned to his home planet of tatooine to get Han Solo back from job of the hut
so you're like oh my god we're we're gonna meet job of the hut because this pre -special edition right
they go into job as palace you see fucking uh lando undercover in the palace you see boba fat you're like
Jesus Christ a bounty hunter brings chewbacca in you're like i don't even know what to do with myself
right now right the bounty hunter that brings chewbacca and goes and def the my favorite parts
well my two favorite parts still the first one is when java when the bounty hunter goes and you
don't know at this point that it's layered she goes i'm here to bargain for solo's life
and java goes i'll never get fit rid of my favorite decoration and he goes like this in the camera
pans left and you see Han Solo in carbonate in the wall i was like i'm getting chills right now i'm
getting overwhelmed and i was like oh my god he's there he's okay right yeah so uh that that cannot
happen in this day it can't i'm so dead inside this yeah so i don't like star wars and i'm excited
for you as a child this was incredible so that all happens she frees Han you find out she frees
Han cuz she's leia which is when you're six you don't see that coming you're not saying they're
coming yeah yeah and it's it's playing the fucking lion Han music and they kiss and it's it's just
you're just beyond yourself then Luke comes in because they're all captured at this point
Luke comes in wearing the fucking dark cloak the java guards try to attack him he does the
Vader choke move and you're like oh my god like Luke's like for real now like he's not the kid anymore
he's a fucking real Jedi now he goes in confronts java pulls out a blaster
falls into the pit has to fight the rancor the whole time you're like why isn't he using the lightsaber
like oh my god they take all of them out to the sarlac pit to kill them i might tear up
they take them off the sarlac pit to kill them uh they put Luke on the plank you're six yeah you're
like my favorite human being that's ever been in a movie is gonna die right now right they're gonna
push him in the sarlac pit Luke says java it's your last chance free us or die java laughs they say push
him in they push Luke over the plank he falls grabs the plank flips upside flips and does a back flip
into the air whatever lands back on the ship the fucking lightsaber shoots out of R2T2's head
he catches it unsheathes it and it's green because he lost the blue lightsaber in the last movie
in a very traumatic experience for a kid to see and you're just like I was fucking losing my mind dude
I can't I can't put it into words yeah the fact that you finally saw the emperor the fact that you
show them shoot Luke's hand and it's like the robotic circuits underneath uh the fact that he
you he unmasks Vader at the end I I was out of my fucking mind well then how was it that you speak
somewhat critically of Jedi to this time he is now that I'm older yeah I love that whole sequence to
me is is infallible yeah I don't like what he did in the special edition by adding the musical number
to it that bothers me but I do like some of the other stuff he had in the special edition he adds a
couple more like sort of rank or hints and stuff that actually I think work very well uh but
that whole sequence to me is perfection and as a kid uh you know I loved Ewoks just like my
six -year -old nephew loved Jar Jar Binks when the Phantom Menace came out it was a thing meant for kids
and right when I got older I was like I don't like how the these little teddy bears are like
making keystone cops out of the empire like they're getting hit in the head with rocks and shit
that bothered me I still love the redemption of Vader I still love all the emperor scenes
Ian McClellan is as Darth Sidious is fucking incredible
is it Ian McClellan sorry Ian McDermott excuse me Ian McDermott um that's the
the nothing will ever top that you can never be in that place ever again no that is to you don't know
what going in yeah that to me is like when somebody says yeah I saw the doors before Morrison died
or so it's like you don't know that that's gonna be the pinnacle but it was and it will
never be so I was trying to convey to Heather my my very first movie going experience was an
American tale and I was just trying to convey to her how like it just overwhelming and exciting it is
and my my I'll be most excited about having kids to share moves with them and taking
Oh yeah I mean that's the dream oh yeah you can kind of get excited again through them
but anyway that was your number two oh that was my number one there's your number one
so I'm my number one yeah my number one you had two glasses of wine as far as I can tell when
you told me this I knew my number one and the rest were gonna be you know things I had to come
up with but my my number one without any hesitation was what would unseat home alone and who framed
Roger Rabbit as my number one movie of all time at the time it's changed but uh I gotta say
Jurassic Park all right so you're 13 right there's a movie about dinosaurs where they're like
legit actual dinosaurs back to life like that was that was one of the few movies where like even like
2020 would talk about like the special effect I'm sure I love 2020 and they'd show you the special
effects and my parents are back pack I'm watch this and I was blown away by it but
uh my my best friend at the time Ryan who's visiting in a couple weeks can't wait to Sam
uh he's like I'm reading the book me and him started reading the book and then we we did it
a couple times it was the race to get the book done before the movie came out sure and I had so many
friends in school at this time that we're all reading the book and we're like did you get to the part
where this and that right and the book and the movie is not all that I mean there there are some
similarities of course there's a lot of differences oh I think you're gonna see the opposite I was
I think it's it's it's it's some but like the the movie is infinitely better than the book oh really
Michael Keaton are um Jesus Christ Michael Crite and RIP is uh you know what I wanted to say Michael
Keaton earlier when we were talking about punchline because he was a stand -up before an actor Michael
he makes a lot of sense to me and he's I've actually seen his stand -up and it's funny I'm sure it's fun
but Michael Crite and uh we're all these little kids trying to read this book it's just like how all
these little kids were trying to read the stand the next year right before the miniseries aired as I'm
sure kids did with Harry Potter yeah I gotta get this god damn definitely how those book done exactly
yeah sure but um you know we're reading through dress part we're talking about it we're all excited
but that was a movie where I remember to this day it came out June 11th 1993 wow I remember it
very well and our tickets were bought the moment they went on sale the mid -roofers mall six cinema
I went to school that day I my friends and I our I remember a teacher was like could you guys calm
down like what's going on over there and I was like I'm sorry Mrs. Taylor we're all going to see
Jurassic Park right after school like it was that kind of thing that's great like the kid we were all
so fucking excited and we went in and we're waiting at the mall this thing that this stuff does not
happen anymore they pulled back the little maroon uh thing and this is before assigned seating too
right to get there right and wait yeah we waited forever good seat and when they lifted that little
lever to bring us into the theater we pushed forward and me and Ryan are good we'll probably talk
about this when he comes out here next week this is a grown man with kids of his own but the crowds surged
into this theater they let us in and me and Ryan were so little that we were pushed between two
morbidly obese people's asses and me and Ryan looked at each other and our eyes locked and we laughed
hysterically because we were both off the ground push between some fat asses right and the entire
way down to the theater we were kind of like early crowd surfing like we're 13 room we kind of crowd
served our way in we sprinted in we got front and center great and when direct the beginning of
Jurassic Park is horrifying and I would say way scarier than we were expecting yeah that great
scene is very good at the top it's great when they lower that the the uh the the goat or whatever
in and again there's a very Indiana Jones feel yeah for sure a lot of snap oh yeah movements with
the camera and it's it's the mysterious crate and all that stuff Spielberg does not I mean Spielberg
directed the fucking shit out of Jurassic Park and it started up and this you're also talking about a
time when I'm 13 and it's PG 13 right so I'm newly allowed to see this movie right but it starts
up and I was fucking terrified and my parents never went out even though they were they were my age
now probably they didn't really go out much they had kids to raise they couldn't afford a babysitter and
I knew that they had bought tickets for the next night the Saturday night show and that added an
element to like my parents were excited enough to buy advanced tickets that's how big an event
that said and you also get to be the cool kid that goes home and goes you gotta see this film yeah yeah
I mean I was spazin out we we love that movie so much it was incredible I still think it's an
incredible movie and the closest I've come to that kind of excitement weirdly was me and some friends
and Heather when we first started dating got really high and went up to the Universal City walk and saw
3d Jurassic Park five years ago and they released it oh yeah yeah yeah and it was like seeing it for
the first time like that's great that that to me was the the biggest and to have that much anticipation
and then have the movie be that good that's great is that was that to me was I put you rest park above
all the Star Wars I mean we're very different of course but I flip my shit over that movie I was I
was terrified by it it also felt adult even though it was kind of a family movie at the end of the day
it made me feel like an adult again it was a nuanced popcorn film which we don't get to see much
anymore you don't you don't feel like anyone is trying to bring you the best product right so
that's great as you said for me I am not a fan of Jurassic Park the series but I'm excited for you
thanks Joe you're welcome Pat that's our show we're at we're almost at an hour and 20 here so
I'm always happy to bleed into some extra time for these patreon listeners I love
me too love that they they give us the support I appreciate it me too this might be our longest
episode ever that didn't wasn't a commentary but what was the by the way what was really quick
was the word you used to describe your mood when you went into boogie nights per what
so I went to see boogie nights oh I think I was I use purient okay so if you if you have a
purient interest in something it means you want to see people fuck this here here's my here's my
request yeah from now on in your life when you use that word will you say it like cat woman and put
a purr purion yes yeah I will I've never used it before I'll probably never use it again but
if I do I'll say purr just do a purr with a rolled -r I will stillable folks on the Facebook page you
know I want to see what your experiences were what your top five would be so I remember by the
way requested to join the Facebook group I don't know if I've been approved yet but I did request
now you didn't I cuz I would have gotten that I requested join you know on Facebook I am on
Facebook I have a fan page on Facebook I request a join do it today weeks who cares I never got
that request but I did request to get in I don't want to make it sound like I don't give a
shit I do give a shit so I'd love to see what what yours were and I know that this one I think more
than any other topic age plays a big role because you're never gonna be as excited as you were when
you were like 12 13 or our kid forgot say yeah let us know please folks thank you for your your
patronage okay and see you next time we'll see you next time we'll see you in hell