I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, and when the sound of your screams
Home's big cards are they on the dreamy, and yeah I'll say they they they I'll see you in hell
You know I'll see you in hell, you know I'll see you in hell, you know I'll rule
Ladies and gentlemen this is it episode number one of we'll see you in hell the new
podcast featuring myself, Joe DeRose, and my good buddy, Patrick Walsh, or PT
Dubbs, as I call him. Hi everybody. How are you? We're here under the
Fangorian network. We're going to be offering commentary on horror movies
that you can watch along with. Or if you're so inclined, just listen in your
car. And we're going to try to make it entertaining for those listeners as
well. I like that we're giving the listeners options. Yeah. Well, you know,
in this internet age, Joe, you have to. You know, Pat, I've read that people
want entertainment their way. They want it, they want it all our cart, Joe.
It's not like when you and I were kids and there was one channel,
and you had to watch what Papa government told you to.
And he's not talking about the government. That's what he called his dad.
Today, we're going to watch children of the corn, which Pat has never seen
which made me think, I don't know if this will be a recurring theme or not
throughout the show. Pat is certainly a horror fan. I'm a huge horror fan.
I think I've seen a little bit more than he has. I was wondering if there would
sort of be this theme where I'm showing you a movie you haven't seen before.
Doesn't have to be that, but you know, we can do it however we want, but I
certainly of the genres, the one I've seen the least of would definitely be horror
sci -fi because it's just never, I'm a pussy. You're frightened of it.
At least as a child, I was always obsessed with comedy and other things and horror was always
off limits to me. But you are a cinephile. I'd go as far as to say.
Million percent. I've never seen most things, but like when you get into like these considered
classics, your children and the corn and all that kind of stuff, I've never seen.
Oh, well that's okay. I like that this might be a budding theme here. We're discovering it
on the first episode. Yeah. I've read it. I've read all the Stephen King books.
So you read children of the corn? At some point I must have. Yeah, because I read all those books.
Well, I must have, and I read it at a two different statements, Pat.
I don't remember it, but let's start it off. And this is where the podcast is going to get a little
tricky, but we're going to basically count down. We're going to start it, hit pause. Right.
And then when we're all on the same page, one, two, three, boom, and then we all go on together.
If you're watching at home, yeah. Well, I'll tell you what we're going to do here is what I want you to do
is I want you to pause. Not yet. Hold on. When I count to three, I want you to pause. I mean, now this
is the, these are the, these are the hiccups of a podcast, Pat. We had it all set up here.
And then the Apple TV just chose to go back to the menu screen. Why did that happen?
He talked to Steve Jobs.
Now two stars for children of the corn. Two stars is what they're given. I got to tell you,
I don't think it's a great movie. Well, now it's directed by Fritz Kirch,
right, who I have to assume at least has some ties to the Nazi party.
At least a grandfather who has killed aju at some point. Fritz Kirch, I don't know if that's
a slander or not. Sorry. If you're listening, Fritz, I'm sure you're a great guy who loves all race.
Let's let's look up Fritz Kirch because you know, well, let's start. I mean, like, we got 90 minutes
to fill with our with our commentary. Let's start the movie. Yes. I agree. So you're going to click on
the play button. You're just going to see the spinning wheel. Right. And as soon as you see the
first frame, pause it and that'll make sense in a minute. So on three, pause this podcast, go find
the movie, hit play. When you see the spinning wheel, great. When it's the first frame comes on hit
pause, which also looks like a spinning wheel. Yeah. So one, two, three, play.
Okay. You're here. You got the first frame paused. And now one, three, we're going to hit play
together. Here's what we did it that way because everybody's load times might be different. You might
have shit internet where you're at. I got the good stuff, people. I know my load time depends on the
lady. All right. Disgusting. I don't remember. All right. On three, we're going to hit play.
You again, you were paused on the first frame of the film. One, wait, is it on three play or on
are you two three then play? Okay. So one, two, three, play. There we go. Terrific. I got audio,
Patty. You got audio. Have audio as well. Looking at just the most bargain basement graphic here for
image entertainment. No offense to the people at image entertainment. Well, I mean, I know some of
the folks over at image. And they said, yeah, they said they chose not to put money into the graphic.
They want it on the screen. Yeah, they went on the screen. Right. I got the old fritz. His full name
is George Keith Kirsch. For some reason chose to take on the name of fritz. Yeah, he was like, let's
really assess it up. What are the greatest title screens in this movie? Look at that title screen. It
pops. Very command. It pops with a yellow font. I like it. Here's what else fritz is to
directed. Tough turf. To you, FF. Yep. I don't know. Very good. Winner takes all. Is there anything
we've heard of? You know, don't read all these swamp thing, but the series that the many of the movies.
The stranger, the hunt. And a Crayola kids movie. So this is it. How weird is that? So your first
movie is shooting on the quorum, which is kind of a cult classic. And I think probably did okay at the
box office. And then he just does a bunch of nothing. I'm curious as to what this made at the box office.
Let's see. I'm going to go to reception here on a weekend. Oh, no, there's budget 800 ,000 dollar
budget. You ready for this? Yeah. 14 .5 million. Yeah. So that's like a few made 15 times your money.
Yeah. That's a great deal. Yeah. Good job, Fritz. There will also be bits of math information
throughout this podcast. And from there, he's he moves to the swamp thing series. I feel like Fritz
got a raw deal. It wasn't the next thing. It was just down the line. Maybe he was difficult on set.
I mean, the movie looks like it was made with my dad's old home movie camera. I'll say that so far.
It does. And this opening voiceover has always disturbed me. It's a little boy talking. And it
disturbs me because I'm like, is this boy going to be evil? Is he going to die immediately in unreliable
narrators way? Very smart enough to have a grown up narrator. Because then you say,
what's one of the grown up kids of the corn? Now let's talk Stephen King adaptation.
Yeah. So here's this guy. Here's the kid from the burbs with the red hair that looks. I always
called him a poor man's Eric Stoltz. Yeah. And the modern day equivalent is the Shermanator from
American Pie. Yes. And I'm not positive. They're not the same person. Well, they could be at least
related, I would say. Speaking of Shermanator, Linda Hamilton involved who was the star of the
Terminator. Yes. Linda Hamilton is in this film. I don't think I've ever seen or anything else
that other than the Terminator series. I only ever saw in the Terminator one and two, which is why
I was thrilled for the Terminator salvation cameo. Was she in it? She's in it for her voices in it.
Her voices in it. It's a terrible movie. I'm telling you, I don't know if you're going to like
this one much better, Pat. Okay. I mean, it's a classic. Yeah. This scene's great. Now you're
in it. We're in a diner. Things are being zoomed in on slowly. Okay. Things are being dumped
secretly into drinks. So something bad's about to happen here. These corn shakers look mighty
suspicious. Here we go. Look at this shmuck. Doesn't know what's about to happen to him. Look at this guy.
Here we go. And the kids are all just standing around the perimeter of the dining room staring
ominously at all the grownups. Nobody seems to notice anything. Yeah. This kid. But now
did the kid control that woman putting the powder in the coffee? No. He's just
over there grabbing their throats. People are obviously choking now poisoning is happening.
And they're looking at this lady. I mean, is that how you a choke? Would you choke like that with
wide eyes? Absolutely not. Also, here's my question. Why when people are choking, do they grasp their
throat? The thing that needs loosening and they clench it. Why do they do that? Well, I don't
I haven't seen anyone choking real life. That might not be what happens. But maybe you're just
telling everybody, hey, my throat, help, choke. I mean, well, even if that is what you're saying.
Oh, here it goes. It handed to a meat slicer. This scene was also in kingpin.
You remember they put his hand in the bowling thing. I don't need to see blood splatter on the six
year olds face. Kid seems to be kind of loving it. Well, the kids are evil. So I can't. That
man blood on my face. I'm going to be like, oh my god. Let me at least wipe this off.
Now, clearly the kid outside Malachi is his name that looks like the young Doug Benson.
He's the he's the overseer of all this. Okay.
So everywhere in Gatlin that day, Gatlin's attend the living, the kids all murdered the parents.
All right. So now the kids are running the town, I guess.
Yes. Oh, Pete Horton. Wings? No. That's Tim Daly and Steven Weber. Again, Tim Daly.
Richman's Peter Horton. Peter Horton was on 30 something. Yes. And he was in singles.
Yeah. Yeah. He was the biker. Yeah. Yeah. I love singles. I love it too.
Underrated movie. I love singles. You know, a part always perplexed me in singles. Let's talk
about that. Just watched it. When she goes, when she goes, I'm going to make a salad.
She makes the most gigantic fucking salad I've ever seen. She's like hacked apart the cucumbers
and carrots with like a, it looks like she cut them up with a samurai sword. Just these hunks
of vegetable. I'm like, who the fuck ate salad like that? Um, that couldn't have had less of an
effect on me. It is always, I've always found it confusing. And I was like, that's clearly some
character trait thing. Like that's some subtlety about the character. I'm supposed to be understanding.
And I never got it. Oh, I didn't. I just figured she's making a big old salad. And they wanted
to be visually exciting. I mean, you eat salad like that. You're going to be a fat shit
defeats the purpose of the salad. You can eat vegetables all day enough because I know.
Right. It was a joke, Pat. I mean, if we went to pick apart every bit now. I didn't like it.
Let's talk. That's the present day. Wait, wait. What was that opening? I didn't notice that that
hit. Uh, I just saw a south paw with Jake Gyllenhaal. Yeah, which is corny, but I enjoyed it.
The character's name is Billy Hope. That tells you anything about the tone of the movie.
I mean, but, uh, they talk for 20 minutes about how he's going to be boxing at this upcoming charity
fight. Uh, for like the, let's say it's the boys and girls club. Right. They keep talking about,
talking about, talking about, then they cut to the exterior of the fight and hear the bell go off.
And they put up on the screen a title card that says charity fight boys and girls club.
They've not done any title cards of the whole movie. Uh, like the entire theater was like,
we know, south paw. Well, you don't have to tell us. Do they keep up with the title cards after
that at least? No, there's not another title card in the film. So some executive was probably like,
are we going to be confused? That's ridiculous as to where they are. And name the guy Hope,
so everybody gets it. Yeah. There's also a scene where Jill and Hall, uh, he has an estranged
daughter. And he's helping her with her homework. And he's in a really dark place. And she's like,
help me with these spelling words. And he does one word. And then the second word is helplessness.
God. And I bet, Pat, I bet you felt helpless at that point in that theater. It's a very heavy
handed movie. But I did enjoy it. And I do recommend that I like the film written for M &M. And then
Jill and Hall is kind of trying to do the M &M thing. And with him, it seems a little like
menstrual show kind of offensive to me. Uh, that was how I felt when Ed Norton did it in that
denier, in that denier room. Very uncomfortable Hollywood. Fifty cent. Fifty quote Curtis Jackson
quote sent is not an actor. And we have to stop pretending that he is. Is he bad? He's terrible,
Jill. And they give him job after job. He's better than common who is the worst rapper actor.
Well, common was in Terminator's Salvation. Well, there you go. No further questions,
Your Honor. Yeah. Ludacris is a bad actor. I like Ludacris as an actor.
Wait, do I? No, I like, well, I like ice cube as an actor. Ice cube is a fantastic actor. I like
ice team. Everybody is. Yes. Uh, Ludacris are being pretty good in, uh, what's that movie? Well,
like the racist pulp fiction. What was that movie called? Uh, the racist pulp fiction. Oh, crash?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. It's like all the races and stories. Was it was ice cube in that? No,
Ludacris was in that. With Lorenz Tate, who I haven't seen in a while. Yeah, I always liked Lorenz Tate.
By the way, we've sort of drifted away from the movie for a second. Right now, Linda Hamilton is doing
a song and dance number. A strip tease where it seems she's putting more clothes on throughout.
Now, on the rich man poor man scale, where do you put Peter Horton above or below Steven Weber?
Definitely below Weber. Uh, above daily. Uh, no, I put daily above two. Daily is a solid enough actor,
but I really liked him as the screenwriter on sopranos. I know you don't like sopranos. And Weber,
I think, is a very funny likeable dude. I didn't see him in the shining for TV. I wouldn't watch that.
I mean, I don't understand. Stephen King prefers the Steven Weber shining to the Nicholson shining.
I know. I know. I know. I don't understand. I tried watching it because Steven King said he preferred it.
Yeah. And, you know, his whole argument was it was more true to the book, which, okay, that's fine.
Right. You could be mad at Kubrick for ruining your book. I've got no problem with that. You can say,
I hate the Kubrick version of the film. I got no problem with that. And you can say that the
mini series with Steven Weber was a better adaptation of the book. I got no problem with that. Sure.
What you can't tell me though is that that fucking mini series was entertaining,
or that anybody was buying Steven Weber as a lunatic. No, it's true. And, you know, it's just,
it's simple math. Steven Weber compared to Jack Nicholson. There's no scenario where Steven Weber
acts a scene better. And I think Weber would tell you the same. I don't know. I met Weber once.
Pretty pleased with himself. Sure. I met Weber as well. Weber. Nice enough. But he guessed it on a
sitcom I wrote for. And I don't know if he had, like, glanced at the script. I don't know if he had
touched a script. Yeah. And it was in front of an audience and it got a little tense. No offense to
Steven Weber who I do. I do like it. I find him very funny. Handsome man. Did the fat guy on
wing? Let me tell you this. Now, you were on better call Saul. I'm going to go ahead and butter
your bread a little bit. The fat guy in better call Saul who spoiler alert dies at the end of the
season as the heart attack. That guy was great. And he's also on a HBO show called Getting On or
Getting by the medical show. That guy looks identical to the fat guy from wings. But they can't
be the same man because they're 25 years apart. Who's the fat guy from wings? The fat guy with the
mustache from wings. Did he ever act again? Well, I can look it up. Crystal Bernard on wings. Did
she ever act again? By the way, real quick, how much does this kid look like a young Paul Rudd?
Well, it is a young Paul Rudd, is it not? I don't think so. I'm going to look it up. Hold on.
Did you see Ant -Man? No. I liked Ant -Man. I love Paul Rudd. I like comic book movies. I don't
want to see Ant -Man. It's pretty entertaining. Marvel is turning everything into a comedy now.
Age of Ultron was like expendables level one -liners. I didn't see Age of Ultron, but I think all
those superhero movies, like Terminator Observations, a perfect example. You have to have some humor
because these movies are ridiculous. Terminator 2 is a funny movie. Terminator Salvation,
you're not, they act like it was Schindler's list, with the level of intensity. Right. I don't mind a
little bit of humor, but I don't want a comedy. Ant -Man is largely a comedy, and I didn't mind that at all.
Well, and then they just said that the new, the guys that wrote the vacation remake are writing
the new Spider -Man, and they said it's going to have a John Hughes feel. What are you doing? I don't
do that. Well, we don't need another Spider -Man. God damn it. You and I saw that last one with Jamie
Fox as the nerd who turns blue. That was the worst movie I've ever seen in my life. It was a real piece
of shit. Hey, who can we get to play this nerd? How about one of the strongest,
pancumist men in the world, Jamie Foxx? That does enough straight hair yet he's going to be
holding with a combo. Just a terrible movie, but luckily it was only three and a half hours long.
Now, Sheldon of the Corn, Joe, where do you put that in terms of Stephen King adaptations?
I've enjoyed Stephen Weber adaptations more. I don't even know if there are any. I don't.
The 80s really were the prime time for your Stephen King adaptations. It's insane. This is from the book
Night Shift, I believe. Night Shift. Let me pull this up because it really is an uncanny.
I bought this book when I was home last. I had never purchased it. I was home last Christmas.
I bought it while I was home for something to read. I was sitting at the table. My mom's a
big horror movie fan. I was sitting at the table with her. The day after I bought it, reading her the
table of contents. I said, Mom, the money that this guy made off of this one book, just this one.
Ready for this? Yeah. Graveyard Shift. Turned into a movie. The Mangler. Turned into a movie.
What was the Mangler? A Robert England movie. I remember the catch or the phrase, the famous line
in the trailer was he goes, we all make sacrifices. The actual release? What? The actual release?
Yeah. And then they made sequels that didn't make it. The Boogie Man. There's a horror movie called
Boogie Man. I'm not sure if it's an adaptation of that or not. So we'll say that's a bonus track
possibly. Trucks, which was turned into maximum overdrive. Sometimes they come back. Yeah, that's a movie.
TV movie. The lawnmower man movie. I've never saw the lawnmower man. It's a despicable adaptation of
the story. The story itself is great. It's about a weirdo, creepy lawnmowering service. It's not
about a simple minded man that becomes a power god. Well, from age 10 to 20, I mowed lawns
easily 20 a week at 20 a pop, bringing me a nice little chunk of change each week.
Always an entrepreneur. Under the name, the lawnmower man. Really? And that might have been what got me
the business because I was kind of like wink, wink. But I never saw the film. It's it's it's not
good. Okay. Not not. I want to pierce brazenen's shining. Oh, right, right. Quitter's ink. Not familiar.
And the ledge, which are both short stories that appeared in the film Katzai, one of my favorite Stephen
King adaptation. You and I watched Katzai. Yeah. Children of the corn. And he also gets a piece
of the 12 sequels to show another corn. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Let's let's go to those actually.
But I mean, I can't I just it's the the amount of money. Oh, wait, here's it. Okay.
Well, Stephen King, I would wager as a billionaire, right? He'd have to be.
I mean, he's got to be unless Oh, and battleground also was was turned into an episode of nightmares
and dreamscapes. Battleground's the best episode of that. Oh, they hit that mannequin.
They they just hit the young Paul red with a car. I'm going to look at Paul red and see if he
was ever in children of the cork. I mean, it's uncanny. How much that looks like it?
Well, I wasn't sure. Yeah. But what's your favorite Stephen King adaptation?
Well, you know, we've talked about this. I go back and forth, but you know, I think you you'd
said misery last time. And I think misery, misery probably is the best. That's a perfect movie,
but it's a thrill or not a horror. Yeah, but I mean, it's I have it in my horror movie section. Yeah,
of DVDs. I don't put it over, you know, I don't put it in the dramas. It's just a perfect movie. You
know, have you or you should go sometimes on the Wikipedia or IMDB or whatever and look up all the actors
who they wanted to get before landing on James Conn. Because it's every actor in Hollywood.
Who else if they weren't? Oh, you're big Danero, Pacino, Hoffman, Nicholson, etc., etc.
You look uncomfortable. You're comfortable with the way you're sitting. I'm fine. I mean,
I'm always uncomfortable, but I'm fine. Okay, good. They wanted Nicholson. They wanted Pacino,
Beatty, Pacino, Danero, basically every actor that was around before landing on Conn,
I think Conn's really good in it, but I could definitely see any of the other people.
I could not picture anyone other than Kathy Bates playing that role. Now they're doing a Broadway
musical of misery with Bruce Willis and Laurie Metcalf. Is it a comedy? I assume it's a dark comedy,
like I consider misery a dark comedy, but I'd like to see it, even though it sounds like it's
probably so. Oh, that I don't know. Everything does need music added to it on Broadway.
I disagree. There's a lot of great straight plays up there. Sure, but people don't go see him.
It doesn't put asses in the seats. I mean, look, all I heard about was that one that Chris Rock was in,
everybody was going to see that thing. What was that? I couldn't tell you. If my life depended on it right
now. Poodie Tang, the musical. Bradley Cooper did the elephant man. Was that a musical? No,
no. No. John Merrick not known for his song and dance abilities. And you love the myths,
I remember you saying. Yes, I was struggling. I was like, I can't remember what I said when we
talked about this. The mist is way up there. The mist is awesome. It's a contender for number one.
I'll probably give number one to misery and number two to the mist. The mist, the fact that a
major studio allowed a movie with that ending to be released blows my mind. I love it. I
never heard an angry group of people leaving a theater. I saw it with my parents and we all loved it.
And my mom was visibly shaken by the ending. Yeah. She was upset. Well, let's not say what it is.
Maybe I let a lot of people have not seen the mist. And I think that's a shame. Yeah, it was it was
an amazing movie. And I love that guy. What's his name? The guy that played Tommy Jane? Yeah,
Tom Jane. I'm fine with him. Tom Jane. Now I call Tom and this is not an insult to Tom Jane.
Big fan. I call him the poor man's Aaron Eckhart. He certainly is. Although Aaron Eckhart does nothing
for me at all. I love Aaron Eckhart. I love him and in the company of Mem, everything else. I'm like,
all right. I love him. I love him. I love Tom Jane and everything. Aaron Eckhart just says
a higher profile. All right. That's fine. You know, after all, he was I Frankenstein. Did you see that?
No. Okay. That's good. I don't like those movies. Like that was like that when they made van
Helsing with Hugh Jackman. I don't like like those like horror adventure movies.
Yeah. Well, now they're rebooting all the old classic universals. Yeah.
Well, they did Wolfman three years ago. Nobody cared. They're going to read it. Well,
they was terrible. They fucked it up. I swear to God, I think Benisha, the tour is an amazing
actor. You watch, you watch that movie. I'm like, he didn't want to be there. Yeah. He's,
he's like mailing in and away where I'm like, I don't, like he, it's, he's not capable of being
this bad unless it's on purpose. What I find interesting about Benisha, the tour is if there's ever
a movie with any element of drugs, Benisha, the tour was like contractually required to be in it.
And I find that a little weird. Well, what? I mean, he's in traffic. He's in 21 grams.
There's an upcoming movie from the guy who did prisoners, which is a fucking awesome movie that
looks like traffic in del Toro's in that. Okay. It's just like, why does every every epic drug movie
get sent to him that that still Oliver Stone movie savages. Del Toro was in that thing. He is.
I didn't see that. Sure. Yeah. I, he was in an episode of Miami Vice Guarantee. There was some drug
business on that. Definitely drug paraphernalia in that. How was savages? I really like savages,
but it's just hot trash. It's really trash. In what way? It's just, it's almost like an exploitation
movie. Like it's a lot of like just nudity and people chewing the scenery and travolta hamming it up.
And it was fun. It really was fun. But it's just trash. All right. All right. I never, I never saw it.
Stone lost me a few years ago. Yeah. I'll always see what he comes out with. But he's clearly lost his mind.
Wait. What's his new movie? The Snowden one, right? Yeah. Yeah. With who's who Snowden Eisenberg?
No. Isn't it like, wait, is it? No. Isn't it like Matt Damon? No. Isn't Matt Damon's snowden?
I'm probably not right, but I'm closer than Matt Damon.
Oh, you know, who's playing him as a Kyra Sedgwick?
Star of singles, which brings us back to Pea Horde. I loved her in singles.
As far as like dream women in movies, for me,
Sedgwick is number one. And also, I'm going to go Holly Hunter in Raising Arizona.
No. I love a Holly Hunter, but I don't, that's not a dream woman to me. In that movie, I mean. I really do.
I love the accent too. Broadcast news. Yeah. Broadcast news. That to me is more dream woman, Holly Hunter.
The movie opens with her sobbing uncontrollably on a bed. And that was like, yeah, dream woman.
And you got Albert Brooks. Joseph Gordon Levitt is playing JGL Snowden. Good for him. I like him.
You also got Melissa Leo in there, big fan. Tom Wilkinson, big fan. Nicholas Cage making his theatrical
comeback. What's he going to be? Uh, he is playing it though. It's unlisted. Okay. So, uh, maybe
Barack Obama. I'm going to tell you, it bothers me so much how Nicholas Cage is like a big joke now
because he, he was growing up my favorite actor and remains one of my favorite actors. And I'll still
see what he comes out with. The fact that he has to do made for TV shit, basically, to pay off the
dinosaur eggs that he's decorated his mansion with. It's sad, but he's still a great actor with a
bad lieutenant port of called New Orleans. I look, he was amazing in that. I can test that it's, it rivals
the original. Of course it does. I mean, it's a masterpiece in my mind. I watch honeymoon and Vegas the
other day. That's a perfect romantic comedy. And he is so funny in that that it's like, it's almost
unbelievable how funny he is. Like when he explodes and screams at people in that movie,
I had to pause it every time. And then raising Arizona, of course, is as good as movies get for me,
personal. Uh, match stickman's one of my favorite pieces of his work. I mean, it's him, Sam Rockwell.
And, uh, in rock, the rock's not in match stickman. Oh, the movie, the rock. Uh, the movie, the rock
stars Nicholas Cage. And also, that's how I refer to Sam Rockwell as the rock. I was going to say
dream woman, the, what the fuck's the girl's name in match stickman? Uh, and she's in drag me to hell.
Oh, you talk about Allison Lohman? Yes. When she shows up at the end and you realize she's like a grown -up
yeah. And she's like that sexy like hustler. Oh, she's a lesbian. No, she's married with a kid. I looked
it up. Is she? Yeah, I'll look up like women that have only been in a few movies like that,
that I think are hot, like, and be like, I wonder if they're made a chance. I mean, who knows?
They show off the improv one night. I think maybe her star has fallen far enough that she's
willing to entertain a Joe DeRosa. Yeah, I mean, I, who knows? Yeah, okay. Stranger things have
happened because you read those things. You'll see a like real hot actress. You'll be like, who
she made to it? I'd be like, she married key grip. Laurence Sandy Bullock married a key grip. Yeah.
So it's possible. All right. She also married that dildo with the tattoos. Yeah, and he cheated on
all right. Yeah. How do you do? Julia Roberts married a grip, I think. And Lyle Love it. You
know, there's a lady who's willing to explore the darker side of men. So now what's I'm tweening
by the way. I'm tweeting by the way that we're recording the first step so people can send
all right. Questions if they like, what's going on here? There's a kid dressed like Charlie Chaplin.
So I really, at the end of this, I can't even really say I've seen the movie because we're just
shooting the shit. I'm going to have to watch it all on my own. Well, what's happening is, is this
Bugsy Malone now? Are they playing like their adults? I think maybe these two children are bearing
one another. I mean, they're wearing, we're in grown -up clothes for some reason. So there is,
is this a straight -up cult thing like, like, does this go to places like kids fucking each other?
Is it not that dark? No. Okay. No. It's just the basic, the basic gist of this is, do you hear him
just say I act according to his rule? I did in a highly questionable accent. Him is, he who walks behind
the rows. Okay. Creepy description. Sure. The rows of four. Yeah. So they're in service to this god
and the children shall lead them. Okay. I think the basic plot is maybe just wiping out humanity,
starting fresh with the children in service of this god. The corn god. Yeah. I just saw a
preview of Sinister 2 and I thought Sinister 1 was an excellent horror movie. Best horror movie
that year. I thought it was fantastic. And the opening scene of them like hanging like that slow
motion scene. I thought it was like a perfectly shot scene. Yeah. But now Sinister 2 seems to have a
very children of the corn element to it because the preview, there's three people hanging on
crosses in the middle of a cornfield. Yeah. So I guess they're doff in the cap to COTC.
Well, oh, COTC, very nice. I like that you already have a nickname for it, even though you've never
seen it. Yeah. I can't wait for Sinister 2. I am a little concerned with the whole like
now we're going to show the other side of it. This is going to be more about what the children are
doing in their world. Yeah. Well, that never seems to work out when they try to go to the other side
of the thing. Yeah. Like Poltergeist, the other side, which was literally. Although in the Poltergeist
remake, the only part that I thought was worthwhile because it made me so angry and depressed because
it was so bad. And Poltergeist is my favorite horror movie. The remake when they went into the other
side and showed you like the other world of souls was the only interesting development in the new movie.
I didn't even like that part because they ruined it by flying a fucking drone into it. Yeah.
Yeah. A lot of drone material on that one. Which by the way was the setup
for which or excuse me, which was the which that scene where he comes in with all the merchandise and
is like even though we're broke, I bought all this stuff inexplicably. It was just setup to be like,
I got this drone now. Yeah. I mean, they couldn't have written just this thing like, don't tell
your mom. You're going through a tough time, kiddo. I'm going to get you this drone. And then the
kid has to hide it from the mom. And then at the end, he pulls it out. I've been hiding this because
you dad didn't want you know as she spent the money, but we need it now. Yeah. But was that 20 seconds,
10 times better? Yeah. I mean, I so on by top 10 movies of all time are both Poltergeist and
National Amputance Vacation. We're in a summer now. We're going to see remakes of both.
I went into Poltergeist like, all right, this isn't going to be one of your favorite movies of all time.
This isn't going to be anywhere close to that. I lowered my expectations to their bare minimum.
And I was let down. And I'm hoping vacation doesn't do the same. It looks like it might be kind of funny.
I don't know. You're you're nuts. You're literally nuts. I am maybe building my hopes up. Now,
here's what I'll say. I went into Poltergeist with only with moderate expectations because you
told me it was bad. When I heard it was being made, I was thrilled. I thought the trailer looked great.
Sam Rockwell, arguably my favorite actor out there right now. Oh, wow. Yeah, I love him. But yeah,
for sure. So I had very high hopes. I was I was unfortunately let down. And it wasn't that great.
The to me, it was like being kicked in the throat. The vacation remake. I mean, I I become angered
during the trailers. Okay. I mean, just the redoing of the jokes and making them like more extreme
and zany now, like the first vacation movie feels like a real movie. It or real, excuse me, it feels
like a real story. It's believable to me. This stuff he does is just crazy enough that it's believable.
Now he's doing it out of love for his family, which to me make, honestly, there are times,
especially if I've had 10, 12 drinks, where watch a vacation on a Saturday night, I can get a little
misty because he just cares so much about his family. And that seems to be lost in this, but maybe
it isn't. I don't know. Well, I'm sure that element of it is there. But I mean, it's like my point is
is Chevy Chase driving with Christie Brinkley in the car next to him. And when they hit, I don't like
that. You know, it's believable and funny. And then this one, they redo it and she gets hit and
hell, I'm just makes that face like, hmm, it's like you'd be screaming in horror, first of all. Yeah.
You know, the thing with like how now they they have the weird car, like in the in their like, oh,
that this happened again. And it's not believable at all. Yeah. The joke where Chevy Chase is like,
you know, who gave me that guitar? Bob Dylan. And then the kids like, and the kid goes, wow,
you knew Bob Dylan. He goes, no, no, no, no, just a guy whose name happened to be Bob Dylan. This
is a joke in the trailer in one of the trailers. And then he goes, but you know, who gave Bob Dylan
that guitar? Jimmy Hendrix. And the kid goes, Jimmy Hendrix gave your friend this guitar and he goes,
well, not the Jimmy Hendrix. It's, it's, I'm like, what the fuck? That's like a 30 -year -old joke. Yeah.
It's not going to be good. Well, I hate, I like everybody in the movie. I wanted it to be good.
It's not going to be good. I don't know. I don't get my hopes up, but anything anymore in every
aspect of my life, it served me pretty well because I'm always like, yep, there's another disappointment.
Now, when in the Terminator, Jen, yeah, thinking it was going to be a shit show. Me and Joe,
go, we go see Term, Termi Jens. Front to back enjoyment. Had a great time. I enjoyed every second of it.
Yeah. I had a really good time with Termi Jens. A lot of fun. Yeah. A lot of fun. Certainly
better than salvation. Good movies this year. You know, I didn't, I thought it could have less comedy,
but I thought Age of Ultron was great. Didn't see. I enjoyed Termi Jens, as you call it. I think
Star Wars is going to be phenomenal. Sure. You can't call that as one of the good movies of the year.
Well, I mean, look, I stuck with Star Wars through the prequels. Definitely fucking out.
Yeah, I mean, we've seen that it is possible. Yeah. But I am a, that's literally going to be the
most excited I've ever been to see a movie in my life. Yeah, I think that's going to be
that's the kind of movie where you like carefully choose who you're going to see it with. Like there's
like everything about it is kind of important. And I don't even really give a shit about Star Wars.
I'm more of an indie Jones guy, which is why the fourth one was such a, you know, bottoming out
for me. I saw it alone so nobody could ruin it. I wish I had. So I could have whipped silently
in the back row. It's not twice an opening day. Yeah. I liked it. I think it was great, but I liked it.
Hey, that's moments. It had a more prairie dog reaction shots than I was expecting. I'll say that.
Meerkat. Meerkat, they're not sure. Shilobuffs. Now, what's going on here? He's got a bloody pair
of underpants. I gotta be honest. We've been talking so much about other movies. I've lost where we're
at the film. Well, and that's probably good because I imagine at least half the listeners are not
watching along with children's porn. Uh -oh. Like, also nobody's died in a while. Look, the Steven
Weber guy could be dead by now. I wouldn't even know. There's the kids have killed, I think they killed
his dog. I think that hanker chiff was around his dog's neck. Now, have you seen the children of the corn
sequels? No, but I'm glad you bring it up because I want to look these up. So hold on. Sure.
All right, children are the corn sequels and I own one of them. So I know they go at least up to
children of the corn six, six, six. Yes. I mean, they were just, there was a guy sitting somewhere that
was like, we just got to make it to six. We just got to make it to six. Yeah, uh, children of
is it a satanic cult? Can you at least give me the bare minimum of information on this movie?
It's a, uh, yeah, it's, it's a, it's a cult involving, you know, the underworld or black magic
or something along those lines. I don't know that they ever use the word Satan. Yeah.
But it is sacrilegious. Uh, you know, there's the creation of a weird sort of Jesus
mosaic thing behind an altar. Okay. And as you can hear right now, the choir's chanting.
Anytime this choir's chanting, it's a little hellish, right? Yeah.
Um, okay, the film series, uh, oh, well, this guy's about to die. Yeah. I think.
Yeah, I don't think. And then they cut the old mechanic wins this. I don't think they cut away.
Wouldn't it be great if he came out holding a kid's head? Where are they driving, by the way?
Like this, I'm not, I'm not watching the movie really, but like they've been driving a very long time
for this to be a movie. Portal into Hamilton spent her entire movie career and cars driving
away from people. It's not fair. She never, you know, what, what, what other movie involves a lot
of driving through cornfields is jeepers creepers. Terrible film. Let me tell you this. I like jeepers
creepers a lot. And I like jeepers creepers too a lot. I'm going to ruin jeepers creepers for you.
I'm going to tell you this. Both movies were directed by a convicted pedophile.
So that ruins it right there. The man directed the funhouse. Francis Ford Coppola produced.
I know. I know. I know. Like, hey, he molested a kid on the set of this movie.
Then years later, he was allowed to direct powder, which was kind of a hit with Jeff Goldblum.
Yeah. Powder, which is a very strange movie, but kind of okay.
Oh, it's a story. A lot of powder being shirtless. Yes, he was big on that.
Yeah. And then jeepers creepers involves a lot of teen boys, pissing in cornfields, shirtless,
etc. And the whole time, I'm like, they entrusted a large horror movie franchise to a convicted
pedophile. This wasn't that long ago. And I love that is that is most popular work as powder,
which is a movie about keeping secretly keeping a teenage boy in your basement. Yeah, exactly.
And the man's name is Victor Solva. I'm going to call him out. Victor Solva,
we all know you molested that boy.
If you're listening, there's the dead mechanic, by the way. Yeah. But I actually really like
both jeepers creepers. I saw them in New York. I haven't seen them since. Maybe I'd like them.
Well, let me, you won't. Let me ruin the movie for you. All right.
Number one. And you know, we are doing this podcast for Fengoria. And I'm glad with this product.
Because this is something I've said in a previous interview. I do with Fengoria.
Fengoria. Number one, they do the worst thing. Actually, let me just ruin the movie for you in one
sentence. And then I'll tell you all the other shit that sucks about it.
Just picture the monster who drives a truck, even though he can fly. It's like a big sort of dragonfly
bug looking thing. Yeah. Yeah. Just picture the monster who's driving the pickup truck,
even though he is the ability of flight, having to go to the Getty station to fill up his truck,
which he has to do at some point. Yeah. It didn't have any shapeshifting powers.
Movie ruined. Did it have any shapeshifting powers? No. Okay. That monster has to go to a
Sonoco and say I had 10 on three. What pump was I at? Three. Now, what if he had a debit card?
And he could pay without it. It did look like a town where they had pay at the pump. Didn't to me.
Well, I haven't engaged with a gas station attendant in 10 years. Well, that movie came out
about 10 years ago. Yeah. You're probably right. He walks behind the rows. Maybe he had a full tank when
he took the truck. It's his truck. He owns it. He lives in a house. Oh yeah. He's got like a house
he lives in. Now, if I'm not mistaken, Jupiter's Crabers was the first movie to start that horror movie
craze of like playing some old song over like an upbeat old timey song. Well, I'm glad
you bring that up. Wasn't it? One of the horrible things about the movie. You mean the shitty joke
that at the end of the movie, you see what he wanted was Justin Long's eyes and it's playing
Jeepers, creepers. Where'd you get those peepers? Yeah. Oh, they have. I didn't hate it. They have the
worst time movie trip of all time, which is the black woman with the ambiguous island accent coming out
of like nowhere being like. There's always one of them. I'll tell you who the Jeepers monster is,
man. I know a thing or two about a Jeepers creep and his mom. It's just it's just a terrible movie. Yeah.
And you know, who loves that movie? Oh, the guy that played Miles on Murphy Brown.
Grant shot. Grant. Yeah. Grant and I shot an episode of Louis together and we went to lunch. Yeah.
I didn't realize he was who he was. We were like halfway through lunch at this diner. I'm like,
so what else have you done, buddy? He was in Jeepers, creepers? No, he goes. I was in, I was on a sitcom,
and I go, what's that kind of goes? Murphy Brown. I was like, oh, shit, you were my role. Yeah.
And he was like, yeah. And we just started talking about, it was just two of us. We started talking
about horror movies. And he, we hit it off. We had a great talk. He's great, dude. But he was like,
go see Jeepers, creepers immediately. You'll love it. And I went and saw it on Miles' say so.
Yeah. And I didn't have the heart to tell him later. When I talked to him later and he said,
did you like it? And I just said, yeah, I got to say outside of like Rosemary's Baby. It's my favorite
horror movie directed by a pedophile. You know? Oh boy. Jesus Christ. Wow. Yeah. No, I know.
So these two are just driving. That's the movie? Yeah.
That's, it's Linda Hamilton. That's what she used to do. She, she looks, she never age. She
looks exactly the same age in like terminator two. Why doesn't she still go work? Is it because she has
a bit of a masculine face, if you'll forgive me? Well, I don't think that's what it is because I think,
I think she doesn't. It's because I'm thinking of her jacked up in Terminator two. But I think her
sort of rugged, slightly masculine quality is what makes a lot of men attracted to her. A lot of
guys like a girl like that. You know? Closeted? No, come on now. Well, she's wearing
the shorts are terrible. She's wearing like calf length, khaki shorts. Yeah, I mean, she's not,
she's dressed identical to Peter Horton. Except she's just rolled up the part of the appendages.
Well, the scene, I mean, look at those slacks. Now, you couldn't get a female hero,
how heroine, if you will, in a movie today wearing that. Are you kidding me?
Well, here's what I like about your Linda Hamilton's of the world is she, and same with Peter
over here. Yeah. Both good looking people, but normal looking people. Yeah. If that couple came into
your diner, you'd be like, these are normal people. I wouldn't be like, oh, these are the hottest
people in town, where they come from. I am never on board with hot people in movies and it's a problem.
And like, you know, Jeremy Guyer, I thought Tom Cruise was really good in it, but it was supposed
to be Tom Hanks. And, you know, in romantic movies like that, I'm just picking up one random example.
When Tom Cruise is struggling to like connect with Zellweger or whatever, I'm like, both of you
will be fine. It removes the stakes for me. Right. Like when Tom Cruise is like, oh, man,
I might not wind up with this woman. It's like, well, you know who you could probably wind up with
is the millions of women dying to blow you just out of frame. Zellweger's in that movie.
Isn't it Zellweger? Yeah, it's Zellweger. That was a big fan. I always thought that that was
Joy Lauren Adams. No, I always thought it was an older, Haley Jolasmitt.
Oh, you walk. You fell for it, Patty. I said, yeah, if you fell for it. I'm glad to see HJL getting
some work these days. I'm happy he's back, too. He's great. And I love the movie Tusk. It was my
favorite horror movie of last year. You didn't like it. I loved it. Disturbing creepy. I loved
Justin Long. What's the serving? Why it hurts me to say it didn't like Jeepers Creepers.
I shared a 40 ounce with him once. I played poker with him. Yeah, we were watching that movie, the
room, that shitty movie that people go see. Yeah. He knew my friend Ann. And he said, next man,
I snuck 40s in. And he was like, can I have some of your beer? And we shared a 40. And then he
like kind of like toward me, toward guided me through the film. And was like, here's what happens at
this part. Everybody's going to yell this. Very nice guy. Very nice guy. You know, since the moment I
arrived in Los Angeles, I have, and I, you know, I love doing all this shit. And I feel like I've seen
most movies. The room I have never seen because I'm always like, it's not, I can't watch it alone.
And it's got to be kind of an event because it's been built up so much. So I've just never seen it.
But I want to get a group together and watch. I would tell you this. It's so shitty. You might be
able to watch it on your own and still enjoy it. All right. I mean, it's shitty in ways that are
like, you can't even wrap your head around like. Yeah. It's not shitty. Just like, oh, the boom
Mike came into the frame there. It's shitty where you're like, why is this green screened right now?
What the fuck is going on? Yeah. Did you like Johnny Depp in Tusk? I loved him. I was my mother
and I were hailing. You're criminally insane and so is your mother. Well, maybe I liked it because
it was a movie I could watch with my folks. And we all enjoyed it. You know, and it's just disturbing
enough. Yeah. I swear to God, last Christmas. Christmas. You gave me your heart to do.
And the very next day I threw it away. Right. Well, I mean, if you're going to cut me to the chase.
No, I mean, if it's the two nights or something before Christmas Eve, I was my first night home.
My mom, dad and I watched Tusk and then bad Santa. Oh God. I love that. I mean, it was never
watched with my parents. It was a raw night. Yeah. I wanted to watch with my parents because I knew
in my heart, my dad was going to laugh to the point of tears at them punching each other in the nuts
in the boxing ring. Sure. And I was like, if I can just get them on board till that part, that's going
to make his night. Yeah. And he liked it. And then I'm sure enough that part hit man, he was, he couldn't
even handle it, man. When I think back on the, on the hardest I've left in my life, thanks giving
morning, I was living in New York and I hadn't spoken to anybody for two months, probably. I was like,
I was, I had become like Travis Bickel. I was doing push ups. I didn't eat. I had no money. I had no
friends. And two friends of mine came up from Missouri to visit me in New York. And we went at like 8 a .m.
to go watch the macy's day parade and started drinking then and there because we couldn't even
get a view of it. So we just started drinking. We go into like a 1 p .m. bad Santa, tripping and falling
down the aisle. So drunk. And I swear each of us at different points in the movie blacked out completely.
Like just went completely unconscious. And I was like, I'm going to have to leave because I'm in
pain. And this movie is the funniest thing I've ever seen. And I still feel that one. The only
other movies that made me laugh that hard were Anchorman in the theater and Kingpin in the theater.
Now I'm a theory about bad thing. Kingpin is the heart. Kingpin and the original Kings of Comedy
are the two movies. All of the Bernie Macs said in that. Jesus Christ. I couldn't, I couldn't,
and then and and and Steve Harvey doing the Titanic band unplug cool in the gang unplugging the guitars
on the Titanic. I mean, I was fucking crying laughing. Yeah. That's so rare and such a beautiful thing
to happen. But Kingpin, like in the slow motion, comb over scenes at the end or whatever, I was like,
I'm going to have to see this at a different time. I'm going to have to collect myself and come back
because I was rolling onto the floor like an animal. And I don't even laugh very much. I'm a very
even -keeled person. But once in a while something will hit me and I'm like, I don't know that I'm
going to survive this. That's how my dad gets. That's how we got during that not punching scene in
Vietnam. The part in the part in Kingpin, I was, I remember going to see it so high with my friends.
Oh, what a dream. We were so high and we were, I had not seen marijuana when I went to see Kingpin.
We were so high and we were like, let's just go see this Kingpin movie. Like, maybe it'll be
funny. Like it didn't, nobody thought it was going to be funny because it was like the weirdest cast
it was about bowling. Like, you know, it was written for Chris Farley playing Randy Quaid. Yes.
And then he died. Yeah. It was written for Michael Keaton playing Woody Harrelson. And Jim Carey
in the Bill Murray rule. I mean, and then it got delayed so long that we got this cast. And if you
had told me, Hey, we got three of your favorite actors of all time, Farley, Carey, Keaton.
And now we're doing, to me at that time, I would have been like, that's the ultimate poor man's version.
Right. I kind of like Woody Harrelson. I kind of like Randy Quaid. And of course Bill Murray is the
best. Right. But I was like, this isn't going to be great. And it blew me away. That's, yeah. It was
in that weird interim period for Bill Murray where he, the last thing it done was like the man who
knew too little and the elephant movie larger than life. Yeah. A bad spot. Space jam. Yeah.
So yeah, for me, Bill Murray has never been funnier than in Kinkton. He deserved an Oscar nomination.
And apparently he every day would read the script, rip it up and throw it on the floor. And he
every line in the movie, every word of the movie from what I've heard was made up. When he goes running
out of the potato bar. Yes. And he does that like hop on one foot and trips and falls or whatever.
Jesus Christ. Like it's, he's so funny in that movie that everything he says is like, well,
mind blowing. We were in line. We were in line for the movie. Again, high as hell.
And I turned to my friend and I go, well, where are we seeing this man? This isn't going to be good.
And even following dumb and dumb or you a dumb and dumb or fan? I didn't know it was the same guys.
Okay. I will confess this. I didn't like dumb and dumb or that much. I think it's funny. I think
it's funny. But when I saw it, I kind of equated it to like, you know, like dirty work. Like one of
those movies, I was like, it's funny, but I don't love it. You know, like, I was when I came out,
dumb and dumb, when I was 13, dumb and dumb, I came out. So that was hit me on a repeat spot.
18 when that came out. Yeah, that's maybe a little. So, so anyway, I saw, so we're standing
when I said, why are we seeing this movie? It's, it's not going to be good. And my friend said,
I forgot to tell you my mom saw it today.
Uh, she said it's the dirtiest movie she's ever seen in her life. And then I was like, well,
now we're getting somewhere. And it's PG 13. No, it's our, no, it's our Joe. It's PG 13.
There is no way it is PG 13. They have since released like an unrated DVD version.
I know for a fact Kingpin was PG 13. Otherwise, it wouldn't have been allowed to see it.
All right. Fair enough. It is. And they, they get away with a whole lot of shit on that movie.
That I, I can't really believe, but it's an amazing movie. I was sold from the minute.
Woody Harrelson walks in in the opening sequence. Actually, I was sold from the minute of the
dad whistling and going, sweeter than you, who? And when, what do you hear?
Grab in the pizza and then doing the split and making the ball stop and roll. Yeah. I was like,
this movie is going to be amazing. I think. And then the hardest I left in the whole movie was Bill
Murray saying, that's, that's total bullshit. I pulled out of her way early. Yeah. And I was like,
I can't fucking believe that this is a movie that I'm watching. It's just, it was, it's a fearless movie.
And then the funniest, like everything is the funny, like the funny is drink order ever in a movie.
He goes, uh, the bartender comes over. He goes, uh, tanker ray and tab sweets and keep him coming.
I got a long drive ahead of me. Right. Right. Right. Tanker ray and tab. Right. Right. It's disgusting.
Gin and like, like off brand coke. It's disgusting. I've been like the, the asshole in the bar at the end
orders the soda and he goes, Hey, sport. Coca -Cola. Yeah. It's the second greatest drink order in
falsetto. Yeah. And he tells, uh, you know, when he tells what he hears him to eat the food outside in
the parking lot, when he tells the women he's not, I'm not, not you, you. Yeah. Why don't you go watch
that perfume off and come back to the table? I did that at a show the other night and the girl did
not think it was funny. No, it's not something you could get away with in day to day life. I said,
look at this girl. You are so hot. Yeah. And the girl next to her was like, oh, whatever. And I go,
not you. Yeah. And she was also very pretty. And I would immediately was like, I'm just kidding.
I swear, I'm just, I'm just saying that to be funny. Right. And then eventually I got her back on
my side, but it took a minute. Okay. Uh, back to children of the corn. Horton's wearing some
Seinfeld jeans. He's walking through a crosswalk. There's a siphon play. Yes. And this whole town does
look like the movie that the whole opening, uh, the movie Kingpin takes place. It really does.
Scranton, PA, I'm from not far from there. That's also where the office series takes place. This,
the quality of this movie, like I believe that it was made for under a million dollars, it looks
terrible. Doesn't it? I mean, I don't think it looks terrible. I mean, it's from 1982 or something.
So I think it's like 84. But if you compare this to the Terminator even, which was released in the same
year, Terminator looks not great. If you watch a non remastered version of it, you know, you just kind of
get that first like DVD release of it. Yeah. It doesn't look fantastic. And, you know, the special
effects are a lot more obvious than you, than you recall. Sure. But it's, you know, it, of course,
it's a little better than this. I, uh, have a bit of a slight gas thing there, Pat. I'm sorry.
Is this crying? All right. Sorry. Look at that Jesus picture. That's scary. Yeah. For those of you
that don't have the visual, it's Jesus with a blue face and big black eyes. That's very creepy. The
kids did it to the picture of Jesus. Do Horton and Hamilton return? Are they killed or what?
I can't remember, man. I've only seen this. Oh, no. In the sequels. No, the sequels are as far as I know,
unrelated. Let's sequels have anybody in them, like sometimes in a horror movie franchise. It's like,
like the whatever that one, Texas James, a massacre where they have McConaughey and Zellweger in it.
Not that I know of. These were all direct to video, because that's how long ago they came out. Yeah.
I mean, oh, look at this Charlize Theron's in part three. I'm sorry. No shit. I didn't know that.
He, uh, takes the old top off. Uh, I mean, she wasn't against it for many years. The early horror movies
are a great way to find your, your big star. Look at this. Showed him to the corn four, Naomi Watts and
Karen Black. No, no shit. I bet they do get naked on them. Well, Charlize's naked throughout
devil's advocate and just, uh, a really special way. Oh, I said the guy's name wrong. I got my
characters mixed up. The Doug Benson kid isn't a Malachi. He's Isaac. Okay. Uh, because he comes back
in children of the corn six, six, six. Okay. And that was the same actor. Yeah. Same actor who had
gone away. Very interesting. His name is John Franklin. Uh, he's 56 now. Uh, but he had, he has
how can that be? Cause he has a growth hormone deficiency. Um, yeah. But he, uh, but he's, he's,
he's almost five feet tall. And, uh, but very interesting guy left acting. And when it became
like an English teacher. Okay. And like, this is a quote after the events of 9 -11, I saw the
show, anness of showbiz and felt a great desire to leave a great, a greater legacy than just being
cousin it. I guess he played cousin it in the atmosphere that way. In the movie? Yeah. Teaching
a hero thing? Yeah. So his face wasn't even shown? Uh, no. I love both out of this film movies. I think
they're great. I never saw them. And I have some values as even as like way funnier than the first one.
And I think he's married to a man. I think he's, if I remember correctly, I'm kind. I think that's the
case for him. Anyway, muzzle, muzzle. Uh, so here are the sequel titles of Children of the
Corn, which again, I own part two. I've never watched it. It's called the final sacrifice right out of
the gate with the final. Yeah. You never say the final. If you're doing a sequel. No,
children are not going to be children of the corn three. You ready for this urban harvest. Oh,
children of the corn four are the gathering. They mailed that one in. I don't like that one.
Children with four five back on the horse with fields of terror. All right. Was that coming after field
dreams, probably? Well, 98. It's quite some time after. Yeah. Yeah. Children of the corn six, six, six,
Isaac's return. And they, and they brought back the realizing. Yes. So now you're telling me,
when you say he has a growth home, are you talking? He's like Simon Birch, like he looks like he's 20
and he's 55. No, I mean, if you see a picture of him, he looks, he just looks like a small
guy in his 50s. Okay. It's not like a Dabney Coleman thing where you can't tell if he's a kid or not.
Dabney Coleman. I mean, Gary Coleman. Sorry. Sorry. Now, Dabney Coleman look like he's been 60 years old
from the day, first day I ever saw. But wouldn't it be a hoot if we'd replace Dabney Coleman with
Gary Coleman and all of his famous movies? Let's get Man TV back on the air for that.
I can actually, Isaac, looking at him right now, he looks like he's 50.
Yeah. He's probably like 20 years old there, seriously. Like, like Webster also, Emmanuel Lewis.
But not quite as young looking. Yeah. So he's got an old man, he looks like an old Irish guy.
He looks like a small guy. He looks like basically every guy who's 50 in my family.
Yeah. There you go. Here we go back with the red headed kid again.
Are they sacrificing Linda here? I don't know. They got her in some kind of corn cross or something.
This movie also reminds me of the Wicker Man a little bit. Yeah, I've seen both versions.
Now there's another, I didn't hate the Nicholas Cage version of the Wicker Man.
No. I mean, I own the original. I admire, I like a million percent prefer an insane movie
to a boring movie. Sure. So the movies that often get like put in a pedestal as being like the worst
movies ever, I completely disagree because they're insane and there's some inspiration and excitement
behind them. Sure. To me, just a boring piece of shit movie is always going to be worse.
Sure. Like if I'm checking my watch a bunch, the Wicker Man, I'm like, I don't know what the
hell I'm watching, but I watched it till the end. I wasn't bored. The original one is nuts.
It is nuts. It's a musical. They do songs. Yeah. No, I love the original. And there's all kinds of
tit and everything. Sure. We got two more children of the corn sequels here. We got children of the
which takes away from Terminator Genesis for me. Billy Drago started that one.
Who was in Pale Rider. Oh, wait, I thought you meant the guy who played Ivan Drago.
No, he played in Pale Rider and he was in the Untouchables. Who did he play in the Untouchables?
I like Pale Rider and I like the Untouchables. Oh, he's Frank Nitty in the Untouchables. Okay.
Greatest scene in the whole movie. Yeah, I agree. You know, your friend died screaming like a pig.
What's that? I said, your friend. He died screaming like a stuck Irish pig. You remember that
when I beat the rap. Yeah. David Mammoth, Untouchables. Throes him off the roof. Did he sound anything like that?
Yeah. My friend Aaron Wexler, you're still always saying college,
Brian Dupalman and David Mammoth achieved the impossible task of making Kevin Cosner sound tough.
Yeah. He sounds like a hard -ass when he does that. Yeah. Yeah, absolutely. Yeah. It's great. I love the
cause. Maybe I shouldn't call him that. I don't want him to get mixed up with Cosby.
Wait, who are you? Oh, you've got to say. Cosner, sure. Yeah, I always like Cosner. You know?
I love him. He's just like he shows up. You know what you're going to get. You know what his best
movie is to me? An underrated movie for all you listeners out there is a Clint Eastwood movie called
a perfect world. Okay. That Clint directed and is also starring in. It's Clint Eastwood, Kevin
Cosner, Laura Dern. For some reason nobody's seen this thing. I only saw it because Mrs.
Doubtfire was sold out in 1993. And I was like, God damn it. I have to see a perfect world. So
let me get this straight. You purposefully went to see Mrs. Doubtfire. Yeah. At age 13,
you're God damn right. Mrs. Doubtfire is a great movie. Still. Oh boy. Still. Oh boy. You're going
to speak ill of Rob Williams now. Listen. May he rest in peace. I'm sad. He's gone. But I mean,
a guy passing the previous work really gets a whole refacing, doesn't it? I mean that Mrs. Doubtfire
is. I love Mrs. Doubtfire. That was like one of the movies that he had to break that small
small from. It was like Mrs. Doubtfire by Centennial Man. Joe, by Centennial Man is an F and I would
consider it among the worst movies of all time of movie history. I think. All right. Without fail,
most people listening right now, at least we'll say Mrs. Doubtfire is a pretty entertaining movie.
Hey, we missed that kid cut in his chest open. I thought I thought it was.
People back me up. This chicks 42 years old. How was she getting past off as a kid? She doesn't
even have a growth disorder. People back me up. This is a call on show, right? You all love Mrs. Doubtfire.
I'm going to tweet it and see what who writes back. Speaking of which, we've got questions.
Okay. Good. By Centennial Man is as bad as it gets and flubber might be worse.
Here we go. This is what I love questions. What do you got? Let's see here.
First of all, I like the sound of this. I like the sound of this. Thank you, Danny 35. That's at Danny
beat with two ease 32. Rob Lark writes, Isaac looked like a creepy puppet. Malachi was a toothy ginger.
True. Who was uglier? Malachi. I feel bad saying that. He's fine with it. Malachi was uglier.
There's your answer. Rob Lurich. Here's from Atclive Gulch. It traumatized my wife as a child.
You won't watch it now. Is it that scary? No. Yeah, I mean, it doesn't seem to be scary at all.
It's a little freaky. Look, anybody saying the words to me, I'm at the, I'm under the command of
he who walks behind the rows. I'd be freaked out. Yeah. I mean, what scared me when I was a kid were the
boxes to horror movies in the video store and also like kids movies that were to me scarier than this.
Return to Oz. I own it. It still freaks me out. Return to Oz is scarier than a majority of horror
movies. It still freaks me out. Hey, let's put Dorothy in an insane asylum. That's the normal part
of the movie. And they do electro shock treatment. Yeah. How much does the corn factor into the plot?
Could the film exist without the corn out? That's from Ken Hanley. His handle is at movie guy, I guess.
That Ken Hanley is our man over at Fangoria. Okay. Ken, I got to say corn's factoring in pretty heavily.
And you're going to want that corn? I mean, they're going to want that corn.
They've dressed the whole town like in corn husks like it's Thanksgiving. Yeah. So I agree heavily.
The only child actors, this is from another one from Rob Lorich or Larich. Another are the only
child actors who didn't grow up to be complete degenerates as adults. What is that? How is it possible
that the child actors on the corn are the only child actors who didn't grow up to be complete
degenerates as adults? And that's true. We're just talking about how this guy leads a very healthy,
happy life. Yeah. I assume children of the corn was just a drug -free set. You know, they kept Michael
Jackson off set. They kept drugs off set. And these kids grew up to be healthy and happy. Yeah,
well, I think a big part of it is that a lot of these kids didn't work again after this.
Yeah, that's true. The Malachi kid did. And the Isaac kid did. Yeah.
But nobody else. I mean, and also when you're under the good influence of a Peter Horton and a
Linda Hamilton, I mean. Yeah, you feel like they had good heads in their shoulders. These are
nice people. Yeah, it's not like downtown. It's not like Downey Jr. was showing up. Like a 1984
Downey Jr. was coming to set with a vial of coke. I would dare to say too that with a film like
this, where you have to have minors acting in violent and murderous fashions, there's probably
a little extra care on set by the adults to make sure that things are pretty light and bubbly off
camera. That's something I've always wondered about. Like, for example, like there's a movie called
Mysterious Skin. You ever see that? With Joseph Gordon Levin. No. It's a Gregoraki movie. It's NC
17. I will never forget it as long as I live. I'll never watch it again. I thought it was a
masterpiece. What's it about? It's about child molestation. Oh, god. And there's really
graphics shit. Did you say that already? No, we were talking about child molestation earlier
for some reason. We were? And Joseph Gordon Levin. But, you know, like, you know, of course,
okay, so he was of age, but in a movie about molestation or a movie about something happiness,
where the kid is hurt that his dad didn't try to molest. I refuse to watch the film.
I refuse to watch it. Well, happiness is also a masterpiece, but it's not a masterpiece.
It's the, to me, it's the depths of depravity. These are the only two times I've ever used the word
masterpiece. So I don't know why I'm using it. I don't need to see Philopsy where Hoffman's come
hit a wall. So have you seen the movie? I got as far as his come hitting the wall. Sure. And then
him saying, but you'll watch porn. But here's the thing. This is come against a wall used for art.
Here's the thing. It's, it's one of those things where it's like, I get it. It's depraved.
He's talking to the woman on the phone. Then you find out he's a pervert jerking off to her. Okay,
that's disturbing. Then he comes and you have to see him come. That's a serving. Then you see his
actual seam and hit the wall. That's a serving. Then he puts a postcard over it to cover it. I'm just
like fuck off, man. And then we're going to get to pedophiles in a minute. I'm good. I'm good. I think
it's a great movie. What's what's the point of it? I'm saying give me the point of the movie.
The point of happiness. It's just everything Todd Salons does is like that. Oh, sure. I'm not,
I'm not vouching for the man's entire catalog. Right. I certainly have liked most of his
but he's a provocateur here. But for what reason? It's like a comic get on stage and being like, yeah,
I was in Kmart and fucking the clerk in her ass. It's like, okay, dude, you know,
unless you were and then it's a funny story. Well, then it, you know, that's just a nice time.
What I'm saying is like that kid who has to play these long intense scenes where he's jealous
that his father didn't try to molest him. How do these kids, what do they say to the kids?
How involved are the parents? How are they making sure that this kid doesn't grow up completely
fucked up and destroyed? How do they do it? I think that they probably don't show the kid the entire
scene. Yeah. They don't fully explain what it's about. They potentially have substitute
dialogue on the other side of the character or a camera with the other actor. Maybe. You know,
it's like if I'm a parent of a child actor, I know these parents are often troubled themselves.
But how do you just let your kid do it? Like with the, because there's a risk of your kid growing up
with the same trauma of it actually happening, not on the same level. But like, you know,
unless they shoot them in such a tactful, careful way as to put them in any jeopardy.
Disgusting. The kid asks his father, would you ever fuck me? His father replies, no, I jerk off
instead. I mean, it's just gross, man. Yeah, there's no way to make that kid, there's no way to
make that scene fine for that kid. The kid has to say that line. Yeah, I just, I just, I don't,
I don't get what the point of that is. I just don't get, I understand the point of making a movie
that deals with the subject of child molestation or pedophilia. I get why a movie like the woodsman
exists. But something like this where it's like nobody's redeeming. The kid wants the dad to fuck
him. The dad wants to fuck the kid. They talk about it too. And then the dad tells the kid he
jerks off to him. It's just like, well, I don't need this. It's something to me. It's like watching a
beheading video. It's like, I don't need to see this. Well, they did that exact same scene basically
on always sunny where he was jealous that the priest didn't try to molest him. Well, they made
the basketball coach. He was supposed to be a priest. But that's, if it's played for comedic
vat, then it's funny. You know what? Then it's funny. And I haven't seen it in a long time. But that
is played for extremely bleak black comedy. Because I remember people laughing when I saw that movie.
The movie is a black comedy, like it's a comedy. All right. Well, that gives it a little more slack in
my book. I'd like to watch it again to see if I change my opinion. I'd like you to watch it again.
All right. And think about you backing a film like this. Not backing it. I mean, I'm not saying I
love what happens in it or anything. Big fan of Dylan Baker, big fan of Lara Flynn Boyle. Yeah,
for sure. Big fan of Ben Gazera. Yeah, it's a great fan of Philip C. John Loves. John Loves,
it's the opening scene where he's getting dumped is such a fantastic scene. I'd watch it again.
Molly Shannon. Yeah, she's great in it. I also love life during wartime, the unofficial sequel to
happen. Did you like welcome to the dollhouse? I never saw it, but that's a real rough one too.
Or it's a, but it's a comedy as well. Yeah, I just didn't care that much about it, but I mean,
I think that like to me is like when he's key, you know, I felt like he walked a better line at
least from when I know about that movie. What happened? Just cut her face. I thought she was being
sacrificed. Pat, I mean, at this point, this movie could literally be about corn and I wouldn't even
know. Linda Hamilton, I'm not going to say her name because that's like a girl that I know. I just
used the sequel to happiness called life during wartime. I absolutely have and I like that a lot too.
Now is it as disturbing? Everybody's played by different people. It's not as disturbing now.
Storytelling was very disturbing, which is a follow -up to happen. What is the, now what is the
pedophile, for instance, doing in the sequel? I don't really remember and I don't know that he's
in it. I don't think he's in it. What's the Philip Seymour Hoffman character doing? You're barking
up the wrong tree. I'd have to watch it again. Oh, I mean, you're just, you said this guy's your
favorite filmmaker, I thought. I definitely didn't say that. Maybe you know these. I have, my buddy's John
and Hayden, John, her, what's Hayden, who did the, here on the Kumar movies, went to school. I might
be wrong. They went to high school with Todd Salons' brother, who is on the FBI's most wanted list
for trying to blow up a building. He is? I may be wrong about the details. I would, I would make sure you're
right about those details before you say something like that. So just so you know, you might want to
look it up, but I believe Todd Salons' brothers on the FBI must want to list for trying to blow up a
building. And I can look that up right now. Would you? Yeah, I can. I can't, now this is when they turn
on Isaac. Why are they sacrificing their leader? Because he got power hungry and now a guy now is the
guy saying, hey, I'm the, I'm the, I'm the guy you should be listening to, not him. Okay. Is there any
sexual elements of this like a weird creepy Amish Mormon type? We're all banging kind of thing
or no? I think, you know, without them saying that I think the idea is, is that they are going to
start the new. Yeah. You know, with everything being rebooted, how have they not remade children of
the court? Are they remaking children of the court? Because they keep making these fucking sequels.
There was a remake on sci -fi, which I would like to see. I think this is a very remakeable film.
You know, it's not a lot of special effects. It's, it's very character driven. You know, I,
I cemetery's due for remake too. And I, that was a great adaptation. I love pet cemetery. I think
they are actually remaking it or they've been talking about it for a while. Yeah, that's, it's time.
I'm ready. I also love the it adaptation and I can't wait for the remake. It, I lost a year of my
life to the CBS miniseries. I couldn't go to the show. I couldn't take a shower. I scared the shit
out of me. I couldn't do anything with my life. We all float down here. Yeah, it's, it's scared
the shit out of me. Now, I was so excited because they had the true detective guy, the guy who
directed season one, doing the it remake. And I was like, we're in great hands. This is going to be
fantastic. Right. Now he walked off to the creative differences and they have the guy who did mama,
which is like an average at best horror movie. Yeah, I didn't care for money. So it's not going to be
good. I didn't care for Rama. The kid playing the clown looks pretty freaky. No, it's the kid from
We're the millers. It is. You see We're the millers? Yeah. The most is an alright comedy, but like
that kid should not be playing the clown unless he'd had an amazing audition and they're going in a
different way. Wait, it's that same kid. It's the kid who's like dick gets bit and blows up and all
that. Yeah, well, I got to say, oh, yeah, that is him. I didn't realize that. That shouldn't, that shouldn't
be the kind of looks like a young Tim Curry to me. That's where I kind of was happy about it. I
just feel like they could have done much better. I don't know unless the kid's a man amazing actor
shouldn't write. He's also young. It's like, why is Pennywise the clown 21? Yeah, I don't get that
either. That's kind of stupid. Also, will they do that, but the spider shit at the end of this
it that destroyed the mini series? How does the book end? I don't remember. I read it when I was
about 10 years old and I don't remember. You read that book and you weren't scared? The book is
way scarier than the movie. The book is scary. For me, it's hard to get scared by a book, but for some
reason, the movies always take me in a different place. Man, that putt Jesus shit. That was scary. How much
did that scare you? For those of you at home, my dog just opened the door to the office and walked in. But
dog wasn't visible. So it just looked like a door opening. And I thought a person's coming into the room.
It was honestly very scary. Here comes he who walks behind the rows. As you can see, there was
clearly a budgetary restraint here. Well, they're using the the tremors bit with the ground going up.
We just watched tremors a few weeks ago. Tremors is one of my favorite horror movies. You seem
dodgy, unimpressed by it. I wasn't impressed. I liked it, but I like tremors in the same way I like
flat liners or the lost boys. Yeah, it's a fun movie. It's not scary. It's just a fun movie.
A big part of it is when you see things, oh my god, this is the worst special effects I've ever seen.
That is bad. Oh my god, that's terrible. Jesus scream. Listen to Isaac scream. Did you hear that?
I heard it. Look, in my life, I have not seen special effects that bad
in a in a major motion picture. Yeah, I mean, I did just I didn't injustice to the aha video by
saying this looks like an aha video. It's unbelievable. Yeah, that looked terrible. Now Isaac is gone.
I don't think I'm done talking about those special effects, Joe. That pixelated blob just ate Isaac.
Pat's very upset. It looked like they did it on an Atari. Yeah, it looked bad. Why don't
these other kids look evil? A couple of them look evil, I guess. Now here goes Peter, given the kids
of speech. And he's telling them that they're they're on the wrong track now. Is there no sexual
element to this cult? Pete, I mean, Pat, you keep asking me this question. Are they trying to
recreate? You're telling me your favorite movie's happiness. What do you what do you want?
What are they trying to repopulate the human race or what is their goal? I think so. I don't remember.
That's going to require some sex. You've asked me six times. I can't remember it. I'm not paying
attention. People are all of age. They're they're not supposed to be though. There's children of the
court. Look at that guy. He's 33 years old. Uh oh. Now Malachi just tackled Peter Horton for giving
a speech about how they shouldn't be listening. And be them with an ear of corn.
Now here is the plot of children of the corn six six six. This is how Isaac comes back. You're ready?
Yep. Because he just was eaten by a pixelated Atari blob. He's gone. Honestly, the worst I've ever seen
in special effects. Hannah, the first born child of the original uh, Gatlin cult. So yes, they had
sex. Pat, are you happy? We found out. God visits the town of Gatlin to find her real mother. On the
way she picks up a street peach preacher by the name of Zachariah whose car broke down.
He tells her about her name and then vanishes after crashing into a cornfield. A lady sheriff.
Look at that. It's described that way. Ladies sheriff. Oh, ladies sheriff. That's a good title for
like a Kristen Wigg movie. Ladies. Well, this is McCarthy. Yeah. Uh, finds her, takes Hannah to a
hospital in town. Once there, she finds out as Isaac was not killed by he who walks behind the
roads, but instead went into a coma. That's not true at all. We just saw him evaporated to flames.
Did you hear that? Oh, there is Isaac. Okay, he's not dead.
Well, now Isaac has a very deep voice. And he has now been possessed
by the corn devils by the he who walks behind the rose pet.
Who's he walked down the road? The tremors thing. Okay. Oh my God.
I mean, you're really not following it. I haven't heard any dialogue. We've been bantering.
I've been explaining this to you the whole. We've been skillfully bantering.
Now this part's scary. Yeah, no, this would have scared me. I forgot about this part. I thought Isaac
just disappeared into the blob. But no, okay, he's alive and he'll be back in 666 in just
17 short years. Do you like Christine? I never saw Christine. I just didn't give a shit.
I was like, I don't care about a car chasing people. Yeah, that's pretty dumb. But I like the book
and the movie. Like maximum overdrive, though. And that was a great adaptation.
You know what? That's way up the list for, and it's not a horror adaptation, but that's
way up the list for best Stephen King movies in my opinion. Same with Shawshank and Green Mile.
They're not a horror, but they're both fantastic. I thought this is the Green Mile good.
Green Mile is great. Yeah, there really is. My mom loves it. It's overshadowed by Shawshank,
which is kind of a perfect movie, but Green Mile is great. Well, Frank, dare about, amazing.
Yeah, I heard Rockwell's. Rockwell plays a bad guy, right? Yeah, no, it's a dream for
character actors that movie. There's like eight great weirdo parts on it. You never see Green Mile.
No, I never saw it. Come over this week. What's the Green Mile? All right.
This kid, what is this kid from? We know this kid from something.
Let me see the kid that's going to help him solve the whole thing right now. I just realized he's a
he's a young actor that grew up to do other stuff. All right. I just just need one cut to this kid.
One cut. I don't know who that is. That kid. What is that kid from? That is the kid from
God, damn it. I got to look this up now. His name's Joe. How about that?
You think he's like a still a working actor? That kid was another stuff as a kid. I know that much.
I got to find him, but he's telling him how to he's telling him how to stop
to stop the demon that walks behind the rows. They got to burn the field. What else would it be?
Horton's selling this baby. He is. He's into it. How did he never have a leading role after this?
He probably did. Well, he 30 something. Oh, you're right. It was 30 something a good show.
My parents loved it. I was always like, I know the Golden Girls make a lot of jokes about it as we
learned last night. They do. One of my favorite Golden Girls lines ever. Darty, are you upset that
you can't find a job? No, Rose. I'm upset because they can't sell 30 something. It stumbled on it,
but with she delivered it impeccably. She always did. I can't find this kid on here. Hold on a second.
I got to go to the IMDB. His name is Joe in the movie. That shot of Linda Hamilton reacting to
the danger was not convincing at all. Well, you know, I mean, I think at this part, this point,
she's over it. Oh, Joe, not Joe. Joe. Robbie Keiger of the doors was also in monster squad. Crazy like a
fox. I love monster squad. I don't know what crazy like a fox is. Welcome home,
Roxy Carmichael. Yep. You used to watch that all the time. It was also in still crazy like a fox.
A sequel. A sequel. One day at a time. I think that's what I'm remembering. I'm fine.
Happy endings. What the hell is that? The show. Some some movie called Happy Endings. The show is
hilarious. I don't know what the movie is. I'm remembering them from one day at a time.
Mickey and Maud. Do you remember that film? Dudley Moore. Yep. I do. Yeah. I miss Dudley.
Yeah, dead. What do you die of an aneurysm or something? It was like 55. No, it's some weird
immune thing. Not, but it was not not HIV. It was like some, I don't know, some weird, okay.
Is the corn taking Peter Horn? The corn is now attacking Peter. I didn't know the corn was a
alive presence. You know, neither did I. Yeah. It's kind of like you ever see the ruins.
That was a cool horror movie. I own it on DVD. I haven't opened it yet. The ruins is great.
Yeah, I got it one day on that when I was working on the Warner Brothers, Brothers Lot.
They had that gift shop over there. That's where I work. I buy stuff there all the time.
Yeah, you get discount DVDs. Yeah. So I bought the blu -ray one day and I just never watched it yet.
The ruins is great and it has some just fantastic nudity. Really? Yeah. How do you still enjoy nudity in
the film? Absolutely. It really means a lot to me. Really? Yeah. Do you think any female will
listen to this podcast? Oh, yeah. Okay, great. Yeah, I think there's probably a lot of female horror
fans out there that are big, fangoria fans and stuff. Yeah, I guess you're right. I don't encounter
many, many ladies who are into horror, but of course they're out there. There's a whole goth subculture.
Speaking of fans, let's get back to the Twitter. See if anybody else has written us any questions.
We need to even have to say it because then now if there's not, we're going to look pathetic.
Oh, yeah. That's our first one. You know, we're just trying to, trying to reach the people.
Well, no, here's a guy with a question for you. Is Patrick the guy from the Screen Queen's podcast?
No, I don't know what that is, but that guy's probably great.
It's a podcast with a guy. Is his name Patrick Walsh? No idea.
Okay. Doesn't say here, but it's a horror podcast. Here's another question.
The fuck is Malachi up to these days anyway? Well, we already talked about that. Oh, not Malachi.
Now we talked about Isaac. Let's see. Malachi is probably still acting.
I know. I bet you he's been in. Hold on. Let's see here. Show them the corn again,
back to the item to be. I should just leave this open again. Anybody with that like memorable look
is always going to have acting. Courtney Gaines, handsome man in real life. Look at that guy.
Yeah, it doesn't look bad. Can't buy me love. Sweet home Alabama. Back to the fuge.
What was he in back to the fuge? I think he's like one of like Biff's friends or something.
Look at this. Eight projects on the docket. Hey, congratulations.
Texas rising. If you can be a working actor for like 35 years, good for you.
He's been on the middle. Look at this special effect. The fire? Yeah, like a weird brain.
There comes. There's like a cloud.
I just wish he who what look at that. Look at that. It looks kind of cool.
It looks better than the thing that I the kid. It looks like a brain cloud. I just said that.
Oh, you did. Oh, they said rain. I wish he who walked by in the rows was more.
Yeah, maybe he's more prominent than the others. I guess that looks okay. I like the way that
looked. That looked like an old 80s tron style effect. Yeah. Now, they just torch the cornfield,
the fire spreading. They're standing and watching for some reason. You think they'd make a run for it.
There they go. They weren't the what blew up? The T who walks behind the rows. Oh, he's made of
gas. I mean, look, I think at this point, they were like, just figure out how to end this fucking thing,
please. Get us out of here. Just blow the thing up so we can leave. But as we already know,
if you blow up in this movie, it doesn't mean you're dead. Do you remember? Is this faithful to the
short story or not? I never read the short story yet. Okay. I have the book. I still haven't read
the short story. I was trying to read the ones I hadn't read yet. Nothing better before bed
than reading a Stephen King short story. Sure. I highly recommend Grandma, which is from the
what's the what's skeleton key? Is that the one with the monkey on the front?
Skeleton key. Skeleton crew, excuse me. Did you ever see monkey shines? I never saw that because the
box terrified me. Yeah, I see monkey shines. Is that based on a Stephen King? Yeah, absolutely.
Is it? Yeah. Yeah, monkey shines is good. But it's I mean, it's just about an evil monkey.
The box is scarier than the movie. Do they use animatronics or an actual monkey? Yeah, they just
use a real monkey. Okay. You know, it's not like it's like one of those little shoulder monkeys.
It's crazy now whenever I go back, like if I were to watch monkey shines tonight, I'd be like the fact
that this box scared me for so many years of my life and this movie is I have to imagine not
scary at all to want to build this crazy. It wasn't scary to a child either. I saw it as a
young boy. It didn't freak me out. Stuff like that didn't freak me out. You know, deadly friend didn't
freak me out. Anything where it was like a crazy basketball knocks the head off. Yeah, she's like the
robot girlfriend or whatever. Anything with a robot. Anything with like an animal going nuts. I just
never was freaked out by that stuff. Sure. It was always like supernatural stuff freaked me out.
The devil demons some kind of like deformed monster thing. Sure. That's what always would freak me out.
You like kooja? I know. Don't care. Did you see it? No, don't care. Rabbit dog. I don't care.
But Joe, you're an obsessive horror fan who has like the most obscure shit you've never seen kooja or
Christine. Don't care about either. They're just the two things I just named machine and crazy. Now,
it was a man that turned into that dog. I mean, I don't care about a dog with reading a dog going
nuts is way scarier than a man turning into a dog. I was never a big slasher guy. I don't like
things that can really happen. It's just not that scary to me. I like stuff that can't happen and
that freaks me out more. I don't I can't explain it. That's so weird because what can actually happen
should scare you more in city as well. Always scare me more than Wolf Creek without question.
Oh, I'm I'm the exact opposite. The 42 year old lady still alive by the way. They just got in
the car. They thought all was good. She's about to cut off Pete's head. He blocked it. I've done a
complete 180 and I'm very attracted to Loma Hamilton by the end of this movie. I want to have sex with
her like nothing else and I love this movie. I think it'd be slow and it'd be tender and it'd be
very passionate. I love this movie now. I've changed my tune. Really? We haven't even been paying
attention to. I like that part where as it came back with the demon face. Yeah, okay. I like
that brain cloud. We think thing at the end. All right. I want to say yeah. Wow, that was
an abrupt ending. He just knocked some kids head. He knocked some kid out by slamming her head with
the car door. This is not the final shot of a of a quality movie. I'm telling you right now.
And then it just said the end. Knocks a kid out with a door. That's ridiculous. It just says the end.
Phil, but do you think related to rage? I mean, I wouldn't I wouldn't be surprised in this town.
Look at this. That was one of the weirdest most abrupt ending. It's an accident. Dan Snook.
Great name. Sure. I don't wear in the credits, folks. You made it through. Children of the corn.
Here we go. First time out. I mean, I hope I hope you guys enjoyed it. I hope you're listening to it.
Hope you tell your friends. I hope so too. I mean, any podcast. I'm like, I don't understand
anybody would listen to this, but they do. But people just like these things. I listen to some. I mean,
a lot of it's, I think, driving to work. I go on long walks. I like to listen to a podcast here.
Just by yourself, just a long solo, romantic walk. Yeah, sometimes I don't want to talk. I want to
listen to people talk. Okay. Fair enough. And that should be the name of your book.
That's a very long title. But yeah, sure. Sometimes I don't want to talk. I just want to hear people talk.
Yeah. Well, folks, thanks for tuning in. This is, we'll see you in hell on the
Fangoria network. We'll be back twice a month. Yeah. And we'll see you on the next one. And of course,
feel free to suggest movies for us to watch on Twitter. We're trying to stick to movies that are
on Netflix instant. So you can watch them too. We figure a lot of people have that everybody can watch
it. But please, if you know like a movie we might not have seen, if you know a classic you want to hear
our take on, if you'd rather hear us do more scene -specific commentary as opposed to shooting the shit,
let us know what you think. We're trying to figure this out too. I believe, I believe the man is correct.
Do just that. You can find Pat at Patrick. Go ahead. What is it at the Patrick Walsh?
On Twitter. And I am at at Joe DeRosa Comedy on Twitter. We'll see you next. You'll hear us next time
and we'll see you in hell.