Hello everybody how are you good good we all good we're good everybody good
Kenny we're good we're rolling up there beautiful all right welcome to it we'll
see you in a little time to talk about some movies okay very special episode
tonight everybody very special you'll know generally a two -chair pod today
there's three I can tell you it's a legend it's not it away I said I said a
legend he listens to this and I will now get a text at three o 'clock in the
morning about Oppenheimer star David Krumholz he's a legend he's just not
here he's just not here it's good to see you buddy it's great to see you Joe
see all of you I've probably seen the people in this audience was also the
last time I saw you yeah we don't see each other much anymore that's the way I
cold snowy whatever is my favorite city on earth and when it is warm it's my
least favorite city on earth and it's very warm today and I'm in Chinatown
every storefront is a bucket of fish heads and when heated well take it easy
when it sounds like it's going in a dangerous it's not going anywhere I love
the Chinese people I love Chinatown I just don't know you Trump I love the
I just I do not understand how a whole city smells like fish it doesn't it's
not a whole city it's four square blocks square blocks I have a joke in my act
about this in in every city across the country here's what Chinatown means it
means you go to a place and there's a couple Chinese restaurants and there's
some like paper dragons and lanterns and you go isn't that cute yeah and you get
some Chinese food to go home in New York what Chinatown means is they have
recreated actual China yeah in a seven square block radius yes and you go down
there you're gonna see some things you don't want to see I'm being honest we
love the Chinese people honestly I just I forgot about it the other and this is
not tied to any any group thankfully but the subway the smell coming up from the
grate and that heat it sends me back and I was so glad I didn't drink last night
because I remembered being hungover in a suit walking to my NBC marketing job
and when I would get that hot blast I would always almost like instantly
vomit where it's like in your mouth before you even know what's happening no
buildup I hate it yeah I hate so much about New York I really do how many of
you are locals all right all right we always do a who came the farthest is
anyone from out of this country off the coast let's start with off the East
Coast where where where are you from why are you guys having to discuss amongst
yourselves where you're from talk to us where where are you from we can we can
wait you know I actually have an additional surprise for the audience as
we're talking for people from out of town yeah for the first time ever he
doesn't even know I'm gonna bring him up here right now folks you've heard us
talk about him Pinkstone is in the fucking I just spotted him myself hello
Jim good to see you good to see you Jim let's let here you go that's the guest
Mike thank you thank you good to be here thank you guys all right you're in from
yes I call it hotlanta Jim and I hung out in a hotlanta yes and we it was we
went to a nice dinner did the players play they did they did I probably when
you saw me I was in a divorce cloud I might not have been fun I just like to
divorce when I hit a new city my favorite my favorite version of you is
whenever you're in the pits of something terrible oh so my whole life yeah
because then you you like to get real fucked up when you're in those zones and
that's usually pretty goddamn fun yeah my favorite of those times was when we
were sitting at the roost and we'd already been drinking for hours you were
working on a TV show that was not treating you well and you were having a
hard time yeah we were sitting at the bar at the roost LA we were drunk and
Pat goes what is the strongest thing you have back there and she brought over
this spiked eggnog and you drank it and it was lights fucking out I felt like in
a cartoon like it as it went down each layer another like chamber of lights
would shut off in my brain and then I drove home and went to bed but it's very
close to my home it was very close to my home so it's fine let Jim sit down he
doesn't want to do this no unless he does I don't know Jim well wait we want
to say hi yeah what what uh what movie what's the last horror movie you've seen
that we could talk about yeah yeah yeah have you seen let me in yes what do you
think oh wait talk to me yes let me in is the American remake of let the right
one which was way better sorry first day with the new tongue yeah we're both talk
to me talk to me yes I very much enjoy yeah we reviewed it on the show thanks
for listening yeah yeah of course I'll get to it so man doesn't have twelve
dollars a month that Jesus Christ I listen to Joe voluntarily yeah did you
like talk to me yeah yeah I thought it was good it didn't quite sock me the way
I was you know being like smiles the best horror movie I've seen in the past
couple years probably smile I'll take a talk to me over a smile I'll take a talk
that was great that was great oh yeah it was uh it was like Demons 2 yes Evil
Dead Rise I just watched Demons 2 yeah Pat in fact texted me he goes I'm Joe
Bob is doing demons and demons 2 and the 4k's I just bought are already on
Amazon for I can tell you the last argument I got in over a horror movie
was people saying house 2 was as good as house that's fucking nuts I know said
that oh no it was it was online okay of course yeah yeah so I had to jump in and
try to set them straight you ever see the the prequel apartment no how did that
apartment divorce why wasn't there a season 2 no I know you did these so I
had a black t -shirt as well we could have been like the black t -shirt boys or
something right little story so I start over here in the sweltering heat I'm
walking over it's about a mile and I'm wearing a shirt that says cash Johnny
cash and it's the famous picture of him with his guitar and he's flicking off
the audience and this guy comes up to me and he's looking at my shirt like this
he goes let's go man and I was like and he goes no let's go and then I used to
get that New York thing where you're like oh there's the crazy tinge in the
eyes this isn't a funny bit and I'm like okay and I kind of look at my phone and
start to walk around and he goes no man you're gonna wear the fucking shirt then
had the balls to back it up man I'm like oh no and then walked behind me back to
my hotel asking about the shirt they're just saying you wear a shirt like that
if you're gonna say fuck you then you've got to back that shirt up so I get to
same as look at me in the face and saying fuck you like okay man I didn't
mean it and I went up and changed my shirt did you watch while you change
your shirt what's that did he watch you change your shirt came up with me yes
but it was horrifying it's like you coward well I like when I lived here I
got wrong by the way you go up to the room and hang it next to the other most
cliche t -shirts of all time Sinatra mugshot Oh John said in New York City
where'd you get this one -of -a -kind item never seen a motorhead she got the
Ramones one
see I try to insult Joe but I'm so nervous at my handshakes that's what the
problem with all these shows is I'm trying to talk and be cool and then it's
like this every time because I guess I do one stand -up show a year like this not
stand -up you know what I mean and I just am sick all day I gotta hear real quick
though I want to go back to this what could be what was the argument about
house two being as I don't I can't even understand how a human being could say
that yeah well cuz it was fun and then they always pulled it well I was little
when it came out but you were little when the first I saw house two in the
theater at like 12 and I was like this movie fucking sucks like what they're
they meet an adventurer there's like a there's an artifact it's like three
episodes of DuckTales they just put together like it's fucking terrible
compared to house that's always by the way that's always the final the most
desperate measure of somebody in a movie argument when they're losing is well I
was little it's like when a you know it's like when you argue with a
religious person they finally go we got to believe in something it's like okay
so you're out of arguments yeah but that's people do that with movies they
go oh well but I was fuck off man yeah yeah you know I don't think I think if
it's good when you're little it holds up when you're older I mean if it's truly
good movie I mean you know there's been things I've revisited that weren't as
good but the things I didn't like when I was a kid I still don't like them I
didn't get goonies then I don't get goonies now sorry I don't understand
there's 500 movies like that that are better in my opinion from that like
kids 500 I was a giant name three right now I challenge you to name what just
three but what am I naming better than goonies I'm saying better like goodies
I'm saying I was a John Hughes kid okay so I liked all those movies but I like
funnier movies racist jokes sexual assault humor he's got a little bit of
those that's that's one that's 16 candles he grew out of that I know but
yeah Hughes yeah here's funny Jim and I used to argue about the when we were in
high school we used to argue about the Breakfast Club and I was like I hate
that fucking movie those pouty fucking bitches yeah that whole goddamn I hated
it and then when I got older weirdly in my like late 30s I loved the Breakfast
Club I felt that I had been seen for the first time in my life well in your late
30s that they became eligible to date for you so that's really shitty and
etc favorite of the gang who's your favorite in the Breakfast Club yeah I
gotta go am AMH Anthony Michael home he's delightful and everything at that
impeccable time my favorite Judd's great I got it you know I might go
shitty I do enjoy shitty and that's very funny I hate that her arc though it's
the same arc as Greece is if you want to get the guy you like change everything
about you and the way you dress and act I think that's a terrible message fair
enough who's your favorite breakfast clubber Anthony Michael Hall it's well
it's my favorite performance yeah characters it's hard to tell he is
Anthony Michael Hall delivered nothing but Oscar -worthy teenage performances
from like 85 to 89 I'll take it up through red scissor hands when he's
playing the bully he's great in that yeah he's great in that but you know
weird offer full metal jacket and turned it down what offered full metal jacket
and turned it down the hold on one second hey Nick Nick Nick's passed away
Nick's running the show I got to see if we for is he here Nick this is where they
came up behind Nick and did one of those wire things and we're like Nick and he's
like oh that'd be great people still get start getting murdered today that'd be
like a movie we turn the lights out and then when they come on there's a body
you guys are gonna love mr. T I tell you what closing words really thank you for
having me you caught me off guard does anybody have a question for pink stone
because we've talked about him so much on the show anybody oh my gosh okay uh I
remember a night when Joe and I and a mutual friend we had like a triple date
with some girls at a school that we didn't go to when it was like 30 40
miles away from our house so you know you can you can be whoever you want or
you can do whatever you want yeah now um Joe his date he had met up with the
night earlier the weekend earlier yeah we were going to like the prom thing or
something yeah well we were going to a homecoming not our homecoming but but
so Joe had already hung out with her once and decided he didn't like her but
but uh it was you know he was too invested he didn't want to pull out of
hang and the other guy and I we got along very well with our dates and so we
go back to his mom's apartment we're all hanging out making out stuff like friends
mom's apartment and I look over and Joe's date is just sitting there like
dead inside with Beavis and butthead playing it's the early 90s we're in high
school and Joe is asleep with his head on her lap and he's fucking drooling and
when Joe sleeps sometimes his eyes don't close all the way and like it was the
whole nine and we had to wake Joe up to give our dates a ride home and and I do
I thank him for oh and I forgot to mention earlier at the restaurant Joey
his entire steak in three bites to make himself unappealing to his date it was
like a Seinfeld plot like it worked it never spoke to me again yeah that's how
a girl Jim Pinkstone everybody ladies and gentlemen why not just be yourself
you didn't have to eat the steak guys guys without and women everybody sorry
without further ado Pat and I are very very excited to bring our guests out
here I can't believe this is happening this is so fucking cool he'd know he
introduction but this man is the face of trauma
Lloyd fucking coffin everybody
oh
Lloyd it's nice to meet you is that a coffee and a monster energy drink
I believe so part's gonna explode here
what do you have
thank you very much and thank you for this great honor Joe and Patrick we
can't believe your we when we when trauma signed on to sponsor the event I
couldn't believe that that happened and we were so excited and then I said to
Nick can you email them this is a real long shot and see if maybe Lloyd would
podcast and you immediately hit us back you're like yeah cool sure Joe DeRosa
beef of course he used to be vegan I used to be yeah three days I was
vegetarian but I eat DeRosa beef now I had a terrible anyway enough about all
right let's talk about Patrick it's finally Patrick are you vegetarian no
not at all not at all what would the great Lloyd
coffin normally be doing on a Saturday night are you you go to the movies still
or you're not you're not enough for you
you don't like to recline
okay all right I was torn we were mixed on Barbie we liked half of it which have
the first half the top half no no the first half of Barbie we thought it went
got a little away from itself at the end when the ghost of Rhea Pearlman show
well I didn't know who she was
no I didn't know it is it is I'll tell you I didn't think that the the Will
Farrell thing they should have removed that that was kind of stupid that's what
we said we said when they went into the quote real world it didn't make any
sense well also I think they could have taken it out and it's weird when you
have Will Farrell and don't give him one funny thing to do in the entire movie
that's kind of an odd choice yeah yeah what's the last thing you saw in the
theater pet Taylor Swift eras okay it's on a date I'm sorry and I enjoyed the
okay I saw I guess mine was that that the exorcist piece of shit the new
exorcist was really tough yeah have you seen that it looks scary but I hear it's
not very good so I stayed away but I'm seeing something on Netflix if you all
like it Kyle Corwin recommended it Usher House of Usher oh yeah very
intriguing good writing I mean great speeches if you're actors some of that
stuff would be great audition work it's good audition pieces it's Mike Flanagan
behind that and yes yes really good he loves he loves a monologue just like
Aaron Sorkin he loves just somebody talking for five hours and he also it's
never the horrors not enough the characters have to be alcoholic and
addicted to drugs and now me when I write and I see a whole page is covered
with a speech I say I better have somebody say a few things to this guy
and interrupt the speech yes so I'm not just watching a man talk for five minutes
yes yeah it's a very good and a good wordsmith and you're right a lot of
drugs and good sex stuff okay all you had to say I'm in I'm in not
explicit enough though trauma we try to be a little more yeah realistic but
it's okay well you yourself are promoting a movie currently are you not
you have a movie in theaters I wanted to see it and can't find it where do I is
it coming soon it was here hashtag Shakespeare shitstorm based on the
tempest was here for two shoot I was talking about the toxic avenger oh oh
that played that the 4k ladies and gentlemen 4k box that is complete it
premiered Tuesday but the it's been playing in a few theaters I just saw it
and I had to go to st. Louis to see it on a big screen by where I'm from looks
great looks terrific for 4k Charlie Kaufman is here by the way it's star of
terra firma I don't know if any of you have seen Charlotte Charlotte Kaufman
amazing Charlie Kaufman who also shot return to Newcomb High and return to
very nice let's start with well let's start with the Toxic Avenger which by
the way they have these shirts for sale they're great and other stuff and we're
gonna be doing a giveaway too for some stuff but um but let's start with the
Toxic Avenger Pat and I rewatched it we both rewatched it very recently I got to
see the 4k it does look impeccable it looks really great one of the things
that I love so much about what trauma does and particularly for me Newcomb
High and Toxic Avenger I love that you guys do the sort of Grindhouse drive -in
style flick it's wild whatever but you can see that you give a shit a lot of
those movies are made and they cheap on the effects they flub on the acting this
isn't commit whatever you watch a trauma thing you watch Toxic Avenger I go these
guys give a shit the effects are fantastic everybody's in their role
they're committed the script moves it's great it works it all makes sense like
you follow a set of rules and logic in the plot and everything yeah I think
it's it's very a refreshing thing that's that that a lot of Indies don't often do
well try to check out hashtag Shakespeare shitstorm based on the
tempest it's it's all that and if you like shit we have the famous we're the
first American company to wear my shitheads out there on the actually
there's a group of my protege's who formed a company called shithead
productions after they worked on hashtag Shakespeare shitstorm and they've just
finished a movie I produced called Curse of the Weir Deer anti -hunting like all
our movies Pat and Joe have a subtext that are serious subjects but you'll
That's what I noticed too in Toxic Avenger is like I was scared of your
movies when I was a kid I hadn't even seen them but I was just like well
that's gonna be too much for me because I was a wuss and I couldn't I couldn't
see our movies so I was 17 couldn't see PG -13 till I was 13 so I just never saw
him until recently but what impressed me was what Joe says as well take the Toxic
Avenger the mayor who I know passed away that guy's given an amazing
performance fantastic what's the actor's name he called himself Pat Ryan he had
his screen actors killed name yeah and he plays the the power plant guy in
Newcomb High indeed he's so good but you know that movie is about from the
opening sentence how we're ruining the country with pollution like yes it's
crazy yes there's boobs yes there's violence and heads exploding but there's
a message there if you want it what's interesting now with the remake the
word toxic yeah has taken on a whole new meaning in our culture now the Toxic
Avenger is literally fighting toxic people yes the bullies are actually
toxic people I don't know if they call that out of the remake or not but that I
was that hit me today I was like oh that's interesting these are reimagining
because legendary who put up the dough for it picked a very very good young
director named Macon Blair who's a huge trauma fan but he's made the toxic his
own very different from our toxic but yet a lot of trauma in it the fans in
the focus groups loved it and Peter Dinklage plays the Toxic Avenger which
you gotta give legendary who make movies like Pacific Rim and Godzilla versus
Kong you know these $400 movies a four hundred million dollar movies they took
we make the $400 they took a huge risk Joe and Pat and they're good for them
because Macon Blair he's only directed one movie but that one movie he did
Green Room right well he wrote Green Room he was in Green Room and then the
movie he directed was called like I want to get out of this world oh I don't feel
I don't feel safe in this world and it's a great it's really good too long too
that notice no one can remember that time doesn't fit on them I just have to
think about the marquees you know we couldn't have long you'd only have one
word with an exclamation mark in those days well that's something and I want to
come back to talk sometimes if they really wanted a movie we've got two
exclamation marks okay and the marquee I wanted to I wanted to ask you that you
you've made up it's God it's you've made like 30 40 movies you've been in but
directing and producing you've got a shitload of movies under your belt how
do you see yourself making more do you want to keep making more do you find
that the shift in the cultural climate has affected you in any way or do you
feel like hey man I was always outside of the box and I'm gonna just keep doing
my thing and I don't give a shit it doesn't matter well like Prospero and
the Tempest in hashtag Shakespeare shitstorm Prospero was banished he was
banished and I'm I waited till I was old and decrepit to do it to make that
movie when James Gunn made Romeo and Juliet with me I would have done
Tempest but I was too young Prospero got shoved he was banished and I get shoved
deeper and deeper into the reeds of the underground so for sure I'm getting more
and more how are you say it underground I guess and the industry has evolved in
such a consolidated manner with only a few of the devil -worshipping international
media conglomerates pretty much controlling everything we see and hear
and eat down to about four I think now right there's like four companies that
own everything pretty much yeah so we lost the fourth one yesterday actually
we're down to three who went down yesterday Amazon went I asked my
parents this all the time Lloyd do you do you think that this is the most PC
time in your life can the 50s compare I mean I know it's obviously for our life
this is the most PC time yeah but you've lived a little longer so what do you say
is it where the 50s this bad was it was anything ever this bad were you I think
the blacklist I think the blacklist was oh sure maybe worse a much better choice
but but certainly today my god you can't say anything we have free speeches as
long as we don't say anything basically on campus for people who have a slightly
different opinion from the mob can't talk and it's a even if I went to Yale
believe it or not and the hashtag Shakespeare shitstorm was in large part
inspired by what's going on there where they drive by they drove out in a Nobel
Prize winning best -selling professor because he he and his wife had a
slightly they felt that a Yale student shouldn't be told what to wear on
Halloween that's what they they wrote the university wrote it wrote and said
to these students don't wear Mexican hats or Chinese pigtails or it's okay
to be where's Elmo that's an acceptable costume okay I mean so that the
professor and his wife wrote an open letter saying we think Yale students
know what to wear on Halloween but see if you dress as Elmo then people are
gonna tickle you and that's sexual harassment it's this is this is the
story I wanted to tell about you and this is what one of the things I admire
greatly yeah go on Joe I admire this very sorry I was watching the
blockbuster documentary that Netflix did now I was about 12 or 13 years old when
blockbuster came into my neighborhood I didn't like it then because even at that
young of an age I saw the difference between this sanitized mall type of
video store and the cool video stores that were around me even the chains like
West Coast video that it still had cool shit in them that started to close it
was it was obvious that there was a problem so I never liked blockbuster and
I'm watching this documentary and I'm watching a lot of people in the
entertainment business a lot of comedians who are my age talking about
Bach blockbuster like it was their sweet fucking Nana or some shit and I'm
sitting there going what the fuck are these schmucks talking about this place
sucks and then like a beam of light from heaven they cut to you and you're like
fuck those fucking cocksuckers and I was like thank God well that was the
truth they preferred 20 movies with 50 copies of each rather than a hundred
movies with two copies of each and sad too bad and I also like to tell you Pat
worked at blockbuster Oh Pat I don't believe it I had to make I had to make
money yeah they paid big money to the clerks actually I started there in high
school and they fired me for something I didn't do and I had I had a friend that
still worked there and I was like I don't know I just kept saying I didn't
do this and they were like you're fired and she was like I asked the manager the
other night as we were closing the store why you got let go and he said it's
because you were making too much money and at the time I was let go I was
making 825 an hour Wow so they fire me because they can bring
somebody in and have him for 575 an hour and say nice I say fuck them too do you
remember the good fusion I remember the confusion walking into the blockbusters
the first time and pressing against the back wall going where is the porn
section where's the secret the saloon saloon doors yeah it just wasn't there
and it was yeah but that was the one thing they got you as a young kid with
was they'd have 8 ,000 copies of Indiana Jones in the Last Crusade or the thing
that at your local video store they'd be like it's about a six -week wait yeah you
know I remember waiting by the door and somebody would come in and drop off to
and I'd be like was either one of those Indiana Jones yeah sad just sad it is
yeah well by the way the trauma movies at Video Shack which was the first store
and other stores were the highest stolen VHS movies that makes sense because the
people wanted them yeah well blockbuster would do unrated right like you guys
were not really no no I thought you could do unrated but not NC sevens maybe later
on okay I don't know they certainly never I don't think they ever the
franchises people who were trying to you know do business they did carry our
movies yeah but there were only about two of them so it was the end of us yeah I
remember when I was about 13 and I figured out how to rent a movie that was dirty enough
that it could give me a boner but still I could get away with renting it as a
13 year old sure and I remember being a blockbuster just furious because you
couldn't find anything yeah let's talk but that's what's interesting we just
said about the the trauma movies getting stolen that's one of the things I go
back and forth with the streaming stuff but I appreciate it in ways and other
ways I don't like it but the thing I really like the best about it and Pat
and I've talked about this in the 80s and in the 90s there was a lot of art
house and indie studios like yours that were making things that played in very
limited theatrical runs or it was a direct -to -video thing and the problem
with the direct -to -video to my in my opinion with like full moon features or
whatever is they were throwing it on the shelf right next to the exorcist or
whatever big studio release they had and it got buried and I feel like now
finally with the streamers you can hand it right to the fan directly and that's
kind of like this new take on on the direct -to -video thing well funny you
should mention that I don't know if any of you have heard of this but trauma now
is the trauma streaming service right thank you we're the oldest movie
studio this our 50th year we've got about a thousand movies there and it's
free the first month and every month we put up about eight new movies of the
James Gunn's and other those types who we've discovered and it's terrific every
movies is individual and unique and comes from the heart of the artiste and
all sorts of buried treasure you really have a good time it's only $4 .95
afterwards but if you can't afford the $4 .95 Pat just told me what you do is
you get a you get another email and you put it back up and you get another free
you just keep using people's emails this is not a good business model
people to do that the opposite of Netflix he encourages it he'll set you
up with another email account if you need to yes but my question for you
Lloyd that I that I I woke up today on my mind I wanted to ask you yes but now
I know you went to you with Oliver Stone and George W Bush correct yes friends
or just they were in your class well I grew up with Oliver Stone we were in the
same school right from second grade on they used to beat me up when we had
sleepovers okay but his parents and my parents were very tight very very tight
when he beat you up would he recreate it for the parents no I go home no but
George Bush George W Bush used to go around the old campus looking for
weapons of mass destruction we never we never understood why it's very strange
very very strange I've met a guy was real quick I bet a guy no no go ahead no
I was just gonna say a quick George every I've been a guy that was in a
fraternity when I lived in Texas and I was at a party and there are these guys
there in their 60s and a guy that I knew goes to his friend he goes hey tell Joe
who you're in frat with I go who when he goes George W Bush I go whoa that's
crazy what was he like and the guy goes he was a blast I never saw I'd never
even saw him on campus but that's what you want in a present is somebody who's
a blast
so Lord here's my guess you're coming up you realize you want to get into film do
you think that you were a sicko you had a sick sense of humor you you went
towards the depraved the messed up or do you think you saw a dollar to be made by
going to the extreme just out of curiosity I don't think I went for the
money I mean I had everything going I could have gone to Hollywood and I mean
I think I'm smart enough to work my way up the absolutely these cocksucking
ranks so but I my final year at my final year at Yale I was offered two jobs one
on the owl in the pussy cat which was a Hollywood I think with Barbara Streisand
and Redford yeah and you were offered to direct the owl in the pussy cat that was
obvious I could have cleaned toilets and then I had this job with a shitty little
company here in New York called Canon yeah and I took acid and I decided I
would work for the shitty little company New York and try to be a filmmaker who
could give what's in my soul to the public thank you cousin LSD no so we
were big we saw you on Joe Bob on shutter we love Joe Bob and it was a
great interview but Joe Bob will show a lot of old movies from the 80s and
Indies and stuff and it's frustrating sometimes how bad these things are and
Joe Bob himself even though he's introducing it and he's funny and
everything he's like look this one's pretty bad you know this one suck but
yours are always as Joe was saying a cut above there's more going on in terms of
subtext in terms of acting in terms of storages or anything else and the
comedy is so weird you know it's like it's not it's not like what are those
movies from the 80s hard bodies you know and summer summer vacation and all that
there was a million of those and I watched them all and paused them and you
know but but there's there's so much more going on in these trouble movies for
sure the actor for instance and I blank on his name I apologize but the actor
that plays the main bully in the original Toxic Avenger I was watching
the special features he's wild he's off the charts through the whole movie he's
going like Gary Gary whatever his name is but there were two of them and Bob
Pritchard yes very good he's very well he's so convincing and then I'm like
holy shit there's he's in the interviews I gotta see what this guy's probably a
maniac and he's just like oh we had such fun on that and I'm like this guy's an
amazing actor he morphed into that like you guys have a lot of that in the trauma
stuff and what's really incredible to me and correct me if I'm wrong but this is
the impression I've always gotten from you is that you're somebody who says I'm
doing it my way fuck Hollywood but if the assholes in Hollywood give me some
money I'll fucking take it you don't say no to it you take the money and you if
you can if it's not selling your soul I mean but if you can get some cash to do
a thing and they will do it on your terms why not take their money and do
something with it or no do you not feel like well I've never been offered other
than pretty bad stuff and it didn't come from Hollywood I've never been offered a
decent fee to write and direct so what about like turning like the toxic like
the toxic Crusaders thing making Toxy a franchise that's for kids and stuff
video games and all that that's pretty impressive yeah the Toxic Avenger for
those of you don't know is the only movie where a young boy like Patrick got
his head squashed by the wheel of an automobile that was made into a
delightful politically correct environmental cartoon show number one on
Fox wait not only not only did they run over a kid's head but later a woman
masturbates to a picture of the exploded head it's wild stuff it's wild stuff yeah
good memory that was based on my experience except we were all men in
those days we didn't have real women they're remaking I forget the company
that did it the company did it also did the read the new Shredders Revenge TMAT
TMNT video game but they're doing the new Toxic Crusaders beat -em -up video
game and it looks fucking phenomenal yes retro wares very very it looks terrific
I've been touring the video game conventions and they have a booth with
where you can play the game although it's not finished but the game's gonna
have all of the trauma sergeant Kabuki man NYPD Chomaville the trauma of the
nuclear rodent all of the history of Chomaville will be and and Toxie's
mother and his significant others will be beat -em -up characters they're gonna
be action characters politically correct oh yeah very woke did you face pushback
trying to take the Toxic Avenger to children like when people saw that movie
how did that pitch go well it just fell from it was manna from heaven this toy
company that had the turtles it seemed that the turtles were in in it called
playmates and the turtles were going downhill they thought and they needed an
environmental character and I some they obviously didn't see the movie so they
started making the toys and then they got the cartoons made by Murakami wolf
who let us write some of them and they're great and then the turtles
started oh and then new line said they were gonna make a big budget movie and
they said there was a guarantee to make the movie and and turtles started to go
up and then new line was able to negotiate Turtles 3 and terrible they
said they had their fingers crossed so I guess that's that actually lets me
rephrase my initial question within a situation like that where new line
cinemas say hey we're gonna take your thing and we're gonna make a big movie
theater movie out of it do you are you in a position where you go great where's
the check and do your thing are you still going no we told they gave us a
and they also they guaranteed to make the movie see most of these things are
option or paying whatever it is but they had a guarantee to make the movie but
usually the producers based on new lines Word of Honor and others based on the
contract they mortgage their house with the idea that new lines gonna pick the
movie up for two million bucks or five million whatever and then new line says
sorry we had our fingers crossed and and the poor guy is gonna lose his house so
new line says well we'll give you a couple hundred thousand bucks and poor
guy on the street so he takes it but we actually you had a war chest and we
fought him for three or four years and we had a big -time law firm which they
didn't expect which took it on the cuff they didn't charge us and until the the
final solution and which was on the sorry use the wrong words that's not
great no no that's a totally they saw they they they they usually settle
these things on the steps of the courthouse because they know they're
wrong so they don't want to go to trial but it took us four years we had to pay
for all the expert witnesses yeah some of them were forty thousand a day yeah
so we understandography all that stuff we paid for so we could have made
probably a lot more movies during that period but we did draw blood pretty you
know pretty decent blood good good that's great I know it's been picked up
by Warner Brothers at that point so they at least they do we knew they had some
deep pockets I know Peter Jackson had to sue New Line Cinema because they were
like oh yeah yeah Lord of the Rings movies didn't turn a profit I'm sorry
they'll just lie they'll just blatantly lie but here's what's so really crazy
about that yeah new line started out like a trauma yeah if you watch the
documentary about Nightmare on Elm Street and they're like it was two of us
in an office we had no goddamn like like everything was the way you guys were
doing and then somewhere I guess through the success of Freddy Krueger yes they
became yeah yeah as big a powerhouse as there as there could be did you have
competition with these other indies did you have like an arch enemy that you
hated that kept you kept you foe I always need an enemy to keep me in the
game you know I sometimes I have more than one many I don't think so there was
room for all of us I was a big admirer of Roger Corman and he and his wife are
executive producing a documentary my daughters have made called Occupy Can
about how we got kicked out of Cannes Film Festival after 50 years of going
there what happened because we think it's a festival and we can't afford to
give parties for half a million bucks or desecrate the front of the beautiful
village Carlton Hotel with giant posters of Brian Reynolds and so we do a lot of
street theater street theater and we also do a lot of noise about independent
filmmaker we have a fact Charlotte was on his loudspeaker talking about why we
need more independent voices and we were trying to both teach the good people of
the festival as well as sell our movies there and basically after many years we
got policed out that was this Occupy Can sort of shows you the culmination of all
that what's that by the way what's the doc this is sort of on about it's a
little off topic but it's on topic what's the documentary where Baldwin and
with tailback go to con and try to sell I remember I watched a last tango in
Paris yeah except it's about Al Qaeda or something like that yeah and then
Baldwin keeps going nobody wants to make the movie because it's like well it's an
insane movie it sounds terrible anyway sorry maybe get made a trauma yeah it's
having a hard time interesting say that again what was it doing last tango in
Paris they've already actually they perform it as part of the history when
they use a lot of butter and they I was in Africa for a year and Chad and the
doctors told me he had to put plastic rings in a number of the assholes of
the men there who were not Jewish let me tell you you know round rings because
they're there are anuses had been so destroyed by last tango in Paris
this was 1965 but Chad the Republic of Chad their asshole was destroyed so the
doctor's solution is let's put more stuff up there but it's the rings were
to reconstruct the asshole yes it was collapsing yes it had been torn to
shreds like hamburger got to tell you look there was a little bit of a tone
with your yes like I was supposed to understand this whole thing I'm trying
to catch up here I totally got it we met at the manhole club it was dark but I
remember there's a gay bar there's a gay bar in my neighborhood there is a neon
rooster in the window and the bar is called the cock unbelievable little on
the nose unbelievable on the nose there's a Looney Tunes cartoon where red
bone or whatever the rooster is and he's singing a song I am the cock of the
walk I am the cock of the walk and it's it's over and over and over and that's
the lyric it's a good song strangely that was the most erotic thing I could
find at blockbuster video many a night with that cartoon the I had an hold on
Pat I got a question down I don't want to forget it ask a question well tell us
about your new movie because you know we haven't let you speak about it well I've
been producing movies by new young directors right like the curse of the
deer Heidi Moore has made Kill Dolly Kill which is coming to festivals and
and in fact the star will be here in town performing Halloween night Josh aka
Donna slash will stay in our house what kind of a performance it's a the movie
is a horror satire horror musical okay very good it premiered at a fantastic
along with the very good question here yes sir what was it how did you come up
with Tony Clifton oh wait these are my Andy Kaufman I'm sorry I met him a couple
of times I met Tony Clifton I met but I was at the JFL festival in Canada the
last comedy festival in Montreal Canada and this was like not even ten years ago
so Andy was long gone but Bob's mood it was there he was doing Tony Clifton and
he was walking around the party as Tony Clifton like you know just saying crazy
shit and it was right around the time when it was like you can't really make
jokes like that you know but he stuck to it 100 % it's got to be easier when
you're in a wax mask we had a guy at the trauma 23rd annual troma dance film
festival a free festival which took place this year at the beauty bar we had
Abraham Lincoln coming by and he wasn't in a mask he was like he spoke French
it was pretty interesting hey that might not have been the trying to gauge how
crazy you are Lloyd by the way man dressed up as really makes the story
nowhere near as good whatever the story is if I came to New York dressed as
Lincoln I'd be going to see every play in town just for the joke I do want to
this to you yes and I mean this and it's just so I just I don't mean it
schmaltz whatever it's I mean this you are to film in my opinion you are to
film what easy was to rap music and what I mean by that is easy if you don't know
or maybe do I don't know I do start out well he started ruthless records he
started it with his own money the rumors are it was drug money but whatever we've
been at the manhole club sorry folks and sorry easy the greatest line yeah the
greatest line on the strata to Compton NWA first album as I keep saying if you
don't like how I'm living then fuck you and it was such an awesome moment for
this rebellious things yeah that's when they did fuck the police like it was
they were causing such havoc and they were doing it on their own terms and I
just have such respect for guys doing that and I love that you're doing that
with film if there aren't a lot I know we're saying these other companies it's
you it's Corman and full moon features now there are indie companies out there
right like you know the was Weinstein's before it went to Miramax well they were
owned by Disney for many years yeah you see now it's like it's like indie
spotlight movies are distributed by Disney or whatever the fuck yeah but I'm
like I don't root for Lloyd the same way I root for a Harvey Weinstein he was the
king of Sundance people would talk about him with hushed words Harvey's up on the
top of the mountain oh he may be at the party they loved him and they really want
to go to a festival that celebrates that piece of shit stay home yeah well you
don't want to go to that festival well Trey Parker and Matt Stone were obsessed
with we discovered them they were obsessed with the Sundance which is the
only time I went the first time I went yeah and they had sent a letter to they
made cannibal the musical which we have it's very good if you like yeah
cannibal it made it music Oklahoma meets the toxic avenger but they they didn't
they wrote a letter to Sundance they applied they didn't get a fuck you
letter so they said well let's go they didn't tell us not to go and Trey set up
a one movie festival and it was a huge success and apparently got to Redford's
ear and eyes and and then we set up trauma dance there for at least 10 years
and eventually got policed out of there this the same year that the Tony
Clifton thing happened at just for laughs Doug Stanhope went up to just for
laughs and rented out a garage across the street from the festival and called
it just for spite and through his own festival and Doug Doug who is a dear
friend of mine in comedy I watched Doug get physically removed by the head of
just for laughs
it's one of the funniest things I've ever seen probably funnier than anything
happening at just for laughs
boy oh thank you tell me tell me finally yeah well you say in the in the duck
welcome to Trombeville documentary you say it's one of my favorite lines in the
movie you talk about cannibal the musical and you go you go everybody
passed on it we got it we took it on then it came out it's a hit then of
course every shithead up and down the block says they got it
exactly I say you didn't get it you fucking idiot it's so true it's amazing
I always wanted that film I always wanted to take that film and nobody
would go near it they just lie and they all just lie it is why yeah it's why
people I've had people they'll say something to you at noon and then at
1230 they'll say I never said it both times looking you right in the eye it
happens all the time if I may interrupt I believe that the film commissioner of
the great city of New York right here in the room a Pat Swinney Kaufman great
mayor Adams in spite of blood -sucking freaks and serve Nazis must I oh sure
been a New York State Film Commissioner for 20 years then that's awesome
yes and now to reward her has been the Commissioner of New York City that's
awesome I'd like to congratulate you too he's much funnier than I am believe me
I want to congratulate you yes promo distributed blood -sucking freaks
blood -sucking freaks is the only movie ever ever that when Joe Bob played it on
the last drive in the fans went this is too far it's not okay and he's played
some crazy made in 1972 folks yeah that's a wild flick but what's his name
the wrestler was on and wrote a song
you guys know no that's a penis what's what is the guy's name Jericho Joe Chris
Jericho he wrote a song the blood -sucking freaks he loves that movies he's had me
on his body it's quite a ride that film so you do other podcasts too well I
my way up that's very sweet that's very different than what David Krumholtz said
to me we're gonna we're gonna do a little giveaway here etc but you're in
New York really the center of independent film it's a it's a generic
question but what advice do you have for aspiring filmmakers because if you hear
that from a Scorsese it means something different from a Lloyd Cough you're you
did it you did it ground up how do you do it if you're starting you got no
money but you got some talent and a dream and a vision what do you do well I
think there's a I guess I'm to be somewhat serious just this one question
yes you got a crossroads if you want to be whoever the biggest Spielberg I think
you have to win your way out West where the the few conglomerates and a few
gatekeepers make the green light but if you want to do what I'm doing or maybe
slightly more pay better paying and I think Shakespeare said it all to my
own self be true he wrote that best -selling novel a hundred and one
money -making screenplay ideas otherwise known as Hamlet but I think you do
what's in your heart they only go around once it's kind of fun to be you know
always looking over the preps are we gonna be in business in two weeks and
my partner 50 some odd years he's really deserves all the credit for the whole
thing and he and I co -directed he doesn't get credit for it but we
co -directed the first toxic Avenger which is the only successful one I I
love that philosophy I subscribe to it I have friends that it's great example I
got see he is a very different approach to comedy he's very clean friendly
mainstream and tonight Nate is holding hosting SNL and I'm playing Arlene
Grocery anyway here we are we're terrific boy can you do the giveaway with
us sure you kidding Nick we've got our other special guests ready to go and
Nick do you have the stuff ladies and gentlemen from impractical jokers Brian
wait
take a seat here Brian
Brian and I have worked together we have I pitched you years ago I did I did the
sergeant Kabukumin show that's right but you sent a script and I sent in a script
about a it was called tiny terror returns to something town and it was
about a little person gangster that came back to terrorize this town 30 years
later and the cop from the eighties who put him away the first time was a
breakdancing cop and he they got him out of retirement so it was a breakdancing
cop versus a little gangster that was about 40 years a long time ago it was a
while ago yeah it's still not worth making today I'm actually yeah it's
garbage I do want to say I did I did work at Blockbuster and we had all of
Shannon Tweed movies so if you couldn't find something to jerk off to that's on
you I've become really good friends with Nick Simmons who's Shannon Tweed and
Gene Simmons his son and I finally said to him like the fifth time we were
hanging out I go bro your mom is so fucking hot dude he's like tell me about
it did everyone fucking friends tells me that he's so tired of hearing it our
number one renter at my blockbuster the mid -river's mall blockbuster you know
it was called whore two oh yeah I remember that they would come up eyes
down and I would always look at whoever was working with we'd be like it's or
two and every time she's going to yeah yeah yeah but I remember blockbuster
carried like clerks and shit like that like when I first yeah it wasn't like a
total wasteland you know no no they had they had you know they had some stuff
but I'm not here to stand up a blockbuster I'm just saying sounds like
you know it just sounded like some misinformation was being given to these
that's incorrect clerks was part of a Miramax yeah they were either parts of
vassals of the majors well I didn't get in so well so you're a Harvey Weinstein
fan is what I haven't seen it the evidence so I don't I don't have an
opinion yet no no he's a monster a couple things would sneak in like yeah
they'd always have a couple John Waters movies sure he was new line right no
Ethel Waters films none whatsoever she was a big star good old days when they
didn't allow black people to go in the same hotels as the white people was she
a black performer yeah she was a very good singer but also in a number of
movies in the sky I think yeah do we have the merch for the we do can you
uh can you hand it off to me and also house one is definitely definitely the
better movie but house two is fun I mean I don't want to knock house two it's a
second story yeah come on what was the one with the old cowboy was that that's
two the grandfather cowboy the second story is the greatest ever subtitle
whatever that's why I remember it that's why I remember yeah other than dr.
giggles the doctor is out dot dot dot of his mind that's pretty good that's
pretty good by the way what or my alt for it the doctor is in dot dot dot I like
them all everybody here knows who Jenna Jameson was oh she turned down citizen
toxic she didn't like the script citizen didn't like the script Jenna well I saw
her Pirates movie and it the script and it was very very tight so they might be
that's tough stuff porn star coming scripts not up to speed no it was the
salary we offered her five thousand actually James Gunn at the time said why
don't you get somebody like Jenna Jameson so we did we tried and no no look
no look by the way Shannon Tweed is in a movie that's on trauma now that we
produce a Western and it's very very it's got me it's part musical but it's
very sexy I can't remember the name of it but it's with the Julie strain
Julie strain yeah she also bring me back she produced details from the crapper
which is also she was great she was a Kevin Eastman's wife and the loveliest
person in the world sorry I'm sorry Joe well nobody is sorry I don't mean to
interrupt you I just don't want to give away too much merch we're very cheap I
could tell that from the Jameson offer you sent me the 4k taxi and I said can we
get to who you want for bad you guys know if I'm Jenna Jameson and you offer
me $5 ,000 I'd say look buddy I get fucked enough at work that's what I
wouldn't say very good that's what does it what does she make for a push make
for pirates I mean I don't fucking know yeah 25 she was probably producer on it
okay so residuals do you want me what do you want me to do so somebody somebody
cat from trauma suggested one of the things maybe we do a costume contest
three best costumes okay give these you're gonna have a lot of hurt feelings
man there's some there's some people like we could do trivia for this let me
give away this first one because I have a thing I want to it's your show you don't
have to ask me permission and her up once again because cat Philip oven and the
team and the Commissioner would like to present Joe DeRosa with this beautiful
trauma diploma
they love you Joe Wow sorry only got the budget for one of those two I see you're
credit shy my friends yeah I'll do the big raves I want to give this to Pat
what are you framing this look at this thing Somerville Junior College Junior
College yep I just I wanted every other weekend
Michael Michael also signed it this is so sweet yeah that's pretty dope that's
really cool you deserve it Joe I do maybe next time you don't fold it eight
times hey the Constitution was in Jefferson's pocket just like that I'll
take it almost steaming out listen thank you what that's so that's amazing
okay this is the only question I have for the audience and it's for our fans
specifically and somebody will know the answer to this for a signed Toxic
Avenger poster what is the worst horror movie ever made by the way if I may
interrupt that is not a poster that's a theater card from the original Toxic
Avenger the back of it it's very old the back of it says trauma ten years of
whatever it was oh see the back the black thing on the back Joe ten years of
film distribution we didn't even know and Michael hers has signed it and he
doesn't sign too many things very old this is very very cool okay this is
amazing Lloyd will put it in his pocket before we give it to you don't worry for
the signed theater card what is the worst Hellions what is the worst horror
movie ever made yes somebody said Jeepers Creepers and that is correct
well wow by the way I completely completely disagree that does all the
artwork right and is that Emily next to you Emily right over here guys gave it to
employees okay you gave it to an employee how cool is that for everybody
that fucking paid to come to the show you gave it to your friend exactly nice
well you guys didn't work that question out in advance not to mention I love
Jeepers Creepers it was directed by a child molester but yeah it was so so
this is a bag of oh oh this has a couple things in it but one of the things in it
and this is very cool an original Marvel Toxic Crusaders comic is in here wow
the 80s well thanks to cat Philippa very generous yeah do you want to well do you
want to make up a question or Brian do you want to make up a question it's Pat
show patchy gonna I have I what I figured I was gonna do for whatever you
had me give away was I was in the back listening to the show and I was
absorbing facts okay that you guys said tonight so I was gonna question them
whoever the fuck was paying attention would win okay okay okay what was the
very first movie that Joe and I reviewed in our pocket wow as long as that wasn't
Emily you win that yeah okay what was the correct answer children of the corn
speaking of which thank you because I did not know the answer I was taking a
big swing there we use the very rare train defecating whales in Albania
where we shot and they actually have corn in there in the duty it's very
whales got corn in their poop so Brian yeah Lloyd I want you to give this one
away because this is the biggie but Brian why don't you give the two we'll
see you in hell hats away no this is cool like I came all all the way from
Staten Island to give away two hats that's fucking it's a lot of tolls had
to find parking whatever nobody I'll give away to trucker caps you got it but
move into civilization wait okay how many this is a how for this hat how
many like movies to the Goonies are better than the Goonies 500 right there
there you go that's right it was it was insane that you said that and I was
hoping that it there aren't many movies like it it was a dumb thing to say it
was a dumb thing to say I agree yeah I meant it's one of those kids movies that
even when I was a kid I'd be like nine nine years old with an apple watching
it like yeah I don't not into this everybody else loves that movie I get it
I get it yeah you're more of an explorers guy I didn't mind one of those
second hat who wants it okay how much per month is this trauma streaming
service who said that who said it first right here I heard over there I get it
to the right person 495 got a first month free that was a double that was a
year this was generously donated by trauma this is a box of 18 DVDs oh it's
a mystery as to what movies are on this outdated media that you've put into this
box they all came from blockbuster previously viewed great would that be
great it would be really fantastic that'd be like a fucking David Blaine
do you want to ask the last question well it's Halloween maybe anybody know
Todd Browning what was your favorite silent movie by what might be the best
that was a good answer yes the unknown right very good don't miss it folks it's
terrific and with loan Cheney very very good now you earn that man that was a
person like give it to somebody deserving and you don't have to decide
yeah it wasn't you she was right she was right oh no what was somebody oh okay
right here I feel like she kind of got robbed like she said it the same not so
you pick one in the mohawk person what's your name I'm so sorry Lauren give one
Lauren if you have to oh good sportsmanship thank you for being here
thank you thank you thank you thank you thank you thank you thank you very much
no joke
you